Oh, I got a love that keeps me waiting.
I'm a lonely boy.
Hey, could I come again, please?
Yeah, the night is worth the pain.
You're listening to New Zealand's number one rated alternative talk radio.
It's the Vinnie Eastwood Show.
Just because we're being exterminated doesn't mean we can't make it fun.
Otherwise, what's the point of being killed?
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen, to yet another exciting episode of the Vinnie Eastwood Show,
broadcasting live on American Freedom Radio.
For your listening discomfort, it's the lighter side of genocide.
Just because we're being exterminated doesn't mean we can't make it fun.
Otherwise, what's the point of being killed?
Now, I have a guest turning up in about 15 to 20 minutes, and I'm going to talk about this whole concept.
I had this interview with Kevin Annett that I've just published up and spread all over Facebook today,
which has been responded with a legion of hate, as expected.
Number one, if you talk bad about any kind of religion,
see, even right now, a whole bunch of people who are deeply religious,
who believe in the Lord and Jesus and so on and so forth,
getting their backs arched up a bit,
because any criticism of the concept of a faith-based religion is abhorrent, right?
I'm just thinking about this.
I've got so many friends who are deep believers in things that I don't really believe in,
and yet we get along so well, because we're not dicks to each other.
I mean, maybe that's the real difference, isn't it?
The difference between somebody who's religious and somebody who's a zealot.
I mean, hell, let's go one step further.
What if it's a cult?
What if you've been part of a cult, right?
What's a cult?
You've got a hierarchical structure.
Organize religion.
You've got a preordained doctrine that everybody has to adhere to.
You've got a central leader kind of thing that runs the whole organization.
Organize religion.
All right, so there you go.
That's how you know you're part of a cult.
Sorry to lay that on you,
but religion isn't the only cult that people are a part of.
There are cults of all kinds of followings.
Fan club cults, cults of personality.
There's TV show cults, you know, like the Star Wars cult.
Just think about that for a minute.
How many films have what they call a cult following?
All right, what does a cultist do?
I mean, let's think about this.
What if you introduce yourself not as a Star Wars fan, but as a Star Wars cultist?
Hello, I'm a Star Wars cultist.
Really, bro?
It kind of seems really creepy all of a sudden.
You're just using a different word, one that's not patently acceptable.
Oh, I know, because I've kind of gotten over the fact that I don't have to lie to myself.
I'm a cultist.
Star Wars cultist. I love it.
Can't get enough of it.
Give me a Jabba the Hutt and a Han Solo any day over a Pizza Hut and a handle of beer.
That's what I'm talking about.
Obsession.
Veneration for a person, object, some kind of thing.
Do you love it?
Do you viciously defend it?
Have you got butterflies in your stomach whenever people talk bad about it?
You don't know why.
You have no clue.
Why would somebody feel bad about it?
You know?
I've just been looking around lately and I've been having these conversations about religion and that kind of thing.
There's red meat issues in that.
I'm not doing it because I'm trying to get a rise out of people and I'm trying to suck a hit off them or any crap like that.
I'm just genuinely interested in the topic right about now.
Christmas is coming up.
Tis the season to believe in things.
Stuff in the Bible.
It's clearly marked in there, in the Bible, that on Jesus' birthday, the 25th of December, that you must celebrate it by having an enormous tree draped with lights and expensive decorations and stuff like that.
With a large meal around everybody and have a whole bunch of products that are made and manufactured in China for everybody that hasn't earned them.
Just give it to them because it's the season for giving.
Leviticus fucking chapter 3 or some shit.
It's right in there, man.
Celebration at Christmas.
You see?
Nobody even follows their religions anymore.
That's what I'm starting to find out that's different as well.
If you're an idiot, saying that you believe in a certain thing doesn't make you not an idiot.
That's the interesting thing that I've been thinking about lately.
A lot of people use their belief structures as an excuse to not listen and to not be reasonable.
This isn't all people that have a belief structure, mind you.
Just some.
Maybe because you need to have that.
I understand that specifically there is a reason why I believe in a higher power and a God and everything like that.
It's because I know that I can derive power from it.
How do I know that?
Because I've done it myself and hit an awakening?
No.
Statistics.
Have a look at the survival rates of people that are in POW camps.
Let's take Vietnam, for instance.
Alright.
Let's have a look at all the atheists in the POW camps.
How many of them survived?
Very few.
Let's have a look at the really, really deep Christian believers in the Vietnam POW camps.
How many survived?
A hell of a lot of them.
See, that alone is a reason to believe in something.
Even if it's not there.
Even if you don't have a defined belief of what it is.
Just believe.
That belief alone is something that will give you hope.
Because when you're in despair, a situation where you have no hope whatsoever, your body starts to shut down.
It doesn't try to survive.
It can't see tomorrow.
So, if I bag religion, it's not because I'm bagging the belief and the power that it gives you.
I'm not blagging morality.
I'm not blagging history.
I'm not blagging anything apart from those who misuse it.
Psychopaths in particular, who develop little cults.
Alright?
There was a joke this morning.
You know, I've never seen an atheist blow shit up or kill people in the name of atheism.
But that's probably because they don't shout,
FOR NOTHING!
before blowing themselves up.
Can you just imagine that?
That would be quite classic, wouldn't it?
Get like a little cartoon or a sketch or something.
Atheist terrorist.
FOR NOTHING!
There's all this dust in the wind.
You know?
He only gets like half a dozen virgins in the afterlife because he doesn't believe that you need 72.
I'm sorry.
Here's another thing.
I apologize if I'm making fun of anybody's belief structure.
I don't mean to do that.
I make fun of everything, just in general.
Belief structure is just part of the gig.
You know?
Let's say you're taking it seriously.
Let's say you're an atheist or a Christian or a Muslim or some denomination of cultist.
And you get offended by the very concept
that I don't like false belief,
that I don't like blind belief,
that I don't like things that aren't fact-based.
I don't like things that don't have a reason to be there.
Now, that means that a lot of you shouldn't be offended
because there is a reason why you believe what you believe.
There are some facts that substantiate it.
Okay?
So I'm not talking about you.
Am I?
Talking about those people who are idiotic,
who's zealotry.
The fucking zealotry.
My God.
All caps, comments all over YouTube.
You must convert.
Otherwise your eternal soul will never be saved.
You must accept Jesus into your heart.
Oh God, I just love Jesus so much.
You don't even know anything about the guy.
I mean, he was a barefoot, unemployed, homeless,
healing, travelling, hippie, Palestinian Jew.
I mean, you can't get any more messed up than that.
Alright?
So if anybody's like that and you want to deify them or anything,
why in the hell do you have a reason to be angry with anyone
if that's your deity?
Yeah?
Am I wrong?
The only person you should be upset with
is somebody who's evil.
Somebody who actually tries to corrupt the innocent.
Yeah?
Think about that for a second.
Who's your enemy?
I wonder this myself.
Who's my enemy?
And I'm starting to realize that my enemies are all psychopaths.
Every single person that I can count off of my head,
people that have screwed me over,
who are really horrific,
who are sexual predators and things of this nature,
all of them that I've had any personal contact with,
who I've since developed feuds with,
are freaking psychos.
Alright?
Some of them feign religion.
Some of them say that they're free men on the land.
Some of them say that they're great talk radio show hosts and patriots.
Dude.
Exposing psychopaths is actually kind of one of the most important things to do
in any institution.
Alright?
Again, have a look back at it.
Is your institution controlled by a psychopath?
Is it hierarchical with one guy at the top?
Psychopathic controlled.
Every time.
You know?
It's like impossible for someone who's not a complete psycho
to get to the top of a giant organization.
Right?
Unless they built it themselves
and are currently running it themselves
and there's nothing to really be at the top of
because it's just them.
Right?
See, there's a difference in it.
Maybe it's just the desire to be surrounded
on all times by fawning sycophantic scum.
I don't believe that I need that.
You know?
People who go,
Oh, Vinnie, you're so great.
I love it.
I mean, you know, it's nice.
Thank you very much.
I'm not ungrateful.
Just as long as people are willing to pull me up on things.
You know?
If I'm wrong, show me the evidence.
Right?
Like I was talking about Kevin Annett before.
And a lot of the reason why people don't like him
is because in 2013,
he launched a common law court case
and arrest warrants of the Queen, the Pope,
and a number of other high-level Vatican and government officials.
Now, that's a common law jurisdiction thing.
So that means you've got an arrest warrant for the Queen.
It's an actual legit one.
You could grab the Queen and drag her away
and you wouldn't technically be breaking the law.
But who's going to do that?
So what happened was nothing happened
apart from a whole bunch of people in the Vatican resigning
all of a sudden for some reason.
And what people have done is they've construed that
as instead of him trying, you know, just trying,
giving it a go, and it's just not working,
they construed that as he's a fraud.
Right?
I don't understand that.
Also, I've heard a lot of other accusations
like he's a womanizer and he's traveling all around the world,
living the life of Riley and stuff.
I haven't seen anything to substantiate it.
All right?
It's like every time somebody throws out an accusation,
I don't care who it is that's throwing out the accusation.
I don't trust accusations alone.
I need to see something to substantiate it.
I need to see.
Because if you're going to pigeonhole somebody,
you know, just go,
all right, I really don't like this guy anymore.
He's off my radar for good.
It's going to take a bit of evidence
before I determine whether or not
somebody's actually a fraudulent bad person.
And accusations simply aren't enough.
You know?
They're not enough.
And that's how you know when you're dealing with a shill
or somebody who's just crazy or somebody who's just wrong,
is they keep playing the name-calling game.
They keep going and going and going,
saying all this stuff and making all these accusations.
And did they provide a single screenshot?
No.
Did they provide any video evidence
or anything that could actually be constituted
as some kind of case that they're making?
No?
Then they're talking out of their ass.
Right?
I'm sorry, whoever you are,
that's like spreading BS about anybody.
This is a very generalized concept
that I'm talking about here now.
People just make stuff up all the time.
And you know what the funniest thing is?
So many people believe it every time.
Don't check up on it.
Oh, that guy's a scumbag all of a sudden.
I knew it.
I knew it all along.
Really?
Somebody came out and criticized them openly?
Somebody who you think is trustworthy
and their words is enough?
Even people I know to be trustworthy,
I don't trust just their word alone
when it comes to throwing somebody under the bus.
I will throw people under the bus
if they're a scumbag,
if they're a parasite on human life,
if they betray people left, right and center
24, 7, 3, 6, 5
for their entire existence,
if that's what they do to people.
Yeah, they're going to be thrown under the bus.
Sorry, bro.
This is your stop.
I'm like that.
As soon as I know,
I know that somebody is a psycho scumbag
who's a manipulator and a liar,
I know for a fact that I cannot trust them
and never want to associate with them ever again.
And what's interesting is that
those people that you block off like that
and say you parted on bad terms or anything like that
or they started getting real uppity at you,
they never come back to you and apologize
and say, oh, I'm sorry I acted like a dick, bro, man.
I was just really...
See, psychos can't apologize at all.
Now, our guest, Brian Kelly,
appears to be ready,
so I'll just get that contact info to the studio there.
But I really am quite incensed
when I see people get manipulated
by accusations and things
that are completely unfounded
and people believing them
without asking for any evidence.
That's all I'm asking for.
If you want to pigeonhole me or anybody,
just ask to see a little bit of evidence
before you believe whoever's opinion.
This person says that about that person
and I believe them because such and such
and blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Yeah, but that's all personality assumption, bro.
Have you got anything solid?
Something that isn't just shifting sand
of opinion and logical fallacy name-calling?
You don't, do you?
Just shush then, okay?
Shh!
I don't care that you've got five fake YouTube accounts.
I will block them all, okay?
They will get blocked just like that
and I will never have to hear from you again
after each and every one of your subsequent fake accounts
has been blocked.
Now, I'm a bit sick at the moment.
I'm holding down a gargantuan,
like an oil drum-sized ball of flames.
That's quite a horrific thing to say on talk radio, isn't it?
No response from the studio,
so I'm going to see if I can bring in Brian Kelly here myself.
No, that's not working.
Okay, sorry about this, ladies and gentlemen.
I have to produce on air
and I'm feeling sick and tired
and I need a holiday, bro, at the end of this week.
It's going to be holiday time.
But my very special guest joining me right now is Brian Kelly
from Brian Kelly's newsroom.
Welcome to the show.
Brother Benny Eastwood, it is good to be here.
It's been a long time, man. How are you doing?
It has been a long time and I'm doing sickly,
but I'm about to go on holiday after a few more shows
to round out the week before Thanksgiving
and I'm looking forward to recuperating from...
I should have just said, I'm good.
That would have been the shorter version, but I'm with you.
I like details, so it's good to hear that you're doing all right.
Oh, damn, that was funny.
That cracked me up, I do.
So anyway, what have you been up to, Brian?
Oh, man, I'm good.
What's been waiting in the wings?
I don't follow the news at all.
Do you follow the news at all?
No, I went through a phase when I was doing my blog.
If you've gone to my blog recently,
you'll notice I haven't made a blog post in probably about six months
and that's as a result of not following the news really at all.
So I've transitioned to doing more boots on the ground kind of projects,
which I'm here in Bali doing now,
but every once in a while something will come my way.
For example, some of the Syria stuff is illuminated lately
because I've got a friend over there that's on the ground in Syria right now
and obviously if something pops up that's as important to share
as what's happening in that country,
then I pay attention.
But for the most part, no, man, I'm not listening to the radio shows,
no offense to you, I know you've got an awesome show.
I'm not reading blogs and I'm staying out of newsrooms and chats
because I feel like if I need to know it,
somebody will shoot me a link and then I'll dig a little.
Brian, if I may,
you just described my exact protocol for life.
I'm out of the game a bit,
but I'm very much in the game in another level.
You just described my exact protocol for life.
It's a good blueprint. It works.
I mean, dude, dig this. I've figured it out
and there's a reason why we do it.
Number one, news doesn't fucking matter.
Once you come to that realization that it actually doesn't fucking matter
staying up to date with shit that's happening 10,000 miles away
that doesn't actually involve you in any way, shape or form.
Dude, that's the honest way to put it, for sure.
Like, oh, I fucking figured it out!
Well, you know, man,
when I first went down the rabbit hole,
it was like I couldn't get enough news.
I needed to know what the fuck was going on
because my entire world view was challenged in so many ways
and then I think I got to the point where I was in news paralysis
and the only way to let go of those symptoms
was to just back away from the whole thing.
And I've got to tell you, it's working.
In a lot of ways.
See, you're doing exactly what I recommend my listeners do
is turn off the Vinnie Eastwood show
and start going and doing your own thing, your own activism or whatever.
In fact, you've got to really turn off everything.
It's like, in life, energy gets given to what you put your attention to.
Now, if you're putting your attention to someone else
as opposed to yourself and your family, your world and your contribution to it,
I think you've missed a priority or two.
I know a lot of people that spend 18 hours a day
staring at their monitor screen.
I was one of them for a long time.
And on one hand, you have information being empowering
because I believe when we empower ourselves with what's going on,
all it simply does is it allows us for freedom
of a much wider scope of options
of how to conduct ourselves
and what's available within the limitless space of possibility at all times.
But you get to that point where all of a sudden that becomes overload.
And it doesn't serve a purpose after a while.
And shutting the computer and actually going and doing something
seems to be the only natural progression out of that mode
of constant overload of information.
You just get to the point where it's like,
fuck man, enough is enough sooner or later.
So yeah, it's fun to be actually creating something.
I've got some cool stuff going on
and every once in a while I'll pop in and pop out as needed.
But it's important that people like you keep doing the work
and putting out information because there are lots of people around the world
that are still new to a lot of what's really going on
and need that shake in order to be able to snap out of the mind control,
cultural, social conditioning matrix that they're in.
And for that purpose, to that end, it is highly valuable.
Well, the whole concept of good management is to make yourself redundant.
So if the concept of the show is to wake people up,
no, it's not to wake people up.
The people who are listening to the show probably have already, quote, unquote, woken up.
The idea of listening to the show is you'll listen to it enough
that you'll want to get out of bed and you'll want to go to work against the new world order.
That's what I'm talking about. That's real productivity.
I mean, there's some people who literally cannot do that though.
They're still – they're tramped.
It's like you can work your life and you find your place in your workforce
and after a while you realize that you haven't played – you found your place in the world.
And you're trapped where you are.
You're trapped in your house that has a mortgage.
You're trapped in your job that has set hours.
You're trapped in a mindset.
You're trapped in your family's environment.
You're trapped in perhaps a surroundings that isn't conducive to truthing and activism, et cetera.
Maybe everybody thinks you're nuts in your house.
Maybe everybody tells you you ought to calm down.
You ought to just do your job and shut up and drink the Kool-Aid like the rest of us.
You know, before when I was doing blogging and doing radio shows two times a week,
that was what you just shared was my main theme and message.
If I were to say that I had one on an ongoing basis,
which is that the fastest way to change the world is for people to follow their passion,
to break free of that system that keeps people slave laboring
and doing some nine-to-five job that they couldn't fucking stand
and throwing themselves into the deep end
and realizing that they are capable to break free from that system.
I mean, I quit my job in February of 2013.
I had $8,000 to my name and I had no fucking idea.
Excuse my language. I can swear here, right?
Yeah, you fucking can.
I had no fucking idea how I was going to survive.
But something told me this isn't it.
It's not working.
There's no joy.
There's no passion.
There's no creativity.
I fucking hate it.
So it's worth it to me to throw myself into the wind and just see what happens.
And the fact of the matter was that that was the biggest crucial turning point that led to...
I haven't punched a time card since.
And here we are in November of 2015.
And guess what?
I haven't died of starvation.
I haven't spent any days in the street without a roof over my head.
And the universe has paved very creative and very unpredictable ways
for me to be able to navigate the terrain without having to worry about how to survive.
And I think that at the crux of people staying within that system,
that kind of mind-controlling system,
is that I don't know how I'm going to survive if I step outside of this sense of security,
this sense of being able to ensure that I keep food on the table and the roof over my head.
And that, breaking free from that illusion of self-limitation,
is the key to be able to transcend that process on every level.
And it works.
I know a lot of people that have done it also.
And it's scary as shit.
But somehow, everybody figures out a way to make it work
because we all have some sort of higher calling.
We didn't come into this world to sit in a fucking cubicle,
to die under fucking lamps that are frying our brains,
and to punch fucking numbers into a fucking computer all day.
Now, that's an extreme example, but I know people that fucking do that.
And it's not the way to live.
And the faster people unplug from that harvesting-type scenario,
the less energy, the gas all of a sudden in the tank of this global commercial-based system
that we live in worldwide, that just all of a sudden comes crashing down, collapsing down.
So they don't want free thinkers.
They don't want people that are following their heart and following their passion
because that means less cogs in the wheel of the system that keeps people in control.
So it is a vicious cycle, a vicious system, but highly empowering to break free from.
And sometimes it takes those that are still stuck there to hear stories like mine
to realize that it is very much possible and can be an exciting and scary as shit process.
Well, yeah, and again, this seems to be a recurring theme on the show already.
Everything you've said basically happened to me as well.
Like, for example, you had $8,000 and you quit your job in 2013.
I had $11,900 worth of shopping vouchers and $5,000 cash in 2007 when I quit my job.
But same thing, I've always had a roof over my head.
I've always had a meal in my belly.
I've always had just enough money to pay the bills whenever I need them.
And it's kind of like if you're sitting there and you've got 20 different screens in front of you,
you don't know what any of them are saying because they're all talking at once.
When you turn all of them off but one, because you know that you can't focus,
you can't do anything but by distract and block out everything that doesn't matter,
and you don't do it because you necessarily want to.
You do it because you're compelled to.
There's something that tells you that you have to do it.
You don't have a choice because you're going to drive yourself insane
or kill yourself or kill somebody else, probably the boss,
and it's not going to work out very well for everybody.
Nobody wins in that scenario.
So, yeah, I don't advocate killing your boss.
However, there's been a few that I've wanted to.
But, yeah, the sooner you extricate yourself from that, all of a sudden the world opens up.
Synchronicity becomes much more prevalent.
Meeting the right people and being in the right situations and scenarios at the right time
that seems very divinely, in some level, inspired.
It's just a much more pleasant way of living on every level.
And that doesn't mean it's not hard.
I mean, there's been times where I had no clue,
and I know that you can speak to this also,
but where that next money was going to come from to ensure that rent was paid
or whatever, that you were able to get groceries.
But somehow, at the 11 1⁄2 hour, something pops up,
and then all of a sudden you know.
And the more times that happens,
I think the more faith you have in that process that we're being taken care of.
And then all of a sudden you realize,
okay, next time this happens, I promise myself I'm not going to stress out about it.
And then sure enough, you do.
But the more consistency you have and the more comfortable you get with the process
of just allowing the universe to unfold before you,
the more you realize that there's a whole lot more going on than what we can see,
taste, smell, hear, touch.
Am I missing any other senses?
Above an extra sensory perception.
But when you're working, you've got a schedule, you know,
and you tell yourself what the plan for the day is every freaking day.
But when you work for yourself, the plan tells you what to do.
It's like it actually comes out of the ether kind of thing,
just magically appears, like literally.
There was this one time I got up in the morning and it was bill day,
and I was like, okay, I got the water bill, the internet bill, and the rent.
That's $500.
I don't have $500.
So I go to my PayPal, and there's $500 in there.
Boom.
That's the exact scenario I'm talking about.
Some magical donation that came from somewhere or some tax return check
that you got lost in the mail three years before.
I mean, you really never know where it's going to come from.
But it just somehow seems to.
And I think that it is.
It's this false sense of security that Matrix-style-esque jobs we feel provide for us
that keeps us in those positions.
I mean, I've talked to people.
It's the same all the way up this perceived level of control
that dictates the way that the world works.
All the way up in the upper echelons, the elite and the illuminati.
I've heard the stories.
First-hand accounts that they don't know what they would do
if they exited ranks and went another way
because their livelihood requires them to stay within the system that they have around themselves.
It's not easy at any level.
Just because something isn't easy doesn't mean it's not possible.
But it does.
It takes a leap of faith.
Shit, if we can't do leaps of faith, man,
then we've got a long rocky road ahead of us.
I feel like we're at this turning point
in where we are in the process of human evolution
that it doesn't really matter.
This might be a very optimistic way of looking at it,
but it doesn't really matter what anybody does
because this whole thing is unfolding in this perfect way.
And so you can either resist what's happening
or you can let go of the side of the river and just go slow.
And things have a tendency of just getting a whole hell of a lot easier.
So that's my little bit on that.
And for anybody that's out there that's sitting on the fence
and trying to figure out what the fuck to do and how the hell to do it,
don't worry about how to do it.
Just do it, you know?
Forgetting, letting go of the how and trying to put together a plan.
I mean, let all that shit go
because if I were to try to make a mind map
of how I was going to do it back in February 2013,
how I'm doing it and how I thought I was going to do it now back then,
look, absolutely nothing like each other whatsoever.
And because it goes to the point that you made
that the universe somehow has it all under control.
So you either have faith in that process or you don't, you know?
And I'm not here to try to tell anybody how to live their lives,
but my story, your story, some of these other stories are great examples
that really the only thing to fear is fear itself,
for lack of a better non-creative way of saying it.
Yeah.
Everybody in life is worried about money.
You know, I'm worried about money, you're worried about money.
Even people that have got jobs have to worry about money.
But also the problem is if you have a job,
you also have to worry about the fact that you're starting to hate yourself.
And in life, some people, you know, choose to work.
Some people choose to work for themselves.
And some people just sit on the fence, you know?
And I'm just trying to burn the fence down.
It's time to get a bulldozer and just knock this damn fence over.
We'll do it fucking Gaza-style, bro.
I want to burn it, really.
I want to burn it and I want to do it in a really sacrificial kind of way
that's almost dark, you know?
I don't know if that makes me weird or crazy.
All I want to do is dance around the burning fence
after everybody suddenly had to choose what they do with their life
and not allow other people to fucking tell them
what they have to do with their life, you know?
And it'll be like dancing around it, naked, jiggling in the air,
and the chicken is smeared in goat's blood.
It'll be fucking fantastic.
We're going to mutilate it, like with a spoon.
Just really kind of have fun with it, man.
That's what I would vote for.
It'll be like a...
It'll be like the Doors concerts or something.
I'm thinking pay-per-view.
We make loads of money and we send the money from Africa
to feed starving children.
I mean, it's really, at the end of the day, it's for a good cause.
No, no, no, no.
I've got a better idea of what to do with the money.
You hire African mercenaries to kill all the people
that are giving bad drugs and stuff like that
to all the Africans that's causing AIDS.
If you have that petition, I would love to sign that
on behalf of myself and all of humanity.
That reminds me.
I remember there was an ex-CIA assassin, Chip Tatum,
and he's come out about some of the operations
that he did back in the day,
working for this hit squad under the US government,
sort of privatised, right?
And he says that he has a hit list that he wants,
like a list of really freaking bad people
that just need to be taken out
because they won't go any other way.
And he was asking for donations.
He started a Kickstarter plan.
Now that is taking crowdfunding to a whole new level, man.
Put it on Pledge Me, bro.
You know, I guarantee you that fund
did not end up an empty bucket.
Somebody put some money into that cause, I know it.
Only got $20 in my pocket.
You know, $20 in a third-world country
can go a very long way, man.
That's at least one takeout.
You can find somebody desperate enough to take out one guy.
That's at least one clip of 9mm.
Yeah.
Throw in a few corndogs.
You're good to go, man.
You're talking making serious, serious, very creative business.
I like the way your mind thinks, man.
I appreciate that about you.
I like it, too.
Everybody talks about this as well.
I don't like the idea of violence or killing or anything.
You know, I'm just joking about
sending mercenaries over there to just kill them and torture them
and ruthlessly butcher their families and things like that
and redistribute the wealth, okay?
It's just a joke, bro, okay?
And in fact, that's another thing.
I figured out that my show,
if I say anything that's controversial or really horrific
or something like that
and people want to, like, charge me with inciting terrorism or whatever,
I've got this great little caveat that I can just bust out.
It was a joke!
Yeah, man.
That's a soundbite.
You're good to go.
That's written in ink.
It's on the Internet.
It never goes away.
And, you know, that's your out.
It's called the lack of a smoking gun.
And it works, you know?
Maybe I could have that as something on the opening of the show,
like pre-recorded or something.
The Vinny Eastwood Show.
If anything on this show offends you or makes you want to kill Vinny,
just remember, it was a joke!
And just remember, if that doesn't work,
the way to always get out of everything,
you see it in all the movies,
you just claim insanity.
And Vinny, if you did that, I would believe you.
Because, dude, you're borderline insane,
and that's what I like about you, man.
Well, a lot of people call me insane,
and I take it as a compliment.
Because in a world this fucked up,
if somebody were to say that I had a real handle on things,
I'd feel insulted.
Sanity is very overrated, man.
Insanity is the new cool.
And it really means really letting things go and just saying, fuck it.
And I know a lot of people that are doing that very well.
And it is the way to go.
I mean, on my business card, my tagline is just say, fuck it.
And it works.
It's not really.
I think I might make that now.
At least part of my email signature.
Fuckit.com
Is it an animal, mineral, or vegetable?
Can I eat it?
Can I live in it?
Can I fuck it?
You've got to put everything in life through the can I fuck it filter.
And that makes everything really fun.
Wow.
I'm thinking of a great business idea.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Fuck it glasses.
There'll be an app that you can put into Google Glasses.
It'll highlight in green the things that you can fuck.
Jacuzzi air filter system or something like that lights up in green.
Like, really?
I can fuck that?
Absolutely.
It's a triple-triple abraded cock fucking massager right there, bro.
Who would have ever thought that I could, you know, I could fuck this, whatever the what you want to call it, this widget.
You know, it really just opens up a whole bunch of possibilities.
The can I fuck it widget by briankelley.com
My mother's going to be so proud.
I can't wait to send her the link to this video.
You make your mama bosom swell with pride.
So what else is going on with you, man?
Well, you know, I've just been thinking about the Christmas season and all the shops are starting to put up their Christmas decorations.
And apparently they started doing it a month ago, like on television.
Like, so I've heard I watch fucking television.
But yeah, apparently there's been Christmas advertisements going throughout the whole month of November and October.
It's just like Christmas season starts earlier every year because everybody just goes.
Hey, you know what makes people want to part with their cash guilt tripping them about not buying their loved ones a present.
Boom.
Like where's the Christmas decorations?
I brought it back.
Black Friday.
Yeah, I haven't.
I don't know.
I don't I'm not sure how any of that stuff we're advertising.
I mean, all that stuff is just so so far outside of my reality anymore that I find it hard to believe that anybody is still going out and dropping thousands of dollars leading up to Christmas.
I don't know.
It's just the concept that doesn't make sense to me anymore.
I mean, don't get me wrong.
I go home.
I celebrate Christmas.
I buy my family a few a few a few cool things.
But it's funny because somebody asked me the other day here in Bali where I'm living now.
Oh, you're going over there.
Oh, you're Christian.
They just assume that everybody that celebrates Christmas is Christian.
I'm like, no, even atheists, I think, in the United States celebrate Christmas.
And that's how well ingrained the kit can Christmas condition shopping program is within people that they don't even have to believe in what Christmas is supposed to represent.
They still go out and buy shitloads of stuff that they don't need.
See me.
I celebrate Ramadan by drinking and smoking more because the Muslims can't.
Oh, yeah.
Nice.
Why not see the whole concept of a holiday season?
I got this saying, even notice that holidays never come early enough and they always end too soon.
And I think I figured out why it is, bro.
It's because your holiday is merely a break from working.
All right.
And if your work's not uber fulfilling, that gives you plenty of time to relax and stuff like that and recuperate.
You need that.
In fact, you know, kind of think of it.
Everybody needs holidays, bro.
And some people don't take them and they burn themselves out.
I've seen so many activists just go.
Because I think the whole fucking world will just collapse without them doing their very important work for a couple of months or something like that.
And then before they know it, you know, a couple of months later, they they totally burn out.
They quit being an activist completely.
And then they go back to get a slave job, completely disillusioned.
And then basically join the other side and say that everybody who's an activist is just an idiot that's wasting their time because they were an idiot and wasted their time.
Well, I you you just described many people that I know.
We must swim in the same sea of activists.
Yeah. You know, I mean, it's funny.
I don't I don't have the same perception of holidays or weekends as I used to.
I don't have really a week every day is kind of this.
I don't wake up on Monday morning stressed because I don't have a set schedule.
So, you know, there's not really something that I'm doing that's so grueling that needs to be a holiday, needs to be taken to escape from it.
So, you know, and that's a that's a pretty good place to be.
And I'm very grateful that that's that is the scenario.
But yeah, man, it's you know, when you work a terrible job that you absolutely cannot stand, you know, come four o'clock on Friday, you're ready to get the fuck out of Dodge.
And on Sunday night, you're growing up in anxiety.
You got to go back to work the next day.
And I don't think that's what we were sent here to do.
So we're kind of looping back around on what we originally started talking about.
Well, you just described something there.
And you said by the end of the week, people want to get the fuck out of Dodge.
It takes me six months.
All right, before I just can't handle work and I need a holiday roundabout.
Yeah.
And I usually take maybe a month or two or two off if I if I really need it.
And it's mostly just the emotional recuperation.
The thing about interviewing people with problems, emotional problems, and, you know, people have been ritualistically abused and people who get persecuted by the media and shit like that, because I'm a sensitive and empathetic person.
I actually give a fuck when they tell me about this kind of shit.
So I take on some of their baggage in order to lighten the load for them, lighten the load.
I do.
But however, I get stuck with the baggage.
And after a period of time, I got so much other people's baggage on me that I literally start to have meltdowns, like on a daily basis kind of thing.
I get really angry for no reason.
I start yelling and screaming at the computer.
In fact, I yell and scream in the computer quite a lot.
Fuck this shit.
You and me both, man.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's when we live in a world that is that is fueled by massive amounts of just sickness on so many levels.
I mean, it's very easy to fall within that viewpoint of, holy shit, the world is going to hell in a handbasket and everything is just fucked and it doesn't matter what we're going to do.
I mean, I know a lot of those people that they think that humanity is heading toward its final point where we're not going to be around much longer.
And, you know, shit is fucked.
This shit is really fucked up on a lot of levels.
I mean, I know you've seen the thick of it with some of the people that you brought on your show over the years.
I always seem to have lost Brian.
Yeah, he's gone.
Bugger.
All right.
That's very unfortunate.
Anyway, yeah, well, something you were saying before was kind of interesting to me.
Like when you get up on Monday morning, you know, you're not stressed because you don't have any schedule to keep or anything like that.
And that's not too similar to me.
I mean, like I've got a schedule to keep.
For example, on Mondays I do nothing.
You know, I hated Mondays for so long that I officially, you know, decided that I'd do four days a week of talk radio so I wouldn't have to work on Mondays.
But in the United States sense of the word, it means I don't have to work on Saturdays because we're a day ahead of you on this timeline.
But something that Brian was talking to me about, about time management, right?
I remember I interviewed this guy who's like an expert on what would you call them?
Entrepreneurs.
And he says that they've got a system called organic time.
All right.
Now, really think about this.
If you didn't have a watch, you didn't have a clock or anything like that, and you're just sitting there, you're working away on something for a period of time.
And you go, I really don't feel like doing this anymore.
I'm going to take a break from it.
And you go off and you do something else.
Organic time.
You just operate by your feelings.
You do what you feel you want to.
And you take breaks when you need to.
You know, it's not like having a set schedule.
You know, you've got to be at work by 8 a.m.
You know, I don't – I'm usually up and working by 8 a.m. anyway.
But that's by choice.
It's not because I've got a schedule.
You know, just get up and start working.
There's nothing else to do around here.
You know, what am I going to do?
Sit on my deck chair, watch the sunrise?
Boring as hell.
I'll just stick a camera there and then use it as a slow creeping shot in the video later.
You know, better idea.
But yeah, you'd be surprised how much more productive you can be when you're not on somebody else's time card.
Yeah?
When you make your own time.
And you'll find this as well is that you can make time.
All right?
You can actually manufacture time out of thin air just like that.
Quite interesting.
It might sound a bit confusing at first.
But here's how –
The person you are trying to reach is not accepting calls at this time.
Hang up that call.
Please try your call again later.
Yeah, there we go.
Shoot, what did I do?
Totally missed my place.
Man, that was distracting.
Hmm.
Haven't had any coffee for the entire hour as well.
Brain's starting to freeze up.
Yeah.
I'm saying the word uh and um too much.
When you have coffee, ladies and gentlemen, very important for talk radio show hosts.
Gives you increase in cognitive function and provided it's not GMO or sprayed with nasty chemicals and stuff,
it can actually not be that bad for you.
I heard that people who drink a bit of coffee live longer.
And I can understand that.
Because if I didn't have coffee, I wouldn't want to live that long.
I crack me up.
I do.
But anyway.
Yeah.
You know, I don't want to sound too pushy here, but quit your job.
Because it's dragging you down.
Unless, of course, you actually have one of those very rare instances where you're working with cool people.
You're doing cool stuff.
And it's really fulfilling.
It actually makes you happy.
And you get home at the end of the day and you feel great.
And you can actually raise your kids.
You've got more than enough money to get by.
And you contribute to society as well.
And in your spare time, you're not just working and relaxing.
You're actually doing something else on your own time.
Dude, that's like one of the perfect things.
I actually wish I could do that, you know.
It would be cool to have a nice, fun, cool job with a whole bunch of mates.
And get paid a hell of a lot to do some really awesome stuff that's very interesting and fulfilling.
As well as, at the end of the day, be able to go home and do a whole bunch of activism.
But unfortunately, there's not enough time.
So I made it, you know.
Just go, OK, let's have a look at the things in my life that are soaking up my time.
And let's eliminate them one by one in order to free up time for the things that I want to do.
Just that simple.
Now, American Freedom Radio is having a marathon at the end of this week, I believe on Saturday.
So make sure to check that one out.
There's Jordan Maxwell, Carol Rosen, Dean Clifford, and some dude from Iraq.
Something Ford or whatever about WMDs.
It's on Sunday. Sorry, Sunday.
So, yeah, tune into that, ladies and gentlemen.
And throw a few bucks American Freedom Radio's way.
And while you're at it, throw me something for Christmas as well.
You know, because what am I going to do?
You know, beg the universe for presents.
We'll see you after the break, ladies and gentlemen. Don't you go anywhere.
Welcome to the world's meeting place.
American.
Practically narcotic.
Freedom.
Oh, yes. I like it very much.
Radio.
You're an American institution.
American Freedom Radio.
Did you know there are 3 million edible food plants on Earth and none have the nutritional value of the hemp plant?
HempUSA.org offers you hemp protein powder.
It does not contain chemicals or THC, is non-GMO, and is 100% gluten-free.
Hemp protein powder burns fat, builds muscle, contains 53% protein, and feeds the body the nutrients it needs.
Call 888-910-4367 and see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org.
HempUSA.org introduces 3 brand new detox formulations of micro plant powder.
Brain Fuel for depression, bipolar disorders, and stress.
Total Care, anti-cancer agent that cleans the liver and organs and increases memory.
Rejuvenate, invigorates and heals the body, mind, and spirit.
These products are your alternative to pharmaceuticals.
Call 888-910-4367 and like us on Facebook.
We ship worldwide.
Only at HempUSA.org.
American Freedom Radio is back.
We're trying to become commercial free apart from a few honorable advertisers that we would give ad space to even if they couldn't pay us.
In this quest to deliver quality radio with very few annoying ads, we are now asking the listeners like you to open up and become partners with American Freedom Radio.
We all know the economy is controlled and a new system called the peer-to-peer economy is now within our grasp.
That means if you'd like this network with its incredible hosts and incredible information to be nothing but the content you want to hear,
then you must realize that you cannot be a part of it if you're just sitting on the sidelines watching.
Go to AmericanFreedomRadio.com and pledge your support today.
Donate according to your means.
Some can only afford $1 a month while others can afford $100 a month.
Regardless of the size of your contribution, it all adds up to keeping the network owners and the radio hosts housed and fed at the end of every month.
Thank you.
We are living in a new era.
Partnerships are more important than profit and gratitude is more respected than greed.
As the millennial generation evolves the corporate landscape, our company aims to maximize the achievements of CBD application and push the limits of what's possible by 2020.
Our core product matrix and careful cannabidiol purification process are uniquely designed to be privately made in different regions of the world
and is geared to assist the efforts of different nations to change the landscape, various pain-related healthcare costs, epilepsy and autism, rising mental disorders and even soldier suicides.
Crystal Pure CBD is made with the industry's finest 99.9% pure CBD crystals.
No paste, no filler.
Our solution is a permanent answer and it saves you over one-third in cost.
Crystal Pure CBD.
Come join us.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
The network who perseveres in delivering intelligent debate, constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun, honest and pure integrity behind it provides an example to follow.
Friendships to flourish with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline in their duty to deliver quality radio in service to the community with strength, wisdom and loyalty.
The founders of AFI wish to thank you personally for sharing your views and insights to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs and artillery batteries not included.
No rules.
No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are American Freedom Radio.
Welcome back to our number two of the Vinnie Eastwood show.
Broadcasting via pirate radio signal from the private prisons run by General Zod.
Located in the freshly terraformed Krypton colony of Auckland, New Zealand.
Humanity's last and best hope in the fight against taking ourselves too seriously.
Here's your host, Vinnie Eastwood.
Welcome back to our number two of the fastest two hours and talk radio.
It's the Vinnie Eastwood show broadcasting live on American Freedom Radio.
Now, if the studio is willing, I'd really like to open the call lines up and allow the listeners to ring in.
I'll let you know when those lines are open.
The number is 218-339-8525.
That's 218-339-8525.
If you're in New Zealand like me, you need to call like a plus one or a plus zero or something.
It's definitely a plus one on top of that puppy for that international calling.
And sometimes it doesn't actually even cost that much to call the States.
I used to sell like toll calls for a living and stuff like that.
It should be remarkably cheap.
Sometimes it can even be cheaper than calling other places in New Zealand, depending on the time of the day.
Anyway, I want to also kind of thank Brian Kelly for coming on and being a good dude.
However, moving on.
We were talking in the first hour about religion.
The call lines are now open, so if you'd like to call in and express your thoughts on that or anything else, you want to ask me anything.
Don't feel uncomfortable.
Seriously, I'm Vinnie.
I'm comfortable with everything.
You can just come straight on up and ask me anything you want.
So long as it's not abusive or defamatory or something.
Within reason.
So the caller lines are now open.
The number is 218-339-8525.
That's 218-339-8525.
That's the number to ring in there.
Please call in now.
If you're listening, please call.
Because I've run out of ideas.
I'm coming to the end of my tether.
I'm freaking exhausted.
In the meantime, it's just going to be like a one-man therapy session.
I'm just going to freaking unload on you.
In the last hour, I talked about all the baggage that was being draped on me by all the people that I've got on as guests and all the trolls and everything that come out after the videos and just fucking with them all the time.
It's like, oh, my God.
Sometimes it's just too much, bro.
Honestly.
And it's not just like it's too much all of a sudden.
It creeps up on you.
And I think I only really get about two weeks warning.
I can only handle about a fortnight worth of shows when I don't want to.
That's the only reason why I'm here right now is because of my obligation to the network.
Network didn't ask me.
I can take any day off I want.
But I feel obliged to be here.
And the fact that I really don't feel like it is kind of inconsequential.
I mean, really, there's a broader scheme at play here.
However, I'm not going to risk burnout over it, which is why I'm going to be going on holiday soon.
Holiday for me is doing nothing.
Other people who work when their job sucks or whatever, and life is hard, et cetera, et cetera.
However, when you're an activist, taking a holiday is simply not working.
I just have to stay at home, maybe do some stuff around the house, maybe catch up on some stuff.
It's not terribly exciting.
I would like to go away somewhere, somewhere I haven't been.
And I found out that because of my drug dealing conviction when I was a teenager,
I have to disclose that to the US government if I ever want to come there.
And in fact, I have to disclose it to everywhere.
Because although New Zealand has a law called the Clean Slate Scheme,
which says after seven years all your records are kept secret and nobody can even ask them for you,
unfortunately, New Zealand legislation doesn't apply in other countries.
That's the little caveat that they've got on that.
And they don't advertise that widely as they should, I think.
Clean Slate Scheme, it only helps you if you're in New Zealand.
Which means you can't really leave the country.
Not with a conviction like mine.
I only had like frickin' 13 grams on me.
That was it.
And I got 300 hours of community service.
I was lucky I didn't go to jail for up to eight years.
They treat it more seriously than manslaughter, bro.
They really do.
There was a dude up in front of me who was like,
growing five plants and sexual assault, resisting arrest.
And this is like his umpteenth time in court.
Gets 150 hours community service.
I go up pleading guilty.
13 grams of cannabis.
First time I've ever been in trouble with a law at all.
And 300 hours community service.
Just like that.
It was unbelievable.
Almost as unbelievable as the guy who was before the guy in front of me.
It was like some recovering heroin addict.
Who was in there, quite literally, because he stole a jar of raspberry jam.
And BP took him to court.
You know, pay a lawyer to prosecute him and everything.
And then the court ordered reparations of like $4.16 to replace the jar of jam.
Oh man.
Those were harsh times.
You know, I almost have a panic attack when I start thinking about
back, how hard it was and how young I was.
How naive.
My God, I was a very different creature back then.
It was just 10 years ago.
Bugger me.
The years do fly when you're exposed in scumbaggery, I must say.
And I think I've figured out the reason why time seems to pass quicker
when you mostly focus on scumbaggery.
It's because there's so much of it that you get lost in this kind of K-hole.
The scumbaggery K-hole.
And just a heads up, we've got a caller in there.
The Greek wants to join in via Skype.
So if you want to connect them up, AFR, that'd be lovely.
Or Greek, if you want to message AFR and get them to bring you in.
That will work as well.
And kind of maybe talk on religion for a bit.
The Greek talking about religion.
Fuck me, that could be dangerous.
I've really got to turn down the gain on my mic somewhat, don't I?
It's like so loud.
And I'm like laughing all the time and it's just like going crazy.
It's terrible, isn't it?
So sorry about that, ladies and gentlemen.
Is this better?
I hope it is.
Because if not, I'm screwed.
But yeah, I wanted to kind of relate the reason why I make jokes about everything.
You want to know the real honest truth why I make jokes about everything?
Because I'll go crazy if I don't.
Real crazy.
You know, as simple as I can explain it,
the terrible, terrible thing about being a comedian
is that you're smart enough to realize how bad things are
and your only coping mechanism is to laugh at them.
You can't change them.
You can explain them to people and help them see it for what it is.
Seeing something for what it is is actually pretty powerful.
I mean, here's another thing.
A lot of truthers who don't contribute to the truth movement
don't make videos or do radio shows or do activism of any kind.
They're really hard on themselves and they shouldn't be.
It's a big, big machine, this world.
And if you don't have the kind of narcissistic flair that people like me have
to get on talk radio and just riff it for hours on end just because you can,
don't feel bad about yourself that you're not contributing in that way.
There's your own way to contribute somewhere.
It might just be raising your kids right.
Maybe your kids will do something really big in the future that will change the world.
Just raising your kids right is good enough.
So I told somebody at a party this one time.
Now we've been joined by the Greek.
He's the only Greek I know.
Hey, mate.
Hey, I've heard that before.
Hey, and New Zealanders don't use the word mate.
No, it's Kiwi.
We use the word bro.
Oh, that's right, bro.
Like Hawaii, it's bra.
I forgot about that.
That's also in South Africa.
Yeah, mate, I'll just have to go down to the shop to get some cigarettes, bra.
Yeah, it's the bra.
So what has gotten into you?
Why do you want to discuss about religion?
Or what about religion?
Maybe I'm masochistic.
I need a whole bunch of fucking crazy religious, zealous, crazy, fucking stupid people coming at me and attacking me for talking some sense.
All right, all right.
Religion just means something you do regularly.
Like I do that religiously, right?
I do this or that.
Like I brush my teeth or tie my shoelaces and do talk radio, right?
Or something like that, religiously.
That's all it means.
I think what people have turned it into is...
Wait a second, wait a second.
Does that mean you can masturbate religiously?
Yeah, if you're a master.
Or a priest.
Sorry, you were saying?
Have we lost you?
Just for a moment.
That wasn't very religious.
Okay, all right.
Well, I usually go around saying things like, you know, there's not a religion on the planet that does or knows anything.
That's in the texts that they allegedly subscribe to.
And I'll challenge anyone to bring up anything in any religion.
And I will show you that what they're saying will not be found in context in any of the texts that they allegedly subscribe to.
Period.
That is a fact on this planet.
So I think we've lost our minds.
Because it's not really based on anything.
Neither is the money, neither is medicine, neither is anything.
So in that case it's a lie.
Anything that has a major hierarchical structure and one big central leader or central figure that you're not allowed to question or bring to court on child pedophile charges, it's a cult.
Or pedophile.
A pedophile is someone who likes shoes.
But anyway.
No, no, actually there's also a pedophile is somebody who really likes bicycles.
Right.
Or a velophile, that would be.
Anyway.
And there's also a PDF file, but that's for a Word document.
Yeah, for those that are wordy.
But, okay, you know the secular historians, which are self-professed atheists typically, professors, they'll tell you this is the Christian era.
So it is really when people say Christianity, you know, that is the predominant one.
And in the news lately it's been the Islamic one.
So, I don't know, which way you want to go?
Well, I was also thinking the other day about persecution.
Persecution of anybody for anything is not really a good thing if they're not harming anybody.
But some Christians get persecuted and they freaking deserve it.
You know, just like if you...
What were those people who like hang out outside the... America's most hated family?
They hang outside the graves of veterans holding big signs that said God hates fags.
You know?
Which God?
Which God? Because the fags have their own God as well, so you're going to have to work that one out.
But anyway.
The fag God, you know, and they have a little bath house on top of Mount Olympus.
There you go.
Where the mounting goes on.
Yeah, those Greeks, the guys would all do each other and then go home and beat their wives.
Those ancient Greeks, yeah.
But anyway, that was the festival, I guess, that's coming up that everyone...
The darkest day of the darkest part of the month, you know, it's coming up here for everyone.
They got their own version of it.
But yeah, God is an oxymoron because there's many.
It's kind of like saying aunt or...
You know how we use language in a certain way that's accepted?
You know, we could say it's an army.
You know, we don't mean...
Well, it's just one person in the army.
We know when we say army, it's a multitude.
And people have forgotten that when they say God, it's a multitude of gods.
And that's in all of the ancient texts.
And of course, who cares about what the ancient texts say?
Because those people were ignorant and savage, of course, you know.
We don't have to read any of that stuff.
We have computers now.
We don't have to read anything.
We have religion now.
We don't need to read what these things are supposedly based on.
But yeah, that's one of the interesting parts.
It's part of what I call cosmic censorship.
The planet has been cosmically censored by forces.
I'm not talking about the archons and the reptilians
and all the crap you hear on the internet going on.
Because if you listen to all that and see what it's based on,
it's based on nothing again.
But if you look at what's been memorialized for thousands of years,
there is a cosmic censorship put on mankind
to stuff up his ears and his eyes so he can't perceive.
Isn't that interesting?
Well, I don't know.
It sounds like the mainstream media's job to me.
Along with other things, yeah.
And let's go back to the persecution.
You know, all that persecution,
a lot of those people that do the persecuting
just want to persecute for any damn reason.
It's just the way they are.
I was also thinking the other day,
and this is actually the thought that I originally had,
but I forgot to express it,
is that my heart actually goes out to people
who are persecuted for their beliefs.
You know?
I really do feel that probably
some of the widest persecuted groups at the moment
are Muslims and Christians.
And that's interesting,
because they're persecuting each other.
But hold on, but hold on.
If all you're going on is belief,
maybe you should be persecuted,
because you're really stupid.
Sorry.
You need to actually pursue something that's substantive.
What has happened is that people have,
what's been put on them,
because it's easy,
it's kind of like, you know,
eating out of a can or microwaving food.
Who wants to cook an hour and a half dinner anymore, right?
So what they do is they've convinced everyone,
oh, you have a right to believe in what you want to,
and that's it.
You can't go to war when we tell you to.
Well, you say that maybe they should reprioritize
and try to live a life of substance,
but do you think that having a belief
instead of knowing what it is,
do you think that that in and of itself
can deprive somebody of having a life of substance?
Oh, absolutely,
because your life of substance is governed by law,
meaning not traffic law or tax law or whatever,
or cannabis laws,
but law is what you eat, what you wear,
how you keep time,
how you raise a family,
how you plant your crops,
how you deal with your neighbor,
how you get into a contract.
You see what I mean?
Law is like what they call ethics and morality,
and also your functional,
how you function in the world, right?
That comes from your deity, from your God.
Well, I pray to my God all the time.
No, no, it's nothing to do with prayer.
Now, prayer is when you,
it's like in the military,
you have the communications officer, right?
That's the guy who communicates.
That's what prayer is.
You know, it's interesting.
You ever seen the Christian meme?
They show you putting your hands closed, right?
You know, when they pray.
Yeah.
That comes from Hinduism.
Namaste.
Yeah.
Biblically, it's your hands are spread out
and palms faced.
Palms faced to something else.
Greg, you're cutting out a little bit today there, bro.
You still back with us?
Why?
Hands spread out, palms faced up.
That's the method of communication
for the biblical deity.
Now, the Christian deity is,
here's the thing.
The Christian deity is not biblical.
Zero percent.
I've been looking at this for over a decade,
and I haven't found anything
that Christians do that's in the Bible.
Now, hold on a second.
That might sound very general and irrational,
but if I try to maintain some rationality,
if they did one out of a thousand
or .01 percent of what they did was biblical,
I'd have to grant them that, right?
To be rational.
But I haven't found anything that Christians
believe in, say, or do that's in the biblical text.
Now, that's fascinating to me,
how far off and opposite the mark they are.
Maybe it's because the biblical text
was, you know, cobbled together
a couple of hundred years ago in the New Testament,
and it doesn't actually apply to today,
you know, with all our technologies
and our cultural changes and stuff like that,
believing the earth is round and shit.
Well, there's actually several places in the Bible
that tell you the earth is round.
So...
Well, when I say and shit,
I also mean just a broad-brush caveat
of a whole bunch of superstitions
that we're sort of left go of,
even if they didn't believe in the flat earth at the time,
as they didn't even believe
that there was a flat earth
in the time of the Greeks.
You will never find a flat earth memorialized
in any literature in history.
Yeah, exactly.
That is because people don't read
and they make stuff up.
What is it called, telephone or something?
When someone tells a story to someone
and when it's five times removed, it's changed?
No, that's all that Chinese whispers in high school.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right.
Chinese whispers, yeah.
It's better than Chinese handcuffs.
But here's the interesting part
about any deific communication.
There's something called paganism,
which is basically,
the people were peasants
and the feudal lord wanted them
to do their job
and when it was discovered
that understanding what the gods
wanted to communicate
required a lot of study,
he just made up a couple of simple stories
so they could go back to work.
That's all your religion is on the world right now.
Whether it's Hinduism, Buddhism, Judaism,
Christianity, Islam,
they're all like that.
They're just little tales.
None of them have anything to do
with what's in the text.
Now, what I mean by the paganism part,
do they do in New Zealand,
when you go to court,
they have you swear on a Bible,
put your hand on the Bible,
say the truth, all truth.
No, no, no.
In New Zealand,
they just turn off the recording devices
and most of them here,
use them as door stops.
They're just communications.
What if you have it on a thumb drive?
Can you swear on the thumb drive?
You see what's going on here?
It's a little rabbit's foot talisman.
Humanity's been reduced to this
little tiny slave class
and the priests and the scholars
that were familiar with these texts
in any part of the world
realized the proprietary of the information
and looked at how people behaved
and said,
well, it was a bad judgment call
because now the people,
how are they going to elevate themselves
and understand law and physics and science
and all that stuff, right?
Because there's a very high level of science
in these ancient texts as well.
So anyway,
I've spent the past 10 years
almost full time
looking at all of the texts
throughout the planet
and it's hard to make these statements
that I'm making.
I really never wanted to say them in public
because someday here coming
people are going to start
trying to figure out
why things aren't working out
and they might actually go back
and look at the materials
that they're supposed to be based on,
whether it's laws.
That's why I think once in chat, Vinnie,
I was looking for the New Zealand
cannabis laws because they're all,
typically they have a little thing.
Could be the Misuse of Drugs Act 1978
or 1976.
That's right.
And then there's another code
that says it's been repealed
because they hide that away.
And the U.S. is Title 21, I believe,
and possession has been repealed.
It's just intent to distribute
and manufacture that people are.
I don't know how you can manufacture cannabis,
but anyway.
With a Budman processing machine
that churns, you know,
bud goes in, joints come out.
Yeah, it would be like
counterfeiting money.
I guess you need the right ink
to do that.
Okay.
Yeah, that could work.
Or conveyor belt.
So with the religious part,
your law comes from it.
Now, here's the interesting part.
It's a completely lawless society,
completely at this point.
Now, it doesn't mean there's no order
when what's what the mainstream
puts in people's mind is
if you don't have any law,
there is no order.
You can have a lot of law
in the world.
You know what I mean?
America?
Possibly.
Which one, though,
North or South or both?
Is it North or South?
Either way,
it doesn't matter.
It's still lawless.
But New Zealand is the same.
So the entire Western world
and Eastern world is lawless
at this point.
Let's just throw in a little trivia,
biblical trivia.
I know because no one,
I'm one of the five people on the planet
who's read it, believe it or not.
You have this thing called Christmas, right?
Coming up.
Now is the time for
biblical TV trivia
with your host, Luke Rieck.
So there are these big mega churches
over here in,
well, I guess they have,
do they have mega churches in Las Vegas?
We have what's called Destiny Church
where Bishop Brian Tamaki
named himself Bishop
and then gets a whole shitload of millions of dollars
and buys several houses
in swanky suburbs in Auckland
and tells everybody he's a pauper.
Yeah, that's exactly what I'm talking about.
So they have these big sites here
on the Internet
and they say,
well, no one really knows
when this J-E-S-U-S character was born,
so we're just going to go with it
and it's not pagan.
I'm like, wait a second.
Well, you know how timekeeping
changes from society to society
and giving a name or
let's say an existing time period
way of keeping time
doesn't carry over, right?
Like there was no January through December
2,000 years ago
or Monday through Friday.
These are recent timekeeping inventions
so the way you keep time
is astronomically
because astronomical occurrences
are extremely accurate
and regardless of what timekeeping
you use,
the stars and moon and the sun don't lie.
Exactly, and that way
everything you do in your life
has an astronomical chance of occurring.
Yeah, or sub-astronomical
in this case, being on Earth.
But what's interesting,
if you want to know,
it's very specific,
the Christ was a biblical Christ.
Don't confuse this with Jesus, by the way,
because there's like ten Jesuses.
There's one that says,
if you don't believe in me,
you do this, you do that.
It's just too confusing.
They may have a black one,
an Asian one,
and also the letter J
was invented in 1500,
so unless you're into medieval history,
forget it.
You hear that, Jesus?
Your name doesn't even exist!
And I've actually met
a couple of Jesuses in the past
out here, there's a really good
fish taco shop
and he has J-E-S-U-S
Jesus served me three fish tacos.
It's like, bro,
has he got enough fish to feed the whole party?
Yes, he fucking does!
Yeah, he does.
Now, here's the point.
In the biblical text,
I saw a great sign in the sky,
it was a virgin giving birth,
she was cloaked with the sun,
the moon at her feet,
and she had 12 stars at her head.
Holy crap, that's the constellation Virgo,
Draco, part of the Draco
is at the top of the constellation.
He's in the middle of the constellation
and we know it's the middle of the month
because it's a crescent moon,
because the sun and the moon are in the west.
So what you do is you go to an astronomical observatory
and you say, hey look,
I've got this constellation, the moon, the sun,
and this here, when does this happen?
And they'll tell you, oh yeah,
this astronomical observation happens
maybe three times every 20 years or so.
Well, if you look at when the Christ
was supposedly born,
King Herod died two and a half years later
and Caesar cast a census on his empire,
so we know secular records show
between 2 AD and 8 BC.
So you just go to the astronomical computer
and you say, when did this event happen
between 2 AD and 8 BC?
And you get a pinpoint day of 3 BC,
the day of 11, the month of September.
There you go.
So that's when he was born
according to the Gregorian calendar.
Now, does the 11th day of September,
has that somehow brought an inference?
Yeah, I was going to say that.
Yeah, September 11th,
like somebody like did a star chart
and then says, okay, well this is what they said
the stars look like on the night of Jesus' birth.
What date did that happen?
Well, it had to be September 11th.
Yeah, well that's,
and this is, what I'm saying is not my opinion.
It's not for debate.
Anyone can do that.
Anyone can look this up because
when I first started doing this
I had to go to a planetarium.
This was 12 years ago.
The computing power,
it just wasn't available to get that.
So the university wanted 500 bucks to do it.
But I went to the planetarium.
We know they do the light show at night.
And all the guys, they got nothing to do
during the day, they're just smoking pot,
whatever, and you go in there
and they'll just show you the light.
I think you've confused the planetarium
for the sanitarium.
There you go, okay.
So yeah, it was very interesting.
So these things go on and on.
Also they show you this little nativity scene
with three wise men,
and we don't know how many, whatever.
That's not true, that didn't happen
because in the biblical text it says
that these men from the east came
when he was in his father's workshop.
So he was about two and a half or three years old.
Now what this is,
I'm not saying that the biblical story is true
or anyone should believe it or anything.
I'm just showing the stark contrast
between what people believe
and what is in the text that they say
they're being bribed to, right?
The text is true.
Let's just say this for a conjecture.
Let's say the text is true,
but nobody's read it or understood it.
Does a tree make a sound if it falls
and no one's there to hear it?
No, no, no.
If a man speaks his mind in a forest
and no woman hears him,
is he still wrong?
Why does it matter?
Isn't he the king of the castle?
I don't think so.
Because she says so.
I mean, look,
the wife is the boss, all right?
She runs shit here.
I just live here.
Well, here I'm the boss
and I know that because she tells me I am.
Anyway, never mind.
You can't trust what women say, bro.
Yeah.
Okay, here's another one.
You know in the Islamic community
they think they're so righteous
because the women are covered in hajibs
and burqas and all that stuff, right?
It's so righteous.
Hey, and speaking of which,
I saw an amazing video today
of this Muslim couple
and they had two seats
and the street was flooded
and the guy was standing in the water
and he would take one seat
and then put it in front of his wife
and she'd step from one seat to the other
and he'd grab it
and he made sure that she didn't
drown in the floodwaters.
I thought that was very sweet.
Yes, but again,
if you read their text,
well, in ancient times,
let's just say it this way,
in ancient times,
you know what a uniform is,
you could see what someone's profession
is from a distance, right?
In the ancient world up until recently,
actually, in that part of the world,
if you saw a woman that was covered
the way women are supposedly covered today
in that part of the world,
that's a constitution.
Yes, so these people have lost their minds.
It goes across the board.
All religions, they're just insane.
Well, here's the good part.
You know, what you just said
makes a whole shitload of sense right now.
Well, let me just,
there's a family actually
that moved in not too far from here
and the husband has the wife covered
and I'm suspecting it's a wife or a sister
and she's holding a baby
as she's walking around
for an hour with that woman, you know?
I mean, she's wearing the uniform.
But anyway, this is, yeah,
and they think it's a form of being righteous.
It's just, this is,
who was it?
Wolfgang Goethe.
He said that you need not visit
an insane asylum to meet disordered spirits
because the earth is the insane asylum
of the universe.
Sounds about right.
There's madness everywhere you look.
I mean, nobody can be on Facebook
or YouTube comment sections
for more than five minutes
before knowing that that is a self-evident truth.
Yeah, I want to throw this in.
Important.
Remember how we talked about being lawful?
What's lawful?
It comes from your deity.
Well, it's very simple.
If you don't have a deity,
then it's real simple.
Do you obey the laws of the state?
Well, yes.
Okay, then the state is your God
and April 1st is your holiday.
Well, same thing.
Here's the interesting part.
You know what legal claims are
or lawful claims?
When someone makes a claim,
it stands until someone else rebuts it
or counters it accordingly.
So if it's written,
you should write it down
if you're going to rebut someone's claim.
What's interesting about the biblical text
is there's some claims in there
that this particular group
created everything
and they sit at the highest position.
And as far as I could tell,
it's never been rebutted.
So that requires,
if you have a lawful mind,
some investigation.
Now, what I mean by that is,
someone could go to their house
and have a white piece of paper
nailed to the door and says,
yeah, greetings, this house will be
foreclosed on in 30 days.
Well, if they don't have a lawful mind,
they just take it off the door
and see what happens.
Or if someone has a lawful mind,
looks at the notice and says,
oh, is there contact information here?
Who's the authority?
I need to work this out
before it gets out of hand.
See, most people see these things,
these claims,
and they've been trained socially
to disregard them.
It reminds me of this time
that my wife accidentally
put margarine on my toast
and I asked her to scrape it off
because margarine is alien.
You put margarine in the body,
the body says,
well, I don't know what to do with this.
That never happened.
That was a fictional story,
like the Bible.
Here's another thing.
Is the Bible actually 100% true?
Because it's been so many thousands
of years of whatever.
Let's say,
if you've got a legal case,
there's a thing called
a statute of limitations.
There's things called cold cases,
things that are so old
that nobody solved them at the time,
and nowadays,
there's just no fucking way.
Maybe that's what the Bible is.
It's a giant cold case
that people are investigating
and still haven't managed
to come to the bottom of.
Well, here's the thing.
If it's a legitimate communication
from a deity,
it doesn't seem like,
why would they act in futility?
They have an IQ of 2 million or so,
let's say.
But here's the thing.
Have you ever heard of Aesop's fables,
The Fox and the Grapes?
No.
Aesop was one of these Greeks,
you know, right?
The story of The Fox and the Grapes
was a fox is walking along a path.
He's really hungry.
He sees these beautifully ripe grapes
and he says, oh, I'd like to have some.
So he jumps up and he's trying to reach them
and he's spending a good part of the afternoon.
Well, he's hungry now anyway.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Right?
So the biblical text is like this.
For example, I've studied it quite a bit
and it's a language of preservation
because it's never been translated,
by the way, into English.
All the versions you get are not translations.
There's 4,800 critical errors
in the first 10,000 words.
So anyway,
it's just a communication.
I'd never recommend that anyone
go and read the biblical text or study it.
Why?
Because you're not going to understand
anything in it anyway.
So why waste your time?
That's actually the conclusion I came to
just before finishing Genesis.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Well, first of all,
it's written on a 100th grade level
and your, quote unquote,
smartest professors are operating
on a 5th grade level right now.
So you're not going to,
there's no way you're going to do,
it has to be deciphered.
It's backwards.
But here's the thing,
that's irrelevant.
All the ancient texts are very similar.
But what's good about it
is that you're coming up into
a part of human history
where people you've heard before
are going to realize
that they've got to go back to basics.
Like you've heard,
I think AFR used to run a David Icke voiceover
where he said,
look, we've got more lawyers than ever
before, you know.
The more banks, the more poor we are.
Doctors destroy health.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Lawyers destroy the law.
I have it on here
somewhere
on my computer.
But yeah,
here it is.
Boom, I've found it.
It's by Chris Hedges actually
and Icke was just quoting it.
We now live in a nation
where banks destroy justice,
universities destroy knowledge,
governments destroy freedom,
the press destroys information,
religion destroys morals
and our banks destroy the economy.
Very good.
Okay, now how much of that can a society,
a planetary society take
before,
where all they have to do
is stop and say,
what are these things based on?
So they're going to call the lawyers
on their laws,
they're going to call the religious people
where they get their information,
they're going to call the doctors
on their studies that you see.
This time has not come yet
and when that time comes
there's going to be some sanity.
Is that what you've been waiting for, bro?
Because you've got whole bunches of information
that you've refused to share.
You've started to bring it up
and then decided not to share it.
Is that what you're actually waiting for?
The general realization by the planet
that every single institution
and then people
will be able to receive
what you can tell them?
Man, I couldn't have said it better myself.
Thank you, Vinnie.
Are you asking or telling?
Well, I guess I just answered
my own question.
There's a time for everything.
It's just like, remember,
have you ever heard of,
what is it, the guy who,
back in the early 1900s
who used to catalog all the anomalous,
paranormal events,
starts with an F, I think.
What's his name?
He was like the first,
anyway,
they asked him,
if all these,
everything has been,
there's nothing new under the sun,
why did the steam engine
only come out 100 years ago?
He says, because it was steam engine time.
You see, Hero's engine, 200 BC,
the Greeks had a turbine,
a steam turbine,
it wasn't steam engine time.
They had to wait for Fulton.
You see, so right now
it's not time for that.
You've got to know the right time as well, right?
Well, the elite have a sense of timing,
and I think,
what was it, astro-theology,
you don't believe in astro-theology
or any of that stuff?
Oh, no, well, astro-theology,
all that stuff is the fox and the grape,
so they don't understand what they're reading,
so they'll make stuff up.
It sounds good to other people.
What do you believe, though?
I mean, here's the thing,
you don't actually have any beliefs,
you've got what you know
and what you're curious about.
Yeah, because they used to hang around
farmers and miners.
If you're on a mine or a farm
and you start talking beliefs,
you'll get kicked off that place
because they have to function
on things that work.
Well, maybe that's an interesting way
that the world is misfiring,
misfunctioning,
because,
just hear me out here,
maybe people are so stupid
that they don't realise
that they're stupid.
I heard an interesting statistic
that tells you everything you need
to know about America.
Lewis Black, comedian, said this,
there was a recent study
in the United States
that determined that 4% of Americans
believe that they're below
average intelligence.
And it's always not the one
being interviewed,
it's the next guy,
like the T-shirt,
I'm with Stupid,
remember that,
with the finger pointing over,
in the 70s?
Exactly.
Stupid people are like insane people,
they don't know they're stupid.
Insane people don't know
that they're insane.
So I ask these questions,
am I going crazy?
But a crazy person does not.
Well look,
I think there's a level of stupidity
around with everyone,
it's just that some people
are less stupid than others,
and there's a level of insanity
going around with everyone
and some people are just less insane
than others.
You know what it's like?
It's like when I was in a wood shop
and we had to plane
these little shafts
of bloody wood off this thing
in order to smooth it down
to the shape that we want.
Get this one off,
and that one off,
and this one off,
and before you know it
you've actually got something
that you can be proud of,
something that's got craftsmanship.
But it takes a hell of a lot
and you have to discard
most of what you had to start with.
It's like climbing a glacier
and getting off the stinking rock.
But anyway,
did I just say that on air?
Okay, so anyway,
you see how it goes?
Everything's just kind of nuts anyway,
and maybe,
maybe that's part of the reason
why so many truthers
think that they're going crazy,
is because everything else
is fucking nuts, right?
And everything's so stupid.
Have you ever noticed
that?
Well, you know,
just on a tangent here,
which is along the same path,
there's a lot of talk about
misinformation, disinformation,
lack of information,
ignorance, stupidity.
I haven't found that to be
the main problem.
The main problem is
when you confront someone
with a piece of information
that is newly imparted to them,
okay, new to their psyche
and consciousness,
put cognitive dissonance aside.
We're talking about rational thought here,
okay, and critical thought.
Very often you'll get,
you know, I haven't heard of that before,
and you know what?
I don't want to know about that,
and I don't care.
Wow.
Okay, so that's not ignorance anymore.
That is a response
of stubbornness, rebelliousness,
let's say apathy.
Do you get where I'm going with it?
No.
It's fear.
They're afraid to admit
that they're wrong
because they've been taught
throughout their entire life
that being wrong is a bad thing
as opposed to an experience
you can learn from.
Well, hold on.
I didn't say something right or wrong.
This is a new bit of information
that they could have never gone
either left or right on it.
This is a totally new bit
of information.
It doesn't conflict
with their belief structure at all?
It's just a random factoid?
Yeah, yeah.
Like, let's say chemtrails,
you know, sometimes I'll be
in a parking lot
and I'll see a rational,
a seemingly rational individual
and I'll say,
well, you know,
it's interesting,
there's not contrails, you know.
I'll say, oh, really?
I've never noticed that.
They're steam, right?
I'll say, no, they're not steam.
I'll explain why they're not steam.
They're like, you know what?
Yeah, I'm not into that.
I don't want to know about it.
I'm like, dude,
you're breathing it.
What do you mean
you don't want to know about it?
Well, it's the psyche.
No, no, no.
Because those people
are operating under
a belief structure.
The belief structure is
I'm not a lab rat
in a giant open-air
fucking
breathe tank experiment.
Okay?
Hold on.
Yeah, but it's not about belief.
There's just like,
go to a Christian,
open the Bible
and show them something in there.
The first thing they'll tell you,
well, that's not my Bible
so it can't be the same thing in there.
Or, you know,
I have three books in the car.
I have the Book of Mormon,
the Koran,
and the Bible.
So if I ever get into
these conversations in public
and they want to argue,
I say, I happen to have a copy
in the car right here.
And I once had a parking attendant
who was a Muslim, self-professed,
and he was telling me
about this and that,
this and that.
I said, where'd you hear that?
And he said,
well, at the mosque with the imam.
I said, that's not in the Koran.
He says, yes it is.
And I said,
I happen to have a copy right here.
Let me show you.
You see?
It just, yeah.
So the belief,
what does belief have to do with it?
Well, I think
what you do is
eventually you lose curiosity
and you don't want to know.
All right?
It's not like you can't know.
It's that you don't want to.
All right?
But how can you lose curiosity?
You can lose curiosity
by a number of different mechanisms.
Curiosity, for example,
getting punished.
You know,
if you're curious about something
and you go do that at work
or whatever
and you fuck something up
and the boss punishes you
or even maybe
that could start to manifest
during your younger years
and your parents punish you
for questioning certain things
or whatever.
And basically,
through a series of
trauma-based mind control incidents
called modern life,
you can lose your curiosity
quite easily
and most people have already.
You know what's interesting?
I'll throw this in there.
I've seen that in ancient life as well
through what's been memorialized.
You know,
the ancients were like this as well.
When an old idea gets old enough
that it becomes forgotten,
when it returns,
people think that it's new.
Yeah.
That's why if you want a really new idea,
read a really old book.
When the hell was the last time
somebody actually came up
with a new idea?
Oh, no.
We'd have to redefine the word new
if nothing is new.
There's nothing new under the sun.
It's all just a repetition
and stuff like that.
God damn it.
There's an experiment going on here.
That's what I'm starting to really think about.
There's actually a point,
like a computer game,
or a hologram,
or something like that.
There's actually an objective here.
Now, the human race hasn't fulfilled
whatever the fuck that objective is yet.
And until we do,
we're going to keep repeating
the same fucking cycles.
No, you're not.
Hold on, it has.
Because it's just like baking a cake.
It needs a cure.
There's a curing period.
Just like a cake is, what,
45 minutes at a certain temperature
or certain epoxies hold for 30 minutes.
There's a curing period.
In other words, until it's set.
And that period ended already.
And that's what's so freaking exciting.
But the problem is that time isn't reckoned
with the Gregorian Pope's work schedule.
So, anyway.
You know how they say it's 2015 or whatever?
Whatever happened all the other years before that?
What the hell's going on?
And if today is what they call
whatever this day of the week,
last year was another day of the week.
So what day of the week is it?
You know, the biggest problem that I see
is that everyone is,
that's not a problem.
I don't really see it as a problem.
I'll retract that statement.
Is that everyone is operating
under the Pope's work schedule.
And even something maybe as trivial
and as minimal and as insignificant
as keeping time has been lost.
It's a very heavy slave outline
that's been put on mankind,
which is the Pope's work schedule.
That's why when I hear people
bad-mouthing the Vatican,
all I have to do is ask them what day it is.
And if they say anything between January
or December, Monday through Friday,
they're admitting with their own mouth
that they're the Pope's subject.
So they're pretty twisted.
But not that bad-mouthing the Vatican
is twisted, but I'm just saying
that people don't have their house in order.
You've got to get it in order first
before you go about and do things like that.
That's why I sort of kind of stay retracted.
But anyway, I'm open to all suggestions
and considerations if there's anything
you'd ever want to hear discussed.
So I'll just put that out there.
Yeah, I don't know.
I was just thinking about
the purpose of life itself.
For me, it's quite easy to find
my purpose in life.
But I'm talking about life in the aggregate.
I'm talking about all the organisms
and everything.
It's working together in some way
in a symbiotic fashion.
And behaving independent of each other.
But is there actually an overall purpose?
There's a reason why this fish died today
of radiation poisoning and a reason
why that squirrel died yesterday
after getting run over by a kid
that stole his mum's Jeep
and filled it up with really high-octane petrol
and drag-raced his mates on a skateboard
that had rocket boosters attached to it
and the poor squirrel got run over.
There's a purpose that's an overlying
real strange interconnected web.
And here it is.
It's very simple.
Humanity is too egocentric.
The world revolves around me.
It's all about us.
We'll get over it. It's not.
There's a multitude of cosmic things
going on right now.
And there's an element or an entity
called death, as you so gave us
the examples on.
And when this element,
this thing called death,
or in other circles it might be called
entropy, which is degradation, rot,
decay, entropy.
Like an energetic system suffers
entropy when they lose their power.
This entropic destruction
or something called death.
This is a time for its peaking.
And death will be put to death.
It actually already has at some point.
Not here.
And when it reaches here, meaning the Earth,
there will be no more death.
And that will really change the consciousness.
And what I mean by that is imagine being born
and not going through puberty
until you're about 35 or 40.
You know, if there's a funeral
for someone at 100 years old,
it'll be a child's funeral.
So this is kind of pretty amazing.
And yes, there is a meaning of life.
And it's not about us right now, even though it is.
Yeah, that sounds about right.
It's when death, it's very difficult to see.
Here's another analogy of it.
Have you ever heard of anyone being brought up
or raised or born in a war zone?
You know, if you ever discussed anything
with old European people,
oh, I was born during the war,
and childhood was terrible.
We had to eat shoes and couldn't find any food
and all that.
This is a period of over 6,000 years
where mankind has been in a war zone.
Don't take it personally.
Yeah, the meaning of life is quite simple.
It's just that it's so simple
that it can't be described
because we're mid-range thinkers.
We cannot comprehend the complex
and we cannot comprehend the simple.
And explaining the meaning of life
in a mid-range way is very difficult.
But I just use the contrast
that when there is no more death,
you will see more meaning
in what just happened,
the entire human epoch.
Well, that's because at the point
where you no longer fear death,
you're not struggling in the survival
because when you're struggling for survival,
you're in a lower brain fight-or-flight mode
and you can't access higher fucking consciousness.
So imagine how many people
would be able to access higher consciousness
if they had no fear of death.
Yeah, but look,
okay, fear of death,
I don't like that.
Look, I'll just throw in this,
it's not whether I like it or not,
but the ancient Greeks
used to say that those who were afraid of dying
or have fear don't know how to live.
So maybe focusing on how to live better
and then the fear part goes away.
Yeah, well,
like I said before, it makes sense
because to me, the only things
that make sense have some kind of cosmic
irony to them.
Oh yeah, there's a sense of humor, there's irony,
there's everything, yeah.
Everything is something
and nothing, right?
That's cosmic irony.
Like, for example, somebody could be
a great lover and a complete
bastard.
Alright, well,
anyway, the Greek, thank you very much.
It was great.
And ladies and gentlemen, remember on Sunday
to check out the American Freedom Radio Marathon
we need to raise some
cash for the studio, so please
check that out, promote it,
share it out on social media,
email your congressman
and stuff like that, tell them to shut us down
because if they do shut us down, it'll give us a hell of a lot
more attention. Please,
just go apeshit, alright?
Support American Freedom Radio,
support the Vinnie Eastwood Show,
and we will see you again sometime, assuredly.
Thank you very much for listening.
...
Hemp is not marijuana, and marijuana is not hemp.
They are different varieties of the same species.
HempUSA.org wants the world to know these basic facts
and to help people understand that hemp protein powder
is the best kept health secret you need to know about.
Remember, hemp protein powder contains 53% protein,
is gluten-free, anti-inflammatory, non-GMO,
and is loaded with nutrients.
Call 888-910-4367, 888-910-4367,
and see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org.
What kind of person are you?
How do you see yourself?
Are you the kind of person that lets everyone else
do all the work, just hoping that you'll be able
to get some of the crumbs that fall from the table?
Or are you the kind of person that rolls up their sleeves
and does the dirty jobs that no one else wants to do?
Are you hoping that all the activists giving their blood,
sweat, and tears to serve humanity
are going to solve all the world's problems?
Or are you just wondering,
is there something simple I can do to contribute?
Yes, yes, there is.
Help us.
Help us do what we do.
Partner up with American Freedom Radio today
by gifting a regular amount to support the network
and your favorite hosts, bringing you less commercials
and more information.
Go to AmericanFreedomRadio.com and start donating today
from between $1 and $100 per month,
according to the kind of person you are.
Thank you very much for your support.
We are living in a new era.
Partnerships are more important than profit,
and gratitude is more respected than greed.
As the millennial generation evolves the corporate landscape,
our company aims to maximize the achievements
of CBD application and push the limits
of what's possible by 2020.
Our core product matrix
and careful cannabidiol purification process
are uniquely designed to be privately made
in different regions of the world
and is geared to assist the efforts of different nations
to change the landscape,
various pain-related healthcare costs,
epilepsy and autism, rising mental disorders,
and even soldier suicides.
Crystal Pure CBD is made with the industry's finest
99.9% pure CBD crystals, no paste, no filler.
Our solution is a permanent answer
and it saves you over one third in cost.
Crystal Pure CBD, come join us.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com,
the network who perseveres
in delivering intelligent debate,
constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun,
honest and pure integrity behind it
provides an example to follow,
friendships to flourish with the moral altruism
that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline
in their duty to deliver quality radio
in service to the community
with strength, wisdom and loyalty.
The founders of AFI wish to thank you personally
for sharing your views and insights
to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back
and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs
and artillery batteries not included.
No rules, no taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are American Freedom Radio.