Oh, I got a love that keeps me waiting.
I'm a lonely boy.
Hey, could I come again please?
Yeah, the ladies want to fight.
You're listening to New Zealand's number one rated alternative talk radio.
It's the Vinnie Eastwood Show.
Just because we're being exterminated doesn't mean we can't make it fun.
Otherwise, what's the point of being killed?
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen, to yet another exciting episode of the Vinnie Eastwood Show,
broadcasting live on American Freedom Radio.
For your listening discomfort, it's the lighter side of genocide.
Just because we're being exterminated doesn't mean we can't make it fun.
Otherwise, what's the point of being killed?
Now, I have a guest turning up in about 15 to 20 minutes, and I'm going to talk about this whole concept.
I had this interview with Kevin Annett that I've just published up and spread all over Facebook today,
which has been responded with a legion of hate, as expected.
Number one, if you talk bad about any kind of religion,
see, even right now, a whole bunch of people who are deeply religious,
who believe in the Lord and Jesus and so on and so forth,
getting their backs arched up a bit.
Because any criticism of the concept of a faith-based religion is abhorrent, right?
I'm just thinking about this.
I've got so many friends who are deep believers in things that I don't really believe in,
and yet we get along so well because we're not dicks to each other.
I mean, maybe that's the real difference, isn't it?
The difference between somebody who's religious and somebody who's a zealot.
I mean, hell, let's go one step further.
What if it's a cult?
What if you've been part of a cult, right?
What's a cult?
You've got a hierarchical structure.
Organize religion.
You've got a preordained doctrine that everybody has to adhere to.
You've got a central leader kind of thing that runs the whole organization.
Organize religion.
All right, so there you go.
That's how you know you're part of a cult.
Sorry to lay that on you,
but religion isn't the only cult that people are a part of.
There are cults of all kinds of followings.
Fan club cults, cults of personality.
There's TV show cults, you know, like the Star Wars cult.
Just think about that for a minute.
How many films have what they call a cult following?
All right, what does a cultist do?
I mean, let's think about this.
What if you introduce yourself not as a Star Wars fan, but as a Star Wars cultist?
Hello, I'm a Star Wars cultist.
Really, bro?
It kind of seems really creepy all of a sudden.
You're just using a different word, one that's not patently acceptable.
Oh, I know, because I've kind of gotten over the fact that I don't have to lie to myself.
I don't have to lie to myself anymore.
I'm a cultist, Star Wars cultist.
I love it.
I can't get enough of it.
All right?
Give me a Jabba the Hutt and a Han Solo any day over a Pizza Hut and a handle of beer.
That's what I'm talking about.
Obsession, veneration for a person, object, some kind of thing.
Do you love it?
Do you viciously defend it?
Have you got butterflies in your stomach whenever people talk bad about it?
You don't know why.
You have no clue.
Why would somebody feel bad about it?
You know?
I've just been looking around lately and I've been having these conversations about religion
and that kind of thing.
It's those red meat issues.
I'm not doing it because I'm trying to get a rise out of people and I'm trying to suck a hit off them
or any crap like that.
I'm just genuinely interested in the topic right about now.
Christmas is coming up.
It is the season to believe in things.
Stuff from the Bible.
It's clearly marked in there in the Bible that on Jesus' birthday, the 25th of December,
that you must celebrate it by having an enormous tree draped with lights and expensive decorations
and stuff like that with a large meal around everybody and have a whole bunch of products
that are made and manufactured in China for everybody that hasn't earned them.
Just give it to them because it's the season for giving.
Leviticus fucking chapter 3 or some shit.
It's right in there, man.
The celebration at Christmas.
You see?
Nobody even follows their religions anymore.
That's what I'm starting to find out that's different as well.
If you're an idiot,
saying that you believe in a certain thing doesn't make you not an idiot.
That's the interesting thing that I've been thinking about lately.
A lot of people use their belief structures as an excuse to not listen and to not be reasonable.
This isn't all people that have a belief structure, mind you.
Just some.
Maybe because you need to have that.
I understand that specifically there is a reason why I believe in a higher power and a God and everything like that.
It's because I know that I can derive power from it.
How do I know that?
Because I've done it myself and hit an awakening?
No.
Statistics.
Have a look at the survival rates of people that are in POW camps.
Let's take Vietnam for instance.
Alright.
Let's have a look at all the atheists in the POW camps.
How many of them survived?
Very few.
Let's have a look at the really, really deep Christian believers in the Vietnam POW camps.
How many survived?
A hell of a lot of them.
See, that alone is a reason to believe in something.
Even if it's not there.
Even if you don't have a defined belief of what it is.
Just believe.
That belief alone is something that will give you hope.
Because when you're in despair, a situation where you have no hope whatsoever, your body starts to shut down.
It doesn't try to survive.
It can't see tomorrow.
So, if I bag religion, it's not because I'm bagging the belief and the power that it gives you.
I'm not blagging morality.
I'm not blagging history.
I'm not blagging anything.
Apart from those who misuse it.
Psychopaths in particular, who develop little cults.
Alright?
I had this joke this morning.
You know, I've never seen an atheist blow shit up or kill people in the name of atheism.
But that's probably because they don't shout,
FOR NOTHING!
Before blowing themselves up.
You know, you just imagine that.
That would be quite classic, wouldn't it?
You know?
Get a little cartoon or a sketch or something.
Atheist terrorist.
FOR NOTHING!
It's all dust in the wind.
You know?
He only gets like half a dozen virgins in the afterlife because he doesn't believe that you need 72.
I'm sorry.
Here's another thing.
I apologize if I'm making fun of anybody's belief structure.
I don't mean to do that.
I make fun of everything, just in general.
Belief structure is just part of the gig.
You know?
Let's say you're taking it seriously.
Let's say you're an atheist or a Christian or a Muslim or some denomination of cultists.
And you get offended by the very concept that I don't like false belief.
That I don't like blind belief.
That I don't like things that aren't fact-based.
I don't like things that don't have a reason to be there.
Now, that means that a lot of you shouldn't be offended.
Because there is a reason why you believe what you believe.
There are some facts that substantiate it.
Okay?
So I'm not talking about you.
Am I?
Talking about those people who are idiotic.
Zealotry.
The fucking zealotry.
My God.
All caps, comments all over YouTube.
YOU MUST CONVERT.
OTHERWISE YOUR INTERNAL SOUL WILL NEVER BE SAVED.
YOU MUST ACCEPT JESUS INTO YOUR HEART.
OH GOD, I JUST LOVE JESUS SO MUCH.
You don't even know anything about the guy.
I mean, he was a barefoot, unemployed, homeless, healing, travelling, hippie, Palestinian Jew.
I mean, you can't get any more messed up than that.
Alright?
So if anybody is like that, and you want to deify them or anything,
why the hell do you have a reason to be angry with anyone if that's your deity?
Yeah?
Am I wrong?
The only person you should be upset with is somebody who's evil.
Somebody who actually tries to corrupt the innocent.
Yeah?
Think about that for a second.
Who's your enemy?
I wonder this myself.
Who's my enemy?
And I'm starting to realise that my enemies are all psychopaths.
Every single person that I can count off of my head,
people that have screwed me over, who are really horrific,
who are sexual predators and things of this nature.
All of them that I've had any personal contact with,
who I've since developed feuds with, are freaking psychos.
Alright?
Some of them feign religion.
Some of them say that they're free men on the land.
Some of them say that they're great talk radio show hosts and patriots.
Dude.
Exposing psychopaths is actually kind of one of the most important things to do
in any institution.
Alright?
Again, have a look back at it.
Is your institution controlled by a psychopath?
Is it hierarchical with one guy at the top?
Psychopathic controlled.
Every time.
You know?
It's like impossible for someone who's not a complete psycho
to get to the top of a giant organization.
Right?
Unless they built it themselves
and are currently running it themselves
and there's nothing to really be at the top of
because it's just them.
Right?
See, there's a difference, isn't there?
Maybe it's just the desire to be surrounded
on all times by fawning sycophantic scum.
I don't believe that I need that.
You know?
People who go,
Oh, Vinnie, you're so great.
I love it.
I mean, you know, it's nice.
Thank you very much.
I'm not ungrateful.
Just as long as people are willing to pull me up on things.
You know?
If I'm wrong, show me the evidence.
Right?
Like I was talking about Kevin Annett before,
and a lot of the reason why people don't like him
is because in 2013,
he launched a common law court case
and arrest warrants of the Queen, the Pope,
and a number of other high-level Vatican
and government officials.
Now, that's a common law jurisdiction thing,
so that means you've got an arrest warrant
for the Queen.
It's an actual legit one.
You could grab the Queen and drag her away,
and you wouldn't technically be breaking the law.
But who's going to do that?
So what happened was,
nothing happened,
apart from a whole bunch of people in the Vatican
resigning all of a sudden for some reason.
And what people have done is they've construed that
as instead of him trying,
you know, just trying, giving it a go,
and it's just not working,
they construed that as,
he's a fraud.
Right?
I don't understand that.
Also, I've heard a lot of other accusations,
like he's a womanizer,
and he's traveling all around the world,
living the life of Riley and stuff.
I haven't seen anything to substantiate it.
It's like,
every time somebody throws out an accusation,
I don't care who it is
that's throwing out the accusation.
I don't trust accusations alone.
I need to see something to substantiate it.
I need to see,
because if you're going to pigeonhole somebody,
you know, just go,
all right,
I really don't like this guy anymore,
he's off my radar for good,
it's going to take a bit of evidence
before I determine whether or not
somebody's actually a fraudulent bad person.
And accusations simply aren't enough.
You know,
they're not enough.
And that's how you know when you're dealing with a shill,
or somebody who's just crazy,
or somebody who's just wrong,
is they keep playing the name-calling game,
they keep going and going and going,
saying all this stuff,
making all these accusations,
and did they provide a single screenshot?
No.
Did they provide any video evidence,
or anything that could actually be constituted
as some kind of case that they're making?
No?
Then they're talking out of their ass.
Right?
I'm sorry,
whoever you are,
that's like spreading BS about anybody.
This is a very generalized concept
that I'm talking about here now.
People just make stuff up all the time.
And you know what the funniest thing is?
So many people believe it every time.
You know,
don't check up on it.
Oh, that guy's a scumbag all of a sudden.
I knew it.
I knew it all along.
Really?
Somebody came out and criticized them openly?
Somebody who you think is trustworthy
and their words is enough?
You know?
Even people I know to be trustworthy,
I don't trust just their word alone.
Okay?
When it comes to throwing somebody under the bus.
All right?
I will throw people under the bus
if they're a scumbag.
You know?
If they're a parasite on human life,
if they betray people left, right, and center,
24, 7, 3, 6, 5,
for their entire existence,
if that's what they do to people.
Yeah, they're going to be thrown under the bus.
Sorry, bro.
This is your stop.
I'm like that.
As soon as I know,
like know,
that somebody's a psycho scumbag
who's a manipulator and a liar,
I know for a fact that I cannot trust them
and never want to associate with them ever again.
You know?
And what's interesting is that
those people that you block off like that
and say you parted on bad terms or anything like that
or they started getting real uppity at you,
they never come back to you and apologize
and say,
Oh, I'm sorry I acted like a dick, bro, man.
I was just really...
See, psychos can't apologize at all.
Now, our guest, Brian Kelly,
appears to be ready.
So I'll just get that contact info to the studio there.
But I really am quite incensed
when I see people get manipulated
by accusations and things
that are completely unfounded
and people believing them
without asking for any evidence.
That's all I'm asking for.
If you want to pigeonhole me or anybody,
just ask to see a little bit of evidence
before you believe whoever's opinion.
This person says that about that person
and I believe them because such and such
and blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Yeah, but that's all personality assumption, bro.
Have you got anything solid?
Something that isn't just shifting sand
of opinion and logical fallacy name calling?
You don't, do you?
Just shush then.
Okay?
Shh.
I don't care that you got five fake YouTube accounts.
I will block them all.
Okay?
They will get blocked.
Just like that.
And I will never have to hear from you again
after each and every one of your subsequent
fake accounts has been blocked.
Now, I'm a bit sick at the moment.
I'm holding down a gargantuan,
like an oil drum sized ball of flames.
That's quite a horrific thing to say
on talk radio, isn't it?
No response from the studio,
so I'm going to see if I can bring in
Brian Kelly here myself.
No, that's not working.
Okay.
Sorry about this, ladies and gentlemen.
I have to produce on here,
and I'm feeling sick and tired,
and I need a holiday, bro.
At the end of this week,
it's going to be holiday time.
But my very special guest joining me right now
is Brian Kelly from Brian Kelly's newsroom.
Welcome to the show.
Brother Benny Eastwood,
it is good to be here,
and it's been a long time, man.
How are you doing?
It has been a long time,
and I'm doing sickly,
but I'm about to go on holiday
after a few more shows to round out the week
before Thanksgiving,
and I'm looking forward to recuperating from...
I should have just said,
I'm good.
That would have been the shorter version,
but I'm with you.
I like details,
so it's good to hear that you're doing all right.
Oh, damn, that was funny.
Oh, God.
That cracked me up.
I do.
So anyway,
what have you been up to, Brian?
Oh, man, I'm good.
What's been waiting in the wings?
I don't follow the news at all.
Do you follow the news at all?
No, I went through a phase
when I was doing my blog.
If you've gone to my blog recently,
you'll notice I haven't made a blog post
in probably about six months,
and that's as a result
of not following the news really at all.
So I've transitioned
to doing more boots-on-the-ground kind of projects,
which I'm here in Bali doing now,
but every once in a while,
something will come my way.
For example,
some of the Syria stuff
has illuminated lately
because I've got a friend over there
that's on the ground in Syria right now,
and obviously,
if something pops up
that's as important to share
as what's happening in that country,
then I pay attention.
But for the most part,
no, man, I'm not listening to the radio shows.
No offense to you.
I know you've got an awesome show.
I'm not reading blogs,
and I'm staying out of newsrooms and chats
because I feel like
if I need to know it,
somebody will shoot me a link,
and then I'll dig a little.
Brian, if I may,
you just described
my exact protocol for life.
I'm out of the game a bit,
but I'm very much in the game
in another level.
Well, you just described
my exact protocol for life.
Yeah, man.
It's a good blueprint.
It works.
I mean, dude, dude, dude,
dig this.
I figured it out,
and there's a reason why we do it.
Okay, number one,
news doesn't fucking matter.
Once you come to that realization
that it actually doesn't fucking matter
staying up to date
with shit that's happening
10,000 miles away
that doesn't actually involve you
in any way, shape, or form.
You know?
That's the honest way to put it,
for sure.
Like, oh, I fucking figured it out.
Well, you know, man,
I mean,
when I first went down the rabbit hole,
it was like I couldn't get enough news.
It was like I needed to know
what the fuck was going on
because my entire world view
was challenged in so many ways,
and then I think I got to the point
where I was in paralysis,
news paralysis,
and the only way
to let go of those symptoms
was to just back away
from the whole thing,
and I gotta tell you,
it's working
in a lot of ways.
So you're doing exactly
what I recommend my listeners do,
is turn off the Vinny Eastwood show
and start going and doing your own thing,
your own activism or whatever.
In fact, you've got to really
turn off everything.
It's like in life,
energy gets given
to what you put your attention to.
Now, if you're putting your attention
to someone else
as opposed to yourself
and your family,
your world,
and your contribution to it,
I think you've missed
a priority or two.
You know, I know a lot of people
that spend 18 hours a day
staring at their monitor screen.
I was one of them
for a long time,
and on one hand,
you have information
being empowering,
because I believe
when we empower ourselves
with what's going on,
all it simply does
is it allows us
for freedom
of a much wider scope
of options
of how to conduct ourselves
and what's available
within the limitless space
of possibility at all times,
but you get to that point
where all of a sudden
that becomes overload,
and it's just not,
it doesn't serve a purpose
after a while,
and, you know,
shutting the computer
and actually going
and, you know,
doing something,
you know,
seems to be the only
natural progression
out of that mode
of constant, you know,
overload of information.
You just get to the point
where it's like,
fuck, man,
enough is enough
sooner or later.
So, yeah, it's fun
to be actually
creating something.
You know,
I've got some cool stuff
going on,
and every once in a while
I'll pop in
and pop out
as needed,
but it's important
that people like you
keep doing the work
and putting out information
because there are
lots of people
around the world
that are still new
to a lot of what's
really going on
and need that shake
in order to be able
to snap out
of the mind control,
cultural,
social conditioning
matrix that they're in,
and for that purpose,
to that end,
it is highly valuable.
Well, the whole concept
of good management
is to make yourself
redundant,
all right?
So if the concept
of the show
is to wake people up,
no,
it's not to wake people up,
okay?
The people who are
listening to the show
probably have already
quote, unquote,
woken up.
The idea of listening
to the show
is you'll listen to it
enough that you'll want
to get out of bed
and you'll want to go
to work against
the new world order.
That's what I'm talking about.
That's real productivity.
I mean,
there's some people
who literally cannot
do that, though.
They're still,
they're trapped,
okay?
It's like you can
work your life
and you find your place
in your workforce
and after a while,
you realize that you
haven't played,
you found your place
in the world
and you're trapped
where you are.
You're trapped in your
house that has a mortgage.
job that has set hours.
You're trapped
in a mindset.
in your family's
environment.
You're trapped
in perhaps a
that isn't conducive
to truthing
and activism,
et cetera.
Maybe everybody
thinks you're nuts
in your house.
Maybe everybody tells you
you ought to calm down.
You ought to just,
you know,
do your job
and shut up
and drink the Kool-Aid
like the rest of us.
You know,
before,
when I was doing blogging
and doing radio shows
two times a week,
that was,
what you just shared,
was my main theme
and message.
If I were to say
that I had to,
on an ongoing basis,
which is that
the fastest way
to change the world
is for people to
follow their passion,
to break free
of that system
that keeps people
slave-laboring
and doing some
nine-to-five job
that they couldn't
fucking stand
and throwing themselves
into the deep end
and realizing that
they are capable
to break free
from that system.
I mean,
I quit my job
in February of 2013.
I had $8,000
to my name
and I had $8,000
and I had no fucking idea.
Excuse my language.
I can swear here, right?
Yeah, you fucking can.
I had no fucking idea
how I was going to survive,
but something told me
this isn't it.
It's not working.
There's no joy.
There's no passion.
There's no creativity.
I fucking hate it.
So,
it's worth it to me
to throw myself
into the wind
and just see what happens.
And the fact of the matter was
is that
that was the biggest,
crucial turning point
that led to,
I haven't punched
a time card since
and here we are
in November of 2015
and guess what?
I haven't died of starvation.
I haven't spent any days
in the street
without a roof over my head
and the universe
has paved
very creative
and very unpredictable ways
for me to be able
to navigate the terrain
without having to worry
about how to survive.
And I think that
at the crux
of people staying
within those,
that system,
that controlling,
kind of mind controlling system
is that
I don't know how
I'm going to survive
if I step outside
of this sense of security,
this sense of being
able to ensure
that I keep food
on the table
and the roof over my head
and that,
breaking free
from that illusion
of self limitation
is the key
to be able to transcend
that process
on every level
and it works.
I know a lot of people
that have done it also
and it's scary as shit
but for some,
somehow,
everybody figures out
a way to make it work
because we all have
some sort
of higher calling
where not,
didn't come into this world
to sit in a fucking cubicle,
to die under fucking lamps
that are,
are frying our brains
and to punch fucking numbers
into a fucking computer
all day.
Now that's an extreme example
but I know people
that fucking do that
and it's not,
it's not the way to live
and the faster people
unplug from that,
that harvesting type scenario,
the less energy,
the gas all of a sudden
in the tank of these
global commercial based
system that we live in
worldwide,
that just all of a sudden
comes crashing down,
collapsing down
so the faster
they don't want free thinkers,
they don't want people
that are following their heart
and following their passion
because that means
less cogs in the wheel
of the system
that keeps people in control
so it is a vicious cycle,
vicious system
but highly empowering
to break free from
and sometimes it takes
those that are still
stuck there to hear
stories like mine
to realize that it is
very much possible
and can be an exciting
and scary as shit process.
Well yeah,
and again,
this seems to be
a recurring theme
on the show already.
Everything you've said
basically happened
to me as well.
You know,
like for example,
you had 8 grand
and you quit your job
in 2013.
I had $11,900
worth of shopping vouchers
and 5 grand cash
in 2007
when I quit my job
but same thing,
I've always had
a roof over my head,
a meal in my belly,
I've always had
just enough money
to pay the bills
whenever I need them
and it's kind of like
if you're sitting there
and you're sitting
and you've got
20 different screens
in front of you,
you don't know
what any of them
are saying
because they're all
talking at once.
When you turn
all of them off
but one
because you know
that you can't focus,
you can't do anything
but by distract
and block out
everything that
doesn't matter
and you don't do it
because you necessarily
want to,
you do it
because you
there's something
that tells you
that you have to do it,
you don't have a choice
because you're going
to drive yourself insane
or kill yourself
or kill somebody else,
probably the boss
and it's not going
to work out very well
for everybody.
Yeah,
nobody wins
in that scenario.
So yeah,
I don't advocate
killing your boss,
however,
there's been a few
that I've wanted to
but yeah,
the sooner
your extra cash
all of a sudden
the world opens up,
you know,
synchronicity becomes
much more prevalent,
meeting the right people
and being in the right
situations and scenarios
at the right time
that seems very divinely
in some level
inspired,
it becomes,
it's just a much more
pleasant way of living
on every level
and that doesn't mean
it's not hard.
I mean,
there's been times
where I had no clue
and I know that you
know,
where that next money
was going to come from
to ensure that rent
was paid or whatever
that you were able
to get groceries
but somehow
at the 11 and a half hour
something pops up
and then all of a sudden
you know
and the more that time
that happens,
I think the more faith
you have in that process
that we're being taken care of
and then all of a sudden
you realize,
okay,
next time this happens
I promise myself
I'm not going to stress out about it
and then sure enough you do
but the more consistency
you have
and the more comfortable
you get with the process
of just allowing the universe
to unfold before you,
the more you realize
that there's a whole lot
more going on
than what we can see,
taste,
smell,
hear,
touch.
Am I missing
any other senses?
Above an extra sensory perception
but when you're working
you've got a schedule
you know
and you tell yourself
what the plan for the day is
every freaking day
but when you work for yourself
the plan tells you
what to do.
It's like it actually comes out of the
it just comes out of the ether
kind of thing
just magically appears
like literally.
There was this one time
I got up in the morning
and it was bill day
and I was like,
okay,
I got the water bill,
the internet bill
and the rent.
That's 500 bucks.
I don't have 500 bucks.
So I go to my PayPal
and there's 500 bucks in there.
You know,
boom!
That's the exact scenario
I'm talking about.
You know,
some magical donation
that came from somewhere
or some,
you know,
some tax return check
that you got lost in the mail
three years before.
I mean,
you really never know
where it's going to come from
but it just somehow seems to
and I think that
you know,
it is.
It's this false sense of security
that,
you know,
Matrix-style-esque jobs
we feel provide for us
that keeps us in those positions.
I mean,
I've talked to people,
you know,
it's the same
no matter,
all the way up this
perceived level of control
that dictates the way
that the world works,
you know,
and all the way up
in the upper echelons
of the elite
and the Illuminati.
I've heard the stories.
First-hand accounts
that they don't know
what they would do
if they exited ranks
and went another way
because their
livelihood
requires them to stay
within the system
that they have
around themselves.
It's not easy
at any level.
But that doesn't,
just because something isn't easy
doesn't mean it's not possible.
You know,
but it does,
you know,
it takes a leap of faith.
Shit,
if we can't do leaps of faith,
man,
then we've got
a long rocky road
ahead of us.
I feel like we're at
perhaps this turning point
in where we are
in the process
of human evolution
that it doesn't really matter,
you know,
this might be a very optimistic way
of looking at it,
but it doesn't really matter
what anybody does
because this whole thing
is unfolding
in this perfect way
and so you can either
resist what's happening
or you can let go
of the side of the river
and just go slow
and things have a tendency
of just getting
a whole hell of a lot easier.
So,
that's my little bit on that
and,
you know,
for anybody that's out there
that's sitting on the fence
and trying to figure out
what the fuck to do
and how the hell to do it,
don't worry about how to do it,
just do it,
you know?
That's the,
forgetting,
letting go of the how
and trying to put together a plan,
I mean,
let all that shit go
because how,
if I were to try to make a mind map
of how I was going to do it
back in February 2013,
how I'm doing it
and how I thought I was going to do it now,
back then,
have,
look,
absolutely nothing like each other
whatsoever
and because it is
it goes to the point
that you made
that the universe
somehow has it all under control.
So,
you either have faith
in that process
or you don't,
you know?
And I'm not here
to try to tell anybody
how to live their lives
but,
you know,
my story,
your story,
some of these other stories
are great examples
that,
really,
the only thing to fear
is,
fear itself,
for lack of a better
non-creative way
of saying it.
Yeah.
Well,
everybody in life
is worried about money.
You know,
I'm worried about money,
you're worried about money,
even people that got jobs
have to worry about money
but also,
the problem is
if you have a job
you also have to worry
about the fact
that you're starting
to hate yourself,
you know?
And,
in life,
some people,
you know,
choose to work,
some people choose
to work for themselves
and some people
just sit on the fence,
you know?
Yeah.
And,
I'm just trying to burn
the fence down.
It's time to,
yeah,
it's time to get a bulldozer
and just knock this
damn fence over.
We'll do it
fucking Gaza style, bro.
I want to burn it,
really,
I want to burn it
and I want to do it
in like a really
sacrificial kind of way
that's almost dark,
you know?
I don't know if that
makes me weird or crazy.
All I want to do
is dance around
the burning fence
after everybody
suddenly had to choose
what they do
with their life
and not allow other people
to fucking tell them
what they have to do
with their life,
you know?
And,
it'll be like
dancing around it
naked,
jiggling in the air
and like chicken
smeared in goat's blood.
It'll be fucking fantastic.
We're going to mutilate it
like with a spoon.
Just really kind of
have fun with it, man.
That's what I would
vote for.
Yeah,
it'll be like a,
it'll be like the
Doors concerts
or something.
I'm thinking
pay-per-view,
we make loads of money
and we send the money
from Africa
to feed starving children.
I mean,
it's really,
at the end of the day,
it's for a good cause.
No, no, no, no.
I've got a better idea
of what to do
with the money.
You hire African mercenaries
to kill all the people
that are giving
bad drugs
and stuff like that
to all the Africans
that's causing AIDS.
If you have that petition,
I would love
to sign that
on behalf of myself
and all of humanity.
That reminds me,
I remember there was
an ex-CIA assassin,
Chip Tatum,
and he's come out
about some of
the operations
that he did
back in the day
working for this
hit squad
under the US government
sort of privatised.
And he says
that he has
a hit list
that he wants
a list of
really freaking
bad people
that just need
to be taken out
because they won't
go any other way.
And he was
asking for donations
and started
a Kickstarter plan.
Now that
taking
too much
crowdfunding
to a whole other level,
man, I...
Put it on Pledge Me, bro!
You know,
I guarantee you
that fund
did not end up
an empty bucket.
Somebody put some money
into that cause,
I know it.
Only got $20
in my pocket.
You know,
$20 in a
third world country
can go a very long way,
man.
That's at least
one takeout.
You know,
you can find somebody
desperate enough
to take out one guy
on $20.
That's at least
one clip of 9mm.
Yeah,
throw in a few
corn dogs,
you're good to go, man.
You're talking
making serious,
serious,
very creative business.
I like the way
your mind thinks, man.
I appreciate that about you.
I like it too.
Now,
everybody talks
about this as well,
and I don't like
the idea of violence
or killing
or anything.
You know,
I'm just joking about,
you know,
sending mercenaries
over there
to just kill them
and torture them
and ruthlessly butcher
their families
and things like that
and redistribute
the wealth, OK?
It's just a joke, bro, OK?
And in fact,
that's another thing.
I figured out
that my show,
if I say anything
that's controversial
or really horrific
or something like that
and people want to, like,
charge me with inciting
terrorism or whatever,
I've got this great
little caveat
that I can just
bust out.
It was a joke!
Yeah, man.
It's about the sound bite.
You're good to go.
That's written in ink.
It's on the internet.
It never goes away.
And, you know,
that's your out.
It's called
The Lack of a Smoking Gun.
And, um,
it works.
You know?
Maybe I could have that
as something
on the opening of the show
like pre-recorded
or something.
The Vinny Eastwood Show.
If anything on this show
offends you
or makes you want
to kill Vinny,
just remember,
it was a joke!
And just remember,
if that doesn't work,
the way to always
get out of everything,
you see it in all the movies,
you just claim insanity.
And Vinny,
if you did that,
I would believe you
because, dude,
you're borderline insane
and that's what I like
about you, man.
Well,
a lot of people
call me insane
and I take it
as a compliment
because, uh,
in a world
this fucked up,
if somebody were to say
that I had a real handle
on things,
I'd feel insulted.
Sanity is
very overrated, man.
insanity is
the new cool
and, uh,
it really means, um,
really letting things go
and just saying
fuck it.
And I know
a lot of people
that are doing that
very well
and, um,
it is the way to go.
I mean,
on my business card,
my tagline is just
say fuck it
and it works.
It's not really,
but I think
I might make that
known.
At least part of
my email signature.
Fuckit.com,
um,
you know,
is it an animal,
mineral,
or vegetable?
Can I eat it?
Can I,
can I,
can I live in it?
Can I fuck it?
Dude,
you just gotta,
you gotta put everything
in like,
can I fuck it filter?
And that makes
everything really fun,
you know?
wow,
I'm thinking of
a great business idea.
Yeah,
yeah,
fuck it glasses.
You know?
There'll be,
there'll like be a,
a, um,
an app that you can
put into Google glasses
that will just,
um,
you know,
it'll highlight
in green
the things that
you can fuck.
You know?
Like,
Jacuzzi air filter system
or something like that
lights up in green
and you're like,
really?
I can fuck that?
Absolutely.
You know,
it's just
triple,
triple-hybrided
cock-fucking-massager
right there,
Never have I ever
thought that I could,
you know,
I could fuck this,
whatever the,
what you want to call it,
this widget.
Um,
you know,
it really just opens up
a whole bunch of possibilities.
The can I fuck it widget
by briankelly.com.
Oh my,
my mother,
my mother's gonna be so proud.
I can't wait to send her
the link to this video.
You make your mama bosom
swell with pride.
So what else is going on
with you, man?
Well,
you know,
I've just been thinking
about the Christmas season
and all the shops
are starting to put up
their Christmas decorations
and apparently they started
doing it a month ago
like on television,
like,
so I've heard,
you know,
watch fucking television,
but yeah,
apparently there's been
Christmas advertisements
going throughout the whole
month of November
and October
and it's just like
Christmas season starts
earlier every year
because everybody
just goes,
Hey,
you know what makes
people want to part
with their cash?
Guilt tripping them
about not buying
their loved ones
a present.
Boom!
Cha-ching!
It's giving me like,
like,
where's the Christmas
decorations?
They've got probably
margins for manufacture.
Oh my God, man.
Black Friday.
Yeah.
I haven't,
I don't know.
I don't,
I'm not sure how
any of that stuff
we're advertising.
I mean,
all that stuff
is just so,
so far outside
of my reality anymore
that I find it hard
to believe that anybody
is still going out
and dropping thousands
of dollars
leading up to Christmas.
I don't know.
It's just a concept
that doesn't make sense
to me anymore.
I mean,
don't get me wrong.
I go home,
I celebrate Christmas,
I buy my family
a few,
a few cool things.
Um,
but the,
it's funny because
somebody asked me
the other day,
here in Bali,
because it's where
I'm living now.
Oh,
you're going over there?
you're Christian?
They just assume
that everybody
that celebrates Christmas
is Christian.
I'm like,
no,
even atheists,
I think,
in the United States
celebrate Christmas
and that's how
well ingrained
the Christmas
condition shopping
um,
program
is
within people that
they don't even have to
believe in
what Christmas
is supposed to represent.
They still go out
and buy shitloads
of stuff
that they don't need
for Christmas.
See,
me,
I celebrate Ramadan
um,
by drinking and smoking more
because the Muslims can't.
Ha,
ha,
Because I'm a sensitive and empathetic person,
I actually give a fuck when they tell me
about this kind of shit.
So I take on some of their baggage
in order to lighten the load for them.
Lighten the load, I do.
But however, I get stuck with the baggage.
And after a period of time,
I got so much other people's baggage on me
that I literally start to have meltdowns.
Like on a daily basis kind of thing.
I get really angry for no reason.
I start yelling and screaming at the computer.
In fact, I yell and scream at the computer
quite a lot.
Fucking piece of shit.
LAUGHS
You and me both, bro.
You and me both, man.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's when we live in a world that is fueled
by massive amounts of just sickness
on so many levels.
I mean, it's so, it's, you get,
it's very easy to fall within that viewpoint
of holy shit, the world is going to hell
in a handbasket and everything is just fucked
and it doesn't matter what we're going to do.
I mean, I know a lot of those people
that they think that humanity is heading
toward its final point,
where we're not going to be around much longer.
And, you know, shit is fucked.
This shit is really fucked up on a lot of levels.
I mean, I know you've seen the thick of it
with some of the people that you brought
on your show over the years.
Oh, we seem to have lost Brian.
Yeah, he's gone.
Bugger.
All right, that's very unfortunate.
Anyway, yeah, well, something you were saying
before was kind of interesting to me.
Like when you get up on Monday morning,
you know, you're not stressed
because you don't have any schedule to keep
or anything like that.
And that's not too similar to me.
I mean, like I've got a schedule to keep,
for example, on Mondays I do nothing.
All right, you know, I hated Mondays for so long
that I officially, you know, decided
that I'd do four days a week of talk radio
so I wouldn't have to work on Mondays.
But in the United States sense of the word,
it means I don't have to work on Saturdays
because we're a day ahead of you on this timeline.
But something with Brian was talking to me
about time management, right?
And I remember I interviewed this guy
who's like expert on, what would you call them?
Entrepreneurs.
And he says that they've got a system
called organic time.
All right, now really think about this.
If you didn't have a watch,
you didn't have a clock or anything like that
and you're just sitting there,
you're working away on something
for a period of time and you go,
I really don't feel like doing this anymore.
I'm gonna take a break from it
and you go off and you do something else.
Organic time, you just operate by your feelings.
You do what you feel you wanna
and you take breaks when you need to.
It's not like having a set schedule.
You gotta be at work by 8 a.m.
I'm usually up and working by 8 a.m. anyway.
But that's by choice.
It's not because I've got a schedule.
Just get up and start working.
There's nothing else to do around here.
What am I gonna do?
Sit on my deck chair, watch the sunrise?
That's boring as hell.
I'll just stick a camera there
and then use it as a slow creeping shot in the video later.
Better idea.
But yeah, you'd be surprised
how much more productive you can be
when you're not on somebody else's time card.
When you make your own time.
And you'll find this as well,
is that you can make time.
You can actually manufacture time
out of thin air just like that.
Quite interesting.
It might sound a bit confusing at first,
but here's how...
The person you are trying to reach
is not accepting calls at this time.
Can we hang up now?
Please try your call again later.
Yeah, there we go.
Shoot, what did I do?
Totally missed my place.
Man, that was distracting.
Haven't had any coffee for the entire hour as well.
Brain's starting to freeze up.
Yeah, I'm saying the word uh and um
too much.
When you have coffee,
ladies and gentlemen,
very important for talk radio show hosts.
Gives you increase in cognitive function
and provided it's not GMO
or sprayed with nasty chemicals and stuff,
it can actually not be that bad for you.
I heard that people who drink a bit of coffee
live longer.
And I can understand that.
Because if I didn't have coffee,
I wouldn't want to live that long.
That cracked me up.
I do, I do.
But anyway, yeah.
You know, I don't want to sound too pushy here,
but quit your job.
Okay.
Because it's dragging you down,
you know,
unless, of course,
you actually have one of those very rare instances
where you're working with cool people,
you're doing cool stuff,
and it's really fulfilling.
You know, it actually makes you happy
and you get home at the end of the day
and you feel great.
And you can actually raise your kids.
You got more than enough money to get by
and you contribute to society as well.
And in your spare time,
you're not just working and relaxing.
You're actually doing something else on your own time.
Dude, that's like one of the perfect things.
I actually wish I could do that.
You know, it'd be cool to have a nice, fun,
cool job with a whole bunch of mates
and get paid a hell of a lot
to do some really awesome stuff
that's very interesting and fulfilling.
As well as at the end of the day,
be able to go home and do a whole bunch of activism.
But unfortunately, there's not enough time.
So I made it, you know.
Just go, okay, let's have a look at the things in my life
that are soaking up my time
and let's eliminate them one by one
in order to free up time for the things that I want to do.
Just that simple.
Now, American Freedom Radio is having a marathon
at the end of this week, I believe on Saturday.
So make sure to check that one out.
There's Jordan Maxwell, Carol Rosin, Dean Clifford,
and some dude from Iraq,
something Ford or whatever about WMDs.
It's on Sunday, sorry, Sunday.
So yeah, tune into that, ladies and gentlemen,
and throw a few bucks American Freedom Radio's way.
And while you're at it,
throw me something for Christmas as well.
You know, because what am I going to do?
You know, big, big the universe for presents.
We'll see you after the break, ladies and gentlemen.
Don't you go anywhere.
Welcome to the world's meeting place.
American.
Practically narcotic.
Freedom.
Oh, yes.
I like very much radio.
You're an American institution.
American Freedom Radio.
Did you know there are 3 million edible food plants on Earth
and none have the nutritional value of the hemp plant?
HempUSA.org offers you hemp protein powder.
It does not contain chemicals or THC,
is non-GMO, and is 100% gluten-free.
Hemp protein powder burns fat, builds muscle,
contains 53% protein,
and feeds the body the nutrients it needs.
Call 888-910-4367
and see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org.
HempUSA.org introduces three brand new detox formulations
of micro plant powders.
Brain Fuel for depression, bipolar disorders, and stress.
Total Care.
Anti-cancer agent that cleans the liver and organs
and increases memory.
Rejuvenate.
Invigorates and heals the body, mind, and spirit.
These products are your alternative to pharmaceuticals.
Call 888-910-4367 and like us on Facebook.
We ship worldwide.
Only at HempUSA.org.
American Freedom Radio is back.
We're trying to become commercial free
apart from a few honorable advertisers
that we would give ad space to even if they couldn't pay us.
In this quest to deliver quality radio
with very few annoying ads,
we are now asking the listeners like you
to open up and become partners
with American Freedom Radio.
We all know the economy is controlled
and a new system called the peer-to-peer economy
is now within our grasp.
That means if you'd like this network
with its incredible hosts and credible information
to be nothing but the content you want to hear,
then you must realize that you cannot be a part of it
if you're just sitting on the sidelines watching.
Go to AmericanFreedomRadio.com
and pledge your support today.
Donate according to your means.
Some can only afford $1 a month
while others can afford $100 a month.
Regardless of the size of your contribution,
it all adds up to keeping the network owners
and the radio hosts housed and fed
at the end of every month.
Thank you.
We are living in a new era.
Partnerships are more important than profit
and gratitude is more respected than greed.
As the millennial generation evolves the corporate landscape,
our company aims to maximize
the achievements of CBD application
and push the limits of what's possible by 2020.
Our core product matrix
and careful cannabidiol purification process
are uniquely designed to be privately made
in different regions of the world
and is geared to assist the efforts of different nations
to change the landscape,
various pain-related healthcare costs,
epilepsy and autism,
rising mental disorders,
and even soldier suicides.
Crystal Pure CBD is made with the industry's finest,
99.9% pure CBD crystals.
No paste, no filler.
Our solution is a permanent answer
and it saves you over one third in cost.
Crystal Pure CBD.
Come join us.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com,
the network who perseveres in delivering
intelligent debate, constructive dialogue
with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun,
honest and pure integrity behind it
provides an example to follow.
Friendships to flourish with the moral altruism
that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice and show remarkable discipline
in their duty to deliver quality radio
in service to the community
with strength, wisdom and loyalty.
The founders of AFI wish to thank you personally
for sharing your views and insights
to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back
and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs
and artillery batteries not included.
Welcome back to our number two
of the Vinnie Eastwood Show.
Broadcasting via pirate radio signal
from the private prisons run by General Zod.
Located in the freshly terraformed
Krypton colony of Auckland, New Zealand.
Humanity's last and best hope
in the fight against taking ourselves too seriously.
Here's your host, Vinnie Eastwood.
Welcome back to our number two
of the fastest two hours in talk radio.
It's the Vinnie Eastwood Show
broadcasting live on American Freedom Radio.
Now, if the studio is willing,
I'd really like to open the call lines up
and allow the listeners to ring in.
I'll let you know when those lines are open.
The number is 218-339-8525.
That's 218-339-8525.
If you're in New Zealand like me,
you need to call like a plus one
or a plus zero or something.
It's definitely a plus one on top of that puppy
for that international calling.
And sometimes it doesn't actually even cost
that much to call the states.
I used to sell like toll calls for a living
and stuff like that, you know.
It should be remarkably cheap.
Sometimes it can even be cheaper
than calling other places in New Zealand,
depending on the time of the day.
But yeah, anyway,
I want to also kind of thank Brian Kelly
for coming on and being a good dude.
However, moving on,
we were talking in the first hour
about religion.
And the caller lines are now open.
So if you'd like to call in
and express your thoughts on that
or anything else,
you want to ask me anything.
Don't feel uncomfortable.
Seriously, I'm Vinnie.
I'm comfortable with everything.
You can just come straight on up
and ask me anything you want.
So long as it's not abusive
or defamatory or something within reason.
So the caller lines are now open.
The number is 218-339-8525.
That's 218-339-8525.
That's the number to ring in there.
Please call in now.
If you're listening, please call.
Because I've run out of ideas.
I'm coming to the end of my tether.
I'm freaking exhausted.
And in the meantime,
it's just going to be like
a one-man therapy session.
I'm just going to freaking unload on you.
In the last hour,
I talked about all the baggage
that was being draped on me
by all the people that I've got on
as guests and all the trolls
and everything that come out
after the videos
and just fucking with them all the time.
It's like, oh my God.
Sometimes it's just too much, bro.
Honestly.
And it's not just like
it's too much all of a sudden.
It creeps up on you.
And I think I...
I only really get about two weeks warning.
I can only handle about
a fortnight worth of shows
when I don't want to.
That's the only reason
why I'm here right now
is because of my obligation
to the network.
Network didn't ask me.
I can take any day off I want.
But I feel obliged to be here.
And the fact that I really
don't feel like it
is kind of inconsequential.
I mean, really,
there's a broader scheme at play here.
However, I'm not going to risk burnout over it,
which is why I'm going to be
going on holiday soon.
Holiday for me is doing nothing.
Other people who work when...
I mean, their job sucks
or whatever and life is hard,
et cetera, et cetera.
However, when you're an activist,
taking a holiday is simply not working.
I just have to stay at home,
maybe do some stuff around the house,
maybe catch up on some stuff.
It's not terribly exciting.
I would like to go away somewhere,
somewhere I haven't been.
And I found out that
because of my drug dealing conviction
when I was a teenager,
I have to disclose that to the US government
if I ever want to come there.
And in fact, I have to disclose it to everywhere.
Because although New Zealand has a law
called the Clean Slate Scheme,
which says after seven years,
all your records are kept secret
and nobody can even ask them for you.
Unfortunately, New Zealand legislation
doesn't apply in other countries.
That's the little caveat
that they've got on that.
And they don't advertise that widely
as they should, I think.
Clean Slate Scheme,
it only helps you
if you're in New Zealand,
which means you can't really leave the country.
Not with a conviction like mine.
I only had like fricking 13 grams on me.
That was it.
And I got 300 hours community service.
I was lucky I didn't go to jail
for up to eight years.
You know, they treat it more seriously
than manslaughter, bro.
They really do.
There was a dude up in front of me
who was like growing five plants
and sexual assault, resisting arrest.
And this is like his umpteenth time in court.
Gets 150 hours community service.
I go up pleading guilty.
13 grams of cannabis.
First time I've ever been in trouble
with a law at all.
And 300 hours community service.
Just like that.
It's unbelievable.
Almost as unbelievable as the guy
who was before the guy in front of me.
It was like some recovering heroin addict
who was in there, quite literally,
because he stole a jar of raspberry jam.
All right.
And BP took him to court.
You know, pay a lawyer to prosecute him
and everything.
And then the court ordered reparations
of like $4.16 to replace the jar of jam.
Oh, man.
Those are harsh times.
You know, I almost have a panic attack
when I start thinking about bank,
how hard it was
and how young I was, how naive.
My God, I was a very different creature back then.
It was just 10 years ago.
Bugger me.
The years do fly when you're exposed
in scumbaggery, I must say.
And I think I figured out the reason why
time seems to pass quicker
when you mostly focus on scumbaggery.
It's because there's so much of it
that you get lost in like this kind of k-hole.
The scumbaggery k-hole.
And just a heads up,
we've got a caller in there.
The Greek wants to join in via Skype.
So if you want to connect them up,
AFR, that'd be lovely.
Or Greek, if you want to message AFR
and get them to bring you in,
that will work as well.
And kind of maybe talk on religion for a bit.
Hmm, the Greek talking about religion.
Fuck me, that could be dangerous.
Man, I've really got to turn down
the gain on my mic somewhat, don't I?
It's like so loud and I'm like laughing all the time
and it's just like going crazy.
It's terrible, isn't it?
So sorry about that, ladies and gentlemen.
Is this better?
I hope it is.
Because if not, I'm screwed.
But yeah, I wanted to kind of relate
the reason why I make jokes about everything.
All right?
You want to know the real honest truth
why I make jokes about everything?
Because I'll go crazy if I don't.
Real crazy.
You know, it's as simple as I can explain it.
The terrible, terrible thing
about being a comedian
is that you're smart enough
to realize how bad things are.
And your only coping mechanism is to laugh at them.
You can't change them.
You can explain them to people
and help them see it for what it is.
Seeing something for what it is
is actually pretty powerful.
You know, I mean, here's another thing.
A lot of truthers who don't contribute
to the truth movement don't make videos
or do radio shows or do activism of any kind.
They're really hard on themselves
and they shouldn't be.
You know?
It's a big, big machine, this world.
And if you don't have the kind of, you know,
narcissistic flair like people like me have
to get on talk radio and just
riff it for hours on end just because you can,
don't feel bad about yourself
that you're not contributing in that way.
That's your own way to contribute somewhere.
You know, it might just be
raising your kids right, you know?
Maybe your kids will do something really big
in the future that will change the world.
Just raising your kids right is good enough.
So I told somebody at a party this one time.
Now, we've been joined by the Greek.
He's the only Greek I know.
Hey, I've heard that before.
Hey, and we don't,
and New Zealanders don't use the word mate.
We use the word.
No, it's Kiwi.
We use the word bro.
Oh, that's right, bro.
And like Hawaii, it's bra.
I forgot about that.
That's also in South Africa.
Yeah, mate, I'll just have to go down to the shop
to get some cigarettes bra.
Yeah, it's the bra.
So what has gotten into you?
Why do you want to discuss about religion?
Or what about religion?
What do you mean, right?
Yeah, let's go.
Maybe I'm maybe I'm masochistic, you know,
and I need a whole bunch of fucking crazy,
religious, zealot, crazy,
fucking stupid people coming at me
and attacking me for talking some sense.
All right.
Religion just means something you do regularly.
Like I do that religiously, right?
We do this or that.
Like I brush my teeth or tie my shoelaces.
And do talk radio, right?
Or something like that.
Religiously, it's just that's all it means.
And I think what people have turned in a second.
Wait a second.
Does that mean you can masturbate religiously?
Yeah.
If you're a master.
Or a priest.
Sorry, you were saying?
Have we lost you?
Just for a moment.
That wasn't very religious.
OK.
All right.
Well, I usually go around saying things
like there's not a religion on the planet
that does or knows anything
that's in the texts that they allegedly subscribe to.
And I'll challenge anyone to bring up anything in any religion.
And I will show you that what they're saying
will not be found in context
in any of the texts that they allegedly subscribe to.
Period.
That is a fact on this planet.
So I think we're lost our minds
because it's not really based on anything.
Neither is the money.
Neither is medicine.
Neither is anything.
So in that case.
Anything that has a major hierarchical structure
and one big central leader or central figure
that you're not allowed to question
or bring to court on child pedophile charges.
It's a cult.
Or pedophile.
A pedophile is someone who likes shoes.
But anyway.
No, no, actually.
Actually, there's also a pedophile
or somebody who really likes bicycles.
Right.
Or a velophile.
That would be anyway.
And there's also a PDF file,
but that's for a Word document.
Yeah, for those that are wordy.
But OK, you know, the secular historians,
which are self-professed,
self-professed atheists, typically professors,
they'll tell you this is the Christian era.
So it is really when you when people say Christianity,
you know, that is the predominant one.
And in the news lately, it's been the Islamic one.
So I don't know which way you want to go.
Well, I was also thinking the other day
about persecution.
You know, persecution of anybody for anything
is not really a good thing
if they're not harming anybody.
But the some Christians get persecuted
and they freaking deserve it.
You know, just like if you some.
What were those people who like hang out outside
the America's most hated family?
They hang outside the graves of veterans
holding big signs that said God hates fags,
you know, and they get what they got.
Which God?
Because the fags have their own God as well.
So you're going to have to work that one out.
But anyway, it's the fag God, you know,
and they have a they have a little
bathhouse on the top of Mount Olympus.
There you go.
Where the mountain goes on.
Yeah, yeah.
Those Greeks, they would do the guys
would all do each other
and then go home and beat their wives.
Yeah, those ancient Greeks.
Yeah.
But anyway, that was the festival,
I guess that's coming up that everyone
in the darkest day of the darkest part of the month.
You know, it's coming up here for everyone.
They got their own version of it.
But yeah, God is an oxymoron
because there's many.
It's kind of like saying ant or well, no.
You know how we use language in a certain way
that's accepted.
You know, we could say it's an army.
You know, we don't mean.
Well, it's just one person in the army.
We know when we say army, it's a multitude.
And people have forgotten that when they say God,
it's a multitude of gods.
And that's in all of the ancient texts.
And of course, who cares about
what the ancient texts say?
Because those people were ignorant and savage.
Of course, you know,
you know, we don't have to read any of that stuff.
We have computers now.
We don't know anything.
Well, we have we have into.
I mean, we have religion now.
We don't need to read what these things
are supposedly based on.
But yeah, that's that's one of the interesting parts.
It's part of the I call cosmic censorship.
The planet has been cosmically censored by forces.
I'm not talking about the archons and the reptilians
and all the crap you hear on the Internet going on,
because if you listen to all that
and see what it's based on,
it's based on nothing again.
But there if you look at what's been memorialized
for thousands of years,
there is a cosmic censorship put in,
put on mankind to stuff up his ears and his eyes
so he can't perceive.
Isn't that interesting?
Well, I don't know.
Sounds like the mainstream media's job to me.
Along with other things.
Yeah.
And the cons, let's go back to the persecution.
You know, all that persecution,
a lot of those people that do the persecuting
just want to persecute for any damn reason.
It's just the way they are.
I was also thinking the other day,
and this is actually the thought that I originally had,
but I forgot to express it,
is that my heart actually goes out to people
who are persecuted for their beliefs.
You know, I really do feel that probably
some of the widest persecuted groups at the moment
are Muslims and Christians.
And that's interesting
because they're persecuting each other.
But hold on.
If all you're going on is belief,
maybe you should be persecuted
because you're really stupid.
Sorry.
You need to actually pursue something that's substantive.
What has happened is that people have,
what's been put on them,
because it's easy.
It's kind of like, you know,
eating out of a can or microwaving food.
Who wants to cook an hour and a half dinner anymore, right?
So what they do is they've convinced everyone,
oh, you have a right to believe in what you want to,
and that's it.
As long as you show up to work tomorrow,
and pay your taxes,
and go to war when we tell you to.
Well, you say that maybe they should reprioritize
and try to live a life of substance.
But do you think that having a belief
instead of knowing what it is,
do you think that that in and of itself
can deprive somebody of having a life of substance?
Oh, absolutely.
Because your life of substance is governed by law,
meaning not traffic law or tax law or whatever,
or cannabis laws,
but law is what you eat, what you wear,
how you keep time, how you raise a family,
how you plant your crops,
how you deal with your neighbor,
how you get into a contract.
You see what I mean?
Law is like, what is your,
what they call ethics and morality,
and also your functional,
how you function in the world, right?
That comes from your deity, from your God.
Well, I pray to my God all the time.
No, no, it's nothing to do with prayer.
That's, now prayer is when you,
it's like in the military,
you have the communications officer, right?
That's the guy who communicates.
That's communication.
That's a technology as well.
Prayer is a, you know, it's interesting.
You ever seen the Christian meme?
They show you putting your hands closed, right?
You know, when they pray.
That comes from Hinduism.
Biblically, it's your hands are spread out
and palms faced.
Palms faced to something else.
Greg, you're cutting out a little bit today there, bro.
You're still back on this?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Palms faced at what?
Hands spread out, palms faced up.
That's the method of communication
for the biblical deity.
Now, the Christian deity is,
here's the thing.
The Christian deity is not biblical, zero percent.
I've been looking at this for over a decade.
And I haven't found anything
that Christians do that's in the Bible.
Now, hold on a second.
That might sound very general and irrational.
But if I try to maintain some rationality,
if they did one out of a thousand
or 0.01% of what they did was biblical,
I'd have to grant them that, right?
To be rational.
But I haven't found anything
that Christians believe in, say, or do
that's in the biblical text.
Now, that's fascinating to me
how far off and opposite the mark they are.
Maybe it's because the biblical text
was, you know, cobbled together
a couple of hundred years ago
in the New Testament,
and it doesn't actually apply to today,
you know, with all our technologies
and our cultural changes and stuff like that.
Believing the earth is round and shit.
Well, there's actually several places
in the Bible that tell you the earth is round.
So, well, when I say and shit,
I also mean like just a broad brush caveat
of a whole bunch of superstitions
that we're sort of left go of,
even if they didn't believe
in the flat earth at the time,
as they didn't even believe
that there was a flat earth
in the time of the Greeks.
You will never find a flat earth
memorialized in any literature in history.
Yeah, exactly.
That is because people don't read
and they make stuff up.
What is it called?
Telephone or something?
When someone tells a story to someone
and when it's five times removed,
it's changed.
No, that's all that Chinese whispers
in high school.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's right.
Chinese whispers.
Yeah, it's better than Chinese handcuffs.
But here's the interesting part
about any deific communication.
There's something called paganism,
you know, which is basically
the people were peasants
and the feudal lord
wanted them to do their job.
And when it was discovered
that understanding what the gods
wanted to communicate
required a lot of study,
you just made up a couple of simple stories
so they could go back to work.
That's all your religions
on the world right now,
whether it's Hinduism, Buddhism, Judaism,
Christianity, Islam.
They're all like that.
They're just little tales.
None of them have anything to do
with what's in the text.
Now, what I mean by the paganism part,
you know, what do they do in New Zealand?
When you go to court,
they have you swear on a Bible,
put your hand on the Bible,
say the truth, all truth.
All right.
In New Zealand,
they just turn off the recording devices
so you can't prosecute
the judge for being corrupt.
Oh, OK.
Well, they've turned it
into a rabbit's foot, right?
Like the Bible is some holy relic.
It's just a communication.
I have a whole bunch of them here.
I use them as doorstops.
They're just communications.
What if you have it on a thumb drive?
Can you swear on the thumb drive?
You see what's going on here?
It's a little rabbit's foot talisman.
Humanity has been reduced
to this little tiny slave class.
And the priests that were
and the scholars that were familiar
with these texts
in any part of the world
realized the proprietary
of the information
and looked at how people behaved.
And said, these people
behave like savages.
We're not going to sit there
and talk to them
about this proprietary information.
Now, what they did there
was a bad judgment call,
because now the people,
how are they going to elevate themselves
and understand law and physics
and science and all that stuff, right?
Because it's a very high level of science
in these ancient texts as well.
So anyway, yeah,
I've spent the past 10 years,
almost full time,
looking at all of the texts
throughout the planet.
And it's hard to make these statements
that I'm making.
I really never wanted
to say them in public,
that all of the religions are debased.
But unfortunately, they are.
And it is a good thing to say,
because someday here coming,
people are going to start
trying to figure out
why things aren't working out.
And they might actually go back
and look at the materials
that they're supposed to be based on,
whether it's laws.
That's why I think once in chat,
Vinny, I was looking for
the New Zealand cannabis laws.
And because they're all typically,
they have a little thing.
The Misuse of Drugs Act in 1978
or 1976.
That's right.
I haven't gone through
it completely yet,
but most of it is trying to find
where maybe there's another code
that says it's been repealed.
And because they hide that away
in the U.S. is Title 21,
I believe, and possession
has been repealed.
It's just intent to distribute
and manufacture that people are.
I don't know how you can
manufacture cannabis, but anyway.
With a Budman processing machine
that churns, you know,
Bud goes in, joins come out.
Yeah, counterfeiting money,
I guess you need the right
ink and the right paper.
Is that how it would be like
the the cannabis carousel?
OK, yeah, like that could work
or conveyor belt.
So with the religious part,
your law comes from it.
Now, here's the interesting part.
It's a completely lawless society,
completely at this point.
Now, it doesn't mean there's no order
when what's what the mainstream
puts in people's mind is
if you don't have any law,
there is no order.
You can have a lot of law
and not have any order.
I mean, a lot of order
and not have any law.
Right, it's just like what is it?
What's a cold one?
The strong rule, the weak.
You know what I mean?
America?
Possibly.
Which one, though, north or south?
Is it north or south?
You know, either way,
it doesn't matter.
You know, it's still lawless,
but New Zealand is the same.
So the entire Western world
and Eastern world is lawless
at this point.
You know, let's just throw
in a little trivia.
Biblical trivia.
I know because no one,
I'm one of the five people
on the planet who's read it,
believe it or not.
You have this thing
called Christmas, right?
Coming up.
Now is the time
for biblical TV trivia
with your host, The Greek.
So there are these big mega churches
over here and well,
do they have mega churches
in Las Vegas?
We have what's called
Destiny Church,
where Bishop Brian Tamaki
named himself Bishop
and then gets a whole shitload
of millions of dollars
and buys like several houses
and then like swanky suburbs
in Auckland and tells everybody
he's a pauper.
Yeah, OK, yeah, that's
exactly what I'm talking about.
OK, so they have these
big sites here
on the Internet and they say,
well, no one really knows
when this J-E-S-U-S
character was born.
So we're just going to go with it
and it's not pagan.
I'm like, wait a second.
Well, you know how timekeeping
changes from society to society
and giving a name or
let's say an existing time period
way of keeping time
doesn't carry over, right?
Like there was no January
through December 2000 years ago
or Monday through Friday.
These are recent timekeeping
inventions.
So the way you keep time
is astronomically
because astronomical occurrences
are extremely accurate.
And regardless of what timekeeping
function you use,
you know, the stars,
the moon and the sun don't lie.
Exactly.
And that way, everything
you do in your life
has an astronomical
chance of occurring.
Yeah, or sub-astronomical
in this case, being on Earth.
But what's interesting,
if you want to know,
it's very specific.
The Christ was a biblical Christ.
Don't confuse this with Jesus,
by the way, because there's
like 10 Jesuses.
There's one that says,
if you don't believe in me,
you're going to hell.
There's another one that says
that you could do
whatever you want.
You know, there's another one
that says you do this.
You do it.
I mean, it's just too confusing.
They may have a black one,
Asian one.
So, yeah.
And also the letter J
was invented in 1500.
So unless you're into
medieval history, forget it.
But what's interesting.
You hear that, Jesus?
Your name wasn't even existing.
And I've actually met
a couple of Jesuses in the past.
Out here, there's a really
good fish taco shop.
And he has J-E-S-U-S
on his name tag.
And I said, are you Jesus?
He says, yes, I am.
I'm like, wow, I can actually say
Jesus served me three fish tacos.
It's like, bro, has he got enough
fish to feed the whole party?
Yes, he fucking does.
Yeah, he does.
OK, so now now here's the point
in the biblical text.
I don't have to give you where
it says they were.
I saw a great sign in the sky.
It was a virgin giving birth.
She was cloaked with the sun,
the moon at her feet.
And she had 12 stars at her head.
Holy crap.
That's the constellation Virgo Draco.
Part of the Draco is at
the top of the constellation.
We know it's at sundown
because the sun is in the middle
of constellation.
And we know it's it's the
it's the middle of the month
because it's a crescent moon
because the sun and the moon
in the West.
OK, so what you do is you go
to an astronomical observatory
and you say, hey, look,
I've got this constellation,
the moon, the sun and this here.
When does this happen?
And they'll tell you, oh, yeah,
this happens like this
astronomical observation
happens maybe three times
every 20 years or so.
All right.
Well, well, if you look in the
when the Christ was supposedly
born, King Herod died
two and a half years later.
And Caesar cast a census
on his empire.
So we know secular records show
between 2 AD and 8 BC.
So you just go to the
astronomical computer and you say,
when did this event happen
between 2 AD and 8 BC?
And you get a pinpoint day of
3 BC, the day of 11,
the month of September.
There you go.
So that's when he was born,
according to the Gregorian calendar.
Now, does the 11th day of September
has that?
Yeah, I was going to say that.
Yeah.
September 11th, like somebody
did a star chart and then says,
OK, well, this is what they said
the stars look like
on the night of Jesus's birth.
What date did that happen?
Well, it had to be September 11th.
Yeah, well, that's and this is
what I'm saying is not my opinion.
It's not for debate.
Anyone can can do that.
Anyone could look this up
because when I first
started doing this,
I had to go to a planetarium.
Is that the word?
This is about 10 years ago,
maybe 12 years ago.
The the computing power,
what you know, if you wanted
to was just wasn't
available to get that.
So the university wanted
500 bucks to do it.
But I went to the planetarium.
We know they do the light
show at the end, you know, at night.
And all the guys are they got
nothing to do during the day.
They're just, you know,
smoking pot, you know,
whatever. And you go in there
and they'll just you'll show you
the I think you've confused
the planetarium for the sanitarium.
But there you go.
OK, so, yeah, it was
very interesting.
So this these things go on and on.
Also, they show you this
little nativity scene
with three wise men.
And we don't know
how many white or whatever.
That's not true.
That didn't happen
because in the biblical text,
it says that these men
from the east came
when he was in his father's workshop.
So he was about two and a half
or three years old.
Now, what this is,
I'm not saying that
the biblical story is true
or anyone should believe it
or anything.
I'm just showing the stark contrast
between what people believe
and what is in the text
that they say they subscribe to.
Right.
Let's just say
this for a conjecture.
Let's say the text is true,
but nobody's read it
or understood it.
Does a tree make a sound
if it falls
and no one's there to hear it?
And if a man speaks
his mind in a forest
and no woman hears him,
is he still wrong?
Why does it matter?
Isn't he the king of the castle?
I don't think so.
It's because she says so.
I mean, look,
yeah, the wife is the boss.
All right.
She she, you know,
she runs.
Yeah, I just live here.
Oh, no.
Well, here I'm the boss.
And I know that
because she tells me I am.
Anyway, never mind.
Yeah, but you can't trust
what women say, bro.
Yeah.
OK, here's another one.
You know, in the
in the Islamic community,
they think they're so righteous
because they are the women's
are women's are covered
in hijabs and burqas
and all that stuff.
Right.
It's it's so
it's so righteous.
Hey, and speaking of which,
sorry, amazing video today
of this Muslim couple.
And they had two seats
and the street was flooded.
And the guy was standing
in the water
and he would take one seat
and then put it in front
of his wife.
And she'd step from one seat
to the other and grab it.
And he made sure that she didn't
like step in the floodwaters.
I thought it was very sweet.
Yes.
But it's again,
if you read their text,
well, in ancient time,
let's just say it this way.
In ancient times,
you know, you know
what a uniform is.
You could see what someone's
profession is from a distance.
Right.
And in the ancient world,
up until recently,
actually, in that part
of the world,
if you saw a woman
that was covered the way
women are supposedly covered today
in that part of the world,
that was the uniform
of the world's oldest profession.
Prostitution.
Yeah.
So these people have lost their minds.
It goes across the board.
All religions.
They're just insane.
Well, here's here's the good part.
And you know what you just said
makes a whole shitload
of sense right now.
Well, let me let me just
there's there's a family
actually moved in
not too far from here.
And the husband has
the wife covered.
And I'm suspecting it's
a wife or a sister.
And he has she's holding a baby
as she's walking around.
And I want to go up to him
and point to her and said,
how much for an hour
with that woman?
You know, I mean,
she's wearing the uniform.
But anyway, this is yeah.
And they think it's a form
of being righteous.
It's just this is who was it?
Wolfgang Goethe,
he said that you need
not visit an insane asylum
to meet disordered spirits
because the Earth is
the insane asylum
of the youth of the universe.
Sounds about right.
There's madness everywhere you look.
I mean, nobody can can be on Facebook
or YouTube comment sections
for more than five minutes
before knowing that
that is a self-evident truth.
Yeah, I want to throw this in important.
Remember how we talked
about being lawful?
What's lawful?
It comes from your deity.
Well, it's very simple.
If you don't have a deity,
then it's real simple.
Do you obey the laws of the state?
Well, yes.
OK, then the state is your God
and April 1st is your holiday.
Do you have April 1st?
Is April Fool's Day
down there, by the way?
Yeah, but we call it April John Key,
the prime minister day.
Oh, OK.
Well, same thing.
So here's the interesting part.
You know what legal claims
are or lawful claims?
And someone makes a claim
and it stands until
someone else rebuts it
or counters it accordingly.
So if it's written,
you should write it down.
You know, if you're going
to rebut someone's claim.
What's interesting about
the biblical text
is just some claims in there
that this particular group
created everything
and they sit at the highest position.
And as far as I could tell,
it's never been rebutted.
And so that requires
if you have a lawful mind,
some investigation.
Now, what I mean by that is,
you know, like someone
could go to their house
and have a white piece of paper
nailed to the door and says,
yeah, greetings.
This house will be
foreclosed on in 30 days.
Well, if they don't
have a lawful mind,
they just take it off the door
and throw it in the garbage.
Right.
And they wait 30 days
to see what happens.
Or if someone has a lawful mind,
looks at the notice,
says, oh, is there
contact information here?
Who's who's who's the authority?
I need to work this out
before it gets out of hand.
See, most people see these things,
these claims,
and they've been trained
socially to disregard them.
It reminds me of this time
that my wife accidentally
put margarine on my toast
and I asked her to scrape it off.
That toast was never
rebutted either.
No, you can't margarine.
Oh, no, no, no.
You don't want margarine.
That's alien.
Margarine is alien.
You put margarine in the body.
The body says, well,
I don't know what to do with this.
That never happened.
It was a fictional story
like the Bible.
Well, it's not actually.
Here's another thing.
Is the Bible actually 100 percent true?
Because it's been so many
thousands of years of whatever
to let's say
if you've got a legal case,
there's a thing called
a statute of limitations, right?
After so many years,
you know, you can't prosecute someone.
And there's things called cold cases,
things that are like so old that,
you know, nobody solved them at the time.
And nowadays it's just no fucking way.
Maybe that's what the Bible is.
It's a giant cold case
that people are investigating
and still haven't managed
to come to the bottom of.
Well, here's the thing.
If it's a legitimate
communication from a deity,
they don't it doesn't seem like
why would they act in futility?
Right. It's it's operating.
But also, you got to remember,
they have an IQ of two million or so,
let's say.
But here's the thing.
You've ever heard of Aesop's fables,
the Fox and the Grapes?
No.
OK, so Aesop was one of these Greeks,
you know, right?
And the story of the Fox and the Grapes
was a fox is walking along a path.
He's really hungry.
He sees these beautifully ripe grapes.
He says, Oh, I'd like to have some.
So he jumps up
and he's trying to reach them
and he's spending a good part
of the afternoon.
He can't reach into the grapes.
And after, you know, he says, OK,
I'm going to give up.
You know what? Those grapes
are sour anyway.
Right. So the biblical text
is like this, like, for example,
I've studied it quite a bit
in its languages of preservation
because it's never been translated,
by the way, into English.
King, all the versions you get
are not translations.
There's forty eight hundred
critical errors in the first
ten thousand words.
So anyway,
it's just a communication.
I never recommend that anyone
go and read the biblical text
or study it.
Why?
Why? Because you're not
going to understand anything
in it anyway.
So why waste your time?
Yeah, that's actually the conclusion
I came to just before
finishing Genesis.
No, no, you're not going to.
Well, it's first of all,
the level it's written
on a hundredth grade level
and your quote unquote
smartest professors are operating
on a fifth grade level right now.
So you're not going to
there's no way you're going to do
what there is is a level of code
in there that has to be deciphered.
It's backwards.
But here's the thing that's irrelevant.
All the ancient texts
are very similar.
But what's good about it
is that you're coming apart
into a part of human history
where people you've heard before
are going to realize
that they've got to go back to basics.
Like you've heard,
I think AFR used to run a
David Icke a voiceover
where he said, look, we've got
more lawyers than ever
and more people in prison,
more college, more people are ignorant,
more doctors, more people are sick.
You familiar with that?
You know, the more banks,
the more poor we are.
Doctors destroy health.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, lawyers destroy the law.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I have it.
I have it on here
somewhere on my computer.
But yeah, here it is.
But boom, I found it.
It's by Chris Hedges, actually.
And Ike was just quoting it.
We now live in a nation
where doctors destroy health.
Lawyers destroy justice.
Universities destroy knowledge.
Governments destroy freedom.
The press destroys information.
Religion destroys morals.
And our banks destroy the economy.
Very good.
OK, now, how much of that
can a society, a planetary society take?
Before it where they
all they have to do is stop and say,
what are these things based on?
So they're going to call
the lawyers on their laws.
They're going to call
the religious people on there
where they get their information.
They're going to call the doctors
on their studies that you see.
This time has not come yet.
And when that time comes,
there's going to be some sanity.
Is that what you've been waiting for, bro?
Because you've got like
whole bunches of information
that you've refused to share.
You know, you've started
to bring it up and then decided
not to share it.
Is that what you're
actually waiting for?
The general realization
by the planet that
every single institution
that they have some kind of faith in
is a fraud.
And then people will be able
to receive what you what you
what you can tell them.
Man, I couldn't have
said it better myself.
Thank you, Vinny.
Are you asking or telling?
Well, I guess I just
answered my own question.
There's a time for everything.
It's just like remember.
Have you ever heard of?
What is it?
The guy who back in the 19
early 1900s, who used to catalog
all the anomalous paranormal events
starts with an F, I think.
What's his?
No, he was like the first.
Anyway, you know, they asked him,
you know, if if all these
everything has been
there's nothing new under the sun.
Why? Why did the steam engine
only come out 100 years ago?
He says, because it was
steam engine time.
You see, Hero's engine
200 B.C.
The Greeks had a turbine,
a steam turbine, which is
far more advanced than
the regular steam engine.
200 B.C., but it wasn't
steam engine time.
They had to wait for Fulton.
You see, so right now
it's not time for that.
You've got to know the right
time as well, right?
Well, the elite have a
sense of timing.
And I think, what was it?
Astro theology.
You don't believe in astro
theology or any of this stuff?
Oh, no, well, that's just
all that stuff is the fox
and the grape.
So they don't understand
what they're reading.
So they'll make stuff up.
It sounds good.
What do you believe, though?
I mean, here's the thing.
You don't you don't actually
have any beliefs.
You've got what you know
and what you're curious about.
Yeah, because they used to
hang around farmers and miners.
If you're on a mine or a farm
and you start talking beliefs,
you'll get kicked off that place
because they have to function
on things that work.
Well, maybe that's
an interesting way of
looking at how the world is
misfiring, misfunctioning,
because let me let me
just hear me out here.
Maybe people are so stupid
that they don't realize
that they're stupid.
OK, I heard an interesting
statistic that tells you
everything you need to know
about America.
This was a Lewis Black
comedian said this.
It was a recent study
in the United States
determined that four percent
of Americans believe
that they're below
average intelligence.
And it's always not the one
being interviewed.
It's the next guy like the T-shirt.
You know, I'm with stupid.
Remember that with the finger
pointing over, you know,
in the 70s?
Well, anyway, exactly.
Stupid people are like
insane people.
They don't know they're stupid.
Insane people don't know
that they're insane.
OK, intelligent people question
am I stupid?
But a stupid person does not.
A sane person questions
am I going crazy?
But a crazy person does not.
Well, look, I think
there's a level of stupidity
around with everyone.
It's just that some people
are less stupid than others.
And there's a level of insanity
going around with everyone.
And some people are just
less insane than others.
You know what it's like?
It's like when I was in Woodshop
and we had to plane,
you know, these little shafts
of bloody wood off this thing
in order to smooth it down
to the shape that we want.
You know, get this one off
and that one off
and this one off
and this one off.
And before you know it,
you've actually got something
that you can be proud of.
Something that's got craftsmanship.
But it takes a hell of a lot
and you have to discard
most of what you had to start with.
Well, speaking of craftsmanship,
if I was less stupid myself,
personally, I wouldn't be
calling in speaking to you now.
I'd be putting the finishing touches
on my flying saucer
and getting off the stinking rock.
But anyway, did I just say that on air?
OK, so anyway, you see how it goes?
Everything's just kind of nuts anyway.
And maybe, maybe that's part of the reason
why so many truthists
think that they're going crazy.
It's because everything else
is fucking nuts, right?
And everything's so stupid.
Have you ever noticed
that people who are incredibly,
just ridiculously stupid
make you feel crazy?
Well, it's not, you know,
here's just on a tangent here,
which is along the same path.
There's a lot of talk
about misinformation, disinformation,
lack of information, ignorance, stupidity.
I haven't found that
to be the main problem.
The main problem is
when you confront someone
with a piece of information
that is newly imparted to them, OK,
new to their psyche and consciousness,
put cognitive dissonance aside.
We're talking about rational thought here,
OK, and critical thought.
Very often you'll get, you know,
I haven't heard of that before.
And you know what?
I don't want to know about that.
And I don't care.
Wow. OK, so that's not ignorance anymore.
That is a response of
stubbornness, rebelliousness,
let's say apathy.
You get where I'm going with it?
No, it's fear.
They're afraid to admit that they're wrong
because they've been taught
throughout their entire life
that being wrong is a bad thing
as opposed to an experience
you can learn from.
Well, hold on.
I didn't say something right or wrong.
This is a new bit of information
that they could have never gone
either left or right on it.
This is a totally new bit of information.
It doesn't conflict
with their belief structure at all?
It's just a random factoid?
Yeah, yeah.
Like let's say chemtrails, you know,
sometimes I'll be in a parking lot
and I'll see a rational,
seemingly rational individual.
And I'll say, well,
you know, it's interesting.
Those are not chemtrails, you know.
I said, oh, really?
I've never noticed that, you know.
I said, you know, they're steam, right?
I said, no, they're not steam.
I'll explain why they're not steam.
Yeah, I'm not into that.
I don't want to know about it.
I'm like, dude, you're breathing it.
What do you mean you don't
want to know about it?
Well, it's the psyche.
There's no, yeah.
No, no, no.
Because those people are operating
under a belief structure.
The belief structure is I'm not a lab rat
in a giant open-air fucking
breathe tank experiment, OK?
Hold on.
Yeah, but it's not about belief.
There's just like, go to a Christian,
open the Bible and show them
something in there.
The first thing they tell you,
that's not my Bible,
so it can't be the same thing in there.
Or, you know, I have three books in the car.
I have the Book of Mormon,
the Koran, and the Bible.
So if you ever get into these
conversations in public
and they want to argue,
I said, I happen to have a copy
in the car right here.
And I once had a parking attendant
who was a Muslim, self-professed.
And he was telling me about this
and that, this and that.
I said, where'd you hear that?
And he said, well, at the mosque
with the imam.
I said, that's not in the Koran.
He says, yes, it is.
I happen to have a copy right here.
Let me show you.
You see, it's just, yeah.
So the belief,
what does belief have to do with it?
Well, I think what you do
is eventually you lose curiosity
and you don't want to know.
All right.
It's not like you can't know.
It's that you don't want to.
All right.
You lose curiosity.
You can lose curiosity
by a number of different mechanisms.
Curiosity, for example,
getting punished.
You know, if you're curious
about something and you go
do that at work or whatever
and you fuck something up
and the boss punishes you
or even maybe that could start
to manifest during your younger years
and your parents punish you
for questioning certain things
or whatever.
And basically through a series
of trauma-based mind control incidents
called modern life,
you can lose your curiosity
quite easily.
And most people have already.
You know what?
What's interesting?
I'll throw this in there.
I've seen that in ancient life as well
through what's been memorialized.
You know, the ancients
were like this as well.
When an old idea gets old enough
that it becomes forgotten,
when it returns,
people think that it's new.
Yeah.
That's why if you want
a really new idea,
read a really old book.
When the hell was the last time
somebody actually came up
with a new idea?
I don't know.
We'd have to redefine the word new
if nothing is new.
Well, there's nothing new under the sun.
It's all just a repetition
and stuff like that.
God damn it.
There's an experiment going on here.
That's what I'm starting to really
think about that.
Like there's actually a point
like a computer game,
a hologram or something like that.
There's actually an objective here.
Now, the human race hasn't fulfilled
whatever the fuck that objective is yet.
And until we do,
we're going to keep repeating
the same fucking cycles.
No, you're not.
Hold on. It has.
It has because it's just
like baking a cake.
It needs a cure.
There's a curing period.
Just like, you know,
a cake is what, 45 minutes
at a certain temperature
or certain epoxies,
you know, hold for 30 minutes
or there's a curing period.
In other words, until it's set,
you know, and that period ended already.
And that's what's so freaking exciting.
But the problem is that time
isn't reckoned with the Gregorian
Pope's work schedule.
So anyway, you know how they say
it's 2015 or whatever,
whatever happened all the other
years before that.
What the hell's going on?
And if today is what they call
whatever this day of the week,
last year was another day of the week.
So what day of the week is it?
You know, the biggest problem
that I see is that everyone
is not a problem.
And I don't really see it as a problem.
I'll retract that statement
is that everyone is operating
under the Pope's work schedule.
And even something maybe as trivial
and as minimal and as insignificant
as keeping time has been lost.
It's a very heavy slave
outline that's been put on mankind,
which is the Pope's work schedule.
That's why when I hear people
bad mouthing the Vatican,
all I have to do is ask him
what day it is.
And if they say anything between
January or December,
Monday through Friday,
they're admitting with their own mouth
that they're the Pope's subject.
So they're, you know,
they're pretty twisted.
But, you know, not that
not that bad mouthing
the Vatican is twisted.
But I'm just saying that, you know,
people don't have their
their house in order.
You got to get it in order first
before you go about
and do things like that.
That's why I sort of
kind of stay retracted.
But but anyway, I'm open to
all suggestions and considerations
if there's anything you'd ever
want to hear discussed.
So I'll just put that out there.
Yeah, I don't know.
I was just thinking about
like the purpose of life itself.
You know, for me, it's
for me, it's quite easy to find
my purpose in life, you know.
But I'm talking about
life in the aggregate.
I'm talking about all the organisms
and everything.
It's working together in some way
in a symbiotic fashion
and behaving independent of each other.
But is there actually an overall purpose?
Like there's a reason why this
why this fish died today
of radiation poisoning
and a reason why that squirrel died yesterday
after getting run over by a kid
that stole his mom's jeep
and filled it up with,
you know, really high octane
petrol and drag raced his mates
on a skateboard that had
rocket boosters attached to it.
And the poor squirrel got run over.
You know what?
Well, there's a purpose.
It's an overlying kind of
like real strange sort of
interconnected web.
And here it is.
It's very simple.
People are humanities
is too egocentric.
You know, like the world
world revolves around me.
It's all about us, right?
We'll get over it.
It's not.
There is a cosmic
there's a multitude of
cosmic things going on right now.
And there's an element
or an entity called death.
As you so give us the examples on.
And when this element
this thing called death
or in other circles,
it might be called entropy,
which is degradation, rot,
you know, decay, entropy, right?
Like an energetic system
suffer entropy when they
lose their power.
OK, this entropic destruction
or something called death.
This is a time for it's
it's peaking and death
will be put to death.
It actually already has in some
point at some point, not here.
And when it reaches here,
meaning the earth,
there will be no more death.
And that will really
change the consciousness.
And what I mean by that
is imagine being born
and not going through puberty
till you're about 35 or 40.
Or, you know, if there's
a funeral for someone
at 100 years old,
it'll be a child's funeral.
So this is kind of pretty amazing.
And yes, there is a meaning of life
and it's not about us right now,
even though it is.
So that sounds about right.
It's when death is
very difficult to see.
Here's another analogy of it.
Have you ever heard of anyone
being brought up or raised
or born in a war zone?
You know, if you ever discussed
anything with old European people,
I was born during the war
and childhood was terrible.
We had to eat shoes
and couldn't find any food
and all that.
This is a period of over 6,000 years
where mankind has been in a war zone.
Don't take it personally.
Yeah, the meaning of life
is quite simple.
It's just that it's so simple
that it can't be described
because we're mid-range thinkers.
We cannot comprehend the complex
and we cannot comprehend the simple.
And explaining the meaning of life
in a mid-range way is very difficult.
But I just use the contrast
that when there is no more death,
you will see more meaning
in what just happened.
The entire human epoch.
Well, that's because at the point
where you no longer fear death,
you're not struggling in the survival
because when you're struggling
for survival,
you're in a lower brain
fight or flight mode
and you can't access
higher fucking consciousness.
So imagine how many people
would be able to access
higher consciousness
if they had no fear of death.
Yeah, but look, okay.
Fear of death, I don't like that.
Look, I'll just throw in this.
It's not whether I like it or not.
The ancient Greeks used to say
that those who are afraid of dying
or have fear don't know how to live.
So maybe focusing on how to live better
and then the fear part goes away.
Yeah, well, like I said before,
it makes sense because to me,
the only things that make sense
have some kind of cosmic irony to them.
Oh yeah, there's a sense of humor.
There's irony.
There's everything.
Everything is something and nothing, right?
That's cosmic irony.
Like, for example,
somebody could be a great lover
and a complete bastard.
All right.
Well, anyway, the Greek.
Thank you very much.
It was great.
And ladies and gentlemen,
remember on Sunday to check out
the American Freedom Radio Marathon,
we need to raise some cash for the studio.
So please check that out, promote it,
share it out on social media,
email your congressman
and stuff like that.
Tell them to shut us down
because if they do shut us down,
it'll give us a hell of a lot more attention.
Please, you know, just go ape shit.
All right.
Support American Freedom Radio,
support the Vinnie Eastwood Show,
and we will see you again sometime,
assuredly.
Thank you very much for listening.
News and information you can trust.
This is American Freedom Radio.
Freedom, freedom, American Freedom Radio.
Radio.
American Freedom Radio.
Nutritious food is real body armor.
It builds muscle, burns fat,
improves digestion and feeds the entire body
the nutrients it needs.
Did you know the U.S. government banned
the hemp plant from growing in the United States
and classified it as a Schedule 1 drug
to hide it behind the marijuana plant?
People have been confused about this plant
for over 80 years,
and many still don't know what hemp is.
So now you know hemp is not marijuana
and marijuana is not hemp.
They are different varieties of the same species.
HempUSA.org wants the world
to know these basic facts
and to help people understand
that hemp protein powder
is the best kept health secret
you need to know about.
Remember, hemp protein powder
contains 53% protein,
is gluten-free,
anti-inflammatory,
non-GMO,
and is loaded with nutrients.
Call 888-910-4367,
888-910-4367,
and see what our powder, seeds and oil
can do for you.
Only at hempUSA.org.
What kind of person are you?
How do you see yourself?
Are you the kind of person
that lets everyone else do all the work,
just hoping that you'll be able
to get some of the crumbs
that fall from the table?
Or are you the kind of person
that rolls up their sleeves
and does the dirty jobs
that no one else wants to do?
Are you hoping that all the activists
giving their blood, sweat and tears
to serve humanity
are going to solve
all the world's problems?
Or are you just wondering,
is there something simple
I can do to contribute?
Yes, yes there is.
Help us.
Help us do what we do.
Partner up with American Freedom Radio today
by gifting a regular amount
to support the network
and your favorite hosts,
bringing you less commercials
and more information.
Go to AmericanFreedomRadio.com
and start donating today
from between $1 and $100 per month
according to the kind of person you are.
Thank you very much for your support.
We are living in a new era.
Partnerships are more important than profit.
And gratitude is more respected than greed.
As the millennial generation
evolves the corporate landscape,
our company aims to maximize
the achievements of CBD application
and push the limits of what's possible by 2020.
Our core product matrix
and careful cannabidiol purification process
are uniquely designed to be privately made
in different regions of the world
and is geared to assist the efforts
of different nations to change the landscape
of various pain-related healthcare costs,
epilepsy and autism,
rising mental disorders,
and even soldier suicides.
Crystal Pure CBD is made
with the industry's finest 99.9% pure CBD crystals.
No paste, no filler.
Our solution is a permanent answer.
And it saves you over one third in cost.
Crystal Pure CBD.
Come join us.
You're listening to AmericanFreedomRadio.com,
the network who perseveres
in delivering intelligent debate,
constructive dialogue with true independence.
The freedom to broadcast the truth
is not free at all.
So what is American Freedom Radio worth to you?
The empowering information with fun,
honest and pure integrity behind it
provides an example to follow.
Friendships to flourish
with the moral altruism that pulls no punches.
The hosts sacrifice
and show remarkable discipline
in their duty to deliver quality radio
in service to the community
with strength, wisdom and loyalty.
The founders of AFR wish to thank you personally
for sharing your views and insights
to make the best radio and alternative media.
Now it's time for you to give something back
and play a vital role in the future of America.
Be as generous with us as we've been with you.
Click on the donate banner at AmericanFreedomRadio.com
or volunteer by emailing AmericanFreedomRadio.com.
Vaccine, psychotropic drugs
and artillery batteries not included.
No rules.
No taboo topics.
No fear of doom.
We are.
We are American Freedom Radio.
American Freedom Radio.