Rated Y Sonic Event 108, and here we are, Greek, how are you doing?
Hey, before we started we were talking about architecture, dumb people, academia, oh my
goodness, you know, I rarely, I'm usually walking around and doing stuff when we record
this Sonic, but now I'm sitting in the office in front of the big rectangle, and I put in
tornado damage, right, recently, and just look at the architecture, it's like, these
people are stupid, typically that's like stick and mud construction, or stick and siding,
and when I mean by stick and siding, you ever drop, you know the old style wooden matches,
a box of wooden matches, you know?
Oh yeah, I have some around the house now, but yeah, yeah.
You ever drop a box and it completely spills out, that's what these houses look like.
Yeah, it all goes in different directions.
Yeah, it just looks like a bunch of matchsticks falling down, why would you build like that?
And how could you be so stupid to buy into, when I say buy into, I mean literally and mentally
that you could live there, I have zero sympathy for them, as a matter of fact, they should
nuke the place and clear it out and let the stuff grow, what did I just say, never mind,
scratch that, we'll edit that out.
Rewilding?
Yeah, they need to just go, I don't feel any more sorry, actually I feel more sorry for
the cows that got drowned or something, endless miles of dead cows, but anyway, I just want
to bring this up because it's so pathetic, let's get into this real quick, because the
architecture part, there's no reason to talk about it, a half-wit could look at the damage,
right, which will be most of the people looking at the damage by the way, and they will not
stop and pause and say this needs to not be done this way, meaning why are you building,
okay.
Let's separate, wait, let's separate things for a moment, okay, there is architecture
that's planned out, and then there's stuff that just sort of happens as it's needed,
okay, now you have a swelling of a population in an area, so there's more housing needed.
You have livestock, yep, bipedal livestock, yep.
Fine, but yeah, go ahead.
Let's look at it this way, it's very simple, even Jack Fresco went into it, make a little
paper cardboard cube, you know, about six inches or 10 inches or even a foot, you can
pick it up with one hand, it's very easy to grab, right, especially if you have a leaf
blower, you'll notice they'll go off the table.
Make something dome-shaped or conical, especially hyperbolic, where it gets skinnier, you know,
like a hyperbolic, it's not a consistent cone, try to pick it up with your hand, it just slips
out of your hand, there's no way you can pick it up, right, with one hand, right, so why
don't you, okay, so you get it, right?
Now, here's the thing, let's just get into this really simple, by the way, I could have
prevented all of that from here in Tucson where I'm at, that happened in Midwest, I
could have prevented all of it, and they foreshadowed it a week ago, they said by the end of the
week you can have some really bad weather here, I said, well, let's see how it pans out.
I do message with someone who does frequently get devices from me, they're on the East Coast,
I'm not going to mention their name, and we're in frequent contact and doing some fine-tuning,
and one thing that I've watched this person develop in doing weather work is the hardest
thing is to figure out how simple it is, right, because you're, okay, wow, you know, I told you
I almost got in trouble, okay, let me just preface it this way, I was traveling back and forth to
Texas and New Mexico doing stuff, and I always brought up an old-fashioned, well, my version of
a modern cloud buster, right, and one day I was traveling with someone, I sit on the side of
the road, I said, hey, you know, we've never been to this town before, and I looked at it, and it's like,
you know, when was the last time it rained in that town, so it doesn't show, I mean, you know, a month
or so, I said, you know, it's summer, I'm going to go into this town, I'm going to smell their garbage
and all their brake dust, you know, when you walk into a city, you go into a city, it smells
different, right, each city smells different, oh, yeah, absolutely, yeah, yeah, and I'm going to smell
their whatever and their brake dust, you know, because cars, you know, every time a car goes to
a red light, there's a tiny amount of brake dust that's released, right, this, okay, most of the
smells in cities, by the way, is what type of brakes they're using, anyway, okay, I don't want to go
on a tangent, but just think about why is it that large portions of New York City smell like urine,
then that's got nothing to do with the brake dust, yeah, in New York, they can piss on their brakes, it
wouldn't matter, so there you go, okay, so anyway, I was like, you know, I don't want to go to this town
and smell the town, why don't we just make some rain and freshen it up, you know, we're two hours
away, we'll make the rain now, by the time we get there, it'll be over, and this is what we're doing,
it was very successful at it and very consistent at it, so we're at the side of the road, and we're
setting this stuff up, and you know, it was some of these weigh stations, you know, they have
bathrooms, you know, on the side of the highway, people stop, some of them are extra long, you know,
like you park off to the side, there's a building, there's picnic areas, right, of course, where
everybody used to the bathroom, no buffer zone, right, so there's family, there's these children,
and like a young adult, like an uncle type, what are you doing, is that a telescope, said no, it's a
weather machine, we're making weather, oh no, yeah, sure, so they go around, another couple of people
come over, how does it work, well anyway, make a long story short, there's a sheriff there, and he
comes over, and he's very upset that the people are talking about that I'm doing weather work,
you're making weather, yeah, making, yeah, and I said, oh no, weather, no, this is just an
atmospheric device, come on, the weather, only God can do the weather, right, and he's like, yeah,
that's right, these people don't know what they're talking about, right, you get it, so you have
plausible deniability, in other words, once you, the experience that I have over 20 years in this
now, I can teach within a few weeks, depending if you have sensibility and sensitivity, you have to
have sensibility and sensitivity, and make them interchangeable, you can learn how to do this
within, let's say, a few moons, okay, and even advance it, and be on level where I'm at with 20
years experience, working directly with Trevor James Constable, and Joe Blankenship, and people
like that, right, so, but you have to really decide if you're going to give up all the garbage that
you've been carrying your whole life about what these, what the weather really is, and you'll find
out on your own, I'll brief you, and outline you, and what's going on, and we're going to do a little
bit of that now, whether there's interest in weather or not, you know, I'm going to bring up
a few things that you've never heard before, so I could have completely prevented that from here,
because right now, I can do half of the world from where I'm at, right, and we're talking about
radical shit, like, we're getting at the end of spring, when summer starts, I can make it snow in
a tropical place, right, I love when it's Christophe, yeah, I've done it twice already, snow, right, so,
right, because snow is not frozen water, I mean, it's not frozen rain, like they tell you, it's a
completely different system, just like hail is not frozen rain, it's a completely different system,
anyone who's been in big areas where hail comes, you can always tell the hail clouds have a greenish
yellowish tinge to them, right, always, and you know, it's going to be held by the color
frequency, the same with snow, hail doesn't act like regular ice anyway, oh no, no, it's,
these things are not the same, okay, you know, okay, it's like pizza and birthday cake,
right, or cupcakes, completely different, but they're made from the same stuff, right,
they diverge, and they're no longer the same, right, at a certain point of it being made,
okay, by the way, I made a great pizza, I'm learning how to operate this
pizza oven, 800 degrees, talking 42 seconds to make a pie, right, I'll send you a picture of it,
Neapolitan style, 42 seconds, man, it's great, okay, 800 degrees Fahrenheit, okay,
so what's going on is really reasonable, by the way,
because you have plausibility, let me just do a double wink, because you have plausibility on
your side, you can do anything, in other words, if you're feeling evil one particular morning,
you can get up and make a county or municipality 500 or 1000 miles away from you a disaster zone,
I mean, this is how, so this is not a real reality, if you can do that with just a simple
rudimentary devices, right, or you can stop a disaster from happening, if it's known, and it
has all the precedence for becoming one, well, if things are the way that they explain them to us
regarding this, then you should not be able to do with temperature, look, like they said,
yeah, you should not be able to do something like that with a simple device, I mean, it's just that
that's what it comes down to, yeah, but we'll look at the old radios, I don't know, see,
I was fortunate enough to my first teeth kit radio was one that was NOS, new old stock from
the 1930s. So I got this, I opened this thing up in the 70s and built something that was built,
made in the 30s. It was a little crystal with cords around it and some wire and ceramic parts.
And the instruction was to go to a chain link fence. And you had this little earphone, you
can make the right, remember the very early, there's just one never stereo. I remember the
old, old, old earphones, right? Oh, yeah, you can see the twisted wires on it. And it's made out
of that bakelite plastic that turns yellow, you know, right, right. Yeah, anyway, and so I'm making
a radio. And you can pick up all kinds of stuff. And I'm like, Oh, my gosh, this is like primitive.
This is so crude, right? So same thing. It's exactly the same thing. Right? You can elaborate
a little bit more and you could broadcast using the same technology, but it's called a transducer.
So what do we have here? First of all, we have an open plain, an area that was not at that
elevation about, let's say 1000 years ago, the Midwest where these things happen,
were mountainous ranges that were leveled. Okay, how do we know that? Because there's a tremendous,
first of all, when that area was resettled by the Westerners, there was like 11 feet of topsoil,
you know, anything that's got more than a foot of topsoil is a foot of topsoil is considered very
rich. Right? So there's a lot of weird things why that happened there, but we're not going to get
into that now. So underneath that is a tremendous amount of lodestone in the Midwest iron, right?
Let me just give you a hint. You know, the US for about 70 years was the biggest iron producer,
steel producer in the world for over almost 100 years, right? Right. Okay. So where do they get
the iron, right? It's just they go out anywhere and you get it. That's why when I talk about water
treatment or whatever, so just get some magnets, tape them to a stick and drag them on the ground,
then you'll find sand that looks black and sticks to the magnet. That's magnetite, right? It's
everywhere. Very pervasive. Anyway, so you have these conditions. And now we have these conditions
now, these tornadoes strike and it happens every year around the same time, right? Some years worse
than others. Actually, if you'll notice that when we have a 13th moon, it's much worse.
Tornado season, they often call it a tornado alley. Yeah. Okay. All right. So let's get into
the real basic part. Okay. Where else do we see that funnel shape in a bathtub, right? In order
to get that funnel shape happening in your bathtub, it's called a drain. Yeah. Around the drain. You
see it, right? Right. Now, what is a drain? A drain means, okay. A drain could be anywhere.
Actually, let me just get out of the picture for a second. You know, I can have my bathtub drain to
the ceiling if the pressure in a hole, let's say I made a hole in the ceiling. I could have my water
in my bathtub drain to that hole in the ceiling if the pressure in that hole was low enough, right?
Right. Because the greater pressure, the regular pressure goes to a lower pressure.
Goes to a lower pressure. Yeah. The reason why. Now, when the drain pressure starts to increase
and it goes to zero, it's not negative anymore. You have a clog and it doesn't drain.
Right. It means it's equal to the pressure of the sidewall of the bathtub. So,
in other words, that drain hole always has to have a lower pressure than the surrounding tub area.
Right. Give you another example of how to think of this. Your drain hole is plugged, right? Let's
say you live in a place where you got these fiberglass tubs. Okay. So, honey, the tub doesn't
drain. Yeah. Right. So, you go in and I'll fix that. So, you get a drill and you drill right
through the side of the tub. Another hole and water starts pouring out of the tub. Right.
You just put another drain hole. Yeah. That does work. Right. Why does it go out that hole? Because
it sees that that hole that you made has less pressure than the sidewall of the tub. Right.
Simple. Simple. Now, this sounds Greek. I know this. Yeah. But do you know it? In other words,
every time you see a system, can you break it down that simple? Right. And now this is where
you get into this is now. Hey, you ready? I'm going to quote something new. It's probably for
future songs. It's going to be called The Inventor's Lounge. This is how inventors and
creative people think. Right. Right. They don't think like normal people. Right. Right. So,
most normal people say, oh, it's a dream. It's clogged. It's clogged. An inventor will say, oh,
it's not going down because the pressure is not low enough.
On the other side, the pressure must be lower on the other side from where the water in order for
it in order for it to exit. Right. That's how inventors think. Normal people say, oh,
it's very good. There's stuff in there. Yeah. Yeah. That's not how you see. So it's the same
condition. You're describing the same conditions, but you're coming from a completely different
angle. One angle gives you one possibility. Unclog the drain. The other angle is limitless
possibilities. I can drill a hole in the ceiling and drop a vacuum, one of those industrial vacuums
and suck the water out that way. Right. Yeah. Sure. So. Yeah. OK. So the event. Welcome to
The Inventor's Lounge. All right. So what's going on is you have these funnels that are appearing.
They're usually generally appearing anywhere between 700, 900 feet in altitude. You notice
to about twenty five hundred feet. OK, that's roughly the ceiling because some are higher,
some are even lower, the smaller ones. So there's. OK, so what's going on is very simple. You have
cloud cover that forms. Not always. I've seen tornadoes form with minimal cloud cover.
Cause you something else. OK, so we're not going to talk about that.
So there's a low pressure that develops between the height. You know, these tornadoes,
when you look at images of them, they're they're easy. In other words, when you capture an image
or produce a photograph, the tornado is pretty much square in the photo. In other words,
they usually tend to be they're not high altitude phenomenon. So some are taller than others. Right.
So wherever the top of that tornado is, is where that low pressure begins. And as it goes down,
it gets lower. Now, hold on. Hold on. In natural settings, the way we use barometric pressure,
you notice that as we go up in altitude, what happens? The pressure goes lower, doesn't it?
Like if you open the what happens when you open, let's say you're in a jetliner using old terms
and you're 30,000 feet or 40,000 feet. Someone opens the door. What happens?
You get sucked out. Everything gets so low. Right. Right. OK. Now, when you go down into a hole in
the ground or Death Valley, the pressure is much higher as you go down to below sea level or sea
level. Pressure is the greatest. Right. It's one bar, 15 psi, roughly at sea level. If you go up
an altitude up to a mountain, it could be as low as 13 psi. Right. Well, thus, instead of things
being sucked out like they would be at the high altitude, they're now being pushed in. So if you
go to a place like Death Valley or the Dead Sea, the pressure is higher than 15, one bar, a little
bit. Oh, wow. So so what's happening is a reverse of the pressure, but the pressure is dependent
on concentrations of ether. OK, so when ether concentrates, a vacuum develops. Right. And there's
a temperature drop. By the way, there's always a temperature drop when a tornado appears. So it has
nothing to do with thermal conditions. Those thermal conditions are post event. You know,
when it's already formed, when it's OK, it's kind of like I have a joke about Greek speak or banjo.
OK, he started off with banjos, banjos. Yeah. What do what does banjo music and heavy artillery
have in common? Once you hear it, it's too late. OK. Right. So once you see a tornado,
it's too late is what I'm trying to say. Right. So when you see these conditions form a low pressure
because the ether is concentrating. OK, here comes, OK, the weather work.
The most rudimentary weather device is a hollow metal tube. It should be magnetic,
like galvanized iron or steel, galvanized metal, sheet metal. Let's just call it that
sheet metal. Sheet metal is the stuff that you see that has that gal coating. OK, it's very common.
And when you when you ground that to the ground, just like you would ground something electrical
and mist water on one end that's closed and the business end is open towards the sky.
The biggest problem I have with making these things people have is all they can do is make
holes in clouds because what it does is it damps out the ether. It makes a hole in the ether,
dissolves the ether. So if you have rain coming and you swing this thing at 90 degrees, let's say
pointed at 30 or 45 degree angle up in the air, it's on a tripod or some kind of mounting mechanism.
And if you start swinging this thing, let's say from east to north to east to north and there's
a storm there, you're going to see a storm will wipe away, go away. So it creates drought. So
beginners that get into this early cloudbuster stuff that's grounded, a water gun, it's called
all they do is create droughts, right? Because they wipe away the ether.
All you got to do for these assholes out there in the Midwest is, well, let's just say they
have assholes, they're idiots, but more accurately. All you got to do is go to, you don't
even have to, I tell people, don't even go to Home Depot or supply place and buy one for 10 bucks or
20 bucks. Find in the garbage. You know, you see if someone do construction, you're always going
to see a piece of stovepipe laying out there, right? Lonely. Anyway, you can go and buy one
or whatever and make a very simple cap. There's like 3000 websites that show you how to make a
right cloudbuster rudimentary out of sheet metal for less than 50 bucks, right? And start waving
it around and you make whatever atmospheric manifestations are happening. Go away.
Go away. They just, you just dissipate them. So all you need to do, and it's got a 500 mile range.
If you, if you can make a larger one and you know how to ground and you know how to put the water
in there, not going to get into that. Now you could just swing the thing. I don't recommend
swinging it more than 90 degrees. Like don't go from North all the way to South or go three 60.
That'll create another effect. It'll work for a little while, but 90 to 45 degree, you know,
angle as the Cardinal lines go. Right. And you have a few people, 500 miles apart doing this,
and you'll clear all that weather away. And the weather was, well, we're supposed to have a
tornado, clear blue skies. What's going on. That's how easy and simple this is. Okay.
There is definitely no intelligent life forms out there. I tell you that for sure.
Right. Not a lot of things are for sure, but there are no intelligent people living in the
Midwest that we know for sure. Right now. We know that. Fair enough. That's been already proven.
So what you're telling me is what these devices really do is remove the concentration of the
ether. Okay. Imagine you have a fog machine, you see them, they have them in theater and
whatever. Sure. Okay. Special effects. Imagine an anti-fog machine where you go into a place.
You've seen a fog machine. It's like a box and it has an opening, right? And the fog comes out.
Well, a lot of people would think that you sort of vacuum up the fog, but no,
you vacuum up the opposite. Okay. Well, you have fog conditions and you have a machine that sucks
up the fog. Right. But in this case, the fog is invisible. You don't see it with your eyes,
the ether, the conditions that create the fog. Okay. Okay. So this is how simple. Anyway,
one thing we did prove is that there is no intelligent life in the Midwest right now.
So, you know, I don't know about human rights and all that other bullshit they're talking about.
No one lives there. So this is what's going on in the world. So you can't tell me I should be
taking anything seriously here at all or anyone seriously, because that's a joke. It's a joke.
And just to add one more thing, and don't tell me solitary confinement is a bad thing.
Oh, my gosh. There's no other option at this point. Okay. Enough with that rant. So
this is what's going on. I mean, how can you live around people that are so dumb that they cannot
apply what I just said? And by the way, there's plenty of information that's gotten out. There's
got to be an idiot that lives out there. Well, there isn't, obviously, because look, see?
Anyway, let's get off of it, because you know what? I think it's just content at this point,
right? In other words, these disasters are content for the media, isn't it?
Well, isn't it just become content for the media? It's one of the many things. Look,
what do people always want to see? They want to see what, you know, what bleeds leads, right?
What is tragic? What is painful? Other people's pain is entertainment to someone. You know,
either they feel bad. Oh, I feel so bad for that person. You know, they're either doing it that way
or quite honestly, there's other people that just sort of enjoy the suffering about it for a
specific person. You should feel bad for all of them right now. But OK, generally, yeah, I agree
with you there. I mean, yeah, it's just oh, my God. We're all here. We all deserve a little
sympathy. No. Yeah. It looks like they reorganized the landfill and it backwards. In other words,
if you look at the mess right now, I have it open a couple of places in Nebraska or whatever,
Iowa, and it's just piles of sticks. Right. You've seen that with the post tornado, right?
It's just sticks like dropping a box of old fashioned matches on the floor. Right. First
of all, you have to be mentally deficient to buy a house that's made made that way in that kind of
area. Well, you have to be mentally deficient to buy a house like that made anywhere because you're
being ripped off. Right. Yeah. Well, buying a house. Yeah. Well, first of all, there's a
problem with your premise. Can you actually buy the house? No, no. I mean, let's say you're going
to be a resident. Right. Because everything's already been you know, there's no ability to
purchase it. Well, there's no money. There's no money. And who actually owns anything anyway.
Right. So what are you doing? Well, what happens is when you use their money system, by the way,
to buy anything, they always retain an interest in what you're buying because you're using their
private money. Right. So it's kind of like the bastards in the legal system. All of them all the
way up. They you know how they're operating. They're operating no different than imagine a
post apocalyptic scenario where the survivors of society start piecing together a society and they
and they're looking for like, pre war technology because there were more advanced than right.
That's what the legal system that they don't understand what the law is at all there.
You know, they just tell you, OK, you know, they have no idea what you know what it is at all. I'm
talking about like judges and attorney generals. They don't know the average idiot with a legal
practice is really I mean, you could just be serving popcorn at the ballpark. It's he's not
any smarter than that. So or, you know, whatever work, you know, working at the gift shop at the
Supreme Court building, your average attorney there. No, scary, stupid. Right. Talk about stupid.
Yeah. The common tropes of look, you could probably train a monkey to do it and it would
about have the same. Oh, my gosh. Yeah. Yeah. They just really talk about dumb people. But
this whole system is more it's but it's not looking. See, I just gave a scenario post
apocalyptic society that sends some scouts out to find pre war technology. Right. Because it's
valuable compared to what they have now. They're not even doing that. You know, they don't they're
not even aware of stuff that was talked about in the 30s, 40s, 50s, 60s. So even right there,
not even aware. Anyway, application, it boils down to application, right?
I always find that interesting when I read a pre, you know, what they call pre depression,
like news articles and things where they talk about things that people are doing,
creating and stuff like that. You say to yourself, well, if they were doing that in 1920,
whatever, then that means that some progress should have been made from there. And then you
think about it and you go, well, actually, no, nobody ever picked up and took this thing.
You know what I'm saying? I mean, that's a constant in if you read old newspaper articles.
Yeah. The next thing I'm going to do, I'll put this out. Oh, I don't know. Don't hold me to it.
But I want to I haven't done in a long time. A demonstration, a weather demonstration, a big one.
So like, we'll pick a city, a state somewhere, an area locale.
OK, in the Midwest, a thousand miles, fifteen hundred miles from Tucson. Doesn't matter
anywhere in the US. OK, closer, the better. I pick a day, a place and tell me what you want
to do there. What do you want to do? You want to make rain? What do you want to do? OK,
so I want to make wind and we'll do it. When do you want it to? What kind of weather conditions
you want on what day? Tell me and I'll do it. So if I wanted to snow in Phoenix, theoretically,
would that be acceptable? It's a little late now. We have to wait for it, believe it or not,
for it to be change of season. Like I said, at the end of spring, when summer begins, you can do it.
OK, you can do it at change of season points. Yes. You know what I said? I made it snow in
the tropics. It was right at the beginning of summer, at the beginning of summer. OK,
yeah, the way it doesn't the weather doesn't matter as long as you catch it at a transition point.
That's why I'm saying it's so easy. It's so simple. It's stupid. It sounds ridiculous.
Right. It sounds it's not that I can't get away from temperature because they make it snow and
so really hard to get cold. Yeah. How are you going to do that? It's got to be 32 degrees
Fahrenheit. You have to understand the difference of potential taking place and taking advantage
of what you're doing. OK, weather work is no different than acupuncture. Right. OK,
what is acupuncture? Most acupuncturists can't even tell you what they're doing.
Well, I was going to say, I can't get an explanation. Yeah, I can't get an explanation
from somebody. Right. Basically, you're trying to get the energy around the body to zap down into
or do too much energy in one part of the body to go out into the atmosphere of the body. Everyone's
got an atmosphere. It's anywhere. It's over the surface of your skin and it can go out as far as
a couple of feet, a few inches usually. By the way, you can smell when you smell someone. That's
your you're in their atmosphere. Right. Think about it. You can change the atmosphere by putting on
a cologne. I mean, I'm talking about a literal atmosphere. You know how this was discovered by
Galvani? Well, like a field around somebody. Well, hold on. Galvani talked about all metals
that conduct electricity because of their atmosphere. And we're talking about old man
Galvani. These are non-academic people that are the, you know, like Faraday. Right. Galvani.
Right. Hertz. All these people, they were not scientists. So basically there's something
called galvanic reaction. When you put a piece of metal in your mouth and there's a saying like
chewing aluminum foil. Right. OK. Right. That's serious galvanic reaction. OK. You can take a
penny and put it on your tongue. Right. But take the penny and put it as close as possibly tongue
without touching it. You'll start tasting the penny. How's that possible? Well, you're in the
penny's atmosphere. By the way, the atmosphere is very, very thin. That's where electricity travels.
It doesn't travel in the metal at all. Right. And this was already known. This is what these
quantum physics are talking about now. And they're like, don't you read Galvani from like 200,
300 years ago? It gives you a big warning. Make sure you keep your mouth closed. If you're too
close to somebody, you might taste them. Yeah, there's several. Yeah. But anyway,
that's the idea. So back to the weather, it's like acupuncture. You're putting out a needle,
a metal. Right. It doesn't have to be OK. There are more advanced systems, more passive systems
that you can employ that are much slower working and they do not zap all the ether up. But there's
nothing more than a water gun, a basic Wilhelm. Right. Not the Wilhelm multiple tubes. You just
need a standard stove by four or six inches. I have an eight inch pipe that's 12 feet long.
So much is a little overkill. But, you know, sometimes you want overkill. Right.
Right. OK. So much like with with the acupuncture, the weather is the same kind
of thing where it's about taking where there's concentrations of the energy and either dissipating
those concentrations of energy or attracting them and gathering them together and sort of collecting.
OK, let me just give this a mysterious thing. Most if anyone's in the inventor's lounge that
actually might qualify is going to say, well, how can you do it very much if you're just
dissipating? Well, this is what happens. Let's say you want to build up instead of dissipate.
Right. OK. How do you do that? If the thing all it does is dissipate, how are you going to build up?
Right. You said you can do that. So how does it build? Oh, no. OK, well, now this is where you
need three sharpened pencils in your pocket with a pocket protector and a slide rule. Right. Can
you figure it out? Yes. This is how engineers think. Who are the ones that used to be on this planet?
The ether itself is a living organism. It's not, I wouldn't say fully sentient, but it exhibits
sentience intelligence. The weather exhibits all living things and things that support living
things have somewhat of a self-preservation. All living things, whether they appear to have a
brain or a neurological system or whatever, they have some sort of intelligence, even if it's
rudimentary. That leads to that will exhibit some sort of self-preservation. OK, so what
will happen is the ether sees that this thing is being swung around and dissipates it. So it
doesn't want to get into its field, into the business end. It wants to stay behind it.
So this is how you do it. Whether you're on the southern hemisphere, if you believe such a thing,
or the northern hemisphere, if you believe such a thing, the ether goes from west to east. OK,
so if you aim downwind, if you aim with the ether, remember, the ether is going from west to east.
So you aim east. So here comes the ether. It's all the way out here in the west, and it's going
towards the east, and it sees you, and you're aiming east. And you're like, oh, we better stop
right here and slow down, because if we keep moving east, we'll go above him, and then we'll
be in his target range. We don't want to do that. So what happens is, as you're aiming east, the
ether sees you're aiming east, and it starts slowing down and building up, and says, oh,
we've got to go around him. We don't want to get in front of that business end, because we're
going to dissipate. So it starts building up and building up. Now there are certain techniques
where you can move the thing and have more than one device, where you create a real big
buildup behind you, and any time you have a buildup of anything, blue balls, it has to release somehow.
Well, whether you dam the water or you get blue balls, eventually a release must come,
and when it does, it's going to be drastic. So what's going on here is this. When you hear about
weather events, that is the discharge part. That's the discharge. The tornado is not a weather
condition. It's a weather condition discharging. The conditions of the tornado are way before
tornado forms. You always want to be in the formative side of things. When it rains,
it's a discharge. Rain is a discharge. Tornado is a discharge. A hurricane is a discharge.
It's the end of the process. At the beginning of the process, you have a buildup, and then you're
kind of trapping it or damming it or keeping it contained for a moment, building it up.
So if it's raining and someone says, go ahead and stop the rain, well, you've got to wait for it to
stop for me to stop the rain, because it's already in discharge mode. It's in the middle of discharging.
Well, you can build up for the next time. Right. Yeah. Okay. Okay. So this is how these things
work. And one thing we do know for sure, there's no intelligent life in the Midwest.