Rated Y Sonic Event 217, now I made
a little mistake the first couple of days
when I posted 216 and didn't realize I
was posting the wrong one.
It's been corrected.
So if you think the 216 is, I
put up 215 again, it was a duplicate.
That's fine.
It's fine.
You know, we were just talking, by the
way, about whether devices are off and we
won't get wonky Sonics and, and I've had
people that are subs come over here and
see some of them we replicate.
And these are just hollow tubes with reflectors,
meaning like just makeup mirrors you buy at
the dollar store and a small nozzle of
water, let's say on a big water gun
or something, but passive, like primitive, you could
have built these 200 years ago.
Okay.
So you mean like those little mirrors that
come with the suction cup, that kind of
thing?
Yeah.
Or the compact mirrors, cause you need two
mirrors and all that to build a translator.
There's a certain specificity.
Okay.
I had never really got into the golden
mean ratio.
Like a real effective one is like 22
and a half inches and they use that.
You say you go above 22 and a
half and below two and a half using
the golden mean, discuss that with Trevor.
And we did experiments a while back and
we're talking like 2013, 14 and it didn't
really matter that much, but he said, do
it anyway.
But, you know, and I do, so that's
why when people said, how big is your
trend, the translators and I'm like, well, that
one's about nine and three quarter inches and
like, why not in three quarter?
Cause it's a factor of 22 and a
half.
So whatever.
So who was it had a song, my
big 10 inch, who was it?
It was Aerosmith.
I didn't have that one.
No.
Okay.
Look it up.
Anyway.
So what's interesting about it around 2003 or
so I was hanging out with some people
from Raytheon and a guy's making 450,000
a year salary in 2003 and he's drives
a 1989 Toyota Corolla with a broken air
conditioner and all four tires are different tires,
right?
Okay.
Yeah.
Cause here you need air.
Like even people that have, you know, they'll
buy a big borrow and steal just to
get their air conditioner fixed.
Cause the car is 150 degrees locked up,
right?
Depending on where you live.
I mean, you're, you're rolling around in a
heat box.
I mean, yeah.
So anyway, uh, he's passed away since then.
So I'm not going to mention his name,
Clifford Smith, but he passed away and, um,
did the guy with no name, Clifford Smith
die in the car?
No, no.
And, uh, I didn't mention his name.
How did you know his name?
I, I, I, so really the perks, I
said, so, you know, you get everything paid
for by them.
Yeah.
So roughly how much, you know, is your
total is about two and a half million
cause he, anything he wanted to buy, they
bought, right.
And it was, it was for experimenting and
stuff.
So he invited me to a group, a
party kind of thing.
All these are like the kind of to
a party full of people that you would
not invite to a party.
Just think about that for a minute.
And um, I've seen parties, people who are
no fun, don't really talk, just stand around
staring at each other.
Yeah.
And if you meet anyone that says they
work for Raytheon, you know, the missile company
and this aerospace Hughes and all that, and
they tell you they're an engineer, don't be
impressed because they have the dog is an
engineer.
The person working in the gift shop is
an engineer.
So anyway, um, let me, let me just
shorten this up without getting into too many
experiences.
So I saw him, I was building these
weather devices based on William, Mike, and half
of them looked at me and gave me
a bad stare and I said, what's up,
why, what is this?
Because I'll tell you, I'll tell you in
a minute.
So he takes me outside.
He says, you know, cause if a city
that had these devices would be impervious to
missile attack.
And I was like, what?
How can a hollow tube with, um, just
a spray water on one end or, you
know, foil and silk rotating.
And I didn't know about that at that
time, but a hollow tube with a, right,
basically a hollow to make a city impervious
to missile.
And then recently it hit me and they
would never tell me why, because the guidance
systems won't work.
Well, it relies on the ether, the guidance,
the radio, the radio guidance and all that
stuff.
So anyway, that's, what's always amazed me about
those things is like when people talk about
all of them, they got to shoot them
out of the sky, but, and they're talking
about it like, you know, you literally got
to like make contact and hit it with
a Patriot missile.
And I'm saying to myself, why not just
create a disruptive field that they can't navigate
through?
Well, it's, it's the military or is there,
okay, humans are morons and military is weaponized
moron, right?
Right.
So it's still more on the morons.
Um, like, you know, with McNamara, he was,
I think defense back in the day.
And later on, he gave, got a little
seat and I'll make it out to be
a McNamara.
I think it was McNamara.
He came out and said, uh, McNamara, I
sold, I actually saw him speak in, uh,
like 2001 at NYU.
Right.
And the thing is, he was actually pretty
well together still in 2001, but he was
a guy who ran Ford motor company.
Then he came and he ran, you know,
the Pentagon for Kennedy.
Yeah.
Right.
But he released this info on 2015.
So he might've gone see now by then,
but, but he said that basically the nuclear
launch codes for the U S the entire
arsenal back then during the cold war was
0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0.
And the reason why they did that, they
were supposed to change them every day and
scramble them and make them random numbers.
But they said the guys were so young
and dumb at the silos that it would
just confuse them.
And it would make the system ineffective if
they couldn't get the codes, right?
So they just kept them all at 0,
0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 8
zeros, right?
This is the U S military.
And, um, but it's, it fits the population
by the way.
I heard the same story.
I heard the same story once, except it
was, they, you know, they have like a
telephone phone, you know, like numbers.
And what you had to do is hit
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, all the way
to, and then hit zero is the last
one.
And then boom, that's the code.
And I said, you gotta be kidding me.
That's insane.
They're like, no, they taught him.
That's all you got to do.
You know how to count.
I didn't care years ago when someone just
gave him a bank card, right.
And my debit card.
So you need to say, just take my
debit card, go buy what you got to
go.
It's like, I knew someone just was having
a hard time, said, take this debit card,
just go get what you're going to get.
And I'm going to get a bank statement.
I know what you're going to buy, right?
So if you buy whatever, I know where
you want.
So I trust you.
And he says, well, give me the pin
number.
I said, just one, one, one, one, one.
Well, what's your, what's your pin number for
that one, one, one, one, one.
Everything was just pin number for me.
It was one, one, one, one.
You can't do that anymore.
I still try to do it.
He says, no, you can't do it.
They will not let you do a one,
one, one, one, one.
They won't allow it.
And you know what else they won't allow
is if you get a new card, you
can't give it the same pin number anymore.
It's like all these weird rules now where
even because they want to give them the
idea that they're, they're on, you know, they're
trying to look out for you, whether meanwhile,
no, well, they're not really screwing you over.
I want to get into a little bit
of that, but actually I brought up the
zero, zero, zero.
What did I mention before the nuclear McNamara,
right?
And the military and all this other stuff.
There was another place I wanted to go,
but let's not because it's really easy to
it's a, yeah, a chicken, Ella King, you
know, that's all I, that's all I got
to say.
And hot sauce.
So by the way, out in the field
with the people out in the field, in
the army, hot sauce is money.
Oh yeah.
It's my, these little Tabasco.
I don't know if they give them anymore
because the food is so bad or the
MREs that, you know, chicken, Ella King and
this and that up until the early two
thousands, they still had the little mini bottle
of, yes, hot sauce.
And you know, they even still had the
cigarettes in there up to like 2001, I
think.
Really?
Yeah.
I'm surprised.
Two cigarettes.
Was it three cigarettes at least?
No, it was two cigarettes and a book
of matches, two cigarettes and a book of
matches.
Every time.
World War II, they had three cigarettes because
that's what I need to wake up by
the way.
Well, you know what it is with these
people, you know, they always got to cut
it.
Yeah.
I need two cups of coffee and three
cigarettes and a couple of shots of kratom
powder and about a half hour and I'm
good to go.
It's just when I'm good to go, he'd
give a discussion I had with someone recently,
you know, about the state of the world
and all that.
I said, look, all I could tell you
is what I'm experiencing.
I'm in my 60th year and let's say
three quarters of my life.
If you judge that, you're going to go
with the longevity statistics, right?
So I'm past the three quarter mark or
well into the three quarter mark.
You could die tomorrow.
But let's just say and I'm three quarters
into this movie and this movie sucks to
think that it's going to get better in
the end.
You got to be an idiot, right?
It's a rare movie that really just all
of a sudden improves at the very end.
It doesn't do it.
So.
So what you do is like I told
someone, you know, you've been on this planet.
My latest thing is when I talk to
people and they give you that fluoride stare,
you know, and I like that.
I might steal that from you.
Yeah.
So I've seen it around for a while.
But yeah.
Give me this fluoride stare.
And I'm like, have you been on this
planet for more than a month?
Yeah, I've heard of the window licking gaze,
but not the fluorides there.
But go ahead, please.
Yeah.
And I get into it.
Have you been on this planet for more
than a month?
You know what's going on here, right?
And anyway, just I'm going to just bounce
around a lot of economic stuff.
Some people's minds because you're not going to
the last thing that government media church radio
is where they want to dumb you down
as much as possible because they've been getting
away with things for so long without, but
they're not getting away with it without you
being ignorant.
Like I said, it's, they're relying on the
people's ignorance and the people are very reliable,
right?
And it's a very weird situation right now
because I'm going to tell you something strange
and I don't want to just go to
finish this one point.
So we're talking about new cars.
I said, new car, don't buy a new
car.
You shouldn't buy anything that has a touch
screen in it.
So that would be like 2005 and before
is what you want.
Yeah.
2000 cause I know like 2005, six, seven,
all everything started getting a touch screen if
it was considered, you know, not the base
base model, but cameras, big visuals on the
GPS talking about how the car companies are
losing money.
I said, no, no, no, no.
Since 1933 if all the cars were given
away, the car companies would, would make more
money or just as much money as they're
making now.
But when you came to pick up your
free car, you signed your name on a
document and you took your car and you
left that.
They could take that document and go to
the federal reserve and pull whatever number they
put on.
They can get a million dollars a car
per person.
So the whole thing about the car company
is not making, cause they're connected with the
government, right?
Even when here's the other thing that it's
hard for people to understand negotiable, negotiable insurance.
If all the car companies in the world
gave away all their new cars, you know,
and the conditions were that when you go
to pick up your car, you sign a
document, just a little couple of paragraphs, they
can make tons of credit off of you.
Now you think that that will pay for
the car as if you were paying cash
because that's a cash value, but believe it
or not, when the, before the cars are
built, I mean, you know, the fax machines,
you know, are they, they roll so much
paper you get as it's printing and drops
on the floor into a box, you know,
you've seen that, right?
The printers, the old printers, right?
Yeah.
You used to have to put a box
under mine when I ran a different corporate
stores, when we communicated with them.
They had that thing.
You had to tear off the side.
Cause that's what the roller that held it
in there, you know?
Yep.
Okay.
So there's this thing called the manufacturer's certificate
of origin or manufacturer's statement of origin.
It looks like a birth certificate when that
is printed.
That is a banking instrument.
So all the VIN numbers for the cars
are printed before the cars are made.
And that is already payment that is cash.
So the car was paid for before it
was built and then you go to pick
it up and you sign for it free
and it's paid for again.
But here's the other kicker.
How did the cars get from the factory
or wherever they were to your neighborhood through
transport?
Yeah.
Okay.
Now, hold on.
They have something, the transport, they have a
manifest sheet, a bill of laden, right?
It's on the truck and the trucker signs
it and the receiver signs it.
That is a cash instrument.
So it's been paid for again.
Right.
So those cars...
So all the cars, even if you walked
in, in other words, in common idiocy, the
morons on this planet, if you told them,
go get a new car, all you got
to do is sign your name and you
get a new car.
They think it's a free car.
They don't know that it was paid for
before when, in other words, before it was
manufactured or during manufacturing that day with the,
with the document from the factory called an
MSO or MCO, it was paid for again.
In other words, cash was created to cover
its value when it was transported through the
bill of laden or manifest, and it was
paid for again when they gave it to
you thinking you got it for free.
So the car's been paid for three times.
So they can literally give, I can prove
this, everything, anyone who's done the financials, a
little bit of study or listen to some
of the people and check up on what
they're saying knows what I'm saying is 100
% correct.
So even if all the brand new cars
were given away for free, they've already been
paid for three times over.
Now this concept, this scenario is provable.
Any, anyone, any senior banker will tell you,
yeah, that's right.
That's right.
They won't give you details, but they won't
say you're full of shit.
Now below the senior debt banker, they'll tell
you you're full of shit, but everybody else
would tell you you're full of shit.
So how are you going to change anything?
I'm giving this as an example, right?
I'm giving this as an example.
I mean, I hope bread goes up to
a thousand dollars a loaf and I hope
your rent is 15,000 a month and
your gas bill is 30,000 a month,
right?
And I hope gasoline goes up to $300
a gallon, right?
Why?
Because it doesn't matter what number they attach
to it.
They've got everyone locked in, right?
Okay.
Here's another example.
The reason, okay, you pay, I'm just going
to give an example.
These things, everything I'm saying is not 100
% true.
It's a thousand percent true.
Okay.
Lock a rock solid.
But I'm giving this as an example of
what I'm saying, I'm going to stay in
the economic for a little while.
It has nothing to do with economics because
we could switch to any category and show
you how this information compared to what people
are talking about on all of the media,
all the universities and 99.99% of
the internet is a hundred percent relative bullshit.
And they're so deep into it.
They will never understand this.
I assure you never, never, ever, ever within
the ever they have left.
It's like I used to, uh, people close
to me or not when they don't get
something and then they get it like later,
like a month, a week, a year later,
I'm like, okay, do you think you're going
to live like 150 years to learn this
stuff?
You need to learn right away.
If you don't get it right away, drop
it.
You're wasting your time and go to something
that you can take right away cause you
don't have that much time, right?
I'll learn it eventually.
No, you won't.
What do you think?
First of all, let me sit you down.
Do you think you're going to learn this
eventually?
Uh, yeah.
You're going to live four or 500 years.
How long are you going to live?
Huh?
80, 70, whatever.
There's not enough time.
So that's, so here's the thing.
When I say never, these people are never
going to learn this or find out, even
find out about it within the ever they
have, if they lived a few up to
a thousand, there's a chance there might be
some instigation, but, and they would get it.
But here, now here's the thing.
So people have this thing called income tax.
You pay tax on the money you earn
and make, and then you go buy stuff
with the money that that you just pay
tax on, that you earn and make, and
you pay sales tax, you pay tax again,
right?
And then, wherever you live, even if you
have rent that's factored in, the money that
you- Property tax.
Worked, yeah, the money that you worked that
was taxed, is it taxed again when you
buy stuff, and taxed again where you live,
why?
And in the land you're going to collect
it.
And I'll tell you what the bullshit story
they're going to give you.
They're going to say, oh, because it's different
jurisdictions.
Bullshit, you know why it's the same entity
that's taxing you over and over with different
names, but it's the same entity.
Just like, for example, if you say, I
went to Kentucky Fried Chicken and ate today,
and I said, I went to Taco Bell
and ate today, and somebody else said, I
went to whatever.
You know, all of you, no matter where
you eat at these restaurants, all that money
centrally goes to PepsiCo.
Whether you hate Kentucky Fried Chicken and want
to only eat at Taco Bell, you're supporting
PepsiCo.
Whether you hate Taco Bell and just want
to eat Kentucky Fried Chicken, you support.
Okay, so it all goes to the same
place.
And you talk to any of these legal
morons about this, and they're going to say,
well, it's different jurisdictions.
Uh-uh.
Why is it not different jurisdictions?
It's all the same jurisdiction.
Why?
Because if it was a different jurisdiction, you
would be using a different currency every time.
Right.
It's the same jurisdiction because you're using U
.S. dollars.
It's bullshit.
And no one is...
By the way, anything that's in the Constitution,
the original Constitution, anything that comes after it
that's against what's in the Constitution is void.
That's where the injunctions.
You can do an injunction for taxes.
They will notice it.
Sometimes they send it back, you send it
again.
Right, they will acknowledge it.
And you will not do the tax thing.
And by the way, there's a...
If you get a passport, I haven't tried
this.
There's two ways to do it through the
State Department.
One is a passport card, and the other
one is a sales tax exemption.
I've sent the form to some people.
So you go to Walmart and they ring
up $100 and $131.
You give the passport card or the tax
exemption card, and they say the name of
the organization.
You give whatever name is on the card.
And they scan it, and then suddenly it
goes from $131, it goes down to 112.
They take the tax off.
It's good if you're buying cars.
It's good, well, whatever.
If it's close to 10%, you spend $10
,000 a year, you just saved $1,000.
You spent less.
You know, I hate it when they say
you saved the dollar.
Where did I save it?
Where is it?
No, you mean I spent less than less.
Okay, so the idiots here are never gonna
understand this, any, any, any of this.
Now, on both ends of what's going on.
Now, let's go into the medical, every aspect
of the medical.
You know why?
Let's not, because it's exactly the same.
If I tell you how the human...
Yes, I do know how the human body
works, and none of these doctors do.
Let me say that again, in case you
misheard me.
I know how the human body works, and
none of these doctors do, none.
You know why I say none?
Because once they find out how it works,
and they try to apply it, you know
what's gonna happen to them?
They're gonna get, first of all, from the
upper superiors, they're gonna say, you can't do
that, but we just want you to do
standard practice.
And this is our warning to you.
So that's why none of these doctors, and
I know it.
Yeah, you wanna take that however you wanna
take it.
Everything I said about the financial stuff, no
college professors know this.
You know why?
I know this for sure.
Because the moment they teach this, you know
what's gonna happen?
Mm-hmm, yeah.
Yeah, they're gonna come in the office, and
they're a little cubicle.
That's where they put people in cubicles, and
say, do you like your job here?
That's all they're gonna say.
Similar speech.
We have a practice here, you do that,
or you don't.
And you go, yeah.
Yeah, so you wanna talk about this, you
wanna talk about that.
It's all the same.
So let me just paraphrase and underscore.
I gave a more in-depth on what's
going on if the cars were given away,
brand new cars were given away free to
everyone, it's still paid for three times over.
As long as you sign in a pickup,
that's the third time it's fully paid for,
okay?
Do you think that anyone's gonna understand that?
I can prove this.
And actually, you can prove it so many
ways.
You could prove it with the acts and
the federal laws and the policies of the
banks.
You can prove it by subpoenaing and getting
what's called a GAAP.
Oh, a GAAP, G-A-A-P, which
any company that's public, these are public motor
companies, they, you could do a FOIA, you
could do FOIA with corporations that are public,
and you ask for the GAAP, which stands
for the General Accepted Accounting Principles.
They have to show you whatever books you
ask for.
Now, usually when you ask for it, they
just send you a bullshit thing.
But if you ask for this ledger and
that ledger, you gotta know what it is.
Do you wanna get into that?
No, we don't need to get into it
now.
But what I'm saying, this can be proven
so many different ways.
As a matter of fact, the bill of
laden when the cars are transported is insured,
not the cars.
The bill of laden is.
Okay, so anyway, anything we get into, we
can get into super detail.
I'm telling you, you are screwed.
If you were to play what I just
said on a megaphone to the public, I
wouldn't say this to the public.
All I would say to them is you're
all screwed, you morons.
I wouldn't give them any of this information
because they're gonna laugh at you.
And you don't throw pearls to swine.
And because if you throw pearls to swine,
you have to finish up, they will trample
you and tear you to pieces.
No one says that part, do they?
So good riddance to the general public in
this society.
Like I said, it's a big porcelain bowl.
And I don't know why anyone hasn't pulled
the chrome handle and flushed the whole thing
away because that's the status that it's in.
Does anyone ever walk into a bathroom when
someone forgot to flush a big honky number
two and say, how do we fix what's
in the bowl?
No, you don't wanna look at it and
you pull that goddamn handle and flush it
away, reset.
So that's where you are.
So the reason I'm saying this, it sounds
like a rant, I'm not ranting.
It's because you are in a place like
a bad movie wherever you are in your
life.
I adhere to this archaic stuff that we
got 15 years left for the infrastructure.
Doesn't mean 15 years left for everything, everything,
everything, earth will go on.
But the infrastructure, the grid, all that stuff,
government is infrastructure, none of that, right?
So I'm into that.
So wherever you are in your life, whether
you're 10% into that or 15, 20,
it's a shitty movie, a bad movie.
Don't lie, don't lie to yourself.
Now, here's the thing, it's not gonna get
better.
That's why I tell people, like I go
back earlier when I said, listen, have you
been on this planet for more than a
month?
And they're like, what?
So I'm like, yeah, of course.
I'm like, okay, do you know what's supposed
to do?
This is all full of deceit, corruption, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah.
This is a place where you come to
party, to have sex, to get high, to
get drunk, but you do it within a
moral, you have to pick a morality.
If you don't have a morality, that's fine
too.
It's gotta be fine, right?
Because you can't make anyone do that, right?
The consequences are there.
So I realized this recently, past few years,
is that this is a place to get
high, have sex, get drunk, party, have a
good time.
You don't believe it?
When you ask people, what do they remember
from going to college?
Beer and having party, blah, blah, blah.
That's what I remember from college, right?
Mostly, not everyone, but mostly.
And if you do remember anything they taught
you, dump it.
Dump it, it's bullshit.
So yeah, so you could say, I know
a guy that knows more about the human
body than any doctor or all the doctors
put together, right?
True.
So yeah, how many times can you say
that about anyone?
And you know what?
And I'm glad I could say that about
y'all if you heard me speak on
it.
So it's, yeah.
No, guaranteed by extension, we are all more
aware than what that doctor is right away.
Just, you know, it's under a vacuum.
I'm not harping on the doctors any more
than all the brand new cars should be
given away for free.
Okay, the reason why they have you pay
taxes is because when you work and put
equity and send it somewhere and you are
told what you need to send that in
order to support that, now you're invested in
it and you care about it.
So the more corrupt they are, the more
they tax you.
So you care more about it.
Where am I?
They say, I'm not paying tax, I don't
want to support the government.
If no one paid a tax ever, ever
again, the government would be just fine.
Not one penny of taxes ever gone to
any government for anything.
Not building bridges, not roads, not anything.
I just explained, the same way you buy
a car, the same way a construction company
builds a $10 billion road.
When they apply with a bid, the construction
company executive signature, they pay for the road
three times over.
Yeah, you don't have a government.
How many times did I say, there is
no government.
My gosh.
If you think there's a government, what do
you think's gonna happen when Halloween is over?
In other words, you think this guy's Count
Dracula because it's Halloween.
What are you gonna do tomorrow when it's
not Halloween?
What are you gonna do?
Today he's by Count Dracula.
Okay, so for the last whatever 90 years
or so, people think they have a government.
I'm telling you, you've been in Halloween for
90 years.
It's a masquerade.
No government at all.