Sonic Event 46, Ocelli in the Greek rated Y, and here we go. So, I'm just going to get
straight on to the chat stuff, but how are you doing tonight?
Hey, alright, 46. I have a bunch of stuff I wanted to relay also since I got a break
in my mental state from the past, let's say, six months of working on what I'm doing, so...
Has it been six months? Wow, it hasn't been six months of this? I didn't even realize.
Not this, other stuff, other stuff, too. Yeah, I know, uh, yeah, roughly, um, lawful time? Yeah,
yeah, definitely. Okay, no, I wasn't aware that it was... I was thinking that that other stuff
you were doing was only maybe two or three months, but... April. What they call March,
April. Right, okay. First, the beginning of the year. Yeah, it's stuff I want to relay,
and as time goes on, I relay more and more. It's, uh, yeah, well, I'll introduce it before
I talk about it. Yeah, you guys will like it. Okay, fair enough. So, yeah, let's go over to
the chat, though, real fast. I mean, I just got these things in because I said, hey, what have
we missed so far? Because there was a barrage there for a bit, so I figured I'll ask again,
just to remind myself, and I figure if somebody repeats it a couple of times, it must be a little
more on their mind, you know? Anyways, okay, so the first one comes up is a repeat of a question
from earlier, which is how to observe a day of atonement, and I think you already talked about
atonement, but what about a day of atonement? Is there... because I know that in some orders,
there's a holiday and this and that, and, you know, what do you got to say about that,
like how one observes a day of atonement? Yeah, well, there's instructions in Leviticus 23,
and just observing it that it exists is good enough, and then the instructions are there,
basically paraphrasing, you know, what the Jews do. I'm spelling Jews J-O-O-Z. I don't want to
get in trouble with the defamation league. Oh, big lightning strike. Okay, is no food,
no water from sundown to sundown, but we know the day starts at noon. I think at this point,
just acknowledging that it is the day is enough for me. You can be reflective. It's basically a
day, again, paraphrasing in the King James is to abstain, right? So that would be that,
and I can't really move forward any more other than what's in the text and what I do, and,
you know, right? The text says pretty much afflict yourself, you know, basically deny yourself of
things that you normally do, which could be pretty broad. Also take no food and no water. Some
might loosely be interpreted, but in the Jewish Judean tradition, no food, no water for 24 hours,
let's say, I just acknowledge the day. Sometimes I do that, though. Well, I also think it's healthy
on occasion, not necessarily based on what it is directed, you know, for a particular day,
but isn't it a healthy thing to do from now on, you know, from time to time to abstain a bit
and be reflective anyway? Yeah, I don't know. It depends on what you want to do with your health.
Yeah. Like if you're going to run a marathon tomorrow, which the marathon is never really
scheduled, but it could be you don't want to do that. No, of course not. I mean, you got to have
fuel in order to, you know, you got to you got to have things to work with if you're doing something
like that. But I'm saying from time to time, it's probably not a bad thing to pause in your regular
routines and be reflective anyway. I mean, that's just generally a good thing to do from time to
time. And fasting is not a bad thing at all. No, I mean, it depends on what your focus is on. If
the mind is really going, it doesn't need much until it's, you know, until it does. Right.
I mean, I I've gone eight hours sleep in a week and eight ounces of food in a week,
you know, and I didn't, you know, because I've been that wrapped up in what I was doing
cognitively. Fair enough. So it was also mentioned in the chat that you had mentioned
in an earlier sonic about an ethereal parasite detox. Now, I don't remember you wording it that
way. But, you know, from time to time, do I? Yeah. From time to time, though, there are ethereal
concerns. And I guess there are, well, presences, entities that could be considered parasites.
Good. I'm going to stop. Stop you right there. I don't recall ever writing that. Please,
someone bring it up. If I did. Yeah. Might have been the parallel me. Right.
Because I don't think there's such a thing as a detox, really. And but there are ethereal
parasites more in the mind parasite because ethereal go many ways, which I'll describe again
later. Let's mix that one for now. OK, no problem. But it is I think it's an interesting question.
Nonetheless, I just don't recall you bringing it up before. So anyway, they would also like to
hear about a return of Adam as spoken of in the biblical text. So what about that? Because we
talked about Adam, a sonic or two ago, and you had mentioned, you know, what that means or what
that could mean in general. Right. And I asked you about, well, what about this idea of combining
these existing creatures into something else and therefore creating another creature, which
seems to be the walking upright inhabitants currently walking around.
And, you know, we got into a conversation there. But what about that? What about the biblical
notion of this in the story, the return of Adam? I'm not there is nothing. Yeah,
there's nothing there. And about that. So that's a there's nothing in Scripture about
the return of Adam. And if I'm wrong, I'd like to please show me where it is.
OK, excellent. So there you go. We've covered the three things that I had
from the chat that I picked up really quickly. So you said you had a couple of things on your
mind, though, that you wanted to relate. So there you are. Yeah, a couple of things,
three things. First one's kind of heavy. The second one's kind of lighter. And the third
one's even heavier. OK, so let's do the cell phone thing and get to the most important part first.
Right. Like you said, get important. OK, the heaviest one would be, you know, I talk about
induction and all that. Right. Well, typically when you get into the biological side, you have
to use and it does work very much like the electrical metaphor of coils and capacitors.
Capacitors don't really induce. They charge and discharge. But if you don't know what a capacitor
is, you're a simpleton. You should just not be listening to Greek speak right now and go educate
yourself and then come back. And what a coil, a wound coil is the same. If you're not familiar
with these terms, you're you're too simple to really engage in what I get into because these
concepts are I give analogies for. And by the way, the reason I said it that way is because I have
run into a lot of people that will just, yes, you, yes, yes, yes. And they don't know what a
capacitor is. Right. Right. It's basically a battery, but it doesn't discharge slowly. It
discharges everything at once, kind of like me when I was 19. But anyway. So, yeah, what I would
suggest is the concept of induction. This is the most important part is this what inspired this was
I have the whole house wired with speakers and I play things in the background anywhere I'm
working or whatever I hear. So I had a look at what's the ugly fat man doing? Ken Wheeler put
him on and he was talking about dissectable capacitor, but he's not speaking of a dissectable
capacitor in the way that I've seen it. But similar is basically knocking the MIT guys for
not understanding what they're doing. But I want to get into what that is real quick.
And I think everyone here understands that nothing is absorbed. Nothing goes through any of the
tissue directly. Right. It's all has to go into energy. So if you have a salt intake in your body,
the salt has to go through the mouth, let's say, esophagus, stomach, duodenum,
and all that, and then go through the body through induction. The induction actually starts in the
mouth. And once it passes, let's say it's you know, they say digestion starts and with your saliva,
of course, that's why you should chew well, right? Right. So as you proceed all the way down to the
rectum, the parts of the salt, depending on which part of the body gets converted to pure energy,
well, actually, the salt goes from a solid to a liquid to a gas to energy through the wall as
energy. And it appears on the blood side, the inside of the body as energy first, then a gas,
then a liquid, then a solid. OK. OK. So this is how when someone tests blood, this is how when
someone tests blood and they detect like something like a salt level, it's because it was induced in
that way. It is not a direct transfer where it's so through a poor or something. Right.
It's not physical at all. Right. So let's go back to the concept of a dissectible capacitor,
a capacitor defined as it is, is basically a dielectric in the metal. So that's something
that conventionally conducts electricity and something that doesn't layered and somehow it
stores energy. OK. A dissectible capacity is a capacitor is something where you charge it and
then you can obviously see the discharge when you short it out. Right. Or discharge it. But
a dissectible capacitor, instead of after charging it, you instead of discharging it,
you dissect it very carefully. And the dissection, it's built in a way that you can take it apart.
In other words, separate the metal and nonmetal components where you don't discharge anything.
Right. And what's interesting. So if you a simple way to do this is take two aluminum
plates about the size of a square tile. You know, the commercial floor tiles, 12 by 12.
OK. Right. You know, you see at Walmart or everywhere, you know, take two aluminum plates
that size and a piece of mylar, which is like thin plastic sheet about the same size. Right.
So if you put the thin sheet of mylar between the two plates of aluminum and you put a circuit
across the aluminum, let's say 5000 volts, use an old neon sign power supply, by the way. Right.
It was really cheap. They kill you, by the way, if you're not careful because they're very strong.
Yeah. So you get this thing charged up and it just sits there. It's not doing anything.
But if you go to ground it, you see this big spark because you hit it with 5000 volts. Right.
So what you want to do in this case is put on some gloves, use some wood. Wood is a very good
insulator. Go ahead and charge the two aluminum plates with the mylar in the middle. Very carefully
lift up one of the plates, aluminum plates, and then carefully pull the mylar away. So instead
of it being a stack of aluminum, mylar and aluminum, you have the three things spread out
away from each other. Right. Now, go ahead and ground each piece independently with your ground
wire. Nothing happens. As a matter of fact, when you put as long as you separate the pieces,
you can do anything you want. You can put them in the dishwasher and run it through a full cycle,
each piece. But once you stack them again, as they were carefully and you touch them with a
ground wire, whether it's a minute later, a year later, five years later, a month later,
guess what happens when you restack them? Boom, you get a discharge just exactly almost identical
to the charging that you initially did before you dissected it. Pretty incredible, right?
Here's the interesting part. Most people would think that the charge is being held in the metal.
So here's what I was thinking. Yeah. It's actually being held in the mylar because what you do,
if you take those two aluminum plates, because when I say there's two places,
let's consider they're one thing because they're both the same, right? Okay. Go buy,
go buy a new piece of mylar, stick it in there. Nothing. Right. If you get two new aluminum
plates with the old mylar that's charged that you dissected without discharging,
put it between two new aluminum plates, boom, discharges. Okay. You know what's even more
interesting? I'm in Tucson, you're in Georgia, right? Yeah. Right. All right. I'm going to set
this up and I'm going to do the mylar, pull the mylar out. I'm going to put it in a postal tube,
you know, like a round poster tube, you know, and I'm going to mail it to you. Okay. I'm going to
mail it to you. And like a month after you get it, take it out and go get two aluminum plates
and stick everything together and ground it. Guess what happens? Boom, discharge.
Isn't that amazing? So it's like the mylar and the non-metal is holding this memory,
but it needs the metal to transfer it and ground it out. Now there's an old video,
I don't know if it's still up, Dissectible Capacitor. It's two like old ex hippies,
electronics guys on a bench. So the video is very grainy and they actually demonstrate everything I
just said. And it's very exciting when I talk about it, you can hear me be very excited about
it because it's repeated. Anyone can do it. The only time you really focus, if you, if you're
going to do an electrical discharge, it's nice to have a spark, right? Because any, this way,
everyone in the audience or everyone watching can see it. If you, if you charge it with a low
voltage, you're not, you need a meter, you know, and you'll see the meter bounce a little. It's
not very fun. You get sparks. It's easy to discern that something is happening. Yeah.
It's kind of like back in the old days when you're young and your older cousin, you know,
you, you pull a lawnmower, he says, hold onto this. And you're holding onto the spark plug.
Why are you pulling it? You know, he said, you don't know. Right. It feels like you got bit. It's
called like getting bit with a high spark. Okay. So this is what's going on. So let's go back to
induction because when a capacitor charges, it actually creates a discharging in a coil. And when
a coil charges, it actually creates a discharging in a capacitor. So that that's not the focus.
The body works on induction, more like a coil, but it also holds a charge. So how about this?
This is the most important part that I wanted to convey. And I've been thinking about this and
working on this for quite a while now, like more than a year. And now I'm getting into when I pass
the phase I'm in right now with supplying industrial stuff like I'm doing in water devices,
I'm going to start going back into this and I'm going to actually share it with people
and things they can do. Don't hold me to it. In other words, I might get too busy to
get because this is serious stuff and takes a lot of time. And Chuck, we've spoken off,
you know, the Sonics. And you see, when I get into something, it's it's not 100 percent,
it's 150 percent. Right. Right. So this is going to need 155 percent. So I'd like to just put this
out as a preempting to other people to get people ready. So we know since the body and I'm saying
this, we know not for plausible deniability, but there is no way that anything passes through the
body. It's all by induction. This is very easily established. It's just not talked about. It's
denied by the establishment. All right. So you have this charge, this induction that happens
in the midpoint between the transfer happens from inside to outside the body. Right. OK,
so now we have a dissectable capacitor. We can actually take a condition,
biological condition, whether it's health, disease, sickness or nutrition.
Right. Forward bias, if you remember how we talked about forward biasing the silver,
someone said, what about silver coins in water? Isn't that enough? Well, the silver coin has a
atmosphere around it and you want to push it off with a little bit of electricity into the water.
And then you see a bias, just like a tape recorder. You have a forward bias. Right. You need
a little bit just to get that tape going. Right. Just for that energetic transfer. It needs that
bit of forward bias, a little push using energy. So you have all of these other things that we
describe, which are actually physical conditions and nutrition or nutrients and what gives things
its quality. Like, for example, I say nutrients. Let's say you've got a loaf of bread and a bowl
of spinach and some milk. Each one has a different nutritional value in reality in terms of vitality.
Right. One will do this. One will do like if you want to gain 50 pounds in a month,
eat a whole loaf of bread before you go to sleep, eat a whole loaf of bread and go immediately to
sleep. I assure you, you're going to gain anywhere between 30 to 50 pounds in a month.
That's how actors do it when they have to gain weight for a role. Right. Right. If you want
to feel depressed, go ahead and drink a quart of milk a day. Dairy is depressive. That's that's
something that you agree. These are just generalities. And the spinach, you get that
gritty feeling on your teeth. Like, honey, did you watch the spinach? Well, my teeth are really
that's oxalic acid. Right. OK. So that's why you always have spinach with dairy. You ever notice
a lot of spinach dishes have dairy cheese mixed with cheese or butter?
OK, so these are three different examples. So now we know that you have back to the
dissectible capacitor. You have metal and nonmetal. Right. To make the capacitor. Remember, I said it
was milder. It could have been paper. But you don't want to use paper because it absorbs humidity.
Right. Changes. Right. But plastic or whatever leather, you know, if that absorbs humidity,
something oily would work well. OK, so you need to make the capacitor. You make a metal
sandwich basically. Right. The metal on the outside and the nonmetal on the inside. Right.
And the outside of the metal, the two metal plates, one is positive, one is negative. Right.
And what holds the charge is the nonmetal. Let me ask you, is milk metal or nonmetal?
Nonmetal. Well, it's nonmetal. Yeah. I mean, I'm like thinking there. Wait a minute. There's no
metal. No, it shouldn't be. Should not be. Actually, remember the cereal that you have
seen the YouTube's with the magnet with the breakfast cereal and it moves towards the magnet.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. I've seen that before. Yeah. OK. All right. So then you've got bread. Is that metal
or nonmetal? It should not have metal in it. Exactly. Spinach and metal or nonmetal. OK.
So all these nutritive things are nonmetal items. Make a metal sandwich forward, biased it into
the body. Guess what happens? That's all I'm going to say. We'll take it forward later. How
do you get it to the body? Because the body accepts the charge. Right. And here's the interesting
thing. If I accept the charge in Tucson in my body, I could walk over no matter where I walk
until I discharge that. Right. I'm going to be holding that charge. Oh, that's like the trick
with the static electricity, that kind of thing. Yeah. To the capacitor. Yeah. Dissected. You know,
if I take the capacitor apart without shorting it out, I could mail you the pieces and you could
put them together and you'll get the spark. Right. Right. As long as you put them together like
they were initially. OK. It's very cool, isn't it? That's it. I've never thought of it this way.
It's a wild thought. Yeah. It's really low tech stuff. You couldn't get any more low tech than
this. Well, yeah, but it's never the way you're taught about these things, though. You know,
it's never what you generally observe when somebody explains, you know, even how to deal
with a battery or whatever. You don't hear about it this way. Well, if they didn't teach you,
I guess then those that are supposed to be teaching you don't have your best interest in
mind, then do they? That seems to be the point here. Yeah. OK. So that was the important part.
I gave that first and it was rather lengthy, but I'm glad we got that out because this is what I
would say I'm looking forward to working on. Right. How do we mimic biological induction?
Very simply. Right. OK. And that's all I'm going to say right now. There's a lot more I can do. I
might do some solos with it as it goes on, but I'll always bring it back. Great. I mean, back
to what we can do here. Right. So, OK, the SEC, let's go back. Let's go back to the first thing
I wanted to say. OK. It's sort of this is going to sound like science, but it's not. OK. You know,
when we look at things you're taught in chemistry in school and the periodic table of elements,
you have elements. And the reason they call them elements is because they're pure and they don't
change and they define what they are by being what they are. Like hydrogen is a first element,
then helium and lithium. Right. OK. And the reason it's called an element is because it's not mixed
with anything. It's unique. Yeah. It just is what it is. Unique. Right. Right. OK. Well,
on one hand, you have this thing where you have these alchemists supposedly that take
base metals and turn them into noble materials. Actually, that's the you very rarely find that
the alchemic thing is to take base metal and turn it into a noble metal, you know,
lead to gold. It's always taking base metals and turning them into a more noble things.
It could be gases and other. But anyway, let's just say you've heard of turning lead to gold,
taking base metal and turning it. You know, iron goes to platinum, right? Copper goes to gold.
OK. This is the alchemic thing. Now, the alchemic thing is to change something that is very unique
into something else that is very unique. So lead is an element. And alchemists would take the lead,
which is known as lead. And it's an element because it's unique to itself being lead as
an element. Take that and then change it to another element. Right. OK. So this is the
premise of what not the last sonic, but the previous sonic. You know, I kind of laid into
what spiritual is and what it is and how simple it was. And you cannot discuss that without just
like it's like a wet newspaper across the head. It's the only way to deliver something like that,
because everything is spiritual, right? Unless you're laying down in a sleep or in a coma,
if you're not behaving, not talking, not thinking, there's nothing spiritual. The moment there's any
movement, behavior, expression, communication, anything, it's all spiritual because it's of
the mind. Right. Pretty much the way I see it is the moment that there is animation. Yeah,
that's it. Yeah. We basically broke it down to what it really is. So when there's spiritual
discussion, if you're having if you're asking that, it's kind of like, can I ask you a question?
You just did. Right. Kind of like that. Right. So any discussion is a spiritual discussion. So
one thing in the definition of the spirit that I've been getting into is that other unlike the
soul, which everyone shares, it's the metabolism. You can you know, the soul is your metabolism.
So, you know, if you can't breathe, someone administers CPR resuscitation, they're putting
their soul into your body until you carry on with your own soul. Right. Okay. So it's
interchangeable. Most things in mammals, let's say, and others, let's say is simple. I don't
know if you should try resuscitating a fish. I've been using a lot of fish analogies lately,
but I don't know if I've ever seen or heard of that before. But, you know,
I can make a really bad lascivious joke on that one, but I won't. Okay. Okay. So
the soul is more common to the metabolism. Right. But the spirit is what do I always say?
And what can be said is the spirit is what makes you you sort of like an element. Everyone is
different. Everyone is you. Even the people that look alike, it might be like they're still
very distinct. Nature abhors carbon copies. Even with a clone, there'll be a distinct difference
of some kind. Right. So even when you see identical twins, there's always a divergence.
Yeah. Yeah. And that's, again, a very strong spiritual connection. When one dies,
the other one feels it. Or when one is happy, the other one feels it. When one's sad, the other one
feels it. Right. Right. Okay. So what's cool is I know some identical twins. One guy lost his
driver's license from drunk driving, and he needed to use the car. He just uses his identical twin's
driver's license, same birthday, same face. Yeah, as long as they don't fingerprint them,
we're fine. See, there you go. The fingerprints don't match, though.
Yeah, they might. You could always argue that fingerprints are only good for one out of 400,000.
Yeah, I know. That's another whole thing. I know. That's just I think the number I heard. But you
know, I don't know if it's that extreme, but I do know that it's not as reliable as people
think it is. But I just used it as DNA. We all have the same DNA. Right. So the interesting point
here is going back to the element, the spirit is you're you are in a spiritual sense, you are
elemental to yourself. It's not like you're all this hydrogen, all these other things,
you see periodic table, you are you elemental to yourself. You're very unique. There's only
one of you. I'm not trying to be airy, fairy, happy, clappy. I'm saying you are you in the
truest sense, very unique being like an element. So when someone is to perform alchemy, they would
actually work on changing their spirit, because your spirit is what defines you. So when you do a
spiritual change, it's actually a form of alchemy. That's why it's so hard for people to change.
Because they there's the view themselves, you know, for the better or the worse,
actually, it's easier to corrupt someone than to make someone corrupt, not be corrupt, right. So
it's true. Also, with if you have, let's say something that's pure, it's easy to make it
impure. And then if you want to make it pure, again, go ahead, it's real hard, even with water,
right? It's difficult to get the impurities out. Yeah, it's always more difficult in that direction,
going from impure to pure. So there's many people that say they want to be better, they want to do
things better. And when they're shown the they kind of resist it, because they're not capable
or not aware of the alchemical changes need to be made to themselves. Because changing yourself is
literally an alchemic process, no different than changing lead to gold. Well, and you can see that
because it just changing your attitude, as we talked about during the emo discussions, right,
just changing your attitude. What's that behavior? That's the behavior aspect. Yeah. But behaviorally,
just by changing your posture by changing the way you decide to carry yourself the way you dress,
these things can change your attitude, which changes your actions, so on and so forth. The
domino effect, right? Of sorts. Sort of, but I'm saying that when you change yourself,
give you an example. When I found out everything, I knew everything was fictional.
And I really did not want to be the person that I was three decades ago.
I had a box of my memorabilia, I just took it all through it in the garbage baby pictures,
they know certificates, memorabilia, love letters from you know, whatever. So this isn't me.
Because when I got all this stuff, I was believing that this world was real.
Or what they were telling me was true. You see? Yeah, when I see an artifact from earlier part of
my life, which is a rare thing for me, but when I do see an artifact from an earlier part of my
life, I am very disconnected from it. Because I don't recognize who I was at that point. Because
I, I change. Yeah, exactly. But these are things you can do, just like someone would do a certain
process, you know, when they bring out, they have to make a certain fire or crucible, it has to go
through this, you know, acid first, and then cooked at this temperature to turn to gold, right? You
see this in the movies is the Hollywood version of that doesn't really go to gold. Okay, so
that's why they promote it in the Hollywood version. So So this is an interesting thing. So
a personal alchemy. So, you know, this is have you, I don't this is not I looked around for there's
none of this, this kind of talk doesn't exist. By the way, I looked around a little bit on the
internet the other day for this, right? Yeah, something along the speech to see if anyone so
now we're now we're putting down traces for plowing on new ground, right? So I just wanted
to put that out. Let's get to the second and last thing if you're not confused by now, right? We're
going to the second and last thing. And then second and last thing was, was the second one
kind of third, actually, because you started with the discussion about the battery in the third,
which was the last I started with the last thing that we went to the first now we're going to the
second Oh, excellent. Important. Yeah, there you go. So there's something called, you know,
the for people do castaneda and whatever, the recapitulation and in the castaneda writings,
from Don Juan, it's they had this exercise where you you put out some time and you go and rip
recapitulate bring back in memory, not just in memory, but the feelings and everything,
basically the email of past experiences and work them through work them out. And I've discussed
through Greek speak how that happens anyway. Can I just ask you about a term here? Because
you use the term recapitulate. And that sounds a bit wishy washy and complex to me because
yeah, it just means go back and remember, go back and remember. Okay, because it sounds to me more
like go back and give up. You know, yeah. Did I say recapitulate? Yeah. But maybe I'm not using
the right word. I just did. That's what it did. That's how it struck my ears. It sounds like to
give up again. Yeah, to go back and work things through. Okay, now he does it basically, you do
this at some point in your life, you make a box, you spend hours in it for days and weeks or
in a tree or whatever. I'm like, no, no, no, no. Okay. You do it every day. You do it every day.
When you start becoming aware that the spirit is something that can be worked out and made stronger,
just like when did you discover that if you go to the gym and work out or do exercise,
your body will get stronger, right? Well, we talked about this when we discuss muscle memory,
basically, that if you do something in a ritualistic way, if you do something religiously,
okay, it becomes an automatic and therefore doesn't require a lot of forethought and etc.
So we Yeah, we went through this. Sure.
But the discovery of it ritualistic way is, you know, like, rituals are spiritual algorithms.
Just define them that way. Green Greek speak definition. Well, true. But even going to the
gym on a daily basis or on a, you know, every other day basis that becomes religious. Yeah,
because something a ritual ritual would be a spiritual algorithm, like an algorithm would be
for, you know, in a logic sense. Okay. In other words, if you don't do the ritual, right,
or pronounce something wrong in a grimoire doesn't work, right? It's an algorithm, just like if you
punch code in the computer out wrong, one, you know, the wrong space, or the right, it won't
work. Gotcha. So ritualistic is specific, religious is just repetitive, and therefore,
okay, routine, routine, religion, religion is routine, by the way, look at people go to church
on Sunday, right? Yeah, routine. Yeah. Okay. So what I'm suggesting is at the end of the day,
before you sleep, or even not before you sleep, as you're winding down, think of the entire day,
since you woke up and more of the prominent things, why? And do this every day. The reason
why is you'll start picking up all of the influences that you didn't notice you, you
recapitulate or remember each day, all of the things that you may be too busy to focus on other
things, they will come to you. And you will start seeing patterns, maybe there was thoughts in your
head, that you will pick up were not yours. And what was right, you'll see weird synchronicities
that you normally wouldn't pick up. And then you start seeing these patterns. And then you start to
see what spiritual influences are happening in your, in your life on a day to day basis,
non physical ones, as well as the physical ones. By the way, this is how you learn,
like the mailman always comes in between one and 3pm. Right? You learn that by remembering it,
right? Right. So, so these things, you do them with your life, do them every day. It doesn't
mean that right before you go to bed, but towards the end of the day, think of your day and in not
about what necessarily you did, but what happened, what occurred, what you were involved in,
and start adding those up. And you will start to see patterns and influences much more clearly.
And then that was the second thing.
Well, and then that'll allow you to anticipate those things to like you said, with the mailman,
because okay, the way I handled the mailman is I know by a certain time of day on the clock,
it's a good time to go check the mail because it's likely to be there.
You know, I could tell you how the way my ex girlfriend handled the mailman,
but that wouldn't be right. Well, you know, look, I don't want to hear about your heartbreak today.
I never had, you know, these things are like ripe and fertile for coffee. Of course they are. No,
I look, you know, it's just, it's just like, look, I'm very sure that you look like the mailman
because that's just the way your mom was. I know it's okay. You know, you can, you can do it that
way too. This is very right. Yeah. Any, any conversation can be right in any direction,
usually, but the lascivious part is just too easy sometimes. I wonder if that's more of an,
is that more of an East coast thing? You think I really wonder about the personal choice thing
because a lot of the jokes, you know, you, the, the witnessing with Eddie Murphy in the eighties,
everything went like, you know, it was very, that shock culture came out before that it was
George Carlin or whatever. George Carlin was shocking in the sixties, right? You know what
I mean? He's mild compared to other things. So it goes back and forth. It's a personal choice,
but here's the thing. Let me just jump back to Castaneda. The reason why he suggested the
recapitulation is that way. He suggests that it frees you because what you're basically doing is
you hear like a near death experience. Life flashes before you write your entire life. Essentially,
that's what you're doing because that's what you're here for. So pretty much download or upload all of
your life experiences to a being he calls the Eagle that takes that and thrives on that. But
if you're already recapitulated everything and you don't have that experience when you die,
he lets you go and you move on to being in a higher space, right? That's the reason that
they give from the tall tech tradition. Well, it doesn't almost anyone who's aware that they are,
you know, at the end of life. I mean, pretty much I've never known anyone who didn't reflect
on something if they were aware that, you know, without the, without the case of sudden death,
you know, something totally unexpected car crashes kind of thing. Sure. But the custom
native point was that, that, that commonality of recapitulating and having your whole life
before you before you pass is not a normal function. It's a function of another being
that comes and gets you that he was here to pick that up when you pass,
and it's extracting it from you. So if you're already have extracted perform that
you're free from that being at the point of death, and you can move on without being under its
hold, let's say or control. So that's separation. Yeah, I'm sorry,
that's separation. You don't think it's metaphoric, and therefore also a part of the being
it is a separate being feeds off of that, just like we are in a being where the earth is in a
track. For example, let me just suggest it like this. The earth where it is in orbit is in an
orbit where another world is here. It's a non physical world. And when the earth came here,
and it's in the orbit or in the zone or in the area of this other non physical world, it doesn't
because it's not physical, it doesn't mind the physical intrusion, but it sees all of our energy.
So it's kind of like imagine Las Vegas in the 50s. And while Las Vegas looks now when the
earth showed up, it got really colorful for these other beings. And they're the ones that put
things in your head, by the way, in the right, they're very evolved,
by the way, non physical. So So this is like the the conversations to be had
in many, many ways that we can't really say are for sure. But they're wonderful to think about
if you have a way to, let's say work around them in your own way, to maintain your strength and
sanity here. I mentioned, these are broadcast tomatoes, I've been listening to a lot of this
stuff. And it's like, it sounds just like Greek speak. And this was mentioned, I've never read
it. And it's been was mentioned to me people that were into it in the 80s. And they would bring up
metaphors. And that sounds pretty like some wisdom, whatever, but, but it's Toltec shamanism,
basically. And I suggest that doing it on a daily basis will benefit you more on little steps,
right, like grains of sand in an hourglass instead of a shovel of sand in the end, you know what I
mean? And that's was that's, the first part was the alchemic nature of the spirit and how why it's
so difficult for people to change. It's like changing lead to gold. It requires an alchemist
to be an alchemist with your spirit, you can actually do it. And for the betterment, right?
So in other words, if you find that very often, I hear people say, I'm not good at math, right?
I'm like, good, that's great. I thank you for telling me now I'm going to remember remind you,
now you know what to work on, because most people go through their whole life like that, right? I'm
not good at math. So everyone pats him on the back, that's okay. But when you tell me you're
not good at something, I said, Oh, is it right if I remind you that you should be working on that?
Now you know what to work on? How can you be bored? I think you brought up being bored or
something. Yeah. You know, I know to work on now why? Why would I do that? Oh, the Greeks are real
asshole. He makes me want to work on math. And I told him I wasn't good at math. No. The point
here is this, it's an indirect way to say that if you actually take your what you admit to be a
weakness, and work on it, so it's no longer a weakness, I didn't say make it a strength,
no longer a weakness, what do you think it's going to do in terms of technique and abilities
for the things that you consider yourself to be already strong in? It'll make you what even
stronger, right? So you learn new ways, right? And also gets rid of spiritual emotional laziness.
So I just wanted to throw those things out there. And the second thing was the room at the end of
the day, rehash your day, and you'll see patterns and non physical influences very clearly,
more clearly as you do it. And the third thing was, let's start working on real induction
in a very simple fashion. Now with those non physical, you know, interactions that we're
talking about here, is there a possibility that in some cases you get induction in that way?
I mean, where you certainly have energetic? Yeah, it's non physical. Yeah, it's non physical.
Because let's go back to the analogy that I always gave you look at the intestines,
nothing penetrates through that they should do cross section of the intestines or any of the
tissues, lungs, skin, whatever, do cross split the computer screen or whatever and do a cross
section of a steel belted radial tire, they're the same. In other words, they're two,
you structurally, they're the same, you know, what is it? What is the purpose of an automotive tire?
For the inner environment, not to call us with the outer environment, right? Because if it doesn't,
you have a flat, right? Yeah, it doesn't work. So it's structurally set up to separate the two
using pressure, and the same with the human body. So how do you have the interaction
by induction goes from solid, to liquid, to gas to energy back in reverse on the inside of the
body and in reverse, when the body wants to get rid of something, it turns into energy,
right? solid liquid gas into the bladder into the kidney into certain ducts into the sweat
into the skin, right? Okay. So that's, that's basically the premise is this, this, this
interaction.