Event number 33 in the Sonic Listings on Ocelli and the Greek Rated Y, so here we are.
And let's begin where we started before we started recording real fast. Greek, you know,
people occasionally get intimidated by some people's presence. And I was sharing with you
just before we went to air and you said I should be recording this. So here we go.
I have two odd reactions with people in person, and it's totally different from what they get off
me this way, you know, through the recordings. If you've never met me, never been face to face
with me, never been in the same room with me, they have one impression of me, and it's usually not
very accurate. It's very interesting, the ideas people have about me. But when people get around
me in person, one of two things seems to happen. Either I'm a very, very heavy, like deep dark
sort of presence, almost foreboding, or I'm unnoticeable. I seem to slip in and out and like
I'm invisible to them emotionally, like I don't shake up a room or I'm a heavy presence,
one or the other. It's these two weird extremes. And you were talking about because I mentioned
to you that somebody emailed me that said that they were a little intimidated by you.
They didn't say that directly, but that's what I gathered from what they were saying.
And they didn't want me to pass along the email to you, but gave me permission to talk about it on
Sonic. So we'll get into that in a minute. But what about that, you know, being in person with
somebody and picking up something like that? What does that indicate? What do you have to
say about that? In person, I want to just deal with the first part, when you're through the
Sonics. What's interesting about technology, you know, remember the old rabbit ear TVs,
you're not getting the image, you got to start playing with it, right? So you can actually
using technology, even like before the technology of the written word, when people were pen pals,
they fell in love and they made each other and they're like, Oh, you're nothing like the letters,
right? Because it's technology or you can tweak your persona with technology, right?
So that's the first part. Oh, this is true. And I've met people in person that I've encountered,
you know, doing shows and things. And they do look a little different. They do feel a little
different. They sound generally the same, right? The technology is a filter. And let's go back,
forget about the computers. Back when people used to write letters to each other,
the pen pal thing, remember? Or even the telephone. I remember the telephone. Yeah,
there you go. It's technology. You and I are old enough that there was a point in time when
people would meet and somehow you'd end up like in a telephone conversation with a girl or something
for a little while. I mean, as teenagers, did you ever have that experience?
Yeah. Like, you know, you got a friend. Okay. So the friend's trying to hook up with this girl.
He's over your house. He's talking to the girl over the phone and she goes, Hey, look,
I'm here with my friend. Do you have a friend there? And all of a sudden you get introduced
to friends. This, by the way, is a weird thing because this is how I'm told my parents actually
met each other. And I met a couple of the girlfriends, you know, in my early teenage years,
exactly that way where it was like I got a telephone handed to me and then started a
conversation with somebody I didn't know. Pleasant voice went with it. Definitely created a picture
of who they were in my mind that hardly ever really totally matched exactly who I met.
I mean, it was close, but never exact. You know what I mean? And I would go off of some of what
they described themselves as, which is part of the projection, the intentional part that they put out.
And this is with a phone, by the way, not with a computer, but I mean, just with a telephone alone,
right? You could have impressions. And then what your mind does with them
is another issue. And what your emotions do with it on top of that, by interpreting what your
mind has decided is the picture is the image is the experience, right? Or reading what the other
people have. I'll say this humbly. I've always whenever I met women, they were always like,
oh, hello, right? It's like, come over and meet this guy or whatever. And I'm like, they're like,
okay. And they see me like, oh, hello, you know, so I've always had women being attracted to me.
So it's kind of an unfair advantage in that respect on that side. And on the on the on the
other race, because there's two races, male and female, right, man and woman. It's, it's where
the more of the dynamics are based on what you were saying, you're invisible, or you're, or they
see you as being heavy or something like that. But well, that's, that's the weird thing, too,
is with the opposite sex, because I was going with everybody overall, with the overall impression
about when they meet me in person, with the opposite sex, I would tell you that women to one
of two extreme reactions, right? Either and who cares? Or Wow, the Hello, usually, it would be
focused on Oh, you have, you know, beautiful blue eyes, because I have an unusual color blue eyes,
because of my, my, my condition, right? Because I'm lacking pigment in my eyes. So it's a weird
color blue. It's an odd sort of color blue, or it's just, yeah, not blue. Yeah, I don't trust
the scientific reasoning anymore, by the way. But it's good to mention is allegedly allegedly,
but here, here, let's, let's, I feel like we're going a little wonky. So what's interesting about
it is, look at the intelligence operatives perspective on the on that, because the email,
there's a lot of talk about the email, I want to say a few things about it, maybe.
When you're an intelligence operative, and you want to go check out another society,
you become a bartender, taxi driver, or homeless person, vagabond looking Why? Because those people
are generally those that's the two first two are service industry that are no one pays attention to.
And the third one is a aspect or rank in society that no one pays attention to.
So actually not being paid attention to is the best way for the one who is not being
attention to be paid attention to to collect as much as they want, if they can. Well,
that's what they do. Yeah, because people would relax. Look, a homeless guy. Okay,
it's just a homeless guy. He happens to be around. So no matter what you're doing,
it just you know, it's a matter of proximity. Yeah, I've done that. And there's you're completely
invisible. There are people. There's a woman and a man ready to cross the street. And I'm standing
there looking homeless. And she's like, you know, you can't just push it in so hard. You got to wait
for me to adjust my diaphragm. You know, it's like, that's not really good, you know, to do
that. Just like, you know, I'm like, Oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh. You know, this is back in the days
when we use diaphragms, right? So who cares if the homeless guy hears this? Yeah, no, it's like,
oh, my gosh. And then the next, you know, few hours or so I start hearing conversations about
like the deepest, most personal stuff, financial stuff. You know, what they're going to do,
personal stuff, family stuff, business stuff. Oh, my gosh, even on the telephone on the cell phone,
right? Super private cell phone conversation. No, not if a homeless guy is there. It's still
in other words, it's still super private for them, but you know, so it's look at it that way.
It doesn't matter what they think. It's what you think based on what you think. In other words,
you know, I always say people look for approval, right? Okay. All right. So why do some people,
if I never wonder what someone else was wondering about you, it's always from the
perspective of what you want to get out of the situation, what you see the situation as being.
And like I've said before, if you go into any group of people, which is two or more
and you're not in control, guess what? That situation is out of control because people
don't know anything there. In other words, they're unlawful. They're as seen, listen to them
speak. Every word, every thought is as seen on TV, right? But their behavior will adjust based
on how they interpret you to be there. Cause like you're saying, I mean the old,
what is the old expression? Blending in, right? You go somewhere, you blend in,
you don't stand out. Then therefore you're not a factor. So their behaviors are unaffected.
If you project that, if that's the thing that you're projecting, right? So doesn't this have
to do with the emo when you're projecting, you know, you're sort of, you know, could be easily
misunderstood. Um, the emo could be misunderstood. The emo is not something on its own.
It's something that we have that here. The first thing I talk about when I introduced the emo is
the thing to really lean on. They try to give us reasons for all these things, these aspects,
senses, and things that we have about our ourselves. Right. But they never address
them. Meaning the authority of the people who were supposedly, right. They never address why
we have emotions. Never, never, ever. But we've always find out that the emotions are the strongest
drive or impetus or catalyst or change that anyone can have in their life. The example I give is the
mild mannered guy winds up shooting everybody at work. Is it never, no one would have ever expected
that it was emotional that drove them to do it, right? There's other things too, but the emo then
connects to the inner voice, which is not you, which I keep talking about, right? Which is another
entity. So all these things tie in. It's not, people are trying to still, I noticed in the chat,
tie the emo to other things that we see in scripture that they see in memorialized and
from ancient times. By the way, I just want to throw this out. Someone put a thing about the
evil eye and it has nothing to do with the emo. The evil eye was the eye of God. It was also,
it's a part of the crossing, the crossing. Archaics talks about that a lot. Jason Breshears,
the Phoenix phenomenon, right? The, the, everything, all the planets go from east to west.
I was been aware of this for, since the eighties, but I never got into it. I'm glad he has,
because if I want to listen to something on the internet, I'll put him on in the background,
see what kind of, because I'm a history buff. People who remember me from the days of,
with Seth Michael in 2010, a revolution radio, I was always saying, you want a new idea,
go to an old book. You got to look at the old books before 18, before 20th century.
Breshears is saying the same thing. His whole thing that I thank him a lot for is the 138
Phoenix cycle, right? Sometimes it's bad. Sometimes it's not so bad. And the 552 cycle
and all that. So all those ancient things, if you see something round and it brings bad
in ancient times, it's the crossing. It's what I mean by the crossing is we see all the planets
and stars have gone on the ecliptic. They go east to west, east to west, east to west.
Well, the crossing means you have an object coming from north to south crossing it, right?
That's what the sun disc, the cross was that the right, that the ancients use,
sort of like the crucifix, it's the cry. And when that comes, it's always bad.
Always. Well, that's why the sacred cross is a constant disruptor in ancient scripture,
ancient scriptures and symbology. The, the cross itself, not the, you know,
the crucifix symbology. No, no. Well, that's the symbology that we use around, but they,
they just overlap it. Right. Well, before that, the X, so to speak, where you have
it's the cross. So, right. Yeah. And it says it goes like the evil light goes back 5,000 years.
Well, he, guess what? Another thing this person posted also is about the, I do appreciate their
postings by the way, about old texts. And I've never said it this way before, but this is my
mindset from the beginning for three decades. Now, every ancient text that's out there that
you have access to, right. Check it out, check it out. Right. And the second, first thing is
check it out. Just get familiar with it. Even if it's not interesting, get familiar with it.
Cause it'll come up again. You'll see things that are used from it. Right. That are never given
credit. Right. The second thing you have to, whenever you see an old text, any old text,
biblical, any, any, any, any, any culture, any culture in the world at any time, that's old.
When I say old, more than 150 years old now. Right. Why are they letting it in public?
Hmm. Why? Because 99% of all the ancient texts are hidden. So more than 99%. Right. Right. So,
you know, I say we found this ancient text. What are you talking about? There are perfect records.
I mean, not even a crease on the page from 5,000 years ago that still exist.
If you, if you saw it, it would look like it was written a month ago.
Right. That are preserved that, that carefully, not on the surface though.
Hmm. Not for you. Right. So anything that's old, anything, you know, here's the thing. You want to
have fun with this. You want to make it light and easy to study old stuff. Sure. Uh, go look up on
the internet, uh, vintage ads from 1800s. Just have fun with it. What does an ad do? An ad has
to appeal to the society. Some people, a sector of the society, a group of, you know, what do you
call it? Demographic. Right. Sure. Go check it out. And that's all I'm going to say about that.
And then you'll see what I'm talking about. Well, there's a target audience and that target
audience could be, uh, dependent upon many different things. Right. I matter of fact,
I've gone back for, you know, studying a big pharmaceutical companies. I've gone back and
studied the ads that they used to have for women, uh, you know, for their menstrual cramps and how
they would sell them a opium basically for their menstrual cramps. Right. Uh, I know that sounds
pretty mundane, but you can see how the ad is structured to get women to understand this will
give you a relief from this problem. You have to go back to cooking and looking pretty. Yeah. Right.
So, you know, you want to feel better. Here you go. We got a way for you to feel better.
Uh, and it's, you know, a little piece of a newspaper. Yeah. Also it's how it's done.
The demographic was the way people, it has to appeal to a mindset, right? Like, uh,
look at the stuff they put out today for people. The mindset is horrible. And guess what? If you go
out and look at the mindset of people, it's well, in my opinion, you have a gender, you have an age
group because obviously up to a certain age, you don't have menstruation after a certain age. You
don't have menstruation. So you have a target of an age group automatically built into this. You
have a gender automatically built into this. You have a, a linguistic built into it because it's
printed in whatever language it's printed in. Right. Right. But what I mean about the,
going back to the eight 1800s is old, right? Yeah. Uh, mid 20th century, there was a flip,
right? After world war two, especially after Vietnam. Well, okay. That's a whole other thing.
The study of what's being shown. The important thing is to know that anything that you're being
shown that's old is for a reason. Why are they, why is it being allowed to be shown? Because it
can easily be, which it is right now. History is being changed. I know people that have children
and I always chide them about what are you doing? Keeping children public school. What's wrong with
you, man? Uh, they're saying, well, the history they're being taught is nothing like the history
I was taught, you know, and they're in their forties or whatever. Right. Well, look, it's one,
one mistake I'm not making, but I do observe what, uh, you know, some of Frankie's playmates are
being taught about history. Dear God. Uh, what a mess. Yeah, it's all, but it's a look at the
human body, you know, blood pressure, diabetes, uh, you absorb nutrition calories. My favorite.
Yeah. Really? You got calories, calories matter. Oh, it means you go to the bathroom. You don't
wipe because you, you know, it's charcoal, right? Yeah. Okay. So let's get into it. Yeah. The email
basically from the gist of it, we got earlier was, where do you start right with the Greek speak
stuff? Well, thinking about and asking the question, where do you start? Is the start
don't, don't think about where to start. Just do. And what you do is what you feel is the best at
the moment. Right. And, but best at the moment, you know, I'm not even going to say, you know,
that helps others and is good for you. What is best at the moment based on the stuff that I lean
on. That's really simple. Yeah. And in fairness, it seemed to me like he was leaning on, okay. You,
you often talk about, you know, what are the things that you can improve easily? Uh, your,
your food, your water, right? Your shelter, your clothing. Okay. Uh, so those things,
if you begin there, that's not a bad place to start for sure. Food, food, clothing, shelter,
the, okay. This is a mismatch. This is what I do for, for personally food, clothing, shelter,
start clean. Uh, like if you speak to people who have some Jewish heritage and they're not Jewish,
right. And they'll say my grant, like, let's say the mother's side was just, so the grandmother
was Jewish, right? So my grandmother, she ate clean. They won't say she was kosher or they were,
she was, you know, biblical law or anything like that. They just say, when you hear eating clean
means they're using, you know, no pork, no shrimp, no lobster, no clams. Right. Right. It doesn't mean
now like no, no fat, you need fat. The reason it's like, you know, your brain stopped working.
If you don't eat fat, so clean with the food, uh, food, clothing, clean, learn how to clean
your clothing. I still get, uh, when I meet people, let's say, uh, when I used to meet people
on a roommate level, we're going to live together as roommates, or, uh, you're going to couple up
with someone, or you're going on a camping trip or a vacation where you're living with other people
for what a few days, maybe a week or two or three, or maybe a month. Right. Right. You start,
what I've always found is I can't help it. I start sharing on tips on how to get your,
your clothing clean, their stains, how to get rid of stains, uh, body, body fluid,
stains, armpits, uh, stains from foods and other things all the way down to, you can imagine,
right? What the easiest thing to do. I've never mentioned this before, other than the
hydrogen peroxide is a strong oxidizer and a spray bottle as a cleaner in the house, right? Like if
you have a pet and it throws up, you wipe it up and you come back with hydrogen peroxide, wipe it
up. Always put a plastic bag over your hand, right? I can't stand. See, seeing people pick up
something that's foul, uh, with a paper. We think the paper towels impervious, put a plastic bag
over your hand, then grab the net, right? Or glove. Right. And you save the plastic bags or
whatever. So hydrogen peroxide and spray ball, excellent oxidizer works really, really well for
like blood and organics, armpit stains, you know, the yellow, whatever, uh, that's a urea. It has a
low pH, not too low. It could damage cotton. By the way, if you have organic fiber and it's very,
very dry out and hot in temperature. And the peroxide happens to be strong. Uh, when you put
apply peroxide, you'll notice it starts to smoke. As a matter of fact, if you use the
pharmaceutical or military grade peroxide, which is 33%, it will catch on fire. I don't know if
you've ever seen that. No, I've never seen that. It's rudimentary rocket fuel. You've heard of
liquid rocket fuel, right? Of course. That's, that's, that's hydrogen peroxide is C one thirties.
When they have a payload, that's too much. And they have a problem taking off on the runway.
They attach hydrogen peroxide rockets. They don't call them hydrogen peroxide rockets. That's what
they are. And you could see videos of them. They're like a skinny, look like very skinny pipes
and this bright, bright orange, red, orange, yellow flame comes out the back hydrogen peroxide. Um,
so I noted that you don't have as much of a discharge of any sort chemical reaction.
Uh, when, when you have a lot more humidity, I think in a drier climate, you see more of that
smoke though. Don't you? Or is that has to be very dry because what happens is if it's not dry,
it's diluted. Yeah. Well, again, with a lot of humidity, a lot of moisture in the air though,
it kind of dilutes it on the reaction. Yeah. There's a, there's a, it's an oxidizer. All
oxidizers require, you know, certain conditions depending on the oxidizer. But so basically I get
into doing the laundry well, right? Okay. And then the next thing is shelter. Well, again,
where do you start with your shelter? Um, uh, Oh, by the way, always when you wear anything other
than a t-shirt or sweat pants, make it look like it's pressed. I used to always, uh, get the
coupons at the, at the cleaners, a dollar to launder a shirt. And I like them. They're folded.
I ask for extra starch to come with the cardboard band, you know, you know what I mean? It's kind
of classy. You know, you got the nice creases and the show, you know what I mean? So, uh,
I used to do that. Not anymore. But by the way, if you have a laundry line in a dryer or whatever,
hang the clothes on the laundry line and then go to the dryer saves a lot of energy that way.
Never dry your shirts, dress shirts, man or woman, uh, all the way in the dryer, uh,
saves on ironing. And it looks real sharp. What you do is you have them damp, dry, uh, 90% dried
is fine. 75% might be better. And you hang the shirt on the line. How, uh, from the label to
the tail of the shirt. So the sleeves are pointing down towards the ground. So right in the middle of
the collar, you start fold, you fold the shirt from the middle of the back of the collar to the
middle of the bottom tail of the shirt. Right. And just pull it real tight. Put that over the
laundry line, let it hang. So the, so the, uh, collar is open sleeves pointing towards the
ground. It takes up a lot of room in a laundry line, but there's shirts that you could overlap
them. Guess what? If you final dry your shirts that way, they look like they were pressed.
It stretches. It looks, it has, in other words, the shirt has a nice body. You know,
it's wrinkled. It doesn't have body to it. Right. But the shoulder. Right. So it has
really nice body and all that. I just want to give that tip that I'm going to, that's
by the way, greekspeak.com, greekspeak.com. It's a double E on the speak part is the solo
Sonics. That's going to be starting soon. Uh, there's an intro with the Archon, but I'm going
to be putting very, very heavy kind of monotonous, not monotonous, but details on these things and
just going through it very, very fast. So Chuck doesn't have to be subject to it. And it is
subscriber only also. Interesting thing about this, hanging the shirts this way, uh, just real
fast. What about, uh, doing it with the, uh, I've seen it done with the upright stick method.
And sometimes that comes out nice and pressed looking. Yeah, it can, it can, but don't,
don't do this. It's too elaborate. Okay. Elaborate the stick. Yeah. This is simple.
You could do that. This is really, you get laundry lines. As a matter of fact, they got laundry lines.
Now you hook them on a door or something for apartments, you know? Oh yeah. There's a big
comeback for that for some reason. Uh, the other thing, you know, laundry line is multi-use,
right? Well, people are trying to save energy, I think is what it is. Cause you know,
electric bills are getting ridiculous, especially in other countries. Uh, uh, quite frankly in the
U S you know, we're getting hurt with our power bills. Uh, it's because the federal
stimulus checks, I don't know. I didn't, I wasn't very vocal. I said, don't do the stimulus.
Tell everybody, stop sending some stimulus checks back. If you get a stimulus check,
you're going to pay for it a hundred times in a decade, 10 times for sure. Real soon.
It's a scam. People don't know how the money it's the easiest thing to destroy a society using the
money system because they know nothing about it. Do not use banking. If you cannot like,
in other words, the minimal, minimal, absolute minimal. And if you have the
digital transactions or whatever, keep them to an absolute minimal, you know, when you write,
I think I've talked about many times when you write a check to someone and you go back and you
see the a hundred, let's say you write a check for a hundred bucks and you come back and you see
the a hundred bucks has gone from the account you're using. No, you reason. Oh, that's because
you know, Chuck got the check, right? And my bank took the check. No, the money's still in your
name. And the legal side is the money that you write for a check for is created with the other
person's signature. Nothing ever leaves one account and goes to the other. Uh, it's so
pathetic. It's so horrible what they're doing under the old fractional reserve rules that actually
creates a thousand dollars, a thousand dollars and they, and they on the other side, right? So
the bank keeps the 900 in this case. Good. But when the government sends you a stimulus check,
you know, they're 30 trillion in debt. They can't even, they can, by law, they cannot even pay their
employees at all. Right. At all. And as a matter of fact, for many years, the IRS employees,
um, their paychecks came from the department of agriculture. And someone asked one of the
IRS people, the admins, why is the department of agriculture doing your payroll? And the IRS people
said, Oh, because they have a better accounting system. No, I'm serious. It's not based on any
accounting. Look, for example, I know someone that the people that are keeping track of
ostensibly, uh, you know, again, agriculture shake, the IRS is a shakedown operation. It has
nothing to do with, uh, going anything or you owe the, it's all present. It's like, if I write you
a bill for $10,000 for whatever. And if you don't answer it, you owe it. Right. Even though I never
met you this, you know, they were actually foreclosing on people's houses. Didn't have
mortgages using this system. IRS uses that system. Give me an example. I know someone who gets a
didn't think about it much. The IRS says, well, your tax returns,
not getting anything back this year. Plus you owe us 1,500 bucks. And he's like, Oh yeah,
I don't want to owe. I'm an honest American. I don't want to owe them 15 or so. He writes
him a check for 1,500 bucks, right? The IRS three months later, he gets another bill from the IRS
for 1,500 bucks. And it says, what's the 1,500 bucks again for, it says for processing the check
for 1,500 bucks, right? There's no, no one owes money to anybody for anything. This is a scam
beyond, but you know what? If the people didn't allow it, it wouldn't last a week. I assure you
that. And that's how they want it. That's why I want nothing to do with these people here on this
planet. You know, this is across the globe. I have no sympathy for them. You know, recently I hear,
Oh, they person passed. I got no sympathy for them. No sympathy for them. You know,
what about you? So when I say to me, well, if I pass, you throw me in a dumpster.
The problem you're going to find by throwing me in a dumpster is that they're locking all
the dumpsters now. So you'll have to throw me under the dumpster or on top of the dumpster. Okay.
So that's what I think about being here. That's what I think about the people here.
It's really, really that bad in reality, not the harmonic romanticism. Oh, I want to make the world
better. Oh, people are okay. If they only know they're not okay. Even if they only whatever.
All right. So wouldn't it be more productive to stick you in a garden though, instead of the
dumpster? I mean, whatever that, well, that's too much effort. And because if you throw me in the
garden, you're going to put flowers and you're going to be safe. Pretty thing. No, don't just,
just piss on me. If you have to, it's really disgraceful to be here from every aspect.
Just by looking around. I mean, geez Louise, but look, I have incredible memories and visuals of
all the beauty here in nature. And in some people, some people I'm holding up one hand and maybe one
finger down when I say some people. So how many fingers am I holding up? Right? So here's the
thing, food, clothing, shelter, shelter, guess what? Keep it clean. You, you like, for example,
back in the days, I get an apartment. I walk, I get to one of those sponge mops, right? And I
sponge mop all the walls and the, and the ceiling even right before I start living in it. Right.
Just clean it out really, really well. So the first step, where do you start cleaning food,
clothing, shelter, cleaning, how do you clean your food? Greek eat clean. How do you clean
your clothes? Greek? Well, there's lots of tips on the way. I just gave you some, right? And how
do you clean your shelter? Well, there you go. Certain things, by the way, if you live in a
place with carpeting and it has that foam carpet, not the, not the jute, you know, not the jute
backing, the natural jute, but that foam stuff, you know, that looks like you ever see white
people make scrambled eggs. Anyway, you have an omelet. It looks like that carpet foam. Anyway,
that stuff is constantly giving off urea and all kinds of nasty stuff. So you have to live
with the window slightly open all year round. It's constantly outgassing constantly foam,
mattresses, foam for in the furniture. You have to, if you have enough of that stuff in the space
that you live, you have to always have a window slightly open. As a matter of fact, a lot of the
new houses, what they have now is like, you know, a little bathroom fans, right? They go on the
ceiling. They go to the highest point in the house and they have one of those things running 24,
seven. So when someone opens and closes the door, it gets to a little fresh air exchange, right?
You could look this up and what they do with the, especially the new builders,
every two years, they come in and change it. Well, the house is under warranty or whatever,
but usually they burn out and people forget. And then all children start dying of allergies.
Allergy just means sensitivity. Now from the spiritual side of things, this is good to
cleanse and clear a space that you're going to live in. You're going to occupy
quite often. Anyhow too, right? Easy, easy to do that. Okay. In order for a spirit to,
okay, you have a spectrum of spirits, let's say from good to bad, right?
They're polarized, really, really polarized. You know what I mean by polarized? Like if you throw
a piece of metal on a magnet, boom, it sticks to the magnet. It's kind of hard to get off. That's
the extreme polarity, right? Of what I mean by that. The really good spirits don't come to you.
The really bad spirits don't come to you because you have to be very much on the end of the
polarity, right? Heavy drug use, heavy insanity for the negative spirits to come. And for the good
spirits to come, we're talking about piousness and a level of dedication that most people
wouldn't have, right? So someone in the middle, spiritual cleansing has a lot to do with that
understanding that little voice in your head that sounds like you, that you think is you,
that talks to you. It's not you. That keeps, that changes. I think just to recap,
how many times have you heard people say, oh yeah, I love this guy's YouTube channel. I woke up in
2010. I started listening to that, right? How many times you heard that, right? A lot. Okay.
Well, when you get through with something like that, or let's say you become, oh, I'm a born
again, you know, born again, Christian. Now I'm born again. Right. Or whenever you change your
modality, that spirit, that voice, the inner voice you had has that, that being has to be replaced.
They bring in another one. Sometimes it happens within the same day. Sometimes it happens within
a few weeks. That's why I like talking to people when they say, oh, I'm converted Satanist. I
remember when that happened, or I'm a born again, Christian. What's the difference, right? Uh, born
again. I said, when did that happen? Or I woke up in 2010. When did that happen? Do you remember?
And I try to get them to go back to that week or day when they decided to do that. And I said,
do you remember like extreme moment of clarity for a few days or a week after you woke up or
converted to Satanism or Christianity aware? Do you remember, you know, when they change their
life, they're like, oh yeah. So when they, when they exchange it, that's when you're really neutral.
That little voice in the head goes away. You have peace and silence. And the last time you
had something like that, maybe you were eight years old, right. Or a teenager, peace and silence. And
then what comes in, they usually, if you say you're going for something, that's better. Like we woke
up to the matrix. They're going to send in a being nine out of 10 times that makes you doubt
everything and brings a little fear bug inside. Right. So you have to be very careful. That's why
very often I say this is for the bold, you're right. You know, when you start becoming more
aware, you're going to be quote unquote medical term tucked with, okay. You're going to be seriously
messed with and, uh, not, not because they want it. They just, that's what they do. That's what
they do. We're in their space, by the way, the earth was dropped in this particular place where
we were, it is on top of their world, but they are a nonphysical world, right? So that's the
spiritual part. There's many, many more aspects to it. The emo part is no, has nothing to do with
what people have been attaching it to that I've seen around me. Mostly the emo is strictly,
you just learned that you have a pinky finger. Of course that's used for picking your nose,
right? You could pick your nose. You just can't pick your friend's nose, whatever,
how that goes. Right. Right. Okay. So what's the appendix for, right?
That's digest to regulate digestion, right? Lower fast digestion, right? You want slow digestion,
faster. And that's what that does. Pinky is definitely for picking your nose. You let
the, you ever see some of the, they leave the long nail on there for picking up things, you know,
whatever. Anyway, it's, it's kind of gross, but okay. So what is the emo for? It's just that,
what is it for? It's to, it's a carrier, right? It is not attached to any other modality. It's
not biblical, but by the way, uh, it's kind of like saying, what's the pinky for? Is it in the
Bible? Well, see, I don't think it's that simple because emo in and of itself is it in my mind
is just there to be a motivator. Okay. Yeah. But here's the thing. No, it's going to do what it
does anyway. It's just that we don't acknowledge it. Yeah. But, but that's what I'm saying. It's
control. If you can't measure it, you can't manage it, but it's just to motivate things.
It's too. And that's the thing. It is to actually put energy, not, not to create energy necessarily,
but to give it directionality. Right. Uh, yeah. Focus. It's the same thing. Like,
what are the eyes for? What are the ears for? What are the, not the eye, the organ,
it's the senses. What are the senses, right? Remember when we talk about senses,
it's all in the brain, right? You don't see with your eyes. You don't hear with your ears.
It's you see in here with your brain, you taste with your brain, by the way,
right? All this other stuff. The emo is very interesting because it is part of the brain
function very much. So just like the others, it's a sense, but it also is the carrier wave. It is
what manipulates. It's what manipulates your abilities within the abilities that, you know,
to manipulate anyway. And then once you discover that it's all emo based, then you find the things
that you don't know how to manipulate that you heard of can be done. Now you can start going
there. Well, it's just like every other sense though, there is a give and take right where
you can experience something else and gain from outside, but you can also push outward, right.
And, and, and have through any of the senses, just like with the eyes, we've talked about this
before the organ in and of itself, actually there's a little bit of light that comes from the
eyes. Uh, you know, so there, there is an in and an out. It's not all about collection coming in
sound coming out of the ear, right? Both things happen. Um, as for which one you acknowledge more,
you acknowledge the one that has the more profound effect. So to your mind, it is the collection.
That's mostly what you get, but that's the whole thing about, you know, the guy who
eventually explodes one day that it didn't happen to just one day. It happened over the course of
time, but he didn't know it. He didn't know that it was emotional, right? Others around them might
look at it, but they don't even know that it's the emo. And then again, how do they know anyway?
Because it's not acknowledged. Yeah. If it's not acknowledged, I mean, look, I can ask you how you
feel acknowledged, but in such a juvenile, stupid way, but I ask you how you're feeling, right.
And a general typical response is okay. Good, bad, whatever. Very general. Um, you might tell
me about a specific complaint or something very good that's happening. You know, one way or the
other, I feel really good today. I feel really bad today. Something's hurting me, whatever.
But you told me next to nothing. Even if you talked for an hour after I asked you, how do you
feel? Um, you still told me next to nothing. There's a hundred other two types of feelings.
There's the nervous feedback you're getting. Then there's the emo in Bushido. You don't talk
about, you're always fine. Even if you're dying of stomach cancer, you say you're fine.
Yeah. Right. In certain cultures. So, um, but the email work, the email work is very different
because now you've found out you have a pinky finger, right? Because your whole life, whenever
you show that, Oh, that doesn't exist. Now you find it exists. And what's it for picking your
nose? Let's say, so now you could teach advanced nose picking, right? Okay. You see where this is
how the email works the same way. Uh, you acknowledge it and you'll find out that the
abilities that you've told that you have, uh, you, you use normally still on acknowledge that
they're emotionally based. And then you hear in the superhero movies and all that, right?
The, the, what is it? There's a whole bunch of X-Men. There's, you can name, you know, heroes
on TV, right? Back in the day, all that, that's, you notice how they changed their emotional state
before they said something on fire, right? Or that's all PK work. Well, it's always the case,
whether it's, you know, uh, one of the X-Men or the fantastic four or whatever,
you know, uh, the Hulk, the Hulk is the best example. Uh, he gets angry and therefore he
hulks up. Um, emo, right. It's all about an emotional motivator that is seized upon that
creates this cascade of reactions, the human torch, right? He gets excited or scared or
whatever. He lights up, uh, et cetera. I mean, there's always the, the emo is always in there.
It's always, it's, it's built into the character's trait. In other words, Oh,
he's getting to the state right now. He's going to blast some fire or Mr. Freeze or
the Hulk. Yeah. You see? So the emo, here's the thing there's a society is to, uh, you know,
we're, we're not all okay. Ultimately when you go to the top, it's non-human, then it's humans,
then it's humans. And it's many tiers of humans that run society. And the whole thing about it
is to give people a low self-esteem. So you see, that's why I always tell people, don't go to the
rapist, the therapist, right? If you look at the way therapist is spelled, it's the rapist.
They know nothing. They have no, absolutely nothing. They're all morons on their own
volition. They don't know that they're morons. Uh, here's the thing. Know how I said, if you want
to save a quarter of a million bucks, go to dermatology school, this is what, this is all
you need to know. If it's dry, you can put something wet on it. And if it's wet, you put
something dry on it. That's the entire basis of dermatology. They know absolutely nothing,
right? Okay. The entire basis of therapy, right? You're ready. Don't even bother, uh,
to getting it. It's all these trades are ridiculous. By the way, the whole basis of
therapy is you try to create in the person's mind, uh, who they're treating, let's say, uh,
a sense of self-importance and how they've been wronged. And it's partially their fault. It's
not their fault or whatever. Why? Because you live in a society that takes any self-importance
out. Generally, you know, the big bang, you know, it came from monkeys. You can't be important,
right? There's 8 billion people on the world, which they're not. It's more like 3 billion,
by the way. How do I know that? Very easy. Who T who gives you the numbers of the population,
the bankers or the bankers? Honest, anything accurate, anything they do accurate on your end,
maybe they tried it, you know? No. Okay. So they're all this we're so insignificant. So
all the therapist does, the rapist, all they do is they try to instill and structure with
emo, by the way, they don't know that they're doing it, but it's in their structure, a little
bit of self-importance, right? And then they manipulate the, the person is manipulated.
How many times have you said, especially with whatever a is another example? Oh, I went to a
therapist. I'm much better now. And if you ask him, what did they do? How did it go? If they
can communicate it, you'll see all they did was they went in feeling like a piece of shit.
Therapist made him feel like they were important in some way. And now they can handle their stuff.
You need a therapist for that. It's a trick they're playing on you, right? Like the AA,
I said, it's a demonic organization. I think we knew somebody mutual person back in the day.
You're going to go to a place that you're going to affirm that you're an alcoholic. Every time
you go, what the fuck you, you gotta be sick. You gotta be sick in the head to not see that right
away. If you go to AA, you deserve it. But the point of that distorted. Yeah. But the point of
that is okay. Now, except that you got this problem so you don't slip. I get the reason
they give you, but it is sick and distorted. No, no, no. I get it. I'm not, I'm not, believe me,
I'm not backing it. What I'm saying is method. And do you know, Bob, I'm pulling it back and
saying, okay, here's the deal though, is that they tell you, look, here's the problem you
actually have. We're going to identify it. You have this problem. Now here's your solution to
that problem. You had this problem. Oh no, no, no, no. No, no, no. You still have the problem.
Remember AA is a constant thing. That's how they keep you coming back. So you, you have this
problem, but here's the solution. Unless you're sitting there drinking a bottle of Thunderbird
right in front of them. If you drank a bottle of Thunderbird five minutes before you walked in,
you still just had that problem. You don't have the problem. Yeah. You and I are using
proper logic here. I can agree with you on this, but you and I, but I'm telling you that this is
the methodology is that you have this problem. So now that you have this problem, here's your
answer to that problem. And since you can do that, here's your self-worth because you were able
to grow, to get better, to be validated, et cetera. Yeah. There's self-importance. It's a
trick. It's, it's all, it's all manipulation. There's no therapy. They don't know anything
like nutritionists. Oh, the calories. Oh my gosh. I'm a nutritionist. I've been interested for 35
years. Calories matter. Really? Do you poop charcoal that matters? Well, my gosh, you cannot
deal with these people that look the way these trades, uh, rabbis, priests, doctors, uh, whatever
lawyers are all screwed up is because society wants it that way. It's really, it's, it's a catch 22
in this case. I think it's an interesting universal methodology though, is that look,
okay. Except the fact that you, you, you were on a lower level, you were lesser because,
all right, now we're going to show you how to climb up the ladder and become greater.
So now you're greater. Now you're special. And because you're special, this is why you're
improved. And this is why you got to give us your money. Keep coming back, participate in our stuff
because whatever it is, whether it's a priest, rabbi, uh, the therapist, the rapist, uh, which
I, I love that by the way, I really feel like there's probably already a t-shirt for it, but
anyhow, um, I, I think it would be a good business. That t-shirt right there, the rapist therapist,
um, anyways, loose idea point is that it makes the person special. Therefore, this is the thing.
It gives them a good feeling. They instill self-importance that that's really stupid.
Yeah. But it's an illusion. Sometimes it's break it down first. It's the, you know,
break down first and then build up. What do they say about the military? Right.
They break you down in order to build you up. It is a workable methodology,
but again, it's just the trick. Now, did it actually do anything concerning what it is you
came in there for in the first place? It does because the people going, yeah,
they're, they're trying to function. They're looking up to the society that they're in
to be quote unquote, functional and normal. They even say that. Right. Yeah. And, uh,
so yeah, it's of course, it's all crap. It's all crap on many levels, but you know,
I think we just touched on it, but there's nothing, there's nothing more to go into.
You look years ago, I knew some guys and they were like, man, I can't, I can't meet a girl,
a girl or whatever. I said, what are you talking about? You know, pick a demographic,
like you remember pizza Uno? I don't know if they had them. It was like a dim light. Yeah. Pizza
Uno is like a deep dish. I said, go down here, pizza Uno and pick up some upper middle-class
chicks with a low self-esteem. You, you, they're easy to meet everywhere you go. I used to say,
go, go to the bar over here and just pick up a chick with as low self-esteem.
That's like the first, the first thing of pimping. You live in a pimped out society.
You're being pimped constantly. The cookie cutter restaurant, you go to your Applebee's or whatever.
They all, they always got a bar section guaranteed. One thing is that there's going to be groups of
women sitting there, uh, at certain points. And what are they out there to do is to run
into somebody who's looking for them. They are there. Um, but the whole thing is the
entire society is based on low self-esteem and unimportance and all this. So the best
therapy they're going to do give you is tell you that you're important. Oh, wow. I'm important.
Cause you said, so now it works. That's the whole crux of the therapy, just like the dermatology,
you know, the method or whatever. So that's also the preferred way of meeting women too,
as they tell you, you know, you compliment them in this and that you make them feel important.
You make them the center of attention. And this is your methodology for a hooking up with women
too, right? Yeah. It's ridiculous. Yeah. What does that do for the curve? In other words, you know,
what does it do for anyone? It, it, because again, you're floating in a, it's a type of fish,
you know, like, you know, when you go fishing, you got to know the characteristics of the fish,
right? So the society has been so knocked down. And, uh, but look, can you blame the upper
echelons that do this because they, they want control, right? The last thing they want is,
you know, billions of people, each wanting to rule the planet, you know, cause that,
that could happen. Right. And by the way, there was a city States, you know, back in the day,
right. So, uh, that each, you know, each little city state had a King. Imagine each neighborhood,
by the way, you don't have to imagine it right now. It's going on in Somalia. They have warlords,
each neighborhood, literally neighborhood, you know, a group of city, few city blocks
has its own warlord, literally. And, uh, when you go from walk through a neighborhood in certain
places, like in East Congo or Somalia, places like that, you, you see like city streets or
whatever. And then you get to the certain, you walk a little bit and you get to a certain point.
And there's like this corrugated sheet metal laid out, like a, like almost like, what do you call
it? Where they stop the cars? What do they call it? A checkpoint, almost like a very loose
checkpoint. And you're like, you're coming in this part of the neighborhood. This is run by
Mustafa, whatever. Right. You're like, what the fuck, you know, what's going on here? You know,
Mustafa's whatever neighborhood. Yeah. You see that in South America, you see that in South
America, there was actually a fairly popular, like, you know, artsy movie made not too long ago
called the city of God. And because there's a place called the city of God in, uh, in, uh,
I forget which South American country, but literally what you're talking about is laid
out there. This is all over the place, actually. So in other words, if you're going to have a big
city, you can't have that. I mean, it's still, by the way, it exists growing up in, in Brooklyn,
New York. It was kind of like that. Each neighborhood was a certain way,
right. Uh, you know, um, then jerseys like that very much. So also where you hearken from,
right. So a lot of ethnic, it's not extreme. No, it's not extreme. It's not warlords,
but you do have people that sort of run neighborhoods based on there's an ethnic,
uh, similarity between them and that this is their area. And, uh, yeah, no, exactly.
And the city that will be coming back when times get hard, because that's basically how,
when people get closer to the land and they're poor or enslaved, that's how they operate. There's
no castle doctrine, right. It's all, it's that type of grouping warlord stuff. But again, I just,
we kind of jumped around, got a little wonky again, but the emo stuff is just acknowledging
what the emotions are for. It kind of sounds crazy to say that the Greek is acknowledging,
or trying to tell people, uh, many things, but one thing is that, uh, emotions are not
acknowledged for what they are as a given sense and a given ability, but they are acknowledged
because look, uh, the only way that emotions are acknowledged is, uh, I cared enough to give
them the very best. That's the television moniker for Hallmark cards, right? The greeting cards.
And that's a weird thing with the younger generation actually is a lot of their,
a lot of their modality is now based on what their emotional experience is, right? Everything,
in fact, centers upon their emotional experience. Um, it's very warped. It's very disconnected.
It's very convoluted and artificial, but still it's like, look, well, the emo cons on the,
on the, uh, they changed the language, right? They're using abbreviations and the emo,
um, I don't know what they're called. The little images or something. Yeah. Well,
you got emojis and emojis used to be emoticons, but emojis now with the little smiley faces that
do this or that. So they are using them, but they're not, but people do. Oh yeah. That's it.
But they don't know that the actual facilitation of the emotion in the human body is a carrier
and a facilitator of all their actions potentially. Well, there's the natural version
of this and then there's the artificial. And what they've done is sort of taught these,
uh, younger people, the, the artificial version of it. But in reality, there is a
totally natural built in organic, uh, way of doing this. You know, the projection of like,
I can send you a smiley face right now, or I can send you one with boxing gloves or whatever.
It's synthetic. It's actually almost a, what do you call it when you're making fun of some mocking
it's mocking, um, anything that they, yeah, it's a mocking. Uh, like if, look, for example, banking,
if you look at banking, all those, you're being mocked, right. Uh, constantly, uh, you know,
read a credit card application, read a PayPal thing, read it, whatever it's all you, they're
mocking you right to your face, but you don't understand the language. Right. So, so when they
do these, uh, anything that has to do with emo is downplayed and mocked and childish, right.
Except for the, with the industries that are based on it, you know, and a lot of the holidays that
are based on it. But anyway, uh, the reason I'm bringing this up in the way, kind of in a roundabout
way is because people are trying to attach it to something and it's, it's, it's nothing. There's
nothing to attach it to other than everything that you're already doing that you just never
acknowledged it was there. It's the funniest thing. It's all based on distraction, right?
Because we have a tremendous amount of energy and robustness. For example, uh, when people go for
medical treatments, none of those medical treatments work, none of them. Uh, the only
things that work with the medical treatment is anesthesia and painkillers. And of course,
uppers and relieves like that. And the reason why people surviving surgeries, uh, is not really
because of hygiene is because the anesthesia is holding them down. If you woke up or were not able
to be put under for a surgery, you would die of shock. Most of the people that died back early
on before modern methods was several reasons. One was called poisoning of the teeth. They had really,
really bad teeth and they had infections in the blood from it. And the other thing was because
they died from a shock, right? So, um, because they, you know, they weren't able to be sedated.
So those are the two things really, all the other treatments are, they don't work. It's obvious
because, um, if you go study the pharmaceutical companies, any drug that's supposed to be
approved or put out has to show a report on how well it works against what placebo sugar pill.
It's very rare that you'll find any drug that can beat a placebo.
They're usually 50, 50. If it's 50, 50, yeah, it's good. It works. What does that tell you?
It's the power of what the human mind, how can it be that people have a specific illness and
they're designing a specific drug for that? They give half of the control of group, uh,
sugar pills and the other half, the drug. And they, and the most of the people that got the
sugar pill occurred or healed from it, or it has the same effect as a drug. How's that possible?
How do some or any of the people with the sugar pill get, get better? How is that possible?
Right, right. So, but they still tell you the drug, right? So you just go read the reports. How,
how does it fare against the placebo, any drug? And you'll notice that, Oh my gosh.
And so it's all right. So what's the problem with taking their medicines is this,
is that they always give you the side effects. You watch the TV commercials, right? Sometimes
the side effects are worse than what you're trying to treat. Yeah. What they never say on
any of the side effects ever is the effects that it has on what they'll give you the effects on the
kidney liver. It could cause sudden death, right? But they never, ever, ever, ever, ever tell you
the effects it has on the brain. Never, ever, ever. And I'm telling you right now, you, you just,
you know, suck on a, a chocolate bar or, uh, anything that you eat right now or take in,
even if you're thirsty, drink some water, it will affect the way your brain works immediately.
One of the main things that I've always discussed is if you want to see the effects of food,
sign your name or write something you're familiar with before you eat something,
eat something, wait 10 minutes, and then go ahead and sign your name. Again, you'll notice
how different it looks or write something or draw something, draw a circle, draw a line.
And you, and you cannot do it the same way. That's the effect it has on your motor skills,
right? This is something to do with children all the time. And, uh, you could see like as a child,
write your name and you know how they hold the pencil. Sometimes like they wrap all their
fingers around it, right? A real young child, right? Hold it upright. Like it's a hammer
and like it's a hammer and they write their name and then have some chocolate milk. They
couldn't even write their name. It was like, wow, that's the chocolate milk on what the brain.
So you're taking these strong pharmaceuticals. So anyway, the only things that work are the
the opium you mentioned earlier, right? For the women for menstrual. And, um, let's get off of
this for a moment. Cause I think whoever's listening, I might say, these guys are killing
this emo thing, uh, without really give furthering it again. It's kind of a defense in a way, uh, on
how maybe people are taking it. I've never presented it as, uh, something that's this new
thing that you can try or that may be this, or it might be that. No, no. I'm just saying,
Hey, guess what? I'm just visiting this planet and you humans, you don't acknowledge what emotions
are for. You know, your feet are for walking, your pinkies for picking your nose, your eyes
are for seeing yours or for hearing. But if you ask them what the emotions are for, I don't know,
man, you know, my only purpose is he, my thought is survival really, because it gives you the
motivation to do all the things that are necessary. If you're paying attention to survive.
Yeah. Sort of depends on what you call survival. Yeah. That's a changes. I've heard people that
managed, uh, who's that? I know someone who manages like Larry King and Ivanka Ivana Trump's,
uh, personal funds. He had like a 3 billion portfolio. And when they did the financial
crash in 2008, he's like, I don't know how I'm going to survive. My portfolio went from like
whatever million down to 18. I'm like survival. You're going to survive on 18. What are you
talking about? Survival is like, if there's no food to eat and I see grass growing in the middle
of the road on the highway out of a crack in the asphalt, I know I could survive. Obviously the
word survival means two different things. Yeah, absolutely. Different people. Survival means food
and water, food, clothing, shelter in that order. Right. So, and I'm thinking that,
but that's the basic why, uh, you know, or maybe I'm missing the point. Let's get to it.
There's no point to miss. The thing is, these are broad, broad topics that are
not acknowledged. The thing is, if it's not acknowledged, how are you going to miss it?
Miss it means that, you know, something was there, there was an intention. And then now
for some reason you missed it, like missing the bus or missing a train or missing your ride or
missing the show or whatever. Right. Uh, yeah, you have to acknowledge it to order to miss it.
If something goes completely unacknowledged in purpose, there's nothing to miss, right? No,
you hear that also there. I didn't never miss. I didn't know. I never missed it because I didn't
know it existed. Right. Yeah. People say that you don't, you don't know what you had. If you never
had it in the first place. Well, what is the old, uh, if you didn't know it exists, how could you
know how could it matter? So, uh, you know, better to have loved and lost. Right. And that way you
would at least experience love. And then other people say, yeah, but if you never experienced
love at all, you don't know what you lost. So it's the better. Yeah. Well, some of those things
can work. Yeah. I think it's a, well, you know, when I hear the word love, you know, it means,
um, do the right thing. Right. Even if it's when, especially when it's inconvenient to work to,
to you, it's dedication. Speaking of which I want to do a short on sex that came up. We
never really taught. I do make lascivious comments. Um, but sex. Okay. The purpose of sex
is to have children, right? That's it. So if you're not planning on having children,
you don't need to have sex. Now, will him right. Put together a treatise for many years
that the purpose of the orgasm for biologicals is not only for procreation and the excretion
of fluids and whatever, but he noticed that certain people on his therapy couch, when they
would confess certain things and he would dig deep, they would have emotional body reactions
that mimicked what the movement and action that someone would have when they're having an orgasm.
So he figured that the two are correlated. You could take that where you want it. I have my
own ideas on that. That's probably going to be an entire sonic event because right. Can therapy is
very powerful, especially when you get into armory. Uh, and I'm not disagreeing with the
Wilhelm Reich treatise, but I'm just saying that sex is strictly for having children. Now,
the next thing about sex is depends on what culture you're brought up in.
Like, for example, uh, certain cultures, uh, like the American culture, Western culture,
they'll make fun of people. Oh yeah. He's a blue collar guy. Watch football has sex just once a
week, you know? Oh, well, it's like, what? It's like, you know, so they're over sex, right. Or
under sex, each culture, depending on how it's viewed, it gets to the point where they even
mutilate their bodies, right? Uh, uh, women, female genital mutilation and all that. So she
becomes a vessel to the man, all that. So it's really culture by culture. And I'm telling you,
the culture that you were raised in, if you accepted it and they're not, didn't see it
coming and you became part of the culture, it's very hard to change. It's very hard to change
that. Oh, you brought up a female circumcision. They call it sometimes. What about, uh, the,
the practice, the seemingly ancient practice of male circumcision. What are you saying?
It's a form of mutilation. Like, uh, so they used to say often is always circumcised.
The answer is no. Right. Cause we were made in their image. Right. It's just,
look, by the way, I don't believe any of that text. Right. I know it and I use it and I use
it as my guide. I use it. It's the laws. That's right. Fair enough. But I mean, it's part of that.
So it's part of that covenant though. Right. God's other God's circumcised. The answer is
if they're a male God with a penis. Right. Right. Right. Uh, are they circumcised? The answer is no.
Right. Because when we're born, we're not served. Right. Right. It's a covenant. It's a form of
mutilation to show that you're in covenant. It's a serious one too, by the way, because
while it's not reversible, I haven't seen too many press plastic surgeons offering.
No, I don't, I don't believe that they do reversal. I know, but yeah. Yeah. And, or, you know, uh,
you know, I, I was surprised at this day, modern day that the people that weren't uncertain,
they're not uncut. They call it, you know, don't, don't put a drawstring or something in it or
whatever, you know, but anyway, uh, draw skin for the foreskin. But anyway, um, yeah, that's what
it is. It's a covenant. It's, it's an intense, it's an intense covenant because, uh, if you read
in some places, they, before they crossed a certain part, all the adult men were circumcised
and imagine that. Right. So yeah. By the way, that was also in Egypt. It's a, it's a sign. It's a,
it's a sign. Right. So, uh, in other words, a covenant, you know, just like a bikers get a
tattoo, right. Well, whatever, you know, um, assassins, whatever. So is that, is that necessary
according to the biblical text? I mean, because yeah, no, it's a covenant. It's a voluntary
covenant. No, it's not necessary. Well, not very voluntary when it's a baby though. You know what
I mean? Because at that point your parents make that decision. Well, the baby, yeah,
it's supposed to do it at eight days old. Cause that's also the highest point of coagulative
ability in the male child, probably female also might be a little longer for the female
cause the peptides and things like that are, are a slower developing in a woman. Um, but
nonetheless, uh, the child is not considered to be alive until they're five years old. By the way,
in other words, you can't be counted until you're five. Right. You know, in other words,
you know, cause it was expected that the mother nursed the child till five. It was expected that
if the child lived past five, it's going to live right now. It's, we have crib death and all this
other stuff. By the way, us now is like the highest or second highest infant mortality rate
in the world. Every third world country, every third world country, except for one beats the
us and infant mortality. Look it up. Isn't that crazy? Yeah. You know what I mean by infant
mortality? Yeah, absolutely. Yeah. So not only that mortality was, yeah, we also have women,
women die during childbirth more often here than a lot of other places too. Yeah. It's basically,
yeah, it's, it's a zoo. The U S is, but it was an experiment. It's an Illuminati experiment.
You know, the U S 17, how do you know? They, they tell you to go grill hot dogs and do fireworks on
July 4th. You know, most people don't even know why supposedly when the country was born, but
they never talk about how do you know it's an experiment because they never talk about March
the 9th, 1933. That's when the country died. Right. You know? So anyway, yeah. So 90 year delay,
the idiots will never figure it out. Never. But anyway, uh, where were we with the, uh,
well, we were talking, you said you were going to do the whole thing on sex and sex is for
that's another it's strictly for procreation by the way. And then there's the William Reich treatise
that certain people, when they get very deep emotional outlet or discharge, they exhibit a
physical condition that looks like an orgasm. So if you correlated the two that if you have an
orgasm, you'll have a good emotional, uh, and help get rid of some armoring was the idea. Um,
and then of course it's what culture you're brought in. Like the American, cause you know,
the sixties right now, it's like, if you don't have sex in a week or two or even a month,
something wrong with the relationship, right? You know, that's what they try to
say. And they found out that if you want to create due population control, you put an oversexed,
culture in. And you think like, wait a second. No, because, uh, if you have them become oversexed,
then they'll have more babies. No, the answer is no, because what you do is you squeeze in and you
narrow down the sex as for fun, not for having children. And occasionally there'll be one or two,
you know, like, oops, you know, I'm pregnant kind of thing. Uh, but actually you can stick in,
you could squeeze in all these contraceptive methods and all these other techniques
to actually start disassociating sex with having children and just for fun. Right. And of course,
there are diseases that are due to transmit that way, by the way. Um, and that was the idea for
AIDS. AIDS was a big, it came after herpes. It was VD, right? And then there was herpes and then
AIDS, but the AIDS thing never really hit because as the herpes and the, um, uh, gonorrhea and
syphilis did. So they said, let's make it a real hit and kill them with the treatment. We'll tell
them that they have a very serious disease. And when they start taking the treatment, you know,
it'll trick the body that the epithelial cells have been replaced and they'll wither away and
die and they'll never figure it out because they respect this as an authority. By the way,
the statistics on people have died from AIDS is between 20 and 40 million people worldwide. That's
20 or 40 million people that have been deliberately killed by the medical establishment. You know that,
right? That's a pretty serious number. You know, you want to talk to the Holocaust, this or
genocide that, you know, tens of millions like that by the medical establishment. It's, and
guess what? Medical establishment, whatever doubt is going its way, it's still strong, right?
More people, more people have been killed by the medical establishment. Okay. In the past
300 years, then all of the wars combined and you could line them up next to each other and the
medical establishment outpaces every single one of those wars, conflicts, every one of them.
Everyone. But that's how they like it. That's how they want it. Because if you tell them that,
first of all, they don't believe it. Second of all, they sign up for a health plan, right? And
all this other bullshit. And they go to these medical people, medical technicians. I don't
even like calling them doctors. They don't deserve that. Because doctor means teacher
and they don't know anything. How can they teach if they know nothing? And the thing about doctors,
so where do they get their education from the state? The state education? Are you joking?
State approved? Anyway. Well, that's the thing about being a doctor is they automatically,
that means you were approved by the state if you are a doctor. Oh my gosh. That means it's
in the real universe. That means you're discredited, actually. So it goes the opposite.
It's backwards. But here's the thing about that. The people want it that way,
whether they know it or not. If you take a profile momentary screenshot of the situation,
do the people want the medical establishment to exist? Yes or no? And the answer is yes.
Emphatically. Right. Right. So there you go. That's why things ain't going to get better.
Um, well, you will have a better society, but not with the people that are here,
not the majority that are here. They got to go. You need it's one. It goes backwards. You can't
have a better society with the people here. And in order to have a better society, you can't have
these people. So it's a moot point to wish it upon. Right. So in either way, on that aspect of the
recovery, the email, I want to just do a quick shot on the yin and yang that we've been covering.
By the way. Okay. And every time I bring this up, just like when I bring up anything biblical,
you know, I always have to qualify. There is no translation available in any language outside
of Hebrew and Greek and Aramaic. So if you understand the Bible, let's say from English
or Spanish or Chinese, those are versions. Right. So whenever I talk, that's how you know if there's
a valid conversation on the Bible, by the way, they have to start out by making that qualifier.
If you don't hear that qualifier, the person is just giving, you know, whatever a mixed bag
of whatever they think they want to talk about. Right. So when you bring that up like that,
you have to qualify. Also, when I say yin and yang, that is an Asian demonstrative
philosophy reasoning of how energies work. There is no counterpart. I'm looking for a
way to denote that subject in with a Western, let's say, lingo.
Unfortunately, you've had to refer to Star Wars a few times because that's the closest thing to a
system that could be. Yeah. The force. Right. The force and balance and things like that.
That's almost a valid demonstration. Yeah, it is. It is very much. But here's the thing with that
also. Force may be close, but it's not it. This is what I wanted to bring up. I've been speaking
on the dietary aspect of it because the dietary aspect is very, very important.
Why? It's very important because it's what the body converts into the body, right? With the food
that you eat. And it's what everyone does. If you suggest someone do something for a health benefit,
they may or may not get to it. Right. But if you suggest that health benefit within the diet,
guess what? They're going to eat. Right. Pretty soon after you tell them about it. Right. Very
often. That's why I used to say years ago, more often when I gave someone a suggestion,
whether it was business or personal or do this before your next meal, I always say before your
next meal, do this. Right. Because it's like timing, because you're going to eat most of the
people to eat at least twice a day, morning and evening. Right. Right. Attaches urgency to the
Yeah, sure. It means it's going to be within that day. So when you make health suggestions
or improvement of one's qualitative improvement in their reality regarding food, you know,
they're going to approach the they're going to come across that at least once or twice a day.
Very important. Right now. That's what I've been stressing because it's very simple. Monkey see
monkey do get yourself some Lundberg brown rice and some burdock root. Incorporate that what you
eat. But you have to learn how to cook the rice well and you have to learn how to cook the burdock
well. Right. And you start eating that, incorporating whatever else you eat,
more of that. And you'll see how you feel. It's going to change you. You can't help it.
Right. So get that going soon. Right. Like remember the changes we started off with here.
OK. The other thing that I have now, this is why I want to bring this up again that I have not
stressed enough is the concept of yin and yang is balance. But these two energies are constantly
in flux. One moment it's a little yin. The next moment it goes to yang. It swings back and forth.
Example. A heartbeat. Boom. Yang. Timing. Stop. Slow. Right. Quiet. Yin. Boom. Yang. Right.
Contraction. Right. Open heart. It opens. That's the blood rushing. Yin. Boom. Contracts. Yang.
Inhale. Inhale. Right. Exhale. Yin. Yang. Right. Exhale. Yang. Right. You see how it works. The
pulse is yin, yang, yin. Expansive. Contractive. Yang. Everything is in flux like that. Right.
You go out in the hot summer day in the sun. You walk next to a building or under an overpass.
Shadow. Yin. Yang. Right. When you take a step, you know a step is a controlled fall.
No one knows how to walk. When you're walking, you know how to control a fall. How do you know
that walking is a controlled fall? When someone's walking forward, not paying attention, throw a
banana peel under one of the feet. They can't control the fall anymore. So what happens?
They continue to fall. You see? If you step on something slippery, it's not that you slipped.
It's that you didn't control the fall. You weren't able to put a braking action on it.
You see how it works. Right. So every time you take, every time you walk, no one knows how to
walk. Say if you were like, Oh, most people don't get it. No one knows how to walk. You want to say,
I teach your child how to walk, raise a baby, right? No, he just still doesn't know. You don't
even know how to walk. You don't walking. It's just a loose term. It's a controlled fall. You
lean forward, right? As if you're going to fall into the direction and then you put your foot to
stop it from falling. Right. Right. Proof of that is when you slip, you weren't able to,
it's a controlled fall. Just like a crash. When I train people on a cycling, whether it's motorized
or non-motorized, I said, you know what a crash is? A crash is an indeliberate dismount. It's
getting off your bike when you didn't want to. Right. That's all it is. Stop looking at it as
a crash as this happenstance. That's something that we have no control. You have complete control
over that. So how do you remedy? How do you become good at crashing?
You figure out like a dozen ways to dismount quickly without even thinking about it. Dismount
off the right side, dismount off the left. You know, a lot of people with bikes,
they have what are called chocolate foot. They always like to dismount off of one side or the
other. I said, learn, you know, it's like lefty or righty, learn how to do both ambidextrous,
learn how to get off the bike from the back, learn how to get off the bike from the front,
learn how to get off the bike by rising over the bike and letting the bike roll from under you,
learn like four or five, 10 different ways to dismount quickly without thinking about it.
And the next time you crash, guess what? That was just another way that you learned,
right? It's not a crash anymore. They actually do teach us. They actually do teach us in advanced
motorcycle riding classes that they give to people. It's rare. Not a lot of people take
them or anything. A lot of the techniques that I used to discuss are very reasonable,
but you can't find them on the internet anywhere. There's no books written on them about cycling,
all this other stuff. You know, you know, you see people stand up next to a bike when they're not
riding, talking to someone. What you got to do is you put your hand on the brake, squeeze the brake
while you're talking most, right? Because the bike could still roll away and you could fall.
There's all these techniques, you know, how to manage something on two wheels. And there's no
information out there. So anyway, walking is no one knows how to walk. It's a controlled fall,
right? Yin and yang. The same thing with riding a bike, right? And dismounting. That's where it
flips also. When you're moving, it's yang. When you're dismount, when you stopped, it's yin.
But at the point of dismount, it's yang. You see? So you have micro yin, micro yang that happens so
fast. Um, when your eyes are open, right? Uh, yang, when you close your eyelids to blink,
yin, right? So everything is going from yin to yang back and forth. It's, uh, like Trevor wrote
a book, the cosmic pulse of life. Trevor James Constable, one of my mentors, but it has more to
do with the sky preachers that live in the sky and other things of work of William Reich. But
what I wanted to say was the qualitative improvement for people by doing the brown
rice and Burdock, by the way, Burdock's really hard to find. I did find for two bucks a pound,
a package of Burdock, non-organic, uh, Lili market here in Tucson. Uh, you might find it in Asian
markets called Gobo also, uh, or whatever. They have several names for it, but some people are
having problems finding it. It's the reason I suggest the Burdock route is because it's extremely,
it's the most young vegetable you could possibly have. Very bracing. If it does the same thing
that meet what meat does to you, people like to eat meat because it gives you instantaneous energy,
right? Is there anything else similar to it? Besides, I mean, let's just say you can't find
that particularly. No, there isn't that I know of it because it's a taproot. It's about three
feet long. It goes straight down into the ground, like a carrot, but it's got a white, a whitish
interior with a dark Brown, like bark on the outside. You have to peel that. You don't want
to eat that. Uh, and it's very, very bracing. Humans are attached to that. And it's a very go
back the most primal, primal, uh, food because it's energetic wise. It's the most attached to
the earth, the most earth energy vegetable you can get there. There are probably roots of certain
other plants that have very deep tap roots. Um, uh, and if you handle Burdock, it almost, if you've
ever done Arbor, Arboretum work with trees, like dig a tree out, it probably looks like a medium
size tree root of any tree. Okay. And the Brown rice, which don't consider it a carb, it has the
shell on it and it's a loaded with, uh, everything the body needs, right? Like they say. No, I was
just thinking if there was an alternative, like a reasonably close alternative to it, that's all.
No, there isn't. And then someone, I got an email from, by the way, your ant powder is coming.
Uh, I had a delay cause I'm sending out these, uh, water devices to industry at the moment.
Uh, and just a, a, a short thing on that, uh, back on the yin and yang, because it's switching
back and forth, uh, on, uh, you know, yearly, you know, the seasons, yin and yang, right.
Uh, daily, monthly, the moon, right. Everything. And also momentary in your body, you have so
many opportunities. This is the thing, uh, because the yin and yang is constantly oscillating and
try and balancing, uh, every moment is an opportunity to qualitatively increase, increase
your, uh, your life. And by the way, just to go back to the ant powder, what the hell is he,
what the hell did he say? Uh, in the summertime, you have these, uh, soldier ants, they go out,
right. And you know, they, they leave a trail of formic acid and the other ones followed in
Right. So if you ever get that, okay. So what I did was I took a
borax, uh, well, you get an old coffee grinder or a new coffee grinder. It doesn't matter coffee
grinder, right. The kind with the high speed blade, let's say, and you can put some borax
powder in there, equal parts of everything that I'm going to mention, uh, borax. And then you put,
uh, silica dec desiccant, those little dry packs you see in things, you know,
a little, it was a hard to find, uh, and they're expensive. So if you're going to make a lot of
this stuff for five bucks at a pet store, you get the diet blue, but it's a food grade blue for kitty
litter. It looks like a crystals. It's desiccant silica gel. Yeah. Right. The kitty litter is
bright blue. Okay. That's the same stuff. Uh, that stuff you put anise in there in the coffee grinder,
also anise, uh, star anise, cinnamon and clothes, equal parts, either by volume or by weight.
And you grind that up and you make a very fine powder and you sprinkle that. You put it in a
little squeeze bottle. Like when I say squeeze ball, you don't go to the diner and they got
the mustard and ketchup. Mustard's in a red bottle and the ketchup, ketchup's in a red bottle. The
mustard's in a yellow squeeze bottle, right? Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Get those squeeze, squeeze
bottles, small ones, big ones or whatever. And you put the powder in there. Don't start shaking
it around. If you have pets, you don't want dogs and cats and birds or whatever in it because of
the desiccant. Right. Right. Uh, so anyway, you put this around the edge of the door or whatever.
It creates a border. The bugs won't cross. I call it ant powder. And it's very, very,
very potent. And it's better than, uh, the killer chemicals that they do because it won't kill
anything really, you know? So I just wanted to bring that up and it's on your, it's on the way.
I also included a squeeze bottle in there for you. Uh, I'll ship it out on Monday.
Sounds logical. And also, uh, it sounds a lot safer than using the diatomaceous earth,
which, uh, which I used to use borders. Well, it did. It does work to keep some things out,
but the problem is yeah. Yeah. Yeah. A little bit. Well, what I do is if you have like a brick patio
or if you have a rough surface on the patio, uh, put some down and sweep it in with the broom,
push it down right into the crevices. Right. So the pets or whatever, don't walk on it
or just do a border under the threshold of the door. Yep. There you go. Yep. That sounds very
logical and sensible. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. That's, uh, that's the recipe for it. I'll go over it
again another time. So there's the ant powder. There's a little more on the emo, a touch more
on the, uh, the, the yin and yang of sex just a bit. Uh, is there anything else that we need to
touch on? You think lots more? I'm going to be, like I said, doing the solo Sonics at Greek
speak.com. Right. It's just going to be me. Uh, our con is, uh, you guys know who it is and he's,
uh, doing all the admin work behind the scenes, uh, hats off to him. Cause I don't do any of that
stuff. The only thing I know about computers is, uh, you know, power on, click on a browser,
send an email, get on Skype. That's it. That's all I want to know. Yep. Well,
you know more than that, but you don't want to involve it. You don't want to start taking up
admin work. Oh my gosh. I set up the uncommon sense radio on common radio.com. Oh my gosh.
I even know Charlie and the Greek.com. I did. I was like, Oh my gosh, five hours. And it's like,
what the hell is going on here? This is like a vacuum and a vampire, electronic vampire.
You only made a couple of pages there and you were like, screw this.
Yeah. This is vampirism and it's geekdom. It doesn't have to be that way. And never,
never, I'll never do it. Yeah. I'd rather go back to the post, you know, go down to the
Kinko's and make copies and send them out in the mail and do a website. Listen, I would love that.
If we could go back to that, you know, the whole thing, let's just make this many copies of it
and, you know, give them the mail. I need to go to stamps. By the way, no matter how many stamps
you buy, unless you're doing a big operation, it's always going to be cheaper than buying a
computer and paying the internet fees, by the way. Oh yeah. Yeah. No, I, I, I love that. Uh,
I used to love the days of being able to mail stuff like that and have stuff going back and
forth, but you know, and flyers, remember flyers, flyers were great. Yeah. Make Xerox,
cut them down the middle of safe paper, right. Or sometimes four ways and just put them in
windshields, hand them out to people. Give someone that you trusted a stack of flyers to hang out,
hand out at work for parties or services or whatever. Yeah. Yeah. And the half sheet,
like you said, was the best, because I mean, you could get a lot of stuff on a half sheet of paper
and boom, you know, uh, you cut your 5 cents in half. You just get one paper cutter and you're
good. Yep. Or you make the little phone number tabs on the bottom and you slice it. You put it
up on a cork board. Someone reads it right. And then they break off a little phone number tab off
the bottom. Oh yeah. I don't know. I don't think people do that anymore. No, no, that you'll,
you'll get back. Actually, you're going to have a pause. Uh, what'll happen is, you know, they asked
Einstein who was Einstein, by the way, means stupid in German. I'm means one and Stein means
stone. If you have one stone means you're, you're dumb. Right. But, uh, he said, they asked him and
others who's part of a collective that, uh, uh, he doesn't know how world war three will be fought
exactly, but he knows for sure. World war four would be fought with sticks and stones. Yeah.
Right. So I don't know. I think after the sticks and stones, maybe the flyers will come again,
three, 400 years or so, but this is it folks. It's what you got.