Ocelli and the Greeks, Sonic Event 18, and we are going to begin in yet again another
unusual place, and we always do because this is an unusual thing, which is why you subscribe.
Anyway, just before I pressed record, we were talking about restaurants and places to eat,
and, Greg, it sounds like that's the same thing.
Oh my goodness.
No, no, you eat at a regular, you just eat out or you eat, but a real restaurant is where
you dine.
There's a difference.
Dining?
So when someone says, I just went out to eat, okay, I don't really ask, was it good?
Because I know it's all right.
You know, you were hungry, now you're not.
Right.
But when you say we dined at so-and-so, oh, what did you have, how did they prepare it,
what was their special, who was cooking tonight, who was the chef tonight?
Big difference.
You know how I used to say most American children are raised, they never had real milk, they
never had real cheese, they never had real bread, you know, like that comes out of plastic
and all that.
They never really had that.
All the way, I think, I still met people in their 50s and 60s that still have not had
real food.
I know it sounds kind of crazy, right?
No, it's not.
But this is something that, yeah.
Yeah, not too crazy, because look, it's rare to me to meet somebody who's actually had
real, I mean, the big difference between, I mean, anything, milk is one of those primary
examples.
They don't know what to do when they actually have real milk because they're used to that
stuff that's in the plastic bottle and has been cooked and God knows what else was actually
in it.
That was planned, by the way, because people, you see, a quick way to survive is to get
milk from an animal to stay alive and to thrive off-season, let's say, or stay alive.
They decided that they're going to put Americans through a hard time in the 1800s and the 1930s
and again, and they said, well, we've got to screw up their food supply before we, right?
Because if we give the Americans a hard time, they're just going to flip us the bird and
say, we have cows, right?
But if we screw up their cows, when it's bad, they're going to go to their cows and they're
not going to get much.
This was proven in Korea when, after the Korean War, they introduced processed milk and the
average height and the average weight went up 20, 30, 40% because the average Korean
was about five foot zero, right?
Now the average Korean's five foot seven, five foot eight.
So tall, they're big, because they got experimented on with processed food.
The expensive nature of it, and most countries, by the way, when they buy milk, by the way,
by the way, in South America, you might buy it liquid in a container, but it originated
as powder somewhere.
So the dairy gets deliveries of powder milk and they add water to it and then they fill
jugs and they bring it to you, especially places like Mexico and whatever.
Now someone might say, well, I live in Bolivia or I live in Mexico, I live in, we get it
from a cow.
I'm not talking about that.
I'm talking about the supermercado.
Cuando compras leche en la tienda, okay, es de polvo y agua.
So when you buy it in the store, it's powdered in water.
Now here's the thing.
This has come up several times.
Like tonight, I had a beautiful salad and a roast chicken on mesquite wood and the chicken
was salted in water for about half a day, then rinsed and then hung to dry.
And this has happened about four times last year when I mentioned to people, if you're
going to have a steak or a roast or a turkey or a chicken, hang it to dry for a few hours,
half a day.
A day is even better.
In the fridge, out of the fridge, doesn't matter if it's, you should brine it.
And the response that I always get back is, no, Greek, because I want the meat to be juicy.
And I go, oh, slap my forehead, not at all.
What's wrong with these people?
Right?
There's nothing wrong with them.
It's interesting because I've actually seen people like they take basically a bottle of
Italian dressing.
Oh, no.
I don't want to hear that.
Please.
I'm still digesting.
Okay.
Yeah.
So, okay.
This is why you dry the meat.
Okay.
There's something called, there's a scientific term for it, but if you have water, the temperature
can only, at present, the temperature can only go to the boiling point of water.
And once all the water is burned off, then the temperature can rise.
You could do this with a pan.
Got one of those laser thermometers.
Get a big-ass cast iron pan and start warming it up.
Put some water in there.
And not until the last drop of water is evaporated will it go above 212 degrees Fahrenheit or
100 degrees Celsius.
It's amazing how that works, right?
So when you're doing an animal in the fire or in the oven or whatever, even frying, that's
why frying is so delicious because it's rapid, you want to rapidly crisp the outside.
And usually that takes between 400 to 475 degrees, mind you, very rapidly.
And then lower the temperature so it cooks the inside up to whatever, 120, 130, 140,
whatever, how you like it.
Okay.
So now, if the meat is full of moisture and you put it on the fire and you want to get
a sear on it, well, it ain't going to get above 220 or 210 until all the moisture is
gone, right?
So now you're boiling and steaming the meat, you're thinking you're getting a sear.
Now a lot of people think, yeah, well, I put it right on the hot cast iron that's dry or
the grill.
Yeah, but this is different.
It's not the same to get it evenly on the entire surface.
So when you, actually there's some, I've caught in through my history of looking at the stuff
that they show people to learn how to cook, oh, just pat it with a paper towel first,
you know?
No, dry it out.
Dry it so it's dry to the touch.
In other words, if you hold it in your hand and give it a gentle squeeze, it should not
release, it should not feel moist, it should feel just as dry as your hands were if they
were dry.
Right.
You're not going to end up with a bunch of liquid on your fingers if you do that.
Yeah.
Right.
And now when there's no moisture that's above the humidity level of the room on whatever
you're cooking, once it goes into a 400 degree, above 350 hopefully, you always want to start
at very high and then lower it down, right?
That's how you get that beautiful sear, that color, that crispiness, that seals it.
You know, people cook a steak and all the, I said, you know, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
What do you mean what I'm doing?
I said, all the juices are going into the fire.
He said, that's all your flavor.
The steak is crying, it's leaking like crazy.
That's all your flavor.
I said, when I do steaks or anything on a grill, there's not one drop, not one drop.
There might be some fat that might melt, but never drop.
You see?
Same with a chicken or whatever.
Right.
So I see people cooking, I said, what are you doing?
Look, it's dripping.
He says, yeah, I'd always like that.
I said, it means you always dump the flavor out.
Ah, I see.
Okay.
You see?
Because the reason why is because it was wet to start with.
Right.
So we'd get into that.
So, yeah, these things are not discussed.
I think I've sent you pictures also of baked goods, pizzas, right?
I think because you appreciate a good pizza probably where you are, you probably can't
get one, right?
Right.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Well, I've got some people here, some fellow has sent me pictures of wonderful pizzas from
a food, I think I might have done on a Skype a while back, and you thanked me for it and
all that.
But there's more tips I want to give on that.
I'll go against any pizza dough method or pizza, whatever, like if I gave it to, you
know, the best pizza in the world, the most snobby pizza people in the world are the Napoletan
in Naples.
It's very precise.
If you don't do it that way, forget it.
If one of those chefs had my pizzas, he says, it's not Napoletan, but it's excellent.
Right?
How do I know?
Okay.
And it's a very simple way to make the dough.
And here's the thing, when you do the classical baking school methods, you have to use a certain
flour, you got to use a certain water, you got to, all right, no.
With this method, you could use any flour, literally, even like just junk, all purpose
flour from Walmart, it'll still come out wonderful.
But you got to follow a few easy steps, it's a no-knead method, there's no kneading at all,
you don't have to do work, anyone can do it, really.
If you can walk, and if you have light in the room, and you got loose, most of the fingers
on your hand in one eye, you can do it.
I mean, it's so simple.
It helps to have good water, though.
Well, yeah.
The water should be clear, it shouldn't, this is what I tell people, this is how you know
if your water, you pour a bowl of water out of the tap, put it on the table, wait 10 minutes.
You can cover it with a plate or something, or a lid of some sort.
Wait 10 minutes, and when you remove the plate, sniff it.
Whatever you sniff at that point is in the water.
If it smells like sewer gas, guess what?
You got sulfur in your drink.
If it smells like chlorine or bromine, guess what you got on your water, right?
Now, I'm a little sensitive to it, and what makes, I ask people, what makes a really good
chef?
And they think, oh, usually the most common thing is the ingredients.
I'm like, what do you mean?
What do you mean the ingredients?
If I give them to your wife or my wife, the ingredients are going to be wasted, going to
be ruined, right?
It's not the ingredients, no.
You have to have a very good sense of smell and a very good sense of taste.
The better your sense of smell and your sense of taste, the better you'll be at cooking.
So I have an old adage where, you know, when someone is a little, you know, fried, you
know, is not too strong of a person, let's say, say we're going to leave you behind with
the women and children, and you're going to cook.
I regret saying that because I didn't ask him if he had a good sense of smell and taste.
But anyway, bad joke.
So, yeah, it's so if if you can smell like a dog, if you can smell through concrete, you'll
be a really good chef. And that's what really discerns the really good chefs is their sense
of taste and their sense of smell.
So I just want to bring up those points in case anyone wants to roast anything, any animal.
By the way, I've talked about calories often, right?
By the way, we're not going to focus on food and all that, but I brought this up, you know,
the calorie thing for anybody that's new here.
Real short, unless you're pooping, charcoal calories are irrelevant for food value, right?
Because calorie in order for the caloric measurement to hold as a as a whole measurement or
an applicable one, the contents are carbonized.
So the contents you pass are not carbon irrelevant.
The other thing is protein and carbohydrates.
What they're there's no such thing as a protein, by the way, it's just the name.
You could look it up in all their clinical whatever.
They're not testing. No one's ever found or tested for a protein.
That's what I don't like. Carbs are like protein.
That's all urban myth, urban legend stuff, right?
What they're telling you when they say they have a protein, it's an amino acid.
That's all. And an amino acid is a trace aspect of it.
Everything's got amino acids in it.
Carbohydrates. OK, I got a hamburger bun.
That's carbohydrate pasta, right?
Carbos, carbs, carbo loading.
Right. OK, but carbohydrate is also gasoline.
Oh, no, that's hydrocarbons, Greek.
OK, so there's no they don't know what they're talking about.
You'll find amino acids and carbohydrates both in in plants and in animals.
Almost sometimes, for example, I think it's you don't want to do.
Here's a shocker. You're ready.
OK, whenever you eat or drink, especially drink, it has to be activated through the liver.
So if you in other words, the liver gets activated based on what you eat, what you drink and how much
your liver can only handle three to five ounces of input at a time.
Hmm. That sounds crazy, right?
Because that's a quarter pounder, right?
Sixteen ounces, quarter pounders, four ounces.
Right. Yeah.
I was thinking three ounces is only what a quarter of a can of soda.
It's small. Yeah, yes.
Well, well, look, that's all your liver can handle at a time.
And when you start putting more than that every 10 or 15 and a half, 30 minutes, by the way.
When you write, when you put more than that, the body gets complicated, very complicated.
That's why you look at European dinners.
They last hours.
They sit there, small dishes, small plates, you know.
Right. So this is the old so they leave a little food on their plate.
You know, it doesn't mean they're going to throw it away.
Yeah, so it's very interesting how all these things work.
Somehow we'll have to get into that because this is crucial in the way people function.
When you drink water, three to five ounces at a time, doesn't matter how thirsty you are.
Right. Unless you're desperate for, you know, drinking a whole thing or whatever.
So, I mean, this is very, it sounds very unusual, but this is how the body works.
Give me an example. When you look at military canteens or how people, when they traveled, how they brought what food and drink.
They had a they had a wine skin, right, or skin or a canteen of some kind.
Sometimes it was a pot, metal or terracotta, or it was an animal skin.
Now they have canteens of every type.
Right. That's all you need. Why?
Because you're not going to sit, you know, the canteen holds 40 ounces, a big one, let's say.
Right. You know, that's enough for the whole day.
Just sip on it. Right. Right.
You see. So this, this, this, this massive consumption of liquids, foods and all this.
Yeah, it's it's tearing people apart.
I'm not talking about fasting.
We're just talking about, you know, you should eat when you're hungry and drink when you're thirsty.
Yeah. Think about it.
That's what I wanted to bring up tonight.
Oh, also from the chat.
Yes. Let's talk about sainthood and all that stuff.
Yeah. Francis of Assisi came up in the chat.
Yeah. Same category as Mother Teresa, Dalai Lama.
I think they're going to canonize Mother Teresa.
Right. The criminals at the Vatican.
Yeah. I think I read that.
Yeah. Yeah. Who's the other one?
Gandhi. OK.
In the 80s. This is information I've had in the 80s and 90s.
This is 30 plus years ago.
OK. Should I go down the list real quick?
Well, you start with Gandhi, though, because Gandhi is one of those guys.
I have read some stuff on him.
And, you know, it's it varies because it's very interesting.
Some of the things he did, the statements he made.
And then you get into some of the stuff about his personal life and his business
life, which was supplying young boys to the English, the what are they called?
The cafe?
The people that ran from England, let's say, that were in charge of the colonial
but I think it was which city it was.
I don't want to get in trouble by mentioning stuff that's wrong.
But I'm paraphrasing here.
For most of his life, most of his life, he was an interceder to supply
the proclivities of the British men for young Indian boys.
OK, that's what he did.
And when they go missing, of course, they would not be returned.
He would have to come up with excuses and payments to the families and things.
Right. Not not not part of the A&E biography.
But yeah. No, you don't get that.
Total scumbag. Right.
The other one, Mother Teresa, I'm not going to give the figure was in the 150
million, 50 million. Somebody needed that in the Vatican.
She goes, I'll raise it by selling children.
She got more than that.
And she was a horrible, horrible individual.
Right. Dalai Lama.
By the way, that that accent, he doesn't have an accent.
He sounds like an American.
He just plays that accent because people think it's more spiritual.
Right. Another scumbag.
CIA acid.
OK, so if you go back to all of the saints, it's exactly the same.
These are the Vatican and these religious authorities are not going to put good
people in front of you ever, never, ever, ever.
That's why they change the identity of the biblical Christ.
Show you show you a guy nailed to a cross wearing a diaper.
Right. Right. Or
Mother Mary and baby J.S.
U.S. in the May.
You're right. And the three wise men that never happened either like that.
The there was two or more Madre that came from the East.
These were bad motherfuckers.
And he was the Christ was two years old in his father's workshop.
I mean, that's really easy.
I could you could look that up right now while we're while we're while I'm
speaking, you could have looked it up and read the verse.
But we don't do that here. Right.
Right. So or anyways, nobody should be doing that.
Right. Well, the and an interesting thing that was brought up there is this
other you know, I love how one report of one thing is supposed to back up the
report of another.
All right. There were stigmata, stigmata, stigmata, because it's not stigmata.
It's stigmata.
Totally different. I know.
Potato and potato.
Right. There are the same tomato and tomato.
Stigmata and stigmata are not the same.
Stigmata means like a scar.
OK. Right. But stigmata is this Catholic thing.
Well, that's where the hands are supposed to bleed.
And you're supposed to bleed in the positions where allegedly supposed to be
nice. Yeah.
But well, what what a scar versus.
OK, so that's what that means.
The scar. OK.
But stigmata means something else.
OK. Like gay.
You know, if you're gay, you're happy, period.
Could be now. Happier man sleeping with a man.
Yeah. It's that it's that much.
It's that much of a difference, actually.
And in the same category.
It's bizarre. Yeah.
Well, look, it is bizarre.
That's that's a little tough to swallow, because I mean, it's it's like, oh, we
just talked about being gay. Now you're going to swallow.
Hey, you know, when in Rome.
So, of course, of course, I got a real lascivious joke for that.
Maybe it's even too lascivious for this.
But anyway, we're all adults here.
No, I don't want to say it. All right.
Fair enough. But anyway, you got you got to break the tension once in a while.
I mean, you will.
The thing is that our first date.
No, it's not. Not for you and me, but for somebody listening.
You know, there's a third party present here.
And I guarantee you some of them.
This is tense because, you know, you just turned a whole bunch of stuff on their
head. Mother Teresa's scumbag.
I know I was raised on it.
Not really. You take it or leave it.
The the I was raised in a Greek Orthodox Greek.
And I have relatives in Greece.
And I talked to him and I'm like, oh, my gosh.
Just in Greeks, it's a story.
And I see go. Yeah.
Yeah. If you ski, I thought, right.
It means if you're Greek, your family and your religion are the most important things
to you. Right. And I'm like, oh, my gosh, I got to go.
I got to go rearrange my sock drawer.
Please leave me alone.
Why are you calling me?
You know, is there anything wrong with them?
No, there's nothing wrong with them.
It's just not for me.
So, well, I figured if you're going to go for what they give you, oh, my gosh.
Oh, my gosh. You're you're not.
No, it's not happening.
But here's the perfect part.
So Thanksgiving is not your thing.
Your family, I guess.
You know that that day was pretty close to Abraham Lincoln, they say.
And then Roosevelt brought it back.
And but I know around that time it was popular to hang thieves and things like that.
So that were that misgivings and things.
No, it's all fake. Of course.
But but what they put out.
But here's the beauty of it.
They tell you within the context and within the story, if it's mainstream media, it's
very accurate because all you got to do is reverse it.
Right. And that's that's how accurate they are.
And when I say 180 degrees, it's like might be 179 or 181, but close enough.
You're out of phase. Right.
So anyway, like, you know, when they say there's terrorism, it's really an exercise
and they tell it. Right. But when they say they had an exercise that they didn't
announce, it's real. It's real terror.
Do you remember the helicopters that were flying?
I shouldn't talk about this.
I'll just bring up the point. I won't tell you what happened because I was asked not to
say. I think it was the Obama days in L.A.
people were freaking out because there were low flying helicopters in downtown L.A.
between the office towers and lots of military helicopters.
Remember that? They said it was an exercise.
Yeah. Black Hawk helicopters.
Don't worry about it. Do you remember that?
Yeah. And there was there was even some gunfire.
That was not an exercise.
Right. That was something that they were able to handle.
And that's all I'm going to say.
And it was international.
Oh, yeah. Well, that's all I'm going to say about it.
I'll give you a fun thing, too.
Just, you know, current events.
You know, Tucker Carlson and Don Lemon both got let go by their networks today.
They were both fired. That's the headline.
Yeah. And the funny thing is, I'm telling you now, that's because they have a new job
and they've been given new jobs.
It's not really that they were fired.
They had more jobs in the equation.
So, you know, but I'll get it.
Dog bites man is not worth news, worth printing.
But man bites dog is right.
Exactly. Yeah. Saying that they're fired is worth making a story.
Saying you got another job is why waste the time or the pixels in this case?
The pixels. Right. They'll have a new job by next year.
Right. And believe me, it'll be according to the season.
They'll have jobs. You watch.
Each of them will have brand new jobs according to the season.
It'll make sense. And their new positions as talking heads.
Will be established. I mean, there's an order to everything.
I agree. Oh, there is. And by the way, just go back.
When I say when they say it's terrorism, it's an exercise.
And when it's an exercise, it's really terrorism.
You know, when I say it's when it's terrorism, it's really an exercise.
People nod. Yes. But when I say when they have an exercise, it's really terrorism.
Right. They shake their eyes open.
I'm like, what do you mean, Greek? Yeah, because you're never going to get all these
exercise unannounced because it's a it's a it's an action.
To put something down because it makes them look bad if something happened that wasn't part of their plan.
And they're very good at stopping them.
And it shows me that how how many people are.
I shouldn't say I have access.
I do. And I'm privileged.
I get a lot of privileged information.
And very often when someone tells me, if I tell you this, you can't share it.
All right. And I'm like, yeah, that's why I can't.
I have to keep my right.
The only time I did share something like that was when Trevor, we were talking about
hurricane abatement. He sent me a package of all of his notes.
And he says, I don't want this going out.
I don't want this design going out.
I said ever. He says, well, as long as I'm alive.
And I said, oh, so while you're alive, you don't want it.
But when you're alive, it's OK.
He says, yeah, when I'm when I'm no longer alive, I'll be on my next journey.
Do what you want. Well, he passed away in 2016.
So anybody wants to know about Trevor, James Constable and what I do for hurricane
abatement, have at it.
I've already put a lot of the stuff out there.
People are building devices.
These I can say what it is.
It's a double mirror with silk.
It's using silk. And it's a I haven't gotten into a lot of people who have the room to
use the big guns, the big water guns to go, you know, the other side of the planet.
There's methods to do, you know, for timing and all that.
So that, you know, I'll share that.
But just to harken back to what I was saying about terrorism and exercise and exercises
are real terrorism. Yes.
If if the exercises that you see, you've seen this many times in this city
or whatever, how low flying helicopters and troops on the ground.
And we called the Pentagon.
We call it no response.
But at the end of the day, they said they were doing and conducting an exercise.
And that's it. Right.
Yep. Nope.
That was they were fortunate.
Let's say so far they've been fortunate where nothing got picked up.
A few things did get picked up.
I don't need to get into which ones they use your imagination.
Maybe we'll do a talk. I have to make a list.
It was a recent one a few years ago.
I had to deal with an RV exploding in Nashville.
Right. That was one that that they missed and they covered up very sloppily.
But the yeah, this.
OK. That was international also.
It wasn't alone, whatever.
Oh, anyway, think about it.
I wasn't aware of that part of it.
But OK. Oh, yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
They they always throw the wacko element in there to distract you.
Like this guy believed the reptilians run the world and all that, which they do.
But they made that the emphasis. Right.
Yeah, I know. It's just like they're panning Bobby Kennedy, Jr.
now because, you know, he's a conspiracy theorist when he really wasn't.
And he actually hasn't embraced conspiracy at all.
But he's been willing to call out the drug manufacturers.
So they dip him in that.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. It's today I was listening to something.
Sky Gills or something saying that, oh, the IRS is a money laundering operation.
I'm like, I've been saying that for like 30 years, man.
Where have you been now? I got some new information.
I'm like, what do you think?
That's why all of the gas stations in big cities are owned by ex-military and ex-cops.
Because you can roll because if you're ex-military,
you know, officer or an ex-cop, you know, more than just doing a beat.
You have a lot, you know, a lot of people that have tons of cash.
They have to move from all, you know, the ones, the public thinks you
you're supposed to be busting them, but you're actually protecting them.
If people don't know what's going on, it's the opposite.
So if you know, you know, a gas station pulls in one, two, three million a month,
they might clear 50 grand.
Right. So if you have a bank account, let's say, and you have 10, 20, 30 thousand
and you run a quarter of a million dollars through there, that's going to flag you.
But if you have a gas station that's running two, three million dollars a month,
you're making shit profit, nothing really.
Maybe if you make five, ten thousand dollars a month, you're fortunate out of two
million. Right. Oh, yeah. I mean, if you're making like nine cents on the gallon, I
mean, it's not, you know, it's a great example.
Huge volume. You have a huge gross coming in.
Yeah. So the bank is used to seeing your balance one, two million, three million, one
of that. So if someone runs a half a million in cash through there, it doesn't flag
anything because you last month you're one and a half million.
Now you're two million. You're already at three million.
You see what I mean? Oh, it's pretty simple, though.
If you look at laundering, these money laundering operations are these high, high
volume, high gross, but very low net businesses.
Right. And that's what I'm saying about the gas station is you got, you know, say
30,000 gallons of gasoline easily through a medium sized city.
You could run through that. Yeah, exactly.
So if you do that in a day and you make six cents on the gallon, your profit is low.
But you need 30,000 times, let's say, three bucks.
It's one hundred thousand a day.
Right. So you're pulling in three million a month.
Right. You're probably going to net for yourself if you're the owner, let's say
five thousand or maybe ten thousand.
If you're lucky for out of three million, which is shit, you know, return.
Right. You don't care because you're ex-cop and ex-military and you got friends that
run. They have tons of cash that need to net.
They need to run it through other accounts and they can't show up to the bank with a
bag full of cash.
So they run it through you and you get a percentage of that.
It works between two or five percent, the smaller the amount, the higher the
percentage. And but then again, if it gets too big, they they bump the up the
percentage again because the risk now is higher.
Well, the risk is much higher because if you had a million dollars to that equation
we just gave you, that's not not even noticeable.
I mean, that's nothing. Yeah, they could run it.
But if you say, Chuck, someone wants to run a million through your account, forget
it. You know, you'll have the FBI at your door.
Exactly. So these are all money you could.
What I'm saying is easily validated and verified.
All the big gas stations are ex-military and ex-cops.
Not all of them, but ninety nine point nine percent because they are they know the
circles. They know all that, you know, you know, like the big the biggest the
biggest. What was it?
Hash dealer in New York, you know, he knew he was going to get busted and the cops
come in his door at 1 a.m.
This is back in the 80s and the 90s or late 80s.
And he says, come on, we're going to see the judge.
And he figures at 1 a.m.
So they take him to the judge's house.
The judge makes tea and he says, listen, I know who you're using for transport.
I want you to use my friend Omar.
So this is people are so this goes back to the saints and the church and it's the
same thing. They the most wicked, most disgusting things are happening.
This is in scripture, by the way, what people what the general society considers
to be whatever is really the lowest of the low, you know.
So anyway, like years ago, I remember this woman, she was having problems.
She was a schoolteacher, administrator, husband, their whole family, like her mom,
her dad, her husband, her whole family worked in the school administration board.
And she had a problem child in and he wasn't academically fit.
You know, he was into not even sports.
He was just a troublemaker.
I said, yeah, if he's like that, he'll probably be president one day because they
pick degenerates. And and she looked at me and she didn't.
She says, you think he could be president?
She missed the whole part that I called her son a degenerate.
But anyway, yeah, yeah.
So anyway, a return to energetic thinking actually wrote that down because.
The there's a separation, but not much.
You know what I mean? Let's say we call things inorganic, OK, things that are not
alive like rocks. And how can you say that?
We're not sure why. It's easy to prove that a rock can be suffocated.
Right. I think I've gone over that.
Basically, take a piece of natural stone, cut it in half with a diamond.
So don't smash it with a hammer or a diamond blade.
So it's nice and smooth and cover it in epoxy coating, which is not clear coat because
that has pores and it's something that doesn't have pores and put it away.
And the other one don't do anything to it.
Rinse it off, put it away.
After about three months or half a year, cut them both in half again and you'll see
the one that was completely epoxy coated is a slightly different color, slightly
different mineral content.
It's not as hard.
Right. Where the one that wasn't coated is almost identical to how it was before you
started. Why?
Because the one that was epoxy coated, you actually suffocated the rock.
Literally now, but it's inorganic.
OK. A rock might have a thought once every thousand years for a few seconds, which is
more than most people admit, by the way.
But it might have a thought a thousand years ago for five seconds.
Hey, look at that rock. And she's real pretty.
I want to move next to her.
Oh, thought goes away. A thousand years later, gets his next thought for a few seconds.
Oh, where's that pretty rock?
I don't see her anymore.
Why am I down here? A thousand years later, another thought for three seconds.
OK. Doesn't that qualify as being alive?
Yes. But to us, it doesn't.
Not at all. Here's the other thing.
You ever grow up in a neighborhood where you have a lot of big trees as a child, you go
back and visit as an adult and say, well, I thought that tree was big.
It's not so big. Right.
You ever notice that? Or I remember this apartment building down the other street here
was really big. It's not so big now.
What happened? Right.
Is the world getting smaller?
You heard that before?
I always thought it was perspective because, you know, you just because you were smaller
at the time when you saw it, it appears bigger to you, you know.
Well, you actually saw more than the tree and more than the apartment and more than the
rock and more than your parents.
I mean, when you actually saw scary stuff in the closet, it was really there, just not
there the way you are told it's there when you're an adult, the same way you're told
like a rock is not organic when you're an adult.
Right. Right.
Let's be fair to rocks, you know, give them a fair shot, you know, just because they have
a thought for three or five seconds every thousand years doesn't mean that they need
to be tossed to the side as as inorganic.
OK, it's funny for someone who got a big gravel delivery.
But anyway, yeah.
By the way, when you when you move heavy materials with a shovel, you know, oh, my
back's killing me. Oh, I'm so tired.
I shoveled sand, gravel, cement.
Right. OK, you see guys at work, you know, unless you're doing this all the time, even
then you have to know how to pace yourself.
Or here comes the Greek and he's got a little baby shovel, a little baby spade.
Well, it's not short handle because you don't want to lean over.
It's got a long handle. It's a garden spade.
It's very narrow. It's like six and a half, seven inches wide, nine inches tall.
It's kind of flat versus a regular digging spade, you know, which is pretty, pretty
large. Well, he's got the little baby shovel.
What are you doing with that? So watch because I'll be I'll be shoveling this at a good
rate all day long. I'm not lifting that much.
Right. And you're like, you know, dropping a shovel down, you know, picking up two kilos
at a time. You can only do that for 15 minutes.
And if you try to do it for more without any breaks, you're going to really feel it at
the end of the day. Right, right.
But I got this little baby shovel and I'm doing high RPMs, you know, it's kind of like
if you look at someone who doesn't know how to ride a bicycle when they're going on an
incline, they're like stomping on mashing.
It's like they're mashing potatoes where someone knows how to use the gears or has
them. We'll go to a lighter gear and they're just spinning away.
Da da da da da da da da.
Right. OK, so it's like it's a form of gearing.
If you're going to be doing moving heavy objects for a long period of time, use a
smaller tool, smaller.
Right. So you want to lose weight.
Don't sit down with a box of cereal and a big quart of milk and a tablespoon.
Get the little Demitasse spoon.
Right. Demitasse is like a quarter of the size of a teaspoon.
You can eat your Cheerios with that one bite at a time.
Watch what happens. After like 15 of those, you'll be full.
You know what I mean? If you eat real slow.
Right. Same thing is true.
The opposite is true when you're working or the same is true.
Use a smaller tool where if if possible, when you're lifting heavy and moving heavy
material for a long period of time.
The same thing here. We have something called caliche.
Very, very hard dirt. It's basically bottom of a lake bed.
All of the southwest was under was basically underwater about 2000 years ago.
Anyway, you can't dig here.
It's very so I use a small you see people with big shovels and stuff.
Right. I just got this little pick and a small, tiny shovel.
And three hours later, I've got, you know, hold deep enough to bury someone.
Why would you have to do that? But anyway.
And yeah, like a dog.
Yeah, you still got to bury a dog five, six feet.
It's best. Yeah.
Thinking energetic thought.
Let my mouth run away there.
You go back and you find things that they look they don't look as big and it's about
perspective. Exactly right.
So what kind of a perspective do you have and how can you maintain it here?
Give an example. We all start off.
I don't like seeing kids.
Right. Because, you know, well, some a lot of them are kids, by the way.
There are very few children that are left.
They have this thing in the Western culture, mostly in America known as the kids
culture, right? The Disney, the toys, the shirts, the parks, the, you know, fast foods.
Right. When do you switch over from Santa Claus, let's say, to know Santa Claus?
When do you switch over from that to the other?
You see, when does the perception change?
Some people want to argue and say, oh, between eight, nine or six and seven.
Some children are like, no, there's no switch.
It seems like it's personal preferential or it's just when do you change your
perception? But it's not just your perception, but the people around you.
Right. Because I've seen, quote unquote, these what they call disabled, whatever
adults the guy thinks he's thirty five or a big old fat white boy living at home
with his mom's mom takes care of him like a baby.
Have you seen that? Yeah, mentally.
Yeah. OK. Right.
Well, when does that what does that perception have to do with it?
Right. Well, then it's because he's being accommodated to be like that.
Right. Right. Well, it's kind of difficult to do it.
You know, I've seen somebody try and do that the other way.
OK. There are some people that are incapable.
I mean, they're just not, you know.
Mm hmm. No, I understand.
But we're all incapable, right?
To a certain point. At a certain point.
Yeah. Yeah. When you're when you're growing.
But when you've grown and you're incapable and you have your all your physical
whatever, it means you missed the boat somewhere and it needs to be retrained.
It's kind of like when a child can't walk.
When do you stop helping him walk?
How many tries? You don't stop.
You just keep going. Right.
Something went awry.
A lot of these cases.
Anyway, there's a perception here.
And when your perception changes, when do you decide no more Santa Claus?
Right. What I've seen is the child is eight or nine and wakes up.
Mama, where's Santa Claus?
You know, what's wrong with you?
Your little baby is no such thing as Santa Claus.
But last year she was saying Santa Claus.
So, you know, oh, my gosh, what's going on here?
Right. Well, that's why when parents have rebellious adults, I say you need to
apologize to children for all the lies.
You know, I don't rely on my children.
You know, Santa Claus, Tooth Fairy, birthdays, it's all lies.
Did you ever apologize or you just kind of transition them over just without talking
about the transition either?
Right. Right. You see?
So this is like basic thinking.
When do people and why?
OK, the why this child culture was put on society is very obvious.
The same reason they took nutrition out of food and all that.
Right. Is because to make them ill prepared.
Right. Because children are just small people, inexperienced, small people.
This was known and abused, by the way, in the 19th century.
If you look at factories, there were five year olds.
You know, if you if you can hold a tool, you were put to work.
It could have been as young as five.
Right. They tended not to go younger than five because you weren't considered alive
unless you were five years old, because the typical age for breastfeeding was up to
five years old. And if you died before five, it was considered infant mortality.
Right. Not childbirth death, but infant mortality.
Well, even today they have the what they call the WIC program.
It's for women and infant children.
And when do they stop counting as infants at five?
OK, so keep that tradition.
Yeah, it's more than a tradition.
Slaves also when when a woman had a child less than five, the slave was counted as just
the woman. Right. But they knew if it was near five, you get a bonus.
You know, it's like getting the car with the CD player.
Anyway, I think we've gotten into slavery, which is, you know, slavery is a legal
condition and it's lawful and it's people as property.
Right. So if you're numbered, if you have a number that's specific to you, a serial
number, your property.
So the slavery issue never needs to be discussed because it's like, why is you know,
the sky is blue. Did you know that?
Right. No need to have a sonic on that.
But the energetic thinking part is very interesting because the trees, let's say I
noticed the apartment building that went back was a lot smaller than I imagined it.
But the tree, I can imagine, kept growing.
Right. Usually it was an elm.
I think so. Yeah. But it seemed a lot smaller because when I was younger and on my own
perceiving these things, because I was able to perceive what I did on my own.
Of course, people point things out to each other.
But while I perceived them on my own, they perceived really large because I was looking
at not just the physical structure, but I was looking at everything that went into it
also. Right.
Well, I would say a field does that, too.
If you visit a field later in life, you'll notice that it is much.
Smaller, much smaller.
Yeah. Yeah. Typically.
Yeah. So on the aspect of the energetic thinking, it should be rationalized that those
things have not changed so much, but we perceive them differently because of all the
overlays that we have as we as we change and we continue thinking in our minds.
You know, I've always brought up the idea like when you recognize something, cognize
is to have knowledge and recognize you're getting now.
So what you're taking in, you're comparing it to everything that it might be similar to
that you've taken in in the past.
And this is how the human mind works, just like a computer.
Right. Same thing.
It just compares things.
Right. Well, this is one of those reasons why memory is not a reliable recording device,
because you remember something as much larger.
And like you said, because the perspective, it changes.
And it's not that your memory is wrong.
It's just that it's been it's been affected by what you've taken in since.
Sure. And what happens is, especially when you I think more and more now, I'm not so
timid when I say this and I always suggested it, but now I don't suggest that I just say
it is fact and truth that it's all external input.
I wanted to send you an audio today and we had problems opening it, but I think I have
to put it up on the cloud and you grab it from the cloud.
Right. Probably.
See how easy. OK.
All of your memories, all of your thoughts, all these things are not in the brain.
They're processed in the brain, just like a transistor radio or radio playing jazz at
the picnic table. If you broke the radio, opened it up.
There's no jazz band in the radio.
It's broadcasting and transmitting devices now transmit more transmit more than receive.
I should say it's it's it's receiving.
That's why they're called receivers.
We do so much receiving that we have found I have found by speaking with people that
I ask them very nonchalant.
Do you ever get a time when you don't have any thoughts?
I'm like, sure, I see. I mean, I mean, not just thoughts, but I mean, like no voice in
your head, like you're not there's absolutely nothing going on, like you're not thinking
of anything or when you're looking at something or in a room or whatever, you're not
pointing things out to yourself, you know, whether it's your own inner voice, whatever.
You ever get a time where you could just clear your thoughts and have all that chatter
stop? They're like, you know, that's that's really interesting.
Actually, no, because wherever I go, I kind of like relate to myself mentally.
What's going on? I said, yeah, I'm not saying don't relate to yourself.
What's going on is, but is there a chatter behind it?
And they're like, yeah, there is.
I said, yeah, you'd better stop it because the chatter in your head is bothering me.
Right. But anyway, you know, are the voices in my head bothering you?
You know, so.
What happens with that chatter is I'm going to suggest that ninety nine percent of it
is not you. It's coming, it's just noise.
It's ambient noise and crosstalk.
What I mean by cross, but it's more direct and crosstalk.
Let's start off with crosstalk.
Crosstalk is back in the day with landlines when you go down in the basement, let's say
an apartment building, all the telephone lines come in.
It's like a trunk, hundreds and hundreds of wires.
You ever pick up a landline and in between dial tones or when you, you know, when you
start dialing the dial tone stops, stop dialing for a little while and put your ear to the
earpiece and just listen real quiet.
You hear other conversations going on.
Right, right, right.
It's called crosstalk.
That's because the wires are next to each other and the signals through inductance is
jumping off. It's very low level.
That's how taps work, by the way, they tap into the line.
But this crosstalk that's happening is directed towards you, just like the cell phone.
You know how indiscriminate landlines where, you know, it's on the wall, pick it up,
whatever, you know, they don't want number it's calling from.
But now you have a cell phone that's got not just the number, but it's got more
information. It's your personal thing.
It's almost like a digital ID, which is what they're talking.
When you get a digital ID in the future, by the way, it's going to be a number.
It's going to replace the phone number.
It's going to replace the Social Security.
It's going to replace the address, everything.
Right. So you just give that one number and that's your entire being there.
Right. They're trying to figure out how to present.
This already exists, by the way.
If you have an FBI file that they're going to use that number.
By the way, if anybody, if the FBI has a file on you, that's going to be your digital
ID. So if they've had a file on you for a few decades already, that's they already got
one for you. I already have one.
Yeah. So whatever number they have on your file is your digital ID.
That's so in other words, they're going to be pretty busy because they could probably
somewhat a group like that is going to have to sort it out, you know, through the AG,
Attorney General. But OK, so this crosstalk that I'm talking about is not indiscriminate.
There is a direct focus on everyone's mind that makes you think that it's your thought.
And it's not. It's and it's custom tailored to you based on what culture
you live in, your familial experience, your religion, your education and then your
personal proclivities.
Right. Like I've known people that he says, oh, I love my wife.
And when I'm out in public with him, he's looks like he's undressing other women with
his mind. I can tell I could see right through it.
I'm like, shouldn't be doing that.
He's like, what do you mean doing what I said?
Undressing women with your mind.
We're here trying to order a bagel.
He's like, he's like, God damn Greek.
How can you tell? I said, well, I don't know if everybody else could see it, but I could
see it, you know.
Right. So these guys.
So whatever proclivity you have, whatever desires you have.
And I'm talking about your most inner desire revealed to those that are sensitive
enough, just like if you're having a sensitive phone call on a cell phone, a very
sensitive. Do you think it could possibly be listened to?
Of course it won't be your neighbor or somebody else that maybe it is.
But, you know, right.
But there is equipment that could do that very easily.
Anyway, what I'm trying to say, this is a hard thing to tell people, is that your
thoughts are not your own.
It's what you decide to take in as a thought or recognize while things are
happening. The media, mass media and alternative media, so much as we say, are
masters at manipulating this, by the way, making you think things are said when
they really haven't.
One perfect example is when they did 9-11 two minutes later that a guy we believe
it alleging that is a possibility as a suspect is Osama bin Laden.
Five minutes later, everybody on the street saying Osama bin Laden did it.
And I said, well, where'd you get that?
The television said it.
I said, no, you didn't. He says is a possibility alleging that he's might be a
suspect possibly.
Oh, shut up, Greek.
What's wrong? They said he did it.
I'm like, oh, my gosh, these people listening.
You see what I mean?
No, I've seen that hundreds of times with all kinds of things.
That's what they said.
And I go, no, that's not what they said.
They said, you know, the people that are promoting things in school and the mass
media, pretty much religion is the same.
I had some Jehovah's Witnesses come to the door and it says, we're from the
whatever, whatever Jehovah says, oh, you're in the Jehovah's Witness Protection
program. And I started laughing.
Right. One of them started laughing.
But the senior one didn't find that funny.
And she goes, oh, no, we're here to tell you about Jesus Christ because
Armageddon is coming soon.
I said, hmm, Megiddo is in Israel.
It's not coming here right away.
And I said, don't you guys have me flagged, you know, you know, corporate
corporate to not come here because, you know, I teach this stuff.
Right. But not not your stuff.
But I said, oh, so you got the fear porn going pretty good.
I see. And I said, hold on a second.
So I came out with like a stack of Bibles, not a stack of Bibles, concordances
and Hebrew and Greek stuff and all this other stuff.
And I said, you ever knock on anybody's door and they and they study this stuff
and teach this stuff? And they're like, no.
I'm like, so you want to talk about Armageddon or Armageddon?
And she goes, well, you know, it's what we believe in.
I'm like, all right.
Right. OK, so this is not this is not what they're used to.
So what I'm trying to say is they have even though they're going and knocking
on hundreds of doors all day long at the end of the day, they're going to say
everybody is pretty much the same except for one or two or three.
How can that be possible?
How can it be possible that they show you the towers being nuked?
You don't know that. But, you know, the jet fuel burned them.
Right. And they presumably allegedly suspected possibly Osama bin Laden and the
people five minutes later say it was definitely.
But they don't know what ever said.
How does that happen?
How does that transition happen?
The media is a master at doing that because they know that if they use terms that you
don't use, you're going to ignore them and you're only going to lock on to the terms
that they're that they're using, like a name.
It's like, oh, they're going to tell us who did it.
Right. And they're ignoring he's alleged suspect and all this other stuff.
Right. But the same thing goes on right now.
Been accused of sitting in jail.
I've been accused as a constant one, because when they say someone has been accused, I
go, OK, so there's been an accusation made.
That doesn't mean sure that that's been proven or it's known.
And I've been accused of stealing rocks from the moon.
Well, I'm not at it. Yeah.
Let them have at it. But that's the thing is, you'll see something like that and
somebody will tell me, well, they said they did it.
No, they didn't. They said they were accused of doing it.
Right. Because you go to the well to get water, not popcorn.
Right. So what they're doing is they're going to the TV to learn, but find out why
and who did what. They're not listening, you see.
So what there was a heavy amount of programming to get people to rely on the
bullshit. Same with the church, not one particular church, all of them, all of them.
There's no exception. The same with the attorneys and the same with the doctors with
very little exception.
They're the only doctors.
There's some attorneys that you need attorneys for corporations, by the way, because
the corporation can't speak.
That's why I tell people like I think we were speaking to someone who just started
corporations that you screwed up.
If you're going to do a corporation, you go look at what Ikea done.
Right. That's how you set it up.
But anyway, you have a trust that's held by another trust that starts the corporation.
Right. You don't go and you know, anyway.
So all these things, where was I?
Oh, the how they get you to to the attorneys, you need an attorney to represent in a
legal court, the corporation, unless whatever.
And the doctors, you don't need any doctors at all except for emergency medicine.
That's it. The rest.
And and by the way, if someone needs surgery and it's not elective or if it's
ambulatory, that's emergency medicine.
You don't need them at all.
They don't know anything.
And here's the thing.
When it comes even to emergency medicine, they don't know anything at all.
Very little. Just enough to keep you alive.
There's micro surgery and there's chemicals that will keep you from passing out into
oblivion. By the way, when when you die, you you're one of some some people, most
people, I should say, if you don't die violently and in trauma, severe trauma, you
still have some consciousness and you realize you have consciousness.
But there's no breathing.
There's no feeling of body of warmth, sensation, you might sense that you're laying
down on the ground or in a twisted mess, but you don't feel it and you know you're
not breathing. So how can you be thinking?
Right before whatever, you got to be careful.
That's one of the things that I'm so harsh about is, believe it or not, if you're a
staunch Catholic, when you die, if you think you did something wrong.
You're going to hell and it's going to be just like the hell they show you in church.
Or if you're a Christian or whatever and you think you're good, you're going to go
to heaven, it's going to be just the fairy tales they tell you.
Right. If you're in ancient Greece and you think that you when you die, you're going
to go down to the River Styx and you're going to see Morpheus and you need a coin
and all. You're going to see all that they're going to play out in your mind,
everything that you believe in.
That's why I tell people, careful what you believe in.
I'm very venerable. Part of this mass media thing is to tell to respect other
people's faiths and religions.
And the Bible says that to leave them alone.
Right. But the thing is, what I'm saying, if you read scripture, it says someone's
whatever, just leave them alone.
Don't talk about their gods.
Don't talk about whatever. Yeah, that's that's fine.
I know it says that in scripture, but that's not what I'm doing.
Yeah. Among the Greeks, you go to Tartarus.
Wasn't that the thing?
Yeah. Tartarus.
First, yeah. The river of forgetfulness and Morpheus.
And anyway.
Yeah. So but but here's the thing.
What people think is in the law book, you know, what's called the Bible is not in
there. So I'm telling people, if you think your morality is based on something that
you've been told about, you better check it because it ain't so.
Right. Just like there's a guy I listen to about the Treasury's corrupt, the IRS is
corrupt, the politicians are corrupt.
You know, they're embezzling millions and billions of dollars.
I'm like, no, they're not asshole, because the money comes from your signature.
You're just a sore ass, you know, just go to the bank with a pen and whatever number
you want to write, one hundred and fifty million.
They're going to honor that, but they're not going to give it to you.
They're going to take it. Right.
Yeah. So anybody can do this.
I don't want to hear about the government or politicians embezzling hundreds of
millions. Look, if you got a pen, you can do it, too, but you're not going to get
it. They're getting it because they're part of the inside thing, you know, because
they're part of a racket.
That's why it's called racketeering.
So that's why when let's say I go shopping somewhere and the checkout, you want to
donate to this, whatever.
I'm like, what's wrong with their hands broken?
Like what? I'm like, well, you know, money comes out of your signature.
If it's an orphanage, all you got to do is give all if they're 18 years old, give them
some pens and whatever they need for food or money or expenses, they just write it
down, blah, blah, blah, and get it.
What? I don't need to donate for that.
Anybody could generate funds from your signature.
This is the law. This is how it works.
But then it doesn't work that way.
They're not going to give it to them. I'm like, yeah, that's right.
So what are you doing here? Where once you get pitchforks and torches like the end of
the Frankenstein movie, you see, it's not my fault.
Right. I don't care.
But anyway, so there's something going on with mind control.
You notice I haven't said neuro linguistic programming.
I haven't said mind control and all that stuff, because that's part of the alternative
media. The MK ultra just means mind control ultra.
And the control is spelled with a K instead of a C.
Presuming. Right.
Because it's the Germans, the Germans.
All right. Deutsch.
So what I'm saying here has nothing to do
with all the mind control and all the brainwashing.
Because, look, the elements of brainwashing are fine.
But I don't I wouldn't call it.
I would prefer not being brainwashed, but I would prefer washing my brain.
Right. Why don't you wash your brain instead of being brainwashed?
Because brainwashing sounds dirty.
But washing your brain sounds clean and proper.
It sounds intentional.
Yeah. Intentional and positive.
Where brainwashing sounds negative effect.
So notice I haven't used any of that because that's not where I'm going with this.
Where I'm going with this is mind your thoughts.
And you've been told about this.
Even in scripture, it says who wants to go into the man, the man's thoughts and his
heart? It's wicked.
Now, it's not it's that is not a direct condemnation of people, but the
thoughts and what they feel is it's a condemnation of there's a big difference
there. When you read that, I think it's in Jeremiah 17 or something.
Don't hold me to that.
That's always the concept they go into where it's, you know, not because you say, OK,
well, look, the person's never done anything wrong.
And you go, yeah, but.
But their thoughts are wicked because they're being input and they're and they're
putting up with it, just like the people that put up with whatever.
Right. Right.
So it doesn't mean the people are wicked, but what's passing through them is it's just
like there's a little rascals.
Don't drink the milk. It's sour.
If I say little rascals, we lost like 90 percent of the people here.
Right. Yeah. I bet you a lot of people have no idea what that is.
Yeah. OK. Don't drink the milk.
It's sour. Do you remember that?
Yeah. Yeah.
OK. Does that mean that milk is bad?
No. This particular milk is sour.
You're. But here's the thing.
When you spend your entire life from raised in a children's kids culture or at five
years old, you're holding a shovel in a coal mine.
Right. And you're beaten to death if you don't work, by the way.
And it's very easy to say that he fell down.
Right. Of course.
There's a lot of stuff going on like that more than anyone wants to believe.
But if you look into it, you'll find it.
Not that I'm looking for it, but I come across it.
What I'm trying to say and to really, really implore here is that just because it
sounds like your voice in your head, it's not you.
Not until you know how to shut it down.
Now, I've gone into this in the past.
It's very important when the mind is busy, the body must be still.
And when the body is OK, when the mind is busy, the body is still.
And when the body is busy, the mind is still.
Give you an example. You ever see like a gable roof that's got quite a good slope on
it. You're nailing shingles and you got to really careful because if you start falling
off the roof, there's nothing to grab on.
You know, land on your ass. Right.
And the thorn bushes or something.
If you want to if you just pull up in somebody's driveway and you want to have a
conversation while they're nailing shingles up there, what do they say?
Hold on. I'm going to nail these next few shingles.
Then I'll come down and talk.
What? We can't talk. You can hear me just fine.
Because he's he's got to mind the angle of the roof so he doesn't fall over.
He's got to lay the shingles just right, because if he doesn't, if he leaves a waffle
print with the hammer too deep, guess what it's going to do?
It's going to leak. Right.
Right. So he's got to do all these physical things and he can't carry a simple
conversation because his mind has to shut down.
OK, here's the opposite.
They had all these degenerate guys from India as they were not all from India.
They gave them new identities as gurus and they sent them over here.
They had even the Beatles prop them up and other people.
There were these are total degenerates.
They're not gurus to get the American culture to to sit in a cross-legged style,
all the hippies in the 60s and slow down their body and then slow down.
They're sitting stationary now and to slow down their mind.
There's no way the minute you cross your legs and close your eyes and try to meditate,
your brain is racing so fast.
You're getting crosstalk from people next to you.
So they were trying to tell them they weren't doing it right unless they stopped
their brain while their body stopped.
That's how you make an entire generation insane.
You see, so when you're busy, let's say you're running a marathon, you can't think.
But when you're sitting still, let's say right before you go to sleep,
all these thoughts, very easy, very easy to come up, right?
Well, that's why clearing your mind, actually using something like,
you know, the whole like raking the garden, you know,
like when you rake the rocks and you do the Zen garden thing.
That's why that makes a little bit of sense because all of it does.
All of it does.
Going for a walk with a dog, right?
Or actually, that's too relaxing.
If it's too relaxing, the mind goes again.
But if you're, let's say something critical,
let's say like when I run power tools, you know, when I have a 12-inch cross saw,
you know, I really respect that.
You know, I don't have one of those saw stop things for the saw table.
That's where you put your finger on it.
It works a capacitive discharge like the phone stops the blade automatically.
You got to buy a new section.
It's really funny, you know, when you put, if you ran your hand over a table saw,
cut your hand or finger off indiscriminately.
If it's, the stuff that I use is very sharp.
I mean, I could cut a two-inch thick plank and it doesn't, you know,
hardwood and it goes through just like butter.
It's a really good demonstration saw stop where they have the saw going
and the guy puts a hot dog there like it's your finger and it stops, boom, right away.
You know, it just barely cuts the hot dog, right?
Because if you know anyone that works in a cabinet shop, you know,
let me see everybody who works here.
Everybody raise your hand.
You can have at least two people with missing digits, right?
So anyway, when I do stuff like that, the mind is totally empty.
So like sometimes if I tell the wife, listen, I got to just think,
I'll just fire up the chop saw for five seconds and, you know, because it scares me, right?
I mean, not scares me, I'm very respectful of it and, or the cross saw or the table saw,
let's say, and it clears the mind because I have to focus on the physical, right?
If you're watching a very violent action movie, you can't think about the,
you can't make the telephone bill, let's say.
Now that goes, that just goes right out your, you know what I mean?
Video games, you're playing an intense video game, all of your worries go away, right?
Right.
Okay, so keeping the body and the mind busy slows down the mind.
But here, what I'm talking about is something different.
Okay.
Oh, by the way, let me just reinforce this with what's going on.
When you stop the body, the mind starts to race, okay?
So if you lay down in bed before, and you can't sleep because you have all these thoughts,
that's good, and you're probably picking up on other thoughts.
Just like teenagers, okay, just, if you know anyone who runs ham radio or CB radio,
the length of the antenna is very important, and the equipment spacing, wiring, all that stuff.
Right.
When you're, when you start to mature and get bigger, and you get more gray cells hopefully,
and your body changes, you pick up different frequencies,
more like the frequencies that the adults pick up.
And you just came from an adolescent to an adult, let's say you're an adolescent.
Now, some adolescents, I remember a 13-year-old that looked like grown men, right?
13, 14-year-olds.
And others were slow.
I was a late bloomer.
But either way, they stay up all night because all the adults with all the fucked up mental
stuff going on are asleep, and their transmissions are shut down pretty much.
So the air is clear.
So the teenager's like, wow, isn't it great staying up all night?
Yeah, man.
And they don't know that it's because all the fucked up adults are sleeping.
That's why.
Right?
You do experiments with this.
This is in the American culture, Western culture more than other cultures.
But it's also prevalent in other cultures as well.
It's in the Mahabharata as well, somewhere.
I remember reading where the young people, there was hard to wrangle them because they
wanted to be up in a certain time, in a certain place.
But anyway.
I pretty much can't do any creative thinking until after midnight, generally speaking.
So the thing is, this is basically how the convention works.
The body is active.
The mind slows down.
The body slows down.
The mind is active.
So what I'm saying is to get a neutral perception and stop all that, because there are people
that spend their entire lives from adolescence, when they become adults, until they die, and
they don't have any original thoughts.
It's always like they walk into a room, and they're talking to themselves.
In your mind, you have an inner voice, it's called.
I'm telling you, that is not your inner voice.
That is an overlay of what society or education and your proclivities have.
And also, you've got to throw in what condition you're in.
Let's say you're hungry.
How can I be so hungry?
It's not even lunchtime yet.
I had breakfast an hour ago, right?
Things like that.
Or I'm feeling horny.
Or I'm feeling tired.
Why do I feel like I want to go to sleep when it's two in the afternoon?
Right?
Because you didn't do it right.
You're not noticing the day starts at noon.
But anyway.
Yeah, that's the problem.
That's a big deal, too.
So all these things in your mind, I'm telling people, I've been telling them, when are you
going to have an original thought, thought that is yours, that you have control over?
I don't know how to do it, Creek.
I don't know what you're talking about.
That's always my thoughts.
Look, are you sure about that?
Because I've found it to be contrary to that.
Just because it sounds like you and you think you're just very familiar with it.
Go talk to someone who's never...
You tie shoelaces all day long.
They say, well, which one do you tie first?
The left or the right?
People got to think about it.
Right?
Switch it up.
So here's the other thing.
If you run into someone as an adult who's never tied their shoelaces and you got to
show them, that's really something they really have to work on.
So I'm trying to say, start working on your thoughts and disseminating them.
And once you start clearing your mind enough, how are you going to clear your mind?
By being busy?
Not really.
We'll talk about that.
When you clear your mind and you'll notice your perception will change and you're going
to start developing who you are in your mind to yourself and this other stuff that's been
put on you from religion, family, culture, education, the way you're feeling, whatever
proclivities you've had.
Remember, I think we got in trouble for talking about women with big feet, you know?
So all this other stuff.
So that's not you.
I mean, it is, but it's not.
So what I'm saying is take a break from that if you think it isn't.
Watch what happens.
Now, most people are going to jump in and say, so that means that I have to make the
body really active so the mind slows down.
No, because then it just slows it down.
It's still the same feed.
If you put Fox News on and you slow the speed down or speed it up, it's still Fox News or
CNN.
What I'm telling you, it's all external input and you've been caught in a trap is what
I'm saying.
We all have.
So what I'm trying to say here is you must change your perception.
That's why I brought up when you go to a place that as an adult that you remember as a child,
everything looks smaller.
Typically.
It has nothing to do with it shrinking or you being bigger.
It has to do with the overlay.
So many years of overlay and input that you have that as a child you were fresh and you
saw more than the physical is why it seems so big and everything and everyone is much
bigger than you can imagine.
Is what I'm trying to say here.
So one thing, again, to go back to perception.
What I do is it's been doing this for years and recently the reason what motivated me
I put on a Castaneda audio book, something about fire.
Talked about there's one other one, a short part of it.
He talked about this and I told my wife said, you know, I do all this stuff.
I never, I never got any instruction.
Just like the emo stuff.
When I was teaching the emo stuff privately, I told someone, I think it was in town.
You have a person that was doing.
I said, you better stop doing that Greek.
I said, why?
Well, huh?
Excuse me.
Why would tell me why I should stop doing so strong about it?
Well, obviously you've been in some of the, the Taoist schools, some of the Qigong schools,
and you'll get in trouble if you do.
You're not supposed to say that.
You know that, right?
I'm like, no, I didn't go to any of the inner schools and all that.
No, no, no.
All right.
So it was funny listening to Castaneda and saying the same stuff that I've been doing
and trying to impart to people.
It's all perception.
So if you want to get this overlay, this crap that you think is you in your mind, just stop
it for a little while.
And then you discern.
It might be you.
If you're happy with it, with your inner dialogue, and you think it's you chatting to yourself
and all that, that's fine.
I'm not saying like you want to go to church and say a hundred Hail Marys and whatever,
and bow down and kiss the Pope's ring.
That's fine with me.
It's on my business.
But I'm just trying to tell you, they're not representing what you think they are.
Right?
So let's get everything straight.
It's kind of like when I talk about money, ain't no, it's not real money.
It's not even a bank note because the bank note is supposed to get something for it.
Take the dollar bills.
They're bills.
Who's going to pay those bills, right?
Right.
If it's a bill, who's going to pay?
They don't make laws in Congress.
They make what?
Bills.
And you're going to pay them.
They're passing the bill, passing the beginning to you.
Anyway, because they're in debt, not you, but you could pass the debt just like you
could pass whatever.
Like Chuck, if you owed someone a hundred bucks and you were ready to come and break
your fingers for it, could I just give me their number?
I said, give me their number.
I'll pay it for you.
What?
He's going to refuse?
Of course he's going to.
I could fill in for you, right?
Right.
I could fill in and say, hey, leave Chuck alone.
I got the hundred bucks.
Who are you?
Well, I'm the Greek in here.
I'm going to give you.
We're good now?
We good with Chuck?
Yeah, of course we're good.
You see, you could fill in.
So what is the United States is in debt and they're never going to get out of it.
So they pass it off to the people.
But the officials are not liable for it.
This is a criminal enterprise.
But this goes back to Babylon.
It goes back to Egypt, actually.
People think it's Babylon.
Sorry, I retract that.
It goes back to Egypt.
Okay.
So it's not like they're bad now.
They've always been bad.
You've heard me talk about George Washington.
He died at the first battle, you know, and then they found a guy with no teeth and that
looked like him and had the personage of him.
And that's why all the history around George Washington after that battle is how we're
going to put teeth in this guy's mouth to pass him off as George Washington.
There's some nasty stuff going on here.
Founding father is my ass.
I'm doing the jerk off sign now while you say father.
You know, that was an old sign people used to do when something was whatever.
Yeah, when it does not serve its purpose.
Yeah, at all.
Yeah.
And if you use your if you're a righty, use your left, you'll think it's someone else.
But anyway, what's new to you anyway?
Yeah, what's new to you is new to.
Yeah, it may not be new, but it's new to you.
So the thing of going back to perception.
So what happens is we when people admit to me that they have that is their voice Greek,
leave me alone.
That is me.
That is my inner voice.
It's very hard to get people to prime to the point where they actually can have a discussion
and dialogue about their inner voice.
Most people are like, get the fuck out of here.
I know it's I don't know what you're talking about or what they're saying.
If you translate it is I don't want to get I don't want to go.
I'm quite happy being, you know, the way things are.
Right.
So because it's perception back like when you were a child, what I'm suggesting is break
your stream of focus when you go into a room or a new situation to rec before you recognize
something right before you recog it, you will call it recogging for you.
Don't focus on and don't look at it with the typical stare and visual stance you normally
do.
Try to unfocus your eyes.
Maybe use your peripheral vision when you first go into a room.
Don't walk in head on before you walk in, turn your body sideways and try to look in
there peripherally just from the peripheral vision, which you can't focus.
By the way, your peripheral vision is designed to pick up predators.
OK, that's where your safety is, your peripherals.
That's why I tell people, you know, when you're more than two people in a car, no stereo.
Don't listen to music.
Everybody's looking at the road.
Everybody watches all the road.
Right.
Because the driver could be focused on one thing and the other person's focused on another.
Here comes a car sideways.
Boom.
Nobody saw it.
What do you mean?
Nobody says two people in the car.
Right.
It's just like an airplane.
You know, I got the left, you know, it's a check five.
Check five means in the Air Force.
It means I got your tail.
Right.
So anyway, start looking at things by not looking at them before you recog it.
Don't look at it straight on like you normally do.
Same with your hearing.
Practice hearing when you're having a conversation with someone in a room or put some music on
in the room that's pretty, let's say, not too loud, but fills the room with sound.
Try to focus on the sound outside of the room.
But I can't Greek.
I can only hear.
Well, it's too loud.
Then just turn it down.
So like, you know, let's say you have people in a living room and you have the television
on that volume.
But while you're there with them, try to focus on the sounds outside of the room.
It's kind of difficult, isn't it?
Right.
It is difficult to discern that.
Very difficult.
But that's what I'm talking about.
The same with your sight.
When you're looking at something, look what's going on around it.
Or before you look at it straight, look at it from your peripheral.
What you might find.
He'll give some personal experiences before.
When I do this, when I walk into a new space, I'll walk ahead.
Let's say a new house, right?
You walk through the door facing forward.
I won't.
I won't do that.
I'll turn sideways about two feet from the entrance and look across the road.
But look, my face is pointing across the front of the house.
I should be looking inside like everyone else.
But I'm trying to pick up peripherally what's going on.
And here I see this giant shadow being run across the room.
Right.
Okay.
A lot of people, once we've had this discussion,
they say, do you see like creepy crawlers?
Never in front of you.
Always on the peripheral vision.
Right.
Things like flash.
Boom.
Run by.
Yeah.
I see that kind of stuff all the time.
Okay.
Now you see what's going on a little bit more.
When you start to focus this way, or let's say perceive,
by listening through the sounds that you should be listening.
By not listening to the things or looking at the things the way you used to.
Right.
Use your peripheral vision.
Don't focus when you see something new to recog it.
Don't look at it head on.
Look at it.
Just turn your head away from it and try to look at it with your side of your vision.
Or the same with your ears or even touch.
If you go to some Asian cultures, when you tell them to feel this,
most Westerners will put their palm side down towards it and stroke it.
If you look at most Easterners, they don't do that.
They use the back of their hand a little bit.
You ever notice that?
Yeah.
It's a cultural thing because the back of the hand is more sensitive
because it's less used.
Well, it should be because you're not gripping things with it.
So yeah.
Yeah, exactly.
But that sensitivity is reserved more for temperature.
When they take a temperature, even on TV, what do they do?
They put the back of the hand, right?
Right.
You see?
On the forehead, not the front.
Sometimes they put the front also.
It's not as sensitive.
So your peripheral vision and your peripheral hearing is much more sensitive.
So what will happen then?
I'm not saying you should do this.
You see shadow creatures and things because they're always around us.
It's just so you stop getting used to that recogging that you're always doing.
You're missing out on a lot.
Once you start focusing on not focusing or unfocusing, right, your visual and your hearing,
you're going to start to pick up on the emotional qualities of things.
You've heard me talk about often when I bring up the emo, traveling, all expenses paid.
Let's say I'm doing a project going from, let's say, Tucson to Louisiana on the way.
I want to stop at a hotel.
I'm not going to sleep in the van.
Go to a nicer hotel and they give me the card, the key.
Very clean place.
I open the room.
Oh man, I think I want another room.
The room is perfect.
There's nothing wrong with it.
I'm not talking about the way I said about the Vegas guys with the ultraviolet light.
Nothing like that.
Well, I didn't walk in square.
I was like, oh, I don't have a good vibe with this room.
So I think I'm going to get another room.
I mulled it over for like 2.3 seconds.
That means one, two, and that was enough time.
And as I'm walking down the hallway to get to the front desk, there's a couple.
Walks right by me as if I wasn't even there and they're arguing.
And the woman says, oh, look, the key still works.
And it was the room that I just wanted another room from.
And she goes, I hope my fucking ring is here.
I hope the goddamn you and your mom.
I'm like, oh, my gosh, no wonder the residue of that couple being in that room,
even though it was clean, is still there is what I was picking up on.
The emo is lingering.
You see what I mean?
Right.
Most people are totally there's still sensitive.
They're just as sensitive, but they will ignore that.
Right now, was I right or wrong to do that?
Does it sound like a cycle instead of a hypochondriac?
Am I a psychokondriac, you know, or whatever?
Right.
Should we coin that word?
Maybe I don't even know if I'm using a psychokondriac.
I never heard of it before.
I'm trying to think of no reference.
Yeah, well, you can make words all day, you know, like agnostic phobia.
If you know Greek, you can make up words like agnostic phobia means fear of the unknown.
OK.
Anyway, we have some people that are Greek speakers here also.
So here's the thing.
Did I do the right thing or not?
I'm not looking for approval, but most people would say Greek.
You did do the right thing, right?
Well, I don't know.
I might say it would be better for you to clear that and take control of that space.
Yeah, but who's working for who?
The hotel is supposed to be working for me, not me working for them.
Because remember, it's temporary.
I'm a resident.
It's the only time that I'm a resident.
It's true.
But, you know, you could encounter the same thing in the next room.
Yeah, that's right.
But then you check.
But then what I didn't get into is I'm tired.
I'm traveling.
I didn't check the hotel.
You can also do the email on which hotel to go to.
That's true.
This has happened also.
We're a couple of parties, groups.
And we broke up and I said, I want to go to this one.
And you guys go to the other hotel.
When you go to somewhere like Palm Springs in the springtime.
OK.
It's all booked.
And anyway, how's the hotel?
It was more expensive.
It was crap.
I said, we had a great time.
Wasn't that great?
You know, so you could pick up stuff with people, you know.
And anyway, what I'm suggesting here is if I go to a place to be where it's service oriented,
like very often I run into people, I do a negative comment.
It's like, oh, that's not someone I'd go to a fancy restaurant with
because they don't know how to act.
Right.
But a simple example.
You ever see somebody, someone who's not used to being in like a being served,
is when they're at a restaurant, they drop a napkin or a fork.
They want to bend over and pick it up.
I'm like, no, no, no, no, no.
Don't pick it up.
You have waiters for that.
But I dropped it.
No, no, no.
You're not at home.
Right.
You get it?
There's a big difference.
How many times you've been in a restaurant out and someone drops a napkin.
I'm not talking about your purse or your phone or something.
Right.
The phone you use.
I'm talking about the restaurant stuff.
You don't pick it up.
That means you're not used to being.
You don't think you've been waited on enough or, you know,
I'm not talking about growing up with a silver spoon.
I understand.
Either.
Yeah.
It's just when you have to understand when you go to a place that offers a service,
are they doing that?
How many times have you gone to a place and you had good service?
And other times you didn't have good service in this place's work up to par,
you know, the similar, you know, one was good.
One was better than the other.
I'm talking like McDonald's or Burger King.
I'm talking about here, you know, which are, which are on the same par.
Right.
Okay.
So, yeah, it would be very similar.
You know, like if I go in to a McDonald's or a Burger King, which I haven't in a very long time.
And you, let's say you order a Big Mac and you open, it's all sloppy.
The patty is off to one side, Liz.
And I said, you know, the reason I go, excuse me, I like to speak to you.
She's like, what's the problem?
I said, well, I don't really eat here very often.
The reason I came here because the picture looks so good.
And look how this looks.
It's because, all right, we'll, we'll fix it for you.
They know this, but you see what I mean?
It doesn't look like the picture.
Right.
So it's either, either I'll take, I'll take it like it is,
but you got to take the picture down because that's why I came here.
You see, you see, you see what I mean about service?
Most people don't think like that.
Most people say, come on, it's fast food.
Now, of course, they're going to throw it together.
These guys are made of, what are you their attorney?
Right.
If you put up a billboard saying that you lend money
and you're a modern day bank, that's a lie.
Right.
You see, if you put up a picture and this is, you come in for this
and that's, you see, you got to, it's a service oriented business.
We're not, they're not trying.
They're supposed to have it done in the bag already.
Right.
Literally in this case.
So it's like this guy's Greek guy's a real asshole.
But you know, some people might, some people say, you know, he's right.
So either way, I'm saying these things because the, the, they all add up.
So going back to the emo, this is, this all ties into the emotional part.
Because you know what?
When I went into that hotel room and noticed that I had to walk
and turn around and maybe try another one.
If you asked me to explain why using basic logic and reason and, you know,
Hey, Spock, what's wrong?
You don't have a good, you know, well, the room was dirty.
Something was unprepared.
It was missing.
Yeah.
Well, the UV light at the Bellagio, that blew my mind.
Cause you know, this, these were like, you know, 700, $800 a night rooms.
This is where a floor you can't, you push the elevator button.
It doesn't go unless you have the card to go there, you know, that floor.
And he's out there with the ultraviolet lights.
It's a beautiful room.
He says, Oh really?
Look at here.
You see the nightstand.
See that splash right there.
That's semen.
I'm like, Oh shit.
Oh my gosh.
That right there.
That's blood.
He goes into the bathroom.
That that's urine.
Like, how can you tell him?
He says, well, you know, that's what he does.
He has one of these companies that does, I don't know what they call it.
Remedial work.
When, when someone gets shot in a hotel and they have to come and they tear out the walls
of floors and everything, you know, anyway.
He also has a power washing company.
I was like, Oh, it sounds real remedial.
The guy's doing like $25 million a month or something.
I was like, Oh my gosh.
Power.
He was doing like all the seven 11s in Nevada, Arizona, Colorado, you know, where they power
wash the oil stains out of the driveway.
Yeah.
Of course.
The contract for that contract for all the parking lots for like this mall, mall of the
main what's the big mall company.
And I was like, Oh my gosh, you know, anyway.
Yeah, not like that, but it's emotional.
So the emotional aspect of it is, you know, it, or you don't, you feel it or you don't.
And one thing we're going to talk about eventually is what this leads to is the emotional
change.
A strong emotional change will change your physical reality.
And a very simple way to say this, I'm just not going to talk about the emo, but I'm
just going to say this.
You have a mild mannered guy, you know, a real thin pencil neck guy, bachelor's degree
administrative at the post office for 20 years, got a really good pension.
You know, he's got, well, like a G 15 salary, which is over 120,000, right?
He's administrator.
Well, he takes a couple of days off, shows up at the office back at the post office with
a submachine gun and kills 20 people.
How can a guy do that without, without emotions taking over?
So that's what I mean about emotions can change your physical reality, right?
Or, you know, he's very mild mannered.
Why did he outburst?
Well, the logic and reason said, would say that's not possible, but emotion would make
him do it, right?
Well, it's a cascading thing too.
I mean, you move differently when your emotions are different.
You, you, that's right.
So emotions, emotions are super powerful.
Yeah.
Your tone of voice changes.
I mean, everything, everything gets altered.
It changes your reality.
And here's the thing.
What it will lead to eventually is you will change other, you can influence people can't
change them, but you can influence them.
I had someone visit here a while back.
We were talking about the email.
This is about what?
2014, 2015.
I think it was, we were already doing the original O and G and he says, you know about
this?
I said, yeah, I've been doing it for a while.
I didn't start talking about it.
He says, don't talk about it.
Greek.
I said, but yeah, talk about it.
I think, you know, I should talk about it.
Why not?
I said, because it's very powerful.
I said, see that woman there?
I'm going to make her scratch her nose.
I'm not saying he's, he's saying that he does.
And he said, well, you see that one there?
She's just started eating, but I'm going to make her put her food down and go to the bathroom.
And if she doesn't go to the bathroom in 10 seconds, she's going to pee on herself.
And she, and she puts her food down and she starts walking in the bathroom.
Then she starts racing to the bathroom.
Right.
Okay.
How can you do that?
Right.
Cause this is just imagine two aliens like in a twilight zone, they show up and they start
making people in the diner.
They look human.
And the, um, they start making people doing all kinds of stuff just for their own fun.
Right.
Imagine a twilight zone like that.
We started playing around people in a Japanese restaurant like that.
It wasn't good.
So I was like, okay, proven, proven.
But I said, I want people to know about this.
I want people to work and cultivate it.
Right.
So if you just discovered there's a game called basketball, do you think you're going to go
to Walmart or circle K, get a basketball and start playing tomorrow?
You could try.
Right.
Yeah.
But you're going to have to practice for what?
Maybe at least a week or two or three or maybe six months.
You'll be, you could make it a recreational part where you enjoy it.
And see if you, if you suck at it in the beginning, you won't enjoy it.
People enjoy things cause they're good at it.
Right.
Oh, usually.
Yeah.
So now what this leads to eventually, you know, influence people to start influencing
things.
I said, I'm going to give a couple of personal instance here.
There's something called PK psychokinetics where you move things with your mind.
Okay.
So about a month ago I'm scrubbing a pot, you know, I like to cook.
So when I, when I say I'm in the kitchen or whatever, you know, it's cause you know, you
got to clean up, right.
Even though it's two of us here.
So I've got this bartender's keeper, I'm scrubbing this big pot and I want to scour it a little
bit, get it clean.
And I'm running hot water and the, and I had turned the water heater up.
So the water is really, really hot.
I said, you know, I'm either going to turn on the cold water or I'm going to just turn
off the hot water.
Cause I have plenty of water here to work with, but I don't want to touch anything.
And this pot's so heavy.
I can't really lay it down.
I'm like, just go like that.
And then boom, I hear this loud sound and a click in front of me.
And the hot water valve shuts off and the water stops instantly mid flow.
You know, when you turn off the valve and the water still flows for about half a second.
This was instant.
This was like the valve snapped shut and the water stopped in the spigot.
And I have one of those kind of fancy gooseneck spigots that come up real high and
curved, you know, and it's wall mounted, not counter mounted faucet.
It's everything I have is for ergonomics.
And I stopped and I froze.
And my wife said, what's the matter?
I said, uh, I don't know how to say this, but I just turned the hot water off with my
mind.
She goes, great.
Fucking cool.
You know, that's great.
Okay.
The other day, uh, three days ago, four days ago, I'm gluing some, um, strips of
wood.
I was making a laminate because I'm building loudspeakers and prototyping them.
Um, and I've got some, uh, tight bond, waterproof glue.
It's wood, wood glue, the yellow stuff, the really good stuff.
And, um, I didn't really, I wasn't mindful.
So the top, you know, you pull, you know, how wood glue or Elmer's glue, you pull the
top and, uh, you pour it out and close the top.
Well, when I, last time I closed it, it was really messy.
So it was all, I try to pull it as like, this is not, I have to soak it in hot water.
I can't get the thing open.
You know what I'm talking about?
Chuck, you ever worked with wood glue?
Then it's hard to, yeah, it's hard to turn.
It got really crusty.
And I said, look, I'm doing some fine work here.
I gotta, I gotta, I can't neglect this.
It's $15 thing of glue and it's not worth, you know, I gotta just, let me just finish
the trim piece and, and, and mark everything off.
Then I'm going to take the glue.
I'm going to run it under some hot water.
Here's the hot water again.
I'm going to run it under some hot water and clean the top off.
Right.
Okay.
So I go back, I do the trim work or so, 15 minutes.
And I turn around, I have the, the wood glue right where it was.
I go to pick it up and it's so hot.
I had to put it down in my hand and the top of it was totally clean.
It was really hot as if it was in boiling water.
Okay.
I told my wife that too.
She's like, oh, that is so fucking cool.
I had not, I had just thought about doing that.
So I'm starting to get these experiences because I'm working on this stuff.
And that's all I'm going to say.
Normally don't share these things, but I think I'm onto something here.
And here's, and here's the thing.
I almost don't want to say this or wish I hadn't because if I don't, if I start getting good at
this and I can't figure out how to tell other people to do it, I'm going to wish I never said
it.
So I'm almost putting myself into place because that I have to figure out how it's done.
And other people, you know, you know what I say?
I won't talk about anything unless I show people how they can technically access it.
Right.
Like if, let's say you hear me playing guitar and you're like, Greek, how the hell do you do
that?
Well, you could learn too.
Do you want to learn?
But you see, you could take guitar lessons now from someone else.
But you see, so the interesting thing here is like with the weather work, you know, you
hear about mystics and whatever doing weather, you could do with your mind using the emo.
But technically, I could show you how to do it.
And I think some of the subs here have good success with it.
You and I think I've mentioned this before when we were on with Danny.
Danny asked me to stop the rain because his brother was visiting.
And you're like, what the hell are you talking about?
And then a week later, Danny's like, thanks a lot.
There was no rain for three days.
I said, you're welcome.
It took me, don't ask me, don't ever ask me to do that again because I lost a day and a
half, almost two days of time just to do that, to sustain it.
You know, that was technical.
It's not emo.
That was setting up devices and all that.
They caught it real bad in the Midwest, though, by the way.
You know, when you do stuff like that downstream, they're going to catch hell for it.
Usually, not always.
So anything about technically accessing is what I'm into.
If you have a special talent, oh, have at it.
I'm glad you do.
That means that no matter how much you tell people how to do it, they won't be able to
do it like you do.
I understand that.
Most things, whether it's playing guitar, weather work, whatever, the emo, all that
stuff, if someone's interested, you could talk about it and have them technically, what
I mean by technically access, you do bullet points.
You know, this is how it works.
This is how you set yourself up, right?
Just like playing guitar, right?
You know, or whatever.
So what I'm trying to say is for a long time, not just sitting in a Japanese restaurant
10 years ago or 9 years ago or 8 years ago with someone that visited, making people scratch
their nose or go to the bathroom.
I'm talking about if you can influence people that way using the emo and the PK, I think
it's time to start influencing objects.
And I've had these two recent experiences, and I've had more, but the other ones were
more subtle.
It can go either way, but these were in your face, like you're going to wake up, you're
going to notice these, right?
Look, it's always better anyway.
I mean, to me, you know, anybody can tell me that they're capable of doing anything,
but unless they can show me or they can show me how to replicate it, you know, it doesn't
mean much to my mind.
You know, it's like you could tell.
Exactly.
Like I've heard people say, oh, I know how to, you know, how to do this.
And I go, OK, do it.
Otherwise, it ends up being like the size of your penis or something.
Well, right.
It doesn't matter.
That's what you got.
Yeah.
So anyway, I would suggest that there is an interesting, I don't know if you guys understand,
there's spoon bending parties.
A lot of these psychics have, and they try to technically access it.
You know, I've actually, a long time ago, there was a video on that.
I said, that's not how I would do it.
I don't think the approach is wrong.
Either of these people are doing it hit or miss or whatever.
But they had a big box of spoons.
What made the video worth watching is at one point, they said, we did all the classes.
Well, no one bent the spoon.
But when we took a break and we kind of got into groups together, got some wine, started
talking, going outside, and we started laughing and joking, the spoon started bending without
even noticing.
Isn't that cool?
Yeah.
You see?
Does that mean like in order to bend spoons, you got to think about it and then stop and
laugh and joke?
No, it didn't work.
So there's more to it.
But what I know from making people scratch their nose or go to the bathroom at a Japanese
restaurant, that was pure emo.
And the level of setting yourself up for that is first, if you're used to and you're relying
on that inner voice in your head, which is not you, and it's not in your head, and you're
used to that and you're happy with that, you'll never even understand the weather work, the
emo work or anything like that.
If you start to unfocus on that and discern what is really your thought and what you are
really recognizing, really, versus what you're told.
Remember the guy who said Osama bin Laden really did it?
They saw it on TV.
He said he did it.
I said, I saw the TV, same thing.
He didn't say anything, but he didn't say he did it at all.
Just the accused, right?
That's how big the difference is.
So what the takeaway is, we've been told to focus a certain way, approach things a certain
way, it's not working very well.
If it's working fine for you, that's fine.
But you're not going to be able to do the stuff that we're talking about right now if
you're happy with what you think you have is happy or good enough.
I'm not saying that everyone, this applies to everyone, but just about everyone, because
the voice that you hear and the thoughts that you have when you see something, go into a
new situation or before you speak is not you.