Rated Y, Sonic Event 111, 1-11 that is. So anyway, how are you doing, Greg?
Alright, we're doing. How about we start going over some questions that have been sent for a while now, just sitting there.
We've got some pretty long emails. Some of them are easy. Some of them require some thinking.
What do you think about that?
Yeah, well, we were talking about the financial system from an email last time,
which bears going over a few times because there's a lot to it that isn't quite as advertised, right?
And we played that clip from that guy who was supposed to be the head of the – jeez, I forget what he was.
He's a financial advisor chairman, so yeah. But they all play that. They all play that.
OK, Frankie the Finger kind of thing. First time I did cocaine. What? What did I just say?
Anyway, we went to this guy's house. His 95-year-old mother lived on the very top floor and he lived on the ground floor in the basement.
Turns out he's a hitman and he has this drawer open. I walk in the room and it looks like he was collecting twigs, like two or three-inch long twigs.
I was speaking Brooklyn, right? And I'm looking at it closely and I'm like, that looks like a big net on that.
When I say twigs, like black pieces of wood. Well, it's not. They're not pieces of wood. They're actually finger souvenirs, right?
A drawer, several drawers. And he said, I don't like to torture people. I just want to do it when they don't know what's coming, right?
I'm like, oh my gosh, this is interesting. One day I might have to write a book and listen to this guy, right?
OK, so he's bragging and talking, right? Whatever, right? And he says he likes – when he has someone with him, they use a lock cutter because when you use a knife or something,
when they hit bone, people flinch and they make the process much longer, right?
Where when you use one of those lock cutters, you have so much leverage, you don't feel anything, right?
He had one specially made.
Bolt cutter, yeah.
Yeah, a bolt cutter. Yeah, you don't feel – people flinch too much with other instruments.
So I'm listening to this. I'm like, all right, why am I here?
Well, I just mentioned I was there to do something. Someone insisted that I go over there.
All right. OK, this whole thing, including myself being there and what I just stated, if you put a camera on his face with a microphone and say,
can you please give us an overview of all the things you said, what do you think he's going to say?
Nothing. Get out of my face. Leave me alone. I don't know what you're talking about, right?
Yeah.
You see what's going on?
Yeah, of course.
So people wonder like – yeah, the real naive mainstreamers are like, oh no, the public couldn't be deceived.
Like that is what most – the more education they have is what they say.
This is – by the way, if you have any relatives, friends, whatever, that have degrees in work, the normal grind job or a professional job,
you bring up any Greek speak or especially with finance, they're going to say, oh no, the public outrage.
That's not how it works. There will be public outrage.
Trust me, I've done this with doctors and people of family that are doctors and lawyers and I give – I always give what answer they're going to say
and they come back and say, Greek, they said exactly what you said they were going to say.
I say yeah, this is not real. This is not real.
It's kind of like when you have a fictional situation or a setup or a phantom situation, there's a script usually.
If you know the script or the play or whatever, it's easy to pretty much state what they're going to say before they say it.
It can't be real.
I was going to ask you about that actually because I was thinking about Hollywood and how – you and I have discussed occasionally entertainment
and you don't have much use for it for one good reason and that is if you ever notice when people do something that's supposed to be based on a real story
or a real story, it's always like a big shock when they get something right.
You ever notice that? Like seriously, it's like everything is always wrong in these presentations
and I don't know how it is that people are surprised by this anymore.
It's the way it's always been. Nothing is presented.
No, but you said it right. It's the way it's always been.
Like with all of these catastrophes that – by the way, I want to bring up Archaics.
I don't endorse him but my stock in him went down quite a bit or his stock went down.
When you have a stock price – when somebody – when a company does something and the stock prices drop because they – in my book,
he talks about something called dungeon programming and he's talking about how this recent jail thing he had is going to cost him $10,000,
another $15,000 attorney.
Now, if that ain't dungeon programming, I don't know what is.
Going and get – OK, Jason.
Going and getting an attorney is a real punk-ass move.
All right. First of all, the reason why people get attorneys is number one, they're too lazy to study a little bit and number two,
they are motivated by penalty.
No one says I want to get an attorney because I want to do this legally blah, blah, blah.
If I don't get an attorney, I might get more fines and go to jail.
It's always – the reason people get attorneys is so – is motivated by the penalty.
If they don't, they think, right?
So a warrant, which would have been a maximum $120 – it's all administrative by the way.
He could have done it all by the phone, whatever, and he gets in it.
Jason, that's a real bitch-ass move, man, getting an attorney and saying you're going to spend $100,000 or $15,000.
Now that is dungeon programming if I've seen dungeon programming.
So anyway, like with Archaic Spring, let's go back to the theme here about all these catastrophes.
If you go and study a little bit of what's been written about the major calamities,
especially the ones that form the Mediterranean and all the floods and the really bad earthquakes
where the earth opens up and flames come out, the main thing the philosophers said is that
the people that survive these calamities that kill 80 or 90 percent of the population
are the ones that are uneducated, the ones that are living in the mountains,
the ones that are the most menial and most base people, right?
So can you imagine a society – for example, if you look at the art – go to a museum.
Look at the artwork of the Elgin marbles, any of the marbles that are sculpted by ancient Greeks, the detail, right?
And then go a thousand years later, cartoonish garbage from the Middle Ages.
It looks like a five-year-old with Play-Doh, right?
What happened? Why did it – right?
Because there's a filter that happens where the intelligent people that can put things together are killed off
over and over and over and over.
That's why I said current society is a product of a certain breeding and grooming program.
The difference between breeding and grooming – breeding is 100 percent biological, right?
Where you have physical characteristics of one and physical characteristics of the other
and you mate them because of the physical characteristics.
Sometimes behavioral as well, but it's purely biological.
Grooming is training. Grooming is the environment that's set up for someone, right?
Social environment, cultural environment, familiar environment, whatever.
It's environmental influence.
So not only have people of intelligence and of however you want to say have been bred down –
people have been bred down. They're killed off.
OK, go to a trailer trash place and knock on each trailer or whatever.
They call it low-income housing.
How many children have you got?
Well, you mean with me right now or how many I've had, right?
I've had five with him and four with him and two – I got one right here.
OK, keep going. You're going to get the same story over and over.
You go places where people are more intelligent, whatever.
How many children? None.
You see the breeding program?
Now did anyone tell the poor people and the dumb people to have more children
and the wealthy people and the intelligent people to not?
No. You see?
No one is putting a gun to their heads.
You better have children because you're –
and you better not have children because you're intelligent.
Is that going on? Not at all.
That's kind of encouraged.
See, it's almost like we're missing two things here when you're talking about breeding and grooming.
I guess we're missing pruning and –
Pruning would be – yeah, that's a good one.
Abortion, car accidents, vaccines, yeah.
And sculpting, right?
Sculpting is the other part of it because whatever you can't sculpt.
Yeah, well Obama – here's a sculpting for you.
Obama and Biden have convinced the population they should start cutting their dicks off.
There you go.
They call it the woke agenda.
It's just – just break it down to what it is, right?
It started – all this stuff, these idiot patriots, conservatives, whatever.
You know how you become a Trump supporter, right?
You know how you actually convert?
I want to – this is what you do.
You rent a big place and you say you want to become a Trump –
a real good bonafide Trump supporter is what you do.
You come here and you pay at the door and then we turn you into a Trump supporter.
You know how we do it?
How do we do it?
You get about a 7 to 10-inch rotary blade and when they walk in, you cut their top of their head open.
You have them lean over and all the brains fall out and you put the head back together
and right now you've got a perfect Trump supporter or American patriot or whatever, right?
OK.
All these people are bitching about this situation now but this started way back in the 70s.
It was outlined to be fully – what do you call it?
Rolled out by Obama, right?
Then you get the diversion, orange face, whatever they call him.
But Trump was born with both organs.
They decided he should be a boy.
You're aware of that, right?
I never heard that before, no.
Oh, OK.
I better not talk about it then.
OK, because then if I keep talking about it, so what's your source?
No.
OK, anyway.
I didn't say that.
I'm not going to ask your source.
But that's –
Yeah, I'm not going to.
All right, forget it.
I thought it was well-known.
No.
Remember Joan Rivers?
Do you remember Joan Rivers?
Come on.
Everybody knows Michelle is a tranny, right?
She's still alive by the way.
She's been seen several times.
She doesn't wear the makeup that's why.
Oh, OK.
But the voice hasn't changed.
There's a couple of people that spotted them in New York and they were eating dinner in
a restaurant, a hotel type restaurant.
OK.
And they heard the voice and the laugh.
I'm like, that's Joan Rivers.
I mean you could – right?
Like if you heard De Niro laugh.
I mean there's certain – I sat at a table next to Danny DeVito and Jack Nicholson.
They were hanging – they're in Hollywood and we went to a restaurant and they were
there.
They hang out.
They're buds, right?
Well, they're both from the same area of New Jersey where I grew up actually.
Yeah, but they're still buddies.
This is 10 years ago.
Yeah.
But they've been friends a long time.
Hey, Jack.
Hey, Danny.
They said, hey, how are you doing?
Anyway, I didn't – it was kind of like semi-booth, semi – it was kind of dark.
I'm listening to the conversation.
I'm like, that's Danny DeVito and that's Jack Nicholson.
Wait a second.
I turn around and guess what?
It's them right next to me.
The table next to me, right?
But behind kind of like on a dangle there's a column halfway.
I'm not paying attention.
They sat after I did.
So I looked there because I was looking at the door, the power seat.
Anyway, they must have come from another end of the restaurant.
But anyway, I recognized them from the voice.
There are certain people that people get familiar with, whether it be hosts or movies or whatever.
You hear the voice.
You know who it is.
You don't have to just see the face, right?
So anyway, Joan Rivers has been coming up.
Just to tie it back, she's like, come on.
Everybody knows Michelle Michael, right?
So I thought everyone knew that when I just mentioned about Trump.
This is very common.
And I have a childhood friend who was that way, by the way.
He could have been a boy or a girl.
You know, they decided to make him a boy.
Anyway, what's called hermaphroditic or dual gender?
What is it called when you have both sex organs?
Hermaphrodite.
Anyway.
Yeah, it's very common in Colombia.
Catholics, when they went, they killed off most of the tribe.
But there was a tribe of people, indigenous people in the mountain area of Colombia,
that did not develop their sex until they were about nine, between nine and 13 years old.
They had both organs.
And then one would close up or fall off or whatever.
I remember reading about that a long time ago.
Look, when I used to go to the public libraries in the 80s,
the way I did my research is like, oh, I'm getting kind of bored researching this right now.
I need to go somewhere else.
So they had a book section, like the area of misfit books, where no one takes these books out.
And they're out on an aisle, like on a table.
But the table has a wooden side so the books don't fall off.
And they're like, please, you know, please, what is it?
Take me out.
What do you do?
Take the library book out, right?
Rent it or whatever.
You take it out.
Check it out.
Because they're going to be removed from the library.
Because no one ever reads or looks at these books.
One of the books I picked up, by the way, back then was The Ten Worst Popes of All Time.
The other one was Indigenous People of South America.
That's where I got that little bit of it from.
These were old books.
Indigenous People of South America.
Yeah, South America, yeah.
There was more of the title Thereabouts.
Thereabouts.
The other one was The Ten Worst Popes of All Time.
Maybe you do a search on that book.
Remember, these were like the misfit books in the 80s in the New York Public Library.
So you get little bits like that.
It's hard to forget.
You know, when you hear about Indigenous people living in Columbia that were mostly killed
off when the Catholics got there and their sex did not develop, their gender fully didn't
develop until they were 12 or 13.
You don't forget that, right?
That's not something you're going to forget, right?
I'm not able to bring up the source.
And when you hear about Trump, and by the way, I heard this about Trump back in 89, right?
Where, you know, he was a Democrat and he just flipped to a Republican right before.
You know this anyway.
Well, I know about that.
He had the exploratory committees and all that stuff, and he looked at running as a
Democrat.
He looked at running as an independent.
He was, yeah.
If you asked him in 89, he's a Democrat.
Right.
All the way through.
So, yeah.
But anyway, and also he had, there was a lunch where he was going to be there and his right-hand
man, and I refused because I knew the guy was, you know, I wouldn't want to be in the
room with the guy.
This is talking about 1989, right?
So, I was working white-collar construction, which is white-collar meaning like a GC that
only does government jobs, post offices, colleges, and stuff like that.
The smallest project was 1.6 million, right?
And basically, it's all subcontractors.
It doesn't matter what, you just, whatever, you hire everyone, you have all the insurance,
the big bonds, and you get 15%, you're allowed to make 15% profit, right?
And you have all these CMs, construction managers, going around.
They really like me there.
And that's, by the way, that's when I got hooked up with that because I was doing a
draftsmanship intern.
I tried for 10 days at a company called Amund & Whitney.
Amund & Whitney is one of the largest engineering firms in the world.
And what was going on was the Statue of Liberty was being restored.
Now you know how old I am, basically, you know.
And the scaffolding has to go up, right?
But they can't screw to the statue.
It's like you can't put, you know, the scaffolding has to be attached to the building or the
structure, usually.
But they were not allowed to at all fasten to the statue.
So how the hell are you going to have this huge scaffolding, you know?
So what they did was they designed a system.
There was a German company, Liebig, that came in and basically made it so when the wind
blows, instead of the scaffolding leaning and hitting the statue or whatever, it would
rotate, it would twist to take up the forces, right?
So each section, every 30 feet or so was able to twist in any direction.
It was kind of wild.
And it had dampers like shock absorbers, so if you're working on it, you're not flipping
back and forth, right?
Like an amusement park ride.
Every time something was changed on the scaffolding, even a bolt, the drawings had to be amended.
And all the time, scaffolds are being reinforced, removed, moved.
So I had to be there to take measurements and take the measurements from someone and
then put them in a formal drawing.
So they had people working 24-7, literally three shifts, making addendums on all the drawings
as built, what was going on, right?
So they needed a lot of...
So I'm there at night, and I'm drawing.
This is very simple stuff.
The hardest part is reading someone else's notes, right?
Because then the drawing gets checked against the notes.
Anyway, a lot of checking and stuff.
One of the old men, Aman's grandson or son, in a wheelchair, says,
So what do you do?
What are you doing here at night?
Young guy, good-looking guy like you.
I used to be young and beautiful, by the way.
He's like, what are you doing here?
You should be out.
I said, yeah, I just want to do this.
I want to see what it's like to be dedicated to this.
He says, great.
I said, well, what do you do when you're not here?
I said, well, recently, I got a mountain bike out of Fat Chance, one of the early ones.
Back then, it was a $1,500 mountain bike, and today's money would be $7,000, right?
And I said, I go down to the World Trade Center in the middle area there where the bronze statue is,
and we do trials.
We try to get up on a bench with a bike and do all this other stuff.
He says, no, you stay away from there.
There are nukes in there.
And I was like, what?
This guy's crazy.
And from all the movies, when they show a nuke, they show the nuclear core.
It looks like a bowling ball made out of metal, right?
So when you go to the World Trade Center back then, there was a sculpture in the middle.
It was a big bronze ball, right?
And it was a sculpture.
You know, an artist or whatever.
That's actually survived sort of.
It got smashed up in a fountain in a bench area.
That's where we used to hang out.
So when I saw that, I said, oh, my gosh.
I've seen it in the movies.
Maybe that bronze ball is a nuke.
I didn't know.
I didn't get the whole story that, you know, in case of an emergency demolition scheme, we use nukes to take these buildings down.
He didn't.
So since 1989, Trump was born both boy and girl.
And there were nukes in the World Trade Center.
This just sat in the back of my head.
Right.
This is before the Internet.
I hope you know.
Right.
Yeah, of course.
Yeah.
And there were the only I don't even think Nexus magazine was out.
Then, you know, these alternative.
It was the most alternative thing I could read back then was the village voice.
Yeah.
Remember that voice?
The voice was.
And in those newspapers, every town has something like that is a big publisher.
And they no longer put them in print.
They were free.
Right.
And it was cool.
You could you could do ads in the back for like one or two dollars.
They go a missed connection or you can send someone a message.
A real cheap or free.
Sometimes.
Remember?
Yeah.
So.
So this is how we got to where we are.
Before the Internet.
OK.
Emails.
Financial system.
I started off giving the analogy of the hitman.
Right.
You put the microphone in their face and they deny ever anything ever.
What are you talking about?
I'm a manager.
I'm the day manager at Domino's Pizza.
What do you mean?
Right.
Or I work at whatever sanitation.
They usually work in a sanitation company or drywall company or plumbing company.
Anyway, the going rate, by the way, has gone down.
I've heard from the grapevine on doing hits.
It's down to like 1980s prices now.
Yeah.
I heard that.
Just desperate, actually.
Yeah.
Very desperate.
I didn't know what to.
It seems like there's not as much business lately.
No, no.
Yeah.
Or the ones that are doing it are willing to accept such a pay cut.
They're taking a hell of a pay cut.
But yeah.
My understanding is.
Yeah.
It's actually less than what it was in the 80s, which means it's less than one-fifth
of what it used to be.
Well, right.
Because let's just say arbitrarily it's 10 grand.
That's not.
Right.
That was the 80s.
But that was the 80s.
Five, 10 grand.
But if you put it in 10 grand now.
Right.
That means it's three grand then.
Two or three.
Or two grand.
So.
That's what I'm saying.
Right.
That's crazy.
That's actually even less.
It's below five.
Anyway, that's why you hear so many things, you know, like relationships.
One spouse hires one of these guys to take out the other one for whatever.
Yeah.
If you notice the recent stories that have come out where somebody tries to hire somebody,
they're hiring non-professionals for like fifteen hundred.
Yeah.
Twelve hundred dollars.
I mean.
Yeah.
Next to nothing.
We're not going to do any instructions on that.
But it's not what you think.
It doesn't work the way people think in the movies either.
No.
But.
Not at all.
The point is, though, the price has gone down no matter where you go.
Mm hmm.
Yeah.
So.
Let's get to it.
Now, the whenever if someone sends me an email and it's multiple questions and it's cogent
and pertains to a lot of stuff and the person's coming with something to share and it's a well
written, I usually reply and say is all right if I do it on a sonic.
Mm hmm.
Reply this on a sonic.
And the answer was I keep anonymous.
By all means, please do.
Thank you for your time.
Great.
So anyway.
Hello, Greek.
I've been listening to your sonics for many years now.
I'm reaching out with some questions and some information that I've developed since I initially
discovered your work.
I will start with the questions.
As a man that grew up in southern Italian household, it was commonplace to grow fruits
and vegetables that may not be native to the location that we found ourselves.
I live in New England and have successfully grown orange and lemon trees as well as figs.
Since these fruits are grown locally, will they be good, quote unquote, to consume because
they're grown in my climate?
Will they need to be avoided in the winter as with tropical grown fruits?
The answer to that is no, not no need, no need to avoid them at all.
They if they grow there, then they're fully adjusted to the environment, just like you
are seeking to be fully adjusted to the environment.
So they have adjusted.
So it's fine.
Right.
So that's that's a good question, because we categorize things in our mind.
Think of our mind as an elephant and the conscious part of our mind is someone riding an elephant.
Well, and this goes directly to your constant refrain of eat locally.
Right.
And the thing is, it is literally about eating locally.
It's not about what's locally available.
If you're able to cultivate something locally.
Right.
Yeah.
Well, it's the that particular plant, those plants and trees that you mentioned had to
adapt.
And because of their their means that they are in harmony.
So it's harmonious.
By the way, kudos to you, because that's very difficult to do if it's going to bear fruit.
I've grown all kinds of stuff in Europe.
It never bears fruit.
Beautiful avocado plants.
No avocado.
Right.
For example.
OK, so that's that's good.
That's a good question.
And then, for example, there's a form of transmutation, like how many times people go to even, let's
say, a fast food hamburger joint, pickle or no pickle.
They never say cucumber or no cucumber, do they know?
It's always just that it's a pickled cucumber, right?
When you pickle a cucumber that way, it's no longer resembles the energy of a real of
a real an unpickled cucumber.
Right.
For example, bananas, let's say are tropical.
If you live in a temperate place, non-tropical, it's OK to eat dehydrated bananas.
Right, because they don't resemble bananas whatsoever.
Banana chips?
No, not anymore.
They're they're now a hard, completely transmuted.
Right.
They're hard and they're completely different.
I'm not saying go out and Greeks had a shitty banana chips.
No, I'm not saying that.
But you when you consider it right, they're completely different.
And there are things that are more extreme.
Right.
That maybe then you would you would still not consider them.
OK.
The hardest thing to break.
Well, actually, you could break it with sugar because that's very tropical.
If you write sweeteners, so you go with sugar or other things.
Right.
Another question is a healing modality such as Reiki lawful under Yahweh.
I don't think Yahweh is that strict with something like that.
Now, I kind of knock.
I make fun of the Reiki people because I see you guys are like worshiping this
Asian guy called your name, George or something like that.
Right.
And they're a very clandestine group.
If there's a thousand people doing Reiki or you'll only find two that know what
they're doing.
But the reason it has a good reputation is because all just about all those
thousand people working on it get results.
So it's one of these things that even if you use a primitive form of what they
teach, it's still going to work.
It's very effective.
I don't think he's that limited.
There's a whole bunch of weird stuff going on.
They do curse.
Anyway, I'm not going to get into it because that'll be a Reiki discussion.
They do curses.
Yes, they've been pranked.
Most of the Reiki practitioners have been pranked.
But even with the pranks, it's it works just like water for every lab that there
is to increase the quality of water.
There's 300 labs to make the water toxic intentionally to kill people.
Right.
I'm talking without adding chemicals and they could succeed.
But the minute the water spends time is on at times on its own time on.
So it goes back to being healing or nutritious.
So like water will hold a blessing, quote unquote, holy water.
Right.
Holy water.
But it won't hold a curse.
It just it just won't.
There are certain modalities and Reiki might be one of them.
You know, like one of the things they do with Reiki, I'll mention why it's good.
Some of the symbols that they use, if you turn them upside down, they become negative.
And a lot of the Reiki stuff that they put out, the symbols are upside down.
You could read your researches on your own.
And but they still they're not getting negative results.
But I think if they turned them right side up, the results would be even better.
Right.
OK, you see.
OK.
Is it possible to have your consciousness removed from your body in a dreamlike state
to speak with deities, angels, et cetera?
I can offer more information on this if required.
Yes, of course.
As a matter of fact, it can be done technologically.
What the device looks like.
I don't know exactly how it works, but, you know, technologically.
You know, when you go to these carnivals as a vending machine, you put a quarter in, it's
full of toys and prizes and you have this claw that you move with a joystick and you
pick up the.
Sure.
You get like a few.
Right.
And you drop it in a shoot.
And if you get it, you get it.
If you don't, you know, it's not very responsive, you know.
Right.
OK.
It's not something you it's not like throwing whatever or shooting, you know, to impress
someone.
It's one of these things you do when you're alone anyway.
It looks kind of like that.
And it has to do with cloning centers.
When they make a clone of you, there's this thing that looks like that claw goes over
the head of the clone and it's able to transfer your consciousness out of your body while
you're in REM sleep into the clone.
And you wake up and you're like, hey, guys, what's going on or where the fuck am I?
This is Donald Marshall testimony.
And if you're not if you don't if they don't turn on the part where you remember it, you
will never know.
But you'll have health problems and nightmares sometimes and things will leak through.
But, yeah, consciousness is nothing more.
Think of.
Your consciousness, the elephant with a rider, right, the main part of your consciousness
that you find to be what you consider being conscious is the rider of the elephant and
the elephant is the rest of it.
Right.
Most of it is dormant.
You know, there's in the ancient cultures that we're in the dream world where you can't be
dreaming unless you're asleep.
We're mostly asleep.
They even tell you only use 10 percent part of your brain.
Well, right.
Because we're very unconscious.
Right.
So, yes, of course it is.
And if you spend enough time with these deities and angels, you'll find they're advanced people
with advanced technology.
Right.
There's nothing mystical and magical in the universe.
Walking through walls is technology.
It doesn't matter what the deities call calls themselves.
You know what I mean?
It's technology.
If a quote unquote God can do something, you can do it, too, if you have the technology.
Right.
Period.
It's demystifying all the crazy stuff that people go through with religion.
What?
Yeah.
Can someone's toys make them special?
Ask a five year old that doesn't have the red fire truck.
Of course.
Right.
This is you know, that's why I keep saying was this juvenile thinking we have.
I'm not referring to who wrote the email.
I'm just saying if you start expanding and making more discoveries, you'll see it's all
tech.
Right.
It's all tech.
So spiritual tech.
Right.
Ether technology.
OK, here we go.
Well, this is more of a confirmation.
Some info that I have found verified from your sonics include the intestines.
I'm an RN at this time.
I have personally examined a cross section of the intestine, both large and small.
They are, in fact, hydrophobic layers that do not allow for the absorption of water or
anything else.
The lining of the stomach also exhibits the same qualities.
We are all told in school that the GI tract, which is gastrointestinal tract, passes through
the body and is not considered an internal organ structure.
Yeah, that's right.
It's not.
It's a it's a tunnel.
It is.
All right.
It is known.
And then we are told the exact opposite for license testing.
Then they tell you it's an organ because it's it's a critical part.
If you remove the GI, you die, basically, even with intravenous feeding.
Right.
Because it's part of the inner structure, by the way, the because the the entire you
have a tunnel, you know, like a tunnel going through a mountain for the train to go through,
like a little choo-choo train open for the choo-choo train, little children right to
eat.
Right.
Yeah.
Don't laugh at that.
I came because from the mouth to the anus, everything in between.
Well, there's there's complex geometries and other things going on is an open tunnel.
So the vacuum that there's a potential loss of vacuum there, right, just like with your
skin.
So that has to be maintained a certain way energetically, the lymphatics and all that
other stuff.
By the way, are you guys familiar with the mystery of the appendix like the idiots?
They tell you academics.
We don't know.
It's part of evolution.
It's not the purpose of the appendix is like having a sourdough or mother culture in your
fridge.
So the next time you make bread, you have the culture.
What the appendix holds is the positive intestinal flora and fauna, quote unquote, bacteria things
in storage.
So if you eat something or do too much colloidal silver or whatever, that flushes out the natural
bugs that and plants, you know, as I said, positive intestinal flora and fauna, bacteria
and fungi and other things like that.
Right.
Out of your system, it could be replenished from the appendix.
It's kind of like Jack London's book, The Call of the Wild, when they're running slays
in Alaska and it's really cold.
One guy's task was to keep the sourdough starter against his skin so it wouldn't freeze.
Right.
OK.
If you know people who bake breads and things and I've been getting into Napolitano style
pizza lately, the starter is important.
Right.
Maintaining a small piece of culture.
The same with cheese and yogurt.
You always keep a little bit on the side.
Right.
How do you start cheese and how do you start yogurt?
You got to get some yogurt or some cheese.
Right.
OK.
So anyway, confirmation is good.
Yeah.
I've had confirmations from several people, including neurosurgeons, which is a long story.
But yes, confirmations all around.
I answered many questions to people through the years that are surgery, trauma surgery,
neurosurgery, things like that, where they bring up why does this happen or they bring
a case.
And very often I ask questions and they're like, oh, we're going to have to meet again
because I didn't think to ask that question.
Right.
Interesting.
And then we meet.
It's like, wow, I'm asking questions that they didn't think to ask about.
Right.
And that and then you start developing rapport and you write and you get feedback.
How is it?
You know.
Right.
So, yeah.
OK.
I've been familiar with the works of Michio Kushi for about 30 years now.
I can recall the first book of his that I read.
There's a quote that states taking medicine when you're sick is like digging a well when
you're thirsty.
I believe it was I believe it was a book by Dirk, which book in which Dirk Benedict explained
that he cured his cancer by living outdoors and consuming apples and oats.
OK.
Just happened to be a good combination for him then.
I'm saying that I did find the yin and yang process described within this book to be a
bit difficult to process.
I did find the yin yang process described within this book to be difficult to process.
Are you able to provide any direction to learn about this type of living?
Yeah, I have been.
And it's about understanding yin and yang.
And I want to go back to that further on.
This is on closing.
I also remember my younger punk rock days that Harry Christian has integrated themselves
in the Boston music scene.
A lot of converts.
I would go with some of my friends to their dinners on Sundays.
I found the food to be extremely energizing.
I often had difficulty sleeping after these meals.
There were actually there was actually little need for sleep as the food in a healing way.
I could not describe it this time.
And that's pretty much it.
Thank you.
So, OK.
Back to yin and yang.
Yeah.
By the way, I got turned on to the Krishna food.
They would show up with their vans.
We keep saying this because such a good memory.
School buses kind of converted and they come out with their saffron robes and they're funky.
They shave their head and they leave a little ponytail thing, a little tail in the back sometimes or whatever.
Right.
And they were serving the most delicious food like basmati rice and things with coconut and sweet and salty.
And I was like, this is the most delicious food I've ever eaten in my life.
And I was asking the guy, how do you make this as well?
I don't do the cooking, but the spice profile is such that if you threw this plate down on the ground,
and you're at the beach or here in the park, no animal would want to eat it.
Right.
So a seagull, if you're at the beach, it has a food, has a spice profile that no animal wants to eat.
It's specifically only humans would eat.
Right.
It's a spiritual aspect.
No onions or garlic because the energy is too down.
So they use hen, which is a substitute for that.
Anyway.
Yeah.
So I really enjoyed the and it's interesting that he brought that up because I could tell and recount the stories of the Krishna food.
The interesting thing, though, is that the new converts, the Westerners, are always told to have as many children as possible.
Right.
Just like the Pope.
Because the more children.
Right.
And there was a young guy.
He looks just like James Dean, John Maudsley.
And he looked just like James Dean.
He says, you join the Christians.
Did I say he looked like James Dean?
Yeah, I did.
Yeah.
But anyway, he looked just like James Dean.
And he was easy for him to get girls.
And he would just verbatim.
This is not a family show.
He says, yeah, I just went on a date.
I just want to pump them up with semen.
Like they said at the temple.
I'm like, oh, my gosh.
Did they really say that at the temple?
He says, no, you know what I mean to have babies.
But you said they said to you that that's what they said at the temple.
So which one is it?
I was like wondering, like, what the hell?
Right.
Anyway, that's just a little addendum.
Pump them up with semen.
There's a phrase I'm not going to forget for a while.
Yeah.
That's what he said.
And I said, is this what they said at the temple?
That's how they said it?
No, just make babies.
Make babies.
Yeah.
But yeah, that's it.
Right.
Yeah.
Anyway, crazy, crazy, crazy.
Not as bad as the fingers, you know, not as bad as the fingers in the drawer.
Right.
So, you know, let's go back to that.
The there's an interesting process.
OK.
Can you imagine looking at, you know, Hollywood?
Like, I think it's they put equations on blackboards when there's a
professor or someone.
What's that?
What's that guy with how you like them apples?
The movie The Smart.
He was the janitor in the college and goodwill hunting.
Goodwill hunting.
Yeah.
Right.
So he would go and do the formulas.
OK.
Yin and yang getting a good when you get good with the yin and yang, it
would be like looking at one of these big equations on a blackboard
instantly coming up with the solution instantly.
The whole thing, like a like a supercomputer.
That's how your mind has to work.
And it's not because you I'm saying this to be discouraged.
But once you practice, that's how fast that's how it works.
And you do it.
How do you do it?
How do you make how do you solve one of those big equations?
One variable, one piece at a time.
Right.
The same way you eat a big animal.
But you do it faster and faster to where someone it looks instant.
Right.
OK, so let's get into it.
Let's we've been talking.
Keep bringing up nukes.
Let's bring up how a nuke works with yin and yang, because that's
very dynamic.
You can't get more dynamic than that.
OK, because it's a shorting out of the ether.
By the way, the atom has never been split.
When they tell you it splits the atom, that's because there's
transmutations going on.
Right.
And the release of gamma radiation and all that stuff from
neutrons and all that.
That's all bullshit.
No, no one has ever split an atom because there is no atom.
The way they say it doesn't work the way they say.
Right.
But you might have certain scatterings that can be picked up
with certain devices that they call split atoms after the atom
has the effect.
Right.
What the nuclear detonation is, by the way, you know, the
difference between a nuclear device and a nuclear weapon.
They're exactly the same thing.
One is used in peacetime.
One is used in war.
OK, right.
Right.
OK, the other thing is nukes do not explode.
That's a fallacy.
They detonate.
The reaction happens.
What you call an explosion is how that detonation or that
reaction reacts with its nearby environment.
Right.
Got it.
Just like kind of like gasoline does not burn.
Liquid gasoline does not burn.
You only the vapor does.
If you look at a gasoline fire, you have a controlled one.
You'll see that the flames are about two or three inches
above the liquid.
Never from the liquid.
It sits on top of the liquid.
Yeah.
Right.
So that's why you can flood an engine.
You know, try to start.
Right.
It won't start.
It's full of gasoline.
Got to dry it out.
Vapors only.
OK, so these things are concurrent in many things.
We have many misgivings, you know, like the black box on
aircraft is not black.
It's a bright fluorescent orange or yellow.
Right.
So we have all these terms that we all agree to use.
And we attach the term to the actually what's going on to
what the term we agree to use, which is sometimes it doesn't
fit.
It's not so OK.
So when you look at what they call reactor core material,
plutonium, uranium, polonium, all these other things
from yin and yang, that's a very yin metal.
Very yin.
It couldn't be more yin than that.
Right.
So as you go, that's a very large atomic number.
As you get smaller atomic numbers, the metals are more
yang.
OK.
So as you get bigger on the atomic numbers, the elements
in general are more yin.
So now you have this.
You couldn't get more yin than radioactive material.
It's the most yin state of any material.
Right.
OK.
So what happens then is the reaction is usually an
extremely yang reaction.
You have the implosion style trigger and you have the
rifle style trigger.
Right.
Implosion style is for more for the uranium one works
best with the rifle style trigger.
So what you do, you have this extremely yin material
and the trigger, whether it's implosion or rifle, is
extremely yang.
Right.
OK.
And it goes in and it super compresses or very, very
fast.
And it creates the reaction.
Right.
And because it may be it is so yang, it's accepted.
But it's so yang that the trigger has become
yin.
So now you have too much yin and the reaction.
Trigger.
And when the action is triggered, it's extremely
spread out gamma rays, X-rays.
And when the moment it hits something more yang, it
makes it even more yang.
And you get fire because fire is yang.
Right.
Cold is yin.
OK.
Right.
You see.
So one.
So when you look at yin and yang, you have one
thing in the middle of its process or what it is
being yin or yang.
And then the next thing that comes next to it is
that yin and yang.
And how do they react?
Do they react to the yin and yang?
And then there's a new thing and then over.
And when that new thing happens, where is it?
How is it?
And then there's a new thing.
So you have to constantly yin and yang.
Everything that I mentioned with that nuclear
reaction happens in like a thousandth of a second.
And then yin and yang flips back and forth.
Right.
From being too yin to too yang to too yin to
too yang.
You know, the lot of heat and flame and fire
and blast is very yang.
And then it flips again.
Then after that, everything's very yin because
nothing is standing now.
Right.
Nothing's standing.
OK.
But when you go look at the stuff, very yin,
everything becomes yin, the buildings, the
bridges, the people become so yin.
But when you go and look at the material, what
was standing that the yin, it's yin because it's
knocked down.
The material is not very yang.
Right.
The person that was standing there, it became
yin because he's no longer standing.
He's powder on the floor.
But if you look at the person turned into
that dry, hard powder, is it yin or yang?
It's yang.
So it's constantly going back and forth
and back.
And it's the yin and yang is flipping back
and forth.
That's what we you're ready for this.
That is the oscillation, the frequency that
they're looking for.
You know, like the unified, you know, the
terahertz megahertz.
It's actually terahertz and beyond.
Plankton.
Plankton means unmeasurable, usually
playing plankton like Max Plank.
Who was he was another one like
Einstein. What a jerk off.
Back in the days, he promoted the
quantum stuff.
There was a quote he did.
There was some kind of World's Fair or
something in Paris or convention.
And the press went and asked him or
someone asked him about how
does this science affect nature?
And he says, science has nothing to do
with nature.
And they caught it.
They caught it in the newspaper.
Right.
So another idiot.
And then they know if he's like the
high, you know, priest.
Right.
So anyway.
Anyway, the yin and yang thing,
you don't get it until you get it.
But here, if it's a mental
thing to get the yin and yang.
Right. That's a mental thing.
Right. How many times you hear that?
Right. You know, sex, by the way, is
mental.
Right.
It's all mental.
Right. Well, you know, there's the
physical vibration, stuff like that,
too.
You know, right.
But most of it, what would people
consider is mental.
So the yin and yang is mental.
You can apply knowing that it's
mental to get the yin and yang.
When you're pondering, just ponder
something that you have no
clue and no answer to.
But you have the you know, the
subject matter, let's say.
Let's say I bring up a new subject
to someone or yourself.
Let's say, Chuck, you never heard of
the thing before.
So when you think about it, how am I
supposed to think about it?
I don't know anything about it.
Well, you know what it's called and
you know, a general thing, what it's
about, you know, right.
Shipbuilding or whatever, you know,
there's all these terms, the odd
terms that they have.
Right.
You know, you haven't gotten.
You just know this has to do with
that. OK, ponder it.
Think on it constantly as much as you
can. You know what they call
meditation.
And you are you are actually
a you become so yin because you know
nothing about it.
It's very unfocused.
Right.
So you're spending a lot of time
spread out on basically nothing.
No form.
Right. There's no young for no
structure.
Right.
If you spend a lot of time thinking
about something, there's no
structure.
You are a good candidate for
getting a new download a piece
because what will happen, it'll
have to be balanced.
That yin condition where you know
so little about a subject and
spend so much time thinking about
it, that a young condition
will come to balance it out.
And that young condition will be a
sharp and new idea.
And you'll be able to contribute to
the community.
This is how think tanks work with
the cross pollination.
And in
Los Alamos, New Mexico, I don't
know if they do it anymore.
They used to open up the
laboratory and invite people
from the physicists that were based
there. They would invite people
from art community and the music
community and unrelated
fields to physics.
And they would have rooms
where they would go in and the
problem would be posed.
You know, the musicians.
And even though they know nothing
about physics and what they're
trying to solve there, they just
wanted them to give some kind of an
idea or say something, you know,
just to stimulate.
Right.
And it was very successful.
It's called like from the mouths
of mouths of babes is what I'm
talking about.
That's a yin and yang thing.
Right.
Just like, you know, taking
candy from a baby.
Right. It's very difficult to do.
So don't believe.
Again, the just like
splitting the atom and the black
box and none of those things are
like that. Right.
Right.
Well, lack of limitation causes
you to, you know, because you're
not limited by the different rules,
different standards, whatever you
could reach way out with the
think tank. Yeah.
But it's very, you know, because
there's no structure.
So if you want to know
about yin and yang ponder,
I want to know about yin and yang
and kind of when
you ponder it, put the if you don't
know about it means you don't have
the right structure and see you
search for the feeling.
And then if you do that long enough,
the sharp, the sharp, you know, the
the yang will come to mouth.
See, being in a state where
you're spending a lot of time with
something with no structure,
will give you the to be
balanced will have to be something
sharp and sharp and focus.
It happens every time.
OK.
That's definitely a new way to live.
I would have never considered it
that way. That's interesting.
Yeah.
Try it.
So did we finish the emails?
Yeah, that email is done.
Yeah. The other if you go to another
email, that's we've got 24 questions
left and it's pretty long.
So I think maybe we'll wrap it up for
this time.
Thank you.