Actual thunderstorms where I'm sitting here today, what is it, Sonic 43, Greek?
Is that where we're at now?
I think so, yeah.
We didn't get into the 42, but 42 is a pretty special number.
I think I might have loosely in other times, but yeah, we're on 43, it appears.
Well, I love it when you start to talk about numbers, because it usually brings you into
different directions, and actually we wind up landing on a lot of other things, and it's
not a numerology discussion like you get from the woo-woo crowd out there that sit there
and they get an answer, right?
I love these people.
Very, very happy-clappy.
Yeah, those people, it's great, because just bear with me a second.
They go, okay, I want to talk about 1, 2, 3, and then they realize they don't have anything
to relate to it, so then they go, well, if you add the 1 and the 2, it makes a 3, so
now you have two 3s.
Well, yeah, on the 42, it's real short.
It's basically scriptural, and it's also where it's in your face, and it's also in your face
in Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy, which is the answer to everything that's 42.
I thought about it really well, right?
I think Helen Mirren's the voice for that, and 42 would be the number of stations that
they stopped in the desert in the Book of Numbers, and also it's the generations of
the Messiah, right?
And many people think one of them is missing, it's really 41, it's an error, but it's not,
because Joseph is mentioned twice, because of her husband and her gauda, in Aramaic, her
guardian, she came, yeah, her guardian, it doesn't say her father.
It seems like what happened, perhaps, was a mother was widowed, and the brother came in,
right?
It's kind of presumptuous, but when someone is, in Scripture, when the father...
Well, that was a matter of culture, though, wasn't that more of a cultural thing that
just ends up in the Scripture, or is that a scriptural purpose?
Which one is it?
It's both.
It's culture.
It's all culture, really.
It is all culture, or cult.
What happens in Scripture, it's suggested that when a woman's husband dies, the brother
steps in, the brother of the father figure.
And that kind of survived a long way into a lot of the, let's call them Mediterranean
peoples, you become responsible for, now, I don't have any brothers, but my understanding
among other Italians who are very tied to their culture, again, I love that, the culture,
a lot of the...
They have brothers, they go, well, now, because my brother has passed away, or my brother's
in jail, well, they kind of take up the responsibility of, I gotta take care of their wife.
And I always thought of that as just a good, solid, kind of like family value, but...
It's tribal.
It was tribal.
It's actually tribal.
Yeah.
I would suggest.
Well, I think a lot of, but a lot of family values began as tribal things, because at
a certain point, we were all parts of tribal people at one time or another, right?
Still is.
Oh, still is.
Yeah, still is.
It's just not, you wouldn't lean on that term too much.
I got you.
Jackie Robinson's uniform, number two, by the way, was 42, but go ahead, yeah.
Oh, okay, yeah.
You'll find it here and there, the popular ones, yeah.
But it's six times seven, which seven is overrated.
Seven just means it's from above, sort of, eight is perfection, completion.
I think I've gone over on the original O and G, Ocelli in the Greek, number four is really
the relative number of a grouping of seven, right?
Being a center number.
And you'll see four being in more divine placements than seven, if you're paying attention.
Well, we talked about this scientifically as well, when we were talking about the balance
of the magnetic, putting the magnets together, right?
The odd number, that way you have a center, or you don't, depending on what it is you're
trying to accomplish.
So there is a matter of energetic force that's attached to the odd or the even number, depending
on what it is you're doing, right?
Okay, so I'm just saying, there's a lot of ways to look at this in a general sense.
Energetic is a big term, believe it or not, because the limited perception we have is
whatever perceptions we have, it's very subjective, right?
Of course.
Well, what some people call energy is negated by others, and subtle energies don't mean
that they're weak.
There's a lot going on with that.
Well, as always, many things are subject to interpretation because of people's perspectives,
because they only know what they observe, or they only know what they were told, depending
on the circumstance, right?
Yeah, the medical does not acknowledge energy, right?
It's just physical and chemical.
Right.
They just want to talk about, and we did that before too, is it's not only just about when
we were talking about the plants and how the chemist looks at the plant and says, okay,
what chemical does this?
But meanwhile, they don't study the actual characters of the plant.
Is it something that grows upward, outward?
Is it something that stays in the dirt?
things are relative to the way the thing behaves when interacting with other natural things,
right?
Right.
When it's taken internally or externally.
Yeah, exactly.
And these things are accountable, but you will not find it in the pocket handbook for
medicine.
It's not going to be there.
It used to be.
It used to be, but now, no way, right?
Yeah.
Last hundred years or so, not at all.
It shows you.
Well, it goes to show you, as they say, who's in control.
There you have it.
And of course, it's hidden for a reason because it would actually give you reason to be able
to navigate things, I think.
I would say it's hidden as much as not unacknowledged.
You know what?
That's a better, yeah.
That is a better way to look at it, if it's unacknowledged as opposed to, because it's
not truly hidden if you can still find it, right?
Yeah.
I mean, it's not hidden very well anyway, like hide and seek.
It's mostly accessible.
Most things are still accessible.
It's just not readily accessible and unacknowledged.
Most people, you know, what they're taught is this is your authority, right?
And once you get that, and then if it doesn't come from them, it doesn't exist.
Well, and that's the largest problem to me all the time, is that, you know, who is it
that somebody accepts as an authority?
And then that becomes the relevant place where information comes from, right?
So, you know, any circumstance doesn't matter if it's, you know, the most intricate political
or geocentric discussion about, you know, the movement of people on the planet, or if
it's a simple argument over what just happened, right?
Depending on what somebody acknowledges and depending on somebody else coming along, if
you weren't there to witness it or experience it yourself, and you're there for by, you
What do they say?
There are some more reliable witnesses than others, sure, on a basic level.
But then there's also this concept of authority where the reason why this person, no matter
how crazy that sounds, what just came out of that guy's mouth, he's an authority on
this because, right?
He's got these letters after his name because he went through the educational institution.
They're very confident to do this because it's been going on for thousands of years,
right?
And people are very reliable in that in that sense.
Well, it's a very, very, very consistent formula that works, and it is literally on the base
level a con game.
It is a matter of putting confidence into the individual, right?
So it doesn't matter that they're there to rob you.
If the guy with confidence presents the three card Monte game like, hey, look, this is a
game of chance, and we're going to have fun and let's enjoy it.
And here I'm going to dangle in front of you the possibility that you're going to get something
out of this.
All of that is only relevant because the guy has the confidence that he is getting from
you because he's now sucked you in.
If it's a three card Monte on the street, he's done it instantaneously.
If it's some other continuous situation, right?
All these things.
Well, they're religious.
Yeah.
Also, well, that's the thing.
Why is it?
Why is it that this guy telling me what's in the Bible or what's in the book is important
because he's a guy who's supposed to have studied it.
He's a guy who's supposed to be an authority on this.
So they rarely, they rarely do tell you anything that they're saying is in the Bible.
And if they do, it's out of context.
And then they and it's not even that they tell you what's actually in there.
They tell you, look, what they mean is they might reference it real quick.
Oh, you know, according to John, blah, blah, blah, whatever.
And I'm callously not even bothering to give an acknowledgement to the specifics because
it doesn't matter.
They have a point they're making.
They make a reference that they say is to that thing.
And you know, maybe it is.
Maybe it isn't.
And maybe it's just an interpretation, which obviously, if they're speaking English to
begin with, it's already an interpretation.
It's a version that they're working with from its roots.
Yeah.
Interpretation should be as accurate as possible.
And it's an information transfer where version means the definitions are loose.
The information is loosely, you know, how would you say, brought over?
Right.
Well, you know, the whole the whole idea when you see subjective based on a true story,
you know what I mean?
Yeah.
It's based on a true story.
But that does that has a very wide variety of possibilities in it when you say it's based
on a true story.
So back to this confidence thing, though, and communication and again, the number 42, which
is where I took you away from.
Your interpretation of numbers is much better and less, you know, OK, I couldn't fit it
that way.
I mean, it's really what they used to call that a cold reading, you know, OK, you throw
a couple of answers out there and you wait for the reaction and you wait to see if somebody
bites.
Oh, they bid on that.
Great.
I'll go that way.
So instead of adding the numbers, maybe they subtract them and they get the right reaction.
Oh, yes, that's right.
Now it comes to two, which means something to me.
You know, now it goes.
Yeah.
It goes.
It goes to six.
We add them together.
And you know what happens if we're talking about it three times, that means three sixes
and therefore and so on.
And they're pulling this.
Well, here's the thing that people have discussed with numbers and it's about we don't live
in a numeric or we could say more arithmetic than numeric world.
It's you also have to bring in geometric forms, the visual.
Right.
So to say that someone is strictly a numerology as numbers by themselves is kind of futile
unless you're deriving it from like numeric values of words again, because those that
structured the words also structured it with the background for number significance.
But in the world itself, numbers as we use them and arithmetic and mathematics, right,
they're different.
It's just another language.
And it has to comport to something real and tangible.
And usually, well, now at the point, you know, they say, well, the math shows that this is
going on.
Right.
And it's fictional.
You know, it's gotten to the point now where all these fictions are coming together to
create reality, which which at some point is actually legitimate.
Right.
If someone's reality is based on fiction, right, and the reality is based on belief,
it's legitimate.
It's it's not true.
Just like very often I bring up when someone gives you a history book and you know everything
in there, pretty much 99 percent is BS.
Why should you get upset?
Because if you look at the title, it doesn't say true history, does it?
No.
Just says history.
Right.
So this is how one can take things, you know, the truth is too minimal to bring out to the
public and it's minimal.
And it also requires full comprehension.
Well, there's the difficulty because an uninformed truth, right, is basically useless.
I mean, the bottom line is, if you don't understand numbers, let's just say, and I give you the
equations that would, you know, give you a working way to deal with everything in the
world and you don't know the way equations just means that one side balances to the other.
Well, right.
Right.
But if I give you the equations to make balance out of many things that are in imbalance in
your life, which is very important, if I give you those equations and you don't know how
they apply, it's kind of useless.
I mean, what's comprehension?
Right.
Because, you know, look, if I if I gave you, you know, perfect knowledge, if I gave you
a perfect medical book, I mean, one that you'd read and go, you know what?
This is somebody who's actually explaining everything top to bottom about the human body.
If it's in a language that you know, it's in it's in Russian and you can't read that
because it's a wholly different language.
It's not even recognizable to to the English language.
We don't even use the same alphabet.
It's kind of useless to you.
I mean, I could give you the whole thing on neurology, the brain, the science of the brain
and tell you how every single thing works in the brain.
But if you don't know how to read Russian, kind of useless to you.
Right.
Well, in most people, nothing in the brain is working.
Well, there's that, too.
Well, this is well, this is where it comes down to, you know, most people think they
are making choices.
No, the choices were already made for you.
You have to make decisions, right?
It's not.
This is not a play on words.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
So you're talking about choices, but they don't they don't take hold of what decisions
they've made.
Right.
So, you know, the choices would be the menu board and the decision is what you actually
order.
Right.
Let's say, you know, in a luncheonette context.
Oh, luncheonette.
There's a word that nobody uses anymore.
Luncheonette.
You know what?
In the luncheonette, though, really, the choices that you order are not really choices anyway.
There's selections from a prescribed menu.
Right.
Yeah.
If you were deciding what it is, those people were going to go and pick up and bring back
to the place and cook and you made that decision all by yourself, then you'd actually be making
a choice.
But you're just making a selection, isn't that right?
Yeah.
But I'm trying to bring out the point that what people view as their subjective preferences
are not what they end up with.
No.
Right.
Think of voting.
Or whatever.
Well, if they were never offered like that.
Well, but they were never offered the ability to make a subjective selection.
Right.
Again, it's it's not a choice because it's still off of the menu.
They didn't put the menu together.
It's the same if all the choices are coming from one place where, you know, where's the
right.
No.
Well, then ultimately it's a narrowed down set of choices.
You know, what was it?
Some dictatorships or communists, they had voting polls, but there was only one person
on the ballot.
Right.
Exactly.
You know, and you can have a a show trial.
It doesn't mean you ever got a fair trial.
Right.
You know, they already know the outcome is going to be, you know, it's either way, either
way.
It's lawful or unlawful.
I would dispute it.
That's one thing that's out of out of the what's used against people will say, oh, this is
an unlawful gathering or this is unlawful.
They really don't have any rights to that because they're not lawful.
They just use that term.
Right.
Like 9-11 is I always use that as a reference.
They call it a terrorist attack.
It really wasn't no terrorism.
It was sabotage because everything that happened was already in place.
All they had to do was misuse what was in place.
Right.
Well, every day is whoever you want to.
Yeah.
And every day.
Sure.
It's L.A. 9-11.
Here's the thing.
You know, a lot of the police out there, you know, the five.
Oh, when they show up, I hear this argument all the time on a lot of videos out there
where people are trying to demonstrate something.
You know, I'm giving you a lawful order.
And I just cringe every time I hear that.
And it's usually, you know, the guy in the blue uniform.
Well, they're law enforcement.
They don't know any law at all.
But, you know, maybe they might go back to something.
Let's say, well, law and 10 Commandments, right.
Or something like that.
OK.
Out of context.
Yeah.
But that's not.
It's it's.
Look, it's a matter of belief.
Someone who believes something, even if it's fictional, it is true to them.
Right.
So, again, if you go back to the way numbers structure, they're basically little bits of
pressure that push the mind to certain directions, you know, like the better numbers like number
seven.
Right.
Or number 21.
And then you've got the worst off numbers, like the most worst off number would be 13.
That puts a different pressure on the mind.
Right.
So there's a sense, again, it's all subjective.
So it's really difficult to get into the, quote unquote, the numbers because they just
don't exist on their own anyway.
And it's based on and it's based on a whole lot of crap that has nothing to do with numbers
which are objective.
Numbers themselves are.
Well, like horoscopes.
Well, yeah.
OK.
But numbers themselves are objective.
And what do I mean by that?
Here's the thing.
Like I like to play.
You've played cards.
I know you have.
And I like to play cards.
I actually enjoy cards a lot.
And I love the fact that they make them in many different forms, a lot of different artwork.
I collect aces of spades.
OK.
Anyways, forget my personal quirk aside.
Here's the thing about it, though.
Some people are intimidated by that card alone.
Now, I've always found it to be as as kooky as this is going to sound to be a lucky card
for me.
Whenever I draw it, I seem to win.
That's according to my memory.
And this is my prejudice.
Now, a lot of other people see it as the unlucky card because they were told at some point it
is a death card.
Well, again, it's a pressure.
In other words, what direction does it send them?
And does it send them left, right, forward, backward?
Right.
Oh, yeah.
But the fact that it's a driving mechanism.
Yeah.
But the fact that it's nothing more than, you know, a plastic coated piece of paper
or a linen coated piece of paper.
We mentioned Confucius, you know, symbols that matter, that direct people's minds, not
words.
Right.
And the fact is that it's just a small piece of, again, paper that's coated or maybe not
coated depending.
You've got a cheap deck, what have you.
And they make them in all sorts of grades, just like anything else.
And you can get high quality cards that are like almost light as air, slide perfectly
and have nice, smooth, durable edges.
They make them out of plastic as well.
And so on and so forth.
Right.
But here's the thing.
All of the things that come into play in somebody's mind can influence them during a friendly game
of anything.
The second that that ace of spades drops out there.
That's not why it's my favorite.
But the thing is, it's just interesting to me how somebody can be pushed by a piece of
paper that really has no relevance to their life or anything else and half the time doesn't
even have relevance to the game.
It's just because it has that symbology.
It has all of those things that are built into it in their minds alone.
It's an image training.
Image training.
Okay.
There's an interesting term.
Image training.
Stop the red octagon.
Any intersection in the world?
Yeah.
Absolutely.
Is there a red octagon?
No matter what's written in there, you're going to stop.
Right.
Universally.
Badge.
Yes.
Universally, people know that that red octagon is a stop sign.
And the color red is an indication.
Someone flashes a badge.
A badge, too.
And because it's a star, you know, and they have eight pointed stars in some places, six
pointed in others.
But either way, it's a shiny.
It's also don't forget, they're always supposed to be shiny.
I like the.
Are you familiar with the doctor who the psychological papers?
It's just a blank piece of paper where whoever you show it to, it ends up representing the
highest authority in their world.
I remember that.
I always I find that interesting.
There's a couple of sci fi tropes like that that are interesting.
I'm actually.
That's commentary.
Yeah.
It's disappointing.
They don't use it more often because that's commentary on top of commentary.
Anyway, speaking of commentary, by the way, Bansky, are you familiar with Banks Banksy
Banks?
The artist.
Yeah.
I like his stuff.
It's just been coming up lately.
And I took some time to look at most of his, you know, let's say pieces.
I'm actually surprised you like Banksy.
OK.
Well, why?
What do you appreciate about everything?
I like everything he does.
OK.
He's he's actually he's sort of going along the lines of Marcel Duchamp, who was part
of the Dada movement in the 1920s and on, actually knew his nephew and cleaned out one
of his studios once on Green Street in Soho back in the early 80s.
But Dumont, you say?
Duchamp.
Oh, Duchamp.
Marcel, M-A-R-C-E-L and Duchamp.
Don't ask me his spell.
So I think it's D-U-C-D-U and then Champ Duchamp.
And he was a chess master.
So the chess community knew him as a chess master that might have painted.
But in the artist community knew him as an artist that played chess.
He disagreed with the way art was.
He says the artists go to school.
It's like a trade, like becoming a plumber or a carpenter.
It's too restricted.
He was when he was invited to a gallery to do bring in something to represent his work.
He completely forgot and didn't care.
And just one hour before the show was open, he went down to the hardware store on Houston
and West Broadway and bought a urinal nailed it to a piece of plywood.
They brought it to the gallery as his exhibit with his name on it.
And it was rave reviews.
This is like back in the 1950s.
And it made him famous.
Basically gave him a piss pot.
They told him it was beautiful.
They told me it was beautiful.
He was really making fun of the artist community.
Banksy does the same, right?
Yeah, I always find it funny when these guys, they start netting a lot of money for stuff
and then they just turn around and really present something as a joke almost.
He was throwing knitting needles in the eyes of the artist community.
Again, this is one of the benefits of being old school.
Yeah, the Greek is old school.
How many young people know about Banksy?
How many people know that he's just like Marcel Duchamp?
They're not old enough.
So there you go.
Old school.
Right, right.
OK.
Fair enough.
I was not familiar with Duchamp.
Yeah, young whippersnapper.
That's why.
Not really.
But anyway, he's one of those guys.
Look, maybe I'm a little more cultured.
Maybe you got a little more cultured than me.
That could be a possibility.
No, it's just I was around these...
Yeah, but more mature palate, not just for food, right?
OK.
Yeah, right.
But maybe I'm more cultured in other ways and it's not just about what they can grow
in a Petri dish.
Look, I got drawn into the community.
It was quite interesting.
No, I got you.
Look, same time that you might have gotten drawn into the artist community.
Look, I spent a little time in the musician, you know.
At one point, the landlady, I'll mention her name, Dori Ashton, she was the most famous
art critic in the world for a long time.
So in her living room, she'd show me like all the...
In other words, if you wanted to be a famous artist in New York between the 50s and the
80s, she had to pretty much whatever, recommend you.
And she had all these Matisse's and you could go on and on and on in her house and all that.
I got you.
Basically, upstairs from where I lived.
No, I mean, culturally, I was immersed in the musician community where, you know, I
met people that, you know, composed ballets and things like that.
I mean, I was a heavy metal musician, but I had a much more diverse cultural experience
than that.
And quite honestly...
Well, you had opera.
I didn't get into...
One of my landlords was Don Yule, D-O-N Yule.
You like Yule Log?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He was part of the Lincoln Center.
He was a pretty...
He was a baritone.
And he was...
I rented a warehouse space that he had in Brooklyn for doing restoration cast works.
Wasn't he instrumental in some of the restoration stuff also?
No, he was just a pretty...
He was just a singer and performer and administrator also at Lincoln Center.
Yeah, no, I thought that he might have been...
Remember when they did the kind of renovations and restoration and they did like some...
Oh, no, he was just a landlord.
He invested in real estate property and I needed a space to do what I was doing.
He was a singer.
He was a baritone.
Fair enough.
He passed away in 2015.
You ever walk in a room, someone's got such a heavy voice that when they speak,
everything in the room vibrates.
Just normal speech, right?
Very few, but yeah.
Yeah, I've been...
Yeah, yeah, he had that type of voice.
Tall, tall guy from Oklahoma.
And Mickey Rooney was his cousin, so he comes from the Rooney family,
on the mother's side.
Some guys that I met in radio over the years are like that.
They have these incredibly just booming voices that just in their regular speech,
it's just so...
Yeah, it's a given trait.
There's a John B. Wells guy that does that.
He used to do the...
Oh, that guy.
Remember the movie trailers?
They used to have a voiceover?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Back in the day?
Not anymore.
Yeah.
He used to do those movie voiceovers.
Well, there was one guy.
That wasn't him, but there was one guy who pretty much did them all for five, six years.
Remember?
Yeah.
That guy, right?
Yeah, right, yeah.
When did they stop?
Probably early 2000s, right?
Something like that.
They stopped all that.
The Wells voice is funny, though, because I joked about it.
I was supposed to be a guest on his show at one point, and then I wasn't,
and I don't know why.
But there was a weird thing that happened there where I was talking to people about,
yeah, wait until you talk to him off air.
I'm like, why?
And they said, because you know how he sounds on air, that really intense,
just drenched in bass voice he's got?
And I'm like, yeah.
It's performance, you know?
And they're like, no, no.
That's exactly the opposite.
It's a rare thing.
They said, no, that's just the way he talks.
Like, that's just him naturally.
You talk to him off air.
So, how are you doing?
You know, I'm like, he's really like that all the time?
Yeah, it's a natural attribute.
Don, you'll like that as well, yeah.
So, I mean, like, I got involved with a guy named David Peele in New York.
Now, that name might ring a bell for somebody if they were deep in the musician
culture stuff, and everybody knows he had a tremendous archive.
But I was in his living room, which was like wall-to-wall tapes of every kind
you could imagine.
He had tape of everybody.
He had stuff from, you know, Jimi Hendrix performing in people's apartments,
in people's lofts in the late 60s, just hanging out in the air.
Jimi Hendrix's studio was right there, Electric Ladyland on 8th Street, right?
Oh, yeah.
Between 5th and 6th.
But famously, he would walk into people's places where, you know,
they would just have these little jam sessions and lofts and stuff.
He would sit down with his own tape recorder and just jam with people sometimes,
if he knew them, in New York.
And this guy had some of those tapes of, like, you know,
the stuff straight from Hendrix and things like that.
And he famously, a lot of people ended up with bootlegs of his, you know,
like in the 90s and the 80s, I think.
But I actually just was in the same neighborhood as that guy.
That was the East Village.
You know, the East Village was a pretty interesting place culturally,
musician-wise.
I lived there, like, from 86 to 89 on 11th Street between 2nd and 3rd.
Yeah, see, now, around the time that you were leaving is when I went in there,
and I went in, it was East 9th Street between 1st and 8th, right?
Yeah, so Venero's Italian pastry shop, I think, is on 9th Street, right?
Between 1st and 2nd.
I don't remember that one because the Chinese place was on the corner,
and then I don't remember any other food going in that direction
because the pizza place I went to would be the one on the corner of 8th and A,
right, which was open 24 hours.
Yeah, I like Stromboli's better on 2nd Avenue.
Really?
Because they put a little sugar in the sauce.
I like when the pizza has that sweet sauce.
You know, Stromboli, I think it was on 7th Street and 2nd Avenue, I think.
No, 1st Avenue.
I don't remember that one.
Yeah, well, it was a pizza joint every two blocks.
Yeah, that was the other thing.
And I would go to Kiev on 7th and 2nd for the Russian food, you know,
the Ukrainian food, let's say.
Yeah, I never got into that too much.
When I wanted Japanese, I went to that place, Dojo's.
That was nice.
Oh, that's where I always used to eat.
I used to get the soy burger dinner for $3.
Oh, well, the vegetable, just the tempura.
I would just sit there and eat the tempura because, you know,
it was the greatest snack, and I don't know,
it was one of the healthiest things I could get to eat in New York.
I loved that place.
It was great.
Most of the seats were outdoors, you know, on the terrace there.
Yeah, I would eat there often, the Dojo.
I still talk about it.
And I did finally imitate their sauce.
It was a great place.
Oh, wait a minute.
You're talking about the dipping sauce?
Yeah, both the dipping sauce and the carrot ginger sauce.
Oh, man.
I can copy that.
Yeah, I make that perfectly.
That dipping sauce, if you can copy that, that's wonderful.
Oh, I can.
I can give you the recipe.
I will gladly take it because I would love to be able to dip just about anything.
Grated ginger, chopped green onion.
You got to get  you could add sugar, rice vinegar, soy sauce, white pepper.
That's pretty much it.
That's it.
You're better off getting and putting  you're going to need mirin,
M-I-R-I-N, which is sweet wine, Japanese sweet wine.
It's basically a sweetener.
Mirin.
It's a seasoning.
They use it for rice.
Okay.
Yeah, mirin, M-I-R-I-N.
It's a sweet Japanese cooking wine.
And that's basically the recipe for the dipping sauce.
And for the carrot ginger, it's carrot, ginger, tahini, a little sugar,
a little tiny bit of tomato paste, sesame oil, salad oil, and rice wine vinegar.
Well, I'll have to get some  see now, here's where I'm going to need a little math
because just because you gave me that doesn't mean I know how much of each thing to put in.
It's a taste.
You'll figure it out.
Really?
What you do is what I do  well, what I tell people is before you start mixing stuff,
regardless of the proportions of the recipe, start tasting everything.
But if something is extremely harsh, don't taste it because it could corrupt your
it could corrupt your taste buds for the rest of the night.
All right.
So like the last thing you want to do is when you start cooking is start tasting just plain salt first
because anything you taste after that is going to taste like it doesn't have enough salt, right?
Right.
So you have to be careful what you taste first.
But basically the main  when you do the dipping sauce,
the main amount of liquid is going to be probably 50-50 mirin and then soy sauce, right?
Okay.
And then a third  then the rule is you're not going to add oil to it
because it's a dipping sauce for fried food.
Then a third of that would be your vinegar.
You could do a little bit of orange rind.
I would heat up the orange rind a little bit with the liquid and let it cool down.
Those really good dipping sauces, by the way, those ingredients that I gave,
if you mix them warm in a double boiler pot  don't boil.
Don't even simmer.
Don't even think about simmering.
Just warm or hot.
Okay.
And then let it cool down overnight and you get more of the flavor out of it.
So those are the fine points of it.
Okay.
But, I mean, it's primarily a lot of soy sauce though and then everything else is
Yeah, a third.
Well, if it's a light soy sauce, if you're getting a heavy soy sauce or tamari,
one is made with soy, tamari is made with wheat.
I would use tamari.
I would water it down a little bit.
Again, taste it.
Get familiar with the flavors, right?
And anything that's  like a really good quality salt should always have a sweet finish.
After you taste it and your palate relaxes, it should have a slightly sweet finish,
not a strong metallic like iodized salt does, right?
Get that good popcorn kind of effect where you have a little bit of sweetness
and the salt together so it's not overdone.
In England they do that.
In England they always add sugar to their popcorn.
That's a thing.
Yeah, a little bit is always good.
Anyway, okay, so I didn't mean to get a recipe from you, but that's great.
That's fine.
We're just kind of free-floating on this one tonight.
Absolutely.
Well, before we get done, though, I do want to get back to not just the numerology
but the communication because numerology, again, I think it's so  everything is subject
We haven't communicated at all tonight.
Okay.
No, I'm just joking.
I was waiting for something good to come out of there like, well, what do you mean?
You've actually been dealing with the virtual Greek.
Imagine that for a minute.
How about the AI version of you?
I don't think that's ever going to happen.
You never can tell.
Somebody might try it.
Anyway.
Think about the logic there.
It won't work.
No, I know.
They can't pull it off.
Again, this is an attempt at jokes.
So anyway, like I was saying about communication, though, and about what is communicated,
one of the more curious things that we have covered before,
and I kind of want to like leave it off at this one if we can,
is this idea about, you know, okay, a while back somebody said,
well, what is the purpose of prayer?
All right.
I don't want to go into the purpose necessarily.
I want to ask you something else, though,
and this is about how things can get misdirected, redirected, et cetera.
You know, when you're putting that energy into this communication that's supposed to be prayer, right,
and there's a lot of weird things built into that, a lot of cultural things built into that,
but let's get to the bottom line.
Let's get to the basics of it.
Let's get to not the why of it right away.
Maybe we'll get there eventually, but what about that?
What about who you're more likely or what you're more likely communicating with when you do that?
I mean, that's a huge thing.
You're spectators.
You're basically indulging in an activity that has spectators watching you, right?
Okay, let's think of it this way.
Even loosely in these quote-unquote spiritual talks, isn't it said very loosely that you're always being watched anyway,
however you want to take that?
Well, you're always being watched, and I've always appreciated, believe it or not,
the idea of the giant amphitheater effect like you saw in, say, the Clash of the Titans movie
or you saw often referenced in the Greek slash Roman what they call mythology about the gods, right?
This idea.
Yeah, they're in a council watching.
Yeah, that we're all on a stage, right?
Oh, I see.
And it's basically just a big play, and they're watching, and sometimes they're influencing,
and every now and then somebody does turn to the audience, say, and says something, right?
The fourth wall break, the directly addressing the audience.
This is something that is done in a lot of plays, and plays were very different in ancient times for sure.
So as an amalgamation of all of it, I kind of think of it in this way when we talk about prayer,
is that we're on a stage, and this is your opportunity to now turn to members of the audience.
But do you know which members of the audience you turn to?
Can you actually see the audience?
There's a lot of large questions there.
Who are you actually communicating with when you do that?
Well, posing the question in regard to prayer is just a matter of, it depends on where it's coming from.
I always give the, in Scripture it's different.
There's preparation.
There's a self-awareness, self-consciousness about your state, right, clean, unclean, all these other things, right?
I would suggest that there's also prayers of desperation if you fall off a ship and you're drowning, right, for immediate help.
All those are taken in consideration, and it is a spectator kind of event.
In other words, you're always being watched.
The thing is when you're praying, who are you praying to?
Well, that's again, how would you say that?
If we're in a reality that's pre-programmed, which all the evidence seems to show that,
and all the evidence is, I'm becoming more Philip K. Dickish as time goes on.
One of Philip K. Dick's things is that time ended about 50 A.D. and all this.
We're not in the year, let's say 2023.
It's still around 50 A.D.
Everything stopped and we're running simulations, right?
I'm a big proponent of that.
Yeah, and a lot of people I've recently encountered on the Internet are saying that actually time ended in 2019 completely,
and that we're now just in this.
We like to always make it more contemporary, always, but I'm suggesting it's way, way back, further.
That's why I brought the Philip K. Dick analogy there, or analogy, I should say, again.
I would say that the amount of simulation and the amount of pre-programming that is in place
makes it nearly impossible to state the validity of prayer directly, directly.
So you don't see any validity to the argument that if you're praying, maybe that was already preordained as well?
Right, so does it work? Of course it works because it's part of the program.
Because it was already going to happen.
This was going to happen anyway.
Right, exactly.
It's sort of a paradox, but it's not a paradox if you understand the outside influence is predetermined to a degree.
Okay.
But you do have a lot of manipulation.
Again, one of the Greek-speak memes and analogies I always give is the cruise ship analogy, right?
Everybody on the cruise ship is going to the same destination,
but you have a lot of freedom and liberties on a cruise ship as a passenger.
So I would take it in that respect as well.
And then the rest of it is personal development in that topic, in that field of spirituality,
and who the gods are and all that.
And what I've always said indirectly, and I've been saying more directly lately, the gods are people, right?
In many respects, they're just like us, except they're gods.
So once you start to harmonize that idea, you'll find more power in many more things that you already have.
See, that's always been the confusing aspect of it for me, though,
because when people are praying quite often, they're reaching out to some entity that they believe is insert, right?
And that entity, they've handed over things to them.
This is always part of it as well, right?
Yeah, but hold on a second.
This information is very rarefied.
What the public, 99.999%, believes they're praying to just simply doesn't exist.
Well, that's the thing.
Since it doesn't.
In the way that they believe it, yeah.
Where is it going?
That's where the program comes in.
Yeah, so.
And the spectators.
This is like going to the chat bot, you know, and they have prescribed answers already for if you hit the right keywords.
Yeah, and also the people will think about an average human, whatever they could be thinking of, not much, right?
So it's very predictable and pretty easy to accommodate them.
For the most part.
Okay.
Well, fair enough.
I mean, what else should people know about this, though?
Because I think sometimes, and people have a lot of discussions about this, that, you know, they've addressed the wrong entity, right?
I mean, what do we know about, you want to go back to the horror movies real quick.
The trope of, right, you play with the Ouija board, you reach out to the wrong people, you know, you think you're playing a game.
That's also very specific.
The Ouija board in general is going to bring.
Well, you know, that has an entity, a specific entity.
Right.
So everything does.
Yeah.
No, that one.
And they do give one of the names for it.
But most people don't evoke it and they don't deal with it.
And I wouldn't because that's part of the that's part of what shows random chaos in the world, even though it's not really random chaos.
Right.
If you invite someone like that.
All right.
So, I mean, in a way, is it prescribed or can you choose to invite for good, for better or worse?
Well, on that level, let's say something like a Ouija board, that would be you're on the cruise ship and you have liberty to do so.
Again, it's many, many levels.
You're not going up to the bridge and telling the captain to steer somewhere else.
Or in the meanwhile, while he's steering the ship, can he take a moment from his busy schedule and accommodate you?
That would be a much different level of prayer.
I say.
Right.
No, it definitely would be.
I mean, obviously, things can be done to accommodate you or to cause you problems.
Let's just say you're one of these people that's causing problems.
You might be dealt with by the captain on the ship.
You might be dealing with real gods.
You're going to have problems in your life anyway.
And if you don't think so, then you're not up.
You haven't done your homework.
Right.
So, you know about that, though.
I mean, could you mistakenly reach out to the wrong entity?
No.
I'll tell you why.
Yes and no.
Lower entities.
Yes.
Higher entities.
No.
Because they have layers and layers.
In other words, the higher the entity, the more protective and surrounding layers it has.
Whatever communication it would get from you or he or she would get from you, really, mostly he, would go through layers.
Right.
And then other layers and other layers, and it gets filtered.
And if it is appropriate, then it's deliberate.
Well, there's a hierarchy.
I mean, look, the CEO of Microsoft is not answering your phone calls when you call customer service.
In very much the same way.
Yeah.
What you see modeled here in terms of authority is exactly the same.
Same kind of structure.
Presumably.
Kind of structure.
Presumably the same structure.
Presumably.
Okay.
No, fair enough.
I always think that that's a fair question because it's always on people's minds because
one of the things that they always seem to seek to do one way or another is interact with the gods because they ask for things.
They ask for, you know, I'm going to pray for someone.
Right.
I'm going to pray for their this and that.
We've talked about that and where emo work comes in and you can do things.
But sometimes people just, you know, no, I'm just going to pray.
The emo work is very important.
And a lot of people misinterpret that as being self-centered and self-righteous in a way.
But what the gods are looking for are for people to discover what attributes they already inherently possess.
And if you don't start searching those attributes and using them, you're considered lazy.
By the way, and this is, you know, subjective comment from the Greek, but I would take it seriously.
Right.
So you're not appreciated if you're squandering your talents that you have.
Yeah. Or, you know, not spending time to discover them, let's say, once once they've been exposed.
But like we talked about the natural talent of somebody's voice or whatever.
I mean, the idea is this is actually the way you commandeer and change your life.
Your law form is how you live, essentially.
And of course, there's exceptions where people are picked out of, you know, other societies, other crowds,
other demeanors to do to serve them.
But I would suggest that the evil work is basically acknowledging that you're given a certain amount of tangible power in that world.
You know, the spiritual world by setting yourself up a certain way.
And of course, it's your law form and your law form comes from your God.
Very simple.
Well, there you have it.
So was there anything else that we needed to get to as far as the chat questions and all that?
I think we covered everybody.
Yeah, I just I threw in a comment regarding thoughts without words.
Oh, you just put one in or?
Well, no, earlier today or yesterday, I think in the morning.
Yeah.
Basically, being able to achieve thought forms without the words that have been put on you through, you know, culture, family, society.
Well, that's another thing, too, just really quickly.
I mean, the difference between imagery and and words.
Right. I mean, if you communicate in pictures, I mean, that's just as valid, if not more than it's called Chinese.
That's funny, but no, I mean, that's true.
The pictograms and so are well, they're antiquated derivatives of pictograms, hieroglyphics to a certain degree.
You know, the oldest writings in Egypt are not hieroglyphics.
There's Sumerian, you know, but they're avoided.
You know, they're not talked about.
I've talked about this a long time ago.
Hieroglyphs were limited for the temples and certain function.
But basically, the cuneiform was the was the Langua Franca and always in Egypt.
Well, while it was depending on when you're talking about in Egypt.
But I would say that images and beyond images, you're ready.
You know, again, the feeling that images give.
Right. If you can imagine what you want to do, which is what people are doing anyway.
They just don't acknowledge it.
And that allows the corruption of the words of the inner voices to come in and influence.
Right. So, you know, I imagine people say, well, imagine it done already.
Right. They don't say tell yourself it's done already as much as often.
Someone tells you, tell yourself it's done.
It sounds like you're being scammed.
But if someone tells you, imagine that it's already done.
It sounds more cogent, more tangible and more achievable.
All right. Well, right. Because imagine you're the image of your you're bringing the image into your mind that this is already.
And you kind of said this, you know, when when you want someone to be restored.
Right. We talked about healing with the emo work.
And you said, look, what you do is you take them back to the time when they were already in that condition.
And that is the image you put in your mind.
That's the thing that you're I don't know if you use the word sending, but sending.
Right. Transmitting, transmitting, projecting, projecting is not a bad word, right?
No. No. OK. So to project that is the way forward.
That's how you encourage that to be by already saying it is.
Yeah. Yeah. OK. Retro causality to an extent.
Yeah. Retro causality. There you have it.