Rated Y, 239, and that's the sonic event.
Anyway, Greek, how are you?
Yeah, you asked me, got anything or get
started.
Just a little bit.
A little member is a good fella.
When a kid comes in here and insults
me, I know you did a little bit.
A little bit.
Do you remember at the bar?
Well, anyway.
Oh, yeah.
I'm not talking about it.
So he's like a little bit.
I got a little bit.
Talk about this.
Get into it if you want.
The shine box.
I've been out.
Issue.
Yeah.
The shine.
Go get your fucking shine box.
Exactly.
I told that to people.
And I was wondering if they saw Goodfellas
and half the people that I've told that
to did not see Goodfellas.
So I had more effect.
Really?
And actually, if you saw Goodfellas, it would
have even more effect.
I would think so.
I don't know.
Look, you know what?
I remember.
Interesting when people get the references and when
they don't.
Right.
Which, by the way, I want to let
you know, so I just want to let
you know really quickly, there's a lot of
thank yous for apparently they had sort of
eureka moments about certain things that we worked
toward in the past couple of Sonic.
So I just want to let you know.
And I was asked specifically to make sure
that you were thanked on behalf of a
bunch of subscribers, that they had gotten something
really interesting out of the past couple.
They didn't describe it to me, but they
wanted to know, wanted you to know that
they were really felt awakened in the past
couple of Sonics.
So, you know, take or leave as you
wish.
Anyways.
Well, like I like I like reciprocation.
So I'm into Kratom, Bolly Green.
I'm into really good.
I get only organic coffee, organic cigarettes, American
spirit.
I got about a six to seven hundred
dollar a month cigarette Kratom coffee budget.
And that's why I'm doing these Sonics.
It doesn't cover that, by the way.
So it kind of lets you in on
how well we're doing.
We're not, you know, rolling in dough here.
But I'd like to cover the the coffee,
cigarette, whatever.
And I mean, I don't know how much
the semi-athletic Latin call girl goes for
these days.
I hear it's pretty high.
That's another that's another request.
So anyway, I haven't been in the market
for that in a while.
So I don't know.
Yeah.
I'm going to bring up just a little
bit.
Sure.
Hey, listen.
I never have.
I'll tell you a quick story.
OK.
Back.
Good.
OK.
Well, what I was going to tell you
is I say, hey, listen, go ahead.
Good.
Shoot.
I got you.
There's a little delay, I guess.
I'm sorry.
Waiting for the resurrection of the dead.
That seriously touched my spirit.
That was one of the comments.
But I want to get to another interesting
thing.
Somebody asked about collaboration when it came to
teaching young people because they already do that
and they would like to do it because
you mentioned something about going to the West
a bit and possibly getting into that.
Now, they may have the resources to bring
you some of those young people.
I don't know.
But how should they get in touch with
you if that sounds?
That sounds really weird.
And by the way, just think about that.
Bring you some young people.
That sounds weird.
I would rephrase that.
But that's OK.
Fair enough.
Young people mean 70 and younger.
OK, let's classify.
Sure.
But no, that's fine.
Look, I'm pretty good at advertising amongst the
those who need to know.
Like we've gotten pretty good shows on the
show.
Let's see people showing up for the webinars
on the weather and whatever else we did.
Scalarator word will get out.
We're going to have music, food, talk, powwows,
stuff like that, because, look, I don't know.
I don't know where young people are getting
their information from, but they're getting crap.
Where are they going to get it from
their parents, their co-workers, their professors?
Oh, come on.
Give me a break just to show them
how to search and see what's right and
basically learn how to read.
Yeah.
And that's let me just tell you, there's
a story.
I'll skip the story for another time has
to do with call girls.
The other thing I want to mention, I've
been out in the world, I'm getting like
right now I'm putting the cases together.
I mean, it has to look really and
feel luxury.
That's why when I offer the finished product
to someone, tell me how you feel about
it.
Then tell me what you think.
And right, because it's the feel.
So I'm going through all these processes, actually
spiritual processes.
You know, when you water clean stuff spiritually,
right?
So I'm actually everything that I'm doing gets
washed several times, even when the interior of
the case put together, which leads me to
this requires a lot of acquisition of materials
and stuff.
So I've been going around town, different places,
and they know me for coming in there.
They're like, oh, this guy's here.
He's got you listen to him.
And I'm like, OK.
But I hear the response back from people
all walks of life.
You know, people say about hope for society,
make the world a better place, all that
stuff.
It's a done deal, folks.
Let me just say it.
I can say it in three or four
different languages.
Let me say it again in English.
Where you're going as a society is a
done deal.
There's no hope about it.
There's no let's change it.
Let's make it better.
It's a done deal.
It's fucked.
You guys, meaning the society at large, is
fucked and you don't know it and you
don't care.
Right.
And you're just going to keep going the
way it is.
And this has been going on for a
long time, but it's a done deal.
I just want to say that.
In other words, nobody's changing.
Nobody's doing anything.
There's a there are fortunately have been around
the exceptions, right?
The subs and other people.
But at large, you know, like I said,
broad sweep through town, various suppliers, various walks
of life and even running into, you know,
what you call your professionals.
It's a done deal.
We're talking dumb as dirt and anything that
goes, anything that they put on you, meaning
your controllers, you're going to take it standing
up, sitting down, however.
And there's no going to be very little
blowback.
The blowback is marginalized very quickly.
What's coming is coming.
And as far as I can say, it's
well deserved because remember, we live in a
voluntary world.
So this is not a grim message, but
you always got to do what you know
needs to be done.
And to finish off with this, what I'm
doing is a catch me if you can.
He's having lunch with his dad.
The two mice fall in a bucket of
cream.
One decides to drown and the other one
got so was so dominant or so persevering
on getting out.
He churned that cream into butter and walked
right out of the bucket.
Right.
So but there's still mice.
And they say it's a rat race.
I'm not in a rat race.
I'm not a rat.
Right.
But anyway, you got to put the work
where the work needs to be done.
Like Gorgeous said, it's called a lot of
people have called it the work.
So I'm going to keep doing the work.
And yeah.
So anyway, that's cool.
The resurrection of the dead.
What was the other thing you said?
Well, I had another thing lined up and
it is Greek said plants are in a
dream state and chickens parentheses animals in an
envy state.
So does eating animals make you take on
those attributes, focusing on plants would lead to
more dreamlike existence and possible interacting other dreamlike
realities?
That's the way they wrote the question.
But I get the point of it.
You do, too.
I'm sure.
Well, think of it.
You know how water takes the shape of
its container.
These other energies are going to take your
shape.
So how compatible are they?
You're not going to turn into a plant.
You're not going to turn into a chicken.
And those attributes, attributes from those various inputs
that you have will not change you because
we talked about predominant energies, your physical body
and the way it functions is a predominant.
It will affect that.
Sure.
Like, for example, it's very well known that
meat eaters and people that are vegetarian have
are very different in many cases in their
demeanor and their quality of fitness on and
on ability to recover.
It's very, very well known.
Whether it's discussed or documented is irrelevant.
You can experiment on yourself.
But does it mean, you know, if one
eats just the carnivore, you know, one of
these vegetable, they're going to turn into either
one?
No.
But is there an influence?
Yes.
Just like drinking really good water versus just
straight tap water.
Is there an influence?
Yes.
Is it subtle?
If you add up enough subtle things, do
they become something major?
Yes.
Well, for sure.
And look, even when people look at things
like the consumption of alcohol, right.
And somebody who drinks constantly and drinks like,
you know, rotgut crap, boy, you can tell
that person when they walk in a room
versus somebody who actually partakes of, you know,
a bit of fine liquor every now and
then drinks.
You know what I'm saying?
Like, I remember the hanging out with the
crowds up on the Upper East Side.
They drank the best liquor and they were
alcoholic.
You couldn't read.
They didn't look like a typically an alcoholic
you'd expect to look.
Right.
But even the people that decide to consume
a little bit, it becomes different.
You see, so the pace and the quality,
these are two different aspects of what can
affect the outcome.
And I think food and all of it,
it's all relative.
Right.
I mean, in this way.
Qualitative.
There you go.
Quality.
Everything.
They don't deal with quality.
Everything's quantity.
You know, like when you look at the
nutritional information or when they talk about color,
there's no such thing as color.
It's photons hitting your eye and all this
stuff.
Yeah.
There's a reason for it, though.
And we've talked about it.
This is not a good place.
Is it a bad place?
Well, that's speculative and open for suggestion and
subjective.
But is it a good place?
Absolutely not.
You mean in this entire existence here?
It's not good, but it doesn't necessarily mean
it's bad.
The best you're going to get is not
good.
You know what I mean?
Right.
That's the best this place could be, is
not good.
And down from not good would be what?
Is not good less than fair?
Yeah.
I'd say so.
I would say so.
Yeah.
So then you go, not good, bad, very
bad, nightmarish, hellish.
Right.
Those are the levels that you exist in
here.
Right.
And then some of the things that we're
dealing with, right, I mean, like I was
reading this whole study on how like, you
know, if a man has like more testosterone
in his system, he's more likely to select
red things, you know, stuff like that.
And I'm going, does that apply to food?
And yeah, it does.
And that's why they put red food coloring
in a lot of things.
And I'm looking at it going, oh, well,
that's just brutally obvious.
But yeah.
But, you know, but at the same time,
red is a dangerous thing, because in nature,
things that have red on them usually are
problematic for us.
You know, walking upright, you know, can be
cultural also.
Like we look at red as alert and
green is as go and in Asia, it's
the opposite.
Green is alert and red is go.
Doesn't mean the traffic, you know, they have
all adopted similar, you know, no matter where
you go in the world, a red octagon,
all right, red octagon means stop, regardless of
what language.
Right.
So there's universal, I call it image training.
That's why I like the doctor who so
much with the psychic papers, you know, is
if someone walks up to you, commands you
and flips open a wallet and closes it,
you see a shiny piece of metal in
there, you intuitively based on all the cultures
in the world, stop and obey them.
You know, so you can literally mess around
with people who just get a badge on
a wall, flip it open, flip it closed.
Right.
And they say, oh, he's an authority.
I've seen people get away with that with
the appeal to authority, which is based on
a flip of just a piece of metal,
you know, in a wallet.
And it's not even in particular in its
like aspects.
It just generally resembles a badge.
Therefore, they begin to submit.
I mean, yeah.
And back back east, like Brooklyn, Bronx, New
Haven, Connecticut, was it Oceanside, New Jersey?
Is there an ocean side?
There is.
I think so.
Or.
Yeah.
OK.
These are places where I know not firsthand,
but pretty close people that work like civil
service jobs, bus drivers, whatever.
And they were bored.
So they went out and bought a Crown
Vic black with one of those lights that
the police have searchlight on it, the wheels
that make it look like police tires and
blue.
And just for shits and giggles, like they
say, they would pull over people with flashing
lights and impersonate a detective and people would
follow through and they would just do that
for their own thrill.
The reason I mentioned those places is because
I know people who were doing that in
those areas that got caught for impersonating an
officer, you know, right.
So because they got a high, they got,
you know, for domination or whatever.
So yeah.
Yeah.
By the way, for in terms of domination,
actually, I won't mention a name.
I think I told the story once the
psychiatrist and the psychologist that I've known, I've
dated them.
And I think I mentioned they're they're the
nuttiest people, by the way, and I've dealt
with one recently.
I actually canceled a scalerator.
I refused to sell to them because they're
too crazy.
They're actually a famous YouTuber.
You could piece that together.
But one of them, I remember with one
and actually two separate ones kept coming, says,
we have a problem at the university, City
University of New York, right at the psychology
department.
All the women used to notice that when
they came back, if their locker changed their
shoes, there was this gooey, sticky substance in
their shoes.
And but that's not the end of it.
We found out that they put a camera
in there.
And one of the other psychology professors was
ejaculating in women's shoes and they busted him.
Right.
Yeah.
The other one who was a psychiatrist with
the drugs, we went out for a nice
dinner movie kind of thing.
And she ordered the cab to go down
to the meat district, a lower west side.
And there's a building kind of funked up,
funky black steel door.
And you walk in, there's a smell like
a lot of strong body odors.
It was an S&M club and you
could see people's leathered up, whatever, going from
room to room.
And it was like a club that had
the red velvet and all that.
And I'm like, what are we doing here?
She goes, you'll find out.
And I said, I'm going to the bathroom.
And I went around and left and never,
never made contact with her again.
She was into S&M, right?
Yeah.
So what I'm trying to say is these
people, the shoemakers' children have no shoes is
right on.
But not with, here's the thing, not with
the shoemakers.
I bet all the shoemakers' children have great
shoes.
But with the lawyers, they're screwed up illegally.
The doctors are screwed up with fitness, health
and all that.
With very little exception, the psychologists are all
crazy.
So it depends on what level, right?
Again, are there any of those professions that
I mentioned good?
Absolutely not.
Are they bad?
Take it.
It's up to you to decide how bad
you want to take it.
But anyway, let's go back to the thing
about the, I mentioned the Doctor Who.
These are all authorities.
I'm not anti-authority.
It's just that we've been hijacked, right?
And it's the norm.
But the Doctor Who, the psychological papers or
psychic papers was just a blank piece of
paper and whoever he flashed it to, anywhere
they were from, they saw it as an
authority figure, right?
So once you understand that, you can follow
suit with whatever you're doing.
I mean, that's what, how many times have
you heard of a story of an old
man that looks semi-homeless going to a
high-end jewelry store, orders up a $50
,000 necklace, he's got cash in a brown
paper bag, and they're all making fun of
him, even with the cash.
Then the next day he comes back in
a $3,000 suit out of a Rolls
Royce, and he tells the people, hey, that
was me yesterday, I just, I'll keep buying
jewelry from you as long as you promise
me you treat everyone with equal dignity, right?
Those kinds of tests.
So there's no reason for that.
But that doesn't, I mean, where's the standard,
right?
I know you don't watch video shorts much,
but there's a modern version of it now
where a guy goes around and acts like
he's deaf and signals, I need something to
eat, can I have some money, and the
people that are mean to him and mock
him and swing their hands at him and
stuff like that, he walks away, and he
goes over to somebody else, and the person
that gives him the money, he takes it,
he starts to walk away, he turns back,
and then hands him back the money, and
then hands him a pile of money.
And this is like- Right, as a
reward.
Yeah, it's a common short.
And then the other person that just waved
him off is usually close by, and they're
like, oh, can I have some?
And he's like, yeah, no.
Yeah, yeah, it's like a public demonstration.
Right, right.
It's actually a very popular YouTube short now,
or whatever, TikTok, whatever the video shorts are,
it's all over the place now.
Yeah.
Well, this is very Daoist also.
In other words, when you have irony like
that, it's very much in the Daoist economy.
When you read Daoist stuff, there's a lot
of irony in there.
No, and Aesop's Fables remind me of that,
too, some of them, the deeper ones, because
- Ironic and cautionary.
Cautionary.
Ironic and cautionary.
Yeah.
Anyways, here's another one.
I live in a state that has the
softest water in the country.
He says, I'll post some pictures of interest
for my four-year-old hot water cylinder,
which has, let's see, whatever, oh, stalagmites growing
on the fittings, rust stains coming out the
top and down the sides, and severely restricted
flow.
And then a response- So you started
off by saying it's soft water, it's very
mild water?
Yeah.
Okay.
That's possible.
That's angry water.
That's the water getting angry, running through pipes,
yeah.
Yeah, and he also states, just because the
local water authority provides figures and data about
the quality of the water does not make
it true.
So it's a bit of a mixed thing
he's saying here, where to me it's like,
yeah, you definitely got some angry water there,
but man, I've seen some very corrosive kind
of stuff happen with supposedly clean water, and
there you go.
Yeah.
I know the suburbs around Atlanta, Georgia have
basically rainwater, like 30 or 40 TDS.
If you were to try to collect rainwater
in a clean pot and measure it with
a TDS meter, it would be up to
20 or 30.
So what I do, for example, with the
device, if you don't have hard water, you're
low on the list, even though you'll get
one, but we've also discovered the device creates
healing water.
So you know how people used to travel
to springs and spas for therapeutic purposes?
You can make tap water therapeutic with this.
But I don't want to make those kinds
of claims, right?
That's much later.
That would be another direction to go in.
But yeah.
Right.
But anyway, is that person, is he just
wondering why the unsightly plumbing, or is he
having an issue with the water quality?
Oh, no, I just read it there as,
like, I'll send you the pictures of, I
just read what he said, which is that,
you know, it says that he has this
kind of water and they say it's soft,
but that's what happens.
And meanwhile, soft water, right?
Don't trust the authorities.
That's what happens.
Water is trying to break out of a
cage is one of the alien second one
where they capture the alien.
And it's like, really, they think they got
it contained and the thing is almost strong
enough to break out of the steel box
that it's in or titanium or whatever.
Right.
You want to leave the room.
So yeah, water will do that if it
can't break out the water, the optimum container
of water.
When in motion, when in motion is look
in the mirror, look at the capillaries around
your eyes or the roots of a tree
or a lightning bolt, you know, that Lichtenberg
configuration.
That's the optimum movement for water when it's
at moderate speeds, at super high speeds, it's
slightly different.
At very low speeds, it's slightly different.
The optimum container for water when it's still
is ovoid, not elliptical, but ovoid.
So those two rules are very simple to
apply.
And the biggest enemy to water quality, immediate
enemy is light, light and heat, and then
air in that order.
Yeah.
That's why all the water that most people
buy or most of the water that most
people buy is in clear containers subject to
light.
Yeah.
Go figure.
Right.
Not good.
All of that you covered years ago on
that special episode, which we have reposted for
you subscribers here on the Patreon at the
Greek's request, it's there.
So it's that special water episode, just so
you guys know.
Also by the way- Yeah, it's offered.
Yeah, go ahead.
No, it's still offered.
Yeah?
Yeah.
No, you're still offering it on the Patreon.
I'm putting it on the Patreon for them.
And also I put up some more of
the weather work as you requested that I
had.
I had the second seminar, two hours, so
I put that out as well.
And trying to give the subscribers- And
there's a third one.
Oh, I don't- I think there's a
third one also.
I don't think I have the third one.
I ask Master Bruce would let you know.
Ah, okay.
I will check with him because I don't
have the third one.
But I do have the first two and
they're up there for you guys.
Okay, that's fine.
Yeah.
And- That's fine.
It's such a thing as too much information.
Even putting one out a month is fine
because it takes a while to digest.
But if you have a sense of urgency
that you got to get some weather work
done, it's good to have all of them
available.
So anyway.
Absolutely.
Hey, I just wanted to let you know
one other thing is that people did start
discussing the cabbage.
They finally got the steak cabbage and a
few other recipes.
Cabbage roast.
Sorry.
What was the steak?
What was that?
What was the- Broccoli steak.
Broccoli steak.
Okay, I got it mixed up.
Yeah, go ahead.
Yeah.
And the names have nothing to do with
how it looks or trying to look like
roast or steak.
It's just the feeling that you get.
When you feel like a roast, do the
cabbage.
When you feel like a steak, do the
broccoli.
There you go.
And- It's just feeling.
Yeah.
And they're sharing this back and forth now.
They're trying it.
And I'm just letting you know that people
are going back in the old Sonics and
going and doing some of that stuff as
well.
So by the time- Yeah.
It's all method.
Just because you've had cabbage doesn't mean you've
had it done this way.
The method, it's the method that changes.
Like I've said, if you cut carrots three
different ways, you're going to get three different
flavored carrots, depending on the cut, you know?
So exactly.