So, Sonic Event 68, I believe it is, and here we are, Greek, you know, they brought up in
the chat room a couple of things, so let's start with the most practical, right, which,
what is the number one tool I would say that anyone needs at any time for any purpose,
whether it's to cook or to survive or... Oh, yeah, yeah, right. A blade. A blade. Yeah,
a blade, yeah. And they asked about sharpening. A jig. It depends on where you are. It could
be called a jig in other places. Oh, okay. But anyway, that's if you're a gnome. Fair enough,
fair enough. But it is, look, it's easily, you know, you need to be able to cut things,
to shape things, I mean, absolutely, right, to be able to eat, to be able to clean your food,
especially meat, to be able to properly prepare vegetables. I mean, a sharp blade,
and you brought up how important it is to have a quality blade and to make sure that these things
are sharp, obviously, because... At least one quality blade, yeah. Okay. Start off with that.
Why? Why do I say at least one? Right. You said blade, not blades, because they're expensive,
and they always were. To put it in context, a good used car was about where you, the equivalent
of a good used car today was what you were expected to pay for, let's say, as something
that appeared to be like a sword back in the days. Yeah, yeah, that's not right. Yeah, it was
in the thousands, and compared to, you know, if you look comparative, you know, what money buys,
let's say. Right. And it's still, so they're much, when you look at a $200 kitchen knife, that's
cheap. Oh, very much so. I mean, comparatively. Like we talked about the pots, right? And you
said, look, you can go get a set of pots for $100 for sure, and you know, you'll be able to cook with
them for a little bit, and they'll eventually look good. For a lot of people, that's all they have
their whole life. Right. That's okay. It's not being snobbish. It's a decent pot. If you were
to just get one pot, let's say, it would be over $100 minimum. Right. For one pot, for at least
something that you can actually control the heat with. But anyway, go back to the knife. Somebody
posted a knife sharpener, which is the one with the strut support to hold the angle.
Anybody that's worked in tooling and machine shops or whatever, any kind of precision tool,
you don't sharpen it freehand, you know? Right. You don't hold it up to the grinder or the stone
freehand, unless you are a knife smith kind of person. Right. And then you understand the angles,
you understand. Right. It's kind of like, you know, when you see baseball being played by the
pitcher and the hitter, who's at base, they don't have any jigs or struts holding them in place,
but they have full muscle, muscular and agility control. Right. By the way, that's why I say
sports are all fixed. Do you know that? And I learned this from hanging around some B team.
A team is, you know, the big, you know, they have a B team, right? Like there's Yankees, Mets.
That's the ones you see on TV is the A team, but they also have a B team, right? Which is ready.
We hear about a rookie coming up, right? They already have another team. You know, the guys,
right. Okay. Anyone on the A team or B team, I found this from a B team person 20 years ago. He
says, anyone talked about sports being fixed. So yeah, it's all fixed, but we don't talk about it
because it's been known for, you know, almost a hundred years or, or, you know, since the big
games became quote unquote professional, because before they became professional, they were,
they were social gatherings more, you know? Right. Baseball. Indeed. You bring up baseball.
I like that one because that was a social gathering, right? I mean, towns,
but here's my point. What I got. And I got asked since then for more than one,
anyone that goes up to bat can hit the ball every time and put it exactly where you want it
every time. That's some of the time every time. So what you're actually watching when you watch a
baseball game is something like WWF world federation, right? You know, the, what's that,
what's that called? Theatrical wrestling, right? Well, that's the difference between Greco and
theatrical wrestling, right? These guys, if they really were punching each other, I mean,
they do say they can kill each other. They do serious damage. I mean, a 300, 400 pound guy,
you know, it's theatrical. Yeah. Yeah. So, so what do I mean by this is if you can be like,
not like what you see, which is, you know, a game of random happenstance based on certain
select talents that happen to do better than others on baseball. No, they can all hit the
ball every time anywhere you want it within a pretty good tolerance. Right. Okay. So that means
that that kind of, they have that much control, but they don't show it at all. Right. Just otherwise
there wouldn't be much of a game. Uh, so when you're sharpening knife, if you have that control,
in other words, if you can hold a knife freehand over a stone or a owning, uh, or whatever,
whatever system you're going to use to form an edge, if you have that kind of control,
right. Uh, and you can rationalize what angle you want and measure it and see that you get it. Also,
you need, uh, you need, what's called a sight glass or a magnifier. And I loop will do like a
five X I loop or an eight X I loop. Right. Um, most people, if an eye loop is just like a
magnifying glass, you've seen people hold them up to their eyes, to look at jewelry and other
things like that. If you work in mining or whatever, you carry one in your pocket.
So, uh, use an eye loop to look at what you're doing. And by the way, the ancients had this,
they were called, um, looking glass. So wherever you can James Bible,
when they were building the tabernacle, they wove the tapestry and the, the young
women and they used a looking glass. Right. What's a looking way. Right. So,
and they also had looking glass to look at the stars. So microscopes and telescopes have always
been around. Right. A lot of people think of looking glass as a mirror though. And it's
sometimes it is also, yeah. Well, you wouldn't use a mirror to weave a fine tapestry. You would be
using a magnifier. Right. Yeah. So you have to look at the context. Yeah. It's like one thing
that's used all around a word that could be kicked around, which we'll get into some other things
that words have been kicked around soon. But so my point here is this, if you can get a good blade
now here, here, I'm going to confess most of the knives that I have that I still take pride in. I
buy it at, at, um, surplus stores like Ross or TJ max or Marshall home goods. Um, uh, and it doesn't
matter what brand they are. I could look at the steel and know if it's good steel or not. Right.
And then I have a good Japanese blade, but, um, that's one of the things that mass production,
uh, things get better, but they may not work better because of the last few finishing items
that are necessary, uh, to make them work better or not. They're like back in the days of VCRs,
when they got really cheap, they only lasted a few weeks and they broke down. Why? Because they
just didn't use a good enough bearing on the capstan. One little tiny part, instead of spending
a 25 cents on it, they spent 2 cents. If they just spent 20 cents more,
the VCRs would have lasted almost indefinitely. You see how foolish manufacture, how it's gotten.
So yeah, that was crazy. Cause that would be the one thing that would tangle up your tape.
You would get mangled tapes really quickly because of this one little tiny part.
Yeah. It's 20, 20 cents difference over a hundred dollar item. They still didn't do it. So,
okay. So what do I mean by this is if you have very good control,
I would recommend, go ahead, get it, you know, go ahead and keep your knife sharp.
There was a, uh, a strut based, uh, a knife sharpener that someone posted. Those are good.
I've used those before too, but I don't need them. I can do just as well without it. But that's me,
right? That's like, if you go up in a professional team and they tell you, Chuck or Greek, get on the,
get on, get on the plate and go ahead and hit, I won't be able to hit any of them,
you know, that are pitched at me. Right. Right. But if I was one of them, I could hit every one
anywhere. Right. So when you get to a certain level and by the way, it's taken me almost 20
years to figure out knife sharpening, because I wasn't happy with a lot of the, you know,
quote unquote, freehand instructions that were given out there. It's like, Oh my gosh. That's
why one of the things I've always been discussing recently is the biggest, one of the biggest
problems people have is communication. Yes. When, when someone can do something or see something or
right. They can't communicate it to someone else in a way. It just doesn't make any sense. It's
a, what do you call it? It's like all crosstalk or information's left out. So yeah, very interesting.
So, and I've mentioned this over and over and over, you must be able to communicate.
So I found out that the best way to do it for me to learn was I was watching Japanese knife and
sword makers and it was all hardcore Japanese stuff, you know, no talking and all that. And
I was just watching how he held his hand when he was honing the blade and sharpening the blade
and putting an edge on the blade. I just said it all in reverse. What you do first is you put an
edge on the blade, then you sharpen that edge and then you hone that edge. That's the order.
What's also important of a good blade is what do you call, well, what do you in war,
when you run out of bullets, what do you have sticking out at the end of your gun?
A bayonet, right? So you're out of bullets, but you could still defend yourself, right?
And if you put it on a stick that's really long, it's a spear. And if you make it really small and
light and put it on a quill and shoot it from a high tension, whatever, it's an arrow. So it's
not just a blade. It's not just a knife. It's a weapon in many forms. You can make micro darts
that you can shoot out of a straw basically, or a pipe, and that's called a blow gun, an air gun.
By the way, there are 50 caliber air guns now, 50 cal pellet guns. So some of these ex-felons
who are not allowed to own a firearm, they could pack a 50 caliber air gun, which at five feet
will kill you, by the way. Well, because technically speaking, it's not a firearm, is it?
Right. No, it's not. Actually, technically speaking, in legal terms, firearms,
the federal law is definition of a firearm is a machine gun, chemical weapons, grenades,
or shotgun modified to a length of less than 20 inches. So a 45 pistol is not a firearm,
but they still call it that, right? I've seen this used in legal terms. It's like federal
charges for bringing a gun into Washington, D.C. They kept saying firearms. It's not a firearm.
I had a nine millimeter Glock and a 45. It's not a firearm. Look at the law,
and they're all like standing there. Oh, but you have a contract. You signed and you said you would,
so now it goes to contract law, which is another thing I wanted to maybe start a small series on
because someone in the chat posted, why don't we talk about legislation and jurisdiction of
courts and things like that? Well, how do you finagle that when no one there knows what's
going on at all, at all? Well, and two of the most famous cases of firearms, once again, in quotes,
being the cause for people being gone after, you know, you think about Waco, you think about Randy
Weaver. What were two of the biggest problems? Modification of a shotgun, like you just brought
up. Yeah, it's a modified shotgun, machine gun, chemical weapons or grenades. If so,
a 38, a 45, a Glock is not a firearm. A 30 rifle, 35 rifle is not a firearm. It's interesting, but
you see how they overuse the term? Of course, of course. I have seen Homeland Security come
after someone for something that happened in the airport and they're charging all this stuff. And I
looked at this. So where did the hell did they get the definitions? Because none of the supplies
and they wrote back and they said they got the definitions and the charging instrument,
you know, the letter from Webster's Dictionary. This is how idiotic. Yeah. So that's why when I
saw the comment about talk about jurisdiction, legislation, well, how do you deal with people
that no one there knows what's going on? Yeah, they're using a book that's supposed to show you
diction to give definition, even though the definition is incidental.
Oh, that's that's that's something you want to avoid. But you just basically look up the
my favorite. What I like to just stick with is two things. One thing is none of their laws at all,
except for the Declaration of Independence, which is not codified as law. It's actually
archived by the way. Legally, when something is archived means it's no longer in use. So when you
go to the National Archives, guess what they have their Declaration of Independence, the U.S.
Constitution. Should I go on? Yeah, look it up. So the other thing is, OK, the thing that I use,
I would use for them is first of all, people is never in any of their codes, rules, regulations
or laws. Never. It's persons. Right. And a person is defined as a corporation, a trust, fictional
entity. Right. Yep. Whatever. But if you're endorsing private credit, like I've talked about,
you start. So here's the thing. You go in there talking like this. The judge has the clerk sitting
next to him. There's different clerks. His clerk of the court is the clerk of the of the judge.
Right. They have a little laptop or computer that's next to them. And while they call your
name and up there, that person pulls up from the attorney general's office all of your information,
everything you've ever done since third grade. So if you have a passport, a bank account,
a credit card, whatever, whatever, you start talking this way, he's going to say,
I know, Jack, I see you got a passport and you're a member of one of those nasty veterans associations
and blah, blah, blah. Right. Tell him how long he gets, Joe. Joe, tell him how long,
how many years he's going to get. Right. So you got. Yeah. So that's the other thing.
But when I say the people is never in any of the laws and the way they tell you you're not a people.
The other thing is all of their codes that are in sections, you know,
or articles, you know, one through 50 or one through 20, whatever. Yeah. Usually you go
up to 50. Most states only go up to the 30s or 20s. Anyway, if just the first and second
articles or chapters of their codes, first two up to five in the US code is definitions.
So you just stick with that. There's no people in there either. And it defines very clearly what
things are. So it doesn't matter which code or title they charge you with. By definition, none
of it applies to you. And then the prosecutor will say, well, you think that the law doesn't
apply to, you know, absolutely does. That's why I'm bringing this up to catch 22 for them. So
that's the way you handle with these idiots, because they're all idiots. And the same with
a medical, whatever, you know, if people go to a medical, this is all tied into because the legal
and the whatever runs the medical, if you don't believe it, go have an offhand discussion with
any medical person that's state certified or whatever state license, they bring up like
some natural remedy. And they'll say, well, legally, I can't say what. So the whole time
you were diagnosing me like that was all legal function. We were making legal determinations
when you told me I have diabetes. That's a legal determination. Yes, it is. He won't answer that.
Also, when they say you should have a certain procedure done because of this condition,
say I want you to sign it, write me an affidavit and sign it. Right, right. And he can never do it.
Never. The most you're going to do is send you a lab report and say that, well, you've been
diagnosed, diagnosed. Remember, 70% of diagnoses are misdiagnoses.
Will assume a potential not that you haven't don't have, you know, you were diagnosed with
what is potentially a serious illness. So presumptive and people take it as if they're
saying that they have this. It's just like when the World Trade Center in the first 10 minutes,
they put a picture of Osama bin Laden. One of the suspects of this might be Osama bin Laden.
And the people on the street is Osama bin Laden did it. No one ever said Osama bin Laden did
anything. Right. But the people take the city. Right. So so it's all presumptive. So anyway,
there's your own flavor, because with the jurisdiction and the courts and the legislation,
legislation is totally hands off, by the way. So there's just nobody there. Look, if you
sure there are people there that know what it is or whatever, pretty evil.
But if you show outwardly that, you know, the law, they will get rid of you right away. The
same with the medical issue. They will show you the door and tell you to leave the organization.
So is the Greek saying that the entire medical judiciary and all that is completely corrupt and
inept? Yes, absolutely. But there are exceptions and the exceptions, like I've always said,
there are two types. One is the person who just woke up to what's going on and is looking for
an exit strategy. What do I mean by an exit strategy? I just got hired on for 150 grand
working as a whatever assistant D.A. and they found out what's going on. It's totally wrong
based on any ethics or morality they might involve in their personal quest on this planet. Right.
And they're like, my gosh, I've got a quarter of a million in school loans. How am I going to pay
that? I mean, how am I going to pay the money? How am I going to survive? What's my wife and
kids going to say if I leave? So they take anywhere between two weeks and two years to
find an exit strategy, like get out of there. Right. Right. The other option is that you got
some real evil people that know that it's bad and they just keep doing it because that's just
what they are. These are like the kind of people that would burn bugs with a magnifying glass
or and when they got older and they could have some loose change or an ounce,
they're going by poisons and poison the family dog. Right. Then or break. You know what I mean?
Like that old psychopaths. Look, bitch, you knew I was a scorpion when you brought me in here.
Yeah. So you have some of those in there, too. And everybody else is just NPC all the way across.
It's kind of interesting. It's funny how now when eight years ago or 10, 15 years ago,
speaking to people, I'm saying, you know, 95 percent of the population is zombie. You know,
I didn't use the word NPC. They have no value whatsoever. Oh, no, it's only 30 percent. Now
people are saying it's more like 90 percent. Finally, they're catching and nothing much has
changed. It's just that their perception has changed because of certain events that have
come across. Right. Like with the vaccine, people are all up in arms with the vaccine. I'm like,
what do you mean? No humans took that vaccine. Yeah. But there was one hundred fifty million
Americans that took that vaccine. I'm like, let me repeat myself. There are no humans that
took that vaccine. I don't care if three hundred and fifty million Americans, no humans have ever
taken that vaccine. Sorry. They're like, what do you mean? I'm like, oh, boy, you don't see it.
You don't see it. Right. Right. So. All right. So anyway, back to the question,
we went a long way from knives. You got to have sharp blades, because by the way,
if society collapsed, people like I've got my guns to protect myself. You'll run out of bullets
really fast, especially when people figure out you have a gun. Why? Because they're going to
try to get it from you. And most right. If you have it because they think it's worth something
to they're just as dumb as you are. So what will happen is they'll make their effort. You have to
sleep. Right. They'll try to take it when you're not shooting. He's asleep. Let's go take gun.
You'll shoot off some more bullets to keep them even further away. Right. Right. So you'll be
shooting up. So once people figure out you have a gun of any kind, they want it. And I assure you,
if you think you have a three month supply of bullets, you'll be gone in three days. Why?
Because the people, again, want it and they will make a concerted effort to take it from you. And
that concerted effort will make you use more bullets. Yeah. Yeah. So it's OK. So if you do
have a gun for when the society collapses or whatnot, do not use it unless it is absolutely
necessary. And you are on the run, on the go. In other words, you are not using it out of where
you plan on staying put. You're already on the road and you're moving and you're using it as
a defense or offense in a mobile situation, never stationary home base situation. It's the opposite
of what they tell you. There's even ads. But you want to protect your home base and your family
with a gun or whatever, you know, those gun ads, commercial, whatever. Fewer and fewer of them.
This is a while back is when Obama took office. Remember, everybody, all the patriots were like,
oh, we got to get our guns now. Right. Yeah, of course. Country's going down.
So, like, no, you never let if you're keeping a castle or a home base, you'd never want anyone
to know you have that stuff because that's what they want. And you're going to end up right. So,
OK, you get the point, right? Right. That's like the only purpose to have those kinds of weapons
for the trajectory of a firearm type stuff. I'm saying is when you're mobile. Basically,
you drive by or when you're driving down the road, they try to take you over.
Mad Max style. You open up on them. Right. Only then do you use it. Yeah. All right.
Right. Left side about that. Exactly. By the way, I've never heard anyone say that, by the way,
online that you shouldn't have a gun. Well, I mean, if you do have a gun, don't ever let anyone
know you have it and don't fire it if you're in a stationary situation like your home or your
castle or wherever, only when you're on the move. But good. Well, it's just like those people who
store up all kinds of stuff. I mean, and everybody knows they have it. And I'm like, well, you're a
target. Yeah, you're a target. Yeah. The people that just ran out that they're going to come.
You know. Yeah. You're going to have to do. Yeah. If it's a society cop situation,
you have to act as if you have no food and water, no matter how much food and water you have.
Right. So you have to be told in deception mode. I'm talking about to the public image that you
put out. Yeah. I mean, it seems like the best thing to invest in really is camouflage to make
it disappear. You know, whatever it is, you disappear when you're right. Right. So, yeah.
Anything that you have that's desirable, you could others might know that you have it. It's
if you're on if you're out of there, if you are all in and all FT running off. Right.
If you're running off, then it's OK because you're running. And but so if you whatever
neighborhood you live in, if everything starts going down, do you have any food or water? No,
I don't. Do you have any food or you don't have any food and water either? It doesn't matter
how much food and water you have always. Right. Because you're right. So the first thing they're
going to do is let's see if we can find somebody with some so we can go take it.
It's not only on a personal level. Let's say you've got a community of 50 households that
do have food and water and you're all cool with it within a matter of time. You pick at the time,
whether a few hours, hours, days or weeks. Others that another community will find out
that this community has. And then you'll all be in danger. So no one should ever show.
Right. Ever. Right. Right. Yeah. Unless, again, you're on the run or you're so isolated.
Right. You put up a facade. Yeah, this is by the way, everything that I'm saying is known by anyone
who's just visited this planet. But it seems like the people who were born here have no clue.
Anyway. So the blade idea is very, very smart. And the worst time to figure out how to get a
sharp knife or make a sharp knife is when you need it. That's the worst time. Right. Right.
So it's very important. Now, it's a matter of preference, of course. But you can't say what
I'm saying is a matter of opinion when having a sharp blade has been important all the way back.
And how far back do you want to go in history? Right. Probably. How far? It's it's prized
possession. Always. Yeah. All known history. Yeah. So forget. Yeah. The other thing that you
would skip the gunpowder and go right to energy weapons, which is another thing. Right. We'll
discuss maybe in the future. You want to go from blades to energy weapons. Forget about projectile
gunpowder, chemical stuff in the middle. So energy weapons are cool, too, where you push a button in
every one of them, a 50 foot radius. If you have any shillings in their mouth, they go up to 350
degrees. That will get their attention very quickly. Right. Right. So, OK.
So titles you brought up. Yeah. Well, the last thing I flip. Yeah. Go ahead. Sorry.
Well, that's I believe the word is Teflon. Somebody I'm going to get in front of the
computer and look. But that term was brought up the house gods or house idols. That was brought
up in the book of Kings when King David was on the run from on the land from Saul and he came to his
house and his wife said he's in his bed and they went and he wasn't in his bed. He put an idol in
the bed and they thought it was him. Right. Just a delay. Just to. Right. You know, the typical
thing where you even when you were young, you know, you you're out all night. You put something
in the bed, make it look you're sleeping in bed. You see this on television. Somebody puts a
basketball under the blanket to make it look like a head and then put some things underneath. So it's
kind of like maybe it could be the length of a body or so. And people think you're still in your
bed and you're actually out the window. Yeah. OK. Exactly. That's what King David did. And he
used the house idol, the Teflon. Why would they have it? Because that's what they have. I mean,
here's the thing where people don't understand. I had someone that was very messianic, messy,
messianic, you know, to Christians out there, mixed Judaism and Judaism that makes Christianity
thinks it makes it better. Right. He stood over the house. This is 12, 15 years ago.
I actually gave him a car and all that. He was trying to go out and be more real about
scripture. That's fine. I felt sorry for him. He goes to this lady that I recommended in New Mexico
and she was pretty wealthy and she was also a messianic. And they had many properties and
with their husband before he died, dedicated a lot of money to art museums and things.
And they had all these art statues in the house. And he gets there and he goes, oh,
I don't know if I could stay here, Greek. She's got the house is full of idols. She says she wants
to study scripture and be faithful. But she has idols. I said, well, what makes them idols? Is she
bowing down and praying to them or are they just works of art? What's the difference between an
idol and a statue? Absolutely nothing in material form. What makes them different is that you bow
down to one and pray to one and the other one is just decorative value. I mean, you see like a bust
of George Washington, right? Those are not an idol. It's not an idol. It's just a piece of art
representative of a historical thing. Exactly. So don't be so sensitive. It's all programming,
right? You know how many times people say, you know, they hear like, if you're not feeling
you got to go to a doctor or the doctor, like there's the doctor, right? Or you got to go to
the hospital, the hospital, like there's one hospital, right? That's programming. That's
all programming, you know, automatic reaction. So they see a statue. It's an idol. No, it's not.
Well, it's like somebody has a crossbar in their backyard. You look at it and go,
you have a giant cross erected in your backyard. And they're like, no, that's just the best design
to hang the laundry off of, you know, it looks kind of cool, like with rappers and rock and roll
people, they wear them. It's just the cross is literally about the crossing. It's a celestial
event. There's also the Southern Cross that we don't see here, but our friends in the upside down
Australia and that part of the world, let's say South America do see it. By the way,
the most interesting part of the sky that we can see is down there. That's where everything's
really happening. In other words, when you do get sky phenomenon, that is based on the ecliptic,
you know, east to west. It's most of the best sky phenomenon are viewed down like down by
down under or, you know, the near southern half of the continent of Africa or South America,
not up here. I just want to throw that in there. So anyway, the cross is just a symbol. It's a
decorative symbol, whatever. Of course, if you've been listening to Greek speak for more than
maybe a few hours, you know that there is no crucifixion in the Bible, no matter how many
times they put that word in there. Right. So, yeah. Yeah. But it's interesting to me. It's
like it's just I've heard this conversation a couple of times where it's like, why do you have
a giant cross in your backyard? Well, that's just really where we string the clothesline from.
And we get separate. It's a good structure. It's a strong structure. So it can be. It can be. Yeah.
So, yeah. So we covered house idols. There's not much more to talk about the house gods or
house idols, because many people would see things in many different ways. Also, you know, a lot of
history that we've got now about things that happened in the past is just simply not true.
You know what the funny thing is, is a long time ago, and I can't remember if it was through you
or with somebody else. But quite honestly, they said, you know, you can find those crosses around
people's necks represented in art long before. Oh, yeah. Eight hundred B.C. You could put in
Assyrian study as T.E.L.E., which is just a stone carving column. Right. I forgot the king.
He's wearing what they call a Maltese cross because it was an astronomical. Jason Brashears
talks about the Phoenix event that reoccurs. That's in other literature. That's called the
crossing the Great Crossing, because all of our celestial events tend to be from east to west.
Right. The what's called the ecliptic. And every hundred and thirty eight years, according to
Brashears, which seems pretty valid, it's you could back it up. There is an event that happens
where the object goes from north to south and it actually goes between the moon and the earth. So
it's pretty close and it's pretty big. So it wreaks a lot of havoc. So that was called the crossing.
I found out about that in the 80s when I was reading stuff about the flat earth. I had a
roommate and we rented a lot of the space that we were renting out of it actually to people that
were just traveling through New York City and just needed to stay for a few days here and there.
And we ended up making more. We're like, how are we going to afford this? So we'll just rent out
some of these rooms. We actually made more than we were paying for rent by rent. Right.
Right. Yeah. A lot of interesting people passing through and upstairs and below us and above us
are some interesting people. And they were really big into flat earth. We're talking about
nineteen eighty four and eighty five and eighty six. All I heard was flat earth, this concave
earth and this and that. And this that's this phenomenon here. Right. Reincarnation, this and
that. And make sure you die. Make sure you die. Conan Buddhism. Right. All this other stuff. So
all the stuff that you hear coming back again. Right. Because there was a big boom in that in
the eighteen hundreds, in the 1920s, 1880s, New Age movement again, boomed. And then again now.
Right. Yeah. They talk about that in the hollow earth as well.
The hollow earth also that we live inside of a hollow earth and we're actually concave,
not convex. And so I studied all that stuff. And the flat earth made a lot of sense when I
we live in a simulation made a lot of sense because someone saw an admin. I was getting
architectural magazines at the time and there was an ad in there for a while. There was a
big, big building boom in the 1980s and especially in Manhattan. And they were short on anyone and
anything in building trades. And they needed surveyors. And they say, you take this 10 day
course and you get twenty five bucks an hour. Now, twenty five bucks an hour in the eighties
is like seventy five bucks an hour now. Right. Maybe more. Right. So, yeah, I mean, you know,
anyway, yeah, like gasoline was barely a dollar and, you know, whatever, you know,
anybody who was alive then can vouch for him saying, I don't know the exact exchange,
but it's at least three to one. It could be as much as five to one now.
So anyway, I was like, oh, this sounds like fun. And I took the surveying course and we could not
plot a triangle on the earth if we got more than a quarter of a mile or a half a mile,
especially a mile apart. You could not make the three points close and have one hundred and eighty
degrees. Never. Which and we couldn't figure out why. Just because the earth is, you know,
got curvature. Right. But again, with the flat earth, I have seen that out on Blythe, which is
near the border of California and Arizona. I've personally witnessed someone who was a feed
feedstock farmer. He grew the stuff they feed animals with, right. All kinds of fine greens
and things like that. And he had quite a few acres and they have these ditches that irrigate
right in California. They're like part government and own part private owned rights. And these
ditches were they were so flat, but they had such a slight decline that you couldn't see the water
really moving. It was they looked completely flat. They only had like a one eighth of an inch every
20 feet. That's all they had to pitch. They had. And that went on for miles. So
only like several miles, even some of them were 10 miles long. It looked completely flat,
but the water flowed in one direction. Now, I'm wondering, is that flowing up the curvature or
down the curvature or are they taking account for the curvature? Because I remember surveying.
I couldn't we couldn't close the triangle because of it. Right. And he's like, oh,
doesn't matter. We do it like the earth is flat. And I'm like, oh, interesting. Now,
when you go to architecture and you're building and you're, let's say, floating a cement road,
concrete road, you float that thing only for water drainage. But otherwise you float it
dead level. You don't account for the curvature of the earth no matter how far you go.
And also you have something called a plumb bob, you know, vertical plumb when you're building a
skyscraper or whatever. And it's totally perpendicular to the level and there's
no accounting for the curvature of the earth either. So I was like, wait a second. With
certain things we can prove the earth is got curvature and other things we can prove the
earth is flat. So what's going on? Not until I started Greeks because like, wait a second,
you know, they have like the law of attraction, which is not true and all that stuff. But your
intent, you know, you can actually create your own reality, right? We do create our own reality. So
if you're working in the in your farmer, so an astronomer can prove to you that the earth is going
around the sun and the moon, right? And all this stuff go around the sun, all the plants go around
the sun. Yes. But if you're a farmer, you can prove that the sun goes around the earth. If
you're farming, right? Because you're on your land with all your crops and up comes the sun in the
east and it goes across the ecliptic more towards the north in the summer and more towards the south
in the winter. And the moon does the opposite. And that's it. And if you start if you're a farmer
and you start trying to make adjustments for the earth going around the sun, you're not going to do
very well. Right? So in some cases, you have some trades or activities that you're involved in,
you have to take an account for the earth being quote, unquote, a globe. And other things that
you want to get involved in, you must take account and rely that the earth is dead flat.
So which is it? Neither. It's what you intend to do. You take account for all the surrounding
energies and forces. That's why I guess it was good to start off with a sharp blade, wasn't it?
Yeah, it was. I mean, look, even a long range sniper has explained to me that he has to account
for the curvature of the earth, which is probably like a like a surveyor, because
surveyor, you're looking through what's called a theodolite. And, you know, that ray of light or
that amount of light is not point source, but it's enough to travel straight and discernance. Yeah.
Right. Depending on the sniper. Also, I think even more because snipers have callers. Also,
they have people with them that do wind speed and distance. Right. Yeah. Spotter. Now they're
a spotter. Yeah. And there are scopes that are that are complex enough to do that. But I don't
know a spotter. So they will give all those adjustments. They have a chart just like
a heavy artillery. Exactly. Exactly.