Sonic Event 145 of Rated Y. Greek, how's things?
Oh, things. What things?
No, I don't know. That's why I figured I'd ask you an open question. How's things?
Well, here's the thing. Before we got started, you were like, you know, I've got some questions.
Do you want me to talk? No, no, no. I work best cold. Just drop me in there.
And kind of like those commandos, you just drop them in a dark hole, you know, when they test you for special forces.
They used to. They drop you in a hole. It's black. And then, you know, you have to no warning.
Nothing. I'm fine with that. And also just want to preface for there's a bunch of new people.
And I'm getting responses and trying to respond as best I can in time.
I want to let people know what the purpose of doing this is initially.
Initially, it was just to get the word out because I found that locally in my environment, speaking to people,
they didn't know any of it and they didn't want to know any of it.
And I figured that, you know, years ago, you would do newsletters and may put ads and try to get an article written.
Now we have the Internet. Right. No more print. Right. It's going audio visual.
So I used to call in on radio starting 14 years ago, wherever I could.
People had questions. And I was kind of embarrassed and actually disgusted to call in and discuss these topics
because you hear like, for example, if you talk about the human body or economics or government or history,
the stuff that they're talking about is completely false. They had all these experts.
And I said, you know, this is all propaganda. You've got your guest right now is he's an idiot.
Basically, I didn't say that. But and this is where you should look and this is what you need to start with.
And that's basically my whole thing. I was kind of embarrassed to be saying things that I'm saying,
because the way I found them, they came very easy.
And I never tell people to go out and look for things that are hidden underneath a stone.
You know, in Tibet, it's always stuff that's right in front of you.
So I figured starting to do Sonics with you and others.
Sam, the Archon a while back was not to do like, what's his name?
Freeman called me the renegade journalist or something like that.
I was like, No, I'm not a journalist.
What I'm doing, what I'm doing is I'm trying to find other people to work with, not do Sonic events with.
I don't you know, I think by now, you know, we don't call them shows.
You can do shows, but I don't I don't do shows.
I do shows. I do Sonic events. I do a lot of things in the audio field.
I'm not you, but I mean, anybody else, they do shows, right?
I mean, I don't want to do a show of Sonic. I mean, it's because we don't do video.
So what I mean, I was looking, trying to find other people to do who are, let's say,
OK, let's be more specific in the research class, but not the way either a class of people, inventors.
I'm constantly making new devices, bringing them from another universe into this universe.
Right. Because they're not your ideas. You know what I mean?
Right. They're given to you. Right.
And just to progress human communication in general, because recently I've been speaking mostly about the meaning of life.
And I'm very happy to have discovered it for sure.
There are other meanings, but the main reason the meaning of it's having a discussion with someone in Romania recently as well.
It's a prison. I was like, no, it's not a prison. It's a university.
Oh, no, it's not a university. So what is it? It's an obstacle course.
You're here to have your time wasted. Not being here is a waste of time.
I think it is. But that's too much to bite off and chew.
But what the meaning of life here is for others to waste your time.
If you look at it, the level of inefficiency, lack of communication, the way things are, the deception.
Just look at it for what it is. It's wasting your time.
And that's what the meaning of this life is, whatever it is.
And here's the part. In the beginning, when you first find out you're here to have your time wasted by others.
I'm talking about others like your parents, your wife, your husband, your friends, coworkers, all the way up.
Everybody's wasting each other's time.
If you look at that as being the meaning itself, and there is no other life other than this, it's kind of scary.
So that, in fact, lends itself to that there is more than this.
It's not a school. It's not a prison. It's an obstacle course.
When you're at an obstacle course, what's the lesson?
There's no lesson. How is it a prison? It's not a prison.
You're performing whatever skills you have to negotiate the obstacle course.
That's all it is. There's nothing more.
Also, I've discussed it takes 50 to 100 years, really, to master a skill, any skill.
So how are you going to do that if you only live to 70, 80, 90? How?
You see, there's not enough time.
And this is by the way that skills…
You can become a master in 5 or 10 years, but not in this situation.
Not in this situation where everybody's wasting each other's time.
The main thing, if you really want to see this proved out,
look at how communication works between people you know.
The media, schools, wherever you get your information.
Look how inefficient it is. Look how unsubstantial it is.
I always give you an excuse.
People ask me, for example, what books should I read?
I say, read everything, everything, but you've got to know how to read it.
Yeah, everything. I've been getting a lot of those questions.
What should I read? Not everything. Why?
Well, you don't want to read everything because you want to read the stuff that matters.
That's good, right?
You want to eliminate your complete, absolute, pointless waste of time.
Yeah, well, they're still going to waste your time because humans aren't good at communicating.
But here's the point.
Let's say I give a recommendation and it's usually when I recommend stuff, no one's ever heard of it.
For the most part, yeah.
So let's say you do that.
You won't be able to communicate with other people,
but if you read the stuff that they read also and watch what they watch,
if it comes up in conversation, you see how well they organized it.
Did they get the wrong message?
Kind of like when I was in archaics with Jason talking about the Bible part.
I was like, there's no one on the Internet discussing what's in the Bible.
No one seemingly knows because there's like a billion copies of it.
No one knows what's in it.
What's going on is when you read the Bible, you've seen, oh, this is the scene we saw in the movie.
This is the part where this happened. Remember the movie? Yeah, yeah.
Okay, and you read it and you gloss over it and you're reading into it what you saw in the movie,
which is completely false.
It's not even in the pages at all.
Like the flood, for instance, is depicted in various ways.
But what does it actually tell you?
Not even the flood.
We're talking about simple stuff.
That's too big of a picture, let's say.
Too big of a flood, too.
Okay, so for example, are you thinking, when you read something, can you visualize it?
For example, the ark had one floor below and two floors above.
How many floors is that in total?
One floor below and two floors above.
If you count the floor, you're standing on four.
Sorry.
It's four.
It's four because you're standing on one.
There's one below you, that's two, and there's two above, it's four.
If you ask most people, they'll say three.
Oh, sorry.
So when you're reading this stuff, you have to...
Go ahead.
Oh, I was just saying, I observed four.
Because you have to be standing on one to have one below you.
Yeah, exactly.
Let me just explain.
But the thing is, when you get to certain things, they just gloss over.
And Jason says he read it 40 or 50 times, and he didn't know about the Ten Commandments.
He didn't know about this.
So it goes on not to harp on him at all.
I actually like what he's doing.
It's just a perfect example.
You could read it 100 times and not get it if you read it the same way every time.
For example, with myself in relationships, I've been around some unsavory people that initially looked unsavory,
that most people would not want to associate with,
that turned out to be some pretty decent people you want to know and have on your side, right?
But on the other hand, if you judge them initially, you wouldn't want to be with them, right?
You see what I mean?
So you have to do both.
You can judge a book by its cover,
but you have to be able to efficiently negotiate.
You know how they say you can't judge a book by its cover?
Bullshit. Bullshit.
The Yellow Pages.
You look at the Yellow Pages, you think it's a cookbook? Come on.
No, but you can identify something about what's in it based on the cover,
but not necessarily know all of what's in it.
Exactly. You get a pretty good idea by looking at it.
Okay. Fair enough.
So here's the point.
Communication is the problem.
The level of inefficiency.
When you have relationships with people,
there is a point where no matter how bad the relationship is,
there was some benefit to having that relationship.
And if it's possible to hold on to that,
you maintain the relation.
I'm not talking about husband and wife or anything.
I'm talking about acquaintances or whatever.
And people say, well, I was having a discussion with someone about this.
Yeah, well, I don't burn bridges.
And I said, well, it's not a matter of burning bridges.
You know what happens when a blowtorch meets a paper asshole?
You have no choice.
It's going to get burned.
So there's those kinds of levels.
So, yeah.
So the whole thing is, from a selfish point of view,
was to meet people that could work on the level that I like working on.
And at the same time, give back, give out what I've discovered.
Nothing that you have to go and do some crazy thing to find somewhere,
or trust me, trust me, trust me.
It's all stuff that is either happening around you within five feet or ten feet
or stuff you're dealing with.
So when we get into the legal stuff and the money stuff,
remember there's a commercial, What's in Your Wallet?
That's right there.
You need to know what, yeah.
All this stuff.
So, and still, I'm looking, I'm still looking.
But here's the, for whoever likes the Sonics,
if I met, let's say, one, two, or three, or four people,
even two people that I could work with on the level that I like to work on,
would I be doing Sonics?
No.
I wouldn't be doing it at all.
We would be working privately and developing things that I develop.
But eventually you'd want to reach out with it then
and implement these things, wouldn't you?
Yeah, well, right now we have the scalar, well, you mean the things,
the fruit of my work?
Yeah, the fruit of your work.
I've been like the Scalarator and the Aqueous Argentum
and now the Acoustic Counterspace.
Yeah.
These are remarkable things that simple people can grasp,
but if you take it to the university, they flip out, you know?
Of course.
So, yeah.
People ask me with the Acoustic Counterspace,
I want to mention something.
Someone did a video I mentioned, and he asked ChatGBT,
and he says, yeah, there's research being done on Acoustic Counterspace
and it seems to enhance the sound quality and lower distortion.
And the guy was impressed because I told him no one's doing it.
He says, well, ChatGBT knows about it.
I said, idiot, ChatGBT knows about it
because every time you write or say something,
the transcript is being made that gets fed to the AI.
Everything is.
So, especially when it's local.
Well, now if you make a YouTube video, it didn't used to be.
You used to have to create a transcript or whatever,
but no, that's now automatically generated
whether you have access to it or not,
and guess where it goes?
Into the grand Google database, which is a huge thing.
That's right.
So, yeah.
So, he asked.
Now, the thing is, if someone that's less local
asks about Acoustic Counterspace module,
they may not get a response because it's kind of localized.
So, in other words, I had about three or four conversations,
not lengthy, but half as long as these Sonics are about it,
and they were able to pull it up to ChatGBT,
and it's a magic trick kind of thing.
But the Scalarator is still,
people that are new don't know about it.
If you go away 10 pages back in the Chatango,
you'll see pictures of it.
Basically, it's a pipe that you run dirty water through
and clean water comes out the other side
if you have hard water.
All these, and no filtering, no whatever.
We're using things that are obvious that no one else has,
and the reasons are very sound once you, you know.
Anyway, so if people sense a sense of frustration that I have,
yes, I do, I'm very angstful
because there's never enough time in the day, right?
Never enough time to get stuff done.
Some things come immediately and are done immediately.
Other things are very slow and require assistance.
So I'm still looking for people that are inventor types
that know a little bit about everything
and a lot about a lot.
So catch up because the next major push,
someone had put a question in the Chatango,
what should we do now with what's going on with the war
and this and that.
Nothing, you just go ahead.
You should always, you have no wants, you have needs.
You should only want what you need, right?
So if you have a car, for example, keep it forever.
Doesn't matter if it's worth $500
and it costs $3,000 to fix the transmission.
Spend the $3,000 on the transmission, don't buy a new car.
When you have things that can be repaired,
even if it costs more than buying a new one, do it, right?
Do it, stop, get out of commerce, get out of marketing, right?
Imagine as if all the shops are closed
and you have to fend for yourself.
There's a lot of survivalist people.
You will not go into this mode for less than a decade still,
but if you, people prepare for survival, right?
The grid goes down, they live on the grid, right?
I said, well, what are you wondering about?
You're listening to all these bullshit ads,
buy this, buy that, no, no, no, no.
Go ahead, buy whatever they're, yeah, you know.
Don't let them sell you rice for $10 a pound, right?
Or, you know, a kilo of rice for 20 euro.
Don't do that, but be smart.
So if you want to know what happens when the grid goes down,
if you don't, if you have an apartment,
you probably could do it, but if you live in a house
or shared environment, go outside where the main,
the water main is, turn it off.
And where the power is, turn it off.
If you have gas coming to us, turn it off.
Turn off all the utilities to the house for three days,
for three days, and see how you do, right?
And then you'll know what happens when the shit hits the fan.
That's true.
Okay, but the thing that I like to embark in,
which is I've been speaking of for a while, is this.
When you live within an area, let's say,
even if you're not very social,
you know there's someone in your neighborhood or you're nearby
that, hey, this guy is good at cars.
If you have a car problem, go talk to him, right?
Or, this guy is good with air conditioners.
Or, this guy is good with, you know, plumbing, right?
This guy is good with plants, right?
You hear that, you know, people in the neighborhood, right?
And you have, like, someone who acts like the mayor.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, okay, you have that, but no one ever says,
this guy is good if you have a broken leg.
This guy is good if you have a bad cut.
This guy is if you're sick for your body.
Where does everyone still go for that?
To the accursed hospital, the accursed doctors.
Actually, the last neighborhood I lived in,
a lot of people were coming to me
because I had solved a few problems for people that were in distress
that I just ran into.
And I had solved a few of these problems.
Like, it was like a miracle.
I'm like, no, it's just common sense, a couple of things.
And the next thing I knew is people were knocking on my door
when somebody, you know, oh, my God, do I need stitches or what?
No, you don't.
Just relax.
What you need to do is put this back together,
compression, very basic, you know,
which I didn't learn from you, believe it or not,
but you reinforced what I had utilized in the past.
And it was just, to me, very common sense stuff.
And it's basic battlefield medic stuff.
It's not a, yeah.
Well, here's the thing.
It's the common sense thing.
Because I used to have a thing called uncommon radio, right?
Uncommon sense.
Right.
These things, people think that common sense is uncommon.
So how do you use everything that you have around you already?
Just like in nature when there's something that's toxic right next to it
is something that's the remedy for it.
So how do you use all the things that you have immediately around you?
I talk all the time.
Especially for fixing.
Poison ivy is a perfect example of this.
You remember the name of the plant, actually, that's a perfect remedy to it?
Yeah, I think it's a white oak bark, not the birch bark.
I think it's white oak.
Something like that.
It always grows around oak, yeah.
Within your line of sight, if you're standing on a patch of poison ivy,
you could, to a 360 turn, you'll find it in your line of sight.
Right, like a venomous animal or venomous insect,
it's the urine that's in the first 30 seconds to one minute.
Now, I'm not saying be a urine drinker because there was a fad for that a while back.
But the antidote is produced in the bladder.
Right.
And I brought this up with medical people,
and they were like, oh no, you can't do that.
The body produces the antidote, right?
For example, certain diseases, certain blood diseases,
they give a real simple example,
is if a healthy person who is processing everything
and eliminating and has proper nutrition
drinks their urine, they will get sick
because they're expelling the stuff the body needs to go out.
But if a sick person drinks their urine,
they're actually expelling the stuff that needs to be in their body,
and that could reverse it.
It's also the induction from it.
But that's more complicated because you have to know how to diagnose what the thing is.
But the thing to get heavily into is dentistry and trauma.
What do you do when someone gets hit by a car and is unconscious?
What do you do when someone's oral health goes down?
Exactly, proper care of a head injury, proper care of broken limbs or displaced limbs,
things like this is very important.
Now, I'm not good with the dentistry part,
but I just don't have that skill at the moment.
I mean, I have some basics on it, but it was something I could never do to myself.
Well, for now, okay, this is the thing before we even got to your questions yet,
but that is very, very important because, you know,
a lot of people got off on the spirit, the soul, and the body,
and you hear people that are seemingly fairly read in,
and they say, oh, I disagree, I disagree.
That is, it's a very difficult one because it was reversed during the Hellenic period, right?
Like, for example, they still say the ideal pneuma,
which literally means the set-apart or the non-earthly breath,
and the ideal pneuma is translated as the Holy Spirit in the Greek, and it's not.
Because here's the thing, there's no word holy in the Bible.
It's set-apart or non-earthly.
Everyone's spirit is not earthly, everyone.
So it can't be the spirit, even though we've taken it as being a,
a spirit is unique to each creature as a unique spirit.
Like, if you met a thousand demons, there are a thousand unique demons, right?
If you met a thousand cats, there are a thousand unique cats,
a thousand chickens, a thousand humans, right?
They're all unique, they're all set-apart from themselves.
So the Greek, the Christian thing that's called the Holy Spirit,
it's really the Holy Breath, and that's where the whole thing became confused
because all spirits are set-apart or holy, all of them.
Now, it's interesting, even if you read in the Piss 4 translations,
they're not unholy spirits, they're unclean spirits is the difference.
They're keeping the main translation, but they've confused everything.
Like, with the Christ, all they have to do is throw in the J-E-S-U-S
and throw in crucifixion, and the whole thing is screwed.
You'll never see what happens. There's no crucifixion at all.
So don't, when you fall for all that,
and people that seemingly are well-educated are the worst,
because they, you know, I've had several people say,
well, I disagree with your etymology, and I say, let's go with the etymology.
Perfect, because that's exactly where I was going to go.
The etymology shows it like black and white.
Now, there's no gray area at all, at all.
And see, because they've reversed it, they don't know what is,
when you hear Holy Spirit, all spirits are holy, all of them.
It's the breath that's set-apart.
So I just wanted to make this correction.
It has nothing to do, I'm not religious, by the way,
and I'm not into all that stuff at all.
I use it as my law, and I use it for timekeeping,
which is the same that everyone did.
For example, if you lived like they did in the Bible,
and you went back to China 2,000 years ago,
you'd be totally accepted, so you'd see exactly what you're talking about, right?
But now with all the divisions and all that,
it's a timepiece kind of thing.
But I'm not into that religious stuff at all,
because it's, you know, it's like politics, you know?
It's all bullshit.
But again, etymology is going to show it to you,
but when you have so many examples that are contradicting,
you can't look at the etymology, because it won't make any sense.
That's why I brought up, I just summed it up,
because I've gotten quite a few messages regarding the spirit,
and it's not really the wrestling with the difference between soul and spirit,
it's because they keep hearing that Holy Spirit thing.
The Holy Spirit is, everyone's got, everything has a Holy Spirit.
It's the breath that makes it different,
and that's what gave particular, you know, the metabolism also.
Well, the biggest problem here is not even the etymology versus,
it's the fact that that common usage, which is shown to you in the dictionary,
which the dictionary is supposed to teach you how to pronounce said word,
and they're only giving you the common usage
so that you know which word, so you can recognize it.
Well, you just, the word nice is very difficult to,
because it's been used so much, right?
The use of an opinion, opinion means, yeah, no knowledge.
Right. In its diction, though, it's very simple.
Nice is very simple in its diction.
Then they're showing you how it's used.
It's not a matter of what it means.
So that's always the problem.
Well, no, hold on, hold on.
It's not a problem if you understand what's going on,
and what's going on is when you have an enemy,
when you have an enemy, it takes a lot of resources to fight them,
because the thing is not to defeat them.
It's to keep them weak.
You ruin, you mess up their communications, their ability to communicate.
Now you have control over them.
Like, for example, recently I was looking again at the Lieber Code
and the things that came out.
I didn't know, by the way, in the U.S. the Treasury closed 12 years
between before 1933 and 1921 or so.
They had already shut it down and shipped all the gold out.
But all the U.S. citizens were declared enemies of Washington, D.C.,
you know, the United States.
And the interesting reason was because they're the closest, right?
They're the closest, so they'd have to be declared enemies first
versus, you know, someone outside,
because everyone is foreign to the United States, by the way.
You're either an alien resident or a non-alien resident.
You're all alien to it.
So there's a very interesting logic that they put together,
and if you brought that out to the public, they wouldn't understand a word of it,
even though it's in third-grade level because, again, of the usage
and what you're pointed to to look.
But anyway, my point, this seems like I feel like I'm ranting
because the sonics will go on as long as they do.
Who knows? We could end them in whatever.
It's just that I'm still hopeful to meet some people that are exceptional
in what they do and see if they could contribute to the topics
that we discuss here.
Mainly, it's the body.
Now, the thing is most people say health.
One thing I just want to interject, again, I keep telling people,
get that word out of your mind, health.
There is no health.
You have things that are healthful and things that are unhealthful,
healthy and unhealthy as such, and there is no health.
It's what fitness level you have, right?
So if you have someone who says,
I want to go climb Mount Everest, they're in good shape.
I want to go climb Mount Everest in a month or let's say in a week.
They won't make it.
They'll get high-altitude disease and they may not make it.
You have to train for that.
If someone says, I'm going to sit in an office for eight hours a day,
they're probably okay to do that, and their fitness will,
if you're active and you go and do an office job for eight hours a day,
five days a week or six days a week, let's say,
your fitness level will decline, right?
So it's all fitness.
Now let's say you have a malady like a brain injury or not an injury,
like a tumor in your head or a heart attack or something like that.
Yes, that's fitness level again.
That's fitness level.
It's a level of fitness that you have,
and these things are known very well in certain circles,
and they're not discussed publicly.
Publicly they tell you you have health care.
You cannot care for your health.
You must decide what level of fitness you want to operate on,
and when your body makes it so,
let's say you have a brain tumor the size of a grapefruit in your head,
your fitness level is the first thing that you're going to notice
that's going to direct you to have that examined, right?
Yes, of course.
Your fitness level, you'll probably be dizzy or whatever.
So all of these things are fitness levels.
There is no health.
So I've been getting questions about health and things like that,
and it's really difficult.
It's worse than the soul and spirit
because the thing is when someone brings up something
regarding their quote-unquote health,
I'm using the common term here,
it's like what fitness level?
In other words, let's say you're diagnosed with all these diseases, right?
Most of them are fictional, by the way.
They're all blood quality issues.
Most of them are blood quality issues,
and they're diverted into being called this, that, or that,
blaming an organ on it or something like that.
They're blood quality issues, I would say.
So what do you know about blood quality?
And the other thing is the reason you probably went
and got diagnosed with that stuff
is because your fitness level was not up to the par that you wanted, right?
Meaning if you feel pretty good,
and then suddenly you don't feel pretty good, you're just fair,
that's not your health.
That's your level of fitness that has changed.
Yeah?
Okay, so once you start looking at it that way,
you'll be able to do...
Okay, if you don't understand that,
you will not be able to diagnose.
Diagnose means like, hey, what's wrong with me?
And look at someone.
If you think there's health, you won't be able to...
That's why these doctors and medical technicians,
they can't diagnose anything
because they don't know what's going on.
I'll give you an example.
When I was in the athletic circles and bicycle racing,
and someone's fitness level was not well,
and this happened all the time,
they would go to a general practitioner,
and I would laugh at them.
I would laugh at them.
People would laugh at them also.
I said, these general practitioners are looking at people
that are of a very low fitness level or very old and sedentary,
and they're basically just bad examples of what a human should be.
You're going to go in there.
You're over 500 times more fit than anyone they've seen in 10 years.
They're going to say, you're fine, right?
They're going to say, you have to go to a sports doctor, right?
That's why the majority of them...
An athlete has to go to a sports doctor,
and everyone should be on that level.
Yeah, well, the majority of people that really are seeking a solution
can find it by dietary adjustment, really.
Well, no, okay, well, it's not even that
because we've gotten into that, the dietary adjustment.
You must understand the energy of it.
That's why if you look at 99% of the people that are vegetarian or vegan look sick
because they don't understand.
They just think taking meat out of the diet
and then eating whatever else is not meat is good,
and they don't understand the energy system.
Right, that's a poor idea there
because they're usually overloaded with something
that's producing this one thing over and over again.
The body doesn't need just one thing.
Yeah, and it's part of the propaganda system.
You see how they're marketed.
We've gone into earlier Sonics,
and I think it's not the teens, maybe the 50s, 60s, and 80s.
Those Sonics, I might even have to do a little bit more.
The energy of the food, you know,
think of it this way, like fruit.
Okay, let's look at fruit.
Oranges, apples, pears, cherries, right?
Think of it this way.
The Westerners will have you do how much sugar.
No one knows what's in fruit, by the way.
When they tell you there's vitamin C,
no one knows what's in it
because the way they find out what's in it
is by crushing it, blending it, and burning it,
and then measuring what's left.
Well, burning is literally the main point of reference
because people talk, and I explained this to someone recently,
the calories thing.
Well, what is a calorie?
It has nothing to do with the body.
And they have people walking around saying,
I'm burning calories.
Does your body have a furnace?
This was my question to the small audience.
Are you able to burn anything inside of your body?
Think about it.
Well, yeah, but that's again like the Holy Spirit
and like an ice, and it's a conditioning.
They've been soaked.
But again, remember, we're here to have our time wasted, right?
Right, but I'm trying to eliminate that by saying,
listen, just think for a moment.
Do you burn?
Just use that one point of view.
Is there burning going on?
Yeah, but it's more than that.
Wait until they've...
I think we've gotten into diabetes and AIDS.
Those are completely fictional, do not exist,
and blood pressure does not exist,
and they're killing like 5 million people a year
with treating them with these things that don't exist.
I'm not you, so I'm trying to start with the most basic thing,
which is, can you identify where you're burning anything?
Yeah, go ahead.
Yeah, let's go back to the fruit of this.
So you're going to say, oh, fruit is this.
It has antioxidants.
Bullshit.
All that's bullshit.
Okay, so let's look at the fruit from an energetic perspective,
purely oranges, apples, pears, cherries, apricots, whatever.
Okay, let's look at it.
It comes off the tree.
The tree is rooted in the ground, and it grows on a trunk.
It could be a shrub, and it goes up into the air.
It keeps growing, and then it blossoms, right?
It blossoms, and then the fruit grows out of the blossom.
And remember, everything is going up, up, up, up, up.
And when a fruit grows, it's all going down, down, down, down now, right?
Remember, if you leave the fruit on the plant,
if you leave the fruit on the plant and it falls off,
does it fall up or does it fall down towards the ground again?
It reaches up first, then the energy starts going downward.
Right, so when you're eating fruit,
you're eating something at its terminal point where it's on its direction down.
That's the way, for example, it's on its way back to Earth, down.
So what is it going to do to your body?
Your body will not get any uplifting.
It'll get an immediate uplifting energy because remember,
the fruit was still attached on one end,
but the other end, the majority of the mass, is going to bring you down.
Right, but when it gets into the body,
because of the quality that brings it down,
the energy is going to run to the top of your head
because that's the part that represents the yang or the contracted part.
Now this sounds complicated, but let's say we did a sonic
and gave 10 different examples like this, like with meat.
Forget about protein and blood and animal and all that.
What is it doing? What have you got there?
For example, here I'll leave off and we'll get to the questions.
Let's say you're cooking a steak.
We'll get specific because I've measured this.
You're cooking a steak on a grill, let's be specific, a charcoal grill,
let's say a mesquite grill,
and you measure the steak with a thermometer down to like a tenth of a degree.
So you measure the steak, and when it gets to about 130 degrees,
you want it rare, let's say.
You flip it, and it's still 130 degrees on the grill, still, right?
You shoot the laser right on the meat, not on the fire.
132 degrees, 133, it's going up, so we better take it off, right?
So it stabilizes at 132, remember that number.
I put it on the plate, off the grill, and I keep measuring it.
It's off the grill now, and suddenly it's 132.5, 133, 133.5.
What they say is it continues cooking.
No, no, no, no, see again.
No, the temperature is actually going up,
even though it's out of the heat source, on its own.
But I said that's what they say, it continues cooking.
Yeah, but hold on.
If you listen to what I said carefully, while it was on the grill,
you're measuring 130, 132, it's pretty stable on the grill.
The moment you take it off the grill, it goes up one or two degrees immediately.
Now, why does that happen?
This is the energy part, and if there's other ways of measuring,
we've gone into temperature also.
Do we base all of our temperature basically on mercury?
There were like four different temperature scales,
and now we've settled down to, well, there's more like eight of them,
but Celsius and Fahrenheit, but it's based on mercury.
So here's the energy part.
Well, mercury, first of all, it's a toxic metal in certain ways.
People don't know this, but if you had a stomach ailment 150 years ago,
you drank a quarter cup of mercury.
Are you familiar with this?
Yeah, I've heard of this, yeah.
Yeah, but it is an interesting metal, but here's the thing.
I've never done it, but I've heard of it.
Here's the energy part again, and this confounds people,
because this is all about once you understand these energy matters,
you'll see how all this has been brought,
how much more with this type of thinking you can get out of any situation.
So let's say the mercury says it's 72 degrees Fahrenheit.
And I'm at sea level.
I'm at sea level.
I can pretty much be outside in a single-layer long-sleeve shirt,
very comfortable, very comfortable, right?
Okay, it's 72 degrees.
We go to a place like Death Valley, still 72 degrees,
which is below sea level a few hundred feet.
Now you feel like you're a little warm in the same shirt,
same temperature, same exact temperature.
Right.
Okay, now we go up near a high altitude, near a mountain,
and what's the temperature?
Oh, 72.
Yeah, but you're going to start to feel cold.
But now you feel cooler.
Yeah.
Now you feel cooler.
Okay, but wait a second.
Three different altitudes gave us three different feelings
with the same temperature of mercury,
so there's got to be a better way to measure temperature.
And it's not just altitude-based,
but you see the altitude also adds a component,
which is, by the way, you use the barometric pressure in a lot of things,
but, again, they brush it under the rug.
We're talking about the way we feel.
This is all part of the way you diagnose things.
Now let's jump to something that's more complicated.
The yin and yang thing.
Barometric pressure is a significant measurement
that can be utilized for good purpose, though, right?
Yeah, yeah, but I'm showing you how that relates to temperature.
Okay, good.
Very much, right?
But, again, who says barometric pressure?
Again, that's another column of mercury again, right?
True.
So let's just jump to what remedies you can do.
Let's say earlier I spoke about a tumor in the brain, right?
Right.
And I'm not going to mention names, Gilder, Radner, but anyway,
that kind of situation, a tumor in the brain,
the top of the head is the most yang, most contractive part of the body.
So anything that goes to the brain has to be very yin to balance out, right?
So because, you know, hot and cold, let's say, yin and yang,
the yin rushes towards the yang.
So if someone has a brain tumor or a brain condition
that can be seen on a CAT scan or something like that or an X-ray,
that is an extreme yang in the body that has rushed to extreme yin energy
from chemical or environment or even thinking
that has drawn and created that situation
and collected itself in the most yang contractive part of the body.
So in order to get, if it got there quickly,
which very often there's people that get these tumors can develop overnight,
by the way, what would be a remedy for that?
Well, you want to find, since it's the yin that ran to the most yang part of the body,
you want to put something in the body that is so yang, so yang,
that it will see this extreme yin concentration and balance it out
and make it smaller, make the tumor smaller immediately almost.
So what do you do for that?
Well, one of the most yin conditions known is radiation, right?
And cockroaches can take the most radiation.
That means they're very, very yang.
One of the most yang creatures or yang things you can take,
which I don't recommend, this is not a dietary thing
because the law that I live by, I wouldn't eat that insect anyway,
would be an animal, a cockroach is the most yang animal
because any other creature you bombard with radiation will die
while the cockroach will not.
But we want to make the cockroach even more yang,
so we broil it until it carbonizes into black powder,
not burn it into ash, but until it turns into a piece of carbon.
Poor roaches, right?
And then you take that and you put it in a capsule
and you take three of those in the morning,
three of those in noon, and three at night.
And within a few days, that tumor seems to have almost disappeared.
This is a purely energy thing.
Now, this is extreme.
What I just gave is like an example of the most advanced course
you can take in macrobiotic remedies, for example.
Actually, what I just mentioned,
you can go to people that are healers
that understand the Taoist philosophy and the Taoist medicine
and they would freak out if you told them that.
Who told you that?
That's like within their innermost circles, right?
And if you don't believe that, go research Taoist medicine online.
It's all fluff and bullshit.
So once you understand the energy of these things,
you can make remedies and combinations.
An example would be when you look at these Chinese medicinal shops.
You go in, they have herbs in containers,
and they see you, they do a diagnosis, they ask you some questions,
and then they walk around and they open jars and things
and throw stuff in a bag and tell you to boil this and drink it.
That is a completely... I mean, that's the right idea.
That's the right idea, but what they're doing
is just taking advantage of people that are ignorant.
It doesn't work that way.
Putting all these things in there.
Some people are helped, of course, because it's a change in their pattern, right?
Let's say, yeah.
So I'm still asking for help.
Another way to call yin and yang, something else,
because now it sounds like I'm doing a modified...
speaking about modified Asian philosophy
or modifying Asian techniques when you say yin and yang.
So if anyone out there has any more suggestions
where, you know, one would be dispersive, yin,
and one would be contractive, right? Yang.
If there's another way to discuss this, another way completely,
because I don't want to sound like I'm a proponent of a modified Asian philosophy,
but right now it seems to be the best.
For example, if we're speaking about geometry,
are we always stuck with Pythagoras?
You could be. You could be.
Okay, so that's my rant for tonight.
Do you want to throw some questions or do you want to do it another time?
I think we should save them up for Saturday
because you actually answered a bunch from one set of questions anyway
without knowing it.
Okay, good.
There you go.