Rated Y, Sonic Event 205 I think it
is now.
Anyway, here we are.
Greek, how are you?
Cool.
I'm me, I guess.
Doing it.
You're you.
Yeah.
I got a lot of, this is gonna,
anyone who's been listening to me for a
while is gonna feel like I went back
like 15 years or 10 years after today,
back to the more of the, let's say,
aggressive way I talked about certain things.
But yeah, got any questions for tonight or
anything?
I mean, there's tons of stuff going on
we could talk about, but go ahead.
Sure, I do.
We're going back to the dummy load tonight,
though.
Sort of.
You're gonna see, we'll get a feeling for
it, yeah.
If you don't know what the dummy load
is, then you did not obviously listen to
the ones that I have opened up for
free at ocelli.com.
The Ocelli in the Greek series is all
up there from the AFR days.
Anyways.
Getting dummy loaded.
Yeah, that's basically what you're gonna get here
on this planet.
Just saying.
I've got such a habit, when I talk,
I meet people, you know, when I'm out.
I'm actually more active than I've ever been
because of the lab project and stuff.
And I start talking to people and they
kind of, I can see they're in between.
And before I really lose them, I say,
have you been on this planet for more
than a month?
And they're like, what kind of question is
that?
I said, did you ever get to ask
that before?
Well, you were the first person to ask
me that, but that doesn't necessarily mean anything.
Yeah, so you got to know these things.
Why are you asking me that?
Because it seems like you don't know a
lot about being here.
Objectively.
Anyway, you know, related to that almost, and
I know we've covered this before, but it's
been so long, I don't remember.
Many people talk about childhood trauma, but what
are the Greeks' thoughts on that?
How to break a pattern that's been a
person with a person since the earliest days.
There had been a lot of talk about
the voices in the head.
Do trickster entities have a tendency to attach
themselves to a person during a moment of
intense shock?
Okay, so there's two good questions there.
You got it.
Okay.
I'm going to answer it indirectly, but it's
the same thing, right?
Okay.
It's like if I have a cut on
my hand from a kitchen knife or a
chain link fence or a plastic knife, it's
a cut.
So we deal with it the same way,
right?
So you're dealing with past something that might
have traumatized you.
So what I would say there is everything
is stored in a visual sense in our
brains.
So get a visual and an emotional feeling
of what was bothering you as a child
and then freeze frame it, stop it, make
a thumbnail of it, a picture that represents
it, and then expand that until it gets
bigger and bigger and bigger, literally fills the
room, bigger than a billboard, the biggest billboard
you've ever seen, bigger than that big sphere
they have in Las Vegas, so big that
it fills the entire sky, that image, that
same image I'm talking about still, so big
that it's bigger than the sky, that's bigger
than the earth, bigger than the universe, and
then stop it, and then shrink it, make
it smaller and smaller and smaller until it
comes down to billboard size, it's in your
room, now it's so small, it's in the
palm of your hand, that same image, so
small it becomes a grain of sand, keep
making it smaller and smaller and smaller to
infinity, and you're done.
And that's it, that's what your brain needs,
because what happens if you retain these photographic,
let's say, or images of trauma or memory,
all your memory is imagery, even people who
have never seen anything have images, but they're
colors and swirls, even people born blind, they
still have images and it's based on emotion,
just like a lot of savants, when they
do these 56,433 divided by 22,160
and they give you the answer right away,
you're like, well, how'd you do that?
So all those numbers become colors, right?
So anyway, what I'm trying to say with
this is, you can play back what I
just said, there's a guy, John Mace, who
came up with that, and I've been talking
about something similar, when I heard his testimony
about how to handle these quote-unquote psychological
traumas, I was like, oh, that's basically what
I'm talking about, but he narrows it down
to everything being visual, which is mostly correct,
so I agree with him and give him
credit on that.
And here's the thing about the psychology, just
like the Catholic Church, by the way, years
ago they would have, 500 years ago in
Europe, there was this evolving medical industry for
surgery, so they needed people to practice on,
so the priests, they went out and collected
confessions, and then a week later the priests
became sheriffs and arrested the people for their
confessions and handed them over to the doctors
to experiment on in prison.
So this is what the psychologists are doing,
you ever hear them say, if you say
something, I have to report it, if it's
illegal, or whatever?
Scumbags, they're all scumbags, the psychologists, psychiatrists, stay
away, I just gave you the thing that
they will never know and never figure out,
not that I'm saying it's illegal, but I'm
just saying, what they make you do is
share, and it's idiots too, you hear idiots
probably in your family, or friends, or on
TV, they say, oh, you know, if you
share it, if you talk about it, then
you can work it through, no, with this
method, I could do therapy with someone, and
I don't want to know what the trauma
is, it doesn't matter if you were butt
-fucked 670 times in a day when you
were 4 years old, it doesn't matter, I
don't need to know, no one needs to
know, but you need to be able to
recall the feeling and the image, that's the
pitfall of modern psychology, and people say it,
they say, why don't you talk about it?
One thing about this, I got a question
from me now, about the blind people and
how it is you know that, because quite
honestly, the only reason why I know you're
correct, is because I spent a lot of
time talking to completely blind people, because I
was close to blind, and went to blind
camp, so I spent time with those kids,
and I used to ask them questions like,
how do you picture these things?
And it took a little while, but I
understood it, and you're essentially right, but it's
about a personal image, not necessarily the image
itself, that's why you don't have to share
it, because you could spend 100 years, or
let's say 10 hours trying to explain the
image to work it through, it doesn't matter,
it's what's already in your head, and here's
the thing, if you don't work out these
young personal traumas, or even recent traumas, what
happens is, when it's stored in the brain,
it's stored in where it's stored, not in
the brain, right?
In you, let's say, in your essence, you
start changing the way your identity is, your
personality, to accommodate that trauma, so most people's
persona is based on traumas that they haven't
dealt with, that they're accommodating through the changing
of their character, how many times have you
met someone, I haven't seen Jim in a
long time, how's Jim doing?
I haven't seen him in years, but I
ran into him the other day, he's changed,
how many times have you heard that, right?
Yeah, people run into me after 10 years,
man, you're saying the same stuff, you haven't
changed a bit, I'm like, well, thank you,
whatever, but you have to work these things
out, and they're personal, and here's, it's the
opposite of what everyone's been taught, you know,
that therapy, that Freudian, the couch, I call
it, just call it the couch, it means,
says everything, you sit down, you tell the
psychiatrist everything, or psychologist, right?
And it's so funny when you call a
psychologist a psychiatrist, and a psychiatrist a psychologist,
how they get insulted both ways, and that's
so funny, and they're both morons, they don't
even know it, right?
Right, one's got a prescription pen, the other
one doesn't, but outside of that, who cares,
you know, it's the same crap.
I want to get into the moronic medical,
it's getting to the point where there are
no exceptions in the medical industry, they're all
morons, I haven't, actually there are exceptions, but
they've run away, completely, I mean, like, they
quit and run away, and I've lost touch,
let's say, but before I do that, before
you go to another question, I brought up,
Brandon...
You're a psychologist or a psychiatrist, though, it's
absolutely based on bullshit, there's absolutely nothing to
it.
Neurosurgeons are based on bullshit, okay, brain surgeons
are based on bullshit, but...
But it's at least based on something, it's
psychology, psychiatrist, psychiatrist, garbage.
I want to bring up another article, too,
a woman who had sex with 500 men
in one day, and they said, what are
the physical things, it just popped up in
the, I look at what really happened, they
put that in there, and it's all, they
said, she has all these chemical imbalances in
the list of all these hormones and things,
and I'm like, bullshit, no one knows, how
did they know those hormones even exist in
the body?
They took a blood sample, they centrifuged the
blood sample, then they isolated what they centrifuged,
then they combined it with other chemicals to
see what reactions would take place, then they
go to a chart and say, because we
put hydrogen peroxide in there, and this much
carbon dioxide came off, that means that there's
this much of this, bullshit, no one knows
what's in your cells, chemically, because actually, to
find out what's in the cell, chemically, you're
actually changing it.
So that's all right, let them categorize, this
is the danger of it, so that you
have too much of this moronic fluid in
your cell, and the way we get rid
of it is by adding this other chemical
that will inhibit it, it's called an inhibitor,
right?
Bullshit, bullshit, and the side effects are far
worse than, it's all bullshit, and it's all
a prank.
There are very few people on this planet
that have ever known what's going on, and
it still is that way.
So, before I get in, I think I
harped enough on the medical people, but this
is, I have to commend, this is Brandon
Joe Williams, I'll play it through my speaker,
I should say, it's called the Sovereignist Citizen
of Land, it's a live Austin meeting, or
somewhere like that, on the end of April,
this is day one, and he gets up
in the middle, because everyone's talking about it,
I took this to an attorney, he told
me this, bullshit, I called a banker, he
said this, bullshit, right, and this is like,
after about maybe half a dozen people giving
testimony, Brandon Joe Williams stands up and starts
saying this, it's just about a minute or
two.
Things from all sorts of different people, there's
banks, there's banks that, it says pending, and
they're like, pending the loan, and it just
sits there, and they call in, nobody knows,
everyone's confused, nobody has a fucking clue, everybody's
running around with their heads chopped off, you
go on the DMV, none of them have
any fucking clue, everyone's lost their fucking mind,
we don't know, I have no idea, there's
so much craziness, and so many people, and
so many things, for all I know, they
just say fuck this, everyone says fuck this,
they jam it in a drawer, and that's
the end of it, and nobody ever sees
it again, I'm not even kidding, and you're
just driving around, and it's just never gonna
get processed, I mean, that's just, everyone sees
it, and they go, fuck, you gonna do
this, fuck, I don't even know what the
fuck this is, the guy says he's an
attorney, in fact, oh, don't call that guy,
you know what I mean, you don't know,
you know, so the thing is, is there's
just so much craziness with this, and these
guys have never ever seen anyone do this,
and they're all stupid as fuck, so I've
talked to bankers with like 30, 35 years
of experience, hey, I have a question for
you, what's a negotiable instrument?
Oh, yeah, I heard about that before, oh,
yeah, is that, that's like a security, that's
a security, right, it's like, motherfucker, you've been
working for the bank for 30 fucking years,
makes me wanna just take like a claw
hammer to the fucking face, you know what
I mean, so I don't wanna get too
many peppered different questions, where it's like, well,
this and that and this and that, yeah,
we're gonna keep seeing a lot of that,
there's gonna be a lot of fucking weirdness,
a lot of chaos, you're gonna see shit,
whether you just stick it in a drawer,
and nobody can ever find it again, well,
fuck it, drive the car around, till someone
cleans out the drawer in fucking seven years,
or something, I don't know, I mean, that's,
you know, that's basically it right there.
So my...
Yeah, so he's getting it, he's getting it
finally, in other words, when you start listening
to Brandon Joe Williams, he's like, yeah, just
tell him this, this negotiable instruments, this, this,
that, go to, yeah, they know what this,
and he finally, finally after a couple years
doing this, he says no one knows shit,
attorneys don't know anything, bankers don't know anything.
So what's going on with all these professionals,
doctors, lawyers, attorneys, is they show up at
a college, and they go work wherever they
do, and they give them this giant box
with square pegs, and they tell them, you
see all these square holes, all these square
pegs, go into all these square holes, and
this is what you're gonna be doing for
the rest of your life.
That's the mental challenge they have.
And then like, someday, a round peg shows
up, oh no, oh no, right, or they
get a round hole, oh no, oh no,
these are the professionals.
When I'm talking about the normies, the normies,
the non-professional people, don't even exist in
my book, they're the space eaters, they take
up space and give off heat.
When I say the people are dumb, I'm
talking about your priests, your rabbis, your doctors,
your lawyers, your accountants, your judges, your prime
ministers, you know, the professional classes, that's what
your society is made of.
In other words, when the alien saucer lands
on the front lawn and they come out
since the 50s, what do the aliens always
say?
Take me to your leader.
Yeah, so who are you?
You don't care.
Take me to your leader.
So that's what I'm talking about, I'm talking
about your leaders.
Your leaders are not necessarily the politicians.
It's what category, when you say leader, what
are you talking about?
Dentistry, that's your dentist.
You're talking about physical health and fitness, that
would be a medical doctor.
You're talking about law, your leader would be
your attorney or lawyer.
For spirituality, it would be your priest.
You see, I'm kind of spreading it out,
right?
Because even if you went to the quote
-unquote president, any questions regarding spirituality, he would
go where?
He would go to the priest.
Any medical question from the alien, where does
the president go?
Bring in a doctor.
Yeah, see, so when I say leaders, it's
subject sensitive.
So I've been saying, anyone who's been listening
for a while, I've been very adamant about
how moronic people are.
I think when you and I got together,
it's been over 10 years now, I haven't
changed a bit.
It's gotten not worse, it's the same, which
makes it worse, right?
Which makes it worse, but the newer, and
I see the newer people come on the
scene on the Internet.
So here's another way to put it.
You can go to YouTube University and research
like bills of exchange to go what is
money, negotiable instruments, law, or even medicine.
And some young podcaster who's been doing this
for six months knows more about that field
than any attorney or any accountant or any
doctor on anything, right?
You wouldn't believe how many times I've been
brought into a Skype call, podcast, whatever, private
call actually, not a podcast, with an alternative
medicine doctor.
And the person was like, you've got to
speak to the Greek.
And I get on, they introduce themselves.
And they say, yeah, tell them about that
thing you have that you said reduces blood
pressure naturally.
And I let them talk and talk, and
I said, okay, I explained how blood pressure
is a fiction, and they get it.
And the first thing they say, but I've
been practicing medicine for 35 years.
What?
I don't care if you've been practicing for
3,500 years.
You're a moron, right?
And this always, whenever I'm brought to a
medical person, it always works that way.
I've met with medical people here in Tucson.
And after a while, it's like, do I
really want to, like, nail them and floor
them, or I just want to, like, be
cordial and change the subject and, you know,
but let them know they don't know, but
it's unspoken, right, the unspoken stuff.
And that's what I prefer to do lately
because if you traumatize them, then any bullshit
care they're giving their patients, this is all
bullshit, the best care you're going to get
from a medical person is when they tell
you what?
Go home and rest, right?
So why don't you just do that anyway,
right?
So anyway.
The only exception there that I've always said
is that it's like the battlefield medic sort
of stuff.
Absolutely.
You got an iron bar sticking out of
your neck.
Yeah.
Right?
They have the tools and some knowledge, some
knowledge to get it out, right?
Anyone in ER, they sit there with a
wound for hours and hours.
That needs to be treated within the first
three to five minutes for it to heal
immediately, right?
Three to five hours, you're talking weeks and
months for it to heal, right?
Because now the body's facilitated.
It is possible.
It is possible to, like, you know how
fast they can scoop someone off, a paramedic
can scoop someone off the street.
They can apply all of the treatment necessary
right in transport or immediately.
And if you know any paramedics, they hate
the doctors, and the paramedics call the paramedics,
the doctors call the paramedics taxi drivers, right?
They don't like each other, by the way.
Paramedics and hospital people don't like each other.
Conflict, because I'll tell you why.
A lot of times paramedics bring someone, and
they're almost ambulatory, they're fine, and then they
find out the person died when they went
to the hospital.
Like, how could he have died?
Right.
I mean, he was doing fine, right?
And then you have other things where the
person is barely alive, and the paramedics do
the right thing, and then they're fine when
they get to the doctors, and everyone credits
the doctors, but it was really the paramedics
that saved his life or her life.
You see?
So there's confusion.
There's no one knows what's going on.
And this is, we went over the last
slide.
It's a testament to the robustness of the
human condition.
I'm using that word however you want to
take it.
You know, the man's condition.
We are very, very robust creatures.
And to hearken back to what Charles Fort
said, we are owned.
We are on a farm.
Somebody owns us.
We don't have real, let's say, politics.
We don't have real governments.
We don't have real medicine.
We don't have real religion, let's say.
We don't have real science.
It's all fake.
And it's all fake for the same reason
that, let's say, you want an aquarium in
your living room.
You go out.
You buy the tank, and you put the
water in there.
Let it sit for a few days.
Check the pH.
Check the ammonia level.
Then you put the fish in.
And then you put like this fake rocks
and fake scenery on the back of the
aquarium.
And then you're like, hmm, I think I
want to change the scenery now.
We're going to go from medieval to pre
-industrial.
How's that?
And boom, you put the fake rock, the
fake thing, right?
It's all fake.
All fake.
There's no continuation of anything.
It's all fake because we're owned.
And what happens when you're tired of those
fish and you can't take them where you're
going to next year?
Flush them down the toilet, right?
That was the thing to do, right?
So, yeah.
So that's why you're getting flushed down the
toilet one at a time here.
However, that's how you're treated.
Oh, my gosh.
Yeah.
So I'm not going to get into a
rant, but I could substantiate anyone who's listening
that's got two brain cells to rub together
and a third brain cell as a spare
gets what I'm saying, hopefully.
And if you've been on this planet for
more than 30 days, you should know what
I'm saying.
So the thing about this, I brought it
up again because there's a lot of seriousness
about people talking, oh, the medical industry is
a scam.
You hear that more now than ever before.
Like people from all walks of life, right?
Not just the disadvantaged or disprivileged, like insurance.
We're talking about everyone.
Everyone's saying the government's a scam.
Everyone's saying the money system's a scam.
Everyone's saying, ah, okay.
So where have you been for the last
4,500 years or the last 90 years?
Because we have a new form of country
here.
People don't know that in 1933, there was
a major revolution on paper and the republic
became a democracy.
But anyway, which is no different.
It would have been better if like the
Red Army came over here and took over
because then it would be, you don't have
to read to know that, right?
But to know that you lost your country
and you volunteered into it means you have
to read.
So people will never find out that happened.
But if the Red Army came over here
and took over, you would know that because
it would be, you don't have to read
to know that because it's in your street,
it's in your face, right?
So why does it have to be in
your face like that for it to happen?
It doesn't.
It can happen on paper.
It can happen in all of your codes,
laws and regulations and behaviors, right?
All the banking that's being done, all the
police, the medical, all that stuff is what
an enemy occupier does.
Everything the doctors are doing, the police are
doing, the government is doing, the banks are
doing, the accountants are doing is what an
enemy occupying force would do to your people.
And you love it.
You actually tell your children to go and
join those professions.
With an enemy occupying force, though, you don't
have the same consent, right?
You have the possibility of resistance.
You have the resistance, and the resistance here
is called the alternative movement, which is not.
It's not alternative at all.
When you go to alternative movement, they don't
know how the body works.
So what the hell are you talking about?
It's not an alternative, but that's the thing.
They have zero knowledge of how the body
works.
All they know is that, guess what?
You get a cut, you better stop the
bleeding.
And how do we do that?
We sit on the motherfucker's arm, right?
Yeah, put pressure on it.
Wrap it up.
But they don't know how to do that.
They can't optimize it.
There are some optimizations going on, and I'm
not going to take credit for it because
I've been talking about this for a long
time.
But the more I look on optimizing wounds,
and so I start seeing methods, things that
I've talked about that rely on the biological
vacuum in the body.
But they will never say that we're under
a vacuum.
They can't.
And they don't know it either.
And they will never say the heart is
not a pump.
There's more and more people, but they're still
bullshit.
They don't know what moves.
So it would be quite interesting.
In the financial one, there's a lot of
people coming out saying, this is how it
works.
These are negotiable instruments.
This is how you signature.
This is how it goes to the Federal
Reserve, the application.
They get the full amount.
Then you sign a promissory note.
They get paid again.
And you might have signed a contract.
And then you make payments, and you pay
again.
And then those interest payments make it as
if you paid twice, and then you pay
again.
So now you've paid five times for the
car over on paper.
Right.
And five times you've paid for it already.
We're not talking about the car's been paid
for.
We're not talking about through your income through
labor.
We're talking about on the books.
So when you apply for a car loan,
the car is fully paid for.
And then you do a contract.
The car is fully paid for again.
Right.
And then you get the car.
You make payments with interest.
The car is paid for again with the
principal, and the interest sometimes doubles.
Paid for again.
So four or five times you've paid for
it on paper.
And I'm not talking about going working and
taking part of your check.
I'm talking about on paper the car has
been paid.
The house has been paid.
So people who say I paid off my
car, I paid off my house, have paid
for it four times at least already.
Maybe five.
In some cases, it could be as much
as ten times.
Because they'll tell you you apply, and they
deny you it's been paid for.
And then a month later, they say, why
don't you come in and apply again?
They deny you again.
They call you a month later.
Come in and apply again.
Every application pays for the entire amount.
Right.
Yeah.
This is what's going on.
So there's plenty of stuff on that on
the Internet.
Actually, yeah, there is.
But there's nothing on the human body.
Nothing.
Zero.
Do we want to be the first ones
to do it?
Do we want to trailblaze that?
Anybody want to invest in that?
I don't want to do it alone.
No, I'd love to see it done, but
I don't.
It needs to be done.
You know, here's the thing.
I'm a cancer survivor, dickhead.
If you didn't get cancer, you would have
died in your sleep.
You ever heard that?
We've got to fight cancer, cure cancer.
Okay.
So if you cure cancer, people will be
dying in their sleep, and you won't even
know why.
Right.
You'll be dying overnight.
You'll be dying of sepsis in three days
if you don't get cancer.
There you go.
Cancer is like, you know how when there's
a car accident and the traffic control comes
down, they put up a blockade and flares
and redirect traffic?
Yep.
That's what cancer is.
Right.
So imagine there's a, have you seen those
videos where there's a, it's really snowy, you
can't see, and there's a crash, and then
it just keeps coming because you don't see
through the snow.
You didn't know there was a crash in
front of you.
And then here comes another car.
Boom.
It's like these a hundred car pileups in
the snow.
Yeah.
They just keep hitting each other because they
can't see in front of themselves.
Yeah, exactly.
That's what's going on with the cancer thing.
Right.
Yeah.
There's nothing to cure.
There's nothing to, yeah.
So when you change your behavior, you change
your input and you change your environment and
your conditions, the cancer goes away.
But you sometimes, is it possible to do
a road?
What do you call it when the traffic
shows up to redirect traffic?
It's not really a road block, is it?
There's a term for it, an engineering term.
I forgot what it's called.
They say redirect, you know, you send police
out to redirect traffic and they- Yeah.
What is the staging called though?
You know, when they put the cones up
and the flares and they redirect, you know,
they do a bypass or whatever.
A diversion or a bypass.
Yeah, a diversion.
Yeah.
So imagine, can you have one that's so
intense that you can't clear it quickly?
Yeah, it's possible.
I've seen like around the White House when
they're going to do the big speeches, they
put these concrete piers in the road, right?
You can't just move those the next day.
They have to bring in special things, you
know, those concrete barriers.
Yeah, there's a machine that picks them up
and moves them.
Yeah, exactly.
So you can get real intense with some
cancers and stuff.
And if a cancer eats you up real
fast, fast acting, that just means the condition
that you had that caused the cancer to
keep you alive was so aggressive that the
cancer was aggressive.
Cancer is a countermeasure.
That's a way to put it.
Cancer is a countermeasure that the body puts
up.
It's incredible.
See, they can't talk about this.
There are people who know about this because
I've discussed it with some people and they're
like, yeah, that's exactly what it's doing.
So they wouldn't say, when you see their
eyes light up, it's like, finally, someone else
who can actually communicate what's going on because
I had a feeling, I just didn't know
how to communicate it, right?
When you view it that way, you can
actually treat the overall condition.
Anyway, so it's very  I shouldn't say
I'm not frustrated.
I'm in the twilight zone, right?
Imagine you've seen the twilight zones, right?
And the victim, I called up the character
that the episode is focused on, the victim
typically, right?
Yeah, that's the one that's always confused or
going, where do I go, where do I
go?
Whether it's an astronaut or whatever.
It could be an entire neighborhood sometimes become
victim to something.
They don't know that they're in the twilight
zone, right?
So I know I'm in the twilight zone
and I'm experiencing the twilight zone, so how
can I be upset or frustrated about it?
I might sound like it because that's just
the way to convey the information.
I'm totally cool with it.
I get it.
The reason why that character is upset is
because they're looking for the normal behavior and
they're not getting it and they're going, why
is this character confused?
It's an episode called the twilight zone.
Yeah, they don't know that they're in the
twilight zone, right?
That's like a cartoon character doesn't know he's
just a bunch of ink drawings or pixels
or something, right?
They don't know that.
Supposedly, some of them do.
I like where the cartoon characters, where one
shows up with an eraser and he starts
erasing the other character, you know, kind of
thing.
Yeah, so that's what's going on.
Anyway, I wanted to just share that because
you notice a big change and Brandon Joe
Williams there, I don't know who I was
listening to, he's like, these motherfuckers don't know
anything.
They don't, and I've been saying this for
a long time.
They don't know anything.
Now, here's the thing for all you people
out there that are just trying to get
by.
In order to be an attorney or a
doctor, an accountant, a priest, you don't have
to know anything.
You just have to smell, look, and sound
like one of those people, right?
And people say, Greek, you're so smart.
Well, typically, my two answers to that are
this.
One is, no, I'm not smarter.
I'm just less dumb, maybe.
And the other one is, how do you
know I'm smart?
Now, I'm just not, like, sounding smart and
looking smart.
What's the difference between being smart and sounding
like I'm smart?
Well, I've never heard anybody answer that properly,
but go ahead.
Yeah, well, here's the thing.
Here's an example of someone who is totally
vacuous but sounds smart and appears to be
smart and is accepted as being smart.
You're eight college professors without exception.
They're all like that.
They're all vacuous.
Because if you actually knew the material, you
wouldn't be there.
You would have been fired, right?
Plus, I'll tell you what my experience with
those people is, is that they never know
anything outside of that material.
I mean, literally, they're incapable of knowing just
about anything else outside of knowing that material,
if you're lucky.
Well, here's the thing.
Let's just take a lighter approach, a more
conventional approach.
How many times have you heard about professors,
and they start doing podcasts about alternative stuff?
What does the university do to them?
Fires them.
We know one, the Arab guy.
The guy, he was on Veterans Today.
He was popular during the Arab Spring.
He worked for some university, and then he
started being pro or whatever.
Kevin, right?
Yeah, Kevin, whatever.
Yeah, and he speaks Arabic.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, you know what I'm talking about.
There's many professors that have been fired because
they said, oh, you're too political or whatever.
No, it's the opposite.
So they're all morons without exception.
Now, the exceptions, this is where the exceptions
with the doctors, dentists, all these.
Now, by the way, if you're going to
go with any of these morons, these professionals,
the one that is the most essential is
the dentist, and then, of course, anyone that's
going to treat an emergency, right?
Dentistry is very important to be close with,
and you have to know what you want
done with dentistry, by the way.
I've actually heard people go, had a problem
with a tooth, and go to a dentist
and ask the dentist what was wrong with
them.
And that was just like a comedy back
and forth.
No, it's ridiculous.
There's no way.
I've got a bad tooth right now, and
I know what needs to be done with
it.
It's just that I can't see well enough
to do it, and therefore, I would just
tell them, look, you've got to clean this
out, and remove this, and then I'm fine,
you know?
Well, yeah, the extractions and all that.
Yeah, it's interesting how it could go.
But you go to one of these medical
morons.
You better know exactly what you want.
Pick a procedure from their manuals.
Pick which one you think you want, and
then tell him, review, review.
Because they don't know what's going on.
They really don't.
They appear like they do, all of them,
if they did know what's going on.
I've also had, by the way, I'll interject
this instead of saying if they did know
what's going on.
There are a few medical people out there,
and they look at the procedures and how
dumb the people are.
And they're like, this could be done better.
And they get reprimanded.
It says, we don't want you to do
it better.
We want you to do it the standard
accepted way is what they constantly get told.
That's why if you know anyone that's trying
to get a patent for a medical device,
it's like 12 years of reviewing.
Even though if it was just implemented right
now, it would help tons of people right
away.
But why do they delay it?
Because you're under an enemy occupation.
They control your medical, spiritual, accounting, blah, blah,
blah.
I've put up letters in the financial group
where the IRS commissioner in 1985 actually put
an internal memo.
He says, what we're doing is completely illegal.
And if anybody states so, we should comply
and give them back any money they paid
us.
I'm just paraphrasing.
It's two paragraphs long.
And he even says, if they do cite
the Constitution, what we're doing is completely illegal
and whatever, these are the forms they should
use.
And you should tell them to set up
a trust so we can send it to
the trust.
Because you can't send it to the same
entity that you've been fleecing.
Because what happened with the IRS and all
these other property tax and stuff, back in
the 50s after World War II, it was
1% voluntary tax.
So most people said, oh, yeah, I want
to help the government.
I'll take 1%.
You know, it's a penny.
And then they started putting people in the
news, like Max Schliemann, who was a boxer.
They made him fight Joe Williams and he
lost just to pay an IRS debt of
like $10,000, which is like half a
million now, right, or a quarter of a
million now.
And they started putting every 10 years a
famous person, Willie Nelson, Helmsley, the owner of
Helmsley.
Then Wesley Snipes.
They put them in the media.
Oh, Schmeling.
You're talking about Schmeling.
Yeah, right, Max Schmeling.
Right, right, right, right.
Max Schmeling was the first one they did
in the 50s, right?
Right, right.
Because back then it was just 1%
tax.
Oh, this IRS is no joke, man.
You put all this stupid stuff.
Because what happened, a whole bunch of bad
actors, maybe Jewish lawyers and accountants, went in
the offices and saw what they could get
away with.
And then that became a culture in the
IRS or the franchise boards.
You know, the United States Department of Fiscal
Services and the Treasury are the only two
people that can do anything legally.
Everything else is by private contract.
So what happened, a whole bunch of bad
actors went into these agencies, your counties, your
cities, your states, and started levying all these
taxes and acting brutally against the people.
And the people accepted.
Why?
Because they also controlled the media, just like
an occupying force would.
Another good thing is there's a couple of
movies.
I forgot something.
I think State is in the title.
These aliens landed on Earth and they took
over all the governments and started taking, you
know, they rarely show the aliens.
They look like these porcupine creatures, very fast
moving.
And they still allowed, the aliens took over
everything, and they still allowed like sport games
and elections and all that.
But when they took over, the aliens told
the human media, every day in the news
and the media you have to put that
the politicians are negotiating with the aliens to
make things better every day.
That was in the news.
But every day things got worse and worse
and worse.
And people are like, they're lying to us,
aren't they?
We got to get these fucking alien things,
right?
So that was perfect because that's exactly what's
going on.
They use the media.
The media, by the way, is university.
Here's the thing why university is bullshit, all
of it.
How can they tell you how the human
body works, history or anything, in university and
then counter it on the history channel on
TV?
They have to tell you what the history
channel or the medical channel on TV is
telling you.
They all have to be synced up.
So what you see, I say, why are
you spending, why are you saving for college?
Just watch TV.
It's the same stuff.
Oh, but you don't get a degree.
Oh my gosh, you don't get it, do
you?
Right?
So when have you gone and looked at
university textbooks, any subject, and look at what
they show about those subjects on TV and
they differ?
When?
Never.
It's the same.
So skip the university, save the small fortune,
and watch television.
You'll be just as smart.
I'm telling you.
And there's nobody saying this.
Anyway, I'm going to, I sound like I'm
on a soapbox yelling at everyone, which I
am.
Any other questions?
Oh, yeah, okay.
I've got a couple of comments and things
here.
Let's see.
All right.
Greek mentioned in 204 about looking through, quote,
notes when he couldn't find a missing part.
I know of dream journals, but he's mentioned
making sure he can see individuals' mouths moving.
Being a dream walker and fixing his attention
on items to verify that he's not in
a dream state.
Is note-taking part of that process to
catch the system messing with you, or was
that just a side commentary?
No, I think note-taking, well, here's the
thing.
If you're really good, like the Terminator, if
you see the Terminator movies, his point of
view, he's taking notes because, you know, when
they give you the Terminator's point of view,
you see the red letters line up, and
he's always choosing the targets as targeted.
You know, the Terminator's point of view in
the movie, the Terminator was Schwarzenegger and whatever.
Yeah, if you're really good, you don't need
to write it down, right?
If you're really good with that.
But I suggest writing things down to memorialize
them for others, because let's say you can
internalize all the notes and be a really
good note-taker and have an indelible memory
and all that.
If you tell someone what you took notes
on and still have those notes mentally from
a year ago, they won't believe you.
But if you have it on paper, you
can share that with them, right?
Mm-hmm.
And you can date that and say, here's
my...
It's called memorialization.
So for memorialization, write things down as much
as you can.
I've heard of people go through dream journals
and stuff, and they wake up in the
middle of the night, and they look, and
they write right away, you know, before they
forget it, you know, in their dream journal,
right in the middle of the night.
Yeah, you can have that.
But you have to discern, you know, the
dreams that we consider conventional dreams are done
by tricksters.
The travel, you know, the reason why we
sleep, you know, the excuses for the physical
body recovery.
Yes, what is it, a week or ten
days without sleep, you die.
Right.
But we're being used.
It's a very efficient universe.
We're being used while we sleep somewhere else.
We're being plugged.
Because our consciousness is not really in our
body, but our consciousness in this realm relies
a body, right?
Because if you kill the body, stop the
body, the consciousness goes off.
It's like unplugging the TV or removing the
screen from the TV.
You know, maybe it's still playing, but no
one can see it, right?
So I would say journaling is very important,
if that would be the crux of the
question.
Absolutely.
Taking notes and seeing what's real or not.
But I don't think we're allowed to objectify
too much here.
That's why I go along with it.
Make some, what do you call it, snap
judgments in your life about everything, and then
remember what those quick judgments were, and then
follow through and see if that judgment was
valid, because that will help you to make
quick decisions and things like that.
Because you're going to need that.
If you wake up from a dream, it's
very rare that you remember all the details
much later, right?
Right.
So work on your memory and all that,
and a quick judgment on what that was
about.
Absolutely.
That's a good way to look at it.
Okay.
Interesting side note on the blockchain.
Your, quote, signature, end quote, is used to
validate the transaction.
It's digital consent in this consent-based terrarium,
is what this comment is.
Yeah, but it's more than that.
The signature is your gold.
The signature, imagine, like, if there was lawful
money, in order to create or complete a
transaction, you drop a silver coin or some
gold or a note for gold or silver.
That's what your signature is.
But you're not told that, right?
That's the most incredible theft.
I was in Walmart the other day, and
people were talking about how prices are going
up.
No, the prices are going up because the
money is worth less.
So that means you have to work more
to get the same stuff because you're working
for that money.
If you didn't work for that money, you
wouldn't view the prices as going up, right?
Because your labor is either getting shittier or
the money is being devalued when the labor
is still good.
So that means you're being ripped off, right?
So if your labor is just as good
as it was a year ago and your
paycheck hasn't changed and you have to spend
more of it to get the same stuff,
you're being stolen from, right?
So it's all theft.
And also you can't save money in a
credit-based economy because let's say it was
1950 and you had a time machine and
you said, when I get to the year
2004, let's say, I'm going to take this
$2,000 so I could buy a brand
new car.
Yeah.
But you show up in 2004 and you
walk in with $2,000, you can't even
buy the tires maybe.
You'll put a down payment on it, they'll
tell you.
Yeah, you can put a down payment, right.
Yeah, which is illegal anyway.
It's either all cash or all credit.
There's no down payments.
But no one's arguing.
The banks are paying off the politicians to
never talk about the money system.
That's what they're paying the politicians off for.
So when Nancy Pelosi goes in on, what
is it, $180,000, $280,000 a year
for a senator and she comes out worth
$80 million, it's because she's been paid by
the bankers or enriched by the bankers not
to talk about the money.
And they don't.
They never talk about the money.
Remember the smart people?
They sound smart.
The government sounds like they're being fiscally responsible
but they're not at all.
That's what they're being paid and bribed and
whatever not to talk about, right.
And it's not up to them.
That's why whenever you bring an argument up,
like, for example, when someone sued Fox News
for libel a long time ago and the
court, they threw it out because the judge
says they're an entertainment company, they can't libel
you.
Well, actually, the defense attorney said it and
the judge accepted it.
That's what happened.
Oh, his own side did it.
His own side did it, yeah.
Or actually, the defense attorney.
Okay, so not the plaintiff, the defendant did
it.
Yeah, so basically it got thrown out based
on, yeah.
Yeah, basically they said defend this and they
said, well, we can't because we're an entertainment
company anyway.
And boom, the judge agreed.
Yeah, they're an entertainment company, so what are
you going to do?
And that's what the university says.
We don't have a duty to educate you.
We provide a credit system and we find
that you have appropriate credits.
The trustees, if you look at diploma, the
trustees believe that you have enough credits to
get this degree.
There's no education in there at all.
Well, whatever, learning.
Yeah, it's really sad.
And the thing is, I've known this for
decades, decades with a capital D.
I've known this, but it's important to reiterate
it.
I've noticed a lot of the new subs
and people that have been communicating lately are
in their 20s and 30s.
And they haven't been rubbed down with this
kind of stuff.
You know when you get a good rub
down, you remember it, right?
Yep.
Whatever you want to call it, whatever body
part, whatever.
So they haven't been rubbed down with this
and they're not going to get this anywhere
else at all because it's a planet full
of idiots.
Anyway, what else you got?
There you go.
Okay, last thing is, as far as what
came first, the chicken or the egg, unless
the chicken was the first animal to lay
an egg, the egg came first is what
this person said.
Well, you could say that, but it's not
the same egg.
It's a different type of egg because that
egg requires a chicken to make it.
So they come at the same time.
Like, for example, they come at the same
time or the chicken comes first and the
intent of the chicken.
That's why when they say, why did the
chicken cross the road?
I said, that's not, don't have to ask
that because who can question the intent of
a chicken?
So it's all based on intent.
So what I'm saying here is very simple.
They came at the same time.
It's just like when you buy a car
and you open the trunk and you see
a depression for a spare tire and in
that depression of the sheet metal for the
spare tire, there is a spare tire, which
came first.
And it was all made together.
Right.
Right?
It was all made together.
It was made to repopulate.
Right?
So that's where the creation aspect comes in
and that creation vessel or whatever.
Yeah.
And then it goes into what an atom
is.
You know, it's all frequency and energy.
It was all set up at the same
time.
Evolution is easy to bust because like a
giraffe evolved a long neck.
Well, you had to evolve a trachea, you
had to evolve this, this, this, this, and
that, and a heart all at the same
time.
Right.
And if those things weren't set up for
a long neck, the neck wouldn't have gotten
longer.
Right?
So anyway, so yeah, the trick is most
of the cliches and paradoxes we put in
front of us are idiot questions.
In other words, they're so simple, but we're
trained to see who's conditioned to say there's
no answer for that.
When they're all answerable, all of them.
And a basic on human physiology is that
women are born with all of the, you
know, what they casually call an egg, but
it's an ovum.
They're born with all of them to begin
with.
Pretty much.
Yeah.
Most studies will show that you come fully,
fully packed.
Yeah.
The weird thing is that one of the
pieces that ends up becoming you, one of
the very little pieces that ends up becoming
you was actually inside the body of your
grandmother at one point.
It's just so simple.
You know?
Yeah.
I mean, it's, yeah, we're not, this is
like what they call first principle stuff, pure
objectification.
You know, how do you tell cartoon characters
that they're actually pixels on a screen and
they're just code that's being projected through some
chips that are animating, you know, the screen?
It's really hard to objectify that.
You know, they don't want to hear that.
And even if you wanted to hear it,
no one's going to say it.
And even if someone, it's done in a
way that we can't really talk about pure
objectification.
Yeah.
There you go.
So that's the end of all my questions.
Anything else you want to cover?
No, I mean, I think today was kind
of like a retrosonic going back to more
of the stuff that I talked about a
long time ago and reaffirming it.
Fair enough.