It's like a submarine. Okay.
Somebody's got to do it.
Oh, I got the house. I got so much custom shit built in here.
Nah, I would figure you would. I mean, just out of boredom, you'd probably do that.
Never bored.
Never?
How can you be bored?
Wait a minute, you're never bored? You're never bored?
Never. We'll talk about that.
So you don't find the foolishness of other people boring?
No, absolutely we're gonna, yes.
Go, go, go. All right, come on, hit the button or something, man.
Yeah.
SonicEvent45, Ocelli here and TheGreek also. How you doing, man?
Hey, I'm doing what else am I supposed to be doing?
So right before and as I was pressing record, actually, because I started recording before
I played the intro, just a fair game to you, I'm telling you. I said, come on, you're never bored.
I don't know if I recorded that part, but you're never bored. Being around people that you know
are not caught up to what you're caught up to are not as informed as you are.
You don't get bored with that?
You can repeat that 10 times. I'll take it 10 different ways.
Okay.
You know what I mean? Here's number two.
Go ahead.
You see what I mean?
Right. And I'll leave it at that.
Okay.
You know, you've heard, look, if you're familiar with Greek speak, it's about, okay,
you know, when you're assessing a diamond, right? Do they just look at it and put it away?
Or does it count how many cuts and facets they're on there and see what you view through each one?
Yeah, of course. They take, they take a couple of notes. They pull out a couple of different
jewelers loops. At least they used to, I don't know. Maybe there's a machine for that now,
as far as I know. But the last time I was around somebody, they use little loops, you know?
And yeah, I've got them. I've got all of them. People think the higher the magnification,
the better you see it. I loops are so subjective. Yeah. I've got some really nice ones. Those
really cheap ones. And the really cheap ones work just as well as the really good ones.
You see, now you're striking on something that I'm extremely familiar with, because as you well
know, I use a lot of devices to try and assist my vision. And you probably are not familiar with
those things because we've never discussed it, but I'm sitting at the office here. I got one
right here. I just opened it. Yeah. Yeah. Look, I'm in my sixth decade. So are you perhaps. And
you know, eyesight is something of contention as these whippersnappers get older, right?
Yeah. Well, I, but I started out from a bad place. So I was getting familiar with the magnifying
glasses and stuff when I was like five and six years old. And the truth is that the stuff made
by Bausch and Lomb is just as good as that stuff they make in Japan, which is, you know, what?
500 bucks, I think is the, the cheapest thing that they sell that one catalog. You ever see
that, that one catalog that does nothing but optical solutions? No, no, but we'll check it out.
Well, there's that. And then there's the Americanized thing. They call it the lighthouse
catalog. It has a whole bunch of optical aids. Maybe you've seen that one. Nope. I haven't been
pursuing them. What I do is I go into a lapidary supply and get it from there. I'll give a plug
for these guys, Kent tools. You know how I gave a plug for the star gems here in Tucson. They're
only people you could really quickly get inexpensive silver. Oh yeah. By the way,
they're going out of business. They're internet only, which I think will make it easier. Oh,
wow. Because before you had, it was old school. You call, they wrote it down on a slip, you know,
maybe you got it. Maybe you don't, you know, you always got it, but it's now it'll be internet
only, uh, Kent tools, K E N T lapidary supply in Tucson. Um, uh, they've got over a million
things in stock, a different, not a million of one thing, but a million different things
for working on small things to, you know, anything that works with metal jewelry,
X, whatever. Excellent. Excellent. Excellent people. Excellent supply. Very inexpensive.
Um, you can get anything. Uh, and that's where I go for that. But yeah, I'm not optically
challenged to the point where I believe you might say you have been. So I can't say that I've gone
down the same, you know, similar path. I understand. It's just that I've used machines. I've used stuff
that projects. I've used things that put it up on TV screens. You know, I used to have a great book.
I would say a camera hooked up to a flat screen is good for everyone. That's excellent. Uh,
and Stevie wonder actually, uh, was partially responsible for developing some of the reader
technology that people now use, you know, that, that, that stuff that reads, uh, you you've seen
that before where you can actually have your computer read an article to you. Uh, audio audio
wise, kind of scary, but yeah. Yeah. I don't, there's something too artificial still about it.
Yeah. Well, Stevie wonder came up with a way of taking that kind of technology and putting it on
a book actually. And it's strange because it sort of disappeared, uh, but it was out there for a
little while where you could take almost any book and you could point this device at it and it would
read it to you. Uh, now they have stuff that's, everything's linked to the internet of things,
you know? So, um, there, there's actually a set of glasses too, that exists. If you're,
if you have low vision and the set of glasses will sit there and give you an audio description
of everything in front of you, including familiar things, like for instance, if you were in your
home, Greek, it would specifically facially recognize the wife and, uh, tell you the wife
is in the room. What if you don't want to facially recognize her? But anyway, I'm just saying it's,
uh, take my wife, take my wife, please. I keep taking her places, but she keeps coming back.
Uh, yeah, I know. Any young men, uh, if you ever see a, you see a guy on the internet somewhere
and in the image, a guy holding a violin while he's telling jokes, that's probably him.
Anyways. The other one is Rodney Dangerfield. Like, like my daughter, you know, she's like
federal express. She absolutely positively has to spend the night. There you go. Plus, you know,
my parents, they had to put a pork chop around my neck there. So the dog would play with me.
Oh, I get no respect. Yeah. Anyways. So Chuck, let's move on. Sure. Look, I'm not trying to just
carry on. Cause the optical stuff is not getting me bored, but it is optical stuff, right? So let's
jump into some chili in the Greek. Exactly. Let's do that. Now. Uh, there was a bunch of talk in the
chat room and I want to address it about the, uh, you know, the Adam and which Adam is which,
cause we talk about how there is more than one Adam. Although, uh, in religious circles,
they discuss one Adam being, you know, the first guy that supposedly has his rib taken out.
It's simple, simple. There's never just one. It's a, it's a survivor race that's been genetically
modified. It's pretty clear. Uh, even if you have someone that survived a cataclysm and they're part
of the original, you could call them part of the original creation. Right. Right. So if I've got a
59, a Chevy that's untouched and perfect condition with 20,000 miles on it outside, I could say
that's what it is, right? Even though it's 70 years later, plus so or less. So, um, it's an
original aspect versus, uh, uh, something newer and newer and newer, by the way, the, the latest,
uh, generation spoken of in these ancient texts are spoken of as if they're, um, not even connected
to the original humans. Go, go figure. If you actually look at the, a lot of the original words,
they're very rare. There's no reference to the last generation of people known as referred to
any relationship to Adam and all those that they're just called the last generation of people.
So by, yeah, but by, by the meaning of the word generation though, it means that they were
generated from something previous. No, no, no generation just means flipping, you know,
reproduction. Okay. Okay. Like a Xerox machine, but it's not really like a Xerox machine,
but that, that story here, that's a, that's a very interesting story because
here, these are the, there's some serious doubts in there. You know, I recently did an
interview with Greg Carlwood again and, um, higher side check. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Right. And he, he's,
uh, he says he's, he likes it because it's a timeless interview. He may not post it immediately.
He could post it. It's not like the news about the fires in Maui. Right. Right. So, uh, which
will be strange if you post it out of content, out of time. So anyway, uh, there's a lot of stuff,
a lot of weaknesses in there. The reason why I pursued it is because I want to know what to do.
If I go somewhere and I don't know what the F is going on, somebody tell me what to do, please.
Right. Or do I have to, I don't have enough time to make things up as I go. Right. And, um, uh,
that's where experience comes in. You know, as you get older, you relate to younger people, you,
you, you relay some information or knowledge that you have, so they don't have to reinvent it,
right. Find out how things work. Not only that, but it would be a good idea to have a good go-to
plan considering that if, if the fire was moving at approximately one mile per minute, which
translates to about 60 miles per hour, if that is the way that it appears to be traveling across
the land, that's a fairly fast moving event, which you need to have some idea about what to do about.
You can't be stopping and going, okay, now what is it we need to assess here? You don't have time.
Life is very fast moving event. I mean, uh, look at the trees. If you go back to where you were
raised and there were large trees, they're still there unchanged pretty much. Right. And, uh, that's,
that's what I've noticed. So anyway, the doubts that I have is not necessarily a doubt. It's just
that you could play blatantly. See, like for example, Yahweh, when they did the generations
and Moses, these guys put it together, they obviously didn't know about the people living
in the South Congo, obviously. And they didn't know about the people living in North Asia
or in the Americas. Obviously they're not mentioned in there. Why? Because they didn't
know about them. Right. Think about it. What I just said, if, well, if he's the God and the
creator of everything, shouldn't he know about that? But obviously he didn't know whoever put
that text together. So what does that tell you? So these weak points, there's a lot, here's the
thing. There's a lot of people that bring up contradictions in the Bible and it's only
lost in translation or version is not really a contradiction. If you see it, just like when you
say there's no crucifixion, that sounds like a contradiction just because they put the word
crucifixion in 50 times doesn't mean it happened. Right. Like terrorism for 9-11. There was no
terrorism. It was sabotage. In other words, they set off things that should not have been set off
without public notice. So, right. By the way, a little diversion, we'll go back to it.
There are more people, civilians, Americans that died in World War Two in the U.S. via sabotage
than attacks. And there was Torpedo Alley. You don't hear about that. Well, 5,000 people died
on the Carolinas, on the East Coast. You don't hear anything about that.
But there's thousands and thousands upon scores of thousands that died on sabotage, factory fires,
accidents, things like that. Just like right now, I think there's a factory fire, like 10 a month
at a rate of 10 a month, either food processing or chemical processing plants in the U.S. going off,
right, on fire. Right. So they're just repeating the same old playbook. So, in other words,
there are things going on that are blatant. And even if you're living in that time you don't know
about, the people that search a little record it. And then they see that those things happened
before. So if you want to talk about scripture here, this is my main concern. It's basically
prophecy, like knowing what's coming, because, hey, anybody who works on Wall Street wants to
know that. Right. You had to hedge your bets. Where did you say the world is ending? Is it
if it's really not ending, why are you going to get so hyped up about it? Right. So you
live more efficiently. The other thing is, how do you live? Right. I mean, I don't know. I mean,
what do you remember? We went last time we spoke about, like, if you listen to the scientists or
watch TV, they'll tell you to eat one thing and then it's bad the next year. And then he said,
no, I don't go by that. Right. You know, there's no mention of the heart being a pump, which is
true. Right. In the Bible, there's no mention of an immune system, which is there's no such thing.
Right. So you just basically see a set of rules that are tried and tested. And that's why I do
it in terms of prophecy. And I'll throw this in. I can't discuss anymore.
When looking at archaics of stuff, I don't endorse them because
just like I don't endorse anyone, really. You go look at the comments section. I'm not
disparaging either. This is just planet Earth. If you go look at all the people that are following
him. Oh, my gosh. Oh, you do not want. Oh, my gosh. It's like talk about anyway. You look at
anybody's comment section. Yeah. Oh, my God. It's like, please, if we ever doing a no comments,
the chat is seems to be fine because we do have a cream of the crop. It seems that come over to
this section of the world known as Grocelli in the Greek rated why the uncultivated humanity.
But what I'm looking at is this timeline. I think he's overstated a lot of it, but there is a lot
of validity there. Right. That's all I want to say. And I'm looking at it very closely.
But the thing on the thing on the 1998, which I've been doing strictly from the Bible
is endorsed by him and Edgar Cayce. I didn't know Edgar Cayce had said that.
I always thought Edgar Cayce was too airy, fairy, happy, clappy, even though he was called a sleeping
prophet. I didn't give him any credence. Well, that may be because of the way people tell the
story, because let me just throw this in real fast. You talked about how people didn't know
certain things. You know, they didn't know about the people in the Americas and whatnot at the
time they wrote that. Well, the authors of the of the operations in Genesis. Yeah, right. So they
don't know about that. That's fine. But here's the other thing. No matter what they knew,
they can only relate a part of what it is they know anyway, even if,
OK, let's just theoretically say, you mean they ran out of ink and paper? No,
they didn't run out of ink and paper. You don't have to run out of ink and paper. Here's the
thing. You got to be selective. You can't tell everybody about every single blade of grass.
Well, hold on. That's why I lean into it only. It's only in regard to that part of the world.
That's why I've said that before as a caveat. But when it says these are all the generations of
Adam, well, we left out the people of southern Congo and we've left out the people in the
Dakotas and we've left out. Right. The Inuits, we left out. Yeah. Right. So obviously, because
they didn't know about them. So what kind of a creator of everything would not know? You see,
there's a problem, big problem there. But it doesn't matter. Well, not necessarily relation
that works. But you see, it may work just fine, though, because it's not necessarily about what
they don't know. It's maybe that's not the same people. How about that? No, no, no. I didn't say
they don't know for sure, but apparently it appears what they're giving. There's a lot being,
you know, you know, the intelligence operatives, you know, the rules of questioning people. I think
we went over that before. Right. Listen to what they say. Listen to what they don't say.
Listen, how look at how they say what they say and look at how they don't say what they don't say.
Right. So, well, look, when you seek to instruct somebody, whether it's about a simplified,
you know, series of tasks that they need to learn how to do, like, say, in job training
or something like that, or it is to literally give them a philosophy by which to live,
you're going to be selective about what it is you give them. The first things you need to
are the essentials. Right. I mean, this is operationally what you need. All right. Now,
these are the things that may come up. OK. And you put these things in order. I mean,
anybody. Well, let's just get just to make it really clear. It's like the U.S. Constitution.
Why is it called the U.S. Constitution? Because it's for the U.S. But in the U.S. Constitution,
though, doesn't it state that the operation of this document will be the law of nations?
What's the law of nations? It's all international. So it goes back and forth.
So, yeah, but the Adam look, this is what I've the last time we spoke about
the spirit. I think I gave a heavy analogy and I don't know how to beat people over the head with
it. But in terms of being spiritual, anything that is cognitive, behavioral, expressive,
communicative, anything and everything is spiritual. Right. The only thing that is not is a
bunch of people laying down in bed sleeping or in a coma. Right. So the moment they start uttering
a groaning, guess what? That is a spiritual emanation. Right. And it's spiritual is both
bad and good and in between. So when you look at these things, you have to see, is it a data point?
Is it some base, a knowledge base? Right. Or is it spiritual? And I would tell you that 99
percent of the Bible is not spiritual at all. It's all data points and knowledge base.
Right. That's why I say religions have nothing to do with the text that they're written on. Right.
So, yeah. So the thing is, going back to people, why I don't get bored is very simple.
Even though I live here the entire life in total disgust when I see people around me,
pretty much everyone to it with very few exceptions, instead of getting bored when
I'm not feeling that or thinking that it's what am I going to do to get the F out of here?
Or gracefully for personally gracefully leave this situation. Right. So what happens is you move
like out of one room to another and or into the street into another building into another country.
And you start noticing that it's pretty much the same everywhere. You remind yourself of that
thought that you need an exit strategy. So instead of being bored of what's in front of you, which I
find utterly repugnant in terms of the behavior of people, I find that pondering an exit is
the next best thing. The better than being bored. That's why I'm never bored.
If that makes any sense. You see, boredom is a form of anger, by the way. I've always
suggested that. And there was a psychologist I spoke to says, well, that's very interesting,
Greek. And I can't really write that up for you. Can't really publish that because you're not a
psychologist. Like, oh, my gosh. But, you know, if I publish it, you know, then then people will
listen to it. I'm like, oh, if you, you know, so. Yeah. Well, you know what you can do always is
you could turn around and write to like a publication like Psychology Today and positive
under a false name. And they will publish it sometimes, some odd things like that and create
discussions. Yeah. You do that. Let me know what happens. Yeah. You have a license to do that.
I thank you anyway. But I'm not suggesting you do that. That's probably not an efficient use of your
time. But I will say that people also brought up a couple of things that were brought up on previous
sonic incarnations of this where you mentioned specifically twenty twenty nine and a couple of
other time periods. And what does this get us into? Well, the favorite topic when you and I were
discussing this on AFR seemed to be the what was referred to as the kill shot, which was the you
know, the thing that's going to happen here, the beginning to reorganize that. But I never really
got into twenty twenty nine as much as I did twenty eighteen plus seven plus seven. You see,
so twenty eighteen plus seven twenty twenty five and then plus seven is twenty thirty two. That's
what I would suggest. The kill shot would be twenty thirty two. So I never really did.
As far as I can remember for three decades, that's all three, three decades ago. I really,
really try to figure this out. What I mean by three decades ago, around 2003, 2006. Right.
So the tens, the ones two thousands is one decade. The tens is second decade. Now we're in the 20s.
That's the third decade. Right. Right. You know, it's funny, you know, how people you know,
when you're born, you're in your first decade. Right. The day you're born, you're in your first
decade, you're in your first millennium, your first century, you're in the very early part,
you're in your first year, but you're only an hour old. Right. So there's a difference between.
Right. Even if it's one hour in, you're still in. So you're still in your first year. Right.
You're still in your first decade. Right. See, however you want to. It's basically a metric.
So for three decades, I've been trying to put this together. And I did pretty good work,
I think, for those three years between what they call three and six. And then I sat on it
and looked at other things and I didn't see any reason to change it. Now, the archaics has got
the Phoenix chronology and these other chronologies. I'm trying to see how valid that is. And is it
valid? And does it work? But right now, as far as I know, if I were to communicate anything,
the last time period change was around 2018. Remember, it's the middle of the time period,
right? So four years plus 2018 is 2022. And the three years actually, there's a year break that
so 2020, 2021 defined 2022. Right. And then we got 2025 is the next period. And then 2032.
Right. I don't talk much about the twenty nines or the twenty twenties or twenty threes. You see,
you see how I parsed it out? Yeah. So what I've always said, and I'm still sticking with it,
is you're going to see the formation of a Middle East Union by 2025.
As far as I could see, meaning but it's a loose union. It's not like the EU where they have one
month. They're all going to kind of gang up and work together and Israel is going to be
kicked in the ass pretty good. But it's not because they could kick Israel in the ass.
It's because the leadership of Israel has got to abandon it. Right. Because that's going to change.
So well, just perfect timing from this part of the world, because honestly, look, we got our
twenty twenty four selection process coming up and then allegedly a new administration will be
taking hold in 2025, which they usually try to make some sort of a mark when it comes to the
Middle East. That could be something that affects those events and empowers some individuals that
might have not been empowered before, which is what I suspect. OK, you're putting it in view,
but I just want to I got to digress and go back. Sure. What I just said about 2025 in the Middle
East Union, I was saying in 2003. So it's not like I'm watching what's going on. You see,
it's just interesting when you watch what's going on. Remember, there was a big thing in Turkey,
like a little civil war and there was Arab Spring and people were saying, Greek, is this your
Middle East Union? I'm like, no, it's not time yet. And that was 12 years ago. Right. Just like
about a year or a year and a half ago, something like that. I asked you about this, you know,
things that were going on in Israel regarding the courts and the change. And it's a nothing burger
and it turned out to be a nothing burger. That's exactly where it went. But do I have it? Do I have
a knack for it? Apparently, it seems like I do. Does it matter to me if I'm wrong or if I'm right?
No. What am I talking about? Stuff that no one else is talking about in a way that's easy to
comprehend. Well, you'll have to answer that yourself. But I think I do. So what else is in
the chat? Well, I mean, there was that there was a little bit of an address to the the water topic
because you would put an image in there for a moment. Yeah, it's not fun that that that is fun.
I like that one piece. And by the way, I don't know if you understood this because I sent you
a text earlier. I just like that from an aesthetic perspective. Wow. It's like a wow. Wow. Wow. Kind
of like, oh, wow. Eye candy. Well, that would be cool as a cloth pattern. I mean, I'm just looking
at it that way. You know what I mean? Like I just shot that, you know, I just put the device
strung across some struts in front of a 430 a 40 inch plasma TV, LED TV. Yeah. And just
flash through some images. That's all I was just playing around because I've got to do some
photo documentation stuff. This is all industrial. These things are for lease and they're for sale.
They're very expensive. Don't ask if you want one, if you want one, just prepare it. It's
very, very pricey because it's expensive to make. It's very elitist.
And yeah, yeah, listen, the last thing the last thing I want is people want 100 people
wanting one of these that I really have to exit this world. There's no way you can make these
things fast. They're there. They're there. They work on subtle, subtle energy that is extremely
strong. You know that you talk about subtle energies, right? Most subtle energy devices
are very weak, right? This is a subtle energy device is extremely strong. So on a transformational
basis, so it's requires before we were even speaking, I was like, I need to find other
people step up to the plate and work with me on this. I can't be the only one that could advance
this, right? So if you're listening, and you're into, you know about the ether, you know about
magnetism, even though this doesn't use magnetism, even though there's a presence of a magnet,
and how to manipulate water, get in touch with the Greek, please, I could use some help,
an associate, an associate, let's just say, right, look, mathematically, Greek, I would say that
there stands to reason that there is a group of people that could be, you know, could work.
That's right. Let me just say what you what you would before you go on on the surface world,
vanilla, the white world, I know that in the black world, it's going on pretty hard.
It has been going on, they're probably laughing at that. I've come up with this. Yeah, I'm talking
about the surface world. Yeah, in the black world, who knows, right? Yeah, well, look, I don't claim
to know. But I'm just saying that on the surface world, I guarantee that there are a handful of
people that you could access, that would be at least up to par to be able to work with me that
guarantee in writing, I need it, please. If you want it written down, I'll write it down to you and
you know, what else? What else? What else we got? Well, look, there's there's a lot of things we
could go into. Let's go back to those Mount Maui fires real quick, though. Because what about Hold
on, I know nothing about them. I saw a headline about two weeks ago, and then it was brought up
by grit call. What I know absolutely is it the claiming claiming do weapons, the let me guess,
the authorities knew that for knowledge, they didn't warn the people I'm guessing. And there
is a conspiracy, whatever. Yeah. And it was for thought, right? I'm guessing correctly.
Oh, listen, you you're you're playing the game that I played the moment I saw the headline and
decided, okay, before I open up Twitter, I'm going to see what it is I know is going to already be up
there. Exactly, exactly that. And it was real quick. It was actually a lot faster than usual,
the the divergence of oddity there regarding the you know, the the the direct energy weapons and
everything else. But at the end of the day, you know what you live on a volcano, first of all.
And secondly, yeah, land management, electrical stuff, this is going to happen.
Why did it move so fast might have something to do with the fact that there was a hurricane
off the coast of the island chain, which changes the wind conditions a bit if it's a little further
away, even though it's not on top. Yeah, good lines up with the sabotage of 1940s. And which
was all internal, by the way, and they blamed it on German spies. No, yeah. But there was some
interesting stuff that went on there. You know, I was restudying that recently, you know, that
when they took down the the German boom, for instance, you know, for instance, and the FBI
becoming involved in that, and actually, that was the first time that the mob was actually weaponized
by the feds. Because that's what I was looking to study on is, you know, they they actually used
some organized crime guys who did not want to prop up the what they would call American Nazis.
So they turned one group against the other until they decided to turn against the mob, you know,
later, just like they used them to try to take out Castro, you know?
Well, here's a sentiment that I got from people that live during the era and also very little,
very little literal support. But the American Nazis, the German Nazis, whatever,
they all had a lot of sympathy for the US. And just without getting into what I mean by that is
that ultimately, they looked at the US as a safe haven. They had no intention of coming over here
and doing whatever they did. They had a big propaganda campaign to cause harm here. But the
people didn't even the troops did not go for it. They could have easily harmed the United States,
they had the weaponry and the technology they were doing. Halo, they were doing suborbital
flights, they had pressurized planes with rockets, they could go around the earth five times in a
day. And, you know, five, you know, they're approaching 20,000 miles per hour, dropping
nukes on in northern Russia. So the Yeah, they were super advanced compared to look, some of the
if you were brought forward the designs and capabilities of some of the quote unquote,
German weapons at the time, they would sound like fiction even today. Right? Yeah. So no,
they viewed the US as a safe haven kind of a place to go when things to cool off. And if things
didn't cool down. Yeah, it was all internal. It was the same people look right now. One thing that
I bring up with, you know, every country has a foreign government, which is united in its own
foreignness. And look at all when you when you're a federal employee, you're actually an unregistered
foreign agent. This is the norm. And then it's no big deal. Just like when they asked JP Morgan,
what are you going to do when people find out how the money system works? So it's easy. I'll just
draft enough checks to pay half the people to kill the other half of the people. Right? So the whole
thing about any quote unquote, foreign government is to get as many people on their payroll as
possible, because they're the ones most likely that are not going to rebel. I always give the
opposite. If you want to change the system, you have to join them and infiltrate and go up as high
as possible. And when no one's looking, you pull all the wires out, right? Oh, yeah. But
like that, yeah, to satisfy the people, though, that insist on being outsiders,
what you do is you assign them a job where they appear to be outsiders, and then you pit them
against each other so that they appear to have causes. This is what I'm talking about with the
mob versus the American Nazis. I mean, because look publicly before the beginning of World War Two,
officially or otherwise, you have these things like that gathering in Madison Square Garden,
I'm sure you've seen the film of it, right? Yeah, I mean, it's just an interesting thing to behold,
considering that, you know, they weren't allowed to display any swastikas or whatever. But otherwise,
you've got the template already for what you're going to see come out of Germany.
And about 10 years later, they were out in Long Island, they had an enclave in Long Island. It
wasn't. It was not hoppock. It was anyway, Nazi enclave, Hitler Road and all that.
They had a great one in Jersey, actually, one where, you know, they bought a big piece of
farmland pretty much and then started developing it for themselves. There was another one in
California. You know about the big one in California, right? That was started by the
guy who was like a screenwriter. And he was like, you know, pissed off at the people that
were actually paying him and he was making a good living. Good enough to Jewish bankers, too.
Of course. Yeah. But that was the fascinating part of it. And then what did they do? They
went to people like, you know, Meyer Lansky and those guys and said, hey, you want to help us
fight this? And they said, sure, of course they did. But this was just to keep people busy.
I mean, that's really what it was about. But I just find it interesting when law enforcement
pits to groups of individuals that they're supposedly allegedly supposed to be in total
opposition to and looking to bust, break down, take down. They pit them against each other,
you know, much like what I find most interesting about law enforcement is they know nothing about
law. Well, that's the beginning of doctors on it. Right. You see what I mean? There's a very
interesting twist. That's why I can't be bored. I'm always thinking, how do I get the fuck out
of here? Oh, there's that medical term again. What else is going on? Look, everybody's got
up. Everybody's got an exit. Yes, everybody's got an exit. But you know what? The strategy
is different because your exits come in whether you want it to or not. I mean,
nobody here gets out alive. OK, that's just the way it is. But yeah, that's
the way you leave is is up to you, isn't it? So in the meantime, do the best you can and help
others as much as you can. I believe in that as well. As strange as that sounds, because
we've got to do more than believe to actually do it. Yeah, I'm not saying you don't. I'm just
saying that's the credo that most people say these things that they don't. Yeah, when I say I
believe when I say I believe I got to tell you something, I imply something else. Maybe you can
give me a different vocabulary word for this, actually, because when I say I believe in something,
I don't just say I have the thought and it's something that I think is true. I need to say
that it is something that I also do. I actively participate in because I believe this. You see,
belief for me goes beyond just the common idea of I believe it goes into. If you don't believe
in something or if you do believe in something, there's no way in hell that you don't take action
that goes along with said belief. OK, I mean, I beg to differ. A lot of the religious leaders
say they believe in their raping children all the time. Yes. So which one is it? See,
I'm talking about me. I'm not talking about them. OK, I don't know. But yeah,
but I have to bring it over to a common premise. Of course. Of course. Yeah. So in other words,
that's why I'm asking you for a new word, because. Well, it's just a word selection.
You don't need a new word. Just figure out a different way to say it. And look,
Greek speak is full of it, you know? Yeah. Well, full of what? Full of it. Full of terms of them,
full of terms that are unique but easy to compile. Fair enough. Dummy load and, you know,
goes on and on and on. Heat space heaters and all that. Absolutely. So back to the back to
the fires, though, it does make me think not of just the fires in the particulars, because again,
like you said, you don't know the particulars right this minute, but you can guess very easily
where it was all going. That's why it's stage stage play, whatever. Here's the thing, though.
You used to talk about the the the kill shot, which I took to mean some sort of meteor. And
I was thinking of the cataclysm that was upon people as they, you know, look from the perspective
of somebody who was just sitting in their home one day and then all of a sudden all hell broke
loose, so to speak. Right. Yeah. But there's two of those. And as far as I could determine,
and one of them is of manufacture. I mean, in other words, it's not a lumpy rock, right?
With craters on it. OK. All right. We discussed that. Yeah. Right. So one more artificial
invention. Yeah. Well, art of manufacture. Yeah. Man, you look like you're not going to get a
picture of the second one. I'll strike fear in the hearts of the week. Right.
Well, why is that thing a disc? It's a mile wide with a hole in the middle of it. That's
500 feet thick. Wow. So it's polished and smooth. Perfect. Well, I always wondered,
does it even require the physical meteor or projectile landing on the planet if you just
simply have the the installation of fear upon the population? If you do that, if you convince the
population that this thing is going to hit, even take a look at what will happen, I'm thinking
without even the fact that it'll happen, they'll just think that if they put brown paper bags on
their heads and lay down, everything's going to be fine. Yikes. So we're going to make this guy.
Yeah, we're doing don't forget about the people. Yeah. OK. When you say people, there's there's
not that many on the planet, no matter what they say. The number of count is is very few always.
Well, that's actually they will be fine. Well, and you know what? Even if they're
killed instantly, they'll still be fine because they weren't really alive to begin with.
Yeah, I don't like that word. I'd like to come up with another word for I never actually
ever noticed. I don't use that word. Yeah, I care about. Yeah. It's because it has a connotation
that it has an effect on the mind, you know, that the one who utters it
is subject to it or capable of that. Right. We're not capable. But, you know,
whatever. You know what I mean? It's it's not a quote unquote.
No, it carries it carries extra sentimentality to it for a four letter word. It carries a lot
of extra sentimentality to it. That is kind of remarkable, because when you say kill,
obviously there's an ominous already a negativity attached to it just by saying that word.
That's why I always hate. I remember there are some places called the kills, but it's from Dutch
fresh kills. Gosh, what a horrible name. Fresh kills. Yeah, I always thought of that. What do
you mean? Are you talking about a fresh corpse? I mean, what does this mean? That's the place
also where they dumped all the radioactive stuff from the WTC. OK, what else? So it looks like
there was a lot of stuff before and after I put some things in there or not really. Right.
Well, there was this one big bombing of stuff about, you know, the atom, the generations.
We addressed that. But again, back to this, back to this meteor or whatever it is that strikes.
Yeah. Do you still stand by that calculation? Is that still the same?
Unknown. But yes, I do. But unknown. I'm trying to see if there's more stuff I can glean from
Jason Breshears at Archaic's work and see if it works together. Otherwise,
I am not ready to make any discourse on it.
So you have some ideas, but you don't think that you have any sort of other confirmation
from somebody who can observe this also on some level?
No, we're not. We're not going to get it. I've met people that work at the Lucifer Telescope
here. Yes, it's called Lucifer. Yes. Mount Graham. Right. And they're just dumber than
rocks. I mean, and it's like it's the guy, the manager, by the way. You know, I'm like,
oh, my gosh. And sorry if you're listening, you know, whatever. Yeah, you're not that smart.
Actually, I found out that long time ago that all of these big, quote, unquote, pseudo government,
corporate jobs are forms of welfare, they just need to fill a position. And all this hardware
that they show and all these offices are just like dressing. There's everything that's real,
that's controlling is not on the surface, right? Well, you know, like, I remember someone who's a
whole family worked on the State Department. I said, Oh, what a bunch of morons. And they're like,
really quiet. And they're like, so are they moronic? I'm not trying to see if you have a
better word, is it? Yeah, they're pretty moronic. I'm like, thank you. Because I just got to gather
I got to do data gathering. You know what I mean? Oh, I got you. It's fairly fascinating. Because,
you know, when I spoke to people that were, you know, involved in things in the what they called
the Soviet bloc, they would tell me about a lot of these positions that were sort of given to people
that had no, no, no good rhyme or reason to be in a position of power at all. And it just boiled
down to they had a nice office and a paycheck. And they didn't really do anything because they
didn't know how they were just given. It's a movie set. Yeah, just like a movie set. So when it when
they blow up a movie set, how much sympathy or do you clap? You know, I mean, do you really care?
No, you don't. You just build another one. You just build another one and you put on another
movie, right? I mean, but that's the thing is that these guys were just waiting there for something
to come up. And then yeah, they would be filmed or they'd be handed a statement to read. And they
would put it out on radio or what have you. And that was their actual purpose is to just fill a
role when it came time to fill the role. But otherwise, they did virtually nothing. And that
happened a lot. And I said, Well, is this a function of their state? Or is this just a function
of the state? In general? You know, is this just normal? So the thing is, I suggest people do
constant probing. Like the other day, I was out at a hardware store, I struck up a conversation,
it turns out they worked at the university here at Tucson, teaching biology and medicine. And I
just gave him a little bit of Greek speak about that. And they're like, I don't know, man,
that sounds pretty interesting. Like, oh, my gosh, oh, my gosh, another moron. And so they're all
morons, all of them. And you know how I've said with attorneys, doctors, lawyers, attorneys,
whatever, what these people are all morons, and until they figure out what they should be doing,
and then they don't last very long, they look for an exit strategy to leave or they stay in it and
just fleece the people. Yeah. Well, you know, look, how can you really blame somebody who says,
Well, I've got a job here. And I really at the end of the day, even though they tell me I do a
lot of different things, I don't actually do much. And I'm still going to get paid the same either
way. Well, they're not really Yeah, they're getting private credit. Yeah, the thing that I
bring that I keep bringing this up, it doesn't seem to hit home with too many. When you go and
file an application with a corporation that has a cage code or a government or whatever cages,
corporate and government entities. I like the terms that they use, like saw, you know,
the patent office, right? You have something usually call it the saw, which is special application
withdrawal system, you know, they put your thing to the saw, right? So anyway, these job fairs with
these companies with cage codes, they have hundreds of these youngsters sign up and fill out these
applications and hand them in. Yeah, I told someone, when they went to one about 10 years ago,
do the application, but don't sign it. Watch what happens. He got followed by three people,
please sign this is no, no, no, I don't feel excited. Please sign it. The moment you sign
your signature, they create the amount of salary off your signature. They have no money to pay
anyone. It's all drawn off your own signature. And then they tell you he's got a tax report,
of course, because you're using private, you're endorsing private credit or, or, or, or, or all
the other BS. It's so simple. It's so simple. So the real kill shot, the ethical moral kill shot
was the money system that was done almost 100 years ago. I see, right. And you're still hanging
around. So which begs the question, when the physical kill shots that you mentioned, maybe
strike fear in them, you don't need the media, right, right? Right. Yeah. So it's going to be
a combination of both, you see. So you figure that a significant quote, what they would call
a monetary collapse or a system collapse, we'll see it immediately. But I mean, a more dramatic
one way to call the money is monopoly money, right? Yeah. Why did Okay, let's briefly discuss
the history of the game monopoly was quote unquote, depression, that people needed to fantasize
with playing a money game, and they use monopoly money, right? That's where you're in right now,
you're in a game that already collapsed. And in other words, there was a perceived economic
collapse in the 30s. So they came up with an op monopoly to keep the people going in a certain
game fashion. And that's actually the real thing. Right now you're in a game, it already collapsed,
can collapse a collapse. Can you was that kind of an oxymoron? Well, no, you get pregnant after
you've been pregnant, can you get killed twice? Well, not all you have to be brought back to
life. Yeah, but not only look, once you have a monopoly game going, right? Look, you already
begin with the premise that the bank owned everything, and then you're given an amount
from the bank, you're given that just to start, everybody gets the same hit this home,
bank doesn't own it, what they have is a higher interest than you. And they could tell you what
to do because they have a higher interest. Oh, hi, no pun intended. higher interest,
meaning a higher place, right? And they consider you whatever they want to consider you a debtor,
a debtor, a tenant, whatever a surface slave, a subject, whatever. Basically, years ago,
there was someone that went in over traffic and driver's license issue. He said this prosecutor
is trying to enslave me. And the judge agreed with him. Yeah, he's trying to enslave you and
prosecute said, Yeah, I'm gonna enslave you. What are you gonna do about it? Everybody's
ganging up on Yeah, we're making you a slave. So what this is in a regular municipal courthouse,
right? In Jersey, by the way, okay, so and they don't mind. So this has got to be cleaned up.
And it will with the movie style reset kind of wipe out. I got you. Well, that's what I meant
by more dramatic. And the thing is, though, when you're playing Monopoly, going back to the
Monopoly idea, yeah, look, it all starts in the box. It all starts in a box, one box, which has
nothing to do with you until you decide to play the game. Then it all does what no matter what
goes on during the game, who wins, who loses, who exchanges what, eventually, it all goes back in
the box. So, you know, what did you actually do reset when the lights go out, everybody goes to
sleep, and you wake up again. There you go. I mean, speaking of waking up again, I put a little
Philip, I was called a dickhead, because I put a Philip K. Dick, which is fine. I get the point
about the simulation, the controllers. I just like the way that Philip K. Dick parses out
phrases. That's why I put it in. Absolutely. And that's not a bad way to look at it as well.
Because, again, as to who is in control or who created the code, there's your question, maybe.
But it appears that there is a code here. OK, there is. Yeah. Go back to the money and God we
trust. It's it's not the God that people hope for to be God. It's the God of this world. Right.
So there's a lot being disclosed. Is there a way to show that the economic system is based on the
monopoly game being fiat, you know, not real. It's pretty real, though, because imagine a game
where it real in terms of physical bodily harm. Aren't weren't there games? I think rollerball
was one of the first one in Death Race 1000 or whatever it was right where they you know,
what is it called? Blood sport. Right. Gladiator type stuff. Yeah. Right. Yeah. That's what you're
living in. It's a it's it's it's all a sport. So the game goes to a sport which is a blood sport.
If someone cuts your guts out because because of a game. Right. That's what's going on.
So, well, and there you go. Look, bottom line. All right. About a lot of this stuff,
as far as I'm concerned, is that we need to recognize that, indeed, it is a game,
but it does affect people. It's brutal. You did mention earlier something a little back and forth.
I'm just going to mention the one line because I thought it was kind of funny for you to say it.
But at the same time, makes sense where, you know, you said something about you can't eat paper.
And I said, well, yeah, OK, you're right. But you can't usually exchange it. It has value. Right.
Yeah. So that's the thing about this is that depending on how you decide to proceed
and depending on what types of paper you get in your hands or digital representations of
things, you know, you can exchange it for some actual real world items. Yeah, sure. Sure. Yep.
And the way that I work, it takes a lot of energy to to do that, you know, hassle. So but either
way, it's it's a is it better to have it in this condition that we're in than not have it? I think
so. Yeah, it does seem that way. I mean, I'm trying to get a down payment for a car. Yikes.
Don't even get me started on that mess. Well, then if the down payment doesn't work, look for
the up payment. I would love to find the up payment. Matter of fact, I've heard stories
about up payments actually recently, and I'm wondering how true it is. But I don't know.
I'm just playing with words because the whole thing is this just bizarre. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Speaking of bizarre. What else have we got? Well, I'm just about tapped out outside of
what else was brought up in chat. I can't even think of anything else outside of, again,
the barrage of questions regarding prophecy. I mean, if you want to speak about that again
or clarify over that. Well, what's what's interesting about prophecy, just look at it as
history. Right. And if you understand that time is not linear, I was very careful to say that that
way. All right. Because the idea of linear time has been challenged, but it's very difficult
concept. Right. It's one of the concepts that I brought up was using the fish analogy. You have
this crazy fish and he comes around and he tells all the other fish, I think we're all in water.
And they look at him like water will show us how we're all in water. You're crazy. Right. But maybe
the one of the last thoughts and thoughts a fish has when it dies is that it's in water. Right. So
if you're one step ahead of the crowd, you're considered a visionary. If you're two steps,
you're considered insane. And if you're three steps ahead of the crowd, it's Greek speak.
You know, just one thing, one last thing about prophecy is I did accidentally stumble across
one of those old Nostradamus things. And it's always interesting how they they pretty much
have piled. I don't know how many different people now. This guy is a composite figure,
more of a composite than even Shakespeare ever was or any of these other odd characters out there.
Sort of portrayed as. Yeah. Just like you could say the Bible is that way, too. But if you start
digging in deep, you'll you'll get a focal point and a nexus point that you could work with.
But it's it's it's fascinating to me how people get so alarmed. And so, you know, it's a trigger.
It's a triggering mechanism now to talk about. But Nostradamus has kind of fallen out of favor.
There's this new guy in South America somewhere who's in his 30s who is being described as a
living Brazilian. Yeah, right. Yeah. Yeah. He brought well, he said that there was going he
was on Veritas TV a while back. Someone sent me a link about hemorrhagic fever is the next thing
they're going to do the real deal. And it has not appeared. So I think that anytime you predict
something bad, people through history are always going to listen and expect it. And when it doesn't
they they're very forgiven, forgiving. So, well, I was going to say that's an interesting thing,
because how many times in history I'm sure you've read some of this stuff where there
have been these doomsday prophets of sorts who have said, look, the world is going to end on
this day in 1892 or 1955 or 1985. It doesn't matter. They claim that there is an absolute
day on the Pope's work schedule that they know is the last day on Earth. And then what happens?
It doesn't work that way. No, never did. And it never did. No, it never did. And it never does.
And here's the funny part is when you start to read these things long enough, you find that this
guy predicted three, four or five times his church did it three, four or five, six times. Yeah. Well,
look, one way to look at it is to relax yourself like the fish. The fish can't tell he's right.
They don't know they're in water. I imagine in my mind, there's another one of me in another world.
It's got whatever different situation than here. And I could communicate with him. And there's
another world with another me. It's in a different situation. I can communicate with them. Right.
On a very subtle level. I mean, that sounds like something they put you in a psych ward for.
But it sounds very much like a dream I had just the other night, by the way. But I actually
felt as though I was actually communicating with myself.
But another self. Another self in different circumstances who had gone through things
slightly differently. And it was very odd. I don't I don't often have dreams like that,
but it was very hard to dream. I was waking up and it was not a dream. And I said, hey,
why am I naked? And there's a mirror here. Let me go look at myself in the mirror. And I was
very bronze colored, dark, olive tone, five foot three tall, very Latin looking.
Wow. Kind of right. I was like, oh, my gosh, that doesn't look like me at all. Usually I
look like Johnny Depp when I was younger. I walk in a restaurant and like if there's a table of
girls or women, look, it's Johnny Depp. You know, that's what I saw as my appearance was. But
anyway, it still is to a degree. So, you know, why did I appear as a five foot something Latin
extraction kind of right? And it was like, Oh, what? Okay, different. You don't have to look
the same to be the same. Right. So anyway, these are just thought forms that exist. And I do borrow
energy from these other worlds, by the way. And I borrow consolence. You know, it's like if I'm
having a hard time here, I'm not having a hard time there. It's it's going to be interesting to
find out how much of that is true later on, isn't it? That can console you just to know that it's
not hard elsewhere. Well, it could be when it's hard there. It's not hard here. I think there's
a law of opposites sort of they did that in the Marvel Comics a long time ago with the bizarro
world or something. Remember? Oh, that was the DC Comics. But yeah, yeah, yeah. So it's all bizarre.
And in the meantime, don't try to make too many friends, but do the right thing as much as
possible. Well, doing the right thing means you got to it sounds sounds to me like you got to
give some love now and then to write because that's what that is, after all, which is to the
And just in closing, I'd like to say, you know, I really wish that I had been more recognized as
Johnny Depp when I was younger. Instead, I got The Undertaker, even despite the fact that I was
probably six inches shorter than him. I got The Undertaker for some reason. I remember that guy,
wrestling guy, long hair, you know, with the beard and sort of, yeah, yeah, sort of look,
he looks like The Undertaker guy. Okay. Anyway, and in Jersey, that was actually helpful now and
but not as helpful as Johnny Depp would have been Johnny Depp. Yeah, it was really easy to
get dates that way. Yeah, not the ones that hang on trees. But anyway, yeah,
but there's nothing wrong with those two.