Rated Y, Sonic Event 209.
Anyhow, Greek, how are you?
Hey, just you.
Yeah, just doing, man.
You brought up the Facebook someone posted or
whatever.
That's Sam or Archon.
It's five more power to him.
I stick with my stuff about the reason
for doing this from the beginning was to
find people a jam with.
I don't mind if someone completely blags.
That means steals everything I'm doing and says
that it's theirs and cusses me out at
the end in the process.
I don't mind as long as it gets
out there, because I see the human condition
as being so piss poor that when you're
really, really piss poor, every penny helps.
Right.
Imagine you're completely piss poor, just living out
in the gutter and someone gives you a
penny.
Isn't that great?
I mean, because it's not, you know, you're
on your way up.
Right.
Look, it's why people will steal the garbage
bags.
When I used to work at a store
and you go, why did somebody have to
steal three garbage bags while I'm doing my
job?
It annoyed the hell out of me because
I got to change the garbage.
It's if you do the math garbage bags,
about 10 cents, maybe more.
But that person doesn't have it.
So just to clarify, Sam's not stealing.
Greek speaks, not sinkers.
That was a project like you want to
do that.
I'm like, I don't know what I want
to do, but, yeah, I'll show up or
whatever.
So it's fine.
More power to him.
But then there's a Jamaican in me and
say, well, I say, start now.
I mean, you don't care about no down
Facebook month, you know, so I don't really,
you know, none of that.
And stick to it, because, look, even now
I got things moving with the water.
I've got things moving, sort of moving with
the audio, a whole bunch of other stuff
going to go back into some mechanical modification
of combustion engines.
This, that and the other.
And it's all being done just to get
it in the field.
Here's the thing.
One of the things that brought me the
most joy in the past two years was
when you get the water device into someone's
hands and they're like, oh, my gosh, this
is the best water ever.
And they're completely unrelated with the last person.
They don't know anything about the last person
who got one who said exactly the same
thing.
So, you know, moving that along, just getting
things out there that just make everything better,
whatever you apply yourself to is really what
I want to do and get other people
on it.
So it is possible for the Greek to
get some satisfaction out of things and not
just look at the entire shit show and
say to hell with it.
It's all garbage.
I don't care.
You actually get satisfaction out of something when
it goes right.
All the time.
It's a joke.
Anyway, forget the jokes.
And Facebook, the only reason why I bring
it up is because people were like, hey,
he said he won't do Facebook.
Why is he on Facebook?
And I just wanted to address it.
That's all.
But it's let's look at, for example, if
you look up Jason Brashear's archaic, I think
there's like 10 accounts on Facebook.
And he's said many times he's been banned
off of Facebook.
So how can it be banned off Facebook
and have 10 accounts?
Well, some people, some people lie and say
that and simultaneously have a Facebook page.
And really nobody ever calls them out.
Some people do that intentionally.
And other people just go and run with
their stuff.
And somehow they get away with it.
So this those platforms, YouTube, sorry, I mean,
however people say I personally view it, our
bottom feeder, the social media, YouTube is all
bottom feeder stuff.
And you like you'll never see a Lamborghini
ad in The New York Times.
Right.
Like think of a bottom feeder newspaper.
You'll never see an ad for Ferrari.
You never see an ad for a really
top notch stuff.
No, you don't have to advertise Porsche.
You don't have to.
Everybody knows what it is.
Everybody knows what a Corvette is.
Everybody knows what a Lamborghini is.
It's not even necessary.
It's vanity at that.
Yeah.
You just want to stay away from that
bottom feeder stuff.
And I've always.
But, you know, I had the advantage of
back in the early 2000s, like before 2010.
This one guy, he's an investment capital investment.
He had a portfolio.
He had like Bunker Trump and that guy,
that late night talk show guy, Larry King,
and always doing their personal finances.
Yeah.
You got to be careful with Larry King.
But go ahead.
Yeah.
But anyway.
He's and his portfolio took a tank around.
This is around 2007, 2008.
He's going through the airport.
Yeah.
Karma's kind of real with Larry, though, because,
you know, he's a bit of a petty
thief.
But go ahead.
Yeah.
But he's this guy was going.
His name is Jim.
And his dad was part of the Filipinos.
CIA guy was part of the Filipino overthrow
of Marcos.
Right.
They did that.
Oh, yeah.
OK.
And, you know, anyway.
So he told me that there's this thing,
YouTube, that Google is going to get in
this thing to stay away from that stuff
because it's all it wasn't even really.
I think Facebook was just coming out around
that time.
Facebook existed right after he did that hot
or not website.
You ever see hot or not?
No.
But anyway, that history of that.
And he got into all the ins and
outs.
And also he was down with the people
who started PayPal and all that.
And I knew someone that was into something
like holistic healing.
And the guy, Peter Thiel.
Yeah.
I very flew in.
He had a foot problem and didn't really
hang out with him.
But so I've been around these people and
the way they casually speak on how negative
these platforms are casually.
It's kind of like here.
Give me a thing.
There's an article that's been on the Web
a while back.
Why do all these famous people have tape
over their cell phone camera?
Have you seen that article?
Yeah.
A hundred different ways.
They reword it and everything.
It's been put out.
I don't know how many.
Yeah.
And all these like they show Bezos.
We know the cell phone's got tape over
the cell phone.
They show who's the Facebook boy.
That boy was Zuckerberg.
Yeah.
He's got camera with tape on it.
And they show this other person who's tape
on their camera on the phone.
And I said, what is it?
What's the deal?
What are they?
Why are they not saying?
Why don't they do it?
Why are they doing that?
Right.
The older version, they used to show you
the laptop with the piece of duct tape
on it, too.
Yeah.
Well, the Lenovo that I have has a
slide switch.
And as you slide it over, you see
a red dot where the camera is supposed
to be like that.
Like they don't have another camera.
You can put a camera right where the
pixels are on the screen and have it
not look like a dead pixel.
You can put a camera in between the
crack of the keys on a keyboard, actually,
if you want to.
And there's a couple of good spots.
Yeah.
Because remember, it's not optical.
We don't do optical, very rare optical photography.
It's all numeric.
If you saw what a cell phone or
a smartphone camera actually sees, the lens, it's
all fisheye.
It's totally distorted.
So they have to numerically.
They know they've mapped out.
It's very simple to do numerically.
You just take a photograph of the grid
and you see how the lines bend in
that fisheye fashion.
And then you do a numeric field adjustment.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Greek, Greek, Greek.
It's already been referenced, right?
So it's all an interpretation.
You might have something in the peripheral part
of the photo.
Stop a minute.
And the photo, you know, the numeric photo
correction takes place.
Greek, Greek, stop.
Can you hear me?
Yeah.
I can hear you.
I can hear you stop a minute because
whatever you're doing is causing you to jump
around like you're a chewed-up cassette Tape
sound you're all over the place like you're
being okay.
That's the whirly gig.
I'm doing some weather work It always works.
I try to make some phone calls.
I set it up yesterday Okay, while I
was doing my setup and the phone would
just not work until I walked really far
away But it just sounded like you walked
near something that was really disrupting you.
So It's the world have you ever seen
a video short video the whirly gig Into
the weather.
No, I've looked at the weather stuff, but
I don't remember the whirly gig.
Yeah, it's a rotating device and It's so
funny because it you'd say it's passive You
can't say it's completely passive because it rotates
with a 30 rpm motor But it really
messes up the whatever the these phones work
on Yes, it's amazing it's a disruption in
many fields which of The ether the ether
which also affects, you know, the the signal
that you get from the Wi-Fi.
Anyway, I'm sorry It was just it was
absolutely useless there for a second No, it
was a good demonstration because if anyone else
can it has the device built because I
always explain how to me Yeah, this is
why I do it like for example here
The weather has been getting warm and it
you know, it's beautiful.
You come out at night in Tucson It's
like a chill.
I'm just want to put a jacket on
but in the day, it'll go up to
hundred three hundred four hundred and Five and
I was tired of that So, you know
the temperature around eleven twelve o'clock is
already at a hundred and then you know
It keeps heating up till about three thirty
four and then it stabilizes at your max
temperature Then it starts to drop again after
five o'clock, right?
Okay, so we had a high of a
hundred and four the other day and I
put the whirly gig on At noon it
was already over a hundred it was a
hundred and four or something And I put
the whirligig on and by one thirty or
two o'clock it dropped it below a
hundred degrees Remember, it's supposed to be getting
hotter and hotter and hotter It dropped at
four or five degrees consistently during the hottest
time of day What when the you know,
the graph the curve is getting going up
not if you say you put it on
when it you know It's big, you know,
if me reached its peak now, it's going
to be going down.
What's coincidental?
No, it actually cooled it on its way
up.
So it's very very effective and I just
want to bring That that's another thing by
the way dabbling with the weather work for
so long.
It's so provable the other thing yesterday I
was doing the weather work and like once
I was trying to make a phone call
and it wouldn't go through It was in
Tucson, Arizona, we had a hundred and three
one thousand and three millibar A Barometric pressure
it was the lowest barometric pressure in the
entire states except for Calgary, but that's Canada.
They don't count Calgary was at one thousand
and two But nowhere in the country was
it below a thousand and eight a thousand
and ten?
Millibar we because of the weather work.
I was doing a drop down to a
thousand three thousand and two millibar They give
me an example anything below a thousand and
ten you can have rain Giving an example
998 millibar is a thunderstorm Anything below 980
is most likely a hurricane.
So in other words, it's 4% humidity
here, right?
30% humidity is pretty normal and toy
you need at least 20% for your
skin to be in good shape It was
4% humidity with one thousand two millibar
and only in Tucson So what I'm trying
to say these are not like does it
work Does it not work, you know, like
when I was working with Jonathan Butts a
natural action tech not to mention They make
these devices like golf balls in the pipe
You know as this structures the water and
you can hardly tell when you use the
device or not anything This stuff is like
in your face.
It just slams you it's like my gosh
Like an example would be in physics if
you make a you give a water device
to a physicist And when you run the
water through it drops it one-tenth of
one degree.
He's like wow that works.
That's amazing one Cuz you know, they measure
things It doesn't matter how much it drops.
It's just that it's dropping it right one
-tenth of one degree.
Wow, that's great Well, the scalarator drops it
one to two degrees Every time consistently what?
That would make a physicist.
I mean to a normal the normie that
doesn't mean much even one two degrees out
any much, right?
So but to a physicist someone who's used
to measuring things critically Because that's what they
do But would be amazed astonished with one
-tenth of one degree imagine and then you
bring in a device that drops it one
or two degrees That's ten to a fold,
you know ten or twenty times more than
that And so in other words the stuff
that I'm dabbling in it's not whether it
works or not or what is it?
It's massive, you know massive influence on the
environment and materials and things like that This
way when someone learns how to make these
things or get involved with it You think
they could really see a change like it
really works, you know I decided to put
that out because when you tell people you
do, you know If you just introduce yourself
and then you introduce you do weather work,
you know the eyes roll and oh You
mean you do weather forecasting or you know
weather measurement?
No, no weather work They can't right now
If I tell ten people in public that
I do weather work weather engineering and then
like five minutes Later ask him what I
said nine out of ten will say yeah,
he's just measuring the weather.
They don't understand You know, it's that you
can actually manipulate it, right?
Well, look anyway another thing since you brought
up Brandon Joe Williams.
I was contacted Let me just get that
name back up in front of me.
I was contacted by Matthew and He was
wondering if Brent, you know Brandon's interested in
either being on rated Y with us or
of course alternatively if you don't want to
do that He could we could do we
have radically.
Well, we're in the same topic but radically
different He kind of brings up the law
side, which is fine And it's kind of
good when people just stand on on their
corner of their square.
I like to say that all four corners
You know look at all aspects, but yeah,
go ahead what about him Matthew?
Yeah, I know Matthew Yeah, it's rather unique
for somebody to want to be a guest.
So do you want to say?
Yes, let's do that Okay I just wanted
to know about that because I have that
message in front of me so I will
concur with him and tell me Let's just
let's just preempt the concept of him as
a guest where he'll have a recording and
he could put it on his channel So
let's just you know that day, you'll find
your cleanest dirty shirt brush your teeth comb
your hair We're gonna be on YouTube.
Yeah, it doesn't matter if I have an
image up or you do.
I don't care.
Whatever.
We'll do it I'm just saying image.
I just said brush your teeth comb your
hair I'm getting to the point where I
just need a toothbrush.
Okay, but it should be it should be
a teeth brush Are you concerned?
I was just gonna say you beat me
to it.
I was just gonna say are you really
that concerned?
I use my teeth brush and after I
mean, I don't have too many left, but
I Actually, I the dentist acquaintance that I
work with, you know, the relationship I would
the dentist is like, yeah, you know I'll
play basketball and after a basketball meet you
at the office.
Tell me what you want to do That's
the relationship I have or you know, I
I sit in the chair and he's like,
all right So what do you want me
to do?
You know, I'm like I just saw him
exactly what you want.
This is how it should be with all
these idiots I'm not it is.
Yeah Mostly idiots and you described this before
you need to know you need to do
your own study and know what it is
You need to ask Attorney a doctor a
dentist even a hair we think about the
hairdresser meme Why don't you sit in the
chair and say what would you like me
to do?
Right?
I'm a little off the top this that
Whatever.
It's the same thing.
You know, you can't trust these people implicitly
on everything because What is it now like
40%?
It's really high Surgeries are either unnecessary or
malpractice as it's like 30 or 2 or
40 percent There's a number thing where it's
either a mistake or something goes wrong or
yeah Yeah, absolutely necessary is like way up
there or they leave 70% Yeah, this
is what they're reporting.
So that means it's much worse, right the
neglect of leaving three sponges inside of you
I don't worry about it.
It won't bother you too much.
You know is where they accidentally leave their
tools in there, you know Yeah studying that
because that might that would be the next
if he into dentistry the next thing would
be surgery and by the way When you
ask a dentist, what is DDS stand for?
That's the most of them forgot and DDS
stands for a doctor of dental Surgery.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Yeah, you can you see the DDS right
after their name?
It's not MD.
I got you Is not a physician by
the way, it's also a computer term.
But good.
Yeah.
No, it's a man Intermix they intermix all
these things but I was studying surgery and
I'm pretty sure that let's say we had
a field hospital I can train anyone in
less than a week on many techniques on
surgery any kind of sir, you know, the
thing is not evasive surgery, but you know
necessary trauma Most surgery should be just implemented
for trauma.
Like for example People that have what they're
diagnosed with cancer.
No one has cancer, but it's diagnosed as
such.
It's a label, right?
And they have a tumor removed.
You never want to have that kind of
thing removed when it's inflammatory or on its
way up You you need to start Quelling
it and making it go away with diet
and other things before you have it removed
because if you remove it when it's growing
and Expanding it's always going to come back
because remember the it's a roadblock, right?
It's to stop energy certain energy Movement in
the body, so you don't want to remove
it when it's in on its way up
you want to remove it on its way
out just like Traffic problem and somebody comes
along and steals your orange Oh, yeah in
the middle You'll just be making more Crashes
and a good example of that is look
at highway crashes during a snowstorm, right?
You don't see the car right there's usually
a hundred car pile up with semi trucks,
you know It's like they don't even know
that there's a pile up in front of
them And it's too late to hit the
brakes when they find out right exactly.
They they wind up running over three cars
that are already crashed Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, and it keeps going on and on
and on.
Yeah, so Yeah, so that's interesting on that
aspect because I'm telling you and I've been
saying for a while We need more people
to understand the physical body and to help
other people with it as we progress in
the shit show known as You know, whatever
society you live in, you know, so anyway
What else you got?
What do you got?
I mean, I think I've just been all
over the place Go ahead you have but
I still have more.
Okay, so kudos to OMG for finally applying
their sonic to the biological vacuum Okay, I'm
gonna shorten this one up Let's see He
said he's had success though with taking a
lot of your medical stuff over the past
10 years and applying it and he wants
you to know that but He also would
like let's see someone who spent those finally
Yeah, mechanical back pain.
Okay, he would like, you know a bit
of a refresher on that stuff because he's
had success on that With issues, you know
with repetition kind of injuries to the back
and if you would generally address that he'd
be appreciative but he's I'll do this and
it's not personal but it is for me
I used to be bedridden for a week
every for several reasons because I've had back
compressions on that but the mental side of
the back pain is when you have a
concept of doom and gloom in your mind,
and it doesn't have to be Forward in
your mind that you discuss it or anything
that just that there's a concept of doom
and gloom One of these psychologists, you know
practicing morons does half-ass get the get
the clue when they start talking to you
About the reason why your back hurts is
because you're carrying around things and it's psychological,
you know Yeah, that kind of it's in
the form of imagery actually So one way
to help mentally back pain is bring up
Catastrophic because you're gonna bring up an image
even if I say bring up an image
of a destroyed city with ten people is
going To be ten different images Even though
they'll be similar bring up an image of
what you consider to be your personal familial
Friendly whatever doom and gloom in your relationships
financial whatever bring up an image of a
destroyed environment And do the the reductionist, you
know The the mace concept on that make
the picture bigger and bigger in your mind
and stop it when it stops getting bigger
You can't make it any bigger I mean
bigger than what you imagine Let's say the
solar system or the universe's then shrink it
down to one pixel and then boom Disappear
it and practice that and that will change
the The the mental feedback and with that
I want to touch on the thyroid but
mechanical I've tried it all I went to
a chiropractor not to mention his name Errol
Turan in New York City He's a he's
a chiropractor for athletes And I think I've
mentioned before when I was in the pro
cycling sort of pro cycling field and other,
you know triathletes runners, whatever Didn't you also
run into Sorenson while you were in New
York to the same guy who wound up
treating Howard Stern with his Back pain and
stuff.
No, I might I went to a bunch
of them and okay No, not only call
sorts and but but here's the thing I
thought I used to always tell people if
you're athletic You can't go to a regular
MD because he's used to seeing old people
people that are really out of shape or
whatever He's gonna look at you and say
you're fine No matter what you have right
because you're an athlete, right?
You have to go to a sports doctor
who's used to seeing people who have a
high level of fitness But anyway, he would
do all this stuff and none of it
really helped And even decompression all this stuff.
So the bone crackers, you know, it's just
another field I'm not saying they're there to
be discounted.
They they they do more mental.
See people think I'm going for a chiropractor
I feel better.
I hear my bones cracking.
So I'm gonna get better.
That's fine But they still don't understand how
the body works.
I mean, I've tried decompression all that stuff
It does What they do does change the
pressure and the distribution temporarily As you said,
it's actually more valuable that you think it's
straightened out.
That's right Then it is that's right, but
it is partially physically valid to change.
Yeah, it is it is temporary It's very
very temporary and you're and you you've already
if you have something that a chiropractor will
relieve You've already facilitated that and that facility
meaning the signal going back and forth It's
like, you know when you go into a
mall, they're playing the same music over and
over That's what I mean by facilitated.
Yeah, you might have some relief But until
you get rid of that background that tells
the body to do that It's always going
to be there and cancer is the same
way All these things are the same way
You have to start with the mental aspect
and if you've got the mental aspect really
strong You could literally be bitten by poisonous
snakes and may and not be Fall fall
victim to it, right?
I mean, that's how powerful the mind is
believe it or not in that crazy group
of chiropractors in New York That was sticking
the you know, the liquid cocaine on a
on a cotton swab up people's nose There
is something to the methodology they were using
even though people were like, you know Outrage
that they were giving people, you know medical
grade cocaine, but there's a hell of a
drug It sure is and from what I
understand the liquid is amazing anyway So speaking
of healthy things and amazing, you know We
did talk about the pet food real quick
and I'll just throw this in and if
you want to continue on the chiropractor Go
ahead Here's a quick throwaway actually shortening it
up again, but he addressed how we brought
up the dog food and the organ meat
and all that stuff and His overall comment.
It wasn't a question He just wanted to
make the observation that it's amazing all the
problems that dogs don't have When you don't
feed them the processed garbage in a bag
And all that smell yeah Like all those
problems from the dog's smell to the dog's
skin issues to the dog's attitude all change
With absolutely better food.
So I just wanted to point that out
that that was something that if people don't
have pets Maybe they think it's a waste
of time.
But believe it or not philosophically.
It's got its uses and it is Truly
a holistic approach dealing with the food solves
a lot of issues for your animals Oh
clearly, it's all the thing is we are
molded from our environment.
You know the material That's formed in the
mother's womb from conception is based on whatever
she inputs into her body, right?
That's obvious, right?
the the blueprint and all that is not
physical but the The right so so that
process by the way continues When you're born
you're constant whatever you're eating like for example
If you know anyone in the military when
they go into the into Korea the bases
there When they get there, they they're like,
oh man, it was okay But everybody smelled
like fish and garlic, right?
Mm-hmm, and then you get used to
it and then they come over here Everybody
there your family and friends.
Here's his man.
You smell like fish and garlic, you know
You're right.
So it's it's inevitable.
You're going to process right?
So once you understand What's going on and
the human body for many reasons and one
of them is when we're the only creature
That's not prepared when it's born.
Maybe a hermit crab or whatever.
We have no fur, you know, we can't
walk around we you know You know like
some way if you know You watch a
horse drop.
Okay, like people like to watch Minutes, it's
up there.
Yeah in a few minutes.
This thing's trotting around like its mother who's
a thoroughbred It's trotting around behind it and
you know, it's fine So yeah, but it's
the same thing.
I was gonna say, you know one who
has a Cattle, you know, they bring the
kid that they bring them in and then
one refuses to come in He goes over
the hill and he sees the cow standing
by a calf Pretty quick just like when
you you know Look when you when you
wake up and you've been in a weird
position You got to like give your body
time like, you know, you say, oh, yeah,
but they're ready to go See, we're not
so we're so dependent on many things That's
the only reason why it takes 30 minutes
though because they were squeezed into the womb.
They were kind of But that's one aspect
you see that we're not prepared here.
So that makes us more sensitive to input
Well, that was my point is that you
know, but but when it comes to human
babies, look we got to carry them around
They can't walk.
They can't talk.
We got to feed them, you know, they
can't chew on anything I mean, they're not
ready for nothing and when they come out,
you know, no, of course for a lot
for quite a while It's called exposure.
All you had to do is leave the
baby naked out in the in the open
and it would die very soon so the
because of that we are extremely extremely sensitive
to our input and food and drink and
when you get along those lines If you're
limited to a diet or you're used to
eating things changing The condiments is the easiest
thing to change and then I haven't gotten
into condiments so, you know, you should always
have time for condiments right to talk about
condiments and That is that changes the energy
Give an example.
I had a burger whenever I get a
McDonald's burger or whatever, which is like very
seldom I say no mustard and they're like,
oh you don't like mustard No, the reason
I want no mustard is because I like
mustard.
Mmm, right because your mustard so crappy It
gives mustard a bad name So but this
time they did no mustard and ketchup and
I took a bite out of it I
was like what the hell, you know, you
need the ketchup and I got some ketchup.
I was like finally nothing now Edible, right
Certain things are necessary.
And you know Greek you keep saying condiments.
I got to tell you what if I
want to have a baby Just saying, you
know Qualified as a joke, but I know
That's okay, but I get you so but
here's the thing the So, what do you
do with condiments, you know?
basically food that's oily fatty Greasy needs acid
and you can what's in horseradish, right?
That that root peppery this ginger Is the
thing that goes in and you can put
that into they put ketchup and mayonnaise together
Yeah, now if you have salt you also
need acid and some sweet, right?
So that's what so that's what I'm saying
that the problem is though Well, don't forget
tomatoes are botanically classified as a berry and
they contain sugar So there are fruit and
a pumpkin is also a fruit.
It has a fruit bearing seed structure There's
many things that are called, you know certain
things It's because tomatoes are in the vegetable
aisle because of food combining they taste they
combine better With other vegetables that combine with
savory foods.
They don't put them in the fruit because
it would be a weird combination, right?
And that's why I always put some direct
sugar into anything I'm working with tomatoes if
I can just to cut down on the
acidity.
Yeah, that's another So your balance of the
thing though by saying condiments, it's the quality
of the condiments is so piss poor now
Even if you go to a Walmart, they
have like the imported foods and stuff You
like I like Santa Cruz peanut butter and
it's the priciest peanut butter You can get
and I go to Walmart and get it
because it's about half price what it is
at the natural grocer Let's say right.
They do give you a break Walmart.
Yeah.
Yeah occasionally So and I've got good at
the organic stuff from there like instead of
spending six bucks for Pomodoro, you know, it's
the whole tomatoes canned You know, it's the
organic stuff is like less than three bucks
and it's actually better than the stuff that
comes from Italy You know the New Yorkers
a ton of call Italy, right?
So well, that's if you're from not quite
in the city if you're from just outside
of the city Italy, you know, you're Italian
anyway, um salt and pepper.
Yeah.
So anyway Quick quick question on the organic
though.
Do you mean the like a great value
organic stuff?
Yeah, great I've actually been getting just on
a side note I've been getting into their
cordless power tools of 30 bucks.
You get a brush with the battery and
charger a Brushless motor drill where if you
got a D wall, you know the yellow
tools or the orange ones There's a hundred
and fifty plus and they work just as
well And I've been addicted to getting their
cordless power tools and just because it's If
the quality is reasonable, it's so cheap I
mean I got a cordless circular saw and
it's like for 50 bucks and the comparable
one of another brand would be three times
four times That and it works just as
well the YouTube reviews on it For example,
everybody's laughing you look I got a Walmart's
cordless circular saw and he starts testing and
he's like I'm surprised They cut this whole
sheet of plywood and did this and that
well guys, you know I don't know what
to say, but it's a pretty good tool,
you know Well, it's like I was shocked
at many you saw that mini saw the
thing that looks almost like an oversized electric
shaver That can actually cut wood Well the
oscillating so I've got a couple of those
as well.
They make a reasonable quality one of those
Over there.
Yeah, they do.
Yeah, that's very very very impressive.
I have fun with that stuff Just like
for example, I drive a 97 I use
a 97 Dodge minivan with faded paint It's
kind of like the ultimate fuck you Right
when you show up somewhere, you know, it's
like why are you driving?
I click you won't see anything that old
anymore.
I go to a parking lot I got
the oldest car, you know other than an
antique car.
That's you know, baby.
No, I got the oldest ugliest That's not
ugly the job at the lines are very
good But it's kind of like saying that
the rest of y'all fuck you, you
know, like your big like middle finger What
the hell are you guys doing trying to
be better than the Joneses?
Running better than a new car.
It's definitely out of place.
But you know, here's the thing aesthetically who
cares functionality and also The the mechanical nature
of the thing when it's functioning properly It's
better on gas than almost any vehicle you
could get that'll carry stuff.
Oh, yeah I've got a put a washer
and dryer in there and you can't do
that with a Ford I mean a big
Ford whatever or a Escalade you can't put
a washer and full-size washer and dryer
in an Escalade Yeah, new SUVs don't have
comparable cargo space Which is weird because you
know, you're gonna pay five times, you know
Even if they produced a brand new one
today, you'd pay five times for your Escalade
or your you know Whatever your rate Land
Rover, whatever the hell but yeah I don't
have the cargo space unless you turn around
and take all the seats out Who wants
to do that when the seat costs more
than half the cars in the lot?
I mean you're taking this out and everything
but yet just some of the cargo space
anyway Yeah, but the idea is it's kind
of like an F you to what people
think they should have because they're not really
thinking Let's go back to condiments The quality
of the condiments should be the best you
can get So if you're gonna use a
mustard try to get a very high quality
one if you're gonna use a ketchup get
an organic one You can make your own
stuff ketchup is just vinegar tomato paste water
and some sweetener Right.
Did you try the Walmart organic?
Ketchup.
Yeah, I do.
I do get that do anything organic.
I look at what Walmart has first Yeah,
I use and they don't make you know,
they don't make anything It's rebirth.
Someone else is making it for them that
qualifies as organic and they're just branding it,
right?
No, they just they just License the label
they tell them you're allowed to label it
for our store.
That's it Yeah, as a matter of fact
that there's a lemonade that I like that's
it's simply whatever It's the same exact one
and it's half almost half price when you
get the Walmart one, right?
Same ingredient same but shape of the bottle
say it tastes just the same actually maybe
a little better So what's interesting but you
know, they got a nice tea matter of
fact, they got a nice tea Walmart does
I don't know if you know because you
you like iced tea, right?
It's it's it's like a really good iced
tea But they dump the same okay the
same stuff that you would pay $2 for
a small can They put it in a
gallon bottle and they charge you like a
buck fifty.
I mean, I'm telling you it's like yeah,
it's that's right It's but they're subsidized just
like the oil industry, you know, they're but
anyway, it's another Thing discussion.
Let's get back to the condiments Understanding the
value of having good condiments and that would
mean spicy stuff also at the appropriate time
If it's getting warm where you are Incorporate
things that grow in hot weather on your
latitude like yes spicy peppers and hot peppers
and things like that But you know mild
I wouldn't go too hot because it does
have a counter effect on the body Get
into citrus get into learning how to use
lemon zest and orange zest, which is the
dry grind ground, right?
Which has the the signal and the energy
learn how to use fermented foods What would
be an example of an American Oh, the
most easiest example for fermented food for the
Westerners would be sauerkraut pickles pickles, right?
Any kind of pickled material learn how to
use those incorporate those like when you go
to a lot of Middle Eastern a Lot
of European especially Asian when they produce a
meal that has a lot of quote-unquote
animal or protein There's always pickles included, right?
I know like this because you pee red,
but you know, they pickle beets as well
You like pickles?
Yeah.
Yeah anything pickling that pickled and canned are
not the same No, no, I mean, but
you can get pickled beets in a glass
jar or you sure I love beets are
wonderful It's there.
Just think about you know, the what the
beet looks like and it's a tonality of
it, right?
I mean That's how you know You got
a good washing machine You get some pickle
if some beet juice on you throw it
in the load and it comes out clean
It's a good washing machine, right?
Yeah for sure Stains things but it also
makes you pee red so don't panic It
can asparagus makes you pee within minutes of
eating it.
It smells just like asparagus, right?
Yeah Definitely like it's like Supposedly because they
produce now.
Here's the thing I was watching Jonah Bay
recently and he's talking about detoxing and I
give the guy a lot of respect I'm
pretty close to endorsing him Mostly, but I
can't really I don't know But anyway, he's
talking people are still talking about detoxing first
of all Anything in your body that you
consider to be a toxin if it's in
your bloodstream lymphatic in your organs your body
created it Because it was in the GI
the gastrointestinal tract Actually, it could be there's
something called the patch various patches And if
you find if you put a tobacco patch
on your skin and you find there's there's
you know Whatever's constituents are in that patch
nicotine in your blood.
Guess what your skin it was created By
your body nothing permeates the skin, right?
So all these so there's the detox People
like I'm gonna detox.
I'm gonna do fruit and berries and water
for a few weeks to get all the
toxins out.
No It's not like something intruded into your
body your body literally produced it So instead
of detoxing trying to clean it out like
they say If you counteract that with an
energetically, let's say opposite opposing saying It will
cancel out in your body and no longer
be a toxin without waiting for it to
go out Eliminate through the elimination pathway.
You see what I mean?
I almost think of it like an antidote
Yeah, I have some related questions to this
too that we can mix in So let's
let's rock on the questions because this is
I'm gonna just start peeling back and talking
more about the biology But here's the thing.
There is no such thing as a detox
and there is a sloughing and cleaning of
the intestines Just like you can clean your
teeth from plaque.
You literally have to scrape it off in
both cases, right?
Right.
So like to clean the intestinal tract is
kale.
There's nothing beats kale Kale that that vegetable
if you eat a little bit of kale
every day It acts like a broom literally
in your GI tract, right?
Especially the large intestine where that's the final
extraction of mostly water right, that's why when
you see someone who has a crack on
their lower lip, that means that the Large
intestine is out of balance in the hydration
mode, right?
That's why you know someone goes out if
you watch like Lords of Arabia the white
of the British They always show them as
having a crack on the lower lip, you
know, they're out there fighting in the desert
Not as balanced as the Arabs, right?
Well, let's all look cracked all the way
around right because yeah, well actually the main
crack I'm discussing is a center crack on
the lower lip.
That's large intestine.
You don't know what wait that split that
shows up Yeah, and it stays there until
you leave the change your diet radically or
leave the environment That's it.
That's where the large intestine is not In
balance with removing getting creating taking the energy
out of water in the final Digestion process
large intestine is mostly to get the hydration
out, right?
The most of the hydration in the body
comes from the mouth throat Part of this
mostly the stomach and then the large intestine
the small intestine is mostly for all of
your real technical Nutrition's but anyway, that's we're
gonna get into all this and I'll show
why From a very basic perspective and I
mentioned also, I think I did mention on
last night You know They say all the
ancients didn't know about the human body, which
the ancient Greeks believe that the blood moved
like a wave Through the body, which is
exactly what it's doing and the heart is
a break Just like you have waves at
the ocean you put breakers to slow it
down, right?
It's the same concept and the wave is
through all of the vessels Anyway, what have
you got in terms of questions?
Because like I said, we're gonna peel back
and discuss more of the biology because look
if you I've known people that were very
wealthy When their health went down they were
miserable They were so pathetic.
So you got to be able to function
So even rich people will tell you oh,
you know all this doesn't really matter as
long as you got your health Yeah, you
know don't emphasize that and because it was
one of the last things you can't just
buy out of a you know Out of
a box somewhere you actually have to do
things.
But anyhow, yeah.
Yeah.
So go ahead.
What are you guys?
So here we go.
Could the idea of absorption of food through
induction be proven by encoding key information?
About a nutrient into an electromagnetic wave that
cells could potentially detect and respond to question
mark Absolutely.
Yes, but not but not an electromagnetic wave
that's commonly available.
It's gonna have to be bio compatible, right?
Because if it is all about reading information
then an EM EM field would Just data
would produce excuse me.
It's too crude.
Yeah, it's too crude the Like for example
If you have a free energy machine that
truly is free energy and you plugged your
toaster in it You put your toast to
come back and it's frosty the snowman.
It's freezing your bread Right.
So what do you know?
What is the toaster supposed to do?
You have to you have to rebuild it,
right?
No, I'm serious there.
It's a negative based.
Yeah.
Yeah Imagine, you know got free energy plug
your toaster.
You come back five minutes later and it's
ice-cold frozen hard.
Well, that's great, right?
No, because now everyone's gonna say your toasters
broken So, yeah, you have to it's the
same thing with electromagnetic waves you're gonna get
Excitement and then a manifestation that it's ain't
gonna be good That's why when people say
they get these wife machines and stuff and
they said does it have AC DC power
supply?
Yeah, it's no no, right.
Okay real quick I just want to let
you know that I did respond to the
Brandon Brandon Joe Williams guy and we're probably
gonna see if we can book for this
coming Tuesday But I'll work that out.
Okay, I'll handle it.
Just just giving you the heads up Okay,
so I had another piece here.
Oh crap.
I pressed the wrong button one second.
I'll get it back but There was let's
see.
Was there a follow-up on that?
I don't think so, but let's just double
check and Let's see.
Oh, okay.
This is a different one.
There was a discussion with a friend about
the depopulation Could it just be an accurate
accounting because people are talking about how the
population is shrinking But he's saying, you know,
because the Chinese are now sort of accounting
for you know Is the fact that their
population is not as big so real I've
been saying that for 20 years Yeah, he
said let's real talk goes into it But
she's looking at it from a mass death
issue along with lying about the real numbers
as their birth rates were never above Yeah,
let's okay Is that right, let me just
say it this way there was a psychological
study this is parallel to it's on a
segue Psychological study which you know just again
they do grunt work where they looked at
sociology for People in college young people in
college and they figured that if you go
to a big College like Zuma sir, you
know UMass University Matt or is Stony Brook
or a big big college obviously you could
have a lot of more friends than if
you went to a College and they did
a study and they found out and if
you went to a big college or just
a little small student body you still had
Really acquainted with three or four or five
people and it was the same people around
you whether you were in a big group
a big Institution or a small institution.
You always had the same number of people
that you associated with So that was interesting
and I would say the same thing goes
for population depopulation.
What are you seeing?
What are you seeing around the environment even
if you're living rural and you don't see
people you're going to go into this town
for a Market, what do you see happening
in your little town?
And by the way, even if I say
little town I'm not excluding places like big
cities because when you live for a long
time in a big city It does start
to feel like a little town Yeah, I
live in a moderately sized or medium-sized
city for America and quite honestly You can
observe that there are less children presence.
That's the way I would do it Yeah,
so for example, there are but you have
to understand trendy, whatever when I lived in
Park Slope, Brooklyn it was becoming yuppified and
gentrified and they Moved in and started having
babies.
So the biggest one of the biggest businesses
in the 90s Park Slope, Brooklyn was baby
strollers Every time you like every other woman
you saw she was pushing a baby stroller
that didn't necessarily work If you were lived
in Morristown, New Jersey that you didn't see
that there, right?
But what I did is they created a
whole bunch of industries not just the strollers
But there were whole sections of baby, you
know, like there'd be a baby section at
the Sears now You know that right in
the 90s a big baby.
This was the gentrification.
So you have these micro trends, but generally
no We're on the way down.
You have to be because the food is
is Toxified it's poisonous At this point not
poisonous, let me just say no, it's not
optimum.
It's a combination of discouraging people from having
children because of the conditions and the fact
that I think we're also kind of being
What you know, what do they call that?
The way you discourage we've got over this
many times people from having children as you
sexualize the society like we've mentioned if you
go A place that has a highly sexualized
society and knock on people's door.
How many children are here?
Let's say none or one or two Maybe
but if you go to a society that
has sexually repressed repressed You knock on the
door how many children you have seven eight
five ten, right?
It doesn't make any sense so the way
you sexually repress a Repressed population is by
when you go into a convenience store Right
behind the cashier point-of-sale.
You got condoms and porn, right?
And all that stuff and then there'll be
no babies but if you sexually repress They're
gonna have a lot of babies, it's the
opposite it's not like farming where you know
In other words, it's the opposite of farming.
If this sexual encouragement is like watering and
fertilizing Nothing grows it's over Don't water.
Yeah, it's over saturation.
You know what I mean?
If you flood the lawn, it's not gonna
grow the grass real well Yeah, but it's
actually the opposite of of what farming is
in terms of energetically It's the opposite the
more you give in that direction the less
Output you're gonna have if you almost ignore
It'll grow better.
Yeah a flooded.
Okay.
In other words, you're not growing stuff in
a swamp plenty of water there But you're
not gonna grow stuff in the swamp You
know what I'm saying?
Because it's over saturation.
That's how I'm looking at it Well, yeah,
but the thing is also I'm looking at
it from point of view like the ether
it always goes backwards It's like it goes
from low to high potential not high to
low Right.
We we live in a society where the
science we're taught is something a high potential
It's always gonna drain into something that's lower
where the ether is the opposite the low
potential feeds the high potential and most human
Character in society functions that way you have
the you have a charismatic Individual at the
deus or the podium on stage and although
less charismatic people are in the audience feeding
energy to him, right?
Right, so he always goes low to high
in the ether also with you doing weather
work Certain types of electrical work, you know,
the dielectric works that way All these things
so that's another way of thinking and both
perspectives are true You know, but anyway, what
else do you got we sound like this
is like the Rambo version of Rated Y.
Yeah, I don't want to ramble too much,
but This is definitely a fun pattern breaker.
Anyways any advice from the Greek on how
to learn a language quickly, especially Yeah, Asian
languages, which have very little in common with
Western languages.
Yes Yes.
Well, why is it that people that live
in a country or as a child grow
up learn the language no matter what?
It's what is it?
Is it because this is how languages work?
No, it's the desire to communicate and it's
You got to be able to go to
a store and talk to somebody in order
to get food Yeah, you know, you got
to be able to desire to communicate right
in the someone who's not good at communicating
is not gonna learn Languages, it's also a
mathematical, you know mathematics is completely artificial It's
a human construct where geometry is not because
you can measure geometries, but you can't measure
math it's a but Fortunately or unfortunately just
like you might say language is a human
construct People that are good at math are
good at learning languages and vice versa So
when you run into someone that's not good
at math you ask them.
How many languages do you know?
One right typically not always but very typical
or people that know many languages if you
ask them if they're good at math They
might say no, but they actually they could
pick up they could learn principles and be
very good at it very quickly But they
don't just think about it because of a
lack of train social Personal personal view of
themselves also, right what they decided what they
what decisions they made about how they're gonna
function Languages There's a desire to communicate now
The thing is when you're speaking another language
and this is accentuated with the French if
you don't put in Vietnamese If you don't
pronounce it, right They just totally ignore you
or if they see that you're trying to
speak French because you're in Paris Anymore because
they have pizza huts there, right?
Yeah, but there's very snobby The Vietnamese will
act like they don't understand what you're saying.
If you just don't have the right intonations,
right?
So that the art is the first thing
you should always learn is the accent like
for example giving there's a you know, the
Fallout video game they did a series on
Amazon.
I loved it By the way, the the
main protagonist in there is a woman a
young lady and she's very British But you
would never get a sense of that she
speaks like totally American born American raised American
spoken.
Yeah, she does the American accent really really
really well and yes, there is an American
accent, by the way, and So you must
get the axe the feeling for the accent
don't how are you gonna get the accent
down if you don't know the Language, right?
You can't so you get a feeling for
the emo a feeling for what it's like
The back of the mouth the top of
the mouth, you know, whatever like for example
Look you can pick up on the cadence
and the intensity all the way words are
spoken that way and that gives you a
good precursor a pretext Yeah, you notice I
haven't even gotten into the language yet because
these things are just as important if not
more important The other thing is whatever language
you want to learn because of internet streaming
go find out the country or whatever region
That has that language and put it stream
on the radio or your listening device The
radio from that country or that nation that
language that you want the talk radio, especially
Yeah, I got a little bit of help
with it with this one time and I
used it for you know a temporary solution
is I took a movie that I was
very familiar with and Changed the language so
that the spoken language was, you know That
language and then put on the subtitles in
English so that yeah, but it was also
it was it Was it a voiceover not
a machine doing it, right?
No.
No, it was a voiceover.
So I think it was probably true to
the Language.
Yeah, they actually used to record and they
still do like stuff like cartoons like the
Simpsons.
They record it in Spanish There's a separate
Spanish speaker good example does Homer and whatever
so you're familiar with that cartoon Maybe you
know Simpsons been around for 30 years.
Sure, you know, but this is exposed It's
a matter of being exposed to it and
then you have to learn it.
Yeah, right.
It's exposure in common stuff, though I'm not
trying to you know, go to well, I
want to be at the Louvre and no
I'm not going to an unfamiliar surrounding I
go to something I'm familiar with and then
inject.
How does that language work in my familiar
setting?
So, what do you think of that?
No, of course.
Okay.
Yeah surround yourself with it, but see again
It's the way your mind works the desire
to communicate get the intonations and the accent
down You still haven't learned any words right
now the way you learn the language, especially
It's going to be very difficult to avoid
reading and writing If you want to learn
a language truly So this is why I'm
going to bring up this point forget about
Rosetta Stone or a lot of other crap
because that's done on the current psychology The
true psychology or the spiritual side of how
languages are learned is as a child, you
know You can have a a child that
hasn't gotten it gotten any schooling or you
know academic training at all and they speak
the language But once they get into like
what they have nursery books Kindergarten first grade,
you know primer grammatic primer.
So what you do is you get a
coloring book from the language you want to
learn Right for the alphabet and basic words
and you actually do the coloring book believe
it or not because when you're coloring in
Let's say the first letter of an alphabet
You're going to be spending a little time
on it right coloring it You're just not
going to be flipping a page so that
that has a another thing where it imprints
again into you And within a few days
Remember if you have the vocabulary of a
five or eight year old in that language
You're pretty okay, because if a five or
eight year old is lost someone finds them
and ask them.
Where's your mommy?
Where's your daddy?
Where do you live?
What's your name?
How are you feeling?
The child can answer all of that.
You're pretty much Okay, right.
So you want to start off forget about
the meet-and-greet stuff, right?
Stuck on you know a tourist stuff forget
about that because that yes, you'll learn the
language that way But you'll be stuck in
that mode You have to do it organically,
which is the way a child learns, right?
Another thing I picked when I was a
kid I wanted to be able to speak
to some of the Spanish-speaking kids, right?
So what did I do?
I went to the library and I got
the dr.
Seuss book You know the cat in the
hat very common It was in my in
my generation the cat in the hat was
a book every kid read it in kindergarten,
right?
So I got that but it was El
Gato in sombrero And in fact, it had
the English page and then the Spanish page
copied every page you open did that No,
yeah, that's that's fine But the thing is
I'm saying is just dive into a primer
which is for example, right people want to
learn Hebrew There's a website in Jerusalem I
mean you literally download the aleph tov a
gobble and all the Hebrew letters on each
page and it gives you a word it
has a picture of what that word means
and There's no English at all.
It's just because it's out of Israel what
they use in Israel for three and four
year olds, right?
That's what I'm saying.
Don't the transfer for example having it in
the language.
You're familiar with the real bridging the language
I don't recommend that I Don't say avoid
it, but I don't I said Go right
into the language without any help your curiosity
will help you remember So when you see
it in your language and then the language
you want to learn that's not very helpful
That's like it's not a form of cheating.
Let's yeah, you know when you get the
answers to a test, right?
you don't want that you you want to
stretch the mind a little bit because Then
you when you stretch your mind and wondering
what the hell is this first letter Just
learn it and then it'll pop up again
later or for this word.
I'm not saying keep it a mystery but
avoid Directly always using the the English to
whatever language you want to learn Again, the
desire to learn the language is very important.
For example, I was not So I was
semi-fluent in Vietnamese because I help people
develop a Vietnamese restaurant Semi-fluent in Korean
Because I had a Korean mobster client and
I wanted to make him show him respect,
right?
I Learned some Korean anything before that.
Yeah, anytime you have somebody who has a
cultural aspect a particular You know where it's
a narrowed cultural group.
You want to be it's a form of
respect Yeah, and just like look at Americans
when you see him in American Let's say
setting when a tourist or someone comes and
they don't speak English.
What are the typical America speak English, man?
You're an American now, right?
You notice how you heard that right?
Oh, yeah Yeah, so that's so you do
the inverse of that when you approach someone
who you want to show respect to They're
like higher than you on the pecking order
You learn their language and you express yourself
in their language.
It makes them feel They know you don't
speak the language but it shows like wow
this person really went to an effort to
accommodate me So you also have to understand
that what learning our language is an accommodation
principle Right and also learning multiple languages will
help you on your path so you might
want to learn a language and it'd be
difficult but I'm saying no matter how difficult
is learn it because if you Learn it
and I'm saying just be semi-fluent because
your average Person uses a hundred two hundred
fifty words a day if you need a
transcript average words, right?
Which is not talking technical stuff.
So if you remember when we used to
memorize phone numbers, you know, right a phone
number is seven words Well, there's no Greek
is seven numbers.
Well write down the write down the numbers
and often numerics.
It's seven words, right?
And so when you do that, you know,
I would remember ten phone numbers easily I
knew I knew my relatives all my relatives
phone numbers friends phone numbers neighbors phone numbers
I would say that any given moment in
that in that era.
I was probably carrying around about 50 numbers
in my head.
That's right Associations to remember them.
So the same thing so They were based
on patterns a lot of them like I
knew how to lay it out on a
key even if I didn't know the Numbers
I knew what how to make the pattern
on the board, you know, so you had
it that was your association The thing is
you can recommend associations, but people naturally have
them where they've decided what they're gonna use
as an association A lot of people already
memorizing ten phone numbers, which is kind of
redundant it's actually useless not redundant to say
that now because You know when someone asks
you for your spouse's phone number You have
to really think about it right because we
don't you just have a cute name for
them on the contacts, right?
I mean how somebody asked, you know for
somebody, you know, can I get your number?
You don't most Exactly.
So this is made a good example for
people under 30 anyone that's under 20 Give
them a dial rotary dial phone.
It's as funny as watching a monkey trying
to fuck a football, right?
That's a try to what is it?
You know, have you that's true though I'd
hope there's a YouTube video and I very
young people and people under 20 trying to
give him a rotary phone That would be
that would be really something I mean they
might get the The touchpad because they're still
they're still familiar maybe with some touchpad stuff,
but the rotary phone is really funny though
I've seen it in real life, by the
way So but here's the thing Back to
the languages you must have a desire once
you learn one language It's a gateway drug
to other things and you're gonna learn other
language much faster because you already know how
to connect right, but the translation there's a
big difference between Translating and learning a language.
That's why I said earlier when you want
to learn what say another language Don't really
rely on the English right next to it.
Try to get away from that and but
I don't know How am I gonna get
into it?
Will you get into it the same a
very young child or infant does in that
country now?
This is not this is what I'm saying
is really top-notch way of learning a
language for about 75% of the time
25% of the time you might want
to just cut to the chase and go
to a YouTube that is if you're visiting
this country as A tourist, what do you
say?
And they give you to you in English
in that language and learn it that way
just to get yourself primed Right.
Sometimes you need to a primer.
I mean a primer like an engine You
got to dump a little extra fuel just
to get it going and see if that
works for you but if you really want
to learn a language most people are not
really learning they're learning how to translate because
They'll give it to you in the language,
you know, and then show you the comparable
No, that is not learning a language that
is translation learning translation, which is very different
Right, so we should do I think I've
given enough clues that about language that I
was thinking of one day doing a mathematics
language Webinar like just like I did the
cooking webinar not yet And just showing what
really works and learning stuff fast.
But okay, what else you got a linguistics
key could be fun How about this look
since I was communicating with Matthew?
He just threw me a question and then
I'll be done with all my questions Okay
regarding Brandon.
Okay.
No, this isn't regarding Brandon.
Actually.
He's asking a question.
He just wanted to run in So we'll
make him happy.
He'll hear this.
I guess he's a so tell him we're
on this doing a sonic right now If
you would to already did, okay, so super
duper good.
Okay, man.
Can't wait to hear it.
Okay Okay, I'd love to know his thoughts
on quote the body attacking itself and quote
if parasites or Microtoxins can cause those symptoms
you can say Matthew asked you may already
be familiar with my case Mm-hmm.
So there it is sort of familiar with
him who he's been going through but here's
the thing.
No, there was no attacking That's the Western
stuff Where you know, I gotta kill the
cancer kill the virus What do you what?
Why are you gonna kill something that your
own body created?
Right?
So what's happening?
The attack is your body is actually Manifesting
the energy from the materials that you've inputted
in it and your environment give you an
example One thing like we mentioned we've discussed
with Matthew early back a few months ago
was why don't you have some raw tuna?
Very powerful, but if it's not working for
you in three or four days, which it
didn't That means that's not the energy that
you need because think of a tuna It's
a fish first of all forget that it's
a tuna because tuna is very specific type
of fish Think of a fish think of
its skeletal structure where its spine is it's
it's the bones are flat spread out The
skin is nothing like yours.
The environment is absolutely nothing like yours It's
a matter of fact The fish body is
so radically different from the environment we are
in that if it's not jiving with you
You're not getting anything out of it right
away like a boost It's actually working against
you because now your body in this environment
is going to try to mimic What the
fishes environment is and that's not a financial
joke, but who's gonna put you under water,
which is gonna make you worse So it
doesn't take very long The stuff that I'm
discussing with the condiments the change of diet
and all that three to seven days If
you don't have a major improvement or change
In three or seven days, that's not you're
not in the right direction.
That's how fast it is Sometimes it's overnight
and give an example with the burdock root
What years of the years ago well years
ago, yes, but recently on these sonics I
told people if you Understand what eating beef
is or you know animal and it gives
you a boost, you know that energy Yeah,
try some burdock root and it'll give you
the same boost and we got a pretty
good response Like yeah, man, Greek said eat
bird.
I got some burdock did it was just
like eating a steak I felt right and
that's a vegetable, right?
Yes People went wild it was immediate.
Yeah So if you so with Matthew if
you're trying various foods and things it should
be immediate improvement immediate Three days to a
week max.
So if you really the three days, he
really 24 hours.
You should feel a difference, but What I'm
trying to say here is many of it
we have to think uncommonly Because yeah, you
know you tuna's got a lot of put
you know, you've you seen a slab of
tuna meat It looks like filet mignon, right?
Yeah, it's very much a strong animal But
it's not as strong as you know animal
that's on the earth You know land.
So One of the easiest things to reset
would be grains But the type of grains
that are the most perky like a brown
rice Sequence when fruit grows it's on its
way down right after the blossom, right?
It's on its way So when you eat
fruit, it's it's going to give you a
little bit You know of what energy you
can get because of the being a fruit
sustenance Ultimately it's going to hang and you're
gonna be feeling like you're going down because
she fruit wants to go down towards the
ground It's gonna be a downer after a
while.
That's it's energetic direction because that's right and
off with a root or the Exactly.
So when you look at grains that grow
especially something that millet Barley wheat brown rice,
they're growing up and up It's actually even
when the fruit the end of the seed
grows The reason it bends down is because
it's so heavy, but it still wants to
go upward, right?
So it's going to be very constructive The
same thing with that is legumes legumes balance
that out because when you see beans grow
they hang down But they're almost the same
geometric pattern So they it's like a positive
and a negative side a sign next to
each other one crosses out the other so
that my recommendation to him was a whole
grains and Legumes which are beans the smaller
the bean the better Even lentils but the
and also a seaweed Seaweed being a plant
Has a very very narrow nutritional value than
Green things that grow on the surface of
the earth, right?
Like if you measure what's in seaweed chemically
It's very basic compared to like something like
Swiss chard or kale or spinach has all
these you know, oxalic acids You know when
you eat a spinach it gives you like
the strips your palate You know that that
makes your teeth feel like they've been sanded
down, right?
That's the oxalic acid You have a lot
of complex things going because it's mitigating, you
know, the effect of sunlight So going for
a root vegetable or a seaweed with the
grain and legume you should have Very positive
results within three days.
Now.
Here's the thing about eating these whole foods
And don't mistake this for processing process because
you're doing it right processed food, but if
you're not used to eating it You're gonna
feel miserable right and What I recommend is
making it in the form of baby food.
So if you're gonna have Legumes for a
few days don't eat them and there's natural
state make like oh you what's that texture?
What do they call that refried beans?
It's like a paste.
Yeah, right.
Yeah, I make a bean soup You know
have a bean, you know, however, you're gonna
have it also but do a variety the
same with the brown rice Don't eat just
the steam, right?
Here's the thing recommending the whole grains for
food.
Most people don't know how to cook it
There was a by the way a documentary
Jira Uno the most prestigious sushi sushi Yeah,
juicy sushi sushi Sushi in Japan and There
was a rice vendor that came to them
and he said the Hyatt Hotel wanted to
buy his rice He had the most exclusive
rice in Japan because I wouldn't sell it
to them because they didn't know how to
cook it Why would you sell rice to
someone who doesn't know how to cook it,
you know?
Cuz then that gives the rice a bad
name, right?
Why are you gonna sell somebody the best
piece of steak in the world if all
they're gonna do is throw it in a
toaster?
Yeah, that's right I've been I worked in
a restaurant for a short time when They
order a rack of lamb well done and
I threw down my thing and I said
they need to go to Jack in the
Box You know if they want that, you
know rack of lamb should be medium rare
at the most.
So anyway So you need to get the
food most digestible so with their grains What
I would do is make something called congee
where you boil The rice down till it
becomes like a paste and mash it up
a little bit.
That's what It's actually a congee soup.
The Chinese soup is just boiled rice till
dissolves into a thick Texture in the soup.
It becomes a weird.
Yeah, it becomes like a weird I guess
almost feel like the Like watery mayonnaise Greasy
no, I was sick.
It's a watery starch What it looks like
that's watery mayonnaise like if you took Mayonnaise
is more grease.
I could say wait.
It's to me is like white axle grease.
But yeah, I get your point Starch always
lays down different than grease in my opinion.
But but here's here's the thing.
I'm bad eyesight, too That's fine.
You I would make a lot of different
varieties of these basic ingredients For example, I
have an abundance of string beans, so I
do a tie a tie string bean stir
-fry then I do Finely chopped string beans
stewed with tomato and onion, which is a
very soft Mediterranean dish, right?
Then you do a steamed String beans in
a peanut sauce.
So I've got string beans three different ways
And if you eat them three days in
a row, you don't feel like you're eating
the same thing Even though it's the same
ingredient.
So you don't do the string beans with
the cheese No, oh the French on you
those who is it the white people do
the mushroom it was an onion soup mushroom
Me not the white people.
There's a Mediterranean version where they put certain
kind of cheese on it.
It's like no, no Never even heard of
it.
Maybe I'll look into it, but it doesn't
sound It's like a cheese and olive oil
kind of comedy.
It's really doesn't sound right, but it it's
If you do a hard cheese, that's very
sharp that always it's all flavor enhancer It's
a condiment by the way a hard good
Parmesan Reggiano Which is not a regular Parmesan
grated.
It acts like a condiment It's a very
sharp like if you have very sharp cheese
a good quality sharp cheese even dare I
say a blue cheese like Maytag or something
That acts more like a condiment in the
body And it's a fermented as well So
anyway, well the cheese go back to the
food recommendation when the body is sort of
attacking itself and atrophy another thing that could
be happening with that is The body is
sending out a signal that it's doing okay
when it's not Let me say that again
This is dramatic, but you know the AZT
stuff and the stuff they you know, there's
no such thing as AIDS No one died
or got sick because the medication is a
hormone That when you take the AIDS medication
It's the hormone that the cells give off
after apoptosis when they're replaced that they have
grown back If you take the hormone the
cells are gonna fall off Anyway, if you
take the hormone the body's gonna think the
cells have grown back and they haven't and
they won't So you start to atrophy?
Right, so that would be if the body
is producing something like that, which is possible
Right almost as if he's taking, you know
AZT and AZT I think was ruled out
They have like ten other drugs now replacement
for it, right?
They have all kinds of stuff now Now
there's preparation to prevent and it makes oh
my god.
Yeah, they got like eight different.
It's it's ridiculous Yeah, that's okay.
I mean let them do what they got
to do You know, if you confront them
on this, you know what they say the
medical people and how do I know this?
No, if you confront them on what they're
doing, they say we don't have a right
to do that You're saying we don't have
a right to exist.
That's what that's sir.
That's their answer to the to what they're
doing, by the way Go they shift you.
Well, yeah, it shifts over to the legal
side, right?
Yeah, there's a weird commercial out there actually
Greek and and it says yeah, this is
great This is you know, this helps prevent
the spread of HIV and AIDS and blah
blah They go through this whole thing and
they show you males females having fun with
each other This and that and you know
laughing and playing drums and then at the
end of it It says, you know all
the warnings one of them says this this
product has not been tested in people assigned
female at birth Oh my gosh.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, let's get off but yeah, it's horrible
But yeah, it's amazing what they're getting you
to volunteer to but anyway, this is the
I'm using this as an analogy So if
the body is producing a certain thing when
I had the circus flu This was after
this was like 2022 23 or something like
that 23 Last year.
Yeah, I was like, oh my gosh.
I got hit with something because the niece
who was living in a condition She was
a carrier of this energy that I picked
up on and it was compatible because she's
related a niece In other words, your sister's
daughter or sister's son is very close to
Maybe people said we even have similar mannerisms,
you know, and we don't even I got
cousins like that It's like you guys kind
of do the same thing.
Yeah, and we know it's been great.
Yeah, it's in there So anyway, I got
really sick and some things I mean you're
gonna die from this or it's gonna get
really bad So I said, well, I know
what's going on.
I need to change the pattern the code
It's kind of like isolating a computer virus,
you know, your computer is running shitty You
got like super super spyware eliminator, wherever it
finally isolates the code Right, and then suddenly
the computer works better, right?
So it's something like that So the body
got into a mode where it was producing
this very very unfit state of existence Where
I was in the middle of the night,
I stopped breathing and I knew it wasn't
breathing It was stopped reading for so long
that I put my hand on my chest.
I'm not breathing I got to get this
going again jumped in a cold shower with
the window open.
It was 35 degrees Outside as well and
that got me back on I said, okay,
this is really stupid So what I did
was I got a really good piece of
chocolate, but if you want to get into
good chocolates Godiva Start off with that you
can get it at CVS Walgreens actually carries
it's like eight nine bucks for a five
ounce bag or six cents worth it I
think there's a little individually wrapped squares at
Walmart even Godiva, I don't know.
Maybe I hope so because then you get
it just they are the chocolatier starting Springboard
chocolatiers lint is not the Hershey's forget it
that that you know, no, it's like saying
Maxwell house is good coffee You know, it's
you'll be happy if you're getting an oil
change and they serve a Maxwell house You'll
be happy waiting for your car.
But no, it's not a good coffee.
It's not even real Dollar General carries the
short bars the small bars to now so
Godiva for Godiva.
Yep.
Oh, excellent Okay, that is your start on
what fine chocolate tastes like there is a
whole slew if you have a market of
local Chocolatiers meaning like they come out of
like San Fran and I don't know about
that You know with places like in the
Northwest some I don't know.
I think I never East Coast source $12
chocolate bars We're talking about the size of
like a regular Hershey's, you know dollar bar.
So but that is a good chocolate There's
a whole bunch of I don't remember there.
But if you want to get started on
good chocolate Godiva, okay, that's your start I'm
not saying just don't say it's got to
be Godiva.
No, but that's your start in quality.
So you have a Whatever chocolate you get
tasted good.
I'd be like, oh wow.
There's a really big difference qualitatively here So
anyway, that Tony that Tony's is not bad
too, by the way on that level sort
of like Godiva Which one Tony's?
Okay, I've never tried it.
Yeah, it's very expensive by the bar, but
Very much worth it.
Their main push is that they don't use
the you know, like the abusive child labor
and all that But oh my gosh, yeah
the quality No, but I don't care about
that.
But the thing is if the quality is
up to par research high quality chocolatiers Yeah,
it doesn't have to be chocolate it could
be cheese right but then what I did
was my way my way of looking at
Wines is I always like a montage a
mix.
I don't get just one grape, you know
in a cab or Merlot Whatever get a
montage where that's several grapes mix.
They tend to agree better There's they're less
critical on adding sulfites or battery acid to
them Even though it still contains some of
it.
So I took a swig of some wine
and the chocolate Went back to sleep three
hours later.
I was fine as if nothing ever happened.
Nothing at all So they just knocked it
out and this is also worked with two
other people That I've been in contact that
thought they had the the kovat thing right
knocked it out right away So it proves
that when they do all killed all the
viruses in the body.
That's what I did, right?
No has nothing to do with that Even
on Wikipedia years ago.
I read on a 2010 2011 I got
interviewed by some very furry people on talk
show And there was a lot of virus
stuff going on in the news back then
and I said, let's look up what it
is even on Wikipedia Virology is a branch
of toxicology and what is known as viruses
are produced in the liver and Expelled out
of the liver into the bloodstream.
Boom.
That is the classic doesn't talk about airborne
doesn't talk about contagion doesn't talk about Injections
as a picking it up on the surface
none of that.
Yes.
Yeah your body creates it again and the
reason I'm saying these things is because for
40 years, I've been reading stuff and the
definitions of branches of the science of physio
of being a physician of physiology and guess
what 99% of the time unless you
get into contagions and Even they're called induced
diseases as a book that I looked at
about tropical fevers and stuff, which is another
thing But everything was produced by the body
and we're looking at the old text, you
know stuff where they really did some hardcore
experimentation on people well, they still do But
And they're putting it in print and I
was like the body's producing everything Then when
I started looking at anatomy cross sections of
skin lung tissue intestines and say how does
anything go through there?
Nothing goes through there.
It's all these layers of water resistant water
repellent actually layers and Closed off with blood
vessels in it.
Nothing is going through so it is induction
just like I read, right?
So but anyway back to the Matthew thing,
so I would break The spell of this
with a good piece of chocolate piece of
hard cheese and some wine if you should
feel it in three or four hours a
difference or an Onset of wellness or better
fitness or a few days.
You don't have to do this.
Don't do this.
It's not a meal I'm not talking about
having a meal of chocolate and wine just
a small amount Of both and wait a
little bit three four hours just like when
you take ibuprofens You take a you take
a fistful ibuprofens, right?
And then you wait three four or five
hours an hour later If you're feeling like
crap, you'll say let me take some more
right?
You don't do that, right?
How is it a seat of my friend?
What is it one works faster?
I think the ibuprofen works faster than the
acetomyophen, right?
They're basically almost the same They are slightly
different chemicals, but yeah, the thing is as
far as their their activity and all that
That's why they put caffeine on the outside
of these things is The combination of the
two.
Yeah, you start I've seen that in a
liquid right they combine a matter of fact
Excedrin itself.
It contains aspirin acetaminophen and Basically the components
of Advil all together.
So it's so it's a cocktail.
That's a definition of a cocktail, right?
That's why it works Actually, okay.
Yeah, that's rapid.
So this is a combination.
So other things to try are Physical and
mental things combination change your mentality change your
physical You might want to get a massage
if you don't get massages You might want
to get some kind of physical therapy if
you don't physical therapy could be a schwitz
Which is you know a hot steam place,
you know Bath massage slash whatever.
I mean use your imagination break break pattern
like Jason Brashear says change your Patterns in
your life and see if that helps Again
the whole grain and legume, you know being
and seaweed would be or and root vegetable
Start off with baby food Consistency not all
the time do like what baby food meal,
you know paste very hydrated with a whole
fruit and eat infrequently because when you eat
a Tremendous amount of energy goes into breaking
these things down, right?
Just like when you have a cold think
of the burning aspect of calories right how
stupid that is If you know anyone especially
I knew someone back in the old old
school boiler coal boilers, they used to heat
the schools They had to go in there
like three four hours before class and they
busted their ass loading the boiler with coal
because it takes A while to get the
coal to burn and then once it gets
burning.
It's so hot.
You'd have to throttle it down, right?
It's a lot of work, you know to
get that going and get it to stabilize
and the same thing with the human body,
that's why When you take these things take
them in small amounts give yourself some time
And that would be that's all I could
recommend The other thing is there's something about
seeing someone in person if you're very intuitive
and you're good at this you almost need
to see Physically see them or train someone
who knows what to look for because there's
very very fine things in someone's character and
their facial Features that features when you're born,
but their condition, you know, like bags under
your eyes as kidneys, right?
This that and the other right?
The bottom of your earlobe a very deep
crease is heart heart is being taxed too
much, right?
There's all these face reading and unfortunately, there's
not much On this online I've picked up
on that from studying Stuff written for years
and years and I started putting and then
speaking to people who did this And then
putting my own version of it together and
you have to be intuitive You also have
to be in good fitness.
If you're not feeling well, you cannot diagnose
someone else, right?
so So all these things, but anyway, it's
going to take a little bit of time
not a lot of time Three days seven
days ten days to see a major change
when you make major changes, but you need
to go into these changes Abruptly because you
don't you want to break what you're what
you're experiencing, but not Radio network