Rated Y, Sonic Event 139, and here we go, Greek, how you doing?
Okay, I need a nap, but this is a good substitute for a nap, right?
Excellent.
You were yawning before we started recording, I was wondering if that was going to continue.
Anyway, look.
Yeah, you know what that means, a yawn, I think we talked about what flatulence is, but a
yawn is when you're, the exchange of nitrogen to oxygen, because you're not absorbing oxygen
and giving off CO2, like they say, oh, that is so, I remember as a child, when they say
you absorb, take in, right, oxygen from the environment, and then you give off CO2, right?
It didn't sound right, because even if you, even if you, how would you say, even if you
establish that, right, and say that's the way it is, it doesn't make any sense, there's
no way, I mean, how does it happen?
And they don't tell you how it happens, right?
Yeah, weirdly, they explained to me when I was a kid, I thought, this is the explanation,
that you take it in and it's got oxygen and all these other things in it, you use the
oxygen and you put back out everything else, and some of the oxygen even comes back out.
But how?
How do you separate it?
Here we go, but then that's where we go with the absorption, you know, where they say we
absorb oxygen.
Or the exchange.
The only way to do that is by ion exchange.
You need something else to do it, and they never get into that, and they give a bullshit
excuse for it, but what that means is the ability to convert the elemental nitrogen
or the compound nitrogen into oxygen is somehow thwarted, delayed, not optimum, right?
That's why, oh, I need some sleep, right?
Because sleep is therapy, recovery.
Right.
And you breathe deeper and you breathe slower and all that stuff during that time, you know,
that's always interesting.
Your heart rate goes down.
And just for a recap, people don't know, what happens is the nitrogen in the air, we're
nitrogen breathers, not oxygen breathers, and the nitrogen, when it meets the lung tissue,
there's a field in the lung, which will get into the ether, there's a field, each organ
has its own composition in nature.
In early Greek speak, I'll get into, by the way, what we might do with, we might want
to recap everything in the future when we start again, or continue or whatever, because
like a reboot, you know, but really go over the subjects again, again, again, and again,
right?
Okay, what's going on is there's some field, or a potential, not field, but a field means
it's already in action.
The potential, just like the block wall and the magnet, you know, the part that doesn't
stick to anything is the potential.
So that part, when the body is ready, again, how does it get ready?
It converts the nitrogen into oxygen.
But in order for it to nitrogen, let's say, if you look at the periodic table, either
the Walter Russell one, or the Mendeleev one, you'll see that as nitrogen descends
into oxygen, it passes carbon, right?
Just like when you take carbon and turn it into iron, it passes nickel.
So you retain those qualities and produce some of it also, and it gets in the mix, right?
And it gives the illusion that there's an exchange, because there is no drop of oxygen
in the air.
You know, if you're in a sealed room, and you say, I'm running out of air, you see it
in movies all the time, right?
I'm running out of air.
The oxygen level doesn't really decrease.
What's going on is the conversion rate of the nitrogen is screwing up the oxygen, the
nitrogen balance, right?
Because of the conversion rate.
That's another discussion.
It can be proven by experimentation.
And there is a decrease in oxygen, because the oxygen then, the ready oxygen, proportionately
decreases, but it's not that you're using up the oxygen.
Sometimes, in some situations, you do require, the body will take the oxygen, but under high
stress.
Right?
Just like, for example, they tell you that, what is it, blood cells are produced in the
bone marrow, right?
Only, okay, how did they figure that out?
They took subjects, and they fasted them, and they had them under closed conditions,
and they noticed that around the end of the bones, you know, where the strands are tied
together, there was an emission.
But under normal conditions, that's not where the blood cells are formed, because remember,
they were under very strict conditions.
That's not normal.
Like, blood pressure testing is not a normal condition, right?
So the conditions that they created are not normal conditions.
In normal conditions, blood cells are produced on the inside part, meaning the outside of
the intestinal walls, right?
So you can, yeah, this is the whole thing on the body.
So once you start looking at this, you can do real research, which the Flexner Report
kind of banned, because if you look at the Flexner Report, which was done in 1910, 1912,
15, or whatever, it said that only exists, listen, he says, this is how the AMA is going
to be run, and only existing techniques and whatever are going to be used.
That's it.
So that means there's no more research, right?
If you make a decree that you're only going to use current and existing techniques, that
means there's, so, right?
So there's no more research.
Well, you can do all the research you want, but you're not going to apply it.
It's not going to be acknowledged, yeah, but it's all based on the military's need for
medicine.
That's why there is research, to a degree, for injuries.
So anyway, that was a big tangent, where the original thing is the Bar Association, right?
Did I bring that up?
We're going to talk about that?
You did mention the Bar Association, but we didn't get there yet, today, anyway.
I was asking you about the ether, and then we got into this thing about the oxygen, so
yeah.
Someone put a Bar Association in the chat, I think, Vandy, what does it stand for?
And that's an age-old question, no one knows, and some say the British Accreditation Regency.
All of the stuff online about them is bullshit, as they are.
Well, does it have anything to do with where they say you go for a side bar, like they
literally say it's a bar?
Yeah, well, the bar is the architecture, it's an architectural element, and there's two
of them, the one in the back and the one in the front.
And it's part of a procedure that they have, it's a ritual.
I think, like, when Christopher Hauser did his research about justice, it's based on
the Greek goddess D-I-K-E, on the Isle of Lesbos, can't make that up, right?
Also interesting that the judge speaks from a bench, and yet the entire audience is sitting
on what I would identify as benches, every courtroom in the world pretty much looks like
that, right?
Yeah, but this is an old tradition, and it's gone away with you, okay.
The bar association is one of those organizations like the CDC.
It doesn't, CDC is a private, like CNN.
So it's a private company that serves a function.
Yeah, but it's an association, okay.
Associations are like Boy Scouts, Sierra Club, Girl Scouts, those are associations, Boy Scout
Association.
It's actually a format for forming an organization, like a title, which is another thing, Brandon
Joe came up with, why don't we just do organizations and no corporations or trustees?
Because when you have an organization, you don't require a charter, right?
So because I remember having trust, well, I still do, and they use it, and they're like,
oh, we want to see your trust.
And I was like, oh, I don't like to see the trust.
But so what you do is a certificate of trust, right, and you have them have it on file.
And it's a lot of paperwork.
Yeah, with an organization, all you need is an organizational principle.
All you got to say is you're an organization and that's enough.
You don't need to show anything, any bylaws or rules or charters or organizational founding
documents.
No, okay.
That would be the way to go.
And also conferring nationality, which I've been thinking about, because now that when
Brandon brought up, you can confer nationality, however, and by whatever means, right, necessary
or possible.
I can say right now I'm conferring the nationality of Finland on us, both of us, and you agree
for this sonic event, at the end of the sonic event, well, we're going to confer the nationality
of, I don't know, Spain on us.
And that makes us that nationality, because I remember when I went to expatriate and everybody
was kind of like the vice counselor, who's the head honcho of the embassy, he's like,
I don't know, you know, you really, you know, do you really want to?
It's like, you guys don't really know what you got to do to say it, right?
Well, it's interesting.
It's almost like that one guy who declared himself, you know, just a citizen of the world.
Right.
He said, I'm just a citizen of the planet.
It helps it.
Well, the title states that it would allegiance to a state, which is a group of people.
So the world as a state, you could say United Nations, which doesn't have a geographical
list.
You don't have to have a geography to be a state.
But let's bounce back to the Bar Association.
There, there was a, I still, you know, Mandela effect.
I'm really, really a big proponent of it, because I remember reading stuff, even holding
a book in my hand and then recalling it five years later, I can't find the book, can't
find the author, can't find any of it.
Right.
But what you'll find is commentary, federal, retired federal judges, several of them have
written books on how corrupt the system is.
Right.
And they always talk bad about the lower courts, but also what they're doing.
But one federal judge went into the history and the whole thing about attorneys, the main
crux of attorneys is that they were most popular in a feudal state because the feudal slaves
and serfs couldn't go in front of the lords, you know, the landlords that would be represented.
And it just means that, you know, you're giving up 30 percent every time you deal with these
guys.
Same as today.
But in ancient Greece, there were a bunch of academics that were trained in arguing
and winning arguments and debates.
And they were so highly educated and they always bitched about not making as much money
as other people who were less educated.
So what they started doing is started accusing wealthy people of things and arguing it to
the point where they made them look like they actually were guilty.
So the wealth.
So the wealthy people would give them fees and retainers to leave them alone.
And that's how the the attorney culture started in ancient Greece or I'm sure in other places
that were just as sophisticated.
Right.
Sounds like talking basic protection record.
But go ahead.
Yeah.
Just like wealthy people have an attorney on.
It's the same.
Right.
Same thing.
I personally think they're scumbags.
Now, as a group, as a whole, you could just get a stamp, write scumbag and put it on their
forehead and it would be apropos.
But I don't want to base that just on opinion.
But the word opinion, when you look it up, it's a judgment or decision made on with very
little or no knowledge based on no judgment or decision based on very little or no knowledge.
Right.
So I can back it up with a lot of things now.
Well, what would you call an opinion that's actually backed up by knowledge?
It's got to have a different name.
Then.
Yeah.
Then it's not an opinion.
That's more of a fact.
But the now what happens, as I've mentioned, with very little exception, there are people
that want to go into the trade and they find out what it's about.
Now they're stuck because now they got to go do something else.
So you got to give them two weeks to two years to transition.
The same with the medical.
Right.
Usually if you see an old attorney or whatever, that's talking about serious scumbaggery there.
Mm hmm.
Very serious.
It's a bar.
I think in Eastwood used to use that term a lot.
A lot.
Yeah.
They're not good people at all.
There's no such thing as a good attorney.
You might have a more competent one, but none of them know any law at all.
I want to go.
Let me go back inside.
I just came outside.
I'm going to go back inside the house and go in front of the computer recently pulled
up.
There's you know, they do court cases online.
Right.
Yeah.
Video tape.
This one is a more of a proper tribunal.
They have three judges about some kind of bill of exchange.
They railroaded this guy into that it was a it was a fake instrument or bogus instrument,
which is bullshit.
It's not in the law.
There's no such thing as a bogus bill of exchange.
But it's it's the name of the YouTube.
You could watch it if you even if you're not really well versed in law, you'll see what's
going on.
It's actually best if you don't know the laws to watch it, you'll get a feeling of something's
wrong here.
And then when you start learning the law, you'll see what kind of a bunch of jokers
and morons these people are.
It's the Law Chronicles is the YouTube channel, the The Law Chronicles.
And the YouTube is from two years ago.
It's called Bills of Exchange Court Appeal SF, California.
I want to see a bunch of idiots and jokers.
They they give.
But what's interesting, if you don't know any laws at all, you'll say, but wait, it sounds
like they know the laws or using law.
It sounds like they are.
But once you study, like I said, if you study law definitions, not the laws themselves, but
the definition.
So each group of law has a title or a section or a subchapter that defines what's in the
group of law.
And that group of law could be hundreds of pages.
But don't delve into that.
Just read the definitions, right?
So if you it doesn't take very long to get familiar with the definitions of a few minutes
a day on each section, you will know more than all the attorneys in the country, because
if there are three, let's say two million attorneys in the country, which two million
times zero is still zero.
So that's how you will know that much more than all of these guys.
It's a joke.
It's kind of like when you say, you know, the pope's work schedule, you go to, you know,
what he taught.
I've never heard of it put that way.
This is the attorneys.
They know no law.
Yeah, it's a scourge.
They're a scourge on society.
Now, are they bad people, inherently bad people?
No, because you can take a wrong turn in life and want to do that.
Right.
But they're not good people.
Like I have a thing that if I offer several devices and things that I do for people, if
you're an attorney, I'm not.
You're not getting my stuff.
Sorry.
You know, if you're a judge, attorney or an M.D., you're not getting a scale rate or you're
not getting accuracy.
Argentum.
Sorry, dude.
Go get go.
Take your medicine.
You know, I'm biased towards them and I don't think they deserve better things.
That's my opinion on that.
Right.
Because someone else might say they do deserve it.
Fair and equal.
Right.
But is that a point of view based on little knowledge?
That's part of you based on my personal bias against them, but not based on knowledge.
And the knowledge base that I have accrued about them has led me to that as my opinion.
OK, because I can't tell someone else.
Well, it would look if I were king for a day, I say that's it.
No, no.
Don't.
If you're an attorney, you're not allowed to come into any store, buy anything.
I would definitely say that.
I would definitely push that on people if I had the power to do that.
Right.
So you can't buy food.
You can't buy clothes.
You can't get gasoline.
Right.
So to starve them out of organized society.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I would.
That would be a good way to go.
So that that's how bad it is.
Now, they know in law, if you have to prove intent, it's going to be hard to prove that
all of them are bad.
Like I said, they're not bad, but they're not good.
Right.
Just because someone's not directly bad doesn't mean that they're good either.
Most of them are just imbeciles.
They're just doing it for a paycheck, like everybody else out there doing something for
a paycheck to feed their family.
But you should actually, after being working in the field for three or four months or even
two weeks, know like, wait a second, you know, but they have a really good way.
I've spoken to people working in banking and they're like, well, why does the bank endorse
it?
This all because that shows that there's a lien.
Everybody goes, oh, OK.
And there is no lien.
You know, the bank is taking your stuff, right?
You know, like the part where you run down your bank account and the bank transfers it
over to a part of the bank that you don't see and they take it from you.
They tell their own people, well, oh, that's because we have a lien on it or something.
And they're like, OK, that's a good reason.
Because if you ask for too many reasons, you may not get a paycheck.
Right.
If you ask too many questions.
Yeah, that's exactly what happens.
Yeah.
So that's so again, but but it shouldn't be that way because everything's already been
paid for.
It's a really fucked up place we live in.
Now, the MDs are just as bad, by the way.
Not very.
None of them know how.
OK.
If you listen to Greek speak for like six months, you'll know more than all the doctors
in the U.S. put together.
Because how many doctors are two million?
What's two million times?
Zero.
Still zero.
Yeah.
Right.
Now, we're not talking a procedure.
Oh, by the way, I have spoken to surgeons.
Right.
Major surgeries, too, like 18 hours.
And they take a break and they come back for 12 more hours.
That kind of surgery.
Right.
OK.
I'm like, well, how do you, you know, basically having a discussion a little bit, then how
does the body.
How do you anticipate recovery and convalescence?
Oh, the body heals itself.
The body heals itself.
Chop.
You know, the body heals itself.
They don't know about doing anything to assist it to heal.
Right.
At all.
They don't know how it works at all.
They admit it.
We don't know.
Well, they'll start.
Yeah.
But, you know, they'd rather not talk about it.
They don't know.
Right.
Which I say is a testament to the robustness of the human condition in the human body.
You are so robust that you can actually.
The human body can take so much, quote unquote, neglect and abuse and still recover.
That's why they're getting away with what they're getting away with.
Right.
So the Bar Association, I don't know what it stands for.
I think they just it was called the crown also.
And in Canada, I think Australia may be most likely that many a lot of ministry stuff in
Australia and New Zealand, all the other places of where England is or was.
They call it ministries and crown.
But it's it's borrowed.
It's the typical pagan stuff.
I haven't used that term in a long time.
Pagan just means ignorant.
It just means ignorant.
They're just ignorant.
So, yeah, it's it's negative.
But that's part of the here's the thing.
If you're just passing through here and like for me, I know and with all my intuition that
I was I'm here because of an administrative error, somebody stamped either for me to come
here at this time.
They fucked up.
So I have to go through this.
Right.
I know I don't belong here.
Let me put it this way.
From when you're six years old, you flip a coin or 10 years old, sometimes you flip a
coin to see or the, you know, the eight ball thing.
Yes or no.
Whatever.
Yeah.
Flip the coin every time I flip a coin or do any kind of, quote unquote, quick divination
on that.
You know, the quick, you know, ask the gods a lot every time.
Not, you know, nine out of ten, but ten out of ten.
Every time it comes out that I shouldn't be here when I cast lots, I could cast lots,
you know, pulling straws every time because I shouldn't be or shouldn't be or should it
solid.
So from a casting box, which is biblically lawful, by the way, it's a form of divination.
Right. Because you're not OK.
Anyway, that's the Bar Association.
We don't know. We don't care because they shouldn't even I shouldn't say this.
But one time I had a discussion with an assistant D.A.
and brought up some things that they were doing and they just stopped and said, are you
saying we don't have a right to exist?
I didn't even bring up anything ensuing that.
Right. That's how they think.
They're on the defensive.
Now, again, if you don't know law now, you know how, you know, law is the definitions
of law, not the laws themselves.
How can you know law? There's like five hundred books and there are five hundred pages
thick. No, it's the definitions that you need to know to apply it.
Right. See, like words are tools and the definition of the word is how you use that tool.
Right. Right. You could use a screwdriver, a Phillips screwdriver or a Torx
screwdriver. You know, the ones that have the five or eight faces.
Right. OK. Spline screwdrivers, flathead screwdriver.
You know, that'll make a fine paint stirrer.
You know, if you have a small container of paint, you can chip ice with it, too.
Yeah. Right. Chip ice with you while your fridge is plugged in and then wonder why it
doesn't get cold anymore. Right.
So that happens often.
And so but you see what I mean, it's that's not that's it's not being used as defined,
like the word nice is not being used as defined.
So they're really a bad thing.
But they're there. They're here.
There's their purpose here is to move things along that actually prevents more controversy
than there would be without them, without law.
And they're part of the scourge.
It just reminds you like, you know, this is not a good place and they will always be here
until the place is redone.
You're not going to change it.
Just avoid them. But just really here to keep things in motion, pretty much.
Yeah. Yeah. And I've got it.
I've been studying these idiots for 30 years now, three decades, pretty on it pretty
earnestly since 2003.
And especially from people who have family members that work in the law field.
And they're like, yeah, they really don't know anything.
I was in some Greeks who asked some questions and they answered exactly.
They said exactly what you said they would.
Great. Duh.
Yeah. Talk about like doing nothing.
But anyway, but that's how that's how things run.
That's how things work. By the way, if you want to know, it's not indirect.
Go. There's plenty of attorney generals that have been quoted in newspaper articles and
journalism. Let's say that, you know, it's not who reads the newspaper now.
It's on the Internet. Right. Right.
So there's plenty of attorney general quotes.
Go, go read them, all of them.
And you tell me this is like some bum out of the eighth grade that's trying to bully
someone. Right. Have you ever noticed how they speak?
Yeah. Not smart at all.
These people are like, oh, the one that was in the spotlight and it was the most verbose
probably since the 70s was that Eric Holder guy.
It's like every time he said something, he put his foot in his mouth.
Right. Right.
And but they all do.
But people are just raised.
I mean, it's a very bad situation.
But is it any worse than having the Catholic Church in your country?
Think about it. Yeah, could be like the worst possible thing is to be Catholic and
attorney, a Catholic attorney.
Can you imagine now you win the ticket?
You win the prize.
Yeah, because I mean, how do you get any worse than that?
I don't know that, you know.
Yeah. You won the prize.
You know, they put the big medals on the medals, like 20 pounds, you know.
You win it. You won.
Yeah, it's it's bad.
That's the gold standard knowledge.
That's the gold standard for being a shit.
The absolute worst thing that could be around.
Yeah. Oh, my gosh.
Yeah. And that's not let's just say that's an opinion, but it's based on a lot of
fact. So, OK.
So, yeah, that question about the ether, though, where I started to begin with,
though, the question that came to me was, is there more than one type of ether?
That was the big question.
No. Yeah. Yes.
Man, man. OK.
Ernst Lehr was I'm paraphrasing here because I haven't been into Steiner for a
long time. Too airy fairy for me.
Get to the point.
People, it's kind of like, you know, the charismatic professor and all the young
girls and ladies like sitting in the front and they will go over, you know, kind of
thing. OK. But that's the point where the guys were doing that with Steiner, too,
you know. But he had a secretary, Ernst Lehr, and Ernst Lehr waited until
Steiner passed before he wrote the book Man or Matter, because Steiner was such an
asshole. The last thing you want is criticism from your boss, who's an asshole.
Right. Yeah, of course.
Yeah. It just makes it doubly worse.
Right. And it's almost worse than having a boss, a boss who's Dutch, you know, from
Holland. I don't think I've ever had.
So, yeah, you don't want to know.
Now, the wife is Dutch.
So, yeah, but she's I don't know.
She's the boss. It doesn't matter.
But, yeah, you don't want to work for a Dutchman or woman or from Holland.
Yeah. Anyway, so he waited.
I'm paraphrasing here.
And Man or Matter gets into the four ethers.
You have the light ether, the heat ether, the life ether and the chemical ether.
And they each have corresponding shapes and colors.
I don't I don't get into that because in order to subdivide the ether means you have to
know enough to subdivide it.
And I don't think we really know enough about it because we're it's the common substrate
of all things. And because it's a common substrate of all things, you can't see it.
You're you're barred from you're barred from objectifying.
You know, because it's so common, there's no contrast to it in our current space.
So and just just as a quick question, though, Man or Matter, you're talking about an
introduction to a spiritual understanding of that book, right?
Yeah. Yeah. So what I don't know the year I'm outside again, so I'm not in front of the
laptop. No problem.
But they did. What year was it?
A third edition.
30s. What was it?
Well, no, a third edition was published in 2014, apparently.
So. Yeah, yeah. Good, good.
That's again, there's too much a lot of Steinerism.
Now, don't don't take it that Steiner stuff isn't good.
I'm not saying that at all. It's brilliant.
But it's just the way that he puts it out is just get to the point, dude, you know, and
your your ideas of cosmology are fine.
You know, you should keep half of it to yourself and tell us what works in the meantime.
But it's just what happens.
What I'm saying is when you get to know people, like if you are a sensitive and very
sensible person, like if you read a lot of people, OK, if you read the Bible and you
find yourself in the setting, like you can almost sense the setting, you know, the
light. Is it a cloudy day?
Is it a sunny day?
Is it winter? Is it summer?
You know, what's the feeling if you if you're like that, like you can pick up a book
and start reading and you get the setting so much like you're there.
Right. They've actually done Disney movies like that, where they open a book and then
suddenly you're in the book. Right.
Right. Right. Yeah. Children's movies and things like that.
Yeah. They do that transition, that visual like they open the book and then they fill.
Yeah, that's a good point. If you can transition into the setting of what you're
reading, you'll pick up a lot of stuff with Steiner and you'll be like, oh, man, this.
No, no. But but I know there's something I can use and it's worthwhile here.
But the rest of it, no, not for me.
And it's kind of like the same mentality that one of those short, short
novelettes that the Lonely Housewives in the 70s, where it was a big boom of these
little. Who is that, Fabio?
The long they they they made these.
Oh, he was one of them. Yeah.
The little like the tawdry little sex novels, like they were romance
romance novels or whatever they call romance novels.
Yeah. He's like a he's like a new age romance novel, whatever.
No, don't buy it for me.
Doesn't work. But he does put out some good stuff and he gets into the ether or
whatever. Am I knocking Steiner?
Yeah, you could take me knocking Steiner.
The Steiner put forward some really good work and that you could use a lot of it.
Yeah, absolutely.
So you have to sift through it.
It's not necessarily like trying to have said this in a long time, eating
undigested corn out of somebody's poo.
It's not like that. Right.
What do you mean? That corn is perfectly good.
Right. So who wants it after it's been?
Yeah. You never you know, I'm the only one who gives analogies like that.
So. Right.
But you're not it's not that bad.
It's not that bad. The mainstream media is like that.
If you're trying to study something based on what the mainstream media put out,
you're definitely eating undigested corn out of somebody's poop.
It is much like trying to sift through that and get it back out.
Yeah, that's true. Like, you know, searching for a needle in a needle stack,
for God's sake, that's what you do.
Actually. Yeah, right.
That would be a needle haystacks.
Easy. You just get a strong magnet or not so strong magnet, a broad magnet.
You'll find it fast.
That's why I said a needle in a needle stack, right?
Yeah, that's right. Yeah. But then which needle?
Yeah, exactly. Which needle?
Real quick. The ether. Yeah. Yeah.
Sorry. No, I get back to the ether.
We don't know enough about it because it's the substrate.
We cannot objectify it.
Right. Fair. Like. Yeah.
It's like asking, hey, I what voltage is it running?
And, you know, what am I? What what are you, AI?
You know? Yeah, that gets in some weird space
because I've seen people do that with the A.I.
And a lot of people are starting to do like little substats
about their conversations with A.I. now.
And it's kind of interesting, I think.
But real fast, the Bar Association thing.
Last thing is they mentioned in the chat, you know, like it's all in all caps.
And again, that's that means that it's something that's not
real thing, right? Because.
Well, yeah. Well, yeah, it's a true.
If you look up the style manuals, every country
in the U.S., they buried the style manuals, except for, I think.
Kansas and Ohio, you can find style manual.
And basically it's grammar.
You know, it's improper whenever you see it.
OK, in the third grade, if you wrote your name in all caps, you fail.
They'll fail you.
Third grade and penmanship class is improper.
So in order to justify why the improper spelling,
they have to define it in what's called a style manual.
Every every recently, the United States style manual resurfaced online, I heard.
And they basically tell you if it's in all caps, it's either an acronym,
abbreviation or trust, legal fiction or corporation.
And so in this case, it would be a trust because it's not a corporation
or a legal fiction. OK. Yeah.
OK, so that's what Bar Association is.
So the last thing we know, we don't know what it is.
We know who it encompasses.
Oh, by the way, there is no license to practice law.
There is no such thing.
It's a bar card. It's a membership card.
It's like saying I have a license to be a Boy Scout.
And the Boy Scout pulls out his membership to the BSA Boy Scouts Association.
I have one of those.
I from 1972 or 1973.
It is always a membership card.
Yeah, and I had one a little later, a couple of years later,
because I'm BSA with the eagle, the phoenix or whatever it is. Yeah.
So the last thing, though, is that you were talking about
Chad GPT just before we started also.
And the thing is this.
I'm watching people write and have these weird conversations.
And, you know, you ask Chad GPT what it is.
And you and I talked about this way earlier.
I forget which sonic way back, though, where we talked about it on Rated Y here.
And and I said, what do you think of this?
You know, what is your and you just said, well, it's really nothing yet.
Uh, do you still think that way or do you think it's
no, I'm with Archaic's on this and I didn't he put it together.
He's got more because this whole thing is Archaic's, which is art.
It's based on artificial intelligence X, whatever.
That's the accurate way.
But years ago, I've said that this whole thing runs on an artificial intelligence
very simply, just like you have self-driving cars, right?
When you're the OK, when you're the boss,
you hire people to do stuff for you, like the captain of a ship, right?
Doesn't do anything, right?
Yeah. I mean, physically do anything or perform any tasks.
He's the captain. Right.
But let's say you have a really advanced ship.
Is it possible to have the captain on the ship and the whole thing is automated?
The dog. Yeah.
Actually, that's offered right now.
Right now on any kind of ship.
So for having it fully, it's just need more sensors.
And I was arguing with someone at the smoke shop recently about AI.
And so that's all sensors, man.
There's no way the more sensors, the more sensitive it gets. Right.
So anyway, you know, the self-driving cars work on sensors.
That's all. The more there's just smaller, miniaturized sensors
and all networked together and feeding, you know, tasks, information tasks.
Yeah. And that's all it is.
And anyway, so if you're the boss and you have a crew doing stuff for you,
can they be replaced by a machine? Yeah, of course.
And that's all it is.
And so basically everything is run by something
that is not how we normally see things running.
Like I know the weather is run by some kind of organic AI.
I know that because I interact with it. Right.
Not on a cognitive level, like I talk to it because they do weather work.
I see what it's doing. Right. Right.
And I know if I know when to do weather work and when not to do weather work.
And when you figure that out, you're like, oh, yeah,
I'm dealing with an intelligent thing here.
So the common people will be fooled by it,
just like they're fooled by everything, the shot, the vax. Right. Right.
Okay. Don't they know there's no such thing as, oh, by the way, tangent.
They're starting to spray New York City fumigate for West Nile mosquitoes.
Guess what you're going to see in about a month to three months.
Babies crippled polio.
Polio. There's no such thing as polio. Right.
Well, they just said they had a few cases pop up for the first time
in like 60, 70 years in in Palestine, in Palestine.
They just had a few of them pop up. Oh, yeah. Yeah. They're spraying.
Yeah. They could also be weaponized.
You could spray the stuff and cripple everyone. It's a neurotoxin.
Yeah. This is not a conspiracy theory.
This is proven.
There was over a dozen doctors that went to Congress
to ban DDT because there was stuff again
with Jason talks about insects appearing and things.
But all through the teens, 20s, 30s and even as late in the 50s,
a lot of medium sized towns throughout the US during the busy time of day
on mainstream, I mean, Main Street and busy time of day.
Swarms of flies would show up like something out of the Book of Exodus
enough that the swarm would cast a shadow over the street.
Right. Like people would be horrified by it. Right. Right.
So they had these DDT trucks going around. Right.
And then suddenly young children and adults couldn't walk.
And they said it was right.
A polio and they did a vaccine, which didn't do any of this.
And there was doctors that went to Congress.
And there was a woman that wrote a book, Spring Time, something,
and who said there's no such thing as polio.
It's the DDT spray. Right.
But, you know, as long as it's not acknowledged by the authorities
and the people look at the authorities, they're going to believe.
So anyway, what I'm saying is in New York City,
it depends on how much spraying they do.
Watch out for babies. That'll be crippled.
And then they're going to say it's a virus and it's not.
You know, so it's pretty insidious.
Talk about the Bar Association.
And now, you know, why lawyers and doctors don't get scaler, right?
Yeah. And so and by the way, there's two of them that have been denied already.
So good. Well, you know, 50, 60 years ago,
there were plenty of things where the U.S.
government finally did admit that they sprayed a whole bunch of crap in New York.
They sprayed stuff in the subway and they did all kinds of specially.
They did radioactivity and bio and chemical.
And there was even that lawsuit in New Jersey, which is another fun thing
is, you know, people say there's no such thing as chemtrails.
Well, there's artificial clouds that are created.
No, there's no such thing as chemtrails.
But if you look up stratospheric aerosol injection, it's fully acknowledged.
Yeah. And not only that, but why is it that the state of New Jersey
would turn around and sue other places over the fact that this stuff
was being generated and there were artificial clouds being created over the state?
So they're just trying to generate revenue.
They don't care. But that happened in the 70s, by the way.
No, no, no. I get you.
But from the stuff that's been released,
but I think there was someone who was hammering the foyers
back in the early days of the I think the teens of the 20 teens.
And they got put a lot of information online.
I checked some of the FOIA stuff and they did radiological in New York City
subway at the at the Battery Park, you know, where the number one ends down by Wall Street.
Yeah, they did. That's right.
Radiological. They did radiological.
And other times they did chemical.
And other times they did biological, biological.
And no one really got sick.
There was no reported mass, you know, mass illness from it.
So again, we're pretty tough.
Right. So we're pretty tough as a species.
But you got that's why I'm a firm believer
in when they talk about custom genetically tailoring the stuff.
That's that's absolutely the way to do it.
You know, like if you look at black people get blood.
What is it? Sickle cell.
Sickle cell. White people get Cooley's anemia.
That's basically when the cell torques itself instead of laying more flat.
It bends in half like a potato chip.
But only white people that have a very distant relative
somewhere way back that was black, really.
Yeah. But there's Cooley cell sickle cell.
There's another one. Yeah.
But the Cooley cells is Sicilian.
That's why I know it.
But that's a Sicilian thing.
That's yeah, there's several.
The African. Because yeah, when you try it there.
Yeah. But still, when you when you try it, when you see it on that level
and that's what you're trying to do.
Yeah, that's how you can genetically engineer.
That's what. Yeah, that one.
In other words, listen to one.
Right. There's nothing.
There's no DNA splicing or anything like that.
They're just mimicking, you know, the trial and error to see what will cause
these things are already known,
you know, to be detrimental. Right.
So like lead poisoning, you know, a bullet is lead poisoning. Right.
I mean, essentially trauma also.
But, you know, what I would say is
just to go back to the ether, you cannot objectify it.
But if you understand it's a it has effects
in other words, William Reich
basically made the statement that it goes from low to high potential.
It's the opposite of the way we were taught potentials move.
So once you understand that, that's how the weather devices work.
The other thing is, I remember reading a report from the FBI.
He was heavily monitored, William Reich.
And one of the reports that they had a plant, a laboratory technician
FBI put in Robert in Wilhelm Reich's lab.
And I read one of the reports, FBI report on the what
the laboratory technician was reporting to the FBI.
And it says, well, we really even though I've been working there,
she said for several months, I still don't quite understand it.
I don't think Wilhelm Reich does, but he's the only one
that could really understand it more than the rest of us.
But what we do know is that the the Oregon experiments
and the ether experiments we do know for sure is that it's slow moving, slow acting.
It's very effective, very potent, but it's slow moving.
Right. So in other words, when you're looking to affect something using the ether,
it's not like hitting a switch on the wall and the lights come on.
It's it could take 20 minutes, two hours, 20 days.
It's very slow, but it does happen.
So they found it was about potential going from low to high. Right.
So that's what we do with the weather stuff.
And I'm still speaking to people that are interested in the weather.
And I coach them here and there.
You know, I'd like to see them come back and what they learned and coach,
you know, tell me.
But, you know, you cannot use basic stuff
that we consider to be science and physics to apply is a new discoveries.
And the point that I always make is just remember a low potential.
So how do you create a low potential with a reflective surface?
The ether, instead of moving, let's say, on a flow would be like
if you put a stick in the river, you don't slow down the whole river.
But when the water makes contact with the stick
and you get this turbulence around the stick, that water is now slower
and represents a lower potential, doesn't it?
And then when it leaves the turbulence around the stick
that you're holding in the water, it goes back to the high potential again.
You see? And that's how the ether works.
So you disturb it using metallic, non-organic reflective surfaces.
Let's say a tube with a mirror in it.
And when the ether is in there, it will bounce around momentarily.
And when it's released into the main flow, it'll reflect the low potential,
which will feed the high potential. Right.
So actually charging the ether when you do this, people are like that.
When you have a very charismatic individual on stage
and all these mainstream normies in the audience,
who's the high potential? The guy on stage speaking, right?
And then who's the low potential? The people in the crowd.
Now, you can't tell me that the low people in the crowd
are not feeding the high guy up on the stage.
I've seen it.
If you look at someone making a speech that's considered charismatic,
has the full attention of the crowd, which is the low potential,
when they get off that stage, they're fully charged.
I've done people who requested me to speak and I'm just some nothing.
And in front of 50 people after an hour and a half when I left,
I was like, hi.
And for an hour or two hours for me to come down off of that
because they were so happy. Right.
Yeah. Now, I've performed plenty of different ways in front of people on a stage
and the people that are out there that. Yeah, absolutely.
They absolutely will charge you up. Yeah, they charge me up.
You can't just finish your performance and go to sleep.
You'll be like wired for hours after. Right. Right.
It's exactly it's exactly what the ether is like.
But you got to keep reminding yourself that now
the man or matter author talked about in others,
but I think it originated with him, the light ether, the heat ether,
the chemical ether and the life ether.
He talked about it in that form when giving different shapes and colors to each one.
Guess which one is the heat ether?
Right. What color you would associate to that?
Right. Red. Right. Yeah.
And the light would be yellow.
Right. Yellow. The chemical ether, I think, is blue.
And the life ether was purple, like a violet violet.
Yeah. Like the purple robe. Right.
So these things are just symbolic in a way to organize it in your mind.
But again, I've been trying to objectify it.
But on other on the other side, there's also the electrical ether
than the chemical. OK, let's go back.
Light ether is pretty obvious because light doesn't travel.
There's no speed.
It just it just vibrates in the field longitudinally, instantly.
And depending what material is in the air,
it will change its ability to, you know, luminesce.
Light ether is pretty obvious.
The heat ether is pretty obvious that things are warming.
But and then the life ether is pretty obvious,
which I would say is biological vacuum.
When in order for something to be alive, it needs to sustain
a slight negative pressure to hold itself together and animate.
And the chemical ether is every old material, metals, mineral.
Water is all chemical ether.
Right. Everything that you find on the periodic table.
And that's the breakdown.
But then there's the electrical ether, which is between light and heat.
But if you go back to the heat ether, for example,
before you get into electrical, you notice that you have two types of heat.
You have descending, densifying heat in natural living objects.
Then you have rarefied rising heat when you do chemical decomposition. Right.
So in all living things, the heat goes down and the cold goes up.
All things that are decomposing.
The heat goes up.
And, you know, a young person asked me, what about a campfire?
The heat goes up. I said, OK, what's in the campfire?
Wood. Right. When the fire is going, are you building up the wood
or are you breaking down the wood?
You're breaking and decomposing it. Right.
Without its oxygenation, really. Right.
So can they get it right away? Just give me an example.
What do you want? And just right away, show them a real simple way to deduce it.
So when you talk about the heat ether from Ernst Lehrer
there in man or matter, he doesn't break it down like that.
So it can be broken down for, you know, there's two types of heat.
There's two types of light. Right.
The chemical ether, what you know, that's all ponderable material,
but there's also imponderable material.
And the life ether, you can pretty much
go across the like a rock has a life also. Right.
A piece of stone. Right. To a degree.
You know, they even in chemistry, the half life of uranium.
Right. Is lead right to a certain point.
Or is it one hundred thousand years or something? Whatever.
I don't trust anything that they say, especially with the carbon dating.
I mean, when I hear carbon dating,
I just relegate that as a dating site for senior citizens
or something, you know.
Right. Anyway, they should make a senior citizen dating cycle, carbon dating.
Anyway, that's a dumb joke.
But yeah, well, age, get it, you know. Anyway.
Yeah, like I'm going to pretty soon,
I'll be old enough that I'll go to an antique shop and they won't let me go.
Right. Anyway. Yeah.
They try to keep you. Then that's. Yeah, that's right. So anyway,
these things are not as simple.
They can be objectified. No, I don't think they can.
I think if you can objectify the ether, you will not be able to communicate it
for the sake of the ether, because now you're going to start
to take apart this place.
You can literally take apart this place.
That's what so you know, when you study nuclear energy, there's so many
what do you call detractors about it?
Oh, no, it's dangerous.
We're going to destroy ourselves. Right.
Walter Russell is big on a lot of people in Tesla.
Tesla make fun of the people thinking nuclear power was strong
because he says my capacitive discharge makes your nuclear reactions
look like an infant's consumptive breath.
And he's right about that.
He made fun of them, you know, but it is pretty dangerous
because it shorts out the ether.
Right. It's literally shorting. It's a short.
What I mean by short is just like when you short an electrical circuit.
It's a violent shorting.
So there's a big thing that's been put out there.
The elite, they always put stuff out there like, you know,
the flat earth, round earth thing. Right.
They they decide what the population because there's articles
written in mainstream about flat earth, round earth. Right.
So the elite decide what will go to the mainstream.
What will never be discussed in the mainstream.
They've also discussed nuclear in the mainstream. Right.
But will never be discussed as the financial system.
Never, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever.
That will never be discussed. Right.
Because it's all based on trust law and they don't want you understanding that.
But what will also never be discussed in the mainstream,
they'll discuss simulation, but then they will not.
They will not discuss shorting it out and how to make it go haywire.
And the way you do that is with nuclear reactions.
Now, what they are doing is they put out in the media,
especially a lot of alternative people.
There's no such thing as nuclear.
Those are just really big bombs.
You know, you've heard that right recently. Yes.
Well, here's people say, oh, it's not nuclear. They're lying.
There's no such thing.
Well, yeah, they are lying because you can't split an atom.
You can't split something that cannot be split
because it's just a gyroscopic movement of ether. Right.
The chemical ether can't splitting.
It doesn't mean any doesn't do anything.
These fusion and fission reactions are just complete bullshit,
like blood pressure and diabetes. Right.
No such thing. You have to believe in it or like the money system.
You have to believe in it in order to have value.
If you don't believe in it
and look at it through a knowledgeable perspective, there is nothing
really as atomic energy, but it is dangerous.
It is shorting out the ether.
You're hacking the physical reality
with a shortcut, with a short.
Basically, it's like throwing a wrench over a big, heavy transformer bus bar,
you know, where they make the main connections.
It's just going to blow. And it's the same thing.
If you've seen anyone blow a car battery with a wrench over it,
you pick up your wrench and whatever touch is vaporized, it's gone.
If you have a Geiger counter, when you do a big short like that,
you will see it peak just like nuclear.
But it's a different type of reaction, right?
Because when you short out an electrical circuit,
so in essence is nuclear electrical, yes, but not as simple
because when you short out something electrical,
you're grounding this potential and work that's already in the circuit.
You know, it's charged up either by you getting it off the grid
or solar panel or a battery. Right.
And then you short it. Right.
With nuclear, it's producing the energy.
It's discharging the energy and charging it
and discharging it instantaneously all at once.
Nuclear would be like you have a dead car battery.
And you remember I gave the example of shorting the car battery.
You see a big flash. Right.
And your wrenches, half your wrenches melted and gone. Right. Right.
OK, so nuclear would be analogous to that would be completely dead car battery.
And in less than a thousandth of a second,
the battery is fully charged and shorted out.
That would be an analogy of nuclear.
And everybody knows you can't charge a battery in a thousandth of a second.
It'll explode. Right.
And we're not saying exploding it when you're charging it.
I'm saying you charge the battery completely full and fully shorted out
is what a nuclear does, because it uses the elements that it does.
Very large elements that are in a very lean state.
And it's usually a very young reaction.
So you have the exact polar opposites of energies of the universe acting on it.
Yeah, it's basically messing up.
Yeah, the simulation, the construct that we're in. Right.
Nuclear is is a quick way to fuck it up.
I mean, the entire reality. Yeah.
So the detractors that went aired philosophically about bad,
how bad nuclear is are. Yeah, they're there.
I'm not wrong, but they they're not talking about what I'm talking about.