Rated Y Sonic Event 94 and here we are. Greek, how are you doing?
I'm doing all right. I did some sleep therapy today, about seven hours of sleep. I highly
recommend that, by the way. You know, the reason I brought it up is, you know, people go to
the gym to build muscle. You know, I ran into someone, we called him The Rock. And actually,
I can mention him because he passed away. Michael Labasso, he was a childhood friend and he
worked for the DEA. He looked like The Rock. And he passed away in 2001. Tragic accident.
And he was the kind of guy that was thin, you know, just nondescript, bookworm looking.
And then one year later, I saw him and he looked like The Rock. He said, what the hell?
Right. It's around 16 years old or 17. Right. All of a sudden, his neck is almost as big
around as his head. Well, well, yeah. Well, no, no. Actually, he looked like a small Arnold
Schwarzenegger. Didn't quite have the pictorial size, the chest size. But what I see is going
to the gym. Right. We used to go to Bath Beach Bodybuilding in. OK, so late 70s. We're talking
now and never had a reaction like that, but basically lived in the gym. You got a part
time job there. And part of the barter was to be in the gym all the time. And he just
turned into a monster bodybuilder in one year. Now, bringing this story, most people say
that happens because you go to the gym. No, it happens because you rest. You don't you
don't build muscle in the gym. You build muscle when you're sleeping. Think about that. They
used to tell us as kids, that's when our bones grow. Right. That's what they would
tell us. I don't know about everything. Everything. Your hair. I mean, growth happens when you're
sleeping, when you're. Yeah. OK, so why do I bring this up? I want to underscore it because
you never hear that. You know, I've been training. That's why I'm strong. No, you're if you trained
it in sleep. Well, you wouldn't be strong. You would actually deteriorate. There's something
called Epstein Barr. I remember when I was training for cycling intensively and getting
like flu symptoms in the middle of the summer, everyone was training with. It's when you
overtrain. Right. You'd say you exhibit breakdown more than buildup. We came in one day as you
have Epstein Barr. I'm like, oh, my gosh, the names of these diseases. But anyway, our
conditions. So I just want to bring that up. It's important whenever you're developing the
body or healing the body. It doesn't happen in your waking hours, by the way. By the way,
you know, it's like certain ailments can happen overnight, you know, so and same way. So I just
wanted to emphasize that, that whenever there is any recovery of the body, even like healing of
when I was younger and had a really good diet, I would get a cut or a scratch or a bruise and it
would heal in two days. I mean, almost completely right. That was because of when you when you
slept, not when you were walking around. So I just want to bring that up. It's it's quite a quite
a thing that's not really, let's just say, cherished in this society. Right. They're always
looking for remedies and things like that. I had by the way, I had much more remarkable skin when I
was younger. My stuff would heal up like even faster than that. And I always attributed to water
actually my water intake because I would take in best quality water I could find. And I did it in
a controlled way. And I was always very conscious of hydration. And I thought this was best
methodology for me. Sure. And Dr. Batman. Other people. Dr. Batman. Yeah. Other people would say,
oh, it's your genetics. You know, you have this skin because I would get cut or something and
it would be the kind of thing that should leave a scar. You know, there's a you have you heard of
Dr. Batman. Batman. Yes. They call him Dr. Batman. Right. And he's you're not sick. You're thirsty
is his book. It's not that great of a book. He was in prison and a political prisoner in Iran.
And he was healing people with, you know, accessing water at the in the prison. And when
it was sentence was over, he says, No, I got more work to do here. Right? Anyway, that kind of guy.
So yeah, it's an okay read. But it'll just make you aware of other things. He uses a lot of stuff
that you know, is not true. You know, the medical speaking of not true there, by the way, YouTube
thing popped up and I clicked on it was a medical doctor critiquing all of McDonald's food and
ingredients. And I wanted to critique him because this will give you diabetes or high blood pressure.
Oh my gosh, you know, it's good for me to watch that because I get spoiled in my own
thinking in my own mind about seeing how they're perpetrating a fiction. But when you have a
doctor getting a million views on YouTube, because everyone likes you know, that he's brought up you
get diabetes or certain ailments that are medical fictions. Everyone approves there was no one in
those 2000 comments. I didn't go through all of them. I what I do is I hit on the comment selection
newest first, right and the right to go through and no one mentioned that his stuff was basically
perpetrating medical fictions just basically would damage the liver. But he was calling it all these
other things, especially blood pressure doesn't understand. So I mean, this is the state that
we're in. It's not very good. Which by the way, speaking of very good, got quite a few bit
feedback from reading on the multiple sundry of questions on that email on the last sonic
92, which even though this is 94, ha ha. We did a little slip up there, folks. So you're not going
crazy. You know what, they're all in order. And it makes sense. It's just the date is now out of
order. And so how about that? Yeah, you're out of order. Yeah, it was a movie with Pacino. Was it
in there? Or was it no somebody else? This place? No courts out of order. And yeah, it was the
chamber. It was not that bad. But yeah, we call it in a date thing. But yeah, just there's one more
question that I left out. That seems to be a proprietary. So what did you think of reading
the what we were on there for about an hour? I think I'm just reading emails. Yeah, that was
just about an hour. Just a question and answer there. Or email one email, one email, but question
and answer question and answer. Matter of fact, before you get to this email question, I actually
have one that I forgot to get to a while ago from somebody who sent me some material again this week,
and they never bothered to mention it again. But you just reminded me about blood pressure, which
is is a funny thing. Look, they have an instrument, they use it. Obviously, it measures something.
So the person wanted to know what in reality are they measuring? Good. I always bring I used to use
the technical terms, but the heart, they measure the beat. First of all, their entire theory that
the heart is a pump is wrong. So anything that comes out from them, because they have a false
theory will also be false, right? There's a maximum on that false theory. Anything that is produced
or emanates from that false theory must also be false, right? It's it's the point between when one
heartbeat, kind of like where the heartbeat hits, and then it relaxes. And then right before it
starts again, right? They have terms for that. And yeah, that's what basically they're measuring.
I mean, it couldn't be any more fallacious, right? Because they don't understand that the heart is not
even beating what you're actually hearing is all the heart is doing is contracting. And what you're
hearing and feeling is the stop of water pressure, kind of like a water hammer, you know, when you
shut off abruptly in the house, flowing water, you hear the pipes in the wall rattle a little bit,
because of the momentum. Yeah, it's not even beating. So there's so many ways that it's false.
Well, okay, here's another way to answer it indirectly. dementia and forms of Alzheimer's are
now considered so they'll emphasize dementia and Alzheimer's are not the same. That comes from
aluminum, usually, because it shuts down the electric brain. But they're telling they're
telling people now that's you have type three diabetes. Oh, my gosh. Oh, and by the way,
bring up that term. Diabetes just means you've you've pissed frequently, frequent urination.
And if you look that up, that's, that's what it means, which is now it's been changed to Mina.
Oh, my gosh. That's kind of like, you know, the World Trade Center being vaporized. It's been
changed into jet fuel fire, right? So it's but that is, in other words, why do I bring that up?
I used to bring up the world, even with biblical stuff, the World Trade Center analogy, because
it's a perfect example of how something that is so big, you know, that everyone knows about have
found out about is a lie. Right? And they still get away with it. So yeah, I haven't found anything
in the medical community. That is true, other than the tracking and monitoring and let's say
effects of their medicines, which are drugs, pharmaceuticals, which mean poison, by the way.
When I say tracking, I mean, not what they tell you on television and the idiot that's prescribing
them. But when you get these prescriptions, they they have this thing called a cut or catalog cut
or a cut, it has the all of the side effects written on it, right, right. And it's extremely
fine. It's like one point font. And none of them do anything beneficial at all. The only medical
medical stuff that works is the nerve suppression, right, the opioid based stuff, which is old,
by the way, you know, in the military medic medics, that's what they rely on. And if you study,
I'm really flying on a big tangent here. But most people died from trauma, not from
the actual right shock. Right. So if you could prevent someone from going to shock by sedating
them and or pain relief, that's the first thing. By the way, if you go into a medical tent
during battle, the first thing they ask you, oh, even a hospital, someone in trauma and I see
first day they ask you is do you want morphine? Right? You want morphine? And then they can write,
they look at you, do you want morphine? And what does everyone say? Usually? Yeah. So it doesn't
always work. So okay. It's all fiction, but it's so powerful. Right? Just like 911. If you tell
people there was no it was not a it was actually 911 was a terrorist event, by the way. Think about
it. Right. So just like COVID was a terrorist event. So it's a terrorist event is a terrorist
event to bring terror. It doesn't matter who's perpetrating it, or whether they're telling you
is perpetrating it. That's pretty much true. Right. But anything else beyond that is, is not
true. So the same thing with the medical system, if you're not well, they can maybe determine that
to a certain degree, not usually. Anything else beyond that is a lie. You know, there's perfectly
healthy, there was a study done where they went to places where there were centurions,
high percentage of centurions, people living over 100. And they measure their blood pressure
and blood sugar, and they would have been eligible for quadruple bypass and type two diabetes. That's
how these were people that were over 100 years old working in the fields totally healthy and
normal, right? They were diagnosed as having severe diabetes and heart conditions, right?
Because, you know, they hide this data very use exclusion. You know, they'll study 2000 people
but give you the results of 10 that only comply with what they want. Like 911. Right? Again,
same thing. This is a I use I used to use 911 for a while I got kind of tired because it sounded like
I was one of those 911 whatever's right, whatever you want to call them. They're also JFK, whatever
still, haha. Not disparaging you. But, you know, because most of the JFK stuff is kind of like
they find something they can't it could be baseless, but they spin it off like it is,
you know what I mean? So same with 911. So if you stick to using it as a metaphor,
it works really well in the mind once you understand what really happens. By the way,
I was having a discussion recently with someone about JFK, talk about super tangent from blood
pressure. And this person knows his family is in intelligence. And what's interesting,
they're older, by the way, they're older than us. What's interesting is it's kind of kind of
like what I say when someone says they're in the military, which military are you in? Like, you
know, the one that everyone knows about that they, you know, be the best you can be on TV or the real
the other military. So this person knew was in the regular, let's say one of the intelligence
agencies, I won't mention CIA. And they knew about the other side, right? And they said,
no one really knows about JFK is interesting thing kicked around is no one really knows,
because before it happened, they knew something was going to happen. But it was only in rumor.
I didn't get into it very much. So in other words, the internal memos,
was there's a rumor going around, right? Yeah, this is going to happen. But no specifics,
right? There's plenty of those. Yeah. Yeah. Does that make sense? Yeah. Based on your research?
Absolutely. I could I could probably get 100 of those together for you. No problem.
Yeah. But you see, let's go use same with 911. Right? Like one of the rumors in 911 was
that Osama bin Laden put suitcase nukes in the building. And that's what brought them down. Well,
we know that can't be true. Because an atmospheric explosion is an atmospheric explosion
would look like Hiroshima, flashbang, you know. Anyway, blood pressure, all that stuff.
I used to use restless leg syndrome. They had drugs for that, right? In the early 2000s. As an
example. I recently spoke to someone again, who's in a retirement community and says there's mostly
doctors here. And I got no one to talk to because they're so stupid. Think about that for a moment.
Right? You know, and you're going Yeah, no. Why? Because they're part of the legal system.
It's kind of like if you don't show up to school, if you have a letter from your mom, it's okay.
In the legal system, if you have a letter from a doctor, you can get away with right? Of course,
you get it. It's part of the legal system has nothing to do for people say, you know, go to
a doctor or the doctor like there's the doctor, right? Yeah. That's like a lot like the God,
you know, Allah means the God. Allah means the and Allah. If you read in Aramaic, e, l, a, h is
God is now becomes a personified figure. These doctors are personified figures of authority,
but really, they're part of the legal system. So the last Do you want some scumbag attorney to tell
you what's going on with your body? Oh, my gosh, hell no. And when I say scumbag attorney, you
would have to be a scumbag attorney to actually be part of the underpinning of a system like that.
Which also, when I was bike racing, I was on a stage race once. And so what do you do? He says,
I'm an attorney. So what do you do? He says, I edit medical books. What?
There's an answer. Yeah. Any questions? Right? Any questions? No, not at all. That's the guy
who's actually honest about his job, though. I mean, most of us sit there and they well,
I actually I pursue this and I pursue that. He wasn't a scumbag. But he did what he did was
scumbag. Gary, let's quotes many used to use that often. Yeah. So anyway, the question in short,
it's about a paragraph. A young person in their 20s are diagnosed with an osteoporosis. Soft
bones were actually their bones were breaking and fracturing. What do you do about that? What
do you think, Chuck? What do you think about that? From based on our past calls? Put you on the spot.
Actually, that's not put you on the spot. You think we could apply Yin and Yang to that?
Well, obviously, you'd have to because, look, the bones are supposed to be young.
Right. Which means that you have to apply some energy to them in order to get that condition
in order to make them young. But apparently it's going the other direction. So
I would try and figure out what to do. Yeah. Two things. Now, if everyone in his geographical
vicinity came down with something simple, you got hit with a radiological weapon of
some advanced type. Right. That would that would not damage the skin,
but go straight to the bones. Right. Also, if there were more than one person in that geographical area
that that happened, then you would have more, quote, unquote, specimens. Right.
To investigate. Well, you mentioned something like that. That would have been a big plus
if you did. He didn't. So I'm presuming he's the only one. We have to go another track.
If you don't have a cluster, then you don't have an environmental event. So.
Yeah. But it's still it could be environmental. But in inverse, his body's protection to that
natural radiation came down. Well, environmental could also mean that it's more of a limited
situation, like the environment of, say, just their dwelling. Right. So maybe. Yeah. But he
didn't mention anything like that. So we have to presume that it's highly specific just to the
individual. OK, fine. Right. And this would this would be part of the query. I used to work with
people that treated people, doctors and other sorts, and they would bring cases to me years ago,
years ago, like five, six, seven, ten years ago. And when they bring the case to me,
I would start asking all these questions. And they were like, oh, we're going to I'm going to
have to get back to you because I didn't ask those questions. Yeah, of course not. Because
a week later, they wouldn't check out what's going on in the neighborhood. They wouldn't check out,
you know, is anybody else in the house experiencing this? Right. Well, it's so
right. So, you know, same with cancers. You know, you'll have one person. There was a person that
was a urologist in Chicago. His wife told me is he's he has some form of liver cancer and
they eat well and live as if he needs to sleep somewhere else because there's some
something coming up through the earth, slicing, cutting through his body that he's susceptible
to. And he actually slept in another room and got better. That's a long another. This is back
2015 is, let's say, a few years ago. But 2015 is not a few years ago. It's nine years ago, right?
Yeah. So in this case, we have like, for example, you know, if you have a pickup bed,
a pickup truck, you're collecting cosmic when if the bed is not covered,
you're collecting cosmic dust. Right. It's just very fine. You can't see it. But if you search
hard enough, you'll find something unusual that's falling. Right. So you don't notice it. So these
things that we don't notice that we're bombarded with constantly natural radiation and unnatural
man induced. Our bodies have, quote unquote, natural protection or compensation for it.
So in this individual, what happened is that natural compensation
collapsed. Right. And it was either. Well, all chemicals have carriers for vitality and energy.
So it was either his intake or it was something in his genetic hereditary code or something. His
body just decided, hey, I'm going to release this energy and, you know, subject this person or
subject myself now to it. You know what, consciously or unconsciously, because the body also has its
own mind. So we the only thing I can do is apply Yin and Yang to that and remedies for that.
Now, the person is recovered. So so in the email showed that he says that he's recovered from it.
He actually does heavy labor. So what I would suggest is there's really nothing you can do
for something like that when your own body decides to crap out on something. Right. What can you do?
Well, it's the Yin and Yang works really well. You could assist it, you know, just like if you
have a burn, you put something cool on it, not too cold, but or cold, but not, you know, free to call
because you can the body can interpret that as a burn again. So there's not much. It's just one of
the realities of being here. And it sounds like I don't have an answer for this. But the answer is
if it's something very specific to the person, they just go along with it,
and the person obviously survived. But the Yin and Yang may not work in a case like that,
where the body's mind releases its ability to protect itself. And what I mean by that also
is I think early on on the Sonics, I gave an example of how does that apply, though?
How does that apply to this this weak bone situation? You know, as far as.
I guess it does it. It's very OK. Could not only be weak bone, it could be eyesight.
Well, I was thinking that was another question. I was looking for that email. What do you do to
improve eyesight? I'll get into that maybe as a as a as a diversion, but a slight diversion,
because I have no answer for that. If you're the only person now back anyway, regarding the bones,
a very simple approximation that I've done on what could be good for bones is tarot root,
the large tarot, not the small tarot. I don't know how many times to say that.
It doesn't seem like people get it like they walk through the shop, let's say an Asian market,
and they see tarot and root and they stop thinking. Their brain goes blank. There's two
types of tarot, large and small, and they're not the same at all. Right. It's not like you
have big bananas and so it's kind of like plantains and bananas. You've had plantains,
it's nothing like a banana. Yeah. You would expect everybody's got that. Yeah. Everybody's
got that weird idea that it's it's the same thing and it's really not. It's really. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. It's not at all. Yeah. So so tarot, I had some slices that I left out and dried on a
windowsill and it was hard like plaster. When I say hard like plaster, indiscernible from plaster.
If you write, you know, like those plaster vases, almost like a rock, almost like a rock.
But, yeah, I gotcha. Yeah. So very much like the fiber in bones. And by the way,
bones are a collection of fibers like fascis, you know, the bundle of sticks. Right. Right. It's
very much like that. And the reason why it's like that is because of the piezoelectric nature.
Let's just use that loosely when you're walking and moving and the bone accepts a force, it creates
a slight charge, electrical charge. One way to actually do therapy for people that are bedridden,
if you spend enough time in bed, you can't walk regardless if you're injured or not. Right.
Your body. Right. So so if someone is in that condition, usually elderly people,
let's say someone gets a knee replacement or a hip replacement, double knee, double hip,
they're going to have problems adjusting for a few days or weeks. What you do is you go and get
yourself what is it? Table tennis paddles. They're small wooden paddles with rubber coating on them.
Perfect. Yeah, they're perfect for this every day for about just a few minutes with an hour,
a few hours interval in between as many times as you can during the day. Use that little paddle to
tap the bottoms of their feet, the entire heel from the toes to the heel for a few minutes at
a time might be uncomfortable in the beginning. Just tap, not hit, not spanking. Right. But but
tapping with intervals and that will be the equivalent of walking for a short distance
electrically and, you know, energetically. And the person, when it comes time to do their therapy,
they'll just get up and walk right across the room and they're like,
you're charging me five hundred dollars an hour for what you get it. So it's it's just wanted to
throw that in because it's bone related. So what really to weaken the bones, it's you know,
when you have a bundle of sticks that is very strong, when you release the tie that holds or
the tire that holds the bundle together, they become very weak. Right. So it's so again,
just to continue on that without much of a diversion, which I'd like to put in because I
have no answer, is that the tire or the tie that holds the bundle together is really what came
loose, which is also young, but it has a yin quality because it wraps around the entire bundle.
Right. So the person also asked about I say, how do you improve? I said the best example I can give
for that is this. I worked with someone on television and they were doing productions.
This is about 15, 18 years ago, and they showed me some videos of themselves 10 years, 15 years
prior to this, and they were wearing glasses. And now at that point, at the current time,
they were not wearing glasses. And they say, why were you wearing? You're not wearing glasses. Now
you're wearing condoms. No, I don't need them anymore. But you were wearing them back then.
And he says, yes, is that I improved my eyesight. I said, well, how did you do that?
Improved my diet and less stress. Stop worrying about stuff. In other words, give a shit factor
goes down. Right. And improve your diet. What is the easiest way to improve your diet? Avoid
processed foods. When you do not eat foods that are processed, you eat more whole foods that are
balanced and have more nutrition, yada, yada, yada. You could take that however you want. Right.
So that's the simplest thing. Like, in other words, if you're buying food for your home or your house
or yourself or others, and it has a label on it, it's been processed in some way.
And the bigger the label, the more processing, right? Right. And ingredients.
Longer label, really, because you ever notice you go to Walmart and buy like a
doughnut and you look at the back ingredients and it's like two paragraphs long of one font
letters. Right. It's like, wait a second. Just doughnuts, yeast, flour, salt, sugar.
That's it. You think most it should be half a dozen ingredients. Right. I mean,
if they use egg in there, let's say. Yeah. Not thirty five. So. Right. Yeah.
That would not be good. So that is a simple thing. And then, of course,
is seasonality. And if it's not. But here's the default. You're ready. If it's not heavily
processed, which are big constituents are preservatives and other things like the anti
spoilage, whatever, it's going to be seasonal. Why? Because it's not going to last that long.
Yeah. So we'll be more. The chances of it being seasonal is higher also,
and save for hydroponics because hydroponics, you know, they grow them all year round, mostly
and geography or whatever. You know, if it's not geographic. Right.
You can play with that. Like I do tropical fruit here from other parts of the world
in the summer, thinking that it will cool me down. It kind of works a little bit, but not
well, because those things not being able to be grown here trumps the ability for them to cool me
down. So, again, it's a it's a tricky thing. And what happens is when you stop eating locally,
that you stop developing ways and methodologies to make food more interesting. Right. You rely
on food from whatever. What is it like in England? The national food for a while was chicken marsala
or something. Or chicken, chicken, chicken, chicken marsala or chicken marsala is another
one. No, it's the chicken tiki. It's an Indian dish. Indian. In other words, Indian food is the
national dish of England. Right. It kind of makes sense when you understand the conquest of it and
the political and how, you know, you won't see too many restaurants. Let's go to this English
restaurant. No, no. For years and years. As a matter of fact, for years and years, anytime I
would talk to somebody from over there, they would just say something that struck me as strange.
I'm going to go get curry. Yeah. And I go curry. What curry is curry to me is a spice. You know,
what do you mean? Curry was a mixture of spices, actually. We've gotten used to it. It's usually a
turmeric based yellow. Well, yeah, but it doesn't sound like something that you would get as a dish.
You see what I'm saying? It's like, OK, if you tell me you're going to get. Yeah, but what I
mean is foreign to them in England, they would have from the meat and any meat you could make
some of the cows, the best cows we have here come from New Jersey and all that come from England.
And then they have they're known for their Cotswold or lambs and sheep. But it's almost
like saying, you know, what are you going to eat for dinner tonight, Greek? And you said, well,
pepper, you know, I'd go. Oh, I mean, it's not very good. Yeah. Well, here's another thing.
You go to a place like In-N-Out Burger. Right. And they tout that they're they're French fries.
I'm putting in air quotes. This is what I want to talk about, really, about them, really,
because it's an issue. They cut their potatoes fresh and right away, fry them. Those are not
French fries. Those are just fried potatoes in order for them to be French fries. They have to
be parboiled, cooled down, par fried and then finished fried. They don't do that. So they're
not French fries. They're just fried potatoes. And I brought the issue up with several people.
Of course, you know what? I get the fluoride stare. Yeah, of course. No French fries at a
bare minimum. You got to take them and soak them in water and parboil them at a bare minimum to
make French fries and fries. Yeah. And then they're par fried, cooled down and then finished
fried. And that's how you get a French fry. If you're just freshly peeling potatoes and cutting
them in whatever shape and then frying them and serving them, those are just fried potatoes.
Yeah. So they don't understand that. Yeah. Nothing wrong with it. But I mean,
you go to the boardwalk and the guy says there is something wrong with it. There is not very good.
Well, no, I'm not saying if you if you don't care about it, you know what I mean? If you don't care
about quality, what I'm saying is that's the way you want to eat them. Great. Enjoy. But what I'm
saying is that, you know, they do this on the board. You remember on the boardwalks, they used
to do this. Some places would go. We have French, you know, we have fresh fries. Right. And they
would do that right there on the boardwalk. They would cut up potatoes, right? Yeah. Fresh fries
is correct. That would be it. But they're not French fries. Right. Right. And they would be,
you know, we got fresh fries and people go, OK, I'm going to take some French fries.
So the people would order it. So, yeah, it's the way we use language like diabetes. You know,
diabetes is frequent urination has nothing to do with it. Yeah, it's pretty, pretty
it's all diversions. Yeah, it's all diversions. But anyway, yeah, that's that's pretty much
just what I just I want to thank everyone who listened to the last thought I can give feedback
regarding the they enjoyed going through the multiple questions and all that. But, yeah,
I guess tonight or today is pretty simple. I don't have much for you other than what I've
brought up. Well, look, I got one last thing to throw in, because, you know, more on this thing
with the bones just for a moment, because you were going to talk about how younger people
ended up with, you know, with some of these diseases. And I've taken note of this lately.
Oh, yeah. The body gives up. Yeah. Yeah. But but the trend now, it seems as though, OK,
the stuff that we used to hear about when somebody was 60, 70, 80. Right. A lot of people
are getting that at 40. And you mentioned dementia earlier. Dementia has become what
that dementia could start at a young age, like a pre adolescence. Oh, yeah, absolutely. But the
thing is, it used to be a lot more rare, it seems for somebody to be in their 40s.
Environmental stresses with toxins in the environment and bad habits all around.
Yeah. But do you think it's just environmental and bad habits or do you think it's all the
medical community is promoting that? Right. They're not your friends. Right.
Well, of course, they're creating the toxins. They're part of the military industrial company.
In other words, who's the head of the doctors, the surgeon general? He's always in uniform.
1952 to 54, they decided propaganda and to keep control of the population through the medical
system. Right. So they got the military branch to do that. The medical is under the military.
Right. So the surgeon general is always in uniform. Yeah. And then simultaneously,
the joke becomes what? Go ahead and eat what, 20 White Castles and smoke a cigarette. That's
healthy dinner for you. Right. Well, it can be. It depends on the yeah, it depends on
many other factors. It's never that simple. But again, a young person, the way you would
approach any health issue is loss of biological vacuum. The higher the vacuum,
the biological vacuum, the more robust the individual. Right. And then maybe we'll just
get into improving biological vacuum. I'd have to think about that because it's full of nuances.
Right. So it's not just putting pressure on something. Yeah. I think in one of the sonics
we talked about some things don't need pressure if the body's trying to release them. Right.
Right. Right. So I guess it would be a proper. How do you how do you maintain the tightness of
your body basically? Right. No, no. The biological vacuum is internal in the cell structure. When
the cells group together. What do they call it, synchronized swimming or how you ever see how a
flock of birds can sometimes change direction in mid direction, you know, and there's no collisions.
Right. Large. I think the robins are famous for this. You could have like 20,000 robins flying
in a swarm. It looks like from a distance it looks like a black swarm and they just move so
fluidly. Right. Or how does a swarm of bats, you know, come flying at you and they're a little
more a little less graceful. But they do it eloquently. They're all in sync like a school
of fish. You ever see these video old Wild Kingdom and National Geographic, the swarm of fish,
and they just move beautifully like one body. But that's why I was with bats that appear more
clunky and everything else. You notice something. Bats usually don't collide with one another,
even though it looks like absolute chaos when they all go. Well, it's usually when they're
leaving the cave. Yeah. But but what I'm trying to say is that that's synchronous,
synchronous because the body is everything working together. That can only happen when it's immersed
or the prevailing condition is a good biological vacuum, which is
just what it sounds like, a negative pressure. So there's many ways to do that,
to improve that. And I think when we started off tonight is what I started off with sleep.
Right. So well, hey, look, we could always call that one proper vacuum maintenance.