130 Sonic Event rated Y, Ocelli in the Greek.
So why not?
Yes, here we are.
Should we start with the emails, Greek?
Yeah, go for it.
Yes.
Somebody new or something.
Yeah.
A brand new.
Now, this is unusual because most Greek speak people, you know, tell me they've been listening
for years or they used to listen.
Then they came back around, et cetera, et cetera, et cetera.
Everybody likes to tell me that.
Also quick shout out to somebody who actually, you know, sent me a friendly message recently.
It was a long time Greek speak listener and had not reached out to me until recently.
Thank you for that.
But a brand new one who said that they were just recommended by somebody and they said
that they found a couple of things that the person said to be fascinating, but didn't
make entirely enough sense for them to follow.
So they wanted to find out what was going on.
It means they heard it right.
Yeah.
So because it didn't make sense in the world around them.
So they came to us and said, look, I'm just catching up and maybe you guys have already
covered these two interesting things.
But curious, based on the Greeks presentation of the laws, morality, things like that, I
was wondering what his views were on the use of drugs.
You know, does the Greek have a position on that?
Because I'm told by my friend who has listened for a long time that he doesn't recall if
the Greek has ever addressed drugs in his discussion and don't know why that is.
Secondly, he wanted to know if you had anything to say about the pyramids, which he finds
quite fascinating, the Egyptian pyramids and also the Aztec and all those all of the pyramids
that people talk about.
He finds them fascinating and wonders if you have any views on those as well.
But he also said he might have missed some stuff because he's just catching up to Rated
Y, just being told about the old archives.
And he's got a lot to catch up on.
But he was curious about those things right away.
All right.
Well, make sure you keep an outline because there's some things there.
So you mentioned the drug thing, right?
Yeah.
Morality and drugs.
How does that fit in?
Well, they're different.
Morality is what if you think of it this way, and it's very hard to answer anything regarding
morality simply because what if you were raised in a society of cannibals, which do exist
still in the African continent, Asia Pacific Rim?
Well, going with the general Western society, right, there's a pill for everything.
And so there's drugs for everything.
Yes or no.
That's right.
Well, the drug thing.
I got to I got to go to Rick James for that.
And here, I could take this.
Okay.
Absolutely.
That's all I can say about that.
And if you're going to do anything else, why bother?
Right.
But here's the thing.
Drugs have always been used.
The whole thing.
Drugs.
Okay.
The.
How do you say this?
From a biblical way, in all ancient languages, drugs are the word for drugs is poison.
Like pharmakia.
Pharmacy means poison.
Right.
On and on and on.
So when you extract something from its natural state, refine it, especially make it commercial
for purposes, which degrades it, you know, like eating out is never going to be as eating
as good as eating at home unless you're white.
But that's different.
But by the way, I just got to say this.
I feel sorry for these little white children come from white families.
They always look forward to eat out.
And I don't ask why, because, you know, mom can't cook.
Right.
And it shouldn't be that way.
But it just is.
It's very sad.
So making these things commercially viable degrades them.
There's a certain group of people, a class system of drug users, right?
The recreational, the hardcore, the addicts, then the ones that die of it.
Right.
So this.
So when you say drugs, it's a subculture.
Right.
You can you can go down that route or you could go down the actual physical mental aspect
of it.
And I would say that even LSD or any drug you could take, even heroin is 50 percent
mental. There is the idea you've seen in movies where they shoot someone with a tranquil
gun, tranquilizer and they fall out.
Yeah. And they don't want to fall out, but they still do.
Right. Right.
Well, actually, there are some people that you could shoot them with a tranquilizer and
they won't go down, just like there's some, you know, the fentanyl crisis, you know, as
it feels like what, 20, 30, 40 times stronger than heroin.
Right. So there are a couple of people I've heard of that can pop them, pop as many as
they want. It has almost no effect on them.
Right. And so there's that aspect.
But I would, as a general rule of thumb, avoid it.
Like give you an example from my personal experience is years ago, back in the 90s,
before I'd wake up and I was doing a restoration of plaster, wood and stone and like
all the mansions and theaters, you know, bringing back stuff that looked like 100 years
ago, no one knew how to do that.
And it was kind of trippy to do that kind of work, you know, casting plaster, gold
gilding and stone carving and all that to restore stuff.
But I had gotten to the point where to make it more interesting, I had a really good
connection for weed and whatever you want to call it, cannabis, whatever.
And when I would wake up in the morning before my feet touched the floor, I already took
three puffs off or something.
Right. And my whole day was being high.
So I stopped that and I recognize that it does have a negative effect if you do that
much. But the other thing now, I haven't touched this stuff in maybe 15 years, 20.
And the last time I did, I was like, oh, I don't like this high stuff.
I'd rather I'm more I'm having more of a good time being sober.
Right. So that OK, where's the morality in that?
You know, some people are not having a good time and they want to they want to take
something. And when they take that something, they feel better.
Right. For me, it's the opposite.
When I take that something, I'm like, oh, what the hell did I do that for?
Right. There's no one size fits all.
Look, I could tell you that, you know, no less.
Sorry. That's the morality aspect of it.
Right. What's right. Morality, by the way, is what society accepts.
Right. Well, there's ethics that mixes in with it.
So. Well, this is true.
But I'll give you a mixed morality situation right where I go to back in the day when I
did still go to the doctor, you know, I go to a doctor because I'm having chronic
pain in my back. And it's because I had broken some bones in the past and it was
hurting. Right. So they gave me something.
So it wouldn't hurt. I felt pretty good.
Not only did I feel good, you know, physically, but mentally I felt better and did
not realize really as stupid as this sounds, didn't realize that eventually I was hooked
on the pills, you know, painkillers.
Now, there's a big difference between just drying something and smoking it that comes
out of the ground and taking the pharmacia of the day, which was common at that point.
Right. I started taking that stuff.
Here's the thing. When they refine it, it has more.
It's more. Right. Yeah, definitely.
So that that. All right.
Remember, we discussed brain tumors a while back.
That's the most lean condition you can have because it goes to the most young part of
the body. So that means it's the most lean.
So guess what?
The more refined and processed, whatever you want to call it, away from its natural
state, it is the more it's going to go to the brain.
That's a very easy thing to surmise.
Right. And they tell you that it targets the receptors better.
It actually, you know, even if without that science side, if you understand the mean and
young, the more refined it is away from its natural state, the more lean it is.
And guess what? Part of the body.
Right. Right.
So if it's something that's extremely young.
Right, like a mineral or a dried meat product, it's going to go boom right down to
the most young part of the body, which is the feet, the ankles and all that.
Right. Right. OK, so.
Yeah. OK. That's why you'll see a lot of Americans with poor diets when they wear
shorts. They have swollen ankles as very reddish rash around it.
Oh, yeah. That's from really bad meat products and bad salt.
Because you got to have iodized salt, by the way.
Whatever this is, a tangent might sound like it.
Fluoride, fluoride, fluoride or iodine.
No one in order to put fluoride into it wouldn't work.
You can't put fluoride toothpaste.
You can't put iodine in salt.
You can't. It's always in a compound form.
So if you're making sodas, let's say carbonated beverages.
Right. OK. We can put carbon dioxide or we can put carbon monoxide in it.
Now, if you drink the one with carbon monoxide, you'll still be OK.
But it's toxic. It's known to be a toxin.
Right. Right. Now, with fluoride, it's sodium fluoride
or calcium fluoride.
Now, calcium fluoride you'll find in tissue in the body.
But sodium fluoride is a toxin, just like carbon monoxide.
And that's what they deliberately put in toothpaste.
So when someone says a fluoride or not, the calcium isn't right.
Is that carbonated with what dioxide or monoxide?
So defining definitions, understanding how ridiculously stupid
this society is and the pitfalls of taking a broad brush.
For example, the fluoride thing, if you don't specify
what kind of fluoride compound, it's either fluoride in general is good or bad.
And yet enough people believe it's good, even though it's overtly a poison.
They'll think it's good, you see, because they're not defining it.
How simple?
You know, there's many people that say I'm a believer in fluoride.
I said, yes, all mine.
I mean, I don't have an idol of fluoride to worship,
but it's not elemental fluoride.
It's it's not and it's not calcium fluoride.
And they're like, well, what is it?
I mean, it's sodium fluoride, which is a toxin.
I give the carbonated beverage analogy with the monoxide and dioxide.
Then they rethink it instead of getting in someone's face and arguing about it.
See, if I meet you and you want to talk to me, right, you're you're an idiot.
Until I'm like Napoleonic law, you're guilty until proven innocent.
Napoleonic law. Right, right.
In other words, you wouldn't be in court. Right.
Why would they bring an innocent person here?
So you're an idiot and a complete moron unless you prove otherwise.
So when I'm around doing my day, waving hello, whatever people I don't know.
That's why I'll just say casually, hey, you know, if you ask me, like,
when I was, you know, anybody, I met three morons today.
I didn't know they're morons.
I didn't speak to them or anything.
But to say that they're not morons is actually a very bad bet.
So even though I didn't really speak to these three people that I met to call
the morons and then show me to go back and investigate,
they'll probably prove to be very quickly.
You see. Right. So there's it's easy to have stereotypes. Right.
But I go beyond stereotype.
It's like you're all fucking idiots until you prove otherwise.
And now what are my chances of being let down?
Like slim than not minimal.
You're typecasting instead of stereotyping.
Yeah. So it's like everyone's an idiot.
You know, someone said, well, he said something upsetting.
Yeah, he's a fucking moron. Right.
Why would you like why would you?
You know. So, yeah.
So this is my moral code that I have within my society of one, let's say.
Right. So you see, morality is based on what society you're in. Right.
So so I would just say from a long
shot to even a focal short shot on drugs. Yeah.
Uh, if if it can help you, like pain relief, if you're in pain,
you know, if to wake you up, if you're sleepy, to put you to sleep,
if you're awake by necessity, you know, all these things out of necessity.
Absolutely. Use it. It's a tool. Right.
So if it's being used as a tool to have a positive effect,
then you don't believe that.
In other words, if you have a plan and you can't carry through,
carry out that plan and you can take a drug that will help you do it, do it.
But not recreationally. No.
OK, so in other words, the trucker who takes speed to stay awake
so he doesn't crash his truck, you don't object to that.
No, not at all. As long as he knows what's going on.
If you take enough of it, it won't work as well.
Right. Because your body will start compensating.
It's not that you get used to the drugs.
Your body compensates, adds more of the other stuff,
and then you'll have physical degradation, eyesight and all this other stuff.
And if you're if you're getting high on no dose as a trucker,
the chances of you falling asleep or eventually if you do it a lot is actually
while you're driving is actually higher than those who never did it.
Believe it or not.
So so it's also the way it's used as well.
So I mean, that's the repercussions like meth.
It's nothing wrong with.
I went to his party once and this guy had some grayish beige
looking crystals in a bag.
So a very wealthy household.
I'm like, what the hell is that crack?
He says no.
And he goes up to the bathroom vanity light, you know,
where they have those big light bulbs, the vanity glow bulbs.
Right. Yeah, right.
Takes the bulb off and he breaks the the end off where the filament
and the screw in part is.
And he puts the crystals in the now we have this globe. Right. Right.
He puts the crystals in there and lights it.
And he says, take a puff of that, you know, and he's passing it around.
I'm like, holy shit.
So he says he's eating up the glass.
He's eating up the glass from the bulb in order to sort of.
Yeah. And you get this dark greenish yellow smoke.
And you take a hit of that.
It's kind of like crack, believe it or not.
Very much like crack.
It even smells like crack.
Well, not really. But so this is I've seen stuff like that.
No, it definitely smells different than crack.
Yeah, I mean, I mean, you'll be high for like you.
You won't sleep for two days or three days when you're on that.
Well, I manufactured crack before and crack is a very short term thing.
It doesn't last very long.
Oh, no. Yeah, that's right.
What gets people hooked when you first do crack?
It's like, oh, it's actually even better than heroin,
believe it or not, on the first shot.
And all you he's like, this is the best high.
Let's get some more and get some more.
And it's not like the first time you're always searching for that first time.
You'll never.
And then what happens is you get a headache and you start blaming.
Well, it was a we got a bum source wasn't a good source.
No, no. That's what happens.
You get one good high on crack and that's it.
It's like a virgin drug.
You know, you lose you can only lose your virginity once. Right.
That's true. We used to call chasing the dragon, actually.
Yeah. And after you smoke enough of it, you think you want some more.
And you think you drop some and you're looking on the ground.
Maybe you dropped one. It's called ghost busting. Oh, yeah.
Right. It's like, oh, you could always tell looking at the ground,
picking up things. I know we have more.
That's it's a spirit behind.
There's a spirit behind all this stuff.
But these spirits are indifferent to us.
Well, see, that's one thing I got a hold of you.
Yeah, I was going to ask you that.
I was going to try to let you finish through this entire rant.
But I got to ask you, because it does seem to me as though.
And I got to tell you, I object that there's nothing wrong with meth
because the spiritual entity that seems to be involved with meth
is really insidious.
I mean, more insidious than cocaine, more insidious than heroin.
Actually, the heroin entity seems to be benevolent to me.
So does the cannabis.
Well, the opiate, the opium, mostly
the heroin, remember, was done by created by Bayer.
It was more refined, right?
Yeah. No, it was processed with dry cleaning material.
It was a refinement to get people off of off of what was the thing before it.
Like methadone is to get people off of heroin.
Yeah, it was a synthetic. Right.
It was the synthetic to get people off of the thing.
It was partly synthetic. Yeah.
But the opium was initially.
And, you know, that's a painkiller, right?
Very effective.
And so places that opium to morphine, morphine.
Yeah. And the heroin was to get heroin was literally created
like and like a thing to get you off of morphine.
That was the truth of it, because there was a lot of morphine addicts.
Everybody was high on morphine in the 1800s.
If you were, quote unquote, middle class, blue collar or whatever, you got morphine.
That's what that was the drug to get.
Well, you had some around.
And also they did. There were studies done.
Even women used to get what he called morphine, basically
morphine and opium in liquid form for menstrual cramps.
That's a true story.
And suppositories. Yeah. Yeah.
That's the. Yeah.
So they did a study, though, that medical services, places that had,
you know, trauma, medical and whatever, that kind of stuff.
They noticed that where morphine was available,
there were fewer fatalities for the obvious reason.
Right. You know, not going into shock. Right.
Well, less stress and less shock from the pain.
Right. Well, if anyone that works in trauma,
the first thing they do, if you're conscious and you're not,
I mean, you want to morphine, they ask you that, you know,
they'll put a bag, drip bag with it or whatever.
However, I'll sit in the street.
It's very popular in hospitals today.
If they ask you, are you in a lot of pain?
If you say, well, maybe this is it.
Well, you know, you're what we've got.
You classify it as you can get.
And we can give you a shot of morphine if you want it. Right.
And any times I was on the phone once with someone,
this nurse says, well, give me a shot more.
I said, take it. Take it. Yeah. Take it. Take it.
And so have someone sneak in a cocktail with you to like a beer or pina colada.
Because that enhances the effect.
Oh, my gosh. Yeah. And it's like tripping.
You'll trip for a few minutes and when it first hits you.
But a little extra. This is a good.
This is all part of the experience.
I think that the drugs take off some of the filtering effect
that we have, you know, normally, you know, the common senses. Right.
So but morality is where you come from. Right.
Like, for example, people don't know this today.
But if you get cut, maybe not.
But I know 20 years ago, if you were caught with any amount
of what they call cannabis or marijuana in Malaysia, it was the death penalty.
Right. Right. Right.
So, I mean, think about that for a minute.
And they were still doing it a couple of years ago in the Philippines.
There was a guy that rather famously was was executing drug traffickers. Right.
Well, I'm not talking drug traffickers.
We're talking about you in your luggage, you know?
Oh, no. That's what they were saying they were.
But it was somebody who had a bag of dope.
Basically, you were caught with it.
You were a trafficker. Done.
Oh, yeah. Well, they could tell.
Their morality there is that you're going to we don't mess with that
because, you know, you'll right.
Suffer capital punishment.
But you'll suffer a capital punishment because you're messing with their capital.
I mean, they're the only ones allowed.
Oh, yeah. What's the golden triangle? Right.
Well, or thereabouts. Yes.
I think there are more people living in the Muslims in Malaysia
and Philippines and one other place than there are all of all of Middle East.
I think so. I think Malaysia.
Yeah. Yeah. And people think all the Muslims are in the Middle East.
They're not. It's like two to one, twice as many Muslims in Asia
than there are in East Asia.
Yeah. Malaysia and Morocco is another place, too,
where there's a lot anyway.
Well, I'm talking about that end of the world.
You Morocco, most people would still consider to be Middle East
or, you know, Arabian sort of a real northern Africa.
OK, but more Muslims live in the Pacific Rim.
Yeah. Than anywhere else. Yeah.
So, OK, what was the other question?
Well, let's see the other question.
Besides, oh, the pyramids. Right.
Yeah. You want to know if you had any thoughts about that?
Yeah. What I do know about the pyramids is from people that have been there.
I've never taken an interest in them
because it's just a big pile of stones and we don't have any history for it.
So first, and I have met some people, interestingly,
that came over here in 2003 that visited the pyramids with some.
We're not going to give any names like Ivy West or Jordan Maxwell,
but they had visited the pyramid and they had
saw what they call ground penetrating radar.
There's an entire city below the pyramids that was being drained
and they've been draining it for a very long time.
And then many years later, 2010, there was a site report that the government's
been draining this place for 10 years to go under there.
And I think it was spoken of
by ancient Greek people.
But I would I would direct, you know, archaics for the pyramid.
His stuff is seems to be pretty tight on that.
Yeah. And the archaics, though, just this year's on the pyramid.
Yeah. Though Jordan visited the pyramids, he didn't actually talk about it too much.
It was on his manager.
Well, I just mentioned I wasn't going to mention
his manager was the person I mentioned.
She stayed here in the house in Tucson until until they parted company,
because, you know, but anyway, yeah, no, I know about that.
And then I was one of the people that came in after they parted company
that was, you know, got more friendly with them after that.
But anyway, so but all right.
So pyramids, not much to say about it.
It's not that big a deal.
So you don't see a spiritual aspect to that.
Yeah, there is. It's a few.
Again, if you go back to what he says about it, it's a major deal.
It's probably one of the most important structures on the planet.
OK, but the great the great pyramid.
But you would defer to him then.
Oh, absolutely. I know all that. Why bother?
Fair enough. Yeah, I'm not even going to get into it.
I would I give it.
I don't endorse him, but he gets a seal of approval on his pyramid research.
OK, so his pyramids and his chronological history, he's compiled everything
that was sensibly and rationally compiled from before.
You know, from decades and centuries.
And he's put it together to show, hey, not only is it
rational and legitimate to say this, this and that about the pyramid,
but it also ties in with what he's talking about, which is the phoenix.
So he gets a seal of approval on the pyramid subject.
Well, you know, it's super rare for anybody actually to do any original work
of their own. At best, people have collected other people's work
that is of useful, you know, abuse.
That's the truth of it anymore.
I don't see people doing original work at best.
They collect, you know, the stuff that doesn't need to be discarded.
And they collect it together and present it to you again.
Well, you can get a notion and then put it together in original form.
And he's done that with the pyramid.
No one else has discussed it the way it was like.
I know you won't find biological vacuum at anywhere.
Right. And the full moon is the first day of the month.
And the day starts at noon.
You use those together and you get a 30 day a month.
You get a 30 day lunar.
Anyway, there are some things
that are extremely original to what we're doing here.
Well, there is one, by the way, by others also.
But generally, the no topic is original.
Now, the topic itself on everything is.
Right now, I've only ever heard one other person talk about solar noon
being the beginning of the day.
One other person.
He's got a weird accent and I have no idea how to get ahold of him.
He's got like a YouTube channel. Yeah.
OK, well, there's solar.
And it was academia acknowledges it to be solar.
And I think you might have run into that right when I say, go look it up.
Oh, yeah. And yeah.
And we know from being children of the 60s, 70s or whatever,
you know, you get a check in the mail when you're really young or whatever.
You go, right. Counted as the next day.
So I mean, it goes on and on and on.
So, yeah, no, that was the proof of it is that if you showed up at the bank
after lunch, it was the next day, even though they didn't change.
They would change their calendar.
The rest of the world didn't yet,
which I always found funny is like, you know, if today was the first
and you show up there at noon everywhere else except at the bank, it's the first.
Yeah, they didn't number it as a second, but they just say it's tomorrow.
So even though it's the first, that was yesterday to them.
Yeah. Yeah.
Because it's an old convention.
But now with the electronic convention, paperwork reduction acts and all that.
Right. But it still holds true on many other aspects of culture.
That reminds me, it's true with agriculture as well.
Yeah, there was a couple of things in chat, actually,
that you just triggered a thought of somebody asked about something else
because it goes along with the.
Oh, yeah. With the last time.
Yeah. Is this is this all on this email?
Yeah, it's the. OK, yeah, I see.
There's one that you remember when I was explaining the shake,
you got through the shake.
Thanks to all the interruptions, Chuck.
Thanks a lot. But no, I'm just.
Yeah, it's usually when I give something new, it's something new.
And I think that I'm not griping about it.
But when I was describing that shake, I was just expecting to be three minutes,
but it turned into 20.
Well, I wanted to make sure I understood exactly what you're saying.
Well, you can go back and re-listen to it.
Yeah. Yeah. So when I have a discussion,
this is what we're like behind the scenes, folks.
Yeah. If I'm going to bring up something new, I'll just tell you, sit back.
Give me two minutes.
And and and and you know what?
Because all this is recorded, there's no Q&A, right?
Yeah. There's no Q&A.
So very often I'll bring it.
I mean, I've got a bunch of stuff, more stuff with food that's very original.
And of course, when they start the subject,
you know, first thing in your mind is, yeah, I know what that is.
But no, you don't.
You don't know what this is because, you know, I've actually
it's just like with their cakes, with the pyramids.
If I'm going to bring up, try something, go look at this recipe.
Yeah, it's out there.
But when I start to get into a process with food, it's
because it's totally original to what I'm doing.
But so that was another thing that would be.
You remember Mr. Rogers?
He comes in and he changes his sweater, puts his different shoes on.
I remember. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Well, we could. I was thinking the other day,
every time we start a sonic, start out with a food tip, right?
Like who doesn't want to make delicious things to eat, right?
That'd be great. But but yeah, I want to keep it down to just two or three minutes
and not make it a part of the show.
And you just listen where the sonic event.
Oh, did I say show? I never say that.
You did. I know.
Hey, maybe. Yeah, I need some drugs.
I had to sit back and say nothing.
I just I was trying to ask questions.
I know what it just sounded very familiar, right?
A smoothie, right?
Like who the fuck doesn't know how to make a smoothie?
But you don't like this.
You may be like this is five star.
Yeah. You know, or three star if you're Michelin.
So anyway. Yeah.
So yeah, this person here sat through.
I'll just read a little bit. I got the gist of it.
It's Greek. I sat through the shake to get the booty.
But we do a verbal dissertation on how the signature or signatory
plays in the digital realm.
Yes. Let's just take that part first.
OK. And OK.
So the digital realm is really about
whatever. OK, we spoke about the banking convention
previous to electronics, right?
How it was all paper. OK.
When digital came in, you could multiply that times
500 or 1000 times more transactions, right?
Possible. Right.
OK, so what they're doing, which was much harder to do
and not in the digital realm, is they take your blank endorsement.
Here's what you sign for the right.
Remember, you you sign it.
You write your name as an autograph.
But when someone asks you to sign, you're signing as a signatory
to represent someone else.
You're always an agent, right?
And don't call it a straw man.
This is one part where Brendan Joe Williams, I agree with him.
It's a public corporation.
And when it was created a few days after,
you get the long form birth certificate.
And you'll see when that name came into being.
So you could actually say your birthday is this day,
but the public corporation's birthday is this day.
Disalignate them.
If you make a big deal about your name and all caps in a legal setting,
they don't they'll they'll make that as a distraction.
Focus on that, that you're crazy.
So if anyone tries to object to that, you just you ignore what they're saying
and just object to their comment.
But either way,
what happens with the digital stuff?
I'll give you an example.
A few years ago, there was a few reports about Wells Fargo's in trouble
because they opened a quarter of a million credit card accounts
without people knowing about it. Correct.
Well, all they did was take their ace hardware.
OK, you know, when you go to a big store like Autozone's hardware,
you return an item, you say sign for it, you know, that you return.
I'm like, oh, my gosh, how much credit do you guys want?
I always make a stink.
And they hate, you know, that most part.
They call me the professor.
But they're like, oh, yeah, yeah.
With the credit stuff. Yeah, we don't care.
You should be very insulted by that.
Yeah. Yeah, I know. But I'm not.
But I understand where from their point of view. Right. Right.
So, you know, I mean, it's I should be more insulted
when a dog wants to hump my leg to a degree.
But either way, I'm not. Right.
Because it's a dog. Right.
And then that's for domination. It's not sexual. Exactly. Yeah.
So in a similar way, what Autozone, they take those.
It's digital. It's an image of the signature, the signature.
And they can put it anywhere they want.
They can do an in-house memorandum that they did a survey
and people signed it for, you know, whatever.
And they could put the signature on it.
It's theirs. Right. And it's their pixels.
They won't say it's your signature, but they control that image. Right.
And Wells Fargo took people's images of their signature
and put them in all kinds of contracts and stuff to show that, hey,
this new credit department that creative came up with
and financial said wouldn't work.
Well, look how great it's doing.
And it all copied, fakes it, you know, copied images.
Right. That's what the digital is.
Now, the problem with digital is that you cannot
control those conditions. Right.
Now, I'll give you another thing.
I was working with someone who was getting 36 million dollars
on an oil and gas deal. Right.
And the bank I was at, we were having lunch and he gets a call
and he says, we got to go. I said, I got it.
I said, why do you have to go?
I said, come, I'll come with you.
I have to go to the bank.
They want me to sign a check. OK.
And I'm like, wait a second, you're selling it.
They're supposed to give you a check. Right.
Why do they want you to?
So he walks in, sits down.
They bring this corporate checkbook.
They're real long ones, big checks. Of course.
And there's two people there and they're covering everything with white paper.
And they tell him, sign here's a check.
So actually signed a check.
And I was like, well, I don't want to make a big deal.
It's not my business, really. It's his business. Right.
I said, why are they making use the second time?
He said, after you said you're taking your signature and there,
you know, how many checks are you going to how many times? Right.
So he doesn't know. He doesn't care. Right.
So and then then we almost get back to his house.
And he's like, this is the second time they had me do this.
I'm like, oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh.
So they have some kind of transaction thing going
to show that he's writing checks. Right.
Right. It's just a signature.
And someone else is signing. Oh, my gosh.
So let's say a bank does a thirty six million dollar deal.
They're probably getting two, three, four hundred, five hundred million.
They're creating all this stuff. Right.
Running it to the Federal Reserve.
Now, imagine, Chuck, that I'm going to buy, let's say, your car
for a thousand dollars, five thousand, ten thousand.
And we're going to use this bank.
And you get a call from your bank saying, all right, the Greek, whatever.
Chuck, you need to come to the bank to sign a check.
I'm like, wait a second.
Well, why am I signing checks?
Yeah. Why am I signing a check?
Yeah, I can endorse it on the back.
So, yeah. But why? And then walk out.
What the hell are you doing?
So this kind of the point here is that, yeah, digital seems like a wild west
to the 10th power.
But also they've done that even without digital, having people come in and sign
checks for one and they cover, you know, they cover the check with a piece of paper.
They like two people, one guy's holding the book, the checkbook.
It's one of the big corporate checkbooks.
And another person, you know, clenching the white paper over.
You can't see anything on the check.
This is like a book where each page is actually a script of either three to five
large checks. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's really, yeah, bank checks.
Yeah. So I'm like, holy shit, this is not my I'm not involved in this at all.
So who am I to say to the banker, what the fuck are you doing?
I know what you're doing.
You know, show us, you know, actually we're going to litigate, you know, whatever.
No, I wasn't. I was just sitting back watching.
So I can someday I got a thrill.
I felt really bad. I was going to throw up. Right.
But at the same time, I was like, great, I can tell this story.
This is what I saw someday in the future.
And no one can tell me otherwise, because I saw it right.
I was there.
So you can't tell me that banks don't make you do that bullshit.
They do. Oh, let's.
Oh, how about this?
This is the only bank in the world that makes people that ask people to do that.
Right. What are the chances of that?
No, no.
What are the chances of someone argues this for against it and says, well,
that was the only bank in the world that did such a thing.
That's like saying, that's the only politician I've ever seen.
Why? Come on.
Yeah. Yeah. So this is.
So that's why when you know something really well
and someone is wants to debate you or counter you, where you're going to find.
I know what I know. I know.
I know how if you don't want. I'm not going.
What am I getting to convince you?
Right. Nothing. This is just right.
So anyway, this is how.
So is it is it any is the digital made it worse than the non-digital?
No, I just gave the example. Right.
Maybe. All right. If you want to be naive.
Yeah, maybe this is his.
The bank in Houston was the only bank that makes people come in and sign checks
and not show them for what? Let's say still.
Well, hasn't it made things happen faster and at a higher volume or no?
Yes. At a higher volume also creates more confusion.
So when you ask for records,
those things can be changed with a keystroke. Right.
Right. You can write when you ask for subpoena records, if they're all digital.
Right. I mean, look at the birth certificate, Obama birth certificate.
Right. By the way, you know, there are programs that can show you
if something's been photoshopped. Right.
Yeah, of course. Right.
And now there's programs to show you if it's an AI voice.
Mm hmm. Right. So I just wanted to put that out there.
Yes, there is. There have been for a little bit.
There have been. It's funny because those really leave signatures.
Yeah, so it does.
They're digital signatures.
OK. You know, I say humans are fucked.
OK, so here's the thing.
The stance that I take. Avoid it. Don't do any banking.
By the way. Well, do it the long way.
Right. You cash money orders in person.
You know, this way you'll make, you know, like, quote unquote,
paying a bill becomes a big deal.
Right. So you have a little more excitement in your life. Right.
And so I don't have time to do that.
Well, watch what happens if you don't do any banking.
How much more time you will have because you won't be doing the shit
that you're doing because you have banking.
You get it. Right.
Cable goes away. Internet goes away.
Right. Your subscriptions go away.
You got plenty of time now.
Right. Mm hmm.
It sounds kind of crazy.
Yeah. I'm thinking to myself, there's a whole lot of people
that would not know what to do with themselves.
Well, you have plenty of time.
You could spend a whole day just going down a quote unquote pay the gas bill.
Yeah. But, you know, if the meaning of life is to have your time
wasted and to waste other people's time mutually.
Exactly. They're wasting your time.
You have two ways to waste.
Well, two ways is you just give so much to someone.
They can't get anything done or you throw so little at them
that even if they get it done, little little got done. Right.
So you need to make it so they're ineffective because they can't do anything
or you give them so much to do.
They're overwhelmed that they can't possibly accomplish anything.
It's never made for the right. Right.
Never moderated. Exactly.
Never would be the Greek, which would be everything in moderation.
It's actually ancient Greek.
It's the actual translation of fun.
Metro Ariston would be all middle
Irish or the best, which we would make more sense
to translate it as all things in moderation.
But OK, so continuing most places no longer require a signature
and credit card receipts, and many banks no longer require deposit slips.
Yeah, that's done by conditions, innovations and things like that. Right.
I know the old system is dead.
Not really. But what replaces it?
Now, how can you avoid the traps and be free while here?
Well, I just set me to get a million.
Thank you, Natalia.
But what what what I would suggest is you I answered that already.
So would you agree?
But what let me just look at those places no longer.
OK, they don't require a signature, because at some point I've seen this.
If you have a bank account or whatever, you'll get a letter says
our terms and conditions have changed.
This is a letter to notify you.
Yeah. Right.
And in there, it'll say that if you've made your marks here
and you make your marks there, it's kind of like if you continue,
you agree to the terms. Right.
Kind of thing.
And they can also have terms that they don't disclose there.
And they said for more terms or whatever, contact this department.
Most people don't.
You'll see it's 170 pages, not just one letter or three pages. Right.
So there's some there's an innovation or something done
to change the terms and conditions.
Well, besides that, I had a guy tell me the other day
that he got a renewal on his driver's license or whatever.
And he looked down and realized
that he had not signed this thing in probably 20 years.
And they had a copy of his signature that they just added to the document.
So, you know, that's right.
Now, to get rid of the driver's license, which I have done.
You need a form.
You just don't give it back to them like Brandon, Joe Williams.
They still show him as having a driver's license.
He's one in giving you send it back in the mail, registered mail.
There is a form.
But when you you know how they have forms for everything.
None of the DMV motor vehicle places have the form.
You have to find out the form number
and print it off a PDF online and then send that in.
And then you got a threatening letter.
You know, if we catch you on the road, I'm always confiscate your vehicle.
You could vote. Right.
So there is a cancellation.
There's that I know many, many people,
there's thousands of people that sent the driver's license in.
It'll just be suspended or still active.
But I once I had it checked out and it showed on the main computer canceled.
Right. So to cancel it, it's a special form.
I don't have the number of the form,
but you can actually some things are easy to find on Google.
And you know, you think might be hard.
Like there's a form the IRS has for to unsubscribe from their service.
It's forty six ninety eight or forty six.
Thirty nine something or sixty four, whatever.
It's called revocation of election.
But you want to read that carefully and maybe, you know, all IRS paperwork,
by the way, you look at 1040, you know, it says this is a 1040 return for this
or you can make your own statement, which is or make a statement,
make a statement statement. Yeah.
Yeah. Make a state says you don't have to use those forms.
I suggest, you know, what's on the form and make your statement short and sweet.
Don't give whatever you don't want to give and punch where you want it.
You know, you're talking about twenty six CFR
fifteen point one dash to the revocation of election to the.
Yeah, there's a form for that's not the form.
That's by the way, if you find the title twenty six, it's somewhere in there.
It says that let it not be construed that anything in this title
has any legal effect, by the way.
Are you familiar with that one?
I haven't read it yet. I just happen to.
Yeah, there's you could put in like the title.
Twenty six has no legal effect.
Basically, it tells you if you copy anything from this title
or use anything from this title, it has no effect.
That's a basically telling you the indirect way that it has no effect. Right.
Yeah. So but it does for certain people.
If you're a federal citizen, they always.
But anyway, it has to do.
And by the way, Congress is one of the, you know, the 16th Amendment.
We're just going on a tangent here.
It does give the lawful money clause in the 16th Amendment itself.
And they also codified it,
which is in 12 U.S.C.
411, the demand for lawful money.
It's codified that the other.
That's a remedy, by the way.
The other remedy is Congress.
If you do a revocation of election with the IRS, they send you back a letter
saying we've got your revocation of election via U.S.
Congress.
In other words, the U.S.
Congress backs that up. Yeah. Right.
Now, I remember Schultz, who does Charlie Brown.
Yeah, Charles Schultz.
Charles, he published this a long time ago.
He is Charlie Brown and the typewriter.
Right. He's saying, Dear IRS, please, I'd like to unsubscribe.
He's telling you there is an unsubscription form for it.
Charles Schultz.
You could actually wonder if you do a.
You might find the card.
You might show up.
Yeah. OK, let me see.
Schultz, a cartoonist, unsubscribed from the IRS.
You'll see. You'll see what I'm talking about.
It's an old car. It was in the newspapers, too, right?
I do these little disclosures.
Yeah, I'm thinking it was in the 70s, wasn't it?
Yeah, yeah, probably.
Yeah, that's that's what it was.
They even did an animation with Charlie Brown.
Well, they did. Yeah, actually, I think they might have made it.
OK, so they had little shorts in between the main story for Charlie Brown
when they were running him on TV a lot.
And I think they put it in one of those.
It just probably was.
They even did commercials, ads based around them.
But anyway, let's see if you pull up the cartoon.
Well, let's see if you've seen it or.
Yeah, no, I absolutely.
But it's Snoopy typing, I think.
It might be Snoopy. Yeah, let me see.
I've got a picture.
Dear IRS, hold on, hold on.
There's images.
And let's see.
Hang on just a second, because anyway, that's.
Yeah, you know, there was a lot of what we're saying has been popularized
because there are people in prison, supposedly.
No one's in prison for not paying taxes.
You're in there for giving false information or conspiracy.
Right. I actually have a comic strip which was printed in black and white,
which is not the TV.
But I know I saw this on TV as well.
And it says, Dear IRS.
And then he's still at the typewriter.
He's at the top of his doghouse there.
Snoopy says, I'm writing to you to cancel my subscription.
Please remove my name from your mailing list.
That's right. Yeah, literally.
That's and that's it.
Yeah. Four panels.
Yeah. There you go.
Yeah. If you like it, that's the revocation of election.
There is a form they have that.
OK, I'll grab the screenshot for you and I'll give it to you.
But no, it's fine.
Yeah, I just because I remember I remember reading that
when it was in vogue at the time.
I remember, you know, that what was that done?
Does it give a date for that?
Was it 74, 75 or something?
Hang on. I'll grab it in a sec.
I was just trying to throw it.
I don't know. We're being we're kind of hanging on the slot.
But this is important to me personally, because I remember
actually reading it in the paper where it was published or the book or whatever.
Well, I remember seeing it on TV as well, which is really odd because.
Yeah, I know. That's why I know it was.
So, yeah. You know.
So right before it gets really bad, they tell you they give you the remedy.
Like, you know, before 9-11, they called a lot of people
in certain offices and said, don't show up, don't fly in an airplane.
And don't you know. Right. Right.
And now they've made it into a meme where Snoopy's holding the letter,
by the way, and standing there with a smirk on his face.
Let's see. Unfortunately, they're not giving you the form.
No, I'm taking it. No, I'm taking it.
No, they're not giving you the form number.
I'm taking a look for 56, right?
Form 56, 56.
Yeah, no, they don't show that.
And I don't see the date.
They have a Facebook page about it.
They got all kinds of things about it.
Yeah, but they're not telling.
Yeah, it's it's still it's skirting around the issue.
It's skirting around.
You know, are there birds in that bush? Right. Right.
As long as there are no crabs in that bush.
But anyway, yeah, no birds in that bush.
Are there birds in that bush?
That shit gets itchy.
But anyway. Yeah. OK, gotcha.
At least that's what I'm told. That's what I'm told.
And scabies. Oh, my gosh.
I've heard of those things. Those things.
By the way, if you live in a college dorm, it's not unusual to get that,
by the way, if you live in a college dorm or military.
It's very used to be famous.
I've read a couple of, you know, fictional kind of.
Yeah, everything's great here, except we all got the crabs. Right.
So you get it from the bathroom or whatever conditions they have.
You know, bedbugs are worse.
Got to be honest with you.
Yeah, I've never had bedbugs.
I did get the crabs from being in a dorm situation.
I was at a guy's house for a couple of hours and I started itching and found out
that the reason why is because I was actually bitten by these bedbugs.
And I took a look at what they're supposed to look like.
And they're pretty hideous looking things. Yeah.
They got a big old shit.
They shouldn't call them bedbugs because that sounds too.
Yeah, they're not. Yeah, that's right.
You know, they should have another name for them.
They should call them syringe bugs because it looks like they got a giant needle
on the tip of their head shape, a company that accompanies it.
Yeah, it looks like a shock absorber boot.
Yeah. With a needle on the end. Yeah. Yeah.
OK, another email we've got is something about the, you know,
the voter's registration, which is something I also learned from someone
who was doing that.
Just to recap, this is in Los Lunos,
Mexico. I'm not going to mention names.
Carl Meyer's son basically grew up in a trailer.
And he's the only one out of four or five siblings
that had a quarter million dollar house and $100,000 BMW
because he was like the second guy or third guy in charge of New Mexico
for collecting voter registration and get a percentage.
And I knew what was going on.
And I said, you know, these things are monetized, you know, for 10, 20 grand.
He puts his thumb up like, you know, up much higher, you know.
So he knew about the money system and stuff.
It's like being it's like being a toll collector, but the pay is much better.
Yeah. OK. Yeah. So he was.
Yeah. So it was in the 50, 55.
I couldn't give you a number thousand.
This is back in 2007.
So someone's if we put a signature on it, does it change it?
No, because again, these things are not scrutinized that way.
If you're doing a voter registration, they're not going to scrutinize
the signature because this is a stack of suckers.
But I think the voters registration thing started out for prison inmates.
Right. A while back.
Don't hold me on this.
I may have been in the US, but they started the whole voter
registration for prison inmates that didn't have a felonious crime
that they could still eligible to vote.
But because they're in the prison, they had to register.
So essentially, if you're registering to vote with that,
you're considered a felon, let's say indirectly.
Yeah, this is how bad it is.
Well, because technically speaking, you're not supposed to be voting
in national elections, are you?
No, the whole thing is really bad.
It's not even a government.
You can't vote for who's the CEO of McDonald's.
But even according to their laws, it's not legal for you to vote
in an election.
No, it's actually an act of insurgency.
Right. Take it if you take it in law because you're not part of that group.
But especially not anymore.
You're three times removed. Right.
By the way, all this stuff we're talking about the system.
If all the laws were followed and everyone we would we would be
in a paradise right now.
In other words, if you wanted to, you know, Social Security card
is a credit card, right?
And they give the Social Security number.
So when so people find out the the their government lost
everything in a card game to the banks, take your number, you'll get what you need.
So everyone knew that they had a credit card.
You know, you don't get a bill at the end of the month.
In other words, it is the bill.
You just give them the number and get what you want.
Where would the poverty and homelessness and all that be?
Or where would the wondering how I'm going to pay for tuition to be?
No, no, none of that.
Well, that's the thing.
I mean, I can't even imagine what it would be like to not have to stress over.
Where am I going to get?
You know, that's right. Yeah.
But how are people going to act with this current?
I mean, that's why I say the people here cannot have you.
If you want to create that society, you have to eliminate ninety nine point
nine, nine, nine, nine, nine, nine.
Let's see what may well maybe a little less than around there
because nine percent of the population, too small of a percentage of people
that would seek self-improvement afterwards and just, you know, say,
you know what, since I don't have to struggle with that anymore.
Now, let me do something really useful and, you know, make things better,
even better. Right.
I mean, you know, that's what a very small percentage would try to do.
That's what the issue is.
You know, it's sort of like a Jacque Fresco thing
where he had the image about the managed cities and all that.
It's a great idea if people would, you know, actually do it, isn't it?
Yeah, but it's not for this.
We were genetically modified and groomed to be this way.
So it is really if you don't.
In other words, if you know, as I know, I know 100 percent
if people got together and just followed all the rules and all the laws,
we'd be in a in a, you know, utopia.
But just like in the Matrix,
you know, it was too perfectly it doesn't work out.
So they rejected it. Yes.
Yeah. All you got to do, by the way, whether it's police, bankers, lawyers,
doctors, hold them to the rules, hold them to the rules and everything's fine.
But no one knows or follows the rules.
And we've gone through that before.
But again, OK, let's go back to the voters registration.
It didn't answer.
No, they're not going to look at the signature
because they're stacking these things up a mile high and they're monetizing them.
And it could take a long time.
They have four years to monetize them. Right.
So for whatever, two years, depending on how the what's part of the cycle
and what which being, you know, because some places that you can have elections
every two years, it's like even checks are only supposed to be valid for what?
Up to two years. Right.
Isn't that the case with checks?
I think it's one hundred and eighty days, six months.
Oh, is that what what?
OK, I thought that up to two.
Yeah. So so no, the voters registration, I would definitely cancel that shit.
I mean, cancel everything that you can if you want to, you know, be more.
Now, here's the thing.
Brandon Joe Williams talks about just the passport.
But I know they'll use that against you,
because when you go to court, the clerk sees what kind of contracts you have.
And I, by the way, they when you you know, the judge is up there at the whatever
and you just come in and they have a clerk, they type in the name
and she just kind of moves the monitor or he has the code of how many contracts
you have and if someone shows up like no contracts, the judge sits up
and he's like, how can I help you today?
He kind of is really different. Right.
Well, if you have a lot of contracts, it's like the you know, you're fucking dickhead.
You're going to come over here and argue, you know, so.
But they will use the passport against you.
I don't think they show much of a difference on that.
But at this point, I have pretty much nothing.
But anyway, and also I'm one of the few people that has actually legally
expatriated legally, not the way, you know, send in mail.
I mean, I you know, one day we'll get into that.
I have the document here
that I'm not a citizen.
So that's that's what I thought it was important.
And that was in the middle of my heightened spiritual sussing out like
you know, if God, quote unquote, is so good,
why would he put us in a situation like this?
And I was in between.
Well, it's to learn or be punished one or the other. Right.
So I was like, let me just get out of anything that I see is unfit to get out of.
But I would suggest that
it doesn't really matter that much
unless you find yourself to be very active in many things
where you increase the chances of interacting with agencies and these whatever.
Then you might want to minimize it and get out. Right.
But even if you're not interacting, if they're going around
just doing a sweep, checking people,
do you want to be listed in their system as, you know, fish in a barrel? Right.
So but I don't think there's enough time left to argue,
you know, for the future. Right.
Because, you know, whether you look at the early part of 2030s
or the 2040, 2046, 2052
as a major demise of the current system, that's really close.
Really, really close.
So so less than a decade left until we have a major, major shift.
Yeah. All the systems go away, but it's going to be really nasty
where the utility companies, let's say, OK, I'm near Tucson, Arizona, right?
The the water, gas, electric utility power plants,
they're going to be told don't show up to work.
All right. OK.
And the people will go home and they're like, wait a second.
I love my city.
I love my job.
And tell me not to show up for work.
You're not going to get paid.
But I know by the way things run, if no one shows up, we'll lose power.
We'll lose water. We'll lose gas. Right.
So I'm going to show up to work anyway.
Well, when you show up to work, you're going to see somewhere there
with a Wackenhut badge and they'll blow your freaking head off.
They'll give you one warning and they'll kill you.
That's how desperate they are about shutting everything down.
Not now, but in the future.
So we'll have people, obviously, that say, hey, I'll go do it for no money
as a social responsibility.
Maybe I'll get a medal one day.
So there'll be people there, you know, black.
The black, what do you call them?
Black ops type or SOG people.
You're Wackenhut, right?
To kill you. Yeah. Yeah.
To make sure the utilities go down.
Guys who are dressed entirely in black and have some sort of badge on them.
Some or not a Wackenhut guy also could have could be 50, 60 years old.
We've really bad hair, kind of like what was
with a big potbelly.
What was the Rocky Horror Picture show?
The guy who played Igor with the stringy hair like that?
Whatever anyone's name.
Well, Meatloaf was in it with stringy hair, which.
Yeah. Yeah. Something like this.
Just like something you see in a horror movie would be a Wackenhut.
That is what they have.
They hire people like that.
Also, you wouldn't have the top of the barrel or whatever, even moderately
looking. They're not like the Nazis.
Like the crazy guy in Friday.
Like the crazy guy in Friday, the 13th, who says you're all doomed.
Yeah. Yeah. You know, lackey there or whatever.
You know, he'll do it.
They don't know what you know. They don't care.
This is really, really bad.
Just like JP Morgan said.
Well, what this is allegedly.
What do you what were you what are you prepared to do
if the people find out how the money system works?
It was all easy.
I'll just print enough money to get half the people to kill the other half.
Right. So, yeah.
Memorialized in the was at the gangs of New York, where the the rich people say,
well, what we'll do is we'll just hire half of the poor to kill
the other half of the poor.
There you go.
Precisely.