You already know what's rated Y because you subscribed to it and appreciate you for doing
that. Also, look for an announcement coming up in your messages regarding subscriptions.
Things are going to change in the next week or two. Anyway, all that having been said,
it's 1 48. And Greg, how are you feeling tonight? Good. I just got up from a nap,
sleep inertia. I got to give my old old ass body more than 10 minutes to wake up,
but otherwise, I'm all right. I had some really good dinner. And yeah, anybody that's in the chat,
by the way, I posted the other day on the sidebar and YouTube pays YouTube for references and stuff
like that. And because it's actually pretty ridiculous. It's all dummy load pretty much
mostly except for specific things that you're looking for. I call it YouTube University.
I saw people go to YouTube. Somebody asked me about some process, electrical stuff. I said,
go to YouTube university, calls me back the next day. He's like, I was looking for this
YouTube university. I can't find it. I said, Oh no, no, no. I mean, you just mean the how to stuff,
which is DIY how to stuff on YouTube. If you have a piece of electronics, you're not familiar with it.
You can find a video in five minutes. That'll get you up to speed. Somebody's already had this
thing three years. You're done with it in five minutes, whatever you want, let's say tear down
or inside or whatever. And you'll have someone like one of my favorite videos is you want to
replace a module inside of a, of a desktop, right? And you don't know how to do it. Okay. No problem.
You can find mechanical stuff for cars. Somebody, I wanted to change a water pump and I found the
exact same model year and everything. The guy introduces you and I did this with a starter.
I had no idea. And, uh, and then you said, look, just look on YouTube. You'll find it. And I said,
okay, so I went and, uh, actually I did. Yeah. So one of my favorite videos is one that I found
the exact what they call vehicle. And the guy starts out, says, we're going to change the
water pump on this year, whatever model make. But, uh, when you see a video, we're going to
change the water pump. It only takes 30 minutes, but I'm not going to do it. My girlfriend's going
to do it. I was like, Oh, cool. You know? So now what does that do for most guys? That's a confidence
builder, right? Cause what girls won't work on cars is what people typically think. Right? Well,
if it's, if he can make it, so it's easy enough to explain his girlfriend who does nothing with
cars, then that means it look, that means I can explain it to you. It definitely builds confidence
in that guy's video because it's like, tell you she's a tomboy and she grew up, uh, you know,
with, uh, hammers and saws, not dolby and stuff. So maybe, but yeah, either way you can have fun
with it. All right. So I posted a video, uh, again, going back to Brendan Jones came around
the sidebar and the channel, but it had this, he's interviewing someone and I'll bring up his name.
Very impressed by him. Uh, it's a Mansa Mahatha. I'll spell it. M A N S A. And then Mahatha M A H
A T H A. It's his YouTube channel. Okay. Brother's been around for a while. And if you've been
listening to Greek on finances and stuff for me through the years, like back, back, back in the
day on revolution radio around 2009, 10, 11, whatever I was on, I would go on there. I say,
Hey, all these job fairs there. Anytime you have an application that is money that is monetized,
you know, you know, people put in applications and got refused. Yeah. Well, you want your
application back because that was deposited in the federal reserve. They got the full value of it.
That's what they're doing to treat people like idiots, but well, if you act like one, right.
So, um, or morons or infants, but he, if you understand what I've been saying for the past
12, 14 years online, he's put it all together in a very cogent, simple way that you actually had
to act on it. Now, one thing, one thing I want to mention, there's a book that needs to be acquired
because it's out of print, you know, like 500 bucks or 200 bucks, but the book is a business
law, semi-colon subtitle is the legal, ethical and international environment.
There's another one that's new. That's like 10 bucks called business law, the legal,
ethical and e-commerce. That's different. I don't know about that one.
So e-commerce would have to include the stuff that's, you know, on the internet, right?
Yeah. Well, we're interested more on this one and it's, uh, the author is Henry R.
Cheese man, uh, as just like, it's like cheese man. Okay, cool. Yeah. That's the author business
law, the legal, ethical and international environment. I'll, I'll do some hunting
around. Uh, maybe I'll find something on eBay or call around some of the used bookstores,
which we have a big in here in Tucson called Bookman's. Uh, I'll look around for it. The
reason, okay, this is an important book because it's basically the backbone of business law and
business, uh, transactions that are bills of exchange. So when a, one company sends another
company, a bill, they endorse it a certain way, send it back and then they bring it to the bank
and it's good. Right. Then when people try to do it with their bills, they get tested and all that.
That's why you want to, I have been enjoying the past few days listening to Mansa Mahatha.
Um, he doesn't have too many trolls or haters, but is the, just like the archaics guys, you know,
Jason, he's got some trolls in here, but they never go against him with anything of substance,
you know? So I've watched a couple of those videos and it's like, shows you how no one's
paying attention, but months, uh, is, and I do, I wouldn't say, you know, like I don't endorse Jason
or brochures. I don't say he's got great stuff, but I don't endorse him. Right. Right. And, and,
and Brandon, Joe Williams got good stuff, but I don't endorse him. Right. I'm pretty close to
saying I would endorse Mansa Mahatha tentatively. He has a pending endorsement. Really? Like,
like Pat, like patent pending, you know, it's not, you know, years ago when we used to hang
out in the ghetto making stuff, make a contraption, you know, point at it and go,
yo kid, Pat pending. And I'm like, yo, cool, man. You know, it kind of like a funny way to say,
like, you know, look how, uh, this is not really, uh, certified, but it's on its way.
I would say a pending, a pending endorsement for Mansa Mahatha so far, very impressed, uh,
for a young man, I'm allowed to say that cause I'm in my 60th year now and he's in his 32nd.
So I remember what I was doing when he was born, you know, that year, like yesterday,
by the way, uh, I'm about five 11, 175 pounds. And I still wear a 31 and a half 32 waist. Like
I did when I was in high school. So when you tell people you're in your 60th year, they think of
like, you know, what happens to most, especially white people when they hit, you know, 50, even
they fall apart. You know, I'm not talking about your body type, fat, skinny, whatever. I'm just,
you start falling apart. I am not falling apart. Uh, as a matter of fact, uh, this might be too
much information, but when I get out of the shower, I stand in front of the foggy mirror. I'm like,
how the hell did this 25 year old get in here? Wait a second. That's not a 25 year old. That's
me. Right. So in other words, is that reality or is that your perception though? You know,
my perception. Yeah. So the thing is, yeah. Uh, and you know, I really don't care about the body,
but on the other hand, I've been fortunate enough that a lot of times I say it's a lemon
whatever, but that's fine. But what I'm saying is, um, when you say this is just for most people.
Okay. When I was younger, I was, I was fortunate to have brief encounters with some wise people.
And I remember being, uh, around 1973, 74 and, uh, an older wise man says, you know,
you're going to be getting old when you go into a room and you're, and everyone in the room is
younger than you. Now, you know, you're getting old. Right. And you know what? That's been hitting
me a lot lately where I go out into public. Oh, really? Uh, I look around and I see everyone's
younger than you pretty much, you know, Prissy, you know, you could tell, right. You know,
but you know, for example, when I go down by the university and I see all the college students
crossing the street, I'm like, Oh my gosh, they look like babies, but they're 20, 21. Right.
Oh yeah. Well, once, once somebody in their twenties starts to look like children to you,
you know, you pay a certain point babies. Oh my gosh. Look, 30 years ago to me, those 20 year
olds were women, baby. You know what I mean? No more. Now I look at them and I'm like,
someone sent me one in a box or whatever. I could go to the beach with, I wouldn't mind.
Right. Kind of thing. You know what happens? You know how people joke around with stuff like that.
But now I look at them and I go, Oh my gosh. You know? Yeah. So, but all that, I'm just giving,
the reason I brought up that stuff is because of perspective. So what I mean is, uh, uh, yeah. Uh,
he, he's also, if you listen to what I've been speaking on for a while,
and man, so he's brings up the same stuff. How could these people be called adults when
they act like children, a lot of stupid people in the world, they choose to be that way.
Leave them alone, get away from them. Your family's going to break up. You're going to
lose your friends, very similar stuff. Uh, in that perspective, he doesn't know he,
he would do really well with like O and G uh, stuff and rated why he would take them to the next level.
Um, because he's, he, he doesn't understand the body. He doesn't understand history that much.
He does know that the holidays and the timekeeping is bullshit.
Well, are you sure about that? I mean, just cause he hasn't spoken on it. Doesn't mean that he has,
he has a little bit. Yeah. He thinks there's a virus and he doesn't know. Yeah. And he brought
up though that he, that, uh, you know, I don't do the new years. I'm doing the real new years,
which is in the spring and Christmas and all that is fake. Yeah. He's on his way. Okay.
So he's got part of it, but yeah, he's got part of it. Yeah. But how can you not, if you,
when you get to a certain level on one thing or two things, everything else becomes suspect,
rightly so, right? Well, that's the thing. Yeah. You start the question, you go, wait a minute.
You know, if this established idea that is supposed to be, you know, the absolute rock
solid thing, it's this agreement, this social agreement. Well, they never say, they never say
it's rock solid either. That's why I tell people to read, but it's always presumptive. We take it
to ourselves. We take it as being rocks. I'd never said it was no matter what it is. No,
it's only because it's been repeated so many times that you just kind of go, well, it must be,
you know, peer pressure, peer pressure. Perfect. Yep. Yeah. So anyway, with him, he understands,
like I've said, you know, nobody will do anything. Even if someone's coming to take
bacon off day back, no one's going to do anything. Uh, right. They just sit there
and he understands. So anyway, uh, you have a pending endorsement, um, uh, for him and for
his stuff. Why? Because he's a doer. He gets stuff done. He's this, uh, I'll try to post another
video or so where some people got remedy. The whole presumption is this, well, not a presumptive
assumption, uh, is this if you go to an institution, government doesn't matter what it is.
Usually the corporations cause they, they get access to the federal reserve discount window
and various other trusts. Anyone asking you for social security numbers, tapping that's a credit
card. You've heard me say that before. Yes. Uh, they're billing that they're getting everything.
And then they send you a bill, which is actually a form of money that they need for you to endorse
for them to continue doing business. It doesn't mean that you're, that's going to pick. That's
why you're like, he gets into all bills. Are they positive or negative numbers? Always positive
bigger numbers. Are you the payee or the payer? In other words, who's sending the bill is the
payer. Remember how I said years ago in the Dunning process, uh, in a credit based environment,
if you send someone a bill, you also have to send them the check to pay for it with,
you know, I've been saying that for a long time. This comes out of various acts and codes that are
old that still hold true. The laws are still the same. They just modify them. Right. And
this is what he's getting about how to actually get remedy based on performance
and setting yourself up using the language. You can't go to them, say the U S is bankrupt.
There's that and the other, you know, there's no debt. No, no, no. It doesn't work that way.
It's all based on contract performance, all contracts. I've even seen people in courts
when they beat, when they beat the charges, they still had to pay fines or go to jail because they
had a contract with the court. And, uh, yeah. And also when they'd steal homes from in the state
steals homes from old ladies, uh, literally, uh, they say, don't worry. It's just business.
It's all business. That's why I stressed that book, which is brought up in one of his videos,
uh, with the remedy. So anyway, yeah, I'm very impressed. Well, he actually talks about how
to apply this too, which is to get remedy. Yeah. Yeah. Anything. So you go to a corporate real
estate agent for an apartment and they give you a lease and ask for a social security number
that goes okay. And that's whatever's on there. Like you go get a car. The most popular one is
to get a car. Right? So let's say a $30,000 car with interest five years is going to cost you
46,000. And then they add this, that, and the other. So that note, they go and they get 46,000,
right? They give you the car. The car is a gift. They're just interested in security on that
security note. That note keepers put on the stock market and sold it. And they sell the note after
for maybe 70%. And that keep keeps processing and processing. So you don't want the car when
you get a car loan, you want to revise the contract or send a letter after because the
contract says you can do this, but you're revising the contract and you want full security interest
in that security and anything that happens to it. Oh, that's why there's so many people in real life,
even that don't know this when, how many times have you heard? I don't know if you understand
the car market. You'll hear this not often, maybe one out of 10, one out of 20 people,
they had the car repossessed, right? Cause they didn't make the payments. Let's say
but three months later, they get a check for $10,000. You ever heard this happen? I have
heard of that. And usually the people don't know why it happened to be honest with you. Yeah. Yeah.
And it's not a technical error. It's because when there's certain codes and laws that when the note
gets sold a certain way, some amount has to go back to the principal and you're always the principal.
He gets into all this, you know, whatever, but he doesn't even do that. Where, okay. You know,
where you're talking about them taking old lady's houses when they take it away for a tax lien,
they turn around. If they auction off that house and you get more money than what the tax lien is
worth in the auction, they refund on your difference. But the lien, okay. Same with
the mortgage. The actual collateral you think is the house. No, it's the actual note. There's a
guy named Raja. Right. But if the note is only, let's just say the note has, you know, $10,000
left on it. Right. And they auction off the house for 40. Then that means that there's a $30,000
actually, it doesn't here. I give you a note, but does that works at all? Sorry. Well,
some people have gotten paid this way. I'm saying, so I'm going to explain, you know,
that's necessarily what the secure is when they do with the house. Okay. Payments are separate,
the security, which is the collateral. Okay. I've seen people, uh, it was, uh, an $80,000 mortgage.
They had $10,000 left. They couldn't do it. They left, but, and the foreclosure was for the, the
10,000 they couldn't pay or the full 80,000 all over again, the full 80,000 all over again. So
payments don't mean anything, uh, cause they're right. So anyway, you don't get a mortgage,
you don't, but anyway, the whole thing is he gets into some of the things with car loans.
You can do anything, anyone in anything that asks for a social security number,
that's your credit card. Now the guy Raja, uh, back in the day, about 2012, 2013, he, they,
he found out about this and he was an accountant that did forensic accounting where you use Fidelity
Merrill Lynch to get into the accounts. And he says, if this is true, I'm going to look up the
mortgage I got for a $400,000 house. And he found out that it was sold so many times it created
$90 million worth of transactions. Wow. Doesn't, doesn't mean it made 90 million. Just, it just
got flipped so many times that if you add it up, every time it flipped became 90 million worth of
transactions in the economy. He flipped out, sued Wells Fargo. And the second time they went to
court Wells Fargo outside of the courtroom offered him a job. I can get more into about Raja. That's
another thing. But, uh, so this goes on and on now. Um, what's his name? The, uh, uh, the fellow
I just mentioned, see, I'm not even, I'm all too, uh, Mansa. I've talked about getting accounts with
Fidelity, for example, they're the cheapest or Merrill Lynch. He went to them, he got an account.
He says, listen, I want you to look up, uh, an account for me. And they asked me, do you have
the QSIP number? He said, no, he gives them the account. They don't tell them what it's for,
for federal, for Fidelity or Merrill Lynch to look up. And these account numbers are long
enough that they're self-identifying. You know what I mean? Okay. So he gave him his Verizon
cell phone account and he says, I want you to look up this account if it's being traded
internationally. And on the online, the guy on the computer in real time is like, yeah, it is,
uh, for 17 million, his phone bill account, you know, when he opened the account and he's like,
damn. And then he started looking up other accounts and the federal, the Fidelity guy says,
you're, you, what do you do, man? You have a lot of spending going on here. Cause he thought
the accounts that he was giving were like corporate accounts, not the social security,
what he gave out social securities for, you know? So he, he says, you're running a hundred
million dollars over the past five years. What kind of business are you doing? He,
just from a social security number, he didn't tell the guy Fidelity, he's given him cell phone
accounts and a business, I mean, um, you know, child payment, uh, service payments and basic
credit cards. You can tell them that because when you're looking up these numbers, it doesn't
classify them really. It just, it puts them in a general category, international domestic, right?
Transferable NPIs and all that stuff. So he was basically running all the accounts that he knew
who he had given a social security number to five years ago, running a hundred, over a hundred
million dollars worth of transactions. Doesn't mean there's a hundred million there. No,
it's transit. In other words, you don't want the money. You want the credit because put,
put it this way. Like he says, if you have a credit card and you have a deal, you create a deal with
the, uh, uh, credit card company, the servicer, their servicers that every month you just endorse
the bill, send it back. Right. You can get it. Let me put it this way. Why do you need cash money?
Tell me what you really can't get with a credit without with a credit card. What can you not get?
Right. Weren't you mentioning that there's something called cash app or something? You
got your weed dealer or whatever you give them a cash app, right? Almost anything you could do.
Yeah. The cash app they have a, what do they call it? There's a bunch of different ones. Yeah.
China. So yeah. So what you do is you could throw down some classes or have a little
bullshit subscription podcast or whatever. You get your cash from that for the weed man.
Right. Yeah. So, so otherwise, if you have a credit card that you just basically endorsed
at the end of every month or whatever billing period, they decide to give it to you on,
you're good to go. Right. You can spell like you said, I just spent the whole day in my draws.
I don't even know what day it is. No need because yeah, you got it right there. You just use everyone
is like this. If you have a social security number, you can do this too. Uh, and for years I've been
talking about, there's so many things you can do with, with credit cards, even just applying for
jobs, applying for jobs. You can make money applying for the job anyway. And someone asked
me about that recently. And I don't think that's the way to go. It's pretty tough to do it. Uh,
but you know, and I'm not talking to applying for a mom and pop store,
trying to like a big corporation. When they ask you certain questions and you don't want to give
them the information and they give you that in writing, you got lit a federal litigation
for three times what the salary is. So I knew that I'm not going to mention
application to like dollar general who would, would work this way. Cause they're a large
corporation. Yeah. They would ask, right. So the woman, she was doing hotel maintenance,
okay. Uh, cleaning lady, a hotel, she was looking for a job and they got to me and I said, Oh,
really? They said that, get it right. They got it writing. So wherever the salary was three times,
she assumed when they got it. So all you gotta do is apply for a job once a month and make a
hundred grand a month, you know, not right away in litigation. If you get the paper,
or if it's like the law, you know, sometimes they, they make a re you, you know, give it to me in
writing like, no, we won't give it to you in writing. Well, then it's kind of hard to prove
that they're breaking, you know, that they're right. Right. Quote, unquote, breaking the law,
but sometimes they're stupid enough to put it in writing. Now, I believe certain acts, if you tell
them that is being recorded in the beginning of the recording, that voice testimony recording is
good enough in some States. I know it is in, uh, in, in some of this, I know it's not in some of
the States and you put it that way. Right. Like in Arizona, it's not, but what they call a single
party, like only one party needs to know in other States, both parties need to be informed as long
as they're informed. Right. Kind of like Rodney King, you know, they couldn't use the videotape
as evidence, right. Remember? Right. But if you, if you tell generally in most States though, most
in the United States, uh, if you basically inform the other person, look, you're being,
that's why they do that when they call you up and they go, this is being recorded.
You know, they tell you it's for training purposes, blah, blah, blah, blah, but it doesn't
matter. They informed you when it's not being recorded because here's the thing, the amount of,
it has to be organized when it's recorded. And I don't think they're investing in that. They're
just saying it's being recorded just in case. Yeah. Right. It's a precautionary. Uh, so anyway,
yeah. Pending, I'm saying this three times, you had a pending endorsement pending, uh, for,
again, what I've, I'm working on my acoustic modules and some stuff getting prepared for
potential big water project, which I'm keeping private right now. I think I shared a little bit
with you, Chuck. Um, and, uh, working around here, like call it the shop, you know, the back of the
shed where all the stuff that it's called the art department, you know, when something doesn't come
right, we put it behind the shed. That's the art department. Okay. Get it. So, um, I have, uh,
outdoor sun. So while I'm doing what I'm doing during the day, I can afford to have on a podcast
or someone speaking, you know, over the airwaves here. So that's how I pretty much get my studying
done. If I'm not doing black ink on white paper reading, which I'm starting to appreciate again,
by the way, there's something about having, you know, the right reading glasses for my story asked
and, uh, the right amount of light to read a book, right? To actually read.
I've always said, I never appreciate it because people are like, Oh, you got to appreciate,
you know, you can have a million books on this device. And I'm like, no, no, no, no. Yeah. But
looking at it for summer, even what's that thing made for a reading? Uh, it's a little thing.
Yeah, that's right. Even that thing doesn't just doesn't do it. There's something about the
reflective light, not the generated light that works. So, uh, works well. It has a lot of effect
on the mind. Maybe it's, uh, you know, one thing I want to get on, by the way, also just total
segue. I think I'm done with that section of it, but I did post a video on the to tango,
which is, I wrote, watch this video, you know, before your next meal. Um, so the other thing is,
uh, what are we doing here? Essentially I've been thinking about this past few days is all these,
you know, how people say, oh yeah, you want to find an exit. Don't get into the soul trap.
There's an exodus period. I'm like, okay, that's fine. If you believe in reincarnation, by the way,
um, or you think, let's say you ponder it right now, but let's say it's considered right.
And that word considered me something totally different in contract law. But anyway,
when you can think about the afterlife of the, uh, I just gave it away reincarnation
and you were here before that makes this your incarnation. Now the afterlife does,
if not it's an afterlife to something that came before it. Yeah, that's right. Well,
just to say it makes this the, the afterlife or an afterlife. So then, so actually talking about
reincarnation negates the concepts of afterlife, right? Because you see, so, and then there's
discussions about this, that are the other, the soul trap coming down. And I'm like, but wait a
second. When people said afterlife, they literally mean a different type of circumstance that you
ascend to. That's outside. I always thought that, but if you're doing a reincarnation,
that negates that because each time you come around is another after life. It's another light
after the one, no one's discussing that. Here's the thing that one is discussing.
What about people that were sent here on administrative error and they weren't
supposed to be here. It was a fuck up. Now what? Oh, I said, well, God, I'll make no mistakes.
I'll see you. But we've already established, even in any Holy book, that the gods have people that
work for them that take care of all this little silly shit. Like who gets to incarnate on earth,
let's say, right? So those guys are fallible. Are they not? Yes. As we find out that the angels are
quite fallible. The ones that are popular, politically correct are called angels and
saints. And the ones that are not politically correct at the time are called demons, right?
But they're all the same anyway. So, so what I would say here is there is no discussion
on people that were set here, spirits that were put here incarnated into a soul and a body
that was due to what administrative error. There's plenty of films about that kind of stuff.
There was a movie Brazil where they went and hunted this guy down because it was a clerical
error, right? A fly went on the typewriter and it was bottle instead of title. And right. There's
mistakes where a number, right. The number falls off and it's a wrong number. And the SWAT team
comes in there, you know, so whatever, or even in the case of a social security number, somebody
hits a five instead of a six, you know, or it looks like a six instead of five because it got
smeared. That's just a credit card. Social security can not be used for identification. Please read
the back of it. And if it's lost, return it back. It's not yours. It's theirs. Yeah. So yeah,
but I get it. Okay. So what about, there is no discussion about people sent here
by administrative. I didn't say by accident, because I don't believe this is thing as an
accident. I'm going to bounce around one more thing because you know how I've been talking
about yin and yang for a long time. It's the balances. I gave the can of beans last time as
an example. Right. One thing that I didn't get into too much, the bouncing back and forth, you know,
the can of beans that I did last week, the reason that you have the bouncing back and forth is the
balance, right? When, right, you have expansion balanced by contraction. So we have that, when I
say, I don't believe in accidents, this is why, because when I hear someone, oh, how such and so,
and they say, well, they got into an accident. They went through a windshield. I said, oh,
you know, most, the first thing that runs through my mind when I hear about someone going through
a windshield, I said, man, that person was so yin that they needed to go through a windshield
to make them yang. It's a balance you see. So when you fall, break your leg, that's you don't,
you see it as a misfortune, but in the big scheme, the energetic scheme, it's actually
you making balance. So when you're really far out one way, you still seem you're okay. Bam,
you get hit with something to bring you into balance. Just like when you pull a rubber band
really far and slingshot, let it go. It's not just attention. It's going the other way to make
balance to where it was before you pulled on the thing, right? You see, you're pulling it slow,
stretching. It's becoming yin, yin, yin can't come anymore. Yin, you let it go. Then boom,
yang, yang is very fast and very sharp. So when I hear about what's called an accident
or, you know, misfortunate events to people and talk to their person, to the body,
I think my mind goes already. It's when I think about what was the cause of the most fortune?
Oh my gosh, that was one hell of a young reaction. I want to know that most people say,
I want to know how they are now that they, you know, went through the car accident. I'm like,
no, no, no. I want to know how they were right before the car accident. That's what you want
to avoid. Cause you couldn't avoid, right? Because if you avoided the condition or how they were
prior to the car accident, guess what? That car accident would not have happened. And this is
also shown in movies, two people arguing, looking at each other in the car and then bam, they get
hit. Right? Well, I'll give you a simple example. I got hit by a guy on a bicycle. I told you some
weeks ago and it slammed me down and hurt me pretty bad. But here's the thing. If I had actually
stepped probably like three feet to my right and decided to walk in a slightly different path,
I wouldn't have been in the path. This guy was on to hit me. Right. Well, then you got to see
if, did it knock you down? Did you both fall down? This is not, you know, this is not all these
little details during the thing, but what's more important to again, this guy, I know he did go
through a windshield and when I, when he recovered, he had, you could see the facial scars and all
that. Cause you still, even though it's safety glass, it will tear you up. Oh yeah. Excuse me.
Matter of fact, I think it tears you up worse, to be honest with you. The safety glasses,
they go through that. That's even more harsh. Cause it, it kind of, yeah. Well, yeah. Yeah.
It won't be a clean cut. Um, the, um, the, uh, I knew him before and after he's personality and
everything completely changed, uh, after that also. So, but anyway, when most people are like,
oh, how are they? I said, again, repeating myself, I want to know what they were doing just before,
just before. And they're like, why? I'm like, oh my gosh, you know, it's too much to explain,
but I figured I'd give this here because the, the idea of understanding balance that's why I'm
still looking for another way to explain meaning young, because it has nothing to do with modifying
some Asian philosophy. It has to do with everything forming a balance, pressure, mediation,
temperature mediation, which is also pressure mediation, uh, event mediation.
Right. How many times have you heard like, oh, that crowd is so angry. They're about to,
you know, explode. Right. Right. Let's do something to calm them down. Right. Mediation
of events. Right. Oh, you can observe that. If you observe a crowd, if you step away from it,
you can sort of see when they're going to get out. I mean, cause I used to do security and you could
see, you could predict what you were about to see, because I mean, you could sense that things were
coming to attention. You could see people getting closer together. You could see people starting to
push more and you could see the action begin before something bad would sort of blow up out
of it. You know what I mean? Uh, for the crowd, uh, Gustav Le Bon wrote a book called the crowd.
Yeah. It's crowd psychology. Excellent book. Really. Uh, what I get out of it is that he's
got the, the positives and negatives is in order when, in order to speak to the general masses on
any concept, you have to simplify that concept so much. And so far that it no longer resembles
its original idea. That's the problem with dealing with big crowds, uh, essentially,
but he has a book called the evolution of matter, which was actually on the FBI book seizure list
for many decades. Right now, people don't know we, the FBI has had or has the dangerous,
dangerous literature, uh, kind of thing is what it's called the book seizure list, right?
Uh, the BSL, but now it's, uh, they just shut down your website, right? You go to the website
and it has an FBI page on it or something, right? That's the problem with the digital books is now
they can do what I, what I describe as digital book burning. It's much easier to flip a switch
and kill, kill a digital book and ebook. Okay. The interesting thing about that book and other
things that were written around them, other periodicals was that at the time was the time
of nuclear physics, but I'm curious, all that was talking about the 1905 or something. And, um,
by the way, we had Dimitri here and you know, the, the nuclear thermonuclear devices and all that,
that was all well known and successfully tested in the 18 hundreds, by the way,
but on small scale, you could still see small scale nuclear detonations, uh, declassified
military where they make a small nuke and it's a, the diameter is only about six feet, right?
So it's very, very contained, but this was very well known by that. Not very well known, but it
was established that it was possible and known to be a direction they were moving in. He kind of
poked fun at the establishment saying, Hey, you can take a ordinary material, certain metals
and make them fissionable. There's no atomic fission, by the way, that's just a way to
describe and not explain what's going on. And that's, I think what, that's what I think put
it on the, uh, book seizure list, but it is available online. I don't, it, and the scans
do not look like they've been redacted and they do. He does give the material properties of things
that can be used as I explained, but no one's going to make anything like that. I'm just saying
that what we've been sold a bag of goods, the purpose of understanding what he's speaking of
is for certain, if you, you've heard of like unlimited energy or material production,
you can modify certain things like aluminum and mercury and things like that to do what,
you know, you only read about Los Alamos laboratory does with $500 million. You can do
yourself that if you, if you understand, you understand the concept and follow, you know,
what he's, what he's given with directions. So, you know, this whole thing about energy and all
that is a, is a whole other blast, so to speak. It doesn't work the way we've been told. Um,
but anyway, yeah, I think that's a, that's, unless you've got any questions or anything,
maybe this is it. Yep. I think we're good. Okay.