Apparently, that's what we're known as and 104 is this sonic event of rated Y.
So anyway, Greek, how are you doing?
Oh, I'm doing, you know, 104 is 41, right?
Not 14 on the palindrome.
Oh, well, I messed up.
Yeah, I looked at 14 zeros and ever factor in numerology.
Well, you could be 14.
No, couldn't it?
I mean, why is it more properly 41?
What do you think?
Because it's it's the way palindromes work.
Oh, all right.
Fair enough.
I'm not going to argue with you because I don't have a defense.
But that's fine.
We're recording now.
So we're going to go with it.
And because it's something that, you know, it gets dusty, right?
Yeah, I just want to bring something up.
You know, if you right now we have a really good orange crop and a really a really good
citrus crop, particularly lemons.
I'll post a picture of a basket of lemons and onions, by the way.
Is it time for oranges right now?
I thought oranges come later.
I thought it was after.
Yeah, it's a winter crop where it's warm, like in the southern like 30 latitude.
OK, yeah, yeah.
But you shouldn't have it if you're in New York, right?
No matter how much the medical technicians tell you, right, present it.
So it doesn't work that way.
But because they always want to break it down to the chemical until you get the vitamin
C out of it.
But that's not what it's about.
No one knows what's in food.
That's why Rudolf Houshka, H.A., I guess it's H.A.U.S.H.K.A.
or Houshka, yeah, German studied.
He wondered why certain diseases and ailments were prevented when you eat certain foods
and you got those diseases and ailments if you didn't eat those foods like scurvy, right?
Oh, yes.
Things like sailors had to take things with them, you know, otherwise they would get ill.
And he says there's something in the food that's a vitality that can be that we could
examine and maybe extract.
And he worked on that.
And he says, well, it only works when the food is fresh and you have it within, you
know, a certain amount of time when you do the extractions.
But they said, hey, we could just tell the people, you know, you can extract nutrition
and vitality out of food.
We'll call it the vitamin industry.
So people that take these supplements, you do have to take a lot of them.
It's I'm not going to knock vitamin therapy because some people have gotten better with
it.
But the original research showed that it must be fresh.
So and of good quality.
But I want to mention onions.
Onions are one of those things.
We're talking about white onions, you know, the ones that are underground, not the green
spring onion.
It's a food that you can eat.
For example, you're usually look, if onions were hard to grow, they would be a delicacy
because there's nothing like onion and garlic that is such a harsh vegetable in its raw
state, no matter how you prepare it.
But when you heat it and cook it, it becomes as sweet as, you know, caramel or anything
else you could have.
Right.
So because of that quality, it would be considered a delicacy like truffles or whatever if it
was hard to grow.
But because it's not hard to grow, we take it for granted.
What I mean by that is raw onion, a white onion or red onion is more than most people
can handle because of this.
Again, it's supposedly, you know, you cut slicing onions and it makes you cry.
It's like a sulfur compound, you know, that can be measured at that point that does that
and a few other things.
If you can neutralize that, now you're making the onion more succulent in a sense.
And the way you neutralize that is go ahead and slice your onions thinner, thicker, however
you want to slice them in a bowl.
Uh, place them in a bowl and add a liberal amount of salt and a liberal amount of vinegar.
Lemon juice won't work.
I've tried this.
So vinegar, like a wine vinegar, balsamic vinegar, rice vinegar works the best.
And toss it and cover it and make a pressed salad with it for 15 minutes.
Pressed salad is like you ever see wilted lettuce, you know?
Yeah.
OK.
So the way you make a pressed salad, you have two saucers.
You just put the, uh, the, the onion on one saucer and place the other saucer on top of
the weight to push on the onions, right?
If you don't want to do that, you could put a piece of cling wrap over the onions and
then put another plate, you know, just to press them.
Or you could put them in one of those resealable Ziploc type bags and roll up the bag real
tight.
Put it under, you know, under your armpit or something.
I don't know.
I'm just joking.
Put some pressure on it for about 15 minutes.
OK.
The salt in the vinegar will neutralize that.
How would you call it?
Obtrusive onion or offensive onion flavor.
If you seal it really tight, it seems like the onion lets off.
That has nothing to do with sealing.
This has to do with neutralizing it.
Well, yeah.
But since you mentioned it in the salt.
Right.
But since you mentioned it.
By the way, you don't even have to press it.
You can just toss it.
You mix it with a fork for about 30 seconds.
That'll do it, too.
But when you press it, it almost acts like a mild pickling.
So try that, by the way.
And so if you end up with a 50 pound bag of organic onions that you don't know what to
do with, you can make an onion relish like this.
Right.
You know how you serve salt.
You see how like in Mexican food they have a salsa, which is fresh chopped tomato, onion,
pepper, things like that.
Right.
I've made something like that tonight with a lot of onion, a little bit of tomato and
some, you know, the salt and vinegar mixture.
It was you can basically eat it.
If someone walked into the room and saw you eating that copious amount of onion like that,
they'll say, wow, this guy is a monster.
Right.
Because who the hell can eat onion like that?
Well, it was wonderful.
It stuck with me all my life.
I had one uncle that used to eat a red onion like an apple, literally, like he would.
So he was probably a monster in that category, but not necessarily.
But what I'm saying is I've never brought this up.
This is just one of these simple things that I do.
And people that know me feel it.
That's fantastic.
When I do it, they're like, oh, my gosh, this is onion.
Oh, my gosh.
You know, it's like doesn't taste it's not it's not offensive at all.
It's actually quite delicious.
So I just wanted to bring that up.
So you take away a lot of the sharpness of the onion and you make it more and more qualities
of an onion and only the pleasant qualities are left when you combine it with salt and
vinegar and a little bit of time.
Time as in T.I.M.E.
Not the herb.
It needs it needs a few minutes to neutralize.
OK, no, but what I'm saying is, I mean, if you really neutralize it, you're left with
like a sweet kind of like very much.
Yeah.
All of the things that we consider the pleasant aspects of onion.
This is kind of like a miracle method because you're left with all the good stuff and all
the things that are typically offensive go away.
It's amazing.
And it is quite amazing when you prepare, let's say, a raw salad with a lot of white
onion and it's visible and people will look at that and they're like, I don't want any
of that.
Right.
Because they're used to the offense.
And whoever tries it is like, oh, my gosh, this is absolutely delicious because you're
getting the onion flavor without any offense.
So try that.
Well, what I did, I did.
I made the Roma one Roma tomato to an onion, which is a very crappy proportion, because
you would only use if you had an onion and you try to make a salad with just tomato,
you'd need like five tomatoes to balance out that onion.
Right.
Usually.
Yeah.
So this was this was an onion and a small medium onion and a small tomato.
And it balanced that was actually quite delicious.
I had that with a side of baby kale and baby spinach tossed with balsamic vinegar and slight
and shavings of Parmesan cheese.
You're talking about one of those little oblong tomatoes, right?
Yeah, they're firm.
They usually make them usually for sauce because they don't have a lot of seeds.
They were yeah, they're more of the vertical type, not the center of the round type.
I understand.
Yeah, yeah.
That's what I was picturing.
OK, the longer.
Yeah.
The aspect ratio is.
Yeah, I've seen some long that some that look like a small banana.
Sometimes it depends on, you know, the variety.
Right.
It almost comes out like a like a miniature squash, you know, like a miniature squash.
Yeah.
It's not round.
So I had that and with a two inch thick porterhouse steak that was slow, low and slow, 150 degrees
for an hour.
It was left out for about 30 hours, salted with a fan on it to dry it.
So you use your onion relishes like a condiment in this case.
Yeah, well, a condiment was actually a horseradish with lemon juice.
Yeah, that's another thing.
If you enjoy horseradish, if you can either grate it, some of the varieties that are coming
in a jar are very good.
Add some lemon juice to it.
Squeeze a lemon.
You'll see what happens.
It just turns the notch up, turns it up in terms of the flavor of the horseradish.
Yeah, just really delicious.
No starches, you know, just some greens and gardens doing really well.
And yeah.
So this season here.
Yeah, I used to like a little bit of almost a thousand island mix with the I know it sounds
good.
Nobody likes thousand island dressing that thousand island would also be the ketchup
mayo relish.
Combinator.
They call it they call it Russian dressing back east, don't they?
As some well, some people used to.
But, you know, to me, no, it's Russian.
What is the thousand?
Is that white and creamy or no, no, you had it right the first time.
Mustard.
Basically, if you put mustard, excuse me, if you put a little ketchup, a little mayonnaise
and a little bit of relish together, you've got the basics for it.
Right.
Yeah, that's good with iceberg lettuce.
But I like taking that and then putting some horseradish in that.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, you could for spice.
Yeah.
And then when I do sushi at home, I can't find I like that.
That's why I like that on steak myself personally.
I know.
Oh, yeah.
It's horseradish.
Yeah.
Balances out the yin and yang, the root.
Right.
I do.
We get sushi, great fish, typically yellowtail tuna salmon here.
And I make it at home because I'm just not happy with what I get out.
It's way better than what they serve in the restaurants.
I think I posted pics quite a bit.
I can't get Japanese horseradish here.
And the one that you can get is powdered form and it has algae in it.
Actually, did you post pictures of that roll in the chat room that you made?
The actual roll?
Yeah, I made a roll the other day.
I didn't post it.
But yeah, it looks like a hockey.
Well, the one that you made like a couple of months ago that you showed me pictures of,
I was like, it's a very, I mean, tightly professional looking roll.
You know, it looks like.
Yeah, you got it.
Yeah, right.
You got your bamboo mat and all that.
But yeah.
So anyway, sorry.
Go ahead.
What I do is I use the standard horseradish instead of the green.
And it works just as well.
You know, they call it wasabi in Japan.
I can't get fresh wasabi here.
For some reason, I might be able to order it or find someone who can send me some and
try to grow it.
But I use the standard horseradish, which is the same family, just like white onion and
red onion are in the same family.
Right?
Right.
So anyway, that's the food talk.
By the way, before we started recording, you got on and saying that there's stuff
going on in the news.
You want to you want to just fill me in on that?
Yeah, absolutely.
Well, what we got going on at the moment is apparently, you know, according to reports
right now, again, I'm not saying this is the day.
What is it?
The middle of April twenty twenty four on the Pope's work schedule on the Pope's work
schedule.
Right.
What we're looking at here is what we're about to enter the 14th, depending on what
part of the world you're in.
We're on the 13th where we are on the Pope's work schedule of April.
Right.
Which is the fourth month on their work schedule.
So but, you know, nearly tax day.
Right.
Nearly the 15th of April.
That's your normal tax day.
All that good stuff.
OK.
And, you know, this Friday, apparently this Friar's Day kicked off attacks that were
allegedly launched from Iran directly.
But they're drone strikes.
It's not conventional warfare, but drone strikes.
And they're being directed at Israel.
And now everybody's watching to see what the White House response is.
There are people from the Pentagon talking about containment and how they don't want the
region to become completely involved.
The entire region.
Right.
Which is it's too late for that because we talked about that nine years ago.
Well, that plus for six months now, allegedly, there's been this activity that was kicked
off from October on their calendar.
You know, this event that took place that was supposed to be a, quote, terrorist attack,
end quote, from Gaza into Israel.
Anyway, what's happening now is apparently Iran is making these moves with drone strikes.
And this is making, you know, the usual.
And by the way, it's Iran.
Iran is not an Arabian country.
They're not Arab.
They're basically similar to Farsi extraction, like the Afghanistan.
So when you look at it from a cultural perspective, I want people to think of it that way, not
like although geographically Persia.
Yeah.
Geographically, though, was part of Persia.
But the people that are there.
Sure, sure.
But the people in terms of in terms of I would say like Mexican versus Spanish from Europe,
it's even more of a difference than that.
Right.
Because the language is different.
Yes, very.
Yeah.
It's in other words, it's a completely different culture than the, quote, unquote, Arab Israeli
conflict.
They're not Arabic.
Well, should we bring that up?
What the what the thing is, the common idea is that Iran is the backer of all of these
other groups.
Right.
So when I do not.
Well, but I'm just telling you the narrative.
I'm not saying that's true.
But they say that they back Hamas.
They back Hezbollah.
They back Boko Haram.
They back every one of them.
They basically say basically for the public.
According to the public, all of the financial backing for every terrorist group that has
ever been given a name, you know, basically, I could tell you this.
I can't prove it.
But from seeing people who I've seen years now, everyone thinks the U.S. is Israel's
biggest ally.
Yeah, commercially it is.
But the biggest ally financially of Israel is Persia is the is Iran in terms of how would
you call the under mess, the black stuff that happens, that runs the stuff?
It's the black world, you know, versus the vanilla world, you know, the non what would
you call non normal, the non meet mainstream world, the underground, the underground.
Yeah.
That's what Greece is the wheels of the of the mainstream, by the way.
Just like, for example, if you go to a mainstream person's party, if they want to get, quote,
unquote, illegal drugs, they all somehow they're able to find it.
Right.
Of course.
So, yeah.
So in terms of the black world, Persia and Iran and Israel are very, very close, closer
than the U.S., by the way, because in the black world, in the underground world that
the U.S. and the Israeli interests are in competition.
But in the mainstream world, it's the it's the opposite.
So I just find that to be very interesting.
And I can tell you the experience from that comes from Mossad in Tokyo.
Now, they've really publicly cracked down on the Yakuza, which is the old Yakuza, but
the new Yakuza is the new Yakuza, which runs the underworld in Japan.
OK, amongst the Yakuza without because they're not isolationist.
There are two other groups that work dynamically in Tokyo.
And Tokyo is bigger than like half the countries in the world.
Right.
You know, just the city itself.
That's 50 million, 60 million people in Tokyo.
You know, an odd headline, too, which is not, you know, at the at the apex of the current
media headlines is this new thing where they're trying to encourage Japan to stop with this
purity of blood issue.
But that's which again, Main Street.
Yeah.
But it's weird because it seems like an odd time to be talking about, hey, look, you
know what?
They're starting to act like they're the master race again, which is part of the trope.
But they are in a way, you know, give an example.
If you go to Japan today, food prices have not gone up in five years like they have
everywhere else.
Right.
They haven't doubled.
So anyway, they have a different the most people's pets in Tokyo live better than most
average Americans do.
But OK, so let me just go back to this.
So the under the Yakuza share the underworld with the Mossad.
Electronics prices, by the way, even the Chinese electronics that are imported from elsewhere
and everything else are at a fraction of the cost in Japan.
Sure.
And like broadband, what they pay for a cell phone and Internet access is less than a
fifth of what is paid here.
But they're paying like twenty dollars for stuff that we're paying a hundred dollars.
Yeah, yeah.
Pretty much.
Yeah.
The same in Malaysia, by the way, which is another tech capital.
And by the way, a computer, no computer, no problem.
Like brand new top of the line stuff that you pay twelve hundred two thousand dollars for
here is two hundred bucks there.
Just say it can be.
Yeah.
All right.
So they share the underworld with the Israeli Mossad and the Persian mob.
The Persian underworld.
Those are the three players that pretty much run the underworld in Tokyo.
Can I prove it?
Do I have certificates to show?
No.
I'm just telling you from what I've heard and seen since my spring two days in L.A.
How would I say?
Let me give a short story.
You're going to do any off the books business in Asia.
Here's a guarantee you are at some point going to have to encounter someone who is connected
to that.
Well, let me just give a short story that might help my perspective.
Sure.
We were able to via studying Victor Schauberger, by the way, Sam reached out to Victor Schauberger's
grandson at the PKS PKS Institute.
I think it's in Austria.
And the grandson responded and he's interested in what we're doing.
Quite interesting.
That's that's that's a really good thing to put on your CV.
You know, the scale.
Yeah, he's interested in that.
Yeah.
So we'll see.
We're having active correspondence right now.
So that's really cool.
That's really, really cool.
Sorry.
Which institute did you say that was?
PKS.
OK.
Yeah.
Victor Schauberger's grandson runs that.
And I was also in Kurt Hallberg was another water guy in Sweden.
He invited me to go out there.
They meet once clandestinely once a year.
I said, no, no, no.
It's all right.
Do a video if you want to.
They don't speak any English, you know.
Anyway, OK.
So when I was doing the the the only person publicly to show a Victor Schauberger water
spring water synthesizer.
Publicly show it and put it in action.
We were bottling water at ten dollars a quart and we were selling it at places like Erewhon,
which is a very prestigious health food store.
It's so prestigious that the tour buses in L.A. stop there as well.
That's one of the things places sites to see on a tour bus for L.A.
Right, right.
Another place we sold that was Rossum when it got shut down, when the feds busted them
for selling raw milk, which was an illegal bus because it's a private club.
Anyway, the vice president of Japan Airlines, his contacts got our water and he started
putting doing the math on it.
And the story got back to me through an Israeli person that lived in Tokyo that did a whole
bunch of business who had very strong Iranian contacts, also money contacts, all working
together.
And the story goes like this.
Well, the first time we served the water to the Israeli Mossad guy.
Did I say that?
No.
He says, you guys are a bunch of liars because you're putting cocaine in the water.
I was laughing because it was so vibrant, like he took it.
I said, first of all, how would you know what cocaine tastes like?
Right.
So, right.
When someone says, right, it tastes like an illicit drug.
Well, how would you know?
I'm sure it's cocaine.
Well, that means you have a point of reference.
By the way, PKS, just for somebody who's unfamiliar completely, I'll give you the simple
phrase.
Comprehend and copy.
Nature is the basic fundamental principle.
The Shawberger stuff.
Yeah.
B-I-K-T-O-R-S-C-H-A-U-R-B-E-R.
I think Shawberger.
B-E-R-G-E-R.
Yeah.
Berg means mountain.
Right.
So, anyway, they started doing the math on this.
And the story got back to me was this.
If you go down to the main ports, the shipping ports in Japan, every day you'll see shipping
containers unloading many containers of bottled water from all over the world to serve to
the Japanese people.
Okay.
And he said that this tap water that we were synthesizing, the way I was, the technique
that we had, was way far superior than any bottled water.
Way superior.
Not just, you know, slightly, but way superior.
And far superior to any springs that he's ever had, other than maybe once in his life
he had a spring that might have been equal to that.
That if it all is required is this device, it's a string of devices, it's three devices
basically.
You could put them on a pallet in a forklift and move them, you know, wrap them up and
ship them on a pallet.
Right?
Let's say, right?
Okay.
So it's very portable.
So we could set up a station somewhere and take the Japanese institute of in-place water
and convert it to this and serve it.
And we eliminate the cost of shipping and bottling and all this other stuff that has to be brought
over.
Yeah.
One time you ship a pallet one place, one time, that saves you a whole lot from having
to constantly import bottles.
No, well, I meant the pallet, the equipment fits on the pallet.
Okay.
The equipment to make the water, but then you can make thousands and thousands of gallons
of water a day with it.
Right?
Well, that's the point is if you import it to another location, just import the equipment.
Yeah, well now you don't need the water itself to be shipped from France or Sweden or Switzerland
or whatever.
They can take their own water and convert it to the super high quality water.
And he was looking around for investors to give to, and my answer was, I don't want any
investment money because I don't know how to run this particular water business.
This is something unusual.
This is not the regular water business.
This is something different.
And so the only way to grow what I'm doing is just buy more water.
I don't need money.
We don't not looking to invest.
We don't know what to do with it.
You know, it's like we don't know how to grow this because it has nothing to do with the
typical model, bottled water model that exists.
This is completely different.
So we need to sell more water and we'll learn that way.
Well, it turns out these guys were making a lot of rounds to disturb the bottled water
industry in Japan, and I was at the center of it.
Now, here's the thing.
You don't have to even be good at math or know a lot about history.
Just watch some old movies and you will find out that most of the mobster movies somehow,
except for the Godfather or whatever, maybe the Godfather 2 implied it, always end up
somewhere at the loading docks, don't they?
Yes, there's always a mobsters are always near the loading dock.
So now why are they to load?
Because they get a cut from things getting moved.
So now we have containers that no longer are going to be unloaded.
And oops, do you see where I'm going with this?
Well, yeah, even during World War Two.
Right.
What was the deal that was struck with my great great uncle Sal, who history would remember
as Lucky Luciano?
Why is it they let him out of prison?
Well, because he helped them out with the dogs.
Yes.
Speaking of just to go on a little segue here.
You only hear about the battles, sort of what people don't know.
It's like, was it a quarter of a million Americans?
Half a million Americans died in the U.S. from sabotage in the U.S., like factories
exploding, bombs, fuel depots, all this other stuff.
You don't hear any of that.
You hear about Americans dying on the beaches of attacks and stuff like that.
If you do read about.
Yeah.
If you do read about that, it's called an industrial accident.
And they state that there was some accident at the shipping port or at a warehouse where
suddenly a factory burst into flames and it happened to blow up this other place.
Yeah.
There's a lot of I mean, like there's Torpedo Alley.
Five thousand ships were sunk.
You don't hear about that.
Right.
You know, on the East Coast.
Yeah.
West Coast, too.
I knew I pulled out of that because now if you know these shipping containers and ships
are no longer coming to Japan to unload, someone is going to lose, quote, unquote,
their what would you call it?
Their cut.
Yeah.
Right.
And that wouldn't be a good thing.
That's what came back to me eventually, is that this is in place because of other things
that are in place.
Right.
It's sort of like the initial pressures on some state lotteries.
Don't bring the lottery in because you're going to cut into the numbers business that
already exists.
That's right.
So anyway, from all these machinations, I learned a lot about the underworld in Japan because
of the interest there.
And by the way, if you have high quality stuff, like, for example, there's a speaker company
called Magico, Ilan Wolf.
And he made his money in the 80s with his brother selling security systems to the wealthy
people in L.A. and stuff like that.
A lot, like in the 50, 100 million range, which is a lot in the 80s.
So he opened a really high end speaker manufacturing.
It's called Magico, M-A-G-I-C-O.
You can buy a pair of speakers for nearly a million, whatever.
I don't think they sound that good, but they're considered the best speakers in the world.
Anyway, these top of the line flagship speakers, I think there's only two that were sold in
America and like 15 that went to Asia.
So do you see my point?
So if you have an elitist, upper crusty product, Asia is your market, right?
Right.
So actually speaking, and we're talking 2011, 2012, when this was going on, 2010 even.
I knew that that was a fact without giving a direct analogy like with Elon and Magico.
In other words, a lot of the top of the line products that are made in America are not
sold to Americans, they're sold to people in China and Japan.
Yeah, so I just wanted to bring that up.
So just tie that back to what's going on.
Breshears, again, to bring up archaics, he talks about the second seal being peace taken
from the earth with small arms conflict and all that.
Yeah, I pretty much see he made a pretty good point of that.
Combine that with since 2009 or 10, since I've been on the internet, I talked about
seven year periods.
Breshears talks about the four year Olympiad, but I also talked about the four and a half
year because that's the middle of the seven year period.
I also discussed on Sonics with you, 2017 to 2024 being another period and another period
starting in the spring of 2025.
And by then, the Middle East will be in the news every day and a center focus in the world
and look for that.
So things going on in the Middle East, especially the thing that chalks up as being a little
more advantageous to focusing on like what I talked about in Breshears and all that
and all the talk behind the scenes, not what the mainstream people are saying, but what
I if you've listened to old Greek speak, I did keep bringing up 2024 2025 as the Middle
East as being a big deal.
Right.
Which is years ago and being very relaxed about it, which is why I've gotten messages
recently about, you know, is this still on time?
This idea that you had about the way the union.
But but but here's the thing about it.
There's nothing that can be done about it.
Right.
And the thing is, are you involved in anything you whoever's listening that have business,
family, whatever affairs or whatever, you know, any business affairs, personal affairs
that has to do with that area.
You we've talked about it for many years now.
Right.
So it shouldn't be a surprise.
And hopefully, if you some people might have more intensive, like, for example, again,
when I was in L.A., I gave the typical Greek speak on what's coming in the Middle East.
And there was a pretty wealthy Palestinian lady that has a jewelry business in Beverly
Hills.
Now, there's a lot of people that have jewelry businesses and stuff.
But when you have a storefront in Beverly Hills and your palate, you know, you're pretty
well off.
Right to do.
And most of her family was in Palestine.
And she took what I was saying very, very seriously.
And I said, well, there's no reason to get upset.
You have about nine or 10 years.
This is nine or 10 years ago to do something about it.
You see what I mean?
OK, so that's the value in this.
If you feel like you have to do something now, it's it's now you're getting swallowed
up into the fear mode and all that.
No, it's a little late, too.
I mean, look, the best time to get out of the way of the, you know, the oncoming train
is to not be on the tracks.
You bet.
It's still a bet.
Like, you know, who's this guy is the only one talking about it.
Right.
You know, so you have to weigh it out yourself personally.
If it's not meant for you to weigh it out and to go through some tragedy or whatever
because of it, then that's that's fine, too.
So but yeah, this is all talked about it a while back.
Was this accurate?
The the the events are going to be I'm not one hundred percent sure, because, again,
I'm going off off the biblical information, which is quite sparse.
Well, do you still feel as though we're looking at something coming called the Assyrian?
Yeah, OK.
Because that was that was the thing there.
That was the key thing that everybody prompt.
And the logic behind that is a civil war in Iraq that was split off.
Now, ancient Assyria had parts of Turkey and parts of Syria and parts of Iraq.
Geographically, geographically, in order for it to come back.
It has to somehow retreat, somehow dominate and, you know, gain those territories,
territories as part of the country.
And years ago, I talked about watch.
Syria will be in the news and watch.
Turkey will be everything.
All that has happened also.
So, yeah, it's not a big deal once, you know, because I'm actually kind of tired to talk
about it because I don't have any more information other than the little sparse stuff that you get
in the Bible.
And it's basically just extrapolating off of like a single verse.
Right.
What does that mean?
And you have to parse it out to where else you can make connections.
But I'm happy with what I've said.
And I'm always open if we're here to learn like this person, someone comes up with more
information or better information, obviously go with that.
And the only person that I could see that speaking on that note would be Jason Breshears
of Archaics to supplement stuff that I've said, right, regarding the Middle East.
Right, right.
Because I think the point that he made on the second seal and the first seal is pretty
solid.
It's pretty good.
I like it.
You know, and, you know, you've known me for a while.
People have heard me speak for a long time now.
I rarely say that.
So you got to give credit where credit is due.
And it's based strictly on merit.
So, you know, whether it's you want to consider it purely academic, that's fine.
But see how it pans out.
Well, here's the thing to consider geographically.
Right.
I mean, there are loose ideas about what the borders are currently as compared to what
they used to be.
So when one looks at Iran, which is in the headlines currently, right, you can see that
it directly borders Iraq, which we all know because of the Iran-Iraq conflict.
Sure.
It's just slightly adjacent to Saudi Arabia, Afghanistan.
But they don't really live that.
OK.
The concept of borders is something when the English went in there and did all these
Mohammedan treaties, you know, and that's why all their flags have red, white and green
and all that.
Yeah.
So their concept of borders is very different than the Western.
They are, let's use the word tribal, but not in the way that Westerners think of it.
They are like a tribal way to say it.
Basically, the borders are not federal like they are in other places.
They're more tribal.
Right.
By bloodline, there's a subnationalistic culture.
So you have the overall Persians.
OK, this is like Italy that we look at modern Italy.
Most people don't know that Italy has a lot of subnational groups.
Yes, you're Italian.
But if you're not fully done, you want to go have you're not going to go hang out with
people from Palermo, Sicily.
You don't want to do that.
Right.
There's a bit of a cultural clash there.
And that's because, quite frankly, Italy is.
Yeah, it not it wasn't really recognized as a country until recently.
Yeah, it was sort of a loose monarchy.
And it was it was sort of viewed as a colonial power over Libya.
And it had culture.
And you have Sardinia, Switzerland.
Actually, if you wanted to know about more about the Italian culture, you had to be part
of the Swiss.
It was really odd.
Well, Sardinia were not considered.
Yes, Sardinia is in on this mix.
It's not just as simple as the Sicilians versus the rest.
Right.
It's not a matter of squirting ink on paper and saying this is the border.
This is how we're going to live now.
They don't work that way.
Right.
That's why I always said what you will see is a loose confederacy, not like the EU.
Where everyone just capitulates to some federal type federal meaning central.
By the way, the word federal is a religious term.
Look up in etymology what it means.
Right.
It's a it's a religious term.
But anyway, I think that it's no surprise.
But on the other hand, do the anyone listening that wants to learn more about it?
If you do learn more about it, let me know, because I think I've pretty much said everything
that could be said on the matter from the sources that I went to and sources would be
singular, not plural.
I pretty much try to extrapolate biblical prophecy.
And the only reason I did that and have been doing that in my life is because we all heard
about the Bible.
We all are part of the Judeo-Christian.
Even if you are Muslim, it venerates a lot of the similar things.
And we live in that culture.
And what things that I heard about within the religions were not in the Bible and things
that are in the Bible are not discussed.
So I felt it was kind of like a personal duty, almost like a hobby of mine to just simply
go into the Bible and, you know, especially the languages of preservation, see what it
says and start telling people about it.
Very simple.
Just kind of like, you know, we do with the medical stuff.
And for somebody who might question that idea about federal being a religious term, let
me just go to etymology online.
You want to look it up, etymology?
Put in federal in etymology and read that.
Yep, I did that.
And just let me give them a snippet of it, if you don't mind.
Yeah, go ahead.
Is it?
Yeah.
Am I on the mark?
I haven't looked it up in a long time.
Absolutely on the mark.
1640s as a theological term in reference to covenants between God and man from French,
excuse me, federal, an adjective formed from Latin, fotus, genitive, foderis.
OK, anyway, there's a bunch of things there.
Covenant League Treaty Alliance.
And all of it has to do with a covenant between God and man.
That's what we read it again.
Just the first part, I think, had the most impact as a definition as a theological term
in reference to covenants in quotes.
OK, so federal is a theological term.
Yes.
Yeah.
In reference to covenants between God and man.
That's that's that's where that's the whole thing, basically.
All right.
So my memory is still good.
Yes.
OK.
Just wanted to verify that, you know, and these things are, you know, whatever, you
know, and like I say, your law comes from your God and everybody bows down to the federal
law or whatever.
Right.
There you go.
And by the way, the second things work out the second separated paragraph, which, you
know, is significant.
It means the secondary, you know, completely secondary meaning.
Then it says secular meaning pertaining to a covenant or treaty.
Still, the word covenant is used, which is contract.
Yeah.
Which is contract and led to political sense of form by agreement among independent states,
blah, blah, blah.
Anyway, that's right.
But they never mentioned people in any of their codes or laws or statute.
You'll notice it's persons.
Federal union, union based on a treaty.
Yeah.
No mention of people in there anywhere.
Never, never.
Because it's so pure.
It's a business prospect.
So yeah, that's where you got to give the credit to.
He passed away.
He talked a lot about the money.
You've interviewed him a few times.
Jordan Maxwell.
Yeah.
You got to give him credit because he his whole thing, whether he was how accurate he was
or whatever, his whole thing was, it's all contract, right?
It's all business.
It's a business.
So that's where, you know, if you're going to get into Jordan Maxwell and walk away from
what he's saying, that's what you should take with you, basically, put that together with
the definition you just read.
Yeah.
It's all about contracts.
Even when he would also he'd love to take it to the personal and tell you, look, whose
business is it?
You're right.
You're in bad company.
All these things.
And he talked about the marital contracts and how those things work.
What are what are children?
They're a product of the marriage.
Right.
And what is it?
The union of two corporations.
If you take a look at all the language in there, all the language with the work week,
right, the week and your week at the end of the work week, get it?
Yep.
Aren't you a week at the end of the.
That's why it's a weekend weekend.
Yeah.
So, yeah, it's all the people are in a daze when they go into a supermarket because when
they walk in over the door, it says entrance.
And, yeah, it's yeah, you're in a trance.
So, yeah, the word magic, it's all spells.
You know, there's probably in a society that is telepathic.
There probably is very little, if not no spellcasting then.
Yeah.
Wouldn't be necessary, would it?
No.