Sonic Event 11, Ocelli in the Greek rated Y, and you probably already know that because
you're a subscriber and you clicked on it, so thanks for being here and hearing this,
wherever that is and whatever this actually is.
So the Greek is with me and we are recording after the sun has kind of gone away for the
day where I'm sitting, so what time of day is it?
Well you can check out an earlier event and hear all about that, but today I have in my
mind I want to talk about things, in my mind, there we go, I'm taking possession of that,
I'm owning it with my language, what about my government, what about my house, what about
my children, my wife, my family, what about my things, what do you actually own and what
are you communicating with your language when you speak Greek?
You can probably help me out with this because it's awfully confusing if you listen to the
inconsistent nature.
It's the possession of thought, not the possession itself, the material.
Now is that just sentimentality, is that just window dressing or does that have a meaning,
does that have a purpose?
Let's take some examples if you wouldn't mind, right?
Sure, in short the Nuremberg Trials was probably the best example in the most recent history
that people can reference details on, well you know what I mean by details, when you
get a history book and you go through it, it's all like Major League bullshit, right?
But you can't get upset because when you look at the title it doesn't say true history,
does it?
Well, yeah, right.
So you're presuming it's true, it's not, you see, it's not really true.
By the way, if you do research on old stuff, which I'm talking about physical, you will
have true, it will say true history of such and such or the true measurement of such and
such, they took that word out when the legal system came in.
Nuremberg Trials was about responsibility and you know, it was a sham, they used early
days of clones, people that were really low on the totem pole, you know, what do you
call them, scapegoats, such and such.
But what they did there is a display to the world of massive censorship coming in and
a massive change in the way people view what's right and wrong.
And that's another discussion, I mean I could get into that big time, but I want to get
into how it affects the way people think and act in a subtle way.
Well, even scapegoat is a weird term because when one looks at what a scapegoat actually
is supposed to be by its old definition, yeah, they're a leader, and it's actually a Judas
goat that kind of fits more of the descriptor that's often given for a scapegoat, right,
which is we assign blame onto the scapegoat.
I mean, that's the given current nomenclature with that.
That's the Judas goat.
The scapegoat is usually the one that's let go.
Yeah, but the strange thing is, again, when somebody says scapegoat, what is the presumption
by the listener usually now with...
Oh yeah, a patsy.
That's the patsy, which is not right.
But again, etymology, you've always got one.
You know, I'll say kids and nice just because it's a relaxed way to socially accept it,
but I do know what it means and I know how to use it precisely.
It's kind of like I've got an accurate, well, I wouldn't say I do this with a machinist
standard ruler.
You know how you have a ruler, a foot long, and it's got metric on one side and inches
on the other, 12 inches.
Well, there are some real...
I have a precision one.
It goes down to 64th of an inch and it tells you the expansion.
So the measurements are only good at 78 degrees or 75 degrees if it's hotter or colder.
The measurements are not really accurate because of shrinkage, right?
I could use that as a paint stirrer, couldn't I?
You could.
Yeah.
It's a scientific, it's a precision instrument stirrer.
You can get them for about 80 bucks, I think.
Or you could go to the dollar store or Walmart and get one for a dollar.
You see the difference?
So it's still the same.
It's just a stick, you know?
Well, you can bludgeon someone with a heavy book without ever bothering to read it.
I mean, it is useful as a weapon.
Yeah, you could.
That's typically how things are thought of.
But here's the thing.
Thought is this subtle energy and it's dimensionless, you know?
It's kind of like you can't measure it using that standard that I just mentioned, that
paint stick.
You see, I've often wondered that too and I don't want to keep sidetracking you here,
so to speak.
But really, honestly, thought seems to me, although we don't know how to measure it,
I'm almost willing to bet there is a way to measure it.
But I don't know.
I have no clue about what goes into that, what the calculation is.
Well, yes, you do.
It's very profound because you could have a general sitting at the Pentagon, he has
a thought, and then he pushes a button, it gives a command to drop a missile on some
village in Iraq, which you're still doing.
So the thoughts, and it goes from an inspiration to a thought to a, well, unless the general
is probably being told what to do, but it goes, you know, thought and it becomes action.
But what I'm trying to say, the subtleness, the subtle energy effects, it's a dimensional
quantity, a dimensionless quantity.
It has no dimension, no height, width, depth, or weight, right?
But it's the dominant, it dominates the quality of the thing, right?
I just want to preface, this is kind of a preface of a preface, but I want to also retrospectively
go back.
I think we spoke about, unless I was hallucinating, that we spoke about it, how when the master
or the, let's say, the owner or whatever is not present, the manufacturing or the business
goes down 20 or 30% in quality, starts to go down to shit, right?
I don't think we spoke about that, right?
Right.
Okay.
So what I'm saying is if you go get a Ferrari and Mr. Ferrari is dead, well, the best they're
going to do is 80%.
What's the other 20?
Shit, right?
So if you go, right, you see?
So what I was hinting there is a return to what if you lived in a society where things
were decentralized, and just like now, you have places that were known for doing things
really well, like Modena for balsamic vinegar, and certain regions in France for certain
wines that are named after it, right?
Certain things that are named after certain regions, right?
That's because they did them really well there, right?
Champagne.
Sure, sure.
So when you go, and in industry also, so if there is a return or an emergence of where
you have a mastership, apprentice, a master within the organization that is actually functioning,
you can retain near 100% of quality, right?
So when you look at something, again, like a Ford or let's look Ferrari, there's actually
a movie, Ford versus Ferrari or something, but anyway, Ferrari, he's dead.
There's no Mr. Ferrari there anymore that's worth any crap.
So if you give them a million bucks, you're really getting $800,000 worth of product, and
you're paying $200,000 for crap.
That's like an example.
Usually when you go and get something like from Microsoft or the consumer grade products,
it's the other way.
It's like 80% crap, 20% quality substance, right?
So this is a very simple, once it's brought up, it's very easy to see that.
We call it planned ups.
There's this, that, and the other or cheap goods.
No, it's not.
It's just crap.
It's because the reason I brought this up is I had a conversation with a small group
a few days prior to that, and the whole thing was I've had several enterprises that I was
involved in, and I noticed I had a good crew.
Everything was going well.
The moment I take a day off, everything falls apart, and then I said, well, maybe it was
just a fluke.
So let's just run it for another few weeks and go back, take a day off or two days off.
Everything falls apart again, but it didn't fall apart where it was catastrophic, but
it just went down, like really, you know, client complaints and this and that and things
that the quality wasn't up.
So I noticed that I played with this back and forth in various industries, and I noticed
that when the principle wasn't there, the quality went down, the people that were there
started producing crap, but enough to pass it by, but not as good as when the principle
was there.
So I started applying this and seeing it throughout the entire planet.
This is what's going on pretty much.
So unless you're getting something from a source where the mastership or principle is there,
there is a 20% to 30% crap factor built into it, and this is what we're, again, I'm repeating
myself here, but this, we call it planned obsolescence or cheap goods or whatever.
No, it's not that at all.
There's an element that's missing, and it's a subtle element, because here's the thing.
Even if you had the people working for the principle doing exactly what they did when
the principle was there, the day he takes the day off, even if they continue just doing
it exactly the way he did it, it still goes down 20% or 30%.
It's just this weird phenomenon, right?
So no matter what, even if, you know, it's not a matter of, well, okay, what is the old
phrase, right?
When the cat's away, the mice will play.
It's not just a matter of they've decided to slack off.
No, no.
They're trying hard, but there's something, as if an energy or a spirit comes in to replace
the position of the principle to throw in the crappy stuff.
It's really weird how that works.
I've also discussed this with other people.
Some people said, oh, yeah, I'm going to do another business.
I'm not going to be in this business anymore, but I have a good person running it.
I talked to them a few months later, what happened to that other business?
So I had to shut it down.
Oh, really?
Okay.
I didn't think you were so confident, were you?
So what I'm saying is don't waste your time.
In other words, if you think you're going to start a few businesses or do various, let's
say, enterprises and not be present, you have to build in a 20% to 30% shit factor.
If it's not passable to the clients or the people that are, let's say, having an exchange
or transactions with you, then don't do it because they're going to notice, right?
Or don't be there even from the beginning.
It's weird, too, because that goes all the way down the ladder.
I used to have situations where I was brought in to sort of right the ship in a certain
business and I would do it and I'd get everything running fine and inevitably, no matter what
I did, six months later, I would usually have to go back to the same place and fix it
again because unless I was there kind of maintaining that, it didn't stay consistent.
A lot of times, it wasn't just because, oh, people are lazy or it just would happen, yeah.
It's a social practice that you'll see not just in business but in society in many levels.
The reason I bring this up is because you can mechanically measure their ability and
their productivity.
It's almost the same but it just happens to everything just seems to tumble because it's
a very subtle energy and its dominant quality is the subtle energy, the most dominant quality
other than the fit and finish.
How does this tie in?
When you're influencing a society with industries, you know how you went from horse and carriage
to car and now then it went to everything's smart and computerized, you don't have any
principles involved.
The thing is running on its own.
So when things start to go bad, who takes the blame for it essentially is you want to
shift that blame is what they've been doing to the population, right?
Like how many times have you heard people say, well, you voted for him.
It's your fault, right?
Well, actually, the reality is your vote never mattered anyway even since George Washington
days, right?
So the way that's done is by making you the authorizing the outcome and that way that's
done is from children and on and on and on and to skip all the entire cultural development
of it.
For example, you download a new browser, let's say on a computer and it says, click here.
It's called my Yahoo, right?
Or my AOL, right?
Or my this, right?
It's not mine.
Wait a second.
It's you guys made it.
Why?
How does it become mine?
Right?
You know, this is my clip.
Click here to get my coupon.
I mean, you see, everything is my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my,
my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my
I once a cop wrote me a ticket make a long story short a long time ago for
riding a bicycle without a driver's license and I did the proper stuff
returned it and all that and they wrote back says you can't return it that's
your ticket I'm like what do you mean it's mine you guys printed it you guys
are you don't argue with them about what the tickets about you guys printed it
you guys are paying someone it's all out in a uniform to hand out as many of
these as possible or it gets fired right it's yours it's your stuff right so
Obviously, it's someone really low, so what I'm trying to say is there's levels on the
totem pole, whether you're dealing with a state, the government, the two different things
by the way, the state and the government, right?
We've never really got too much depth in that, just like the gods and the religion, right?
Because the religion, when you talk about religion, by the way, it's the purveyors
of the system, the church, the temple, whatever, and the gods are totally different, right?
You know, when you read, let's say, the religious creeds, there's a religious creed for the
Catholic church that says, I believe in one, only one apostolic Catholic church.
Have you ever read the creed?
Something I'm paraphrasing.
Yeah, yeah, I've seen that, yeah.
I believe in one apostolic Catholic church.
Doesn't say you believe in God or a god or any gods, you see?
So you know, the state is the one that does the business for the government when the government
doesn't have certain abilities or certain abilities are taken away, whether it's military, financial,
or whatever.
Okay.
So this is the condition you live in.
You have the state, and when you get higher up within that system, they discern.
Of course, if you speak to like a retired district attorney or assistant district attorney,
they all know that, you know, but when they first come out of school and go into the job,
they don't know that, right?
Like, give another example.
Do you know how the CIA hires people, you know, like entry-level agents, they usually
get them from, usually military experience, you know, I'm not talking about the ones where
they recruit from colleges, but the ones that, even the ones from colleges, what they do
is they have like a little seminar get-together for a few days, you know, you come in, it's
a local thing, and they interview and talk about stuff and national stuff or whatever,
and they tell you to go out into the yard, and they're raised, because they're raising
the flag, and as the flag is being raised, they have a camera down at knee level, and
whosoever's knees shake the most when the flag is being raised is a primary candidate.
Right.
Now, this I've never heard before.
Now, I know about, you know, how they offer, you know, look, you're special because you're
in the military, and the NSA does it, all the intelligence agencies do this, where they
give them special entry, you'll have an advantage, this and that.
Yeah, that's clerical, that's the administrative part, but I'm telling you what they look for,
the actual scouts, you know, the guys that, you know, you have the guys that do it by
the book, then you have the guys out there that make sure that the guys that are doing
it by the book get the right ones, right?
And that's what, they basically look, so they tell you, you know, you're doing this to support
the Constitution, the National, whatever, United States, and they keep that for a few
weeks, right, and then they shift it to obeying your commanding officer is supporting the
Constitution and National, blah, blah, blah, okay, and then they start speaking less about
the Constitution and the national security, and more about obeying the commanding officer
until they completely eliminate, the same people, eliminate the Constitution and all
the laws and morality and ethics, and now it's just about obeying the commanding officer,
no matter what he says, you see how they shift you over once they see, you know, you're weak-minded
enough to buy into the nationalism and do what's right, gung-ho, you see?
Right, as long as we present you with a leader, regardless of what the leader's motives are,
or whatever, you'll follow that because we prescribe it for you, yeah, okay.
But it didn't start off that way, they recruited you by telling you you're supporting the national
sovereignty and the Constitution.
You're protecting the country and the people and the Constitution, and defending and serving.
That's what gets you in, and then they start shifting it, and shifting it through mind
control and all, you know, through, you know, and the more you get in there, the more you
rely on it, right?
So this is exactly what's happening by putting the onus on everyone making everything around
them theirs, even stuff like Facebook accounts, bank accounts, my bank account, you know.
Here's the thing, I don't know anyone who really has a bona fide legal or lawful bank
account alive today, I don't know anyone who does.
But many people say they have a bank account, actually, by definition, you don't.
The bank doesn't have anything to put in any account, right?
It's just ledgers.
So but we still use that terminology, right?
Now, who knows about that?
Who knows about banking the least are the people that work in the banks, right?
They're easy to trick and fool when it comes to talking about logistics.
Speaking of which, someone talked about prepping and stuff, and I want to bring up an example
as we go on to this conversation, and it has to do with banks or anything.
But again, I don't know how much I could lean on the subject.
But if whoever's listening has run into something, especially online, my they try to make their
stuff your stuff, right?
Or it says my so be careful for that, you know, and be careful with it in your own language.
You know, would you bring me my slippers?
That's my coffee, right?
That's right.
That's my wife, you know, or, or whatever.
You see, it's, it's, this, this taps directly into a direct observation of one's place in
the cosmic realm, not just the physical realm.
Well, what is what is fit and proper to describe as mine, then?
Or what?
Is there nothing to describe that way?
No, there really isn't.
That's it's almost like a bad word.
Think about it.
Because ultimately, even if you believe in such a thing as a life review or the resurrection,
or not, if you were to believe in something, wouldn't you want to know more about it?
Well, at that point, you're basically standing naked in a vulnerable position amongst the
beings that are super powerful.
What's yours?
Really nothing.
You see, this is just the aspect of all of it.
You know, when you're passing through, you know, the effectiveness of being a sojourner
or a journeyman, that's why even in trades, a journeyman was someone who was there to
make something better and then move on to something else, right?
You know, in the trades, right?
So, all these things were viewed as a journey.
So when you're on a journey, how would you view it?
And what happens then is you get more acute and more perceptive, and the deception becomes
comical.
Because you live in the situation here where ignorance prevails.
Let me just say it this way.
When we brought up the discussion on the gods, think of the gods as, let's say, imagine a
gladiator-type society, and this is kind of extreme because when you think gladiator, it's
very powerful and dynamic and violent.
So let's just think of it that way, because biologically, we are.
Yeah, well, everybody knows how to picture that, though.
It's pretty simple.
I mean, they're familiar enough.
You have an arena, you have a battle that goes on, this is a mortal combat.
Yeah, the arena situation would be the world.
And you have gladiators that are not in the arena.
They're out, they're not in the arena, they're not in the fight.
They are the gods, right?
So now, big trouble happens when they come into the arena.
But think of it, what I'm trying to say here is, we live in a world where everyone wants
to, you know, the Christians say, give it up to God, right?
He'll take care of it.
No, he won't.
Think about it.
How many people pray?
Oh, I always find that ridiculous.
You know, that is just a, I'm just going to close my eyes and hope everything works.
You know, I don't get that, ever.
Yeah, well, look, if you're in the arena, and you're a gladiator with your opponent,
and you say, I'm just going to give it up to the guy that's back there.
The moment you've even finished saying that, your head gets lobbed off by your opponent,
right?
Because he's not in the arena, so you're being watched.
And that's why, ultimately, well, even if you get your head lobbed off, you know, then
the next thing you know is something, you know, you've never heard of, most likely,
or not familiar with, you're still fine.
There is a, by the way, for the people that are afraid of death, there is a factor of,
let's just say, like, with prey animals, like sheep and goats and cows, when they're
slaughtered, they don't experience pain the way, this has been, this was a study that
was done by Delgado in the 60s, when he attached, well, he was using mind control, he had a
little box, and he would, the descriptions are a little wooden box with electrical
circuitry, and he would make the bull, you know, retract in the arena, or kneel,
or charge, and he was experimenting with animals and looking at pain thresholds,
and he found that their pain thresholds are very different than ours, so it's as if almost
prey animals are made to be killed and not suffer, you know?
So what I'm trying to say here is I would reckon that when you're at the point of
dying, unless it's a very slow death, you won't feel it as such.
You know, you'll be like, oh, that's what I was afraid of,
this, I'm dead, where I died, and that wasn't
shit, it wasn't so bad, and I was told to fear that my whole life,
wow, you know? But watching people die, which I don't know
how much, have you experienced that personally? Yeah.
Twice or three times, yeah, it's very uneventful.
It's pretty uneventful at the end, and there is this
momentary time period where
death has not fully set in, it seems, and
quite honestly, I see people relax. Yeah, of course.
Most of the time. I mean, look, if you're in a whole lot of pain and you're very
confused, I mean, and it's a very violent and sudden issue, I mean, I'm sure that's
different, but generally speaking, there's kind of a
okay, you know, and people say, oh, that's acceptance,
or that's, oh, they decided to make peace with it right there,
they didn't make a decision, I don't think, I think that's just the experience of it.
Multiple observations, it appears to me as though, right then and there,
it's just, oh, okay, you know, there is that
threshold, but you look inside of a house, you know, and you're about to step into it, and you say,
okay, this isn't so bad to go in here. It is definitely a threshold moment.
I just got a, someone here sent me, the Catholics, they do have a creed,
by the way, I believe in one God, the Father Almighty, supposedly maker of heaven and earth, all things,
I think the one that I cited was the Eastern Orthodox Church.
I believe in one holy Catholic and apostolic church. Okay, so it's
more down towards the end there. Thank you for
sending that, and yeah, so just to make a
correction, it's more towards the bottom, but still it's inclusive in there. I think the way that people
read things might be more important than how they place it. By the way,
when you go to a court trial,
the first thing they do is tell you to state your name, because it's a reverse contract,
and all the rest of the offers are done after you sign it, so in other words, you know, when you read
a contract and then sign it, by the way, even a car dealership, they don't want you to
read all the fine print. People get annoyed all the time, and then later on,
when you don't like what you signed to, they said you should have read it, right? Of course.
But when you go to court and they say state your name, that's because you're signing
first, right? So that's another funky thing that goes on, but
about possessions, that's where you know that the people
have lost in general. In other words, it's like shooting fish in a barrel. You could pretty much say
anything to them, and they believe it, and they go for it. Because you're signing a blank contract,
which hasn't been written yet, and now they're going to write it since you signed it. Exactly.
And that's how it works. So yeah, those characters. By the way, one day we should get into the history
of the DOJ. If you put in
history of Department of Justice in a browser, the first thing
that comes up, even on a Wikipedia page, or the comments, it's a historical
anomaly. It means that no one knows where it came from, because it's
the Bar Association. I think Grant signed it in,
it's like 3.30 in the morning, they put a gun to his head, told him to sign it, and they were
supposed to provide attorneys to represent politicians, but now
it's gotten to the point where they're putting cases out themselves.
They're the ones going, it's totally illegal and unlawful.
But so is the rest of the stuff that you hear about in history.
I figure it's just a transposition of the Temple Bar Association
from the United Kingdom. The city.
The city of London. The city of London specifically.
It's known as, if you say the city anywhere in the world, especially
people who are legal, they know what you mean. Not London, but just like
all of the capitals, like in Moscow, you have Moscow and Russia,
but where Putin is, he's not in Moscow, he's in the DF, in the district federal.
Like in Mexico, you have Mexico City as the capital, but there's another
city inside of it, it's called district federal, right?
Washington DC is the district of Columbia. Federal district.
So it's very interesting how
every country shows that you're under occupation, and that's why I brought up the gladiators,
because it's still this model that goes back to that time.
The old adage, if it's not
broken, why fix it, right?
It doesn't need fixing.
If it's not broken, just blow it up.
One of the definitions for capitalism is when you're done using
something, you destroy it so no one else can use it.
To go back,
I cannot overemphasize how much this
me, mine, and whatever, in just basic language. Now we're not talking
about someone saying, whose car is this?
You might say, this is my car, because if you start being loose about it, it's inefficient
and ineffective. But just in the common little points that everyday
people use, you just watch that. In other words, how many people are using
this is mine, this is my building. My favorite is like the
secretary going into, or anyone walking into a big office tower
and this is my building. They point at it, right?
Well, really what it means is this is where you work, but it's not your building.
What do you mean it's my building? It's like a billion dollar tower. It's yours.
It's used all over the place, frankly.
That shows you the level of spiritual development, or where these people can operate.
Well, I mean, we'll go with something even more simple.
They say it's my street. Very good.
My house, my street, whatever. My kids. My kids is my favorite.
Even if you think you own the house, which you most likely don't.
You're a tenant, at best.
You could remedy that, because they like to make you believe that so they can take advantage
of it. There's a guy called Steve,
he's not on the internet anymore. He was a Steve in Florida.
Florida Steve. I have most of his details.
The property taxes that people pay on houses is a presumption.
In other words, all of the laws in all of the 50 states,
even the 48 lower, and even the Hawaii and Alaska are the same,
that property tax is only where you have a for-profit
property. I think I've discussed this before.
Non-profits are exempt from it.
Are you a non-profit in the house? In other words, are you making a profit where you're
eating, sleeping, screwing, working, or whatever?
Even if you're working, it's a private contract. No, it's not. It's none of their business.
Basically, you go to the county and you tell them
this is not for profit. They'll laugh at you.
You draw up a federal court case, because the feds like that kind of stuff.
You say, look, okay, you refuse me, so I'm going to
give you the case before I file it. What do you think? They're like, okay, let's go talk about it.
It gets real interesting when you want all the back taxes,
back treble damages, which means three times. That gets interesting.
That's a little harder to do. It has been done,
where someone had paid $30,000, $40,000 in taxes, and they want it all back
because once they admit that you're not part of it, then you
have a right to take the rest, because they admitted guilt, but you can go for treble damages.
Instead of $30,000, they're refunding you the $30,000.
It's $90,000 plus $30,000.
It gets kind of funky like that.
Also, you're considered a resident. A resident is temporary, like you're a resident
in a hospital, a prison, a hotel.
If someone says, I'm a resident here, where do you live? Where are you inhabiting?
Where are you from? Well, here.
You're a resident here, but you're also an inhabitant here. You're schizophrenic then.
I've seen the word tenant used.
Absolutely, because all of the other supporting presumptions lead to that.
When someone is fighting
a foreclosure, they say, well, this tenant doesn't want to pay their rent.
Why did I get in that situation?
Pretty interesting.
All the mortgages basically state that you own the house fee simple.
It's yours, and now you're putting it in a mortgage, dummy.
The easiest thing is, if you're the grantor, you can change the trust.
Fire the trustee, fire the mortgage company, and put your own people there.
Make your dog the trustee.
Anyway, it's simple.
All this stuff is very, very simple. In other words, the stuff that causes grief,
I used to do, it's very harsh, one day maybe we'll do it,
is how to fix the world in 30 days. It's not that hard to do.
You won't be allowed to do it, because it's like saying you're going to go to the gladiators
arena and turn it into a botanical garden. Everyone's going to fight you on that, right?
No pun intended, because its purpose is to be that.
But it can be fixed very easily in 30 days. You're going to lose
about a third of the population, maybe 40% of the population's got to go.
Build a hotel on the moon or whatever, put them on a big barge in the ocean,
sink it, I don't know, whatever. You get creative, but they can't stay here
once you do that. It's kind of like, imagine,
you remember from being back east, you had these buildings that were left for whatever
reason, and squatters took over. So you bought the building for a dollar on auction,
now you want to renovate it and improve the neighborhood, but the squatters are there.
What do you do? You've got to kick them out, right?
So it's the same with the earth. You have a whole bunch of people squatting here,
a lot of them, and they cannot handle a better society.
All of this is going to be done, by the way. It's going to be
done. I've discussed it in basic Greek speak.
We need to do a video when they start here for a beginner. I think we discussed
earlier, we don't have too many people here that are fairly new.
Some might be newer than others, but they do understand the premise of most of
the things we bring up. So what I brought up
tonight, which is important, which I have not really emphasized, is the
verbal and mental possession of something. Be careful what you
call yours, because the guys, even the guys at the
Nuremberg trials, even though the ones that were hung, they said, well,
we were just following orders, right? But they were still culpable.
They were still held responsible for it.
Well, right. Okay, so maybe it's not
about possession. See, I've always found possession to be a strange thing.
Yeah, because possession is a strange thing. What do you actually possess?
Virtually nothing. Outside of yourself.
It's not a strange thing. Possession is easy, but calling something
mine is different. Okay, here's possession. Here's how simple
See, it's kind of backwards. When you
you're in Walmart or you have a shopping cart pushing it around, you haven't put
anything there. Yeah, here comes somebody who wants to take it, right? What do you say?
Oh, this is mine. Don't you say that? Well, not really.
But what you're trying to say is I have possession of this
cart now for it to serve me during my shopping experience here.
Right, okay. And you just leave the cart when you're done. That is a really
good example because that's kind of like the experience that we're having here, right?
You're using everything, including the body. You're even using the spirit, by the way.
Which then leads to the big question
then if we're even using our mind and the spirit, which is attached to a network, what are
we really, right? Are we that individual? And I would suggest
we're not. I would suggest there's only a few groups. In other words
the human collective is made up of about 50 to 70, 100
tops, different spirit cores that break off and become
everyone else. This is another discussion
perhaps. But the shopping cart idea
or a rental car idea, you know, you're renting a car
for a day or two and it's parked somewhere
that it shouldn't be and whose car is this? You say it's mine. Well, it's not.
You're just renting it for the day, but at that time, because you have possession
of it, right? Right, because you have control of it. Right, but when it's
clearly someone else's stuff and they're offering it to you
as being yours, now you have a shift of liability.
Kind of like the Nuremberg trials. Well, you had a shift of liability there
when you rented the car though, didn't you? You did, but it's
still, no matter how much you say it's yours,
within a very brief, let's say, presentation of it being yours,
you're going to bring up that it's a rental. Yeah, of course. Where something like
a shopping cart, it's obvious that it's not yours.
Actually, it happened to me recently. I had it just in the aisle
and I walked away and someone went to grab it. How convenient, right? And I was like, wait,
wait, that's mine. I even used that terminology. Well, they know exactly.
Everything is very well known, right? I said, oh, okay.
You know, if you go to one of these large big box
stores and you want to get some sheets of plywood or something and you haven't loaded
it yet, you leave it alone for five minutes, someone else is going to get it, it's mine.
But it's a very temporary thing, but you're not living with it.
The thing is, these things that people live with, like MyBank
account, MyYahoo, I still see that. Where did I see that somewhere?
This is MyYahoo. They even had a branch of their browser system
called MyYahoo or MyAOL or something.
I think it's maybe MyGoogle Space or Workspace
or something, right? Sure. That's right. They're very interesting when they do that
because it's a spiritual
shifting of responsibility. So, in other words,
okay, so let's say some stuff goes down and
some bad things happen, ethically, morally, whatever, with Google.
But everything that is
a part of is part of something that people have taken as my whatever.
It makes it seem like they're part of it also and shared, you see.
And eventually they could lawyer their way out of it.
It's not that easy with a browser or something like that, but with a social responsibility
and a moral responsibility and in a spiritual or cosmic
level, it's very, very important and it's very closely watched.
It's just not common to reason that way. The same way when we say
years ago, I came here to Tucson. I went to a library.
The library here doesn't look anything like the ones back east. They're like new buildings.
They're in strip malls. When you go to a library back east, it's very grand
typically. So, anyway, I walk in
and I said, she goes, is the librarian or one of the clerks that's going to help you?
I said, well, this is my first time in this library. I'm new to Tucson.
She goes, oh, okay. Well, everything on this side is fiction and
everything here is fact and history. And I said, dear, it's all
fiction in here. This is a federal Marie Lebrun library, right? She goes, yeah.
I said, it's all fiction. And she kind of looked at me like,
what? So, it's
kind of like on that aspect. But on the cosmic aspect,
you know, on an earlier sonic, I spoke
on a cosmic law level.
When information is given to a group or an individual,
it doesn't matter if it's given to you as fact or fiction.
What's contained in that idea, whether it's a movie, a book, or a thought, an idea, an image,
is known to you. You see, that's why I say the elite
that run the world are the ones that created science fiction
in the 50s and 40s and 30s and the turn of the century.
Actually, who was the author of
20,000 Leagues Under the Sea? Jules Verne.
Well, he was kind of like fighting against the establishment
and making political commentaries because his books have been changed a lot.
But, yeah, things like that were funded
by the elite to put into mind
the world that these things, yes, of course,
they're fiction, ha, ha, ha, but to get these ideas into their heads, right?
And right now, with what people have been speaking on
retrospect since 9-11 is how much they're showing you in movies
or even The Simpsons, right? Oh, yeah, no, that's become very common.
This is the predictive, they call it predictive programming. Right.
That's cosmic law. They're using cosmic law.
The thing is, did you get the idea? Did you get the image? Did you get the script?
Did you get the idea? It doesn't matter if you call it fact or fiction.
You have it now, right, where it wasn't before.
That's how the cosmic aspect works. So when you transfer that over to calling something
like a bank account or a Facebook or something like that yours,
now you're taking whatever they're doing and sharing responsibility
in that cosmically.
Like when we brought up the gladiators earlier, right? I mean, as I said, automatically,
I said, well, look, everybody can picture that. Everybody knows what that is.
The majority of people have not witnessed
real gladiator events. You know what I'm saying?
You could say, okay, maybe you watched boxing or MMA or some crap,
but realistically, even though you know what that historical
paradigm means in one way or another. You might have a very basic understanding
of it, whatever. You know what a gladiator is. You know what an arena is
because these ideas have been imparted to you, but you never actually saw these things yourself.
Right. It doesn't matter. Well, football is very close to it, right?
Well, it's gladiatorial, but it's a team. Yeah, well, then again, the gladiatorial
They fought animals. They fought teams. Some of them, they had sea battles.
No, no, absolutely. They would fill water in their ranches.
Boats and ships.
The start here first is, what do cannibals, birthdays, and dolls have in common?
Since you're bringing up the gladiators, this is really hard to find.
If you could find it online, I've looked a long time ago on someone,
and I brought it up, but I couldn't find it.
The modern clown face with the very pale white skin,
distended eyebrows, distended red lips, that is a product
of when the victor gladiator, not in every fight,
but certain, let's say, groups of gladiators made it
a custom that when you would
remove the face of the defeated
and put it over yours. There's kind of a film
with Hannibal Lecter, was it Silence of the Lambs, where he breaks out of the jail
that way. He takes the face off of the security guard,
puts it on his face, and they think that it's the security guard all knifed up, right?
And he changed clothes. So the modern depiction of clown,
you see, if you were to put on someone's face, there's no bone structure. It's the bone structure
that makes you look like who you are, not the skin. When you wear the skin,
the lips flare out, and the eyes are nothing.
It's totally pale. There's no blood circulating through it. So what's interesting,
there's almost like a genetic memory or a detection
method in young children. Some young children, when they see a clown, they scream.
By detecting that, that is attached to that really
super morbid attachment. Now, I brought this up,
several people have questioned me on the source on this.
I got it from an old book a long time ago
when I was studying Flat Earth around 1986.
Well, see, the only thing I've seen in a book is... No image, just description.
Yeah. Well, the only thing I've seen in a book like this is
they say it's about the plague, and the way
that the faces would end up looking during the plague, right? Contorted, yeah.
The contortion would remove the shape of the face, and they would turn pale, obviously,
because they couldn't come around and collect the bodies quickly enough and all that.
So I've seen that in a book, but I've never seen anything about the body.
Well, this point was that the modern clown and the circus
acts went back and looked at what the gladiators did.
Because the modern clown face was made most popular by circuses.
So they were... In other words, this was speaking of how
running... It was a moral and ethical question
on how circuses do what they do, and they could creep in all this unethical
moral stuff, and people will enjoy it. Like the clown face, which was
a very short line. It just said, which was the victim's face
removed and worn in the arena by the victor. That's all it said.
It didn't get into detail. And I was like, oh my gosh, I could totally see it, right?
If you understand anatomy, right? Because your face looks like it does on a skull.
Once it's removed from the skull, it no longer looks like anything.
So I think I've also spoken basic Greek speak. Just because a line
or a verse is short doesn't mean that it's insignificant. If you were... If you fell off
of a cruise ship and you're drowning, you'll say, help, I'm perishing.
Help, I'm drowning. Well, what did he say? That was too short to be important.
No. Right, right, right. But you see what I mean? Some of the most poignant
things are in very short lines. But the gladiator,
I wanted to just harken back and just touch on what we spoke on the last time,
bringing up the most important part about the goddess religion in effect,
full effect right now. And right now, I mean, since the 1950s, which would put us
around 70 years or so. But the
entire milieu of the gods, there's so many, and there's so many hierarchies
and changing of guard in all this, that I would suggest that
the way that we are referenced, made in the image of, let's say,
it would be on what is dynamic. In other words, the loss of
dynamism of the gods is easy
to perceive if one just looks around. Like, I haven't seen anyone
that's a god walking around or anything. There's the concept of monism
which is like God is in everything, right? Yes. And I would see
that if... I've never found an ancient text that had anything that
leaned on monism. Any of the ancient texts
talked about God being in things. Never.
That's like a very abstract thought that I would
consider as that, just a thought. I wouldn't even bother researching it.
That's some basic eastern phrasing, you know, like the namaste
kind of thing. It's a hybrid. Actually, I found
when you study a lot of the eastern texts, they're actually more
hardcore, or just as hardcore as the western texts, let's say,
what have been adopted as the biblical texts. They're pretty hardcore.
Yeah, they are. Yeah, they're not that ethereal. So these are just hybrids
of the idea. What I wanted to
lean on was that you cannot discuss the gods without
getting into understanding the cosmic nature of how things work.
Just like the... what did you call it? Predictive programming?
Before there, I just wanted to throw something in because you made something occur to me
a couple of things, actually. First of all, Leatherface is another example
of that. The Texas Chainsaw Massacre deal with the expense of the victim,
which is pretty wild, and I'm very sure that a whole lot of people just remembered
exactly, yeah, that's right, Leatherface did that, too.
But, you know, there's another thing that happened, too, that you made me think
of, and maybe you can help me parse this out a little bit, and I'm sorry to go back over it again,
but I think all of it bears repeating. I was watching
a bit of a documentary piece on Jeffrey Dahmer,
right? And obviously, again, I'm sure everybody knows who that was.
If you don't, well, you know, quick search somewhere, you'll find it.
Anyway, he lived in an apartment building in Milwaukee, okay?
I'm not going to belabor this or go deep into it, I'm just... I have to lay these parts
out. He lived in an apartment building, he did horrible things, he cannibalized
people, this and that. Okay. And there's
a long story to it, you can discover it for yourself if you like,
but here's the thing. Once he was arrested and taken in and his crimes
were revealed, right? The people that also made their
homes in the same building. So this is back to, this is my building, this is
my block, this is my place. What's interesting is
even though he was gone, and the rest of his neighbors were not
you know, not nearly as evil as him, regardless of
whatever it is they were doing, none of them were eating other people. Or bad.
Bad, let's say, that word evil, yeah. Okay, they weren't as bad as him.
Their acts, the acts in their life probably did not compare
to the terrible nature of his. How's that?
Oh, that's fine, because evil is what happens when you do bad things.
Yeah, and he did plenty of bad things. I'm just being nitpicking, because
you know, these sonics are about, you know, threading fine needles, right?
No problem, nitpick away, because look, my language is sloppy.
I know this, so it's alright. I need to sharpen it, and I appreciate it.
But the thing is that, let me just get the point across that
he's gone, the events are over with, and
yet the people of that building would tell you that there was
just a terrible sort of way that people viewed that
place, that people viewed the people that lived there.
It was just a bad scene. They all had to leave.
They had to move, and eventually they had to tear the building down.
Not just because it was a morbid curiosity
you know, a tourist trap, but it was just a bad
place now, because there had been some
level, and they felt as though they were kind of attached to this
now, even though they were just the neighbors. They were just there.
They didn't participate in any of these terrible acts.
Sure, sure. It has a field. It's the emo.
So, yeah, I mean, help me out with this a little bit.
This has to do with what we just talked about, though.
Well, let's just say real simple, like, people that have
traveled through their lifetime. You ever go into a decent hotel, they give you a room,
and you're like, you walk into the room, it seems clean, just as clean as all the others,
and you're like, I'd like another room. And as you leave that
room that you were just offered, and you're walking down the hallway
to go to the desk and maybe ask for another room,
a couple starts walking your way, and you leave the door open, and they
walk in, and they're arguing, really like venomous argument,
and the woman says, maybe my ring is still in the room, and that was her, the room.
So that venomous, let's say, interchange or exchange
that they had was lingering in that room, you see.
And this is a direct example. This is something I've expressed, and now I know why
I didn't want that room. It has nothing to do with
By the way, I used to hang out with some people that would invite me to go up every weekend in Las Vegas
They were like high rollers and stuff, and they thought I was
good at conversation. I don't know where they ever get that idea, but I would
go with them. They'd comp me and go on a Friday night, come back Sunday afternoon.
And one of the guys, one of the brothers was a real stickler, by the way. He had one of these
UV lights, right? So we'd go into rooms like
the whale rooms in Bellagio
They're talking like $2,000 a night rooms
or on that floor. Huge beds,
big bathtubs in the place, the whole bit. Yeah, and he'd say
we want another room, and I'd say, why? And he brings out the UV light, and he says, he goes
the room is spotless, right? He brings out the UV light, and he goes right by the headboard
there's a lamp stand there, you see all that right there? I said, oh shit, yeah, what is that? He says, that's semen.
And he goes over here to the light, you see all that
right there? That's blood. You couldn't see it with the naked eye, but the UV shows it. He knew
the different colors. I was like, oh my gosh.
You can do that. People have gotten to know that over the years, but that was
something for many years. Yeah, under the
many rooms that may not carry UV light, you'll be surprised.
Also, there's a system, there's a light you could use to
all the rooms have cameras in them. This was admitted when they did that Vegas shooting a few
years back. When they didn't know who the guy was, they kept changing.
Just like recently, there was another shooting, and the person obviously changed their clothes
in the middle of the shooting, and all these false flags.
Anyway, what's his name? Damagard
is the guy to look for that. He's easy
to listen to. What's his first name, Damagard? He talks about all the false
shooting, false flags. Ole Damagard. Ole Damagard, yeah.
I'm not fully endorsing him. I have him as a contact on Skype.
He's too busy to get into the Greek-speak things. It's very interesting.
He does a lot of the
evidential stuff where he's just sifting through
all the things that they're showing the public. He doesn't have any backdoor
access to anything. He's just saying, look, they're showing right in front of you here.
It's the same traveling people that go from town to town all over the world.
Anyway, I don't know about what you think about his stuff
on JFK. He seems to be a little on the surface.
He leans very heavily on the political side.
Anyway, that's for Ocelli
effect stuff. Yeah, definitely.
I don't know all of his material, but
when it comes to evidence, if you're studying things that
are demonstrable, that's one thing. When you get into deep
opinions about that, it becomes something else.
Here's the thing, Joe. I never got into the JFK thing because I found it
to be very natural what they did there because
there was only one assassination that was not done by the quote-unquote
deep state. That was the one at the turn of the century that they blamed the Polish
anarchist on, but it was actually a Filipino. It's the one where they
put a gun in the cast. It looked like he had a broken arm.
That guy. The rest were all deep state type stuff.
Templar, Vatican, Jesuit, all stuff just to create
let people know that they're vulnerable because if we could hit your top guy
whatever. I would say also the two attempts on Ford were not
deep state. No, that's right. They were just
they were truly disturbed individuals in my mind.
Also, it could have been a toy. You know how there's a mafia and then there's toy mafia and they're more dangerous?
It could have been a toy organization and they're
really wild. It's really hard to talk about. Ford had two
attempts because he's known as the president who kept falling
down. He's two well-known attempts. By the way, he's the only one that we know of that had two
females attempt to assassinate him, which is kind of
interesting there. One of them being Squeaky Fromm and the other one being Sarah Jane Elmore.
That's interesting
but I don't believe for a second that that was deep state run. I think that was
actually organic.
Deep state, by the way, is the way that they're the same people that were involved behind Julius
Caesar. It's not this American thing of people. They're like
the Magi. When you read in the New Testament, the Magi came
to give tribute to the king of Israel
and they went to the king of Israel, let's say, and there's
a king born here and he's scared of them. In other words,
Herod's in his own palace and he's terrified of these Magi that came. Now, what kind
of power are they wielding? Imagine a king being afraid
of his guests. That means that he acknowledges that they are
more powerful than him. It goes back to that group also.
It's been around
since time immemorial. True enough, but back to this thing about the building
suddenly taking on this problem and these people now having
experiencing problems because they lived there and again had to move
away. All sorts of issues came out of that.
Where would you lean? What would be a reason
just so we could start on something there? What would you think the reason is?
Well, I'm thinking that when there are events that occur in a
space, okay, that there is
a sort of a residue that's left behind
from those events and when you have
traumatic events occur in a space, that space
retains that energy and
will continue to kind of vibrate with it
in a way. I know you don't like vibration, but it continues to have that vibe.
No, I don't like vibration. I don't like frequency. Frequency is breaking it down.
Either way, I like them both, but too much of one is not
discounting the other. I see what you're saying. Wilhelm Reich, here's an example of that.
When the hospital was torn down, he went there with
some very fine equipment that he manufactured
and he went where the x-ray room would have been
and he noticed there was a radiation disturbance in the area
where the x-ray room, the x-ray machine was. This is after the hospital
has been torn down and this is a mechanical thing. Right, so the x-ray machine
is long gone, the room is gone, the whole building is gone,
but the space still. An area on the earth, a small
area on the earth. So the EMO work that I've been
speaking on, which I don't think we've ever gone into, that might require maybe a solo
because it gets really deep. I could speak fast, you could slow
it down kind of thing. I promised one on food
and one on the gods and now one on EMO, maybe solos, or maybe
we'll do them together in the near future.
They're very technical. In essence, I don't know how much
to say how important learning of what the purpose of something is.
You can be aware of something
existing, but you don't understand its purpose.
You have the black box in jet airliners, jet aircraft for example.
First of all, it's not a black box, it's painted orange.
It has what they consider high visibility
colors. It looks like red to me, it probably is orange.
Or high visibility, I've seen one that's yellow and black stripes.
So it has to have high visibility. Most people have heard of it, but they don't
understand the true purpose of it. It records
everything. It's basically an up-to-the-minute recording as best it can
and it's indelible, in other words, hard to damage.
Understanding the purpose sometimes
not only offers more meaning, but it adds how
you dimensionally can interact or is it something that you want to incorporate in your life
and learn how to use or not.
How would you say
the emo part is so important
because everyone understands that their emotions
or someone who's emotionless is actually just someone who is highly
controlled. Because if you're able to influence and project
thoughts or have desires, you have emotions, even if you're like
a Mr. Spock kind of person. So I would suggest that on the emo
I would call it imprinting.
In this case, the building had an imprint.
That makes sense, an imprint. I'm saying that a residue stays behind
but that doesn't make sense. You're right, it's more like an imprint.
Right, because the events happen from very strong
emotional projection. It wasn't an accident.
Usually when something is an accident, it was an accident, he stabbed her 36 times
it was accidental, right? Not like that, but usually when there's
an accident, places recover. But when there's a strong emotional
intent, you'll have an area known
to be haunted or whatever.
I have not experimented
most of the stuff that I discuss is either first-hand, second-hand or
through experimentation, right? I have not experimented
with ley lines, by the way. You know how you have positive and negative
ley lines on the earth? If you sleep over two negative ley lines criss-cross
it could damage your body, right?
But what I'm suggesting is those ley lines can be created.
They're called, quote-unquote, holy spaces. These cathedrals
and temples and places were built over, they say, positive
ley lines. The information on this is very airy-fairy
and not really substantial, but how did these ley lines
appear? I'm suggesting you can mitigate
a negative, let's say, energetic zone on the earth or
create a negative one, which you wouldn't want to do, but you want to mitigate a negative
one or make a positive one. That's what they call a sacred
space, right? Well, I know that you can, I know from
first-hand again that you can clear these things away. Yes.
And to me, it's more like you move them along. You don't really
like, oh, can you destroy this or banish? No, you don't destroy it or banish it.
You just sort of move it along so that it's not concentrated there.
It just sort of dissipates in the air.
What is the problem with poison air is when there's a concentration of a particular
thing in that air, right? If you make the
concentration next to nothing because you spread it out, it's tolerable.
It becomes tolerable. What is the acceptable level? What is the safe level?
Well, the thing about the emo work is
there's no tolerance. Well, the tolerances are that you
are going to accomplish this because once the emo is established, the emotional
level that you're looking for, that's it. It's either have it or
you don't. It's not like being a little pregnant.
It's kind of like
induction in the body, right? These things are
dimensionless. When I say dimensionless, meaning they have no width, length, or height,
or weight, or they're not measurable with the pressure
devices we have. There are ways like dowsing,
divining rods, which are an extension of the body. You can use those
for many, many aspects. That is a basic
tool. People say to you, Greek, have you ever worked with a pendulum?
I suggest not to work with a pendulum. There's many reasons why,
but I can't give one that's really solid.
Dowsing rods, the witching wands or whatever, the two sticks,
they go apart or they come together. That is an extension
of your energetic field reacting with other energetic fields.
For example, when I build devices
that are for water or conducting electricity,
you know when you pack battery
cells in a flashlight, you have to go a certain way, right? Positive, negative, positive, negative,
positive, negative, right? If you don't put them in the right way, you turn it on
and try to hit the switch, nothing works because the polarities are messed up.
If I'm building something that's going to conduct electricity or
run water through it and it has multiple components, I usually dows
them for which is the positive side and which is the negative side, as long as there's no
terminal that has to be, like if I have
I'm building something as a positive and a negative terminal and the two terminals
are blank or neutral right now because they haven't been installed correspondingly,
I'll ask which one should be the positive and which one should be the negative.
You know, obviously these are all positive, yeah, they're very much positive and these are very negative,
and then I mark them accordingly. So when you make things with that kind of
subtle energy taken into consideration, it takes it to the next
level and you're actually making that object a sacred object, you see.
So that's just a very rudimentary way to start off
on that. But again, I started off, we started off, I should say
very much leaning on the concept of be careful of what you
take possession of in your mind. Early on we were saying
it's not really possession because you can have possession of a shopping cart and
call it yours, but there are things that linger
amongst your life that
people are taking possession of in their mind
before they even take possession of, like we were mentioning the MyFacebook
account, right, well how do you take possession of that? It's just as elusive
as a bank account, there's nothing there, right? It's just digital
it's just, that's really a sense of emo, it just appears on a screen and it goes
away. So the other thing is the name. Sometimes
instead of asking, if I ask someone, what's your name?
And they say, huh? I say, well what sound do you answer to?
Really what it is, right? There's a couple of people
Batman, not Batman the comic, but there's a guy on TalkShoe
Batman always talks about the name, everything's about the name, right?
You're just using it, right? That's an interesting
and again it's actually on a high spiritual level to realize
you're just using everything and taking possession is fine
it's just calling it yours in a spiritual cosmic sense
now you're sharing in the liability of the deeds of those that really
created it. So when you look at, for example, again
speaking on the gods, whatever doctrines you see out in the world
religions and things to believe in and what to believe in
you'll find are diametrically opposed to what's written in the text for example
and I mean this wholeheartedly with everything
whether it's medical, religious, legal or anything, it's very much opposed
so for example if you look at Christianity
or the legal system or Judaism or Islam and Muslims
and Hindus or any Buddhists or whatever, if you study
the text and you go see what the supposedly
each corresponding religion that supposedly came from that text is saying and doing
you'll find that they're not doing anything that's in the text
pretty much accurately saying it, nothing at all
directly or even may resemble it, but resemblance is not
actual, right? Right, it resembles, it's not
the thing. It's not the thing. So how did it get off
the mark? Because if you ask them, say well you're not doing or know anything
that's in here, say well that's how the church does it
that's how, so somehow the temple
or the imam or the guru or whatever, so somehow there's a point
where, forget about saying they're not doing anything
that's in the text that they subscribe to, forget about that for a moment
how did these other things develop? Someone developed them as a twisted
corrupted whatever and as an
excuse. Well they're not random, look they're not random as if they were
mistakes. Created by someone. Yeah, they're not random as if they were mistakes, right?
You could say well look, that's just a mistake, that's a misreading
okay, but no, because what it becomes is something
that does still have an order to it. It's not like it's
all of a sudden we find that, oh we missed this one guy
in the text named Ronald. No, we didn't miss a guy
in the text, we've added something here.
You said Ronald, by the way, there was one of the art
galleries a few years ago, I put a Ronald McDonald on a crucifix
I thought that was great. I would have found that humorous
Yeah, great in terms of how else can we make fun of this stuff
but here's the take away
is when you become a member of that group and profess your belief
or whatever in it, you're taking liability now and sharing the culpability
and liability of those that created that falsehood.
When you say something is yours and also you're selecting
this as part of your identity, these are both parts of now
taking liability, right? Because if you say
you're a Christian, okay, doesn't that mean that
you're now saying look, I'm in with this group, I'm partially
liable for what this group does, right? No, you're liable for
what you do, but generally speaking, but there's a
certain percentage of the quote-unquote judgment that will come
upon you just by subscribing to that group.
So in other words, let's say the group itself
Well, there's liability, but the thing is the group itself, everyone is viewed
individually, but the group, those that are in a particular group
that group is creating a deficit or
a negative that is going to be rooted out
and you're going to have to share part of that rooting out, you know?
So here's the interesting thing is when the
mop-up crew is very selective, by the way, when this earth
is cleaned up, they're very selective. You could be amongst a crowd of people
and they'll all be slaughtered dead and you'll be standing in the middle like what the hell just happened, right?
It's not like a bomb that goes off, it's
indiscriminate, which just depends on how far you are in the radius, right?
It's not like that at all. So what you see
going on in the world is the constant fear
that they put in, ignorance in the world. They know that the
elite know that, you know, when I say the elite, it's the religions really
and governments and banking and all the other stuff that's going on
They know that their time is limited. They've known it for a long time.
And they want to suck down just because as many people as they can with them
and that's why the mainstream is the mainstream, so crappy.
So the idea of detaching, you know, for example
myself as a young child, before my even teen years, I knew
I was also exposed to people of wisdom
but everything that they're telling you is opposite, it's backwards or it's corrupted
don't trust it, but in a healthy way, right? Because we're known
to be very naive and very difficult to deal with, humans are.
One commonly spoken of thing in law
or in legal terms even, both
seems to be correct still, which is that
ignorance of the law doesn't remove you from liability
I mean, is that not true?
Well, in biblical, let's say it's not true
because if you don't know you did anything wrong, you're not held accountable for it
you know, the group for keeping
if the group knows you're doing it and you don't know it's wrong
then the entire group gets in trouble. It's kind of like in the military
where if PT, physical training, if one guy can't do the push-ups
and they give him a couple of tries and if he chances to improve
and if he doesn't, they make the PT the whole group, right? That's punishment
where if one guy goes off, they punish the whole rest of the group
actually, if you read in Sefer HaYikra, which is Hebrew for the scroll
of Leviticus, it says that if you see your brother
transgressing the law, I'm paraphrasing here, and he doesn't know that he's
doing transgression, if you go to him and tell him
that he's transgressing, now he's responsible
you see?
The legal
aspect is just a rotten group of people
I think Jordan Maxwell said this once
he says that the criminal attorneys, they call themselves right
yeah, they do
if you look at most misery
that's put on by political government, like the genocides
starvations, all that came out from the legal community
every genocide was legal, it was approved by the legal
the attorneys, not the lawyers, lawyers are different
there are no more lawyers
if you ever watch any old 1930s films
a prison scene, there's always a lawyer and a doc
a doctor in jail, you remember that?
because after the bankruptcy
they put together the American Medical Association and anyone who was practicing
medicine in an ethical way was arrested, because you can only do
allopathic, you can only treat symptoms, so those that didn't want to
go along with the modern, I'm not going to say, most people say FDA
but FDA didn't come around until Nixon, but the early American Medical Associations
in the 30s that came with the bankruptcy that were put in by the bankers
the same with the legal system, any lawyer that found that
what was going on was incorrect, they put them in jail
they put the doctors in jail, as an example, they put a lot of them in jail
the ones that wanted to just keep doing what they're doing and not buck the system
got the message, but you'll see that in old films, I was always wondering
why is there always a doc in prison? hey doc, you know
once you understand the bankruptcy, you start to see what was going on
and that was a big earmark, by the way, for, you know, you can do
an early, Ocelli in the Greek have always said, humanity's gotten to the point now
meaning since the 50s, you can do anything to them, anything at all
so, yeah, I think, I don't know how much more
to emphasize, be careful about, again, what you call
mine, mine and yours and this and that, instead of the, just neuter it
make it a thing, what's more important
than that, because it's like a detox or cleaning up your language, your life
your perspective will change, I assure you, once you start
putting things in an objective or neuter perspective
let's say, neutered, you will see also
the spiritual level that other people are operating on, when they start
what they're calling mine, constantly, it's very, very important
it ties in directly to the gods, also, the way they view
because their whole thing is about objectifying