Everybody's different. Yeah, that's why relationships that well, go ahead start. I'll talk about it a little bit
Rated Y sonic event
Ocelli in the Greek. There you go. I marked it. I said it and here we are
Greek, how you doing? Oh, I'm not annoyed. That's good. That's a good thing
I think I define that by the way, just everybody a personal note. That's
That's my termination point when I say that's annoying. It doesn't get any worse than that
It's you know, a lot of people, you know, you ran my dog over with a car or you're an asshole or whatever for me
It's like I just can't take things that are annoying
And everybody's got their own personal preference, but here's the thing I've
Earmarked that word as a very serious condition
So when everybody's different, you know people keep birds in cages as pets, but what happens when you put a cardinal or a blue jay?
Certain birds like that to cage. They just drop dead after a few days, right no matter what you could do for him, right?
They have to be in the wild. There are aviaries that have them but they're large aviaries
Discussed every animal changes in captivity. I mean we've talked about how certain animals cannot breed in cacti captivity and
Indeed the fact that pigs are kept in captivity. This is what makes them crazy. And this is what makes them
Very dirty. In fact, a wild pig is a cleaner animal than they then a kept one in a pen, right?
We talked about that. Well because they were set up to always be moving. Yeah, no, you put them somewhere where they right
Go against I mean and a bird in a cage by definition a flying bird in a cage, but this is not a good idea
I don't I never understood that because well, they could be bred just like people right before we're talking about relationships and it's like
it's very difficult to talk about it because that is so cultural and tradition and
Whatever you call that culture and tradition the way you're raised
Intensive when you hear people talking about what they like to eat
Relationships and like that that is ninety nine point nine nine nine percent their upbringing and what culture they're in strict strictly
There's very little cause of natural. Well, of course, you know within let's just say relationships
You've got different aspects right companionship the sexual part the whatever whatever whatever goes on and on and on all that
I'm telling you that what you people will think is personal preference comes directly from your culture
You have their people don't know what they prefer. Some people do and guess what?
That's called kinky. You have proclivities or what do you call it fetishes, right? You hear that? Yeah again again, that's part of the culture
Well, see here's difficult to say, but but here's the thing in my mind
Okay, there is your natural design if you were not guided by your culture
Wouldn't you follow your natural design if your culture didn't warp it in the first place?
I mean not a human not a human. No. No human is all external input. They know downloads
You don't come with any downloads you come with the equipment to receive downloads in process, but no
Yeah, so if you receive no cultural information
If that's just not part of the cultures program
You'll pick it up from whatever
Here's the most interesting study and that would be to raise someone alone, which would not be possible. The baby would die, right?
It would just around plants and no animals and no humans, yeah, that's not possible
Physiologically, well, they will die. Yeah, they won't make it
Yeah, and I mean like a Truman Show type thing where you have a little trapdoor where they get food and stuff like that
They never have any human and animal contact. Yeah, but that's around plants
But that's no good because we've already seen studies where people's lifespans are significantly short shortened
I wouldn't say it's no good. There's plenty of people to experiment with. Come on
Listen but what I'm saying is that what I've seen is data that shows that if you don't have personal interaction
It shortens your lifespan. It does it at the end of life
It doesn't in the beginning of life a lot of infants can die without that's why they pick up babies
Even if they're abandoned they keep picking them up not just to change them
No, no, I know but what I'm saying is what most people think they're observing as part of their choice
Mechanism and decision mechanism or let's say choice present choices are not decisions, right?
Their decision make it mechanism is completely based on how they were raised and where they were raised
So when you talk about something like relationships, right?
It's what's acceptable within the culture, you know, and how you were raised and again people think they're like, oh, yeah
You know, I'm real whatever because I have a fetish of this or percolating for that
That's still you borrowed that from someone else very little. Yeah, right. So here him. Let me just cut to the chase
Let's say with relationships the ultimate
Ultimate perspective on it. Like when you have man and a woman they would only have sex to procreate period period
That's it. Okay, it doesn't mean they can't be intimate, right?
So the concept of having an orgasm and all that stuff directly with all that is strictly for having children, right?
The rest of it. Okay is if you you want to go to the okay here
See but that's culture to me that's culture because here's the thing from a purely
Reactive standpoint right the fact that it just feels good to do it
Might also be a cause isn't that something at well? Gee, I
Feels good. So I do it. I mean, that's just the reaction of any
Organism if it is positive stimulus if they enjoy it if there is something good that comes from it, right?
to do with having sex though or you know, the
Cover your ears the fucking fart right? That is cultural. You can be very intimate
With someone you naked and all that right? This is rated Y not rated X, but yeah
Yeah, so without the type of quote-unquote sex that but here's an example, you know
One of the experiments they're trying to get those pandas which are not bears by the way pandas are their own species
To have to mate they actually showed them human porn right to maybe to give him the idea
but he was never able to
He was never successful
Because they pulled out when anyway, you know, so right
Yeah, but the whole thing about
Relationships again is custom tailored for you
Right from the beginning
From the beginning meaning where when you when you were brought up and where and how you were brought up
You know
Fetishism look fetishism to one degree or another you could say that there is a
fetishistic aspect almost to any
even the most really standard sexuality that we know of the people expressed because
Let's let's be frank. Like why is it that a man is fascinated with with a woman's breasts for instance again?
That's taught but okay, that's taught but it seems odd because that serves no practical function
Except no, no, but Chuck. Hold on. Hold on. Okay within that man's life
He's going to hear about something like that and he has a choice whether to go to make the decision of that's what you say
They would never be seen that way. There's a story with
Jack fresco, they went to an island to educate the the natives and they were always topless the girls, right?
I was curious. I think about fresco, by the way, but go ahead. Yeah
Yeah, so they gave him t-shirts to cover up and they got the t-shirts and they cut holes to let their breasts hang out
Okay, so it defeated the purpose
you know, it's this purpose is to everything, you know, I don't know you hear about the
Explosion at the cheese factory in France
It was there was debris everywhere
And
Yeah, okay, so it's kind of like that the joke in other words when people are persistent about something they see being normal
Right when you try to change that they're gonna try to normalize which right?
So it's normal for this culture for the women to expose their breasts just like it was an ancient creed
By the way, the Minoan society ancient times when women really got dressed up
The entire body was covered except their breasts and you could go look at the artwork from Minoan, you know
25 3,000 years ago, right?
So much of it. I mean look I've never thought that much of it
I always thought it's strange that we have this cultural need to cover that part. Like why is that it's it's here
Here's the thing
When something is normal, hmm, and you try to change it people want to go back to I wasn't normal
So, okay. So in this case, they're topless, right?
So they they get the point that they should be covered but they found a little loophole
So let's cut holes so the breasts don't hang out anyway, because that's normal for us
But whoever saw that who would have provided the t-shirt so they'd be covered. Well, I'm sure it was like, oh my gosh
They're not normal
You see so this normal thing is very rare here. Let's just cut to the chase on this topic. Mm-hmm. Okay
People have gurus either call them
What did I call him ascended masters a very special humans geniuses, whatever, whatever, whatever that people aspire to
Sure. Yeah
There's a whole bunch of them right
Prophets or whatever that do special things and people aspire to the achievements of these people, right?
That is still part of the culture that is still part of their culture is they're not doing any
They they're doing things that are special because it seems different to the norm
What if you went to a culture where everybody walked on water? Wait a second. That's called Iceland
Anyway, you see
Okay, maybe it was Greenland that was actually I see a nice green. Yeah, that's right. Yeah, there are no trees in Iceland
No, I heard really. I never heard that. Okay. Yeah, but anyway, so you see what I mean?
It's a struggle back and forth. So that's why I always said I'm the stuff wouldn't be covered relationships
Uh, almost three quarters of decades ago on the original OMG and I said look just pick someone it doesn't matter
Don't you know TV Hollywood thing, whatever, you know, they and start working with them and build it up
But guess what? Guess how are you gonna build it? Let's say you build a
Structure you're gonna build it according to the architecture that's accepted in your culture, right?
If I show you a picture of Chinese architecture, how long does it take you to figure out though?
That's in China mostly like a second, right?
Yeah, but you're gonna need a lot of contingent parts that share commonality
See, that's the thing about if you're gonna build a structure
Look, you're not going to do it with one piece of wood one piece of plastic, you know one piece, etc
Etc. Are you know, you're going to come up with a bunch of contingent pieces that have some common
Properties so this is the way that you would build something even if it is foundationally
Something you got to start from scratch. Yeah, we did get into it
Law form and law is not people you say well
That's like tax and traffic lights and stuff like another law form covers it your entire operating system and your entire program
So right because there are similar law form then you're good. Well as we talked about and plainly, all right, look if
Okay, if one of us was a female
It is just what we'll do one of us was a female and we were trying to come together on this
We would sit down talk about it and say okay. Look I eat certain things. Do you eat these things?
you know and I mean we'd have to eat similar foods we'd have to agree that a a
Housing is particularly acceptable or not. We'd have to agree
Okay, no, I gotta stop you there. Okay. I'll show you how fine this is. All right, it's not what I eat
It's what I ate now. What are you going to eat in the future?
You see you have to put the tenses together
well
what I eat is what is currently happening because what I ate in the past is almost irrelevant because I
Last meal you once you have a conversation like that
Yeah
You are willing willing to work together the last meal you had is the last meal you had
Based on what you're going to do now
Well, I always thought that's why when people dated this is why one of the dating rituals was to go to eat together
So this way you could learn
Whether you know you were compatible in some way. I thought that was a common sort of thing, right?
Isn't that why you engage in certain forms of entertainment to see?
Okay. Look, are you a movie person? Are you somebody who likes to go see music?
whatever and you might find common entertainment so that you can pass some of your
You know downtime together a little more culture East Coast culture American culture Western culture. Yeah
It's nothing
Here this goes
Depends on how simplistic you want to keep it. You know, someone says what's your favorite food?
What's savory sweet? I never have a good answer for that. What is your favorite food? It's like well, it depends
Well, I can't be but there's so many tastes in in the palate that you can't lump them all together and say there's one
Food that covers all the taste. Well, right like today
I might really want a sandwich Greek and that could be my favorite food for today. It doesn't mean that next week
I'm not sitting here wanting to eat a
God help me. I don't eat chicken anymore because it's all disgusting
I can't find a decent piece of chicken, but I used to enjoy chicken. I used to enjoy a good piece of beef
When I can get a hold of something that is of decent quality
I still do enjoy it
But I mean, you know there might have been a time where I ate a lot of cheese
There might have been a time where I was all right, but that was all the time
Yeah, but you mentioning the foods, but I'm suggesting that they go into a category regarding the palate. So you have a palate that has various
receptors and sensibilities and sensitivities and every subject can be taken that way, right? Sure. What's your favorite color?
Well for what but right it depends are you talking about my clothing or are you talking about what it what color I like my
House to be because I I don't I like wearing black clothing. I don't want my house painted black, you know
Good I found a study that was done in the 80s and it was one of these Ivy Leagues and they found out by
Testing people not muscle testing, you know, that's more
Whatever, but I found that if you put
People in a pink room for more than four hours their actual muscular strength decreases
You know what they could lift or prefer, you know perform on a maximum level goes down very interesting, right?
So the paint the prisons pink, let's say right. Okay, kind of it shouldn't be any prisons by the way
There's no, you know, that's unlawful by the way to put someone in a cage
Of course and the colors on the interior walls of things do affect the inhabitants if you're constantly exposed to it
If you're constantly exposed to different colors that affects you that's another discussion for another day. Actually, I think
By the way, no pun intended when you have a grouping of colors with color palette. Yeah, right
Yeah, so again, it's a matter of variety. By the way, I think on this sonic maybe I want to go back and do some
scrubbing on the rubbing and scrubbing and leaning on the chat because
We do these sonics. We refer to the chat and there's a couple of things that have gone
Right before we started recording I said, you know, some of these questions are a sonic in their own, right?
Right soon covered some degree before right? Okay
Yeah, you know the silver coin thing. I think you brought up, but I think we covered that for people that understand
Silver has been used historically for its attributes. It's more than just for health attributes, by the way, right?
That's it's the master metal if anyone that works with the metal crafts knows that you can pretty much break
He's not well, but attach any two pieces of metal using silver in between, right?
It's a go-between you almost all things except for aluminum and bismuth and things with a low melting point
Where you couldn't do it. Otherwise, so
That's why I'm fine fine frame building
They use you know for automobiles or bicycles and motorcycles that back in the day
They did silver brazing instead of brass brazing is lower temperature blah blah
but the silver thing is this to get energy if you're chasing the energy of the silver see the
Current scientists will tell you if there's no presence of matte material there. There's no effect, right?
So that's a wrap but the people use silver historically against
Let's say on utensils against their body and in jewelry, right? Yes
And it's been very here's an example how when you go for the materials very dirty
I don't remember people wore silver rings and earrings. I left the tarnish on the skin, right?
It's not very sanitary looking and it's not very sanitary either. So the whole idea with the aqueous Argentum
It's not colloidal silver because there shouldn't be any kool-aid just means very small particle, right?
You know, but you know when you see dust, you know
We turn on a bright light like it's a a film projector back in the day or a projector and you see little particles
In the beam of light. Yes. Those are called kool-aids. Yeah, they they say right I always thought of it as dust
But yeah, yeah, it's almost in a colloidal state actually what keeps those fibers some some fibers look pretty big actually
It's electrostatics the same way spiders cross the Atlantic Ocean
Well, that's likely a bunch of small things that are pulled together into a clot or a you know clump, right?
Yeah, or dust a really small dust bunny will stay up because of electrostatics. Yeah, you know spider wet spiders back in the day
I don't know because
There's a lot of things have changed is they they jump off a tree and while they're jumping they shoot a long thread out
that
Web material where we were called spider silk and once it got electrostatic
Up about a thousand feet into the air if they're in New York or Jersey within about a week or so
They ended up in Paris, France
Yeah, interesting. Yeah, they kind of like flew it was electrostatically. Yeah electrical charge
Yeah, it's a fascinating fascinating thing. Usually not covered in your average biology book, by the way. Yeah, there's no material aspect
No material electrons. Sometimes I'll see a videos or we know electrons have mass. I'm like what?
What so what scale did you put them on I don't get that yeah, it's just the brainwashing and the convention is ridiculous
Really out of place even to say that but that's what they accept. So again with the energy with the silver
There's an energy that's being emitted from the silver. How do you push it? It's gonna stay with the silver, right?
That's what it does and in water. So it's going to the energy
Anybody's guess a really sensitive person a really good dowser that can speak
Arithmetically with measurement and metrics can tell you. Oh, yeah
the fielder on that silver coin in the water is half an inch or an inch or it goes to the top of the bottle some
Sensitive people could pick up on that, right?
Well, how do you get it off the field the field energetically into the water? You need to give it a little push
Right. So a little bit of electricity biological amount DC very tiny amount
Will agitate the silver enough and satisfy the surface of the silver
To release the field into the water you see. Hey, you know what?
This sounds like this sounds like if you took a electronics technology class on how a magnetic tape head works
You know if you run magnetic cassette tape or VHS or whatever does
Yeah, if you run it by let's say you open up the VCR or the tape deck and you start turning everything by hand
Moving and all that are you recording or playing anything? No, because guess what?
There's no plugged in no electricity. Yeah, you have to be plugged in for it to work, right?
So, you know again do that experiment what we're talking about is is already been accepted in a different field known as
Magnetic actually, wait a second aren't hard drives magnetic. Also. They are aren't they?
Yeah
So
It's exactly like so let's say you put the cassette tape in the cassette deck and you start
Turning the spools or anything by hand. There's no music. There's no sound if you try to record. There's no recording, right?
What happens that electricity allows a train energetic transfer? There's no materials. No electrons, but right? Okay, right
So this is what we're doing with the aqueous urgentum. I think it's freaking brilliant. Why?
Because you're not using any of the material which has the side effects, you know
In other words once, you know, the body works under induction nothing goes to your intestines and the body reproduces it
So think about this if you're taking colloidal silver that actually has the particles in it and your body wants to reproduce it
It's gonna have to reproduce physical metal inside the body. Do you know how much energy it takes to do that?
Well a lot right a lot. Yeah, so think about it just needs to reproduce the field. Well, that's great
That's what we do here. Anyway, it says right and it produces the field like crazy
Could you be using it just a little bit though
I mean in such a minuscule amount that it's barely noticeable and therefore it's acceptable
Couldn't that be a possibility or or is it?
No, you mean the colloidal or the aqueous urgentum the aqueous urgentum to where it's such a yes or no. Yes
No, that's in the advanced discussion there. The preparation like homeopathics is very important
There's some videos and how homeopathics are prepared to go through a certain process. It's not material
It's like they whack the bottle with a paddle that's got rubber then they whack it with something else
and they store it a certain way they right right so there's a
Preparation and I would be lying if I said I know how to make a more advanced preparation without it
You know advancing the the skill without me experimenting with it and then having a way to measure it
But I what I have measured and I do know is that it is far superior in every way
For the application of silver to biological or body then the colloidal silver
Right, so again, I think the if anyone questions is the easiest analogy is a magnetic magnetic transfer of information
Hard drives magnetic tapes
videotapes
Exactly the same way. I actually like exactly the same way in every way
You know, imagine you make colloidal silver and you start hearing the Beatles white album or Metallica, right? I'm not saying that
Right or or watching a porn or whatever, right so it's energetic transfer look it's energetic transfer
It allows it allows, you know, again, it's it involves when it comes to the videotape. It involves light, too
But you know, yeah, the energy is in other words
You could play those tapes they will physically wear but as long as you're getting the information off of it
There's nothing material there, right and the same thing with the aqua sargentum
You don't want any material as such
Present and
Yeah
Okay, we'll talk about that soon. I think maybe not tonight or maybe in the next week or so
we'll do the
Giveaway, we'll have someone picked out that gets one of the finalized kits the standard kit, right?
I'm just taking a lot of work for me to do but it's worth doing and I'm just sorting
I'm just sorting a way to absolutely randomize the selection. So
Yeah, that's all I'm doing yeah, I've gathered everything and run enough experiments to be pretty happy
with something that
You know, we can keep making it and it'll be the best possible way to make aqua sargentum and it's called silver made easy
It's a USB connection
Okay, so you don't need bat, right? You don't need batteries or transformers and USB I think is more prevalent than anything else
You're right. You go to Starbucks it at the counter. Guess what? They have a USB outlet right there, right?
Oh, yeah, actually, I bought a lamp recently brand-new lamp. It's got a USB port in it. It's just a regular lamp
Yeah, so wherever you go, you get it. You'll probably find more USB ports in your travels then
You know if you're in a car, it's 12-volt this if you're in a house, it's mains whatever they are
But you know, hi, you know, so yeah
You don't need batteries this way and and it's done a certain way that it filters out anything
Because you know to get the power of USB
The computer runs on DC and that creates an AC
Current which is then dumped down inverted back down to DC. So you get these crazy waveforms in there. It's called ripple
So I've managed to design and set up a wire that eliminates that as a matter of fact
I think he's a sub
Someone I got some of my speakers more than a year ago
And I then after that I sent him some wires that I made
And so what do you think of the wires and he says oh as soon as I put him in there?
Everything sounded louder and clearer, you know at the same volume, right? So the wires do make a difference
Actually, they act as filters antennas
That's why if you're into audio
You want to avoid six foot length wires and it's funny when you go to buy speaker wires or they offer it in six foot three
foot
Planks, that's the worst because they pick up radio waves
At six feet you you want a little less or a little more stay away from the six feet or the denominations of six
You know in half or a quarter of six. No used to crack me up
I always knew when somebody had a cheap patch cord like if I was playing in a band somewhere because inevitably
on stage you'd hear all of a sudden a radio station coming through their amp because they were using an unshielded wire and it was
Like right and the wrong way if it's unshielded you could shield it by tying a few knots on the negative
Yeah on the ground, but
Yeah, so I just want to you know, this will keep coming up and here's the thing
This is the aqueous Argentum thing is a quality of life increase, by the way
It's not just about being a fungicide or a bactericide, right? It's invigorating
Right and at the same time if you're around people who are pretty clueless
which I'm sure mostly everyone is around people that are completely clueless and they just
Especially understand that this is something that could be administered in a spray bottle, you know, the last thing I discovered
I don't know if I brought it up if you got
Work clothes athletic clothes or towels wherever that have BO after they come out of the washing you have a clothes dryer
Throw everything in the dryer right right before you hit the close the door spray the aqueous Argentum over it lightly and watch what happens
It's amazing how it works, right?
So and it's so cheap because the silver will never deplete and right so well just a quick thought here
I don't know why I'm thinking this but you know
Some people use the colloidal silver the bottled stuff and they put it into like, you know
What do they call that a vaporizer machine, right and then they breathe in the vapor, that's fine
Well, that's fine because the vapor will leave the silver behind hopefully well
But that's the thing is I'm thinking to myself if you take it in. Okay, you're not absorbing anything in your lungs, right?
No, it'll it'll induce through the lungs. Of course. It will it'll induce but that's not absorption. I said absorb
No, there's no absorption on anything biological ever anywhere. There's a slight permeability
Okay, right, but when the skin gets soaked, right
Yeah, but that's because it actually has it's permeable. Yeah slightly but it is hydrophobic as a matter of fact
You know if something's hydrophobic when water goes on it it beads, right when it's not what it's hydrophilic
It just lays on top of the object like a full sheet of water
Anybody comes out of the water and they stand there for a minute that the water starts beating on their skin, right?
Yeah, of course. Yeah, so their skin is hydrophobic, but it is permeable
Permeable means able to pass to a certain extent
But if you look anything biological anything that's alive that is experiencing absorption ain't got long to be alive
It'll be dead pretty soon guaranteed
So and this is the thing. Let's go to the next thing
We I think you brought this up also and I caught it when you said it caught my the heart attack
What would cause right? Yeah, I think yeah, what is it?
Well, the question I that jumped out of me is what is a heart attack then because we were talking about the organs a few
Sonics, well many Sonics ago now
Yeah, go ahead. I comprehend the function of the heart. But what is a heart attack?
Clearly happens, but what is true cause and how could it be avoided? Okay, that's a sonic and it's on
I think I brought this up in piecemeal
Well, there's a lot of solo sonic
Isn't there a lot of answers to that though?
Because you have look you have an intake in an outtake
I mean there are chambers that take things in and chambers that take things out and if you have a
An imbalance in one, you know
One's not taking in enough or taking in too much or the other way around or it's you know
And not pulling it all out and some of it ends up sitting there. This is the problem, right? This is a
Bad pump. No, no, it's not a problem. No, no, no, no, no, no, it's not mechanical, but it is mechanical outcome
Okay, it is a mechanical outcome
What's going on is the heart and simple is a breaking mechanism?
You that's why you'll never ever ever ever gonna hear about you hear about Chinese medicine and Vedic medicine
You're from the Hindu culture that you never hear about Greek medicine
Why because the Greeks said that the blood flows in a wave across the body up and down, right?
What and guess what when you translate the ancient Greek texts and you find out what they're really talking about
What they called the heart
Is actually the spleen
Hmm. Oh my gosh
Right, just like in ancient astrology
Venus was mercury and mercury was Venus. Oh my gosh, that's gonna throw you off a little bit, right?
Yeah, so once you sort that out, you can kind of make sure but they've done the same thing in the antithesis
They're calling the spirit and the soul the same thing. They say what's the spirit? It's the soul. What's the soul?
It's the spirit. I mean, come on. What kind of Mickey Mouse crap is that?
So this has been going on, all right, so the heart is a breaking mechanism because
The natural pulse just like nitrogen. Our air is mostly nitrogen, right and they tell you it's pretty it's not a noble gas
But it just sits there
but it doesn't if you evacuate a vacuum tube and put slightly pressurized nitrogen in there with a
You've got even a super high voltage. You'll see it starts to pulse
Right nitrogen is a pulsing gas when it's energized slightly with either temperature or electricity
Now now here's the thing
Frank Chester's got a lot of good old videos about that were some of his old grainy videos
He shows that they say the heart's a pump and I made a pump like he had a 2x4 with a weight on it swing
On a hinge and hit and hit something that hit a hose with a plunger to push
You know something that was like blood down a hose. It wouldn't move more than four or five feet
Right, and I've done analysis with someone over Skype when Skype first came out
They had access to like a console FE analysis computer
You know where they were the it's a finite element analysis where they design bridges and engines and stuff
Okay, and we put in the blood is about 50 percent solids at ninety eight point six, right?
Celsius and and then we put in average 2,000 miles of blood vessels at point
Seven millimeter average or point three millimeter average. Yes, you do have that much blood vessel
Even the big fat arteries if you average them out, they the average length diameter is 0.3 or 0.5 or 0.7
Anyway, that makes sense. Yeah. Yeah, they said to pump through that to pump that you need a pump with 1,200 horsepower
It's only gonna go about 200 miles, which is one tenth before you have cavitation. Oh my gosh
1,200 horsepower whose heart is 1,200 horsepower and does one tip
Oh, this is told the biology, you know
I don't use that too much because all their stuff is stupid, right?
And the worst part is when you have people that sound smart that say stupid things
they're all over the internet and most of them are
Mainstream, but you have a lot of them in the alternative, right? I'm not gonna mention anyone like cliff high or anything like that
but but
I'm nothing against these people, but it's just like oh my gosh. Oh my god. Just shut the F up
But keep going because actually he's what they're doing is accommodating a certain audience that is looking for that crap
So they're stuck in the loop a job dog chasing its tail not to BC
It'd be smirch a dog chasing its tail, which I think is a lot smarter than most people listen to him
But anyway, so I got nothing against him. I don't know the guy but jeez Louise
People stop telling me to go listen to cliff high. I mean, oh my gosh
I got better things to like the picking my nose. Actually, it's even better than I'll pick my neighbor's nose. That's even better
At least picking your nose. Oh, you know serve a purpose. Yeah, and speaking of picking you need to pick a better video. Okay?
So so what's happening is the body is in this pulsation mode and the capillaries are doing all the work when I say average
average
Vessel diameter is less than a millimeter. Does that sound like an artery? No, does it sound like a vein? No
Does it sound like a capillary? Yes
So guess what's moving all the blood right through induction, okay, and I've gone over this I'm confused of whether we've done
Okay, what happens is when there's an energetic transfer between the fluids and tissues to the capillary?
meaning materials becoming
Liquid and then gas and then energy going through the capillary to the other side or what I just said in reverse
If it's not in the capillary, it's energetic. It's material
It goes to a liquid the gas very quickly to energy and then it appears again inside the blood right in reverse
Okay, so when these processes happen, it creates a pulsing action based on we are not oxygen breathers
Sorry, if you think we are they people say we're oxygen breathers because we have an oxygen requirement. It seems right
We're actually nitrogen breathers because most of the air is nitrogen
Nitrogen and what I would just go over nitrogen is what it's a pulsing gas when it's what slightly energized
All this works so well together, you know
Just on a side note
We could show up at any medical convention University and just tear the pants off of anyone teaching anything
Regarding how the body works in like five minutes using their own stuff, you know that right? Mm-hmm. It's just crap. Okay
Well, what you just pointed out right there is just very simple. Yeah, so let's let's get back to what's hard
You can't have people raised
Like okay, what would happen if the culture of developed thousands of years instead of being developed around fire?
It was developed around magnetism. You'd have a very different culture. Absolutely
Okay, what if you have a culture where everyone understands how the body works that the things material things?
dematerialize and rematerialize on the other side of a membrane a
Non-permeable membrane
My gosh, yeah, so that means that we can do anything
Right, so you can't have that in this condition that the earth is in and the human society's in so what is a heart attack?
Yeah, all right. So it breaking let's go
Let's we'll address and now we address basically an overview of how the body moves the blood by the way
Yes, by the way, if you go study how platelets appear
Yes, they don't come from it they're stimulated depending on the conditions appear
You know when someone is they say when there's a wound platelets will develop they say they appear actually use the correct term
Well, and here's the thing about that. It's it's easily demonstrable because
Look, you donate blood or somebody draws a bunch of blood out of you the body replaces it
But I'm saying let's say there's a wound you look at bodily functions. I'm gonna be just continue this thought
Okay, I mean you will eventually nope. I'm just joking
What I mean is what they say when platelets appear in the blood vessel what happens to the blood vessel that dilates before it happens
Right because it has to move out of the way for these
Okay
So what I mean by this is look you ever watch Star Trek where they beam me up Scotty sure
Yeah, you ever see the transporters
They have all kinds of junk and stuff thrown in there or are they always clear because when they beam someone up they want them
To be beamed up on a clear platform, right? They need lots of room sometimes, right?
Okay, so when when platelets appear in a blood vessel, they have dilation
It doesn't say that they dilate so the platelets could come through the vessels dilate
Expand and then the platelets. What do they do?
They appear when you prepare 7-eleven or anything like you prepare a space like in the beaming
Explanation you prepare a space. Yeah, and then look yeah, right
So these things they're they're actually if you look at the language, it's trying to hint into you
You know, like, you know 9-eleven ground zero get it ground zero means atomic event
Anyway, it's the same thing. They use just a few terms that actually should be taken technically, right?
alright, so
The heart is a breaking let's just go so we discuss how things move in
Induction and blood vessels. It's the capillaries that I'd say are mostly responsible mostly
Blood flow, right? It makes most sense to right so
Now let's let's switch over to the heart being a break
Okay, anyone that has any kind of a brake mechanism bicycle stroller golf cart car
What do we know about that in order for the brakes to work?
They have a friction coefficient in other words when they're designed and made they have the optimum conditions
Usually let's say a car or bicycle the brakes are tested. They're made to work in what in the dry
What happens when you're in the rain?
They don't work as well
Friction goes down, right? Mm-hmm
Right. So friction goes down you slam on the brakes remember the old cars before ABS
They don't have any brakes, especially, you know big old car that was slightly worn, right?
Yes, that would happen a lot and with a bicycle
It's real simple because the you can see the two little rubber things clamp onto the onto the metal part of the tire
Well, if it's wet, it doesn't it doesn't grab it as well friction. Yeah
Okay, so how are what are ways to increase let's say you're always gonna be wet always okay because the inside of the heart, right
Always wet. Sure. Yeah, you know never said you have a dry heart
They always say you have a hard heart or whatever, but it's not on but never a dry heart
It might be a new thing colloquialism, but okay. Okay, so your hearts always wet
So then what's what's the other thing that determines?
Friction is the thickness of the blood thicker the blood you can have more friction like motor oil, right?
Okay, a lot in other words when a car manufacturer is being
Feels like they need to increase the MPG a little bit. What do they do?
They spec a lighter motor oil less friction, right?
That's a typical thing based on viscosity how viscous it is, right?
Okay. So what happens when you eat spicy food? It thins out the blood, right?
So you eat enough spicy food and you have other conditions that kick in
When that thin blood goes to the heart and the heart needs to act like a break
Is it going to be efficient or is a lot of blood going to slip through a lot of blood's gonna be less efficient
Because less efficient, right?
So what happens when you're not efficient with something it starts to go and there are intelligent systems in the body
That are checking back and forth and are like there's too much blood moving, right?
So you're you might feel agitated a lot of people before they have a heart attack. They have dizziness
They can't think clearly right muscle pains things like that. Yeah a bunch of warning signs, right, right
So essentially a blood that is too thin caused by eating spicy food. Yes. Spicy food is the number one in most cultures
Combined with other things emotional stresses and other changes in environment when the blood cannot be
Efficiently handled because that's what brakes do they handle the vehicle?
The
Heart can go into palpitation. It tries various things people just have a heart attack. They goes through various stages
It'll be a pain. They call it angina, right?
you'll have odd heartbeat and it'll normalize before you get a lot of signs a pain a pressure a
Flutter this kind of thing all these things happen
Yeah, you can trigger a heart attack with someone it won't be detected by a coronary if you use methylene chloride
By the way, that's a typical thing in prison by the by women have totally different warning signs from men
You know, yes, okay good because there are different species. They are. Yes. Yeah
within the same
Species, I wouldn't say subspecies. It would be superior in many ways sub and some other ways
It just goes back and forth right but men and women are complimentary species
Yeah, complimentary. In other words, we're cosmically we're on a scale equal
Certain things like if I needed a group of people that had
Strengthened their legs. I would pick mostly women
You'd be better off if I needed if I needed people with upper body strength
I would pick men to come for the task right like women more efficiently use water
Utilize water and and seem to have better hydration than men do in general until their water breaks
Yes, anyway
All right, so
So
So here's the thing here
What else thins out blood actually believe it or not?
Blood thinners is a calling for a lot of pharmaceutical drugs years ago. They used to call them blood
You need a blood thinner. You ever hear that? Yes all the time. Yes. I used to hear all the time. Yeah, okay, so a
Blood quality that is thinner than normal. I'm still this is not about addressing the
Energetic
This is just the physical quality of it
Which is caused by and food the energy from the foods also and what you intake there are chemicals that will do that
Is in a prison when they want to take out someone they died of a heart attack
And that doesn't show up in the court. They just put a little methylene chloride in the food. Where do you get methylene chloride?
Right, very simple. It's a very easy ingredient to find
And and it's tasteless odorless and small amounts. You don't don't need much
Yeah, so anyway
Yeah, don't want to get into more but anyway, I gave up the whole thing
So so this is what's going on with the heart attack simply. It's a break that doesn't stop
Now essentially I would steer everyone to directly to Frank Chester watch as much of his stuff about the heart
He does do about the chat the seven-sided figure that is lawful. He talks about that, but
It's a breaking mechanism
He also he was inspired to get into a deeply the geometry of an all of the heart from Steiner's work Rudolf Steiner
You have to say Rudolf Steiner Steiner. Yeah, so
You could look at that. I would highly recommend that
Also, you know the heart has it's more about mixing
It doesn't go in and out one-third of the blood stays within the volume of the heart to mix it, right?
Okay, and it goes back I never goes through the all the volume
It always keeps only two-thirds goes through at a time the hearts over empty in other words. Yeah your heart you have an empty heart
No one has an empty heart in this case. Yeah, at least two-thirds always one-third full
or two-thirds empty, so
So this is basically the mechanism like for example
If you look at Westerners Americans or whatever that adopt the diet, I like eating spicy food
Right if you look at their ear the bottom lobe of their ear just the very bottom part the cut
It's a part that's typically pierced for an earring
What's that doesn't it droop more?
Well, it only droops. It has a very sharp dimple in it
Like a cleft when that develops if you're around someone on a regular basis
Yeah, and you start noticing a very deep cleft developing in the bottom lobe of the ear. That's heart attack
Signal in other words, your heart is being taxed taxed taxed taxed and and it's interesting is
Right before the heart attack. It is really really prominent and after the heart attack it goes away. It's really if they survive it
So look for that as a sign
Another one is the tip of the nose turning red
By the way, that's almost like when you draw caricatures of alcoholics. They typically yeah, well because that does happen
Alcohol is a blood thinner all among Caucasians, especially you you will see a you know
That red or pink tip nose, you know, and sometimes the whole nose turns
Oh, you don't know black people black people blush and the tip of their nose turn they do tan in the dark
What do you mean Caucasians everybody knows my bliss? I'm just joking
I'm just telling you what I see is that I can't see on on on on people with more melanin
Okay, or whatever the hell is I cannot see it
Never get that right. I call some people black and say oh you call me black as a real Negro you call
I'm any girl. So anyway, I stick I don't know what to say
Melanated is probably better, but someone someone won't like that. Yeah, of course
I guess I guarantee somebody if I played this for everybody somebody would get pissed exactly
But no the red nose thing is common among alcoholics, and I think it's good
if you know someone
Physical emotional stress can cause that but if you see it reoccurring way, it's not part of their normal condition
Constitution. So again, or if you're just Irish, I mean in that case, of course, Irish drunk. Okay, so I'm sorry
If you're Irish, you got a lot more problems than that, but I'm just joking. No that too
But I mean Irish and drunk. I mean that's like saying, you know, that's a cliche
Yeah, well the word Greek is French for taking it up that you know, what we had this discussion
Okay, so I'm sorry I had to do it good
Well and the thing with the New York accent you 30 third and third, you know, I always I told listen
If you have a New York accent, no matter how smart you are, you can sound dumb. So stop it, right?
You know a real heavy accent, you know
Anyway, I try and pull back the the the Northeastern Jersey, New York
Sound in my voice a lot when I'm when I'm trying to do things where I'm explaining, you know
Things I was hired. Yeah, I hate that
See the connection to culture you see it's the culture. Yeah, you never grew up saying I want to sound like a New Yorker
No, not at all. But and the thing is I don't notice it
I end up going to other places and they go. Oh my god
Listen to you like they're sitting there laughing at me in Indiana because of the way I say coffee
Like I was coffee. It's coffee. I'm like what I didn't say like that. That's what they hear
I say coffee, you know, I was coffee coffee
It's not it's not and it's something that's beyond like I was once in the South and Jimmy John if he had a
Pickup truck with a rifle rack and two dogs in the back. It's not a it's sound just like the cliche
Yeah, and he says Greek you got to stay in the truck because I got to go talk Southern to them folks
Okay. Yeah. All right. That's no problem. You know, no matter what I do there was a giveaway, right?
So you see there's extreme conditions, right?
it's crazy because you know you and I hear that as if you and I sit in a
Frankly if you and I sit among some of those guys
You'll just hear stuff like he has getting off and going over down to town to boom, right?
And I guarantee you I just said something there, but you don't know what I said. No, I got it. I got
Jamaican is another Jamaican sounds like a completely foreign language
At least that sounds musical, you know, at least that's that's a gotta gotta, you know
It's got a bit of a melody to it. But I mean that Southern stuff. Oh my goodness
and and they think that we sound crazy because it's like
Anyway, and there you go culture again. It's all culture
Big so so anyway
The heart is a break
Let's just like we did a little dissertation on colloidal silver in the magnetic devices the magnetic tapes and hard drives same
Analogy same analogy here part is a breaking mechanism
Part is a breaking mechanism and guess what? The heart is also a breaking mechanism
Can that be can you consider it as a breaking mechanism because it is a breaking mechanism
They say the heart is a breaking mechanism. You certainly did
You know the last the last thing they hear though
I just want to ask you real quick and you're probably gonna scoff at me, but let's do it
Anyway, you know, I've studied a lot of these death certificates, right where they have these explanations of why it is
Someone has passed away and they they give a cause of death
I always I look every time I see, you know cardiac arrest as the cause of death. I look at it and I go
Okay, so this is somebody who was either lazy or didn't know what they were doing
Because that is never in my mind the actual cause of death
Because by the way when they use the word arrest, you know
If a cop stops you just to ask you what time it is if any any official
quote-unquote municipal government without
Claiming the government is too much but stops from your normal path or travel is considered an arrest
Yeah, when something is look a very simple arrested development. We've all heard this term
Well, that simply means you were on a normal trajectory
You were in motion in development or you're supposed to be in motion in development
And therefore it was arrested which means guess what a stop. Yeah
It's for any reason but here's the thing the the coroner used to be a very respected in high position now
It's just trashed through the street like everything else, right? Yeah in a lot of places in a lot of places
I mean as I know you don't you know hold much faith in doctors
But at the very least if the coroner was a doctor you might have a chance that they might understand
You know to be able to identify the organs anyways
Doctors you do have to have faith because it is a religion
Fair enough, but the thing is I mean at least they might have a chance at knowing what went wrong in the body
Maybe sort of you know, okay. No, they don't have a chance because they they were how did they how did they get their medical?
knowledge
Listen, it's pretty easy to understand that if the head was separated from the body that might be the cause of death
Okay, it's not hard
I'm just saying but when I see this laziness of cardiac arrest or heart attack basically being three
I always think to myself heart attack car accidents and what else but it's but it's nonsense because here's well
Here's the question. I have for you. Isn't a heart attack. Generally not the cause of death
Isn't that the thing that actually results from something else having gone wrong?
Like in other words, the heart attack is a symptom not the thing that did it usually I mean, isn't that the case or?
Yes, it is, but it could be accepted as a cause of death
I could see how it could be because you it's not a card attack
It's more like you killed your heart and the heart didn't do its job and it's breaking now. That's fine
That's fine
But what I'm saying is that the majority of the time and yes indeed there could be instances where that is the cause of death
I understand that but what I'm saying is the majority of the time how often I've seen that on death certificates
How often that is there as it's like listen idiot at any point in time you could list that
Okay, though it has nothing to do with the gunshot to his head. That's what did his heart stop?
No, I guess it's overused like the word virus
Doctor and they don't know they can't diagnose you real quick. So you have an unknown virus
You have an unknown virus, which is great because I literally just told you it's unknown
Which means I don't know what it is, but it's a virus. How do you know that?
Good question complete
Ridiculous. So I think we're gonna get into the next part here on how the heart is a breaking mechanism
No, we did that, okay
Why am I why am I? Yeah, it's very important to consider it as such don't be fooled by the rest now
What is moving the blood is the pulsing action of what being a nitrogen breather?
We're not nitrogen breathers. Well oxygen breathers
Oh, really go look at the ratios and not when the majority of what it is
Look, if you agree that you're taking air into that area of your body, which is called the lung
What are you taking in if you look at the concentration far as I understand?
Maybe the measurements are wrong
But everybody seems to keep coming up with the same percentages and it seems to me like more of it is nitrogen than anything else
Is that right or wrong?
Yes, so we're nitrogen breathers, which is a pulsing gas
We have an oxygen requirement as a catalyst to get the nitrogen to become oxygen in the body in the in the lung tissue
So the the pulsing action of the natural pulsing action of the soul in the metabolism
Is regulated by the heart now, hold on. Let's go back to the brakes
I think we did mention
The heart is a braking mechanism, right? Yeah, we okay brakes
We mentioned the friction part only but you know, you're here's a the brakes didn't work because the brake lines were cut
Right for if electric. Okay. The other thing there is
Okay, there's a communication electrical impulse
It's secondary by the way that happens from other parts of the body
You know why a lot of dead people are found dead on the toilet old people
So they say dead people are fun a lot of very old people seniors that live alone are found dead on the toilet
Okay, there is a nervous
Nerve path and a pulsing electrical path that runs around the rectum goes back to the heart
Okay. Yeah interesting, right?
so a heart attack or a failure for the heart to do its job as a breaking minute mechanism can be
Induced electrically and electromechanically. Oh, by the way defibrillators, right?
Can't say that words right now, but right when they try to revive someone know you said defibrillator. That was correct. Yeah
Yeah, okay. I didn't didn't feel like I said it right you did though
Okay, so you see maybe they should put one of the pads on the on their ass and the other pad on there
Anyway, oh wait and most people the pad on their ass would be right on their head or where would you put?
Oh, no. Anyway, sorry
Yeah interchangeable there now you're a part of the accuracy which one of these probes goes in your butt which one goes yeah
So there is a nervous impulse, you know electrocution
Electrocution stops the heart right that it does
Okay. So again, my brake lines are cut. Did we mention the heart is a breaking mechanism? We did mention I think so
okay, remember that and
everything in
The uncommon sense realm of reality because sense is uncommon right not common just any sense
Everything shows that the heart is a breaking mechanism