Gonna give the Greek a call and get a rated Y going here.
That's what I'm planning on doing.
Let's see what happens here.
Bring up my Skype.
Okay.
And here we go.
Holy crap, the ringer is loud. How you doing, man?
Yeah.
Okay, let me see here.
How do I sound?
This is the...
It's definitely the phone. I can tell.
You can tell?
We'll keep it. Keep it, right?
Yeah, it's not bad. Not bad.
All right. All right.
A little better. A little warmer.
I got up from a nap, too. I'm exhausted.
Gotcha.
I'm not exhausted. I'm just tired.
No worries. It's a little warmer than the...
The computer is a little warmer sound, a little more natural sound, but it's not a big difference.
It's okay.
All right. Let's see. I can rotate the mic.
This is a...
Oh, there you go. You just lifted up the quality a bit.
It's a post...
It's a...
I did a microsurgery.
And...
All right.
Let me see if I can get this thing rotated.
I'm usually more impeccable about getting stuff together.
All right. How's that?
Sounds good.
Okay.
Yeah. Improvement from before.
All right.
Yeah. Yeah. It was pointing towards the shirt.
It's a little tiny microphone hanging from the wire, which I surgically grafted.
Oh.
From another set that I like the microphone better.
It's better anyway.
Yeah. Excellent.
Maybe we'll do stuff.
All right.
Hey. Rated Y 42, I think.
And here we go. Ocelli in the Greek.
Real quick, I want to address something in the chat room real fast.
You guys gave me a couple of ideas about T-shirts and hats.
I promised to mention that to the Greek, and so I'm doing so.
Greek, first, how are you doing?
And second, I'll ask you about the T-shirts and the hats.
Oh, no. T-shirts and hats, please.
But, yes, do it.
I think it's part of the culture.
Just visiting, taking notes is fine.
I think I picked up on that.
Okay.
Yeah.
Just here taking notes, that'll work.
But just visiting, taking notes wraps it up a little better,
which I'd like to read an email also that was sent,
which is the common sentiment for many, many years.
But this individual's brain works really well on stringing words together
and gets the sentiment across.
Nice. Go ahead.
Yeah, that'd be great to hear.
I want to bounce back to the chat.
By the way, I haven't been around, and I went into the chat,
and I dropped in some pics, photos of some magnetic secrets.
Oh, that's what that is.
Okay, so that's that.
I didn't understand that.
I looked at the picture.
If you blow up the picture, it's self-evident what the two pics are, right?
Okay.
And you read the description.
But I wrote anyone with at least three sharpened pencils in their pocket
can figure out what to do next if you want to build what's called a magnetic motor.
And once you understand this,
you'll see why all the free energy motors don't work and will never work
and can't work, right?
Okay.
And that's all I'm going to say about it.
I think around what they called,
last time I had a discussion around what they called January
and the Pope's work schedule.
I'll talk more about the water.
Okay.
But up until then, I'm kind of bound by agreements to just keep it under wraps
because it's gotten to the point right now where it's just the stuff you see
and hear about that sounds like fantasy, right?
And it's gotten to the point where even if you had a device,
you couldn't replicate it.
Okay.
It's that sensitive and that much detail goes into it.
And there's nothing like it in the world.
And, yeah, the Greek thinks he's got a high opinion of himself.
No, it's not that.
It's just that I happen to make some extraordinary things.
And that's all I'm going to say about that.
I want to go back to what we were saying earlier and then back to the chat.
Gotcha.
But only extraordinary in that they are not ordinary literally
because people don't have these things,
but it's really practical knowledge that's applied properly, right?
They never will have them because they're looking at it the wrong way.
I see.
For example, I went on to a COMSOL, C-O-M-S-O-L,
their F-E-A, finite element analysis, where it's the program to get for engineers, right?
And you just put in all whatever you want to do,
and it shows you what's going on in terms of whatever,
stresses, materials, deflections, magnetism.
So I put in what I was doing, and it didn't show anything at all.
It just showed the standard conventional BS.
They're never, ever going to figure it out.
Never, ever.
I've discussed some of it online.
Because if you explain a principle to an engineer or a scientist,
and they want to go, let's say, level two, three, four,
where level five is industrially, you know, make it,
they're going to go to a computer, right?
They're going to sit down in front of, you know,
one of these CAD computers or, you know, F-E-A analysis.
Someone's going to do it.
Because I don't think you're going to get any 90-year-old engineers
that used to draw stuff with, you know, pencil and slide rule doing it.
So the minute they get on the computer and put the parameters in,
they're done.
They just killed the entire project
because the computer does not acknowledge what's happening here.
Does that make any sense?
Well, it doesn't make sense that the computer doesn't acknowledge it
because I thought, well, no, actually, maybe it does.
Because, you know, it only works with what parameters you put in it, right?
Well, yeah, exactly.
It's subject to human input.
And this reminds me of back in the early days
when they were doing computer graphics, they couldn't do water very well.
You know, like an ocean scene?
Oh, yeah.
Too complex.
It looked too fake, right?
This is different because they're not even acknowledging things
that are going on with, let's say, a magnet and water at all.
It doesn't even show the parameters at all.
So if the computer negates it, the engineer, well, anyway,
it's another discussion.
It's kind of funky because it goes back to reverse alien technology, right?
It's not alien at all.
Well, funny stuff to me is that, you know,
a lot of these guys who are supposed to be engineers in these fields,
they never account for magnetism when they're talking about electricity ever.
And I go, well, isn't that one of those things that just comes along with it?
It's just a passenger.
It's part of the equation.
It has to be.
Otherwise, right.
But here's the thing.
I'm not an engineer.
I'm not even I'm using magnets, but I'm not using magnetism.
It's like this.
You've heard me give the analogy in prior talks.
I've been saying this for three decades now.
Imagine, well, this society was developed around fire technology.
Right.
Imagine a society that was developed around magnetic technology.
But it's not so as you might think.
Go back to the society that was developed around fire technology.
So all of your technology is based on fire as the premise of production or something.
Let me ask you, when you're using and developing your society,
is everyone putting their hand in the fire all the time?
Well, of course not.
It wouldn't survive.
So what and the reason they're never going to figure out a society developed on magnetic technology,
because guess what?
They're putting their hands in the magnetism the whole time.
And the key is not to put your hands in the magnetism, to use the part that is not magnetic.
So the society whose technology is based on fire is using the fire in a certain way where they all survive it.
Right.
So right now, the society, this society is using the magnet,
the magnet in a way where they're not going to survive advancement with magnets.
That actually makes a whole hell of a lot of sense.
The utilization of fire has caused a great deal of progress.
So one could say that there were progressions at a certain point.
Right.
There were progressions from just, say, having nothing to fire.
And you could utilize fire to build things, to reshape, to mold, to change, to destroy.
Yes.
But this was a methodology that could be used to do everything from forging metal to keeping oneself warm.
And that's all great and good.
But it's more about when you don't utilize the fire and when you're able to not engage with it.
Well, you sequester the harmful sides, and they don't know how to do that.
By the way, it's not just fire. It's fire in the wheel.
Uh-huh.
Right?
In the other case, it would be the magnet and the toroid.
There you go.
Which is a donut, basically.
Yeah.
Which I heard the donut reference.
And I was going to say, that shape in that image that you put there,
that was the first thing that occurred to me, is that constant toroidal occurrence that seems to be...
Why don't you blow them up? I don't know if you can get them really big.
The north is a certain way, and the south side looks very different.
Same magnet.
Uh-huh.
So what's going on?
So you're looking for an imbalance, right?
If a system is in balance, and you ask someone to describe it, guess what?
It's static. It's not moving.
Right.
So the way you make a motor is by creating what?
An imbalance.
How does a water wheel work?
Because there's an imbalance.
Yeah, there's an imbalance.
The weight goes in one direction, and therefore pushes the water wheel down,
and the other part lets go of the water, which lets it go up,
and this is the imbalance, which causes the motion.
Yeah.
Right.
If you put water on both sides of the wheel at the same time, well, now it's a fountain, right?
It's not a water wheel.
Now it doesn't do anything if it's perfectly balanced.
Right.
They're making magnetic fountains, is what they're doing.
They don't know how to make a magnetic fountain.
They never will.
There you go.
By the way, what I'm saying is regarding the surface society,
the surface-dwelling human earth inhabitants,
the black vanilla world, the black world,
the black projects underground, who knows what's going on there.
You can get an idea, and I think they've always had it.
So anyway, I get a little bit of smell of suppression, not too much lately.
Speaking of suppression and things of the opposite suppression,
someone also left, before I get to email, 618, the 7-ish of the 4th,
sprayed some aqueous argentum on a load of clothes and dryer,
took the shtank out of the windbreaker.
Good looking Greek.
Yeah, I got you.
Yep, that works.
I do it often.
I have been doing it often.
I have mentioned in another Sonic that, you know,
I just don't take anything for granted, right?
Don't take stuff for granted.
I've been doing things for decades that in passing I've shared with people,
like just trivial stuff, or they'll come over and see what I'm doing.
And I'm like, wow, what's this?
I'm like, oh, I never thought of that.
Oh, I said, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I was like, you know, a lot of the things I take for granted
that are like energy-saving, space-saving, economical, efficient,
I take for granted.
And I said, you know, these little things need to be shared, right?
Like putting soap in a spray bottle, my gosh, and diluting it.
You know, you buy dishwash soap once a month.
If you dilute it and put it in a spray bottle,
you'll be using less water to rinse it off.
It'll be more effective.
And you'll buy soap, dishwash soap, twice a year.
Well, the total savings of $5 will be, right?
Well, no, it's actually more for me.
And I'm doing that.
Now, there's something where I affected a change from doing these Sonics
with you where I went, you know what?
He's right.
That makes sense.
Let me try it.
And I already know that's going to be more than a $5 savings for me.
Yeah, I'm just giving the scale as low.
It could be more.
Actually, if you get the good soap, it could be $50 a year.
No, it could be.
The organic soap, you know.
Well, that's the next step.
Yeah, this is important because, you know, years ago,
especially in the 70s,
there was a lot of talk about cancer being caused by a lot of the chemicals
in our society, right?
More so than now.
Yeah, for sure.
Believe it or not, 70s, 80s, for sure.
There was a movement to go organic and, you know,
these chemicals and everything we use are causing cancer.
But here's a study.
You ready?
This was done by the Germans.
This was done by various other serious people, let's say, looking into it.
Okay.
Yeah.
It is the chemicals introduced in the consumer products, right?
But specifically the fragrances,
specifically the fragrances is what's killing us, right?
Let's say.
Well, that kind of makes sense because of the way it's always been described
to me physically.
You get these little particles that get up in the air and end up kind of
making contact with you,
and therefore that engages your olfactory sense the way they always
explained it anyway.
Well,
it's actually the chemical constituents compounds that to make these
synthetic fragrances that are more dangerous than the actual synthesized
product itself.
Okay.
So in other words, we're talking about the price of dish soap.
It's get the ones without the fragrance.
Now, what I did state,
this is sounds really trivial.
Oh my gosh.
These guys are going to talk about soap for the next two hours.
No, we're not.
No,
the blue soap or the green soap,
the popular brand it's got a fragrance in it,
but it cuts grease really well.
Yes.
So what you do is you get some of the,
the,
the airy fairy soap to do the organic one.
I forgot what it's called.
They even sold it at Walmart.
It's got no color,
no smell.
Yeah.
There's a couple of them,
but yeah,
there's,
and you mix them,
you mix them together.
So you do a squirt of the blue in a,
in a container of water squirt of the other one.
What the other one does is it breaks down the fragrance.
It does.
It breaks down the,
so the fragrance becomes more innocuous.
So not only,
not only does it not contain the fragrance,
but it actually breaks down the other one,
or does it just simply dilute it?
Yeah.
It mitigates the other one.
It breaks it down.
So it's not present or harmful.
Yeah.
Excellent.
Okay.
That's a big deal,
believe it or not right there.
yeah.
All right.
Well,
another thing to add to my regimen here,
because that's something,
look,
I was definitely interested in,
in more efficiently utilizing the stuff I'm buying one way or another.
Let's be more efficient about it.
I mean,
it's just only sensible given the economic conditions that I find myself in.
It's gotta be,
you know?
So yeah,
definitely.
Okay,
cool.
Yeah.
And there's others where we've mentioned,
you know,
the hydrogen peroxide,
as an oxidizer,
right?
Oh yeah.
It's safe,
you know?
So all right.
Email real quick,
because I've gotten thousands of emails like this,
but this one is really put together.
Well,
it really explains much.
I might leave out part of it,
but it's anonymous.
So wanted to send a brief greeting.
I'm going to actually,
I have to break.
It's kind of long.
So I'm going to break,
skip around.
Sure.
Wanted to send a brief greeting before I hit the sack here.
This pleasant evening at the land between we're okay.
Camping.
All right.
I just wanted to tell you that your weekly Sonics with Chucks are being
listened to personally,
and it's been for several years.
I'm able to put some of the basic suggestions to use,
always looking for crossover between you and a few others.
Clean some knowledge and wisdom.
I glean knowledge and wisdom from it's obvious.
Thanks to your bringing attention to that.
Our bodies are a closed system in which the body utilizes is inducted
where needed as food passes from mouth to anus,
that the heart is in the pump,
that the full moon is the new moon,
not the dark moon,
but the 12th month is February.
And occasionally there's a 13 month when the moon after the 12th is
smaller than the 12th moon,
the first and seventh being the largest,
that there are proper and lawful ways to conduct one's business,
that the USA wanted to receivership in 1933,
practical and helpful ways to use aqueous,
our gentlemen peroxide,
that children aren't kids,
that it's an insult to be considered nice,
a different way to consider scripture and many other practical,
ponderable things.
You're going into a little more detail about subjects.
You discussed there the last several months with Chuck and it's
appreciated.
I also think Chuck has been getting better,
better at carrying out as part of the dialogue,
which brings the main reason why I'm contacting you and so on and so
forth.
So compliments to both.
And it ends up with,
thanks for your offering with Chuck and to Chuck for the time being.
So thank you very much.
Yeah,
sure.
The body of that paragraph,
I think is really a good summary of what I've been hitting on lately.
So thank you.
Excellent.
And I'm always pleased to,
you know,
when,
when I hear that I actually served a purpose during these discussions,
you know,
I appreciate it.
Yeah,
no,
it's not about that.
It's just,
I think that he put it together really well all around.
And by the way,
before we go on a different subject or subjects,
what about the shirts and the hats?
Yeah,
no,
no problem.
We can work that out.
I was just curious if,
cause a couple of,
I,
I got a couple of emails where people had said,
Hey,
you're doing shirts and hats for other shows that you're producing and your
show.
Uh,
how about Otelli in the Greek?
Why aren't you doing one for that?
And I said,
because Otelli in the Greek is not a show.
Right.
It is a simple answer.
That's better.
But either way,
some people like the idea of having,
you know,
things that represent something they appreciate.
Uh,
you know,
so I said,
well,
I guess I can discuss that with the Greek and see what he thinks about it.
And,
and,
Jokes about that kind of stuff in private actually that's what it's like
But when you put if you if you put a camera lights and a microphone space will deny the whole thing
So if you start dealing and going
Let's say a lot of the Greek speak stuff to a bank or to an attorney. You just walk off the chase
He's gonna deny everything
But once you get to know them they brag about it, right?
The joking yeah the joking to I'm telling you I mean, you know, they like my favorite one
I heard many times told many different ways. It's sort of like, you know
What's what's the difference between when you crack open, you know a Jewish guy's head and a Catholic said, huh?
You know what lost him open with a brick and you split him wide open and his head's totally open right out there his brains
Everywhere. What's the difference?
You know, I don't know
nothing
Okay
Why is money green
Because because did you take it before it's right? Yeah. Yeah
So now I heard that if you say Negro you're considered a racist or if you say Puerto Rican, you're considered a racist
well, I don't know why Puerto Rican is racist and
American racist they still use Negro as I think
People crazy and by the way, this is all set up. You know, I've been saying this for a long time
You're being set up the whole way. There's no power shift. It's the same people playing with you, right?
Oh, yeah, they just give you a different different, you know, fable now is to turn your attention to but the truth
Well when it's being ultra conservative and religious, it's the same people but they're gonna say oh no these people not took over. No, no. No, no
It's the same stuff. He was me too. Here's the new boss. Same as the old boss. Oh always
Yeah
I mean the same people that were telling you embrace your sexual freedom or the very same people who said we should go back
Where you don't
Engage in your sexuality and well, that's why I say before you go, you know, the purpose of life is to be alive, right?
That's like there's nothing else to it
I think I've gone over this many many times where if you read all the ancient writs other than being
Contemplative and let's say worshiping your God and respecting your God
what is the
Systematic, let's say the the whole thing. That's that's
Basically the subject of life is agricultural based to have food and have clothing to have shelter and be happy generally, right without pain
Be reasonably, you know
Healthy, you know, but not in that way that most people think anyway
Right. It basically it's just being alive, right? It's all agriculture. It's all food food clothing shelter based, right? Sure
So so basically the purpose of life is to be alive
That's it right so here's the thing if you're being
Subjected to these things mentally don't you want to kick them in the shins at least once before you go?
And the way you do that is by you know speaking about it, right?
And and not participating. That's that was the greatest by the way the greatest
What is it? I don't like bringing up Gandhi because he's not who people think he is wasn't in character even
But not participation is the greatest
Resistance, right?
So right
But some things are seem unavoided but doesn't mean that you have to completely endorse we've got over this with the draft
When they had a draft people thought it was not voluntary. It was voluntary, but you just don't know where it's not voluntary
the same with court people just don't know where it's
Not voluntary, right? I got I've gone over both of those. So
Yeah, anyway, cool. All right anything else in chat, by the way
I think you covered it all much as I can remember for sure. I'm looking back now. Just take a quick look
No, I think I think you pretty much got it all didn't you let's see
Yeah, I mean your email you took care of that. So, okay
Let's see. We kind of ended we got into some of the questions about
Last week
Which were we got into depth towards the end of it basically about how the the energy works, right? How silver?
Yes, basically taking the energy off the silver the way you take the energy off of one magnetic tape to dub another
By the way, let's call biasing
You know if you remember the old tape decks that had their bias current had to be adjusted, right?
That's but when you buy something it's an extra push, right?
Yeah, I think we got into that and I didn't get any response on that but I think the the message was pretty clear
No, I think that was absolutely clear. You described energetic transfer as opposed to physical transfer
Where you know, you literally have to take a portion of something off of something in order to deliver it over
You push it with other energies. Yeah, but this can all be done with the mind by the way
But that makes it
People people have too much of an inferiority complex and a low self-esteem
I'm just saying it plainly to think that they can do things with their mind when they're doing them. Anyway
You know what? I mean?
so
In other words your emo and your mind affects things, but we did they don't feel that they're significant enough literally
I mean this literally well a lot of people directly attract
I mean, I know you don't like any of that stuff and neither do I that whole you know
The the concept of what do you do you attract things to you?
But the truth is you do you do and you don't you okay?
I've been in a situation for years where I figured if I changed my mindset
about it
That those things would not happen. Let's say a negative thing and they just don't still kept happening
right and
Because it's just part of you got to see is it is a format in the program of the construct that we're in
Or is it something you know what I mean?
But but quite often you don't need to encourage things to come to you
And and this is what the the trouble is a lot of times people do actively encourage
Certain things to come to them is certain problems certain patterns patterns. They're formed patterns, and they don't know what they're doing basically
it's kind of like
Patterns it's the way you look if everyone has a New York accent you all sound pretty normal
But the moment you leave New York you sound pretty fucking stupid right well you sound definitely different
The people from Indiana, I don't know if that was on air or off air
But I told you about it, and they were just cracking up at the way. I said coffee
You know because yeah, well there's different ways you could tighten that up coffee or coffee. Yeah, well
That well they were
Indiana but either way a coffee, and I'm like oh that sounds bizarre to me
You know and they they're like no, that's like a New York thing, and I'm thinking to myself
That's just the right way you say it just coffee
It's not right, but the patterns you see if the patterns fit if everyone is in a similar pattern
Manifestation that's where the normalcy comes in that's what Greek speak has all been about is due to
Objectifying patterns basically and
Methodologies and concepts and words and all that stuff right, but words not in the way that people use them
But in the one in what there's and how they were supposed to be used
And literally supposed to be used right otherwise the reference manuals go away the other thing is the concept of time I?
Had a discussion with someone recently about it. I'm gonna make this just interjection really short
The way people always refer to time is with some kind of scale right years months seconds hours minutes, right of course you begin
Yes, it's it mentioned at the end of the sentence, but yeah, it's literally what it frames
It's a scale the measure so sure so a tape measure doesn't do anything right until you start using it against something else
Right of course, but what is the tape you got a tape measure in your pocket or whatever it has no value at all
You know in itself as a scale
It's when you start comparing it you're right on op physical objects so time scales have no met no worth
until you start
Comparing them and including them as a function of an event
This went on for this long right or this happened then right so this is what some people say
There's no time yes there. There is there are events and the way we record and memorialize events is using time scale
Right right, so that's it. It's very simple, and it's it's kind of like the soul in the spirit really hard for people
If you have a Catholic upbringing or a Jewish upbringing the soul and spirit part is very very difficult to accept
Why?
Because subconsciously those two cultures were quote-unquote religions. Yes have indirectly drilled into the people that this is
Something that you're supposed to hate, but you're supposed to say you like it meaning their religion
It's interesting that and now let me branch out a little further sure you always hear about how Catholics and Jews
Have a guilt trip kind of mindset right? Yeah, I just broke down. Why they're made
To hate their religion in the culture, but they can't say it
They always have to say how they associate with it right and how they like it and how they identify themselves with it
Yeah, that's it has to be something that they own and owns them simultaneously
Yeah, but they they're brought up in a way that it's it's hateful
I mean not hateful to others hateful within its own self full of contradiction because none of it applies to anything that it's supposed to
Be based on well something that I'm forced to own and also is forced upon me to own me
I gotta say I would develop some resentment of it. Whatever it is you know
Personally maybe I'm taking it too personal
That's not what I mean
In other words the culture and the religion and the way that it's administered and procured to the population on every level whether it's a
Conservative or liberal group. Yeah is internally designed to be quote-unquote schizophrenic
I'm not going to use the psychological terms here in other words where?
It's you know the idea like you tell someone you love them in a minute later
You punch him in the face, and you say oh, I'm sorry
I love you, and then you punch him in the face like well. Oh my gosh now
Associating love with being beat up well
It's more about duality than schizophrenia because schizophrenia is not really that much about the contrast
Say is when you bring up anything that might even slightly have a lick of religious connotation to it
That's someone who has a Jewish or Catholic upbringing, but like for example if you bring up
This is again the soul and the spirit definition
Mm-hmm
That's doesn't when you say soul and spirit doesn't have a little bit of a licking of a religious connotation slightly slightly yes
Anyone who has a Jewish or Catholic upbringing will resent anything you have to say, but they'll let yes you to death yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, because this is how they are right like for example no matter how
the JES you it right or the
Being kosher no matter how adherent there that you start discussing that from a biblical point of view oh, no
To do with what I'm doing you see
So they're kind of crazy, and you have what between Jews and Catholics would you say about a billion people?
I don't know maybe yeah, yeah pretty close pretty pretty fucked up
You asked me, and how do you how do you fix them?
I don't think you can't you can't fix anyone they have to want to fix themselves good luck with that
Well, that's the other problem is I think both of those
persuasions from what I understand
Definitely imply that you you begin in a bad place
I mean before you even have a conscious thought or take an action which you have
Taken of your own volition you're already. That's a fail. Yeah, it's not it's a failsafe that was put in
Early on humans were quite advanced
And they started advanced you know they started that way and they were destroyed and on and on and on
And the cycle keeps good archaics is a good place to look up the chronology on that
So the last iteration that we've witnessed now was to make a dumbed-down version that can be used not necessarily as a slave
But yeah, they're happy with being owned you can tell them they're being on don't rub it in their face
And they think they that the world is theirs
Also that you could play with in other words
You know toy soldiers you know some of the back in the days
You know the little plastic figurine toy soldiers right right I don't think that they might be offered as a collector's item
We're very rare now. I guess right
Common growing up no no they still sell those little plastic
You know just like three four poses toy soldiers in a couple of different colors, so you can have a pose
I mean remember the ones that came in a box like 50 or 100. They're real small
Plastic all right well what I'm saying they don't but you the second iteration of human
Made them so they don't mind being played with and I mean like when you get the little toy soldiers and play but some of
The children back, then they played real rough when they finished playing with the soldiers
They threw a bunch of turpentine and lit them on fire. Yeah, of course right and
This is what I mean. You know play with people don't mind being treated that way
So this is the iteration that you have right now
Now the question is maybe you're a leftover if you here's the thing for sure
If you're interested in Greek speak you probably got some of the genes of the other ones
And that we're not into this kind of stuff. You know they're not just made from the three four poses, and they're just perfect
It's getting pretty
Pretty sick here because it's all gonna be wrapped up pretty soon pretty soon within the big scale so
Yeah, anything else. We're gonna make this a short one in
No, I think I think we've covered everything pretty well
You know I actually don't have too many other we covered the alien
Proclamations not too long ago unless you had something you wanted to add to what a joke yeah
No, but you did mention the reverse technology thing there a little bit ago in the black area, and I said to myself
Well, you know it's not that hard to make stuff that the these idiots can't figure out when I say idiots meaning
They're best engineers right of course
I mean you know because again
They're just not even including everything in the equation that could possibly be there to begin with so it's a you know
And and it's evident in the computers that they put the stuff into to do the work the short
Yeah, well when I saw what I put together in a computer, and it says basically it's not doing anything
It doesn't show any of the effects. I was both happy and sad
I was happy because all these idiots are never gonna figure it out. Even if they try to copy it
Because they're already
What do you call it when you psych someone out psychologically before?
Someone has to perform physically, but they get really bad news before they have to perform. They can't perform now
You know what I mean. No you psych them out exactly
They're so psyched out, and they're never gonna, but the sad part is that they're not gonna figure it out
You know in other words, so yeah, it's both the same thing makes it make can make one happy and sad
Well, yeah, because on the one hand look you do have a window into something that is rarefied and is
Interesting and is something that can you know actually accomplish something and at the same time you see that
It's just even though it's so obvious and should be there within an arm's length grasp to anyone
I mean because let's be honest again even though you're a more intelligent guy than most
The fact is that there's a whole lot of things right in front of people's faces that they could just reach out and grasp
if they bothered to open their eyes and
They don't
They just don't that's why I tell her to close her eyes
Anyway, that was a bad lascivious joke
But anyway, okay, so we'll leave it at that and maybe in the near future
I'll play around with the idea and ask you a couple of questions about what it is
We might do regarding a t-shirt or something. Oh, yeah, I think that's better visual show me
in the chat
By the way, I just there's a everything is going AI right they're gonna replace the search engines with AI
Yeah, so you won't be able to you won't have any choices pretty much
But there's a lot of most of the graphics design
online now is AI and they'll generate memory you went online or got a program like Photoshop to
Put a logo together and you you have a sidebar with all your tools and you start fitting and putting well now you just tell
Basic certain parameters type in and it'll give you a hundred different logos to choose from if you don't like them
Sure, we'll change this for you get another 200 logos pop up, right?
Well, that's why I don't want to do it. I don't want to go to the I want to go to
Where you could this is where you should?
Okay
No, hey, where did we go there what happened?
It's been a while, it's it's it's all right, by the way sex is if you want to have children
Otherwise you stay away from him. Hey, listen, I got you and look if it's been a while for you
That's fine. That might explain some things. But anyway, it's okay
So that explains it anyway 51 I'm done with it I've done that already and yeah, okay, so
We'll just leave it at that
I