77, and we're going to take a look at what's going on in the chat room, I guess, here on
Rated Y.
Didn't get any other feedback this week in the email, but, you know, if you heard the
last one, you got the email addresses, so I refer you back to that one.
Anyway, Greg, how are you doing tonight?
Doing well.
Well, you know, this is a hand-free operation for me, so I'm actually making some rolls
right now as we speak.
I'm going to continue with what I was doing.
Yeah, sushi rolls.
Ah, yeah.
I was going to ask you to clarify for, you know, those listening, because you say rolls,
they might think it's bread, right?
Goes all kinds of ways.
I've seen women take their shirt off and I see rolls.
Yeah, that happens too.
Anyway, yeah.
So, yeah, let's do it.
I might take a little smoke break.
Yeah, in the chat, I've been bringing up Jason Breshears of Archaics a lot lately, and I'm
very grateful that he's doing and does what he does.
And just to jump to the point, any criticism on him would have to be considered that his
own statement, right, let me just say, when you listen to Greek speak, it's Greek speak,
it's stuff that nobody that's born here knows, but people visiting here, right?
No one's paying attention, right?
Okay.
His whole thing, his statement is that he is a chronologist.
So once he, he is very apologetic or not apologetic when he broaches other topics, he'll be very
careful to say, I'm not expert on this, but he does get into them in great depth, right?
So my criticism on that would be just that.
So as a chronologist, I wouldn't say he's impeccable, but very, very good.
I think that the greatest thing that I've ever gotten from listening to his stuff is
the 138 cycle of the Phoenix, which he kind of uncovered many, many ways how it's in code
all around us anyway.
And there's other two other bodies, you know, there's the Nemesis X and the other one, and
they all have different periodicities, you know, like a 138 years, 592 and 700 something,
right?
762 or 732.
And that I'm grateful for because it does line up with a lot of the disasters and calendrics
that we have.
He's brought up a lot of calendrics.
I really didn't, I've never seen anyone break down the Mayan Papu Vuh, the Mayan calendar
and the Bactans as simply as he's done.
There was a guy, Jose something who was pushing the Mayan calendar for a long time, even went
and spoke at the U.N.
Contreras.
I don't know what his, I forgot his name, but his associate used to come over to my
house for dinner, a white guy, and always talk about the effects of the Mayan calendar.
I asked him to explain it to me.
And he's the guy working with the world renowned expert of the Mayan calendar, and he couldn't
explain it to me as clearly as Breshears does in 15 minutes on one of his sonics, right?
One of his shows.
So, so hats off to that, right?
It's really good.
And maybe I'm not the smartest tool in the shed.
Maybe I couldn't understand it.
But the way he's able to explain certain things simply is very good.
A lot of the stuff I know from the folks listening to Greek speak will be in total contention
when they listen to Breshears talk about what's called the Bible and scriptures.
And if you don't know what I'm talking about, basically, he's taking a stance that is almost
strictly Gnostic, where Yahweh is the Demiurge and referred to as Satan, right?
And all this other stuff.
And also regarding that aspect, he doesn't care or doesn't know about there is no crucifixion.
He doesn't care and doesn't know that there's no burning bush.
He uses that analogy often, right?
Right.
So downright blasphemous, right?
From that point of view, right?
From the point of view like that, people that are like, if you're from the Bible Belt or
the belt buckle of the Bible Belt, you wouldn't be able to listen to him.
I listen to everything.
I don't listen to everything, his stuff, but I listen to everyone, you know, a little bit
just to get a flavor and see where their direction is.
So I don't need to clarify my position on the Bible.
I told, you know, I don't believe any of it, but I need something.
Right.
Well, I know what I know out of it.
OK, when I say believe, you know what I mean, right?
It means that you don't know.
So you have to believe.
Right.
I only believe in what I know out of the scripture.
So you know, I don't use it as a religious document.
Right.
It's not my faith.
It's not my religion.
It's my law book.
That was the word I was looking for, faith, because that's that's what usually people
say.
Well, that's your faith.
Right.
So, you know, that's that's usually the key.
Totally different.
Yeah.
That's that.
That could go different places.
The only time I have any kind of faith in what's called the Bible, which is in prophecy
and the true identity of the Messiah.
Right.
There's that, you know, because I'm not I wasn't there.
The only time you have to have faith is based on testimony.
Right.
So on that respect, I do.
But in terms of building a faith or no, no, I don't.
So, OK, yeah, I'm not I have no religion.
Right. Right. So but it's my right.
It's my basis. It's my law book.
Right. And all that. So and I go there first, you know, whatever.
Right. My covenant, the covenant that I live by.
Right. So it's simple.
Right. OK.
On that part, it's very contentious with the archaic stuff.
So where would I start off by saying anything?
Well, first of all, he's a chronologist and it is very abbreviated on his chronology.
In other words, he does a chronology book, chrono something.
There's someone that read all of it.
And there's a YouTube with 200 something videos.
There is a lot more stuff in between some of those dates that he brings up in 1938
that were also very significant.
But again, the purpose of that, I think, is to muster up that hundred thirty eight
cycle year cycle, which the last time was 1902 and the next would be 2040.
And there's a lot of eschatology on the eschatology.
Part that I'm still the jury's out, you know, because I've been saying, you know,
twenty twenty five, twenty thirty two.
But he's saying it starts at twenty forty and all these other things.
Right. So we'll see.
It's so close enough. Right. We don't have a lot of time left.
Right. Well, relatively speaking, I mean, if you're talking about a difference of two
years, it's really not a big difference.
I mean, well, almost eight years or more, almost 15 years in some cases with other
things. So I'm not sure I just do the best I can with the chronology that I can get
out of the Bible itself.
He's gone outside, which I think is has a lot of validity because of the repetitive
cycles. And also the you've heard me say that the Bible is not inherently pure.
You know, it's very corrupted.
Right. Right. But in order for it to pass as being something holy or writ, it has to
have enough of that in it.
Right. Like, you know, like every lie has to have enough truth to make it believe.
Rat poison is 98 percent pure starch and two percent, maybe less than two percent poison.
Right. Right. Right. So anything corrupted, you know, doesn't mean that, you know, the
all the content of the ingredients are not edible.
Right. Unless it's mixed in severely.
So and I've also gone on record many times.
Don't even bother with the New Testament unless you've mastered the one before.
Right. Don't even bother with it at all.
You're just going to be you're going to get wrapped around the axle.
What do I mean about wrapped around the axle?
You know, when you're young, riding a bike and you have your pro kids, the old sneakers
with the extra long laces you get on your bike.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Right.
Yeah. OK. Yeah.
That's what will happen every time with everyone.
If you just believe in any religion, that's going to tell you just read the New Testament
and that you're done. You're finished.
You're a hopeless case.
Move over to the side.
You got nothing to say.
You know, you've got swallowed up by the collective and you're done.
Yeah. That's how I used to lose the bottoms of some of my pants, because they would be
ragged hanging. They'd get caught on a crank and that was the end of it.
They would just get wrapped around and gone.
Yeah, that's exactly the moment you believe that that's what you got to do.
Just the New Testament. You're finished.
So it's Greek speak is not a place for you, for sure.
So you got to start somewhere.
Right. And you start back to the basics now.
Right. He has a thing called the dark scriptures.
And he says, well, the academics say the Old Testament was written around the same time
as the New Testament. OK, that's all.
That's all he has to say about that.
Nothing else. Just the academics.
So we know how the academics.
Right. I mean, I'm sure they talk.
The academics talk about AIDS.
Right. And covid.
Right. So we've gone over that many times already.
Right. So it's not valid.
But there is no to besmirch or besmeet.
What was the man at all besmirch?
Because he states that he is basically a chronologist.
And on that, I find very little flaw.
And I'm actually grateful on that.
The rest of it, I take it more like the Fox News thing, like entertainment.
Remember, we talked about people taking Fox News seriously.
Then you launch a case against them, launch a case against them.
And what does the court say? Fox News is entertainment.
What's your problem? Right.
So very often in the beginning, I'd say a while back when I started finding out about
it, I was like this brochures of archaics.
Go listen to them. It's a Texas country.
It meets the Internet. Right.
So that's fine.
I've got nothing against them.
I am grateful that he's a good enough chronologist to show the 138 year periodicity.
And that's pretty much in a nutshell.
There are little things they throws out.
I like some of the terms that he uses, like dungeon programming or breaking pattern and
things like that. I've adopted some of that and try to give him credit when credit what
I can. And that stuff, you know, here's the thing.
And I just got off a call, someone who reached out to me, a sub that knows the same
people we know in New York.
And Michio Kushi, Shizuko Yamamoto, and basically we said, you know, so how am I doing
on the stuff? He's doing great.
You know, it's macrobotic, you know, the yin and yang, because he's a veteran.
He's 11 years older than I.
And he was around those people way before I was.
And basically the like Michio Kushi basically said, you do and you use what works
ultimately. Right.
If it works right, use it.
Right. In other words, if you form an opinion about something before you implement it and
you hold to that opinion instead of the virtues of what it has to offer, you're doing
yourself a disservice.
So if you have a sort of an opinion about something that is not venerated or high, but
that's something works, go ahead and use it.
Right. So so you can get it.
You can enjoy the features and benefits because others do.
Why not you instead of standing by and, you know, criticizing it?
Right. So it's like that with everything, including what we're talking about now with
our kids. You know, if there's anything you can take and use that you find useful, but
you have to objectify.
And even if it's subjective, look, everything ultimately is subjective because of our own
perception, perceptual limitations, but anything and anywhere you go, use it if you can
use it. I know ultimately we're asking why during this, you know, and that's what I
usually try to do. But in this case, I'm going to ask how, you know, how does one use
that chronological cycle?
How does one use recognition of these cycles?
How what would be the first step?
OK, now I recognize this.
I see that it is a psychic prophecy.
Prophecy. OK, I've gone over this many times with people are, you know, when Obama
came into office in the U.S., that there was a big survival Patriot movement.
Right. Well, that were up on everything, you know, people, people to this day, Greeks
still send me, you know, this stuff about Obama's the Antichrist, you know?
Yeah. Well, I know what the people.
Yeah. And one more thing, by the way, before we get into how to use it.
Go ahead. I don't know.
I you know, I've said I would never, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever to the 10th
power, open a YouTube channel and put content.
That's what the YouTube people of content.
Right. So, I mean, that's what Internet content.
Right. Contents may settle.
Right. Anyway.
I would never do that because that platform to me, which is Google, is just something
that rubs me the wrong way.
Now, something private that you and I and Sam discussed the arc on is maybe we should
do some shorts, Greek speak, blurbs, two or three minutes and put them out.
They haven't been done. Right.
Still not out there. Right.
And I don't. Yeah.
I just said something about.
Yeah. YouTube is just whatever.
Whatever. Anyway, it's more than a bad date for me.
Right. But a lot of people have benefited greatly on it.
Right. Including the archaic fellow that went from living in a wooden shack to buying
three houses and two new cars.
Right. With YouTube and whatever else.
So it's not for me, you know.
But let's go back.
Obama Patriot movement got survivalist.
Oh, because the world was going to end in 2020 or 2018.
Right. Remember? Remember, it's 2014, whatever.
Yeah. World's going to go.
I'm like, no, it can't, because I know prophecy.
There's a certain amount of things that have to happen.
Right. And I think I've been a far more correct.
And yeah.
So if they're telling you the world's going to end in 2019, what was when did they say
September 2019?
Remember, September 23rd, 2019 was a big one.
Or was it 18 or 17?
You know what? I'm mixing that one up.
I think it was 2019.
But the first big thing, of course, was the Mayan calendar, which you started with
here. That guy, Jose, began with an A.
I can't remember his name.
Yeah. His associate used to come over here and have dinner at the house all the
time. And when he invited me to his place, by the way, I showed up with my
pots, pans, some rice and my knives.
And I said, what are you guys having for dinner?
He's like salmon burgers frozen from Trader Joe's.
I'm like, oh, no, no, I'm cooking.
I'm going to make a nice meal for everybody.
First time he had a nice meal in years, probably.
But anyway. Right, right.
Yeah. Well, the main thing about the Mayan calendar is it's 360 days versus 365.
In the 50s, when they did the Mayan bactons with 365, it was 2012.
The math was correct, just the year number.
But in 713 B.C., we went from 360 days to 365 days a year and a quarter.
Right. So if you factor in the Mayan calendars based on 360 days, it ends up being
May 2040.
So it's pretty accurate. Elected 2046.
Sorry. 2046 is when time will end.
Right. OK, so that seems to be cleared up
pretty well on that.
But no, not much.
What I found using the prophetic stuff, which might be right, might be wrong.
Right now, I'm looking at more of the archaic stuff, see if I could piece it together.
What I've cobbled together and the jury's out.
I'll do a presentation on it if I find out which way or what.
But I find 2025 to 2027 to being critical in terms of everything flipping.
Right. You know, so.
Yeah, so that's where I'm at with that now.
And what I like, one of the comments in the chat was, because would you please talk
about archaics? And, you know, it's bringing in someone else, you know, someone else
here, just Greek speak, you know, Shelley and the Greek and all that, because we're all
here to learn. And it was like a little conditional thing, you know, and absolutely
you don't you don't even say we're all here to learn.
Absolutely. If there's anything, anyone out there at all worth listening to, listen
to them. Right.
Of course. And we'll always discuss it.
But just don't fall for like I won't mention names like Cliff High, people that sound
smart but are not smart.
Oh, what did I do? Did I just.
Oh, yeah. OK.
You might have. Yeah.
All right. Yeah.
Yeah. But stuff like that, like that's that's study that one and you'll see what I'm
talking about. There's nothing there.
It sounds like most professors.
Right. They sound smart.
But go have lunch with them.
You're like, this guy's a real dummy.
He's just learned how to speak by watching other people speaking.
Right. Don't fall for that.
Right. Don't fall for the.
There was a film the BBC did a while back, Brave New World.
It was a three hour film on the Aldous Huxley book, Brave New World.
Right. And one of the savages, you know, they called him that lived outside the
communities, had found a Shakespeare book.
And when he spoke, all he could say was recites the what he read out of the
Shakespeare book. Right.
Right. So.
Oh, no. And I find that, you know, people often refer to it as the monkey see monkey
do kind of thing. I find that all over the place, though, that you'll find sometimes
I call them parrots and all that's all they do.
And it doesn't even have to be good information.
They just find something to their liking and they mimic it.
And you can hear the shallow whatever, even in like all media
circles. Right. Which hardly exist anymore.
But to the extent that they do, you got people sitting there that are just repeating
buzz phrases from stuff they saw on YouTube.
I mean, you know, like the old PBS, you know, the petroleum broadcasting company.
I mean, the public broadcasting service.
Yeah. Yeah.
They sound, you know, right.
When you turn into PBS or whatever.
Oh, they sound so smart.
Right. Yeah. It's all real smart.
But all they're doing is, again, running the same.
Anyways, I find it's a style of speech, let's say.
But but someone who actually, you know, does some work and discovers something, of
course, take a listen, see what it is they discovered.
But there are a lot of parrots out there.
And I mean, I guess there's something to sit in and listen in the course as a parrot,
if that's what you want to do.
You know, Papagayo in Latin, we call it Papagayo.
Well, it could be that.
But she's a parrot.
Yes, exactly.
It could be that. And but the thing is, it doesn't get you anywhere.
You can do it if you're entertained by it.
But no, no, no, no. It does get you.
Oh, are you kidding? Are you kidding me?
Entire communities, entire societies are based on that.
Well, fluff. No, right.
It's all no, no. So it's the cover.
It's the no, it does get you.
Are you kidding? Well, no, that kind of I'm not being contentious.
I'm just saying that it's not a certain way that triggers people
that you're smart or whatever.
You're going to get a lot of people.
You know, I see that.
And I see that there are people that look, if you learn how to behave a certain way
and you meet people's expectations, you'll be rewarded.
That's for sure.
But I don't find it rewarding.
You know, I was on YouTube also, but I never got these big rewards
because I didn't do the stuff that you're supposed to do.
You have to behave a certain way.
You have to back. Let's back up now with the YouTube thing.
I'm not here to disparage anyone on YouTube.
I use YouTube a lot. I call it YouTube University.
I told someone once I was doing some car work, go to YouTube University.
You'll find a video.
He kept looking YouTube University.
I couldn't find it. No, no, no.
I just YouTube. Just YouTube.
Because, you know, you see a lot of people, you know, if I have to change,
let's say a guidance module in, you know, in a Maytag washer.
You know, I'd rather watch a video right from 10 minutes. Right.
Look, exactly. Before I do it.
I've had glitches with software.
I've had computer issues.
I've had things and I've been able to clear it up.
My mixer, the first mixer I got, something broke on it.
I couldn't figure out what was wrong with it.
And I went on YouTube to see if somebody had a video on that mixer.
You know what? Took about 10 minutes and I knew I could diagnose the problem.
You got familiar. Yeah.
You know, it was just a great.
Here's the thing. Let me just clarify.
The thing that I disparage YouTube about is purely a personal problem,
meaning my problem with it.
I have a personal preference
that I find it problematic with my own persona.
Like if I had to sit down and say we're putting doing a YouTube video,
I am or whatever, I'm like.
Now, I have done interviews that I've been on there, of course.
O and G and all that we have gotten when we did the O and G back then.
You did put them up on YouTube and we got fantastic response.
You actually brought brought it further to a further wider audience, I should say.
Right. And people did find out about it and they were quite happy.
Most of the comments, if not all the comments were positive.
Not that they should be, but they were.
So, yeah, it was a success.
Yeah, I'm thinking the Freeman at some point.
No, no, definitely.
And I'm thinking at some point we should stick just and, you know,
a sonic up on YouTube somewhere just to have it there.
And well, yeah, in other words, I am not a YouTube country.
I decided a long time ago not to
to do that because there was just something.
Again, I'm not being dualistic because I do use it.
But it doesn't feel right to engage with it.
As you know, I got just something about it.
But by the way, I did.
Intuitively, it did prove correct with all the censorship that came about before.
Could you imagine doing a video up there
talking about how the aid scam really works and all this stuff?
Could you how long would that look?
That would not have made it, you know, they call it YouTube community guidelines.
What do they call it?
Oh, yeah, exactly.
No, we'd get hit with YouTube community guidelines possibly within the hour.
We'd be taking it. Right, right. Exactly.
And they were probably the I would probably alert a human.
Exactly. Yeah.
The I would flag it and then say, hey, get some human
intel behind this and find out this guy's dangerous,
you know, in terms of what we're trying to do here.
You know, medical disinformation, as they call it now.
Yeah, that's a new term.
As a matter of fact, yeah, you know, just about everything
medical is disinformation, right?
Well, we know that.
But that would be their terminology.
Yeah, we yeah, we know that they believe that it's not right.
There's a difference.
You see the choice of words.
There are very specific. Exactly.
So we know. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. So that's pretty much all I have to say.
I am taking into account the chronology
in terms of eschatology, meaning the things to come.
And that's still out.
And when I do feel like I can do a presentation on it
and whatever, I will do a presentation on it.
You know what the archaic material and other material is.
By the way, there's no other material other than archaics and Greek speaks stuff.
There's nothing else out there.
Well, if you start bringing up any eschatology, guess what?
You end up with a Judeo Christian website, which is if you go there, you're lost.
Yeah, because even if they begin to hint at anything outside of it,
eventually it'll get back to, OK, you know what?
I'll tell you what it earns you on on YouTube.
University is unless you're paying the premium,
you'll start getting commercials for churches.
So, you know, either way.
No, I'm just saying the mentality.
I mean, anything religious in any any form, you know, is not good.
You know, you know, and you can see who falls for it.
But that's my point is that the artificial is geared to do what?
OK, it's geared to sell you products.
It's geared to engage with you in products that it knows
you want based on stuff you're doing.
So guess what?
The A.I. turns around and twists your commercial grabs to that.
So what I'm telling you is that the the the, you know, rudimentary thing
that is the A.I. that does feed your feed, right?
Well, by the way, it's not really A.I.
It's just very fast network, right?
Comparative, right?
You know, we we live in I think I brought this up even before
because we there is a cosmic A.I.
Right. And let me just bring this up because this is our case is for stands
for artificial intelligence X or something, right?
So the reason the logic that I came up that we are in an artificial
intelligence system, which will not let it like our cakes,
another artificial intelligence to to take hold is very simple.
If you are very advanced at whatever,
let's say to the point where you're advanced to doing everything.
Don't you build?
You know, one of them I spoke to years ago in the 80s, an anthropologist.
And so what makes anthropology so interesting is for him,
it was because you can watch the development of human society
and gauge it by the tools that they make.
And as the and the way society is considered advanced is by how advanced
not they are personally, but their tools. Right.
And that's why I was bringing it up, because I recently spoke with Blake
Lemoine, who is the A.I.
engineer that they fired from Google, if you remember the one that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. That's right. Yeah.
So, you know, and that's why I'm bringing it up, because it's
due to the feed.
What I'm saying is that the tool that they use is to attract you.
Once you start digging into these things that way,
they're going to immediately divert you into the standardized
Judeo-Christian religion that are available.
Oh, yeah, I get it.
Oh, yeah. Hold on. Hold on.
Hold up. Sure.
Let me just the thought is.
So if you're a quote, unquote, let me just get maybe make it a little couch
and a little more abbreviated.
If you're a god, you don't have to do anything.
You can make tools and other gods or other things to do it for you.
Right. Right.
Think about your super powerful.
Why do you go out and dig ditches?
You don't. You have a machine that does it.
And if the machine needs to be operated, you make another machine
to operate that machine, another machine to operate that machine.
And that includes biological machines, of course, meaning animals or people.
Right. So when you get to a certain point where you are
sort of not a demiurge, but basically everything comes out from your direction.
You like the captain of a ship.
You don't do any.
The captain of the ship doesn't do anything, even when,
you know, five degrees to starboard. Right.
Does he go and turn the rudder?
No, someone else does.
Look, I know you bring up Star Trek every once in a while,
but take a look at what the captain does on Star Trek.
He doesn't actually fly the ship.
No, he tells Sulu, take it out.
You know what I'm saying?
He tells it. Look, take it out of space, Doc.
OK, go. He gives them exact directions.
And that guy. So and that's just the captain of the ship.
Imagine someone much, much higher.
That's a captain of a planet or a solar system or a universe.
You would have even more elaborate machines.
As a matter of fact, your devices, machines, contraptions and creations
would be so elaborate that some would even mistake those as gods.
You see what I mean? Exactly.
So we are in an off course, you know, when creation and things are done,
they are not done directly or indirect.
It would be I cannot imagine that they would be done directly at all.
It doesn't make any sense that they would the gods, quote, unquote,
would do anything directly.
They would have things that they've made do it. Right.
So that's why I believe that the the artificial intelligence is us
mimicking that.
And of course, what they're putting out to the public, you tell people it's a I.
And it sort of acts like a I.
And, you know, it's not a I.
I think we have Megsy here.
She did some stuff with the chat, GBT, and they made fun of Christianity.
But when it comes time for Islam, so I can't make fun of anything religious.
So you can see, in other words, you know, the chat, GBT is a woke agenda.
One hundred percent. Right.
Yeah. Supposedly. Right.
Yeah. It's all woke, you know, which is goes back to hope.
You know, sizzling liquid there.
I hope you didn't come in too loud as loud here.
No, I'm OK. OK.
So, yeah. In other words, it's all agendas you look.
You know how I say, if if you've ever heard of someone's name, seen their picture,
their face, even historically, their voice or they're not in power, none of them.
You've never seen.
We don't know who's in power, because once you get to the point
where you do have a power, you one of the things you make sure
is that no one knows who you are, what you look like, what your name, blah, blah, blah.
That is the first priority. Right.
That's why. Because that's how you maintain it.
Exactly. So everybody I'm talking about, George Washington,
all the way, all the presidents, right, all the they're all
delegates, they take delegation. Right.
So, again, they think about it.
If there was an A.I., a real A.I. that humans did,
they would never let you know that there was no.
So it's it can't be A.I.
Right. Could not possibly be revealed.
But again, you know, it reminds me of that old phrase, right?
You'll know you'll know them by their works.
You'll know them by what it is they created,
not them directly, because that's not the way it goes. Right.
Yep.