The Sonic Event 2.2.2 Rated Y.
Anyway, how are you doing today, Greek?
Oh, I'm doing okay.
I just want to let people know, if
you're sending me messages and stuff and I
haven't responded yet, I will get to it.
I'm only one and a half people here.
So I will catch up to your messages.
I'm not one to get a lot, fortunately,
but I'm not really in the public like
other people are, you know, my subs or
anything like that.
But getting more emails than I usually do,
usually.
And most of them I've seen through the
subject is I want to be down for
the audio or sonic counter space webinar, which
is going to be a shorty.
But, you know, yeah, you'll get you'll if
you found out about it from me speaking
here, you'll find about when it is, maybe
we'll do it in a couple of weeks.
It's gonna be a real short one.
And this is because it could be so
short.
I mean, it's really a false back inside
of a container, or an enclosure, whether it's
a room, or a speaker box, or an
audio, you know, a dashboard or whatever.
It's a very small, thin module, it's mimics
the back of the wall or enclosure in
a certain way, it's couldn't be any simpler.
And don't try to wrap your mind around
what how it works.
But once until you build one and employ
it, and then you're going to be Holy
crap, I can't believe the sonic difference.
This little thing does all that.
Wow, you know, we're really onto something now.
Nice.
Well, other thing I want to get into,
which I've been holding back for a few
years, I've been just to inject this out.
And you don't have to give feedback.
But in the future, if fine, if you're
interested, I might be doing more of a
webinar, I should have done the cooking, but
I, I'm not going to do that.
It's it's too involved.
I don't want anyone to think that we
can do three, three hour talks about how
to become better cooking, and you will be
so so kind of investing some time on
my own.
I said, that's maybe too big, but something
like that.
But the other thing is people have been
talking about free energy, not so much as
they did in the 1015 years ago.
Remember?
Right?
Yeah.
Well, for the past couple of years, I've
been sitting on something that let's just say
you put 40 watts in you get 800
watts out.
It's very easy to build.
It's mechanical.
Well, easy, right?
To who?
And what I'll do is I'll explain the
principle.
And what it involves, basically, is you're going
to be mimicking, do you remember those flashlights
that you shake?
It looks like, right, back and forth, and
they charge?
Yeah.
Okay, it's just like that, except the device
is motionless, you don't have to move anything.
Except for perpendicular to it, you have a
small rotor that rotates.
In essence, the I'll give the beans out
right here.
You go to like an industrial catalog, and
you find out, look up for your house,
which 10 kW 10,000 watt generator usually
can do your average house, your average house,
you know, like the ticky tacky houses you
see in the row.
Right?
Nothing too special means you could still use
a clothes iron and whatever, you know, like
a lot of people live off the grid,
they can't use dishwashers and irons, it shuts
down their whole system, right?
Or blow dryers, you can still use a
blow 10 kW.
So you look up what a 10 kW
generator requires, like the armature, the stator, the
windings, how much material, how much does the
thing weigh, right, you'll see 140 pounds, okay,
you need 140 pounds worth of material.
Right?
And it basically works on the principle of
the scalarator.
And when you see how it works, you're
going to get pissed because you're gonna wish
you figured it out yourself.
And you realize this is a planet of
idiots.
And no other people haven't figured out how
simple it is to take to increase your
input.
Because right now, the input is how efficient
like, oh, this is really good.
80% efficient, that means you're only wasting
20%, right?
So right, well, this thing is eight is
over 800 900.
Actually, I think it's 2400% efficient, something
like that.
Because you put in 40 watts and you
get 800 out.
So if you if it was 200%
efficient, you put if it was 100%
efficient, you put 40 watts and you get
40 watts out, right?
200% efficient, you put 40 watts in
80, you get 80, and so on.
And so you do the math.
So yeah, so it's 10 times 200.
Right?
2000% efficient.
And it's gonna, it's on the it's the
principle of scalar, it looks nothing like the
scalarator.
It's the principle.
And the thing that's winding, basically get the
thing that gets the generator moving is a
little light bulb battery, or one of those
little cell phone, solar panels that is just
designed to cell phone, you've seen those old
portable solar panels.
Yeah, you got some sort of interference happening,
you're probably stepping near something.
But I am I'm walking around.
So anyway, that I wasn't gonna I've been
holding on to this for quite a few
years, like two years, it feels like I've
been holding on to it for 10 years.
And I've been giving hints and private calls
and no one's biting and I'll do a
thing on how to build in how it
works and all that.
And now people say, I just want to
just finish off this thought.
Oh, that's free electricity.
Don't be an ass.
You already not only do use everyone have
free electricity, but you're actually getting paid to
use it.
How do I know that?
Are you getting a bill at the end
of the month?
That's a payment made to you.
But according to the contract, you gave it
up to them, you said that you're going
to pay all the electric companies bills.
And what I mean by that is if
the electric company board of directors wants to
go to Vegas, Vegas, Vegas and have a
core cocaine and prostitute party for the whole
week at $10,000 a night hotels, you're
going to pay for it, you agree to
it in your contract.
Right?
So you do have free electricity and you're
getting paid to use it.
But right now they've got you in a
position where if you don't pay them twice,
they're going to shut it off.
So you got bigger problems than getting free
energy, free electricity.
You see what I mean?
This, this device has nothing to do with
having free power for your house.
It has to do with putting power in
a remote location.
You get it?
Okay.
If you put, if you put a generator
in a remote location, they need some kind
of fuel, doesn't it?
Yeah.
Generally.
Or you could put it, but remember there's
no motion to it.
So it's really quiet.
You know what generators, you always know there's
a generator in the area, right?
What they call electrical generator.
This thing makes the noise of a little,
uh, one of those Walmart rechargeable fans that
you get that are totally silent.
You hold it up against your neck to
cool you down.
So you're telling me this thing will make
less noise than your central air or whatever
in your place.
It makes about the same noise as a
laptop fan does.
Oh, wow.
That's like nothing.
Yeah.
Okay.
No, no, no.
If we were saying this and proving what
we're saying now, which we can, uh, 20
years ago, you know, get us killed, right?
We go missing, right?
Generally.
Yeah.
That's usually what was the legend.
I always heard.
Yeah, for sure.
Yeah.
So I just wanted to bring these things
up, uh, because there's a lot going on
in my world and my world is your
world and your world is my world or
whatever.
I think you guys, I can share it.
Right.
So should be able to.
So one thing at a time, what do
you got, what do you got for tonight?
Yeah, sure.
No problem.
No, in no particular order.
I'll just pull them up.
Uh, here's a weird one.
If you could spend a day with a
biblical character, who would it be?
If any, that's a good question.
The question is, uh, yeah, we'll get once
you get, here's the thing about that.
I'll tell you whenever someone I've asked that
question before, uh, when you have a King
James, uh, it's been asked.
Yeah.
If you, um, look at the King James,
the English Bibles, it has these very American
Franco American names like John Peter, you know,
Isaiah, right.
Uh, David, right.
All this stuff.
Yes.
Uh, what's interesting to add a little more
knickknack to the party.
When you find out what their real names
were in the language, remember names are exempt
from language, right?
So if your name is, uh, whatever, whatever,
and in, uh, Czechoslovakian, no matter where you
go, your name doesn't change according to the
translation.
Your name is not translated, right?
They're they're exempt from translation.
Well, it would be, I'll tell you who
it would be.
Yes.
Okay.
Well, that's interesting again, because I was just
going to say, look in different languages, they
tell you there's a different interpretation of a
name sometimes.
And like when I hear Yesha, I think
to myself, that's Joshua, which is, you know,
except there's no J in the language that
that originated in.
Yeah, that's right.
So you would have a phonetic equivalent, right?
A phonetic equivalent.
I mean, uh, look, okay.
So my first name, Charles, fine.
Uh, but you might find Carlos.
You might find, uh, it should be, but
here, the proper thing, it would be Charles.
They wouldn't change it.
That would be the proper thing, but sometimes,
but if they change it, it's a nickname
just like, remember, there you go.
Well, that's, I was just going to say,
that's why I'm called Chuck.
But yeah.
Okay.
Fair enough.
A nickname, but that's the weird thing.
But then there's the legal name.
And then there's your name, which is different.
Yes, absolutely.
Okay.
Good.
I just wanted to hit that point.
Thank you.
Um, I would be, I would say that
that's who it would be because you have
to be pretty, pretty cool to walk around
with your head shaved and all the hair
shaved off for two years.
Yeah, that's, that's something.
I mean, you know, that's like that movie
powder.
Anyway.
Yeah, I'm out of shit.
I feel like doing that right now.
It doesn't, it's not that bad when you
shave off the hair, I guess.
Uh, anyhow, speaking of possession, uh, cause we
did talk about possession on a recent, uh,
Sonic, uh, what happens to people when they
have a so-called alcoholic blackout, they still
walk around, speak with people, maybe get into
a fight or do whatever stupid things, but
they don't remember anything the next day.
Is there a spiritual component there and possession,
or is it just simply intoxication by alcohol?
I am asking because not all the people
who get wasted experience of blackout.
Like for instance, I've been able to black
out, but I get no hangover now.
Uh, but blackouts are real super rare for
me.
And then again, there's other people that have
like, you know, they touch alcohol, they blackout,
they don't remember anything.
And sometimes I think they're making it up
and it's just an excuse, but go ahead.
Okay.
So that was your interjection.
That wasn't the whole question, right?
No, not at all.
I gave you the rest of the whole
question.
You know, he didn't pause enough there and
I didn't get enough air in between, but
I get it.
Okay.
So the general thing is that, well, I,
okay, let's just go back to the beginning
of the question, blacking out.
That's no different than someone waking up in
the hospital because they went through the windshield.
What I'm trying to say about that in
the spiritual world is they always tend to
look for people that are incapacitated somehow.
Uh, I know this, um, from observation and
accounts that when people are ill, uh, uh,
unstable mentally, you know, their mind is unstable
or they've been through physical trauma.
They're more apt, uh, to be, uh, oppressed,
influenced and possessed.
That's why a lot of people that have
severe drug addictions that were the point where
they, it, what would you call it?
Causes them physical and mental trauma.
They are more apt to being possessed because
they will almost always go into someone that
is disabled.
Okay.
Well, that makes sense.
Yeah.
Somebody who suffers trauma usually is more susceptible
to outside influence, all that kind of stuff.
Look, typical thing, right?
When people go, Oh, now I'm getting psychic
understandings after I got a head trauma, I
got hit by something.
I got these entities influence you directly.
That's because you're changing.
We we've been over this before once.
And then they, they, they fool you.
They hit you.
It's true.
I mean, you get to the point where
the cops want to talk to you to
find a missing body.
That's a bonafide, you know, what do you
call them?
Clairvoyant.
Right.
Uh, that's because they're doing it with you
because they don't want you to start figuring
out things.
They'd rather distract you with that.
I'm not saying it's a bad thing, uh,
but you know, just, just keep things in
perspective.
Well, it's like most things, it's not a
good or a bad thing.
You just have to know how to use
it.
Yeah.
Who's worse.
They're bank robbers or the cops that catch
the bank robbers.
You know, I mean, they're both, uh, both
as illegal.
They're both the police or everything.
The police do is just as illegal as
what the bank robbers are doing.
So everyone's going to applaud the police, right?
Mostly.
Yeah.
Except in the time, but they're both equal.
So, well, that's why I see no problem
with people celebrating people like John Dillinger when
he was robbing banks.
Cause it was kind of like, eh, why
not?
You know, he was so good at it
that he, he was supposedly shot here in
Tucson, but they shot some poor bastard in
the theater and said it was Dillinger.
Dillinger got away.
It was actually, it was, uh, well, just
like you've heard, uh, Ralph Epperson stuff about,
uh, the guy who shot Kennedy really became
a Senator, changed his name, right?
Well, there was that.
And there was also, uh, he had the
thing about the guy who shot, uh, Lincoln
actually.
Right.
Why?
I'm sorry.
Did I say Kennedy?
Lincoln.
Right.
Yeah.
Uh, booth.
And the guy who shot Kennedy, we don't
know who that is, but we have an
idea what, what fraternity they might've been in
most likely.
Right.
Okay.
I, I wasn't going to correct you on
the Kennedy thing, but yeah, I remember the
whole, there is a meme about Lincoln and
Kennedy back and forth.
Anyway, maybe that's where I got it.
Oh yeah.
Cause it's all backwards.
Uh, you know, a secretary named Kennedy and
Kennedy has a secretary named Lincoln.
Yeah.
That's so it's, it's interesting how that just
happened without even thinking about it.
You see?
Yes.
So, so anyway, uh, rolling the dice, when
you tell a normie about things outside of
their box, sometimes one will turn into an
agent Smith and really try to screw you
over.
Uh, that was something that they had to
say, because we're talking about, you know, trying
to talk to somebody normal, normal once in
a while.
And you talked about going out in public.
So that's where that came from.
Uh, what are your thoughts on that though?
I mean, they really try to screw you
over.
Is that just part of the game you
figure?
Or is that, yeah, it definitely, well, the
matrix is a, is a good movie on
many, many points, right?
Many aspects for a reason, you know, whether,
even if the normies say it, but a
real normie, by the way, like an NPC
won't see any value in the metaphors of
the matrix.
Do you ever notice that?
Yeah.
They just think it's an action movie.
So, uh, yeah, they try to screw with
you, but, uh, but don't try to screw
back because they can get pretty nasty.
They usually are.
We're talking about the majority of the people.
And unfortunately that majority is your family members
first.
Well, the important thing that everybody skips, even
when they're trying to over psychoanalyze everything else
is, you know, they tell them at a
certain point, Hey, look, don't forget all these
people you see, they are part of the
matrix now.
Yeah.
They're innocent people, but they're also part of
the matrix.
So maybe they're not innocent people.
So that's how you have to handle them.
Well, you see the lady in the red
dress look again, right?
And then she turns right.
Exactly.
But it's also part of your growing member.
This is not a real reality.
Um, I tested, I tested often.
Uh, but, but it's, it's a joke that
writes its own punchline.
Uh, when you test it, right.
So it's kind of like backfiring, but it's
not, it's not, it's not backfiring.
It's more like blowback.
That's the term.
The intelligence uses that blowback, like, you know,
cleaning something up, right?
Like when you botched something and you got
blowback and then you got to cover the
blowback and you got to cover the event
and all that problems coming back at you
for something you did, which is just normal.
That's just what happens.
Yeah.
And if here's the thing, if you deal
with a normie and they want to screw
with you back, what happened is it's a
good, it's a bad thing.
Cause they want to screw with you.
You don't want any malevolent energy, more malevolent
energy.
It's all malevolent here anyway.
Um, but what it actually means that you
slipped through the cracks because usually the system
prevents you from getting through to a normie
where they want to screw with you.
Right.
It usually separates, you create some kind of
distraction or a barrier where they just are
completely censored.
And they're like, when you're speaking that all
they hear is the Charlie Brown teacher voice.
Right.
Um, so, so somehow you got through to
them.
That's good in a way.
And also if they screw with you, you're
going to survive.
And even if you don't, it's still fine.
Um, that means that the system is getting,
the matrix is getting weaker.
Uh, right.
So, because typically talking to a normie, they
would just think you're crazy and brush you
off.
But if they want to screw with you,
there's a lot more going on than the
normal interaction with a normie.
Cause standard reaction is you're just an idiot.
Shut up.
It's like calling a call and show with
Hannity.
You're a loose nut or whatever, whatever he
says.
Exactly.
So look, there's a long commentary here about,
uh, you know, the grandmother and they used
to do something about the eating.
You talked about, you know, uh, when it's
proper to eat certain things.
And what she says here is that it
seemed to work in reverse for her grandmother,
which causes another question to emerge.
And this is due to a conversation.
Everything is not one size fits all.
Is it possible that the exact opposite would
work with certain people compared to the way
you laid it out as far as when
to eat heavier, when to eat lighter and
when to transition, uh, yeah, but yeah, good.
No, you have to take into account the
constitution and condition of whoever is going to
be doing this, right?
Like, uh, an extreme example would be the,
the infant, the infirm and the elderly.
They typically, when you have an infant, someone
who's infirm or the elderly, they, you have
to make adjustments in that, in the family
for them.
Right.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
Even no matter where the moon is or
what the season is.
So you have to look at that.
Also, if it's the complete opposite, uh, it's
not, if you really have, um, the universal
principles are absolutes by the way, and you're
constantly being told there are no absolutes.
Yes, they are.
They are absolutes within the construct that we
live in within this, whatever reality we call,
we call reality universal principles are absolutes.
Just like when you're doing a math problem,
the numbers that you put in are absolutes.
In other words, they're going to work here.
They're going to work everywhere, right?
It's mathematics almost.
It isn't absolute.
So you're not diagnosing or assessing who gets
what, when, um, cause the principle is absolute,
right?
Okay.
I got it.
So they may change based on a condition,
but the principle is fine.
So in other words, it may be better
for one of those categories of types you
just brought up because they are the ones
that you definitely have to make an adjustment
for.
They're saying to do the opposite.
That doesn't tell me that you see these
things.
Unfortunately, it's kind of like when you give,
when you talk about real history, people are
used to hearing it like a half hour
sitcom.
You know, they talk about for 20 minutes,
they talk about how bad everything was and
how it got fixed in the last two
minutes, right?
This is people are used to, uh, to
do real history.
It takes four hours to do an introduction,
four hours about any, just a single event,
four hours to pretty much go down and
what happened in four hours and how it
was covered up.
It's never, it's never simple.
Um, so these things are not simple, you,
but the, but you could, because they are
absolute universal principles are absolute.
You could break it down to what we
call expansive contractive, you know, yin and yang,
you know, up, uh, upward is yang, which
takes right.
This energy and downward is yin, which this
energy, the opposite would go to, those are
the principles, right?
So once you start applying those, uh, for
example, if the opposite worked for your grandmother,
she's probably either tall or short than normal,
right?
You take that into account.
She's not quote unquote, normal height.
So what would affect people of, um, of,
uh, in your family positively might affect her
negatively because she's extra tall or extra short.
Now, the reason I bring this up, I
recently visited someone's family and it was like
a nine, 10 and 12 year old child
at the door.
You know how the heights are, right?
And then the grandma came in and she
was as tall as the children.
That's really bizarre looking by the way.
Uh, and, uh, she was like almost 80.
So, you know, it's not, you know, definitely
we could have even been the great grandma.
I'm like, wow.
Um, the, the, obviously she grew up in
a very young environment in the mountainous area
and they did their posh students from Afghanistan.
Oh, well, there you go.
Right.
So yeah.
I mean, they go out and open toe
sandals in the snow.
Right.
So yeah.
At, at 10,000 feet elevation, that's where
she was raised.
And the children were raised here and, you
know, gotten all the chemicals and they're way
bigger than they would have been.
That 12 year old girl would have been
the size of a, um, I mean the,
uh, the 12 year old girl in Afghanistan
would have been the size of the seven
year old here.
It's really small.
They're much smaller.
You ever noticed that yeah, certain people were
much smaller.
Remember, uh, if you've ever been to, um,
Charleston, Virginia or places where they still have
structures that were built in the 16 and
17 hundreds, you walk into the door and
you're like, why are the doors so short?
No, there's colonial parts of a Jersey that
still stand.
Like if you go to the Washington slept
here house, the original dimensions on stuff are
smaller.
They just were the preserved pieces of it
are smaller.
Yeah.
Cause they didn't have, um, they didn't have
all the chemicals in the environment, which are
what expansive.
Right.
And they're going to, they're going to really
get into the people that are young.
You're right.
They're going to really get into the people.
It's much like a marshmallow, right?
Because it's, it's still a lot of sugar.
But that sugar cube contains more sugar in
a smaller space.
It's just a giant marshmallow.
Yeah.
But the interesting thing about sugar though, it
will not really expand you.
It will actually deteriorate you because the sugar
being a natural chemical, let's say a refined
sugar, let's call it a chemical or corn,
corn syrup, refined sugar, or refined corn syrup,
or beat, whatever is all the same.
What happens is when it gets into the
body, that sugar wants to go and be
attached to starches and minerals and water, just
like it was when it was in the
sugar cane.
So you could pretty much see when you
have a refined food product, what it will,
how much it will deplete from your body
when you trace it back and see where
it was taken from.
So if it was taken from a sweetener
taken from a complex plant, it's going to
take more from your body than if it
was taken from, let's say a microbe or
a bacteria, which is very basic, it won't
take much to satisfy it.
Right.
You see my point?
So this is universal principle again.
And it always works.
That's, what's great about it.
So, and it's very rare that people start
hearing this kind of talk and, and get
it right from the very beginning.
It takes constant observation, practice and counsel and
discussion.
So my analogy wasn't, yeah, my analogy wasn't
about the content or the sugar.
My analogy was about how you take something
and you sort of blow it up bigger,
even though it's got less of what the
other thing has in it.
In other words, there can be a more
compact and efficient version of something as opposed
to the, something that's sort of just blown
up.
And a marshmallow is a great example because
that's basically like a sugar cube, blown up
a big old marshmallow.
And that's what people have become like big
marshmallows.
Yeah.
Mars, but actually marshmallow, believe it or not,
is, well, there's natural marshmallow is, I'm not
trying to be contrary.
It's actually a complex thing.
You ever see the ingredients in that?
Yeah.
But the, the old ones I'm talking about,
not the, you know.
Yeah.
I used to, we used to like, uh,
like when they used to catch fire, blow
them out right away with that carbon on
the outside or melted on the inside.
Never, never quite burned you caused any harm,
but it was a get tired of it.
I think white people have a thing called
s'mores or something.
I never had one of those.
So anyway, but yeah.
Yeah.
They take the hot marshmallow, they stick it
with, uh, you know, some Hershey bar or
something and a cracker and a cookie or
something.
Yeah.
I get it.
It lets you hold it.
Right.
Yeah.
But the universal prince, you got anything else
by the way?
No, the universal principles, that's why they call
them universal principles.
They work everywhere.
Uh, but the thing is, unless you, this
is my advice, unless you're actively discussing it
in groups or have a council or I'm
not going to study, I don't know where
you're going to go to study.
You're going to have to find a, an
old library because there's nothing online about it.
I mean, there is, there is stuff online,
but Oh my gosh, it's when people you're
not in the heyday of the internet.
Like what would you say the internet was
like between 2003 and 2013 for finding stuff.
Yep.
Yeah.
For using it.
So it's, uh, you know, I was speaking
with someone recently about, uh, they, they, they
knew Shizuko and Michio Kushi and all that.
I don't mean to be Jap, you know,
uh, Nipa, Nipa, Nipo centric.
Nippon is the proper name for Japanese.
Uh, where they used to call nips.
Right.
In world war two, um, the, uh, uh,
centric, but it is one, a good way
to start.
There's the Vita's the Vedas, uh, which is
a good place.
Also, if you can get through, no one's
really compiled them because the purpose of the
Vedas was to distract and destroy an entire
generation here when they brought it, the West,
the intelligence agencies forced it upon the movements
in the sixties and seventies, right.
It was to make people crazy.
So, but anyway, if you can get to
the core of stuff, I know someone that
was familiar with the same people that I
learned it from.
And I said, can you really do it?
And can you teach it?
Because the reason I'm asking you is maybe
we should get together and do like a
couple of short once a month groups where
people can come and discuss, you know, quote
unquote macro macrobiotic principles or Taoist principles, universal
principles, because you can't go online and find
much, you know, you go online and tell
you, well, this is a list of yin
things and this is a list of yang
things.
So what?
Right.
I mean, it's like going to military and
these are the lists of the weapons that
we have.
And this is a list of the weapons
the enemy has.
So what, how do you use it?
This is what we have in the grocery
store.
Okay.
Yeah.
It's amazing.
It's like, just because you go grocery shopping
doesn't mean you could cook the stuff when
you get home.
Right.
That too.
And the only way to do it is
with direction and people sharing experiences because you,
then you'll learn how to combine things, combine
your point of views, your observations, and being
objective.
To give you an example, like one thing
with the water device.
Now, what we're doing is I have, yeah,
I'm going to say at a university greenhouse
type situation, agriculture and another university that does
hydrodynamics and what, and approaching them and saying,
I want you guys to check this device
out and just tell us what it does.
We, because we can't really say what it
does because we invented it.
But when I say we, the corporate me,
uh, we invented it and have been observing
it and real happy with it.
So I can no longer be objective.
I can only be subjective.
It's kind of like a chick started laughing
when I talk.
It's like, like when you have a child
or a kid, um, and someone asks you,
tell me about your child or your kid.
You're going to say they're great.
They're smart.
They're good looking.
They're intelligent.
Right?
But if you drop them off with someone
who's never seen them before, they're going to
give you a much more objective reassessment of
your child or kid than you would, because
every parent tends to think their children are
good looking, smart and whatever.
Right?
So you see the point?
So if I don't tell you anything about
it, just drop it off and you tell
me, and then I can have a more
intentional.