Welcome to Sonic Event number 2 of Ocelli and the Greek Rated Y.
Obviously I'm Ocelli and the Greek is with me today and we are going to discuss quite
a few things, I think.
We're going to have to start with a little bit of a review, I guess, from Sonic Event
number 1, where the introduction, I suppose we could say, to the concept of the soul,
the spirit, and, well, let's see, the soul, the spirit, and the body, right?
That would be the three things that we were discussing when we closed out last time, Greek,
is that right?
Sure, and these three things are towing, have a multiple of other things in tow, let's say,
and we're going to be a little forthright about certain of the things because telling people
how things are makes some people kind of standoffish, but if you give them hints, they don't get
the hint.
So, there's somewhere in the middle between hitting someone over the head with it and
being very indirect about it, there's something in the middle that gets to people.
Very often I brought up, I had discussions with people I've known for years and they
come to me with some situation and I said, well, do you remember we talked about this
and that?
Did you try that?
And they're like, yeah, I do remember that.
But no, I didn't try that.
And I'm like, well, if you don't try it, what can you report?
So you have to have a workable knowledge, I guess I would call it.
Wouldn't you say that's workable knowledge, right?
Workable knowledge, well, what can you use is usually the big thing, right?
Because after all, look, I could explain to you how to travel in a rocket, okay, let's
say, theoretically, I can't, but let's say I could.
You know, how to travel in a rocket to Mars, but if you don't have the things around you
to work with to get there, I mean, it's kind of pointless.
It's a theoretical exercise.
Sure.
Well, the irony there is the people that say they've been in rockets and left the atmosphere
or whatever, still can't explain it.
That's the irony of it.
So even though they've, anyway, that's another story, right?
Well, yeah, we could talk about Captain Kirk and, you know, going up in the-
That's a little better.
Now you're talking.
That's a lot more fun anyway.
But all right, anyhow, it's a practical knowledge because, look, this is something anybody could
access because anyone, I assume, that is hearing what we're saying has access to a spirit,
a soul, and a body, because otherwise, you know, well, maybe, okay, go ahead.
No, of some quality and, you know, forgive me, I might be going on for a while on some
of these concepts, so don't fall asleep on me, you know, because some of these concepts
are, like I said, these three things, the spirit, which is the mind, what makes you
you, the soul, the metabolism, which is the breathing and all the bodily functions, the
energetic functions, the animating functions of the body, and then there's the body, the
actual shell itself.
They have a lot of various things in tow, meaning you cannot talk about one without
bringing up these other aspects and also how they all work together.
You see, essentially, what I'm trying to say is we're in an environmental suit that has
a, basically, we are the spirit, and the environmental suit is the body, and the status of that environmental
suit is the soul, the metabolism.
I like using the word metabolism, because people already use that word when they get
into, let's say, discussions about how they feel or how things work biologically.
So, it's interesting, though, because the use of the word metabolism up to this point,
I guess you sort of have to reset that, because generally, I would lead to the idea this is
how you metabolize things, and this is how you, now, here we go.
Well, actually, if you actually look up the name on how it's being used and what it really
means, it's slightly different, but I like to use it because it kind of connotates that
you're going to be talking, it's slightly technical and a little more in depth, you
know?
Well, right, but the generally accepted concept, right, you metabolize things, convention says,
you metabolize by absorbing, and there you go, there's a problem there, so could you
maybe give us, I know we've discussed it before, but how about we go back over that, because
I think it's important.
Yeah, well, here's the thing, like I said, I might run with this a little bit.
We kind of try to drive home the distinctions, but if you're in an environmental suit, you
look at sci-fi, you know, they look at their wrist and they have the little screen that
tells them the status of that environmental suit, you know, whether they're low on oxygen
or whatever, you know, in sci-fi, you've seen it all the time, they've got the visor
on and all this, that, and the other, essentially, we are in an environmental suit, and we would
be the mind, the spirit, who we are, it's very distinct, again, and I keep repeating
this, and the battery level of the suit is the soul, the breath, because even in sci-fi,
if you damage the guy's or the gal's suit, what happens to them, right?
They suffocate and die, so there's that aspect, and then there's the body itself, the carne,
the actual vehicle, which, you know, what's that movement called, transhumanism, where
they're going to get you with machine and all that, so mixed with machine, that's still,
believe it or not, I'm not for it, but that is still a viable body, so, right, and I've
talked about consciousness transfer, this is more on the, let's say, esoteric side, technology
to transfer consciousness has been around, and some of these things that I speak on,
that I borrow from science fiction, believe it or not, I don't want to come out and say
that they're not really science fiction, it's a form of disclosure, to give a quick example,
we mark things in time, and on the last Sonic, we talked about, when you're made aware of
a concept, whether it's social, technical, religious, whatever concept, imagine any subject,
it doesn't matter in cosmic theory or cosmic law, whether it's marked or categorized as
fact or fiction, did you get the concept, right, so, if, you know, let's say, remember a long
time ago, there was a B movie called Attack of the Killer Tomatoes, right, it doesn't
matter if it's fact or fiction, now you have this concept of killer tomatoes, right, so
this is what I mean about from the cosmic point of view, it's beyond, it's imagination and
all these other things put together that form reality anyway, ask any inventor, right, so
does that relate to the fact that often we see things imagined in science fiction and
literature well ahead of them actually existing in the 3D world, you know, like you brought
up the wrist, immediately my mind jumped to, yeah, at some point though, somebody created
like this Apple watch, right, where it now monitors, you know, these different things
that your body's doing supposedly and it tells you, now I know, I know I'm gonna say
a bad word here, but, yeah, I know, I know what you're gonna say, but say it, go ahead,
it's supposed to monitor your blood pressure and your heart rate and all these things, I'm
just telling you what it says, now it is doing something, but it is born of the concept that
was initially imagined, you know, and wasn't part of the reality as far as I know, when
they would show people looking at their wrist to find out what their status was, how much
oxygen they have, what their heart rate was doing, et cetera, and then we saw it incrementally
come into play, like maybe somebody saw the movie Apollo 13 supposedly based on real events,
right, where they were monitoring from a distance what the condition of the astronauts was,
these things came into existence, so to speak, over time, but at a certain point, everything
is actually imagined before it becomes reality, right, I mean, an inventor says, I want to
do something, and they are inspired to do it, and then they attempt to take the physical
world and manipulate it or form that idea into the physical reality, so this is, you
know, people act like they're shocked when they go, well, that was imagined in something
before, and I go, but everything is, you know?
Yes, but also from knowing many inventors, many meaning more than, I have fingers on
my hands, I do have all the fingers, by the way, when you find out the real story, see,
we're told that these inventors are clear, great thinkers, and I'll tell you from their
own mouths what I've heard in many fields, their inventions were actually accidents,
they weren't trying to do that, or, you know, it just came about, and they happened to notice
it, other people had done it, but they were the first ones, let's say, to run to the patent
office, right, with it, but what I wanted to mention also was, you know, you hear about
in American schools, especially Columbus sailed the ocean blue, whatever, 1492, right?
Well, that didn't make it to the history books until more than 200 years later, so what was
going on in the 10s, 20s, and 30s of the last century is not in the history books right
now, right?
So they, those that know what happened and have not disclosed it, show it to us through
science fiction, they invented science fiction in the 50s, but what you do is you exaggerate
it, so it's in the realm of entertainment, right, but it's also a form of disclosure.
The other thing is the, you brought up the Apple watch, and yes, the bad word of blood
pressure, blood pressure is a misnomer, it's actually measuring the interval between, let's
say what they call a heartbeat, but it's all on the wrong track, what they're monitoring,
for example, with nutrition and calories.
Calories are not relevant to nutrition unless you're pooping charcoal, right, because a
calorie is derived from burning something completely down into carbonization, so unless
you're pooping charcoal, I think we've gone over that with the old Ocelli in the Greek
stuff, irrelevant, now I wonder how much of that is deliberate to put up irrelevant stuff
like diabetes, for example, blood pressure, calories, all these things, and wait a second,
someone said diabetes is irrelevant, my dad died from it, he had to cut off his leg and
all that, yep, it is, there is no, the pancreas are not an independent organ, just like the
rear view mirror is not independent of your car, really, that whole function is a bad liver
function, and you have diagnosis, and also they have no way to really diagnose blood
sugar, look it up, it's kind of hard now with Google and all that, by the way, who
is Gug, see, because El, you know, a lot of Mikhail, Raphael, is a Hebrew term, El meaning
Elohim or God, or a God, you know, that's the name of their society of gods are the El,
so who's this God Gug, like Gug El, right, you see what I mean, anyway, it's a Hebrew
deity of some sort, but here's the overall analysis that I've come up with to get to
the end, what you are engaged in in this society, you meaning the collective, not necessarily
those that are listening to us, but they've come from the collective most likely, and
you're now separating yourself from it, because of its lack of quality or what have you, everyone
has their own reasons, nothing that the collective approach has approached as being significant
or important or would deem improvement is going to be for the next society, all that
stuff will, like I said, there will be no blood pressure, blood sugar, calories, all
that stuff's going to be, that's just a big foolish, how would you say, it's a category
of nonsense, right, now calories can be used in laboratories or whatever, but not, has
nothing to do with food, the diabetes, the blood pressure, all that is complete nonsense,
and you could go down the line on how they invent diseases, by the way, doctors do, and
I hope people have woken up from the pandemic, they strap people that, anyway, they have
to show numbers, just like 9-11, if they left the people, if they told everyone to come
out of the building, it wouldn't have been such a bad event, right, so you leave people,
so if you tell people there's a pandemic and people are dying, well you've got to supply
dead people, right, and the other thing I want to mention is when you read about death
camps, whether they were in Europe, Cambodia, or wherever, it was always run by doctors,
always, so the whole thing about the doctors inventing, in other words, I've got direct
knowledge of this from many people, they have a, work for a big company, very expensive
health plan, the doctors say, hey, let's prank this person, and tell them they got tested
for cancer and they have cancer, so they go for some therapy, you know, a quarter of
a million dollars a month or whatever, right, just to get the insurance money, I'm serious,
this is more common than not, it's just not known, and when you, and it's always inconclusive,
it's like, yeah, it showed inconclusive, some cells showed up at the blood test, but it's
very serious, you should consider therapy, and the people, of course, you know, they're
in the upper part of the collective, you know, they got a quarter of a million salary with
a three million in health insurance, they're going to go for it and they get ruined, and
the doctors get it from their society, so the other thing before we get into this, it
seems like we're leaning towards the medical thing, I don't know if you guys are familiar
with the Flexner Report, early 20th century, between 1902 and 1910, that's when they decided
to standardize allopathic medicine, and one of the things in the Flexner Report, and listen
to this carefully, is that only accepted scientific practices will be applied in the medical field
in 1902, is what the Flexner Report said, alright, it sounds very innocuous or whatever,
I'll say it again, only accepted current scientific methods will be applied to the
medical industry, okay, it's 1902, 1910, between that time period, alright, stop and
think for a minute, that sounds very harmless, right, how much, so what did that do to medical
research?
It actually doesn't sound harmless to me, but because, yeah, it says no more, there's
no medical research anymore, no more medical research because, it's not established, stop
here at this time, right, I mean, unless I'm hearing it wrong, okay, right, exactly, so
when they tell you they're doing medical research, and you look into it, there's nothing
there, because they actually, they have not improved some of the practices here and there,
and it is true, I do know several people that worked in emergency medicine, and they had,
one of the most typical things when someone comes in from an accident, is their femur and
hip are displaced, so they have to pop it back in, or the shoulder is displaced, they
have to pop it back in, and it usually takes several orderlies, it's a lot of work, so
he developed a brace, a device that will hold the body, and the doctor pulls a lever, basically,
and it resets the joint, he went for 10 years, they would not grant it to him, they finally
did, you see, so they're fighting, so anyway, they do say what they're doing, right, and
it's actually pretty nefarious, but it's the way, you know how they say, it's not what
you say, it's how you say it, right, and that's what they're doing, so I want to go back to
the theme here, which is multiple themes, and maybe end up with the body first, because
that's the easiest one, you know, it's kind of like, it's not how good of a driver you
are, it's what car you drive, what people notice first, right, so the car you're driving
is the physical body, it's actually the suit, but it is powered by the soul, okay, which
is the breathing, the nervous system, and the heart rate, and all that other stuff,
and when the body is alive, and the soul is powered, you know, like charging something,
and it's fully charged, or working, enough of a charge to keep working, then, just like
a computer, or a phone, or whatever, then you could use it for its normal operation,
then the spirit can run, it could work, so back to the body, someone, by the way, had
said, where do I get the older recordings, because we had done two hours, we called it
the container, it was episode number two back then, yeah, essentially, the main thing
that I hammer on people is the body is, we view ourselves as walking around through the
world, through space, or sitting down in a chair, or doing anything we do with our body,
you know, and it has senses, touch, feel, and all this other stuff, we sense temperature,
and hardness, softness, and all this other stuff, what I'm trying to say here is that
we are integrated with the environment, where does the body stop, and where does the environment
start, well, you could say, typically, it's the skin, your hands, the bottoms of your
feet, the top of your head, but I'm telling you that that environment, whether you're
underwater, or in the air, or under, in your bed, covered with sheets, it is integrated
with the environment, proof of that is when you go to different air pressures, right,
you feel the difference, right, in certain depths in the ocean, temperature.
Doesn't this travel all the way through, though, look, from the environment, through the body,
into the other parts here, right, the spirit and the soul, you know, to try and define
where the borders are is sort of important, isn't it, because...
Yeah, yeah, and there is, the borders are boundaries, but it doesn't mean that your
body ends there, like, for example, early electrical research, they found that all materials have
an atmosphere, I know it sounds kind of crazy, but when I say atmosphere, I just mean what
I said, and it's held in with a slight vacuous field, just like, for example, with the Earth,
they say the Earth's, the space is a vacuum, and the Earth is an atmosphere, it's mild,
you know, it's basically air surrounding the planet, well, if we know what a vacuum is,
it's a negative pressure, it should pull the atmosphere out, and there should be never
an atmosphere on the Earth, how does it work, well, actually, the vacuum on the Earth's
atmosphere is greater than the vacuum in outer space, actually, outer space is pushing
on the Earth, it's denser energetically, or in the energy that you need for the atmosphere
to stay on the Earth, than we're told, and how do I know that to be true, because we
have an atmosphere, there's no way that space could be a vacuum pulling away on our atmosphere,
look how gentle it is, you can actually move your hand briefly or wave through the air,
you're actually displacing atmosphere, if you subject anything that were the, quote
unquote, atmosphere to a vacuum condition, what happens, completely collapses and goes
into that area where the vacuum is, so space cannot be a vacuum by very proof of that,
is that we have an atmosphere, so this very simple type of thinking is based on the emperor
has no clothes reasoning, right, it's almost the most simplest approach to view it and say
what you see is actually what's going on, so the body has an atmosphere as well, and
that atmosphere is what integrates with the environment around you, and for example, kind
of a jestful matter, if you've ever, if you want to notice someone's atmosphere, it's
the way they smell, if someone puts on all this cologne and walks by five feet away
from you, you kind of smell them, right, it's because it's in their atmosphere, right, other
people, let's say, have bad hygiene, right, you're smelling their atmosphere, not them
essentially. Isn't that literally due to some little bits
of matter that sort of break off, float off, and you know, end up in your nostrils, I mean
look, I'm not being completely... There's been tests on that, and no, there
is no matter, yes, yes, if you have matter on your nostril, think of it this way, remember
this is the materialist point of view, if there's matter on your nostril, do you smell
it on the sensory organ, on the tongue or the nostril, and then it pops off when you
stop smelling it? No. Right? It would be like a self-cleaning filter, and it's not, it's
all energetic, signaling. Remember, this is a materialist point of view that the collective
has garnered, you know, telling you that all these things about light as a photon and electrons
and all that, you know, it's just completely ridiculous.
So going back to the body and the environment, there's nothing that ever enters or leaves
the body directly, so nothing goes through the intestines, nothing goes through the lungs,
nothing goes through the skin, in either direction, right? There are organs that we excrete from
that collect these energies and manifest them as energy, discharge them, right? Solid, liquid
and gases, let's say. Proof of this is very simple. Many of the anatomical drawings that
you'll find online or in an anatomy book are very accurate, because you could also look
at photos of skin and intestine and lung tissue, or if you have a microscope, usually 320 to
400 magnification, you will see what I'm saying here, and it all matches the diagrams that
you see online. So if you type in cross-section of human intestine, you will see basically
the lumen of the opening, and then you will see the inside wall and the villi and the
blood vessels and two layers of cells, and there is nothing, there is nothing there that
allows anything to go through, right, at all. The same with the lungs, the same with
the skin, everything is done by induction. Induction is just contact, in other words,
physical proximity or contact, and there is an energy exchange, and the exchange from
one to the other stimulates or changes the other. It's very simple. Now, I have not gone
into this in depth, because it sounds pedantic, in other words, this is not a quote-unquote
biology medical class, but what I encourage people to do, because we're all very young
and new at this, most people will never hear what I just said unless they hear it from us.
I'm serious. I've been saying this since the 1980s, and I've never run across anyone that
directly says, yeah, I know that. Where did you find that out? How did you come up with
never? It's always like I'm presenting something new to anyone I've ever spoken to about this.
Well, the only thing I can say about that is that it's not so new to me, and I told
you about the observation that I have that I don't fully know how to articulate.
Okay, well, communication, then.
Yeah, let's try to communicate this, because I think it's extremely important what you're
saying and extremely correct, but I say that because of my observations. I see the sun.
I told you this before, and you were kind of surprised, I thought, that the way people
explain the sun is absolutely stupid. It beams light down here, and I go, no, it doesn't.
How is it that you people even see this? I see it.
I want to just stick with this, follow this thought for a moment. My point here was, you
know how we spoke about the juvenile nature. In some cases, we have to retain this, and
the reason why I'm saying this is just when you jump online and look at the cross-section
of the intestine, do a cross-section of a steel-belted radial car tire, and you'll see
they're the same. They're the same in function. Nothing goes through them, and because this
is not discussed openly, whether it's done secretly, it should be, I guess, and anyone
that I've ever confronted in the past 30-some-odd years either sees it as a completely new notion
or something acceptable and not ridiculous. What I'm trying to say, this concept is very
young, not juvenile and immature, but still extremely young. Like I said, I didn't want
to get into too much on how it functions because I'm just as young at this in knowledge as
anyone who just found out about it 10 seconds ago. What I'm counting on is, I'll go on with
the sun, but what I'm counting on is people looking at this and coming up with their
own expression, like you said, I just couldn't explain it, and then getting back together
and forming a body of work. Even when PCs became popular with computers, it wasn't until 10
years later until it started becoming a big deal. Enough people understanding that nothing
gets absorbed or goes through any of the biological tissue, plants, animals, fish, anything, within,
let's say, we don't have that much time, but within a certain amount of time, there will
be more and more focus on this, and more and more will come together and establish
it as a form of study, and it still hasn't happened. But you were saying about the sun.
Well, the computers, like you said, look, computers were great and they were very powerful
instruments, but until people learned how to make them communicate with one another,
there was not very much use for it as far as coming together and sharing knowledge and
actually making some progress there collectively.
Sure. It's slow.
It's slow, yeah.
It's slow, yeah. So the thing about, I mean, you had to take a disk and hand it to somebody
and then they had to take it somewhere else and put it on their computer. So you didn't
have a very efficient methodology for transferring information. But what's fascinating here is
that, like I said, the sun is not this thing that beams light onto the planet, okay? And
by observation, what it looks like to me is that the sun does send energy, and the light
is created by contact here.
In the atmosphere. That's why the sun looks different at morning, it does at high noon,
than it does at sundown, yeah.
But I see that process happen, and other people will look up at the very same thing that I
see and say to them, say, no, this beams light. It's like a big flashlight in the sky. And
I go, well, but no, it doesn't, actually.
Yeah, well, that sounds like a personal problem, whether it's on your part or their part.
You see, it's a personal thing. The thing, I believe that we need to get away from that.
Like, for example, there's a lot of people that do Sonics, and I've heard some podcasts,
and they spend half the time talking about their own personal stories, right? And whoever's
listening is just itching to say, I've got a better story than that, right? So the focus
gets away, that the purpose of what we're trying to do, I believe, or at least I try
to focus on since I've been speaking, is to be objective as possible and leave my personal
experiences out unless they need to be shown in an impersonal way to everyone else how it
could benefit them.
Well, but that's the point of this, actually. It's not about my personal story is better.
It's a matter of, but that's what I'm observing. So now I'm trying to figure out why it is
they're not seeing the same thing.
Don't do that. You'll go crazy.
Well, that's what I discovered. Yeah.
Yeah, we'll explain why that works. Also, we've done in the past cosmic censorship.
And also they there are people that come into this reality to kick to manifest the reality
because societies are governed by more powerful beings, and they need to create numbers just
like you create a Dungeons and Dragons thing. It's, you know, to create characters. But
so I just wanted to get back on this, because future discussions will involve references to
this mindset. And these are ideas, not ideologies, by the way. You know, whenever you hear the word
ideology, that's a low level standing narrative. Right. So anyway, I just want to throw that in
there. But the body, again, just is completely sealed. And it works by induction. You have an
induction stove, you know, glass stove, you know, the pot of water is boiling. You move the pot
aside, put your hand on it. Radio waves, you know, waves in the ether, radio and all things
that are transmitted wirelessly is all by induction, forms of induction. So you could
look up that field. It's been around for a long time and apply that to bio to biology.
And we'll cover the human body again, perhaps in a sonic all by itself, because the main thing
with this human body is that it's working right to animate the spirit. Because if your physical
body is so sick, you can't think clearly. And your spirit is now in that sick state also will
follow suit. Right. So there are many other things like eating seasonally and what to eat when
various times of the month. Yeah. Various times of the day and all that. I think that will be
something go to go into maybe even in this one bounce back. Right. You cannot speak about this.
Now, I mentioned a lot of these diseases are fraudulent and how they misdiagnose and all this.
That's in the category of health. Right. OK, I have you. I cannot explain how many times I was
brought into conferences, Skype and what have you, anywhere from three to two dozen people talking
about what's what to do to improve your health. What do you think I say when I get on there?
Well, the first thing you say or just generally, how long do I last? Actually, I should have put
you on the spot like that. I usually leave within two minutes. I'm thinking and I end up giving a
bunch of pejoratives. Why? Because I keep asking health for what? What are you trying to do?
There is no general health. Right. There is no such thing. Give an example. Listen, I'm going
to go over to the Himalayas and climb Mount Everest next week. I need a certain level of
health and conditioning to do that. Or I just got a job. I'm going to be sitting in a chair 10 hours
a day. That requires a different level of health. Right. Or I'm going to be working. UPS requires a
different, you know, delivery packages, different level of health. Or this woman is a single mom
or what level of health? What are you trying to do with your health? In other words, your health
is your condition. That's why people that go out and get physical trainers, right, to help them
in the gym or nutritionists. How many of them actually benefit? They'll tell you they do because
they're, you know, they're paying for it, let's say. Right. But very few, very, very little benefit
because like you said earlier, that communication is not there. And if the concept of what level of
health or conditioning you need is not there, what are you going to communicate? There's nothing to
communicate. You just fall into some niche. So I always leave these discussions about health
because I keep asking what level of conditioning, what level of health, what are you trying to do
with this quote unquote health that we can discuss this general? The reason I say this is because
you'll hear one person pop up. Have you ever heard of a quandroitin, whatever selenium or blah, blah,
blah? I'm like, yeah, but what's that for? What are you trying to do? Oh, this. Well, this
supplement is absorbed much better by the body. I'm like, oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh. Yeah. Well,
yeah. What you see. So what are you trying to do with your health? Some people in health discussions
have an ailment. Well, see, that's what I was thinking, actually, is that most of these things,
if somebody asks for advice on health is due to the fact that they have a condition that is not
negative. It's a negative condition. It's an undesirable condition. I'll call it. Right. Right.
Add that extra word. It helps. Yeah, it does, I think, because it's the undesirable condition.
If it was a desirable condition, you wouldn't seek to change it. OK, so you wish to change
a undesirable condition. And that's what it is. I'll give you a perfect for instance.
I'm in constant pain. There is a pain occurring all the time in an area of the body. Right.
I know there's been plenty of these meetings and maybe not involving you,
but there's been plenty of these meetings about, oh, well, we have the way to deal with your pain.
Uh, and I always say, well, you know, well, what, what, what pain are we talking about? Because
the pain in my head is not necessarily the pain that is caused in my feet. It is not necessarily
based on the same thing. So you address an issue based on an undesirable condition. I think you
got to be specific about the condition. Yeah. To address it. I mean, this is my thinking again.
No, no, no. Let's just tackle that real quick. I'll show you how quick I tackle things like that.
Okay. Because, okay. So the first thing I ask is, uh, are you having the pain between morning
and afternoon or are you having the pain between afternoon and all night? Very important.
Because if the pain is from morning to afternoon, that's when the ether, the energies are expanding.
Right. And we're talking about afternoon and morning where you are.
If you're having the pain from afternoon and through the night, well, that has to do with
something about the energies contracting, right? Because nighttime, the energies contract,
right? Things get colder. Sun, sun goes down. Right. Okay. But in your case, let's say you
said that it was all the time. So it doesn't matter if the energies are expanding daily or
night, uh, nightly contracting it. So you're having it all the time. So that would be
all the time. Then I would ask you, is it all day? You might say what? Yes. Right.
And it's okay. Now here's the thing. Is it all week?
What would you say? Yes. Well, uh, that's important. I can tell you that I've been in
that condition. Okay. So I'll, I'll, I'll go back to that condition. It lasts more than a week.
And it has been going on all day. Does it last more than a month? Bear with me here. Yes.
More than a month. Okay. So then we go into a different field. Okay. Because if it lasted
only a week, let's say two weeks, then it's not really tied in with the expanding contraction
on a daily basis of the environment. It's more of a monthly basis because in half the month,
the energies are expanding and the other half they're contracting actually in the middle of
the month, right? You go from full moon, then it contracts to dark moon. Then it expands back to
full moon. That's a monthly. If it's more, if, in other words, if your pains are lasting more
than a month and you don't see cycles where some day, some days or weeks are there less or more.
Now we have to get into the cycles. Is it more during the beginning of the month and Lester,
then we could work with that monthly cycle. Because if you say it's all the time, we can't
work with the daily cycle. If you say it's all month though, it's harder to work with the monthly
cycle. And if it's more than a month, now we have to work with a yearly cycle. Do you see what I
mean? So let's look at the yearly cycle. Summertime is maximum expansion fall. It starts to contract
winter is maximum contraction of energy, right? What happens in the spring starts expanding again
until it reaches summer where it's maximum expansion. So my next question to you, Chuck,
would be, do you, you have it all the time. How was it in the winter? How is it in the summer?
Well, okay. You have it more or less, right? Some people with arthritis have it more in the winter.
You see what I mean? I was just going to say that typically, uh, and, and, and I've experienced this
personally is that it's definitely more in the winter, but, uh, but here's the problem now, uh,
I have to be able to understand what proper timekeeping is here because, oh, yes, yes.
But hold on, hold on to stick with the health. You see how specific you must be. So in the winter,
if it's harder time in the winter, meaning you're sensing a harder time, because here's the thing,
your physical body could be having a harder time in the summer, but it doesn't show up
until the winter, kind of like, you know, your tires running out of air. It's not flat yet,
you know, but gets flat in the way you see. So you're actually manifesting it in the winter
with your sensory. So that means that you're having a hard time when the energies are contracting,
right? So that means you're not going along with the contractive energies,
or it might be, we need to go a little deeper and see that you actually
need the opposite to balance it out. So you're either not going with the flow enough and you're
feeling drag and resistance because you're not going with it, or you're going too much with it
and falling and hitting bottom. So that's another way to look at it. And this is mitigated, helped
with your behavior, believe it or not, the way you think, what you eat, your actions. And this is the
real, how would you say, treatment of, quote, unquote, maladies. And that's how I go about it.
Do you see the whole example there and how you actually just, you actually set up, gave us the
whole setup, right? Right. I totally understand now. Now this means that there are a whole bunch
of different actions that could be taken to either make it, you know, again, kind of put yourself,
I hate to use this phrase again, in sync with what's happening. But really, it's it is to know
it's fine. You have to be in sync, but you have to know which direction is it a one way street,
you go in the wrong way, or is it a two way street where you, but, but if it's two way,
you have to be on the right or on the left, depending for an, you know what I mean? Of
course. Right. You see what I mean? Or is it four lanes in one direction, four lanes in the other?
Are you in the fast lane, middle or slow lane? So all these things have to be considered. So
do you see, but basically you brought that up and I kept asking questions till we nailed it down
to a yearly seasonal thing. How can you have a general, let's say, well, you get on a group and
there's 10 people talking about health, you can't have a general discussion, you have to approach
each individual's condition or what they desire from it. You see, there is no general discussion
on this. You see what I mean? No, it makes no sense, because you can't have a in this, this is
always the problem. And always the problem I have with the quote, medicine, unquote,
is that, you know, here's the, the solution and the solution. Well, the one size fits all. Yeah.
The one size fits all. That makes no sense to me. Well, it could. I've seen the one size fit all
t-shirts at the rock concerts and three people put them on and one of them, it looks like a dress.
The other one is tight. The other one, right? Yeah. But that's the thing. It's not going to
fit very well. Exactly. It's not going to fit very well. And the chances that it's,
it'll look like a, right? Like, for example, there's arguments with the, what they call the,
the, the lollipop, the whatever, the vax, right? Okay. Yeah. Okay. And I think I mentioned this,
maybe I don't do it again, but someone brought up, got in the nurse's face about it. And she,
she started laughing. You're one of those anti-vaxxers. And I went up to her and I said,
are you taking consideration the age, body weight and blood type as it is in NHS protocols?
She packed up all her stuff and went away. Of course. So, so every time there was a vac center,
if you had a bunch of people going and asking these, because in order to administer a vaccine,
you have to have age, body type race, believe it or not. And blood type and body weight.
And none of it, you know, so it's, it's a fraud on its face. It doesn't mean that a one size fits
all t-shirt is a fraud, but what they're doing injecting, you see at all the medicines, right?
The only time they consider the different medicines is for example, how many mil, the dosage.
And there are some warnings about, let's say pregnant women or whatever, but it's more
in depth than that. An anesthesiologist that has two patients that are coming in for an appendectomy.
One of them is a 90 pound white girl with red hair and freckles. And the other one is a 300 pound
black man in his forties. Well, the amount of anesthesia to put out the little redhead white
girl with freckles will kill the 300 pound black man in his forties. Right? So Matt, you see,
and this is already, well, it's, I call it medical racism. It's very real. The Prozac doesn't work in
Asia, in Korea. If you, if you, if you're from Korea or the Northern Northwestern part of Asia,
you will die if you take Prozac. That's why it's banned. It's why it's banned in some of those
countries, actually, for a very practical reason. Right. So there's, there's no discussion on this.
So what this does is actually, I had someone once messaged me, I listen to Greek speak and I feel
just so depressed or whatever. I said, why is it? I mean, that's good because you're actually
getting the dose of it and you are handling it that way first. That's fine. But it should be
empowering because now you have tools. I said, is it, is it depressing in a way? Like,
let's say you want to start fixing things around the house. If I come over and I give you 14
toolboxes with every woodworking, plumbing and electrical tool and put it on the ground and say,
go at it, you're going to be like, I'm depressed now because I don't know how to use these tools.
Right. You see what I mean? All I have is a hammer and a screwdriver, right? Or in most people's
cases, I have three hammers. I fix everything with small, medium and large hammers. Right. So
do you see where I'm going with this? So the body is very, very interesting in that part.
So the body will let you know through the soul what you need to do. And there is no health.
So when you hear people saying this is healthy, I'm like, for what, for what? Right. What,
they have no concept. It is so juvenile in a not such a good way. Right. That it's just not
explainable. So anyway, go ahead. And what have you got so far before we keep perusing on this?
What do you think? No, I think, I think it's great. And look, the one size fits all. I get
what you're saying. And I guess I shouldn't dismiss it that easily because practically,
yeah, if you make a T-shirt big enough, indeed, yeah, everybody can wear it, but
it's not going to have the same effect. OK, you put it on the four foot tall, four foot
nine tall girl and she's wearing it down to her ankles. You know, that's wonderful and all. And
it does. She can wear it. But that's a bit of a different condition that you've now achieved
with the one size fits all. Now, if you want to properly do this, you know, you have different
sizes. You actually small, medium, large will work. And then you got the extra large, extra
small. But look, Chuck, what does this all say? Let's say we're talking about what people get
administered as, quote, unquote, health care, which is an absolute joke. Right.
It's come comes out of the banking system. That's why if you don't can't show you have health care,
you get fined by the IRS 500 bucks. Right. It's such a joke in your face. By the way,
this is all financially hinged and society. Every society has become fish in a barrel.
And there's a saying that goes, what do you do with fish in the barrel? Right.
So, well, at this point, you know, you shouldn't have been in the barrel. But anyway,
this is the thing. These are things that are being administered inside people's bodies,
whether it's oral injection or therapy or whatever. Right. And you got some quack telling
you you got blood pressure or this is your condition or that. Right. What does that tell
you? That humanity is still around. It's a testament to how robust the human body is.
Right. So the collective, as ignorant as they are, by the way, they are robust. They have not
been wiped out by their own medical system yet. They're in everything they're trying. They don't
have to because, remember, this is not some major. The way that the medical professionals
are acting is nefarious, but they don't know that they're doing it. But it does just because
they don't know what they're doing does not make them innocent. You see, they're guilty by association
and by they're actually the ones manifesting these ill acts. So but what is it saying if the
medical community is so bad and actually people that are being destroyed by it actually leave
saying, my doctor helped me and treated me actually thinking that that is telling me that the human
body is extremely robust, can take a lot of punishment, tremendous amount of punishment
and still maintain, you know, being alive or together in most cases, you see. So can you
imagine taking something as robust as the human or any biology? Also, you can take a trimming off
a plant, put it most plants, put it in a glass of water properly and you will sprout roots and put
it in the ground. Right. That's pretty robust, you know. So you have a very robust biology here.
And it's obviously it's, you know, being abused mostly and it's still continuing, still propagating.
Right. Well, it's still durable. And by the numbers, the population grows despite all this.
Sure. So and it's actually growing. Yeah, that's another thing, because I've driven through parts
of the US for hours and not seen anyone or anything or any evidence of anyone who are not
overpopulated. I think I've mentioned trillions, thousands of billions can be supported on the
planet. I think right now you could fit everyone on the planet in what they call Texas State and
they would still have plenty of, you know, like a suburban community, everyone on the planet. So.
But then again, you're there. This information of global warming and overpopulation is being
communicated to fish in a barrel. What can they do right now? This is the body. Nothing goes in and
out. It works through induction. So when things manifest in the body through nutrition and are
excreted right through the body, giving off stuff, it's literally going from material to energy,
back to material or material to energy into material. It's a palindrome works both ways.
What it literally what literally is happening in the body literally is what you see in the
fictional Star Trek depiction of the replicator, right, where they think when they want to eat
something in the machine makes it, let's say, out of pure energy. The only flaw, by the way,
I do see as a commentary on Star Trek is a lot of times they go down to a planet, they get sick,
so they have to be beamed up. If they were really able to beam you up, they shouldn't be able to
filter out the bad stuff and only beam up the healthy body. Well, there are biological filters
on there, you know, in later incarnations after they. OK, good, because that's that's the most
logical thing that I see if you have the technology to apply. That's what I would think, too. And,
honestly, when I viewed it as a kid, you know, the 60s version of it, you're absolutely right.
And as a matter of fact, I didn't think of the replicators at first. I thought of the
transporter because what the idea is that they're supposedly breaking down
the physical body into energy and then reassembling it into the body, which is,
by the way, in a real reality, you wouldn't do it that way. You keep the organism alive,
but you have them walk through walls, let's say, or walk through atmosphere where you collapse
time and distance. Notice I didn't say space. Right. Right. So, OK, so the human body will
always keep referencing, like even if we don't get again very soon into the human body, how it
really works. I think I mentioned enough right now that if you have access to the old Greek speak,
which somehow will get up on Rumble or one of these other platforms, maybe even YouTube.
I do have a collection of all of the ones we've done. Somehow they will be available. Not now,
not next week, but around, let's say, near future. So you can go and listen to the old
early incarnations. When were they done, Chuck? Twenty fifteen, I think. Right.
The original one. Yeah. Twenty fifteen. OK, so eight years old. They're still fresh. Yes.
Right. OK, so. So this is important because we're covering like who we are in a very
objective kind of way. You notice I keep going back and forth with the health and the soul,
the metabolism. Like if you're going to go into a discussion speaking about general health,
they're really talking about how well the soul is doing in the body and then the how what's the
status of the body because the soul is either working well or not. So if someone has a problem
breathing, that's a problem with the soul. Problem with their heart is a problem with the soul.
Not enough energy or too much energy. That's a soul problem. Right. That's the metabolism,
the breathing, the nutrition, the all that. Right. So this is the basic mechanics. It's kind of like
taking a car for a tune up to a mechanic. He's not going to consider what you can. He doesn't
consider the driving style. He just wants to make sure the equipment is up to snuff. Right. Right.
But if you if you're setting it up for high performance driving, you're going to tune it
for that. You can. And that's what basically health is when you start to go to extremes.
Now, most people on the health discussion will not be climbing Mount Everest or whatever. So
you don't need a special regimen for that. They're basically you can presume they're either
a UPS delivery driver, postman sitting in an office or a single mom kind of thing.
Generally, that that health status is generally overlaps and works OK,
but it's still not specific enough for each individual. It cannot it cannot be effective.
In other words, you could say we had a discussion about health like we can do a discussion about
health, but it does not help anyone specifically. And we are very specific beings ultimately.
Right. So so so that that's the the body and the soul. For what else I could talk about the soul,
there are things that are very specific to the soul, because the soul we went over
in the Greek convention, it's pneuma. So it's used as a prefix in the English with the PNU
prefix. We see pneumatic pneumonia. Those things have to do with the movement of air. OK.
There are specific things. There are certain disciplines, like, for example,
there I remember having a book. I don't have it anymore, but the gist that I got out of it,
you can pretty much heal most things through breathing, just like there's a book that you
could pretty doctor met at Mengele. You're not sick. You're thirsty. You can heal most things
with water. I think it's a little extreme, but there are a lot of examples where people
have testimonies and gone through exercises of breathing. Right. Most Westerners or most people
are shallow breathers. Right. They're not fully taking advantage of breathing. So you inhale
slowly and you hold it for the amount of time that you took to inhale and then you exhale slowly
at the rate of the amount that you took to inhale and hold it. Right. So it would be inhaling for
one second. You hold it for one second and then exhale for one second. So a breath cycle is three
seconds or you double the time. Right. You spend two seconds inhaling. Right. And every time you
inhale, you hold it for that amount of time. What I mean, time by the stopwatch, let's say
and exhale. That is the easiest way to reset your breathing, which is the predominant term
used for the soul. And that is another discussion that we can get in depth depth in. But again,
it's very personal. Right. But in essence, the body is the suit, the meat. Nothing goes in.
Nothing goes out directly. And the soul, you could say the paramount aspect of it is your breath.
But it's the heart rate. It's the nervous system. Right. It's the it's the pulse rate of all of the
various organs or 12 pulse rates. Each major organ has a pulse rate on and on. You see,
it's complex, but simple. Right. And I've read about many of these mystical things,
supposedly. Right. Where it does boil down to quite often just the breathing and the amount
of water and the quality of the water, of course, and things like this. And I say to myself, yes,
quality of the air, the quality of the water and how you use it seem to be two of the very
primary things, but also the food. Now, I do use the word consume, but but maybe that's not exactly
proper. But it is more proper than you think, because when it breaks down energetically in
your body, it's it's pretty well consumed. But it's not. Anyway, it's not the way that people
do explain it generally. So if you said consumer consummate years ago meant you had tuberculosis.
Well, there you go. I mean, I'm just saying the words have changed.
So, you know, just like a, you know, is happy. Right. It's written in songs everywhere. And
now it means something else. But we've gotten into etymology before, and I'm sure we're going
to get into it again. Yeah. But but yeah, the food is very important, but that's going to be hard. I
been sort of a food prophet years ago. I said next amount of years, you won't be able to eat
this because of this. And I tell my wife all the time, she goes, remember, I said this about three
years ago about this. And he's seeing it happening right now. It's very simple once you see the
patterns. Right. If you see something happen in time and you see if it's a pattern of something
that's repeated before and it'll get to that point X amount of time, it's very easy to say
five years from now this. Right. Because you studied how it happened before. It would be
slightly different, you see. But starving a population can be done two ways. One is by
preventing the actual presence of food, of being there, or you give them all the food they want,
but you can't. It's tainted. It has no nutrition. What's the difference? Right. Well, the difference
is that that you have people not being alarmed by the fact that there is a lack of food.
That's right. That's the worst one. Yeah, that's the frog being boiled alive slowly. Right. And
that way it's not as noticeable, you know, because the food just disappeared. You have a reaction.
You're guaranteed you'll have a short term reaction immediately. That's right. You're
deliberate, by the way. You'll find it if you're looking for it. But the thing is not to focus
on how evil this place is and can be and was and will be. It's a matter of focusing on
what you can know and how you're going to use what you know and how simple it is. So again,
let's just, I think we've covered enough about the soul and the body and how there is no one
size fits all. Pretty much everything that we've been told about these things is false,
but the truth of the matter or as close to the truth as possible
can easily be brought up and discussed. And a great deal of it can be observed
if you just have the time to do so. Right. Yeah. Once. Yeah. You know how many times people,
you know, when you have been working at this job 20 years, same parking lot,
what color are the stripes in the parking lot? I don't know. Well, you've been coming here. What
do you mean? Right. See. So I love when that kind of thing happens. Actually, I find it extremely
ironic where, you know, well, I noticed this and somebody is there every single day and they don't
know it. Yeah. What's filtering? It's it's how observant are you? And but you see, it's not a
big deal. And whether you know the color of the stripes or not, the big deal here is that you've
been doing something by repetition doesn't mean you're going to be aware of it or of what's going
on. Right. At all. That's that's something else to get into. And we'll we'll do that.
So. Interesting, the break time there, actually, because I kind of like this where we're recording
as opposed to being on live radio because it allows us to relax a little more. And I like it.
Anyway, hopefully you guys are enjoying this. And the Greek seems to dig this kind of situation.
Sorry to use those kind of terms, but that's fine. I think so. I think it's pretty cool.
Well, you know, we're not doing any canned laughter anymore, are we? No, I'm just joking. None of that.
None of that. Do I want to play 100 year old sounds at this point? You know, some of those
sounds are almost 100 years old. Yeah. Most of those people are dead. I heard that back in the
days is, you know, this is from when the crowds were overly enthusiastic. So. Yeah. So. So anyway.
So, yeah. To pick up where we left off, though, I think it's important to discuss something that
is often discussed elsewhere. But but obviously it won't be discussed the same way here. And look,
common parlance for me. I'll I'll use the term fear porn because people seem to get addicted to
sources which provide them with information that is meant to evoke an emotional reaction.
And fear is one of the easiest ones that that one can observe. Right. They make you afraid
of something. You're afraid of an enemy. You're afraid of a disease. We brought up disease already
dis ease already during this discussion. Right. But they make you afraid. They put it to you.
They broadcast it. And collectively, there is a response. And the collective response is,
guess what, designed to be that way. It's not accidental that that you're being encouraged.
Be afraid of the disease. Be afraid of this nation. Be afraid of this kind of people.
Be afraid of people who believe this. It doesn't matter. Right wingers, Christians,
the Arabs, they're coming to get you. They're coming to get you. This is all a charade, really
meant to evoke what fear create an emotional response. And the same mind is in the spirit.
And it does. They do the same thing when it comes to now fear. Fear porn is easy,
easy to recognize. But they also encourage you about certain things. Right. Hey, listen,
the economy is doing better. You know why? Here's these numbers. Nobody understands the numbers.
Nobody knows how they were collected. It doesn't. Actually, it's irrelevant.
They just told you things are better. And suddenly the behaviors on mass change.
This. Well, that's that's why I want to shoot by you that it's not just fear. You can make
people so overly happy that they'll gladly tie someone to a stake and light them on fire.
Well, and there you have it, because they can now encourage all sorts of things that you
happiness. Yeah. Yeah. Or you can make a group of people in a sports venue so happy that their
team won. They go outside and start flipping cars and setting garbage cans on fire. Yeah,
because you're supposed to care that, you know, insert football team's name here or whatever
that they got a bonus for winning a championship. That matters to you.
It's emotion, basically, and that's the governing. Well, yeah, yes, I would say
governing either limit or or or let's say the limit, because I think we spoke earlier that
there is no memory limit. Right. Where they put a cap on it by saying, look how this intellectual
person or whatever, you know, you can't if you could be as smart as him. That's all you have
to be. Right. There's no limit to what the human mind can, let's say, memorize or learn.
It's limitless. It has no cap on it. Right. That's why I don't buy all the A.I. stuff there.
There is an A.I. That's another discussion, because if you are not our most powerful being,
why would you do things yourself? Right. You know, like if you're very, very wealthy,
you have a staff do things for you. Right. So. We covered most of thing,
most things that are generally purposeful when we refer to the body and the soul
or the health condition. And in a general sense, you cannot generalize those things because they're
very, very specific. But what's even more specific about the lack of ability to generalize on those
things is the specificness of each spirit, because the spirit, who you are is the spirit,
the mind, the personality of each individual. And that is not interchangeable as the soul
and the body might be. With consciousness transfer, your spirit can be put into another body. I love
when they show this in sci-fi, taking someone's mind or spirit, putting it in a dog and vice versa.
Right. Well, again, I know you love Star Trek as an example anyway. Yeah, they've done that there,
too. Yeah. Well, certainly. And even in the 60s. Right. One of the most famous and terrible
episodes of Star Trek, honestly, was they called Spock's Brain. You might recall this one
where they literally took Spock's consciousness and put it in a box. Right. So it's in a box. I
mean, to me, this is transhumanism in the 60s being shown to us. Sure. But it's been done
since the 30s. Oh, look, I'm not saying that it's about the reality. I'm saying that as far as,
you know, public demonstration. Right. They showed, OK, Spock's body is getting to walk around
because they put this mechanism on his head. And therefore, this was supposed to give control of
the brain to somebody with switches and all this. But meanwhile, his consciousness, his spirit,
his soul, mind, his mind. No, not his. Actually, sorry, not his soul. His soul is in his body.
He was kind of listless and on sort of life support when that was done. There's other ones
where another person's body like I think Kirk was switched with a woman back and forth. Oh,
right. Right. She was Kirk. Right. That was another one. Another one of the bad episodes,
right. But Spock, in this case, I think he was just an automaton. They put a band on his head
and his soul was still going and his body was going. But his mind and his spirit,
you see, even I catch myself. I think I caught you on that soul thing. I'm not being a stickler about
it, but it's important that we if we practice enough to be a stickler, then you won't have
to be a stickler. Right. It'll just be natural. And go back to how we started. You can't come out
and tell people this is the way it is. This is how you should do it. They won't you know, people
will find that as an affront. But if you just give hints and suggestions, people won't do it either
if they don't get the hint. So there's somewhere in between where I cannot emphasize enough the
difference between the three, but how the soul and the body are really, really in union. Once
you consider there's consciousness transfer. Right. And, you know, just to transfer an idea
to people, I also set things up so you'll knock them down sometimes. Just OK. That's good. But
anyway, posthumous. Yeah. So so look, put it put it in one way. I wrapped up what we wrapped up,
let's say generalizations, specific generalizations about the soul, health at the body and health
and how they're attached and how to view it in a way that it just means the way the collective use
it is ridiculous from one side and how ineffective it is. There are many people that have gone to
health seminars and feel like they've gained something. But mostly it's because they that's
what they were told to say. Someone else said it and they they really don't get much out of it.
That's long term. And then if they think they are, they hit through long term practice. They'll see
it's not effective. And this is just the way humans have been string along, strung along for
a long time. We gave a little bit of the example of the pain issue. Was it daily? No. Was it weekly?
No. Was it monthly? No. It was seasonal. Right. So it's very everyone is very different. But
even though we showed how you can't generalize with the health and the body because there are
specifics, the spirit is even more specific because the body and the soul are interchangeable. Right.
But the spirit is not no matter where your spirit goes or does, it's going to be you
always and just you. And that's what makes you you. Right. It's it's I mean, how else
can we say it? And you brought up the fear aspect. And is it usually fear based on good,
solid, concrete information? Or is just because some authority figure said you were taught at a
age like we mentioned the last time that was respectable and because they're respectable,
they what they're saying is correct. Right. You see. So it's emotional.
Well, and that's that's the thing, though, is now where does emotion really come from?
I talked about a way to access it. Right. It's just there through external input. Oh,
wait, that sounds familiar. But through external input, you can access that
if someone is susceptible. Right. If someone is willing to accept that word from the authority
and that authority, again, could be the government agent, could be the just the TV in general.
It could be the matter, the chief of the tribe or the coach in a football team, let's say.
But but here, you know, where does it come from? OK, it's just part of the the way the spirit
interacts again with the soul and the body. OK, so the condition of the mind, I'll be using mind
and spirit and personality interchangeably, just like breath and soul are interchangeable. The
body seems to land on itself just being the body. But the mind and the spirit, your personality,
uniqueness, who makes you you is the spirit, the mind, personality. It's very, very unique.
But what's interesting is it has an attribute which, again, if we go back to Star Trek,
certain cultures eliminated emotion. Right. They tried to because it was usually led to detriment.
But if you look at, let's say, why the Vulcans got rid of emotions, because it almost led to
them completely wiping themselves out, which is very extreme. So what that means is the Vulcans
better because they're not emotion. Well, in some cases, but and they went overboard because
they didn't have to do what they did, getting rid of emotion because it was an extreme situation.
One of the markers of of a believable A.I. is that when people communicate with it is that
it has emotion, you see. But what I'm trying to convey is there is this something we call emotion
and everyone accepts it. It goes. It also borders the boundary of sanity, by the way.
And maybe we'll get into it a little bit, because someone who is a very mild mannered person that
does something totally out of character and harms others, let's say, in a criminal sense,
like going postal or whatever. Right. They that was an emotional response they had.
And usually they may not suffer the full consequences because they plead insanity.
You see, that's what I mean. It's the boundary. That's just an extreme example. The same with
someone being overly infatuated and enamored with someone and then noticing that that was just a
temporary thing. So it goes both both many. The spectrum is very wide, but the ability for the
emotions to be a function of the spirit, the mind and it having an overarching effect on the on the
rest of the being, the soul and the body is something that has been completely skirted and
not spoken of publicly. And this is this is goes into this discussion almost of have you ever heard
like in scientific terms, non-Newtonian, right? It's like something that doesn't obey the regular
laws of physics, you know. So they still keep you in the Newtonian thing, like, for example,
cornstarch and liquid. If you vibrate it, it becomes solid during the vibration. Right. And
then you take the vibration off. It goes back to being a liquid. Right. So they call it a
non-Newtonian fluid. So when you when we reach into the study of the mind, it's the psychology field.
So this is all going to be non-Freudian, which is like they have non-Newtonian.
These things do not fall into that limited kind of joke called, you know, Freud, which, by the way,
Freud was more heavily into dream interpretation than anything else. And also he suggested to all
the world authorities that everyone should be taking cocaine, by the way, constantly. So well,
because it excites. But anyway. Yeah. So the spirit and the emotion is they're so linked and so
close together that we live in separation of them, just like the Vulcans kind of like
separated completely. And but yet we cannot. We're always using it. And it's also a major effect on
how the spirit affects the body and the soul. So we're going to maybe delve into that a little
bit because we're going to be bringing that up again in the future. Yes. And I think it's a look
and I have a very solid question about this, I think, because it's it's very important to note
again. And I think I mentioned this on the first Sonic, but they say that you lost your mind,
you know, when you seem to be more overwhelmingly governed by your emotions one way or another.
I think it's kind of a relatively good phrase, actually, when you lost your mind,
sort of because it indicates that you're not using your your more solid, logical mind.
We're not using your mind is one thing, but losing your mind when I hear losing your mind
in a literal sense, it means possession. You're possessed by another mind.
Well, this this is true. But is it? Yeah. But they don't call that losing you. They call that
possession. They call that possession because if one loses their mind and their mind less
unless something else steps in to become their mind. So, look, logically, you could be you can
be mindless, just like if this if you're transferred, the spirit is transferred out of the
physical container, the container, which is the soul and the body. Right. You are mindless. Yeah.
Does it you can be mindless and still be breathing and walking and talking and running for president
or what did I just say? I'm sorry. Or whatever. Right. You did. OK. Anyway. Yeah. OK. That's all
that they should walk. Don't run. Yeah. Someone running is running for a position. I said,
why don't you try walking instead of running? Might be to figure out what's going on. Might
be a bit safer for all involved, but don't run. Yeah. But look, this is one question. I'm sorry.
One question. I think it's going to set you off, actually, into a very interesting direction
because, OK, when people talk about this and, you know, I think much like the mind is limitless
for the information it can take in. We don't know what that limit is. I would say that emotion,
on the other hand, is not the same because I think it's not even non-Newtonian, you know,
non-Freudian or even well, non-Freudian. I don't know because we're speaking of psyche,
the PSY prefix, the mind, psyche, spirit. Right. And that's look. But it's it's it's
interesting to me because I think it's just that the rules are there. There are governing principles,
a logic to it. I think that they're not easily understood at this time. I think nobody understands
it. But emotionally, like you said, you know, even the response that one might have to being
overwhelmingly infatuated with someone. Right. This is another form of, you know, yes, you're
you're adhering to emotional response a lot more than thinking usually. And that's not even a bad
thing there, because, look, anybody could observe that when you first are encountering somebody in
an amorous relationship that often, often, very often, you're much more intense about it, let's
say, at the beginning. You're falling also, aren't you? Right. They call it falling. Why do you want
to fall in love and not rise in love? That's another common issue there. But I think the
language, if we pay attention to the language and it's not like the word nice, you just basically
falling is falling. So no, look, Chuck, what I'm trying to somehow introduce, which it's hard to
put out, is that the emotion is a component of the spirit. But showing the Vulcan analogy, how they
wiped it out, is it really? Yeah. I mean, you could like circumcision, for example. Right. Well,
but they did. Everyone's born with and then they do the chop. So they kind of like emotion did a
spiritual circumcision. The Vulcans, right, where they eliminated it. But here's the thing. They
didn't eliminate it. If you notice, the struggle is still subject to it. They were still subject
to it. It was something they couldn't separate, but they were supposed to be under a discipline,
right, where logic was a discipline. And that was supposed to be this. Well, it was only accepted
and all the emotions were not acceptable. They're not acceptable. But but they did acknowledge that
they were there. I mean, look, you can't say something is unacceptable if it doesn't exist.
So the thing is, it must exist for it to be unacceptable. Right. Right. And when you don't
accept it, it doesn't mean it still does. It still exists. Right. But here's the thing, though. There
is no what I'm trying to maybe look, I've been talking about this for over a decade and I still
haven't prevailed in a very simple way to about emotion. But just because you cannot fully define
something doesn't mean you can't use it. Right. Electricity. Anyone will tell you we don't know
exactly what it is, but we use it. So what's the point? Maybe I'll say it again a different way.
The spirit is the mind, what makes you you and it tends to be dominant. The what the body and the
soul, your living body, a container is animating the spirit. OK, but the spirit can be transferred.
But even when it's transferred, it seems like the emotion is part of the mind and the spirit,
not part of the metabolism in the body. So the emotion discussing emotion that is a quote unquote
psychological or spiritual topic. So and I can't see how it could be separated, just like you
brought up it just because it's not accepted. It's not there. It's still part of the spirit,
just like, for example, the male is born with a foreskin. And then what in some cultures,
what do they do? They cut it off. Right. So when the spirit comes in, it's always it always has
an emotion. And then whether it's dealt with, acknowledged, you know, or cut off, it doesn't
mean that it's separate. You see, it's the same unit. And this is not being there is no science
of it. It's meaning the study of it. It's bundled with psychology. That's what I'm saying. This is
non Freudian, non Jungian. Right. Just like something that doesn't a liquid that reacts
like a solid is called non-Newtonian because it's still trying to preserve the standard BS. Right.
Um, so when here's the thing, we get plenty of examples or try to be specific, how you can't be
general, you have to be specific about the body, the health and all these other things. The spirit
is so specific. And each each individual will who makes me me and makes you you and all the
veritable plethora of people that I've ever been on this planet or whatever are extremely
individualistic, more individualistic than the body and the soul of the body is, let's just say,
but attached to that is the emotional body, let's say. And this is something that is completely,
let's just say there is no science of it. There is psychology, and they blend it, but there is no
science and no discussion. First of all, what is the purpose of it? You know, but then again,
if we speak of the body, okay, what's the purpose of the pinky finger, right? Well, I don't know,
what's the purpose of the thumb? Well, it's an opposing member without a thumb, you can't button
a shirt. What's the purpose of the appendix or whatever? See, so the purpose can be found,
even if what's the pinky finger or the appendix, which is argued, but when we come up to what's the
purpose of emotion, there is not no discussion. Well, right. And even though even the little toe,
you know, where where I've heard people argue that the smallest toe on your foot actually
doesn't serve a purpose, but it does. And it did. You know, and here you go, there is a discuss,
see that what I'm saying is there's no discussion on the purpose of emotion, not discussing emotion,
but the purpose, right. But nonetheless, it's still always part of the situation. So and what
strikes me here is that it would clearly have to be as individual. Like you said, the body, we can
also observe commonalities with the body, right? There is a general given structure, human beings
are bipeds, let's say, okay, so we walk on to two feet, generally speaking, right? This is our normal
construct. There's one head, right? We don't have tails. I mean, there are things five stars,
it's the star configuration, anthropomorphic. And the anthropomorphic representation is in
the pentacle. Yes. But that's the thing is, I think the whole thing is actually represented in
the pentacle, because the circle around it is that atmosphere you were talking about. And each one of
the compartments in the pentacle is a compartment, you know, one section of the star is an arm,
another section is an arm, the top of the star is the head, the two sections on the bottom are
the legs. And it doesn't have to be like an example, an octopus would be far more functional,
right? Well, think about, you know, the one man band, if you're an octopus.
Well, but the pentacle is for the human construct, is what I'm saying.
Well, we've taken it that way. But that's the way I interpret it, that's all. But that's the way I
interpret it, is that's what it is. And that's what it appears to be representing. So I'm just
saying, though, is that the emotion, though, like you said, there is no definition, because I think
it's also individual, like you said, you know, look, everybody's like, we can't generally discuss
health, I don't think you can generally discuss the effectively, you could generally discuss it,
like saying it's seasonal, it's in, you know, don't eat stuff that's toxic, or stay hydrated.
But for each individual person, it's actually far more specific. And it must be a general
knowledge of how specific it is. So it could be applied. So you don't have these general discussions.
But I just want to let's just go back to the, the emotion, there's a lot of talk about emotion.
But there is no talk about the why we were imbued or endowed with it is what I'm trying to say.
And what I have discovered by looking at the behavior is that people do things, you know,
people can you have demographics and people can be categorized, right. And when you hear that person
operating, let's say, out of that norm that they're known to exhibit, it's usually blamed
on what emotion. So it seems like this impetus and it's not part of the body, it's part of the mind.
Right? So what is it? Why do we even have it? Why? What is it doing? What it's doing is it's
tapping in to the way we interact with the environment with the body's ability and super
ability. What I mean about that is, was very popular metaphor given where the 90 pound soccer
mom flips the minivan with the children inside and she's able at that moment of panic,
roll the van back over herself to get the children out. Right? Right. You can get all the 90 pound
soccer moms in the world to lay down a minivan or lay down a minute and have them pick it up.
They can't. But why? What? Well, well, her desire to save the children. Right. Was that
mental? Was it physical? No, it was the emotional component that allowed that to happen.
Right. The mild. Well, you've the postal rate, which is literally the post guy working at the
post office or whatever, goes back on his day off and shoots everyone. Right. Right. Outside
of character. Again, outside of character, outside of I mean, in the case of the soccer mom, you're
talking about something that in the normal circumstance, right in the typical circumstance
is not something that can be achieved, not something that can be accomplished
because a 90 pound woman is not able to lift the car. It's always to lift the car off the kid.
Right. Actually, no one really can. Maybe some elite power lifter can.
Well, it is very difficult. I've seen it done. Small car, you know, lifted up by someone very
strong. Sure. But, you know, so. So what is this emotion? Purpose? Well, it seems that we
the exhibit is we've seen extremely radical behavior come out and actually super physical
behavior. Right. In the case of the soccer mom, that's super physical because from a physics
perspective that she would have torn all of the ligaments in her body, but she was able to do it.
So there's something, quote unquote, supernatural of about the whole interrelation between the
emotional body and the spiritual body, which is the mind interacting with the physical body.
So there's this emotional component. And again, what I'm stressing here is not that there's no
discussion about emotion that's in the psychological field, but there is no discussion intrinsically
about why we have it. And I'm trying to give examples here on it's there. Basically, we don't
know what it is, but we see it exhibited giving super physical powers to the soccer mom or extremely
radical, you know, the guy that goes postal or like the guy who a woman who is super enamored
will do anything for someone that they've, quote unquote, fall in love with. This is all emotional.
And what I'm trying to do is bring up a way of thinking about it rationally, even though all
those things that we mentioned are irrational. There is a rational reason why we have it.
And that is outside of the norm consideration. What I mean by that is that there's no way the
90 pound woman could lift the minivan. There's no reason really, or there's no way someone would go
and shoot all their co workers or fall in love and give up everything they have for an emotion
is so extreme. So outside of forget about normal, just like super physical behaviors and things like
this. This emotion thing should be studied, right. And I've heard in a lot of the black
operations project, there's even TV shows like Stranger Things or whatever, x men or whatever,
where this is not even contemplated, but easily displayed, like when you see, let's go to the
superhero or this the paranormal. If you watch something like x men or the heroes, you know,
they've many things have been in fiction. When Mr. Freeze, for example, or the person who throws
fire or the person who whatever, you notice what before they exhibit their power, they go into a
emotional state, don't they? Right. That's true. And look, I discussed this, like say on my show
with Richard Allen Miller, which is I don't know if you're familiar with that guy. Dr. Ram. Yes,
of course. Okay. So I'm sure we could spend time talking about him if we wanted to, but we're not.
I just mentioned it. Well, here's the thing. I've been on personal calls with him and he did not
like me. So I'm not there to take anyone's thunder away, but yeah, that's fine. But here
is what is legitimate about things that he presents. And that is that he has been able to
instruct people about how to tap into some of that and to change their mindset, so to speak,
to interpret things differently around them and create circumstances by which their behaviors can
be changed, you know, where they can do things that normally would not be, you know, part of
the normal behavior, normal character. Right. Right. And in the physical realm also, not just
the quote unquote mental realm. Well, right. But first he begins with the mind, you know, in his
practice. Right. And what do you have to do? You have to change your mind about the situation first.
You know, I talked to him. Yeah. Yeah. Sorry. Somebody sent me his book, Power Tools for
whatever, whatever. And I didn't I skimmed it. I didn't get anything practical out of it other than
the example of practical examples that he gave. And I didn't find a bit defining what I brought
up, which is why do we have emotions? No, that was the point I was going to get to is that he doesn't
discuss any of the why. Yeah. Why we have emotions. And now that we well, OK, but you may never find
out why. Yeah. Right. But he does talk about and many. But we know enough about it that we could
probably use it just like electricity. But that was that was the point I was trying to get to is
that many people have tried to demonstrate and have demonstrated that if you if you tap into this a bit,
you can willfully change the circumstances, change your own limits of behavior and things.
That's all I'm bringing it up. Yeah, I got you. But I like I said, what I focus like we just did,
let's say, and I have been on the body and all these different subjects, it's because it's
lacking out there. There's no reason to come out and do our project, whether it was the older
Chilean, the Greek, or if I do an interview or even have a discussion, if we're just going to rehash
things that have already been discussed by others. And because I'm not a person, I'm not a
public person. Right. You know, this is not my lot, but I just happen to be because these things,
I think, need to be somehow put out there. But OK, let's get back to the subject at hand in some
capacity, because I don't know why we have them. But I do know that we we know enough about the
effects of strong emotions or even just setting one's emotional state on the rest of the body and
the environment. So what what I came up with, actually, someone else did on one of the private
Skype calls a few years ago, they call it the emo work. It's very easy. Right. Emo. Right. So
what I've discovered on that is that for sure it's part of the spirit. But if you stub your toe or
you're in a lot of pain, it will the body will affect you. It's a two way street. But it comes
with pre preloaded with our spiritual body, our spiritual self, what makes us us. And what's
interesting also, if you read ancient texts, hey, if it says the gods are angry now, what is anger?
It's an emotion. If the gods are happy, it's so apparently the gods are have it as well. OK,
so all of the work, by the way, I don't know how to package this. So it's a continuation. It's a
continual work. The emo work, you know what? OK. Don't know why it comes with the spirit,
what its direct purpose is, but we have enough examples of what can happen when it's used,
which is super physical. So why don't we tap into that? Right. Why don't we start working it? And
the most basic level, the emo work and what I've come up with and really pondering this for about
a decade and a half and in the last five years trying to communicate it to others and then
getting feedback has been tremendous. Right. Right. Just like, for example, speaking of the
body does not absorb anything. It's all by induction. And in getting feedback from others,
there has been tremendous. But still, there is no general field in public discussion about this at
all. So maybe we should get into like a specific example of the how the emotions can be used and
for changing the environment. Well, why not? But the reason why I was just trying to set this up
is that it is important. And I see it in a lot of other people's presentations,
but it's never really explained quite well that, look, your emotional state will affect
every other part. So that's the thing where we could be recording the sonic right now
or doing the sonic. And if someone whispers in your ear some really bad news, it's going to change
your behavior even to the point where you can't continue or the if it's really good news,
it could it might change it again. Exactly. Yeah. Yeah. But that's just on a mild level.
But, you know, of course, someone in constant weather, whatever state it is, will experience
drastic changes in their body. You see, this is beyond that. See, but that's why I brought up
the constant fear point, right, where you're allowing that external input to come in to your
mind. You then have an emotional reaction. And this will change your behaviors. I mean, right.
You've brought this up several times and a lot of people do. I want to address it this way.
If you can, with the fear, maybe we'll help anyone else, because I've been thinking about
the fear thing a lot. So when I hear the fear point, as it doesn't affect me, it's actually
stupid. So it's not the fear point. It's actually the state, the emotional state that it puts the,
let's say, those in the collective. So now when you're dealing with the collective,
they're in that fear state. And because of their lack of awareness or whatever,
they then can become lean on the dangerous side, right? So when it's actually doing the fear,
you know, most people stop with the discussion on the fear point. And that's fine. I usually
avoid it because I don't see it as fear point. I see it as a way to set people up and to keep
them in a state where they could easily be triggered and dangerous, just like you have a dog
that's going to bark or bite. They're doing that with the population. It's part of
self policing. And it's also a part of keeping them, you know, a lot of people say it makes you
unstable. I disagree. I think when you put fear porn on the society, it stabilizes it, but it
stabilizes it in a state of like having a dog, right? That's going to bite, right or bark at
anything. See, and they lack the awareness of what's going on. But that's very well known.
They'll tell you, by the way, I ran into so many people wearing masks. So what it is, I don't care
if it's if it's natural or a weapon, or I don't care. I just I'm just doing it. Okay. Right. So
now it doesn't matter what it is. It could have been slipping on a banana peel. If they're set
up in that emotional state, where they're stabilized in a dangerous, they're ready to
be triggered on that subject, right? Right. So basically, what they're doing is creating an army.
They're militarizing. In other words, they're weaponizing the population with fear porn. I don't
think you've ever heard this explanation. Well, it's actually they're actually weaponizing the
society, right? Usually the alternative media talks about how it's misdirecting. It's not
misdirection at all. Well, I do talk about the old could see the information is false. Yeah,
no weaponizing. I talk about the misdirection. But I go further. And usually, quite frankly,
I don't believe it's being heard. But I try to go further and say, look, the reason why I bring up
the example of like, say, post 911, right, is not because of what the program was, it was the result.
It caused people to instantaneously be ready to attack others, to be in that state where they
could be directed, whether they knew it or not, to do things that was well outside of their normal
character, they became weaponized. Exactly. This is the point of why I try and talk about it,
because so that this is the thing. Yeah, here's the thing when there's no fear porn,
the people are walking around thinking they have blood pressure, and they absorb nutrition,
or when Einstein is genius, or whatever, that's all misinformation, but that so what, you know,
they could be still controlled with that. But when you put fear on the people, you're creating a more
homogenous state. And it's they're easy to make, it's easy to make them reactionary. So I see,
how many times have we said stupid people are dangerous, or a lot of stupid people in a large
crowd, or, you know, whatever, there's many sayings about it, right. So here's the thing,
the collective will never be enlightened, and we're good, we'll get into because if they were,
then there would be no collective, right. So we'll maybe get into the, the emotional aspect of,
of that real, real simple. It's people that are in the collective that fall for the fear porn.
What is the typical comment made about them? They are what asleep? Right? Now, is it really
the sleeping state? They're not asleep. I mean, sleep means you're laying down, eyes closed,
REM state, whatever, whatever. No, they're walking around, they're walking around,
they call them walking dead, or whatever. There's an emotion attached to sleep. It's the emo of
sleep. I'm I feel sleepy, there's an emotional or when you think about what I need to prepare
when I go to sleep, there's an emotion, right? So they're emotionally asleep. It's their emotions
that are asleep. And it's the same with the fear. It's also when they do the fear porn,
it's very important that they don't trigger emotions. They they let them know that this
has been very well thought of, and it's what they should believe, but don't think about it
too much, right? That is the other thing that attaches to that. And they have plenty of things
that if you think about it, you're going to be ridiculed, you're a loose nut,
you're a wing nut or whatever, or you're a conspiracy theorist, right? So you don't want
to be that. Right? So anyway, it's a very difficult subject. But since we're broaching
it here, give an example of the emotional control that or lack of control. But without
even going further on the control of the emotion, you can do a very simple experiment.
How much you could you control something that you know very little about its purpose
is a difficult area to venture. But you know that it's repeatable, right? Just like, though, most
scientists, quote, unquote, if you ask them, explain to me what electricity is,
and you hear all the blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah. If you challenge them on it, you know what
they all finally say is we really don't know what it is, but we know enough about it to use it.
Right? So I always want to land on that with the with the emotion. Why were we you know,
what is it? Why is it attached to the spirit? Why is it attached to the mind? But
I like I said earlier, man repeating myself maybe being redundant, we could see what it does. And
the effects are super physical, supernatural in many cases, as well. So how do you how do you
start wrangling this in? You know, like, how do you like tying your shoelaces, right? If you've
never been if you're an adult, you don't know how to do that. You really have to think about it the
first few times and you may not do it right, right. But this is not a matter of doing it right
or wrong. But let's give an example. With the emotion, for example, you have to pick an emotion.
And when you gesture physically, generally, the emotion comes forward. In other words,
here's the body triggering that what's in reserved or in the on file in the spirit.
When people are sad, you know, there's a old psychological thing is that if you feel depressed
or whatever, tilt your head back, look up towards the ceiling or the sky and smile and hold that
smile for 10 seconds and then just relax, bring your head back down. You don't feel as depressed
or sad, right? Because that smile, you see. So that is a gesture feeling happy. Right now the same
works with the frown. If you are feeling OK or happy and you gesture, let's say a frown.
Hold it for 10 seconds and gesture your body, slot your shoulders and all that.
You will suddenly feel this sadness coming upon you, even though there's no logical or,
you know, rational reason to write. So we see that the body gesture will trigger the emotion.
OK, one the main thing that I introduce on this is most common thing since we just spoke about the
body and health is how many times you hear, especially in the airy fairy community, whatever
this person sick, send them some healing energy. You hear that all the time, all the time. Yeah.
And do the people usually get better? I mean, 99.99% of the time person doesn't get better,
but 0.001% of the time that it was known healing energy was sent and the person got better. That
is totally amplified and exaggerated that it works. Right. You see. So, yeah. So, you know,
they'll give an example. But, you know, if a million people are, you know, do this, why is it
that nothing just like what I religious people pray? Right. Not much comes out of it. But the
one that prayed and it was witnessed that they prayed and this thing happened, this overly
amplified again. So that means it works every time. No. And one of the things to attach to this is
going back to the airy fairy community. Send them some healing energy. The key word there is sending
it. OK, the giving. Right. So when it only let's say this is broadcast on the radio, one person
that can effectively do this will succeed. Very simple. It's the emotional part. Remember,
it led this 90 pound soccer mom to flip the van and do all these supernatural things.
So let's start working with that emotion. We want to send something, a giving feeling. It's a very
gentle giving feeling. The easiest way to gesture that in the physical body, in the being is when
you give someone a hug. Right. You'll notice when you hug someone, you have this rising warmth.
It's like a light feeling that comes through the center of your body and it goes up to your
shoulders and you kind of feel light for a moment. OK. OK. So if there's no one in the room, even if
you're listening to this alone or if you're not, don't you know, you don't have to just imagine
gesturing. If you have to put your arms around right now, let's say physically reach out your
as if there's an imaginary something, someone to hug. You will feel that rising feeling.
It comes up through the solar plexus. You feel light for a moment. OK, that is an emotion. So if
you're hugging, let's say you're at a hug party and you were hugging for a half an hour, you would be
fully drenched in that emotion and you would get high off of it. And it's constantly giving, giving,
giving. And that's the best time to have someone write a check, for example, right after they leave
a hugging party because they just want to give, give, give, give, give. Well, it's also why people
are so generous with their time after an A.A. meeting, because a lot of people hug after the
A.A. meeting or at least they used to. They used to. I don't know if they still do. Yeah, sure. But
I just want to hammer this because the hug, the hug, the hug, because it is very common and
universal. And when you start working with this and you want to communicate it, you want to find
very universal gestures that you can communicate. So let's say you hear about sending so-and-so.
You don't even have to really this is more advanced, but you don't even have to have an
identification, direct identification of who they are. Just imagine you're tapping into what you
heard that person that that person mentioned is enough of an identifier. But we can talk about
identifiers. This gets into the long 12 hour dissertation I can give on this.
But just to open up the subject. Excuse me. Giving the hug will gesture the body emotionally. Yes,
go ahead. No, I was just going to give you a chance to pause there and also say that
it seems to me as though and maybe I'm wrong, but it seems to me as though you need to address
the idea that by observation or by imaging in your own mind, because I was thinking while you
were talking about someone hugging themselves or gesturing, gesturing the hug. If you picture
an embrace that you had in the past, remember it, recall it. Right. You do that. You can also
get a feeling from it. A feeling will be generated by it. And that's something that happens.
And sure. All of it. The idea of sending to someone else, I think, comes from the very real
experience. The idea comes from the very real experience that when you're in a room with
someone, people commonly talk about anxiety now. Right. If someone is acting nervously around you,
OK, you observe it. A lot of people and to varying degrees, most people that I know in some way will
be affected by someone who's, you know, antsy. They're they're they're moving around. It's
contagious, like a yawn. It becomes a contagious thing. So it seems to me as though other people's
gestures that are observed and interpreted can also cause this to happen. But it's not a direct
transference like, you know, I'm beaming this to you. It's more of, again, induction. Right.
Well, it's it is it is very much. But let's go back to it. So maybe I'm running through this
too slow of a pace. So when you're in that state, when you feel that emotional rise through the
body, you think about what you were requested to do to send healing energy to so and so.
And while you're in that gesture, you make a request and a demand or however, actually demands
work better than requests that now that I am feeling this right, you don't have to. However,
you do it. I'm my body is in that state of giving. That's when you evoke the thought of what you'd
like to manifest. Basically, this person healing. But that that is, again, very general. So one,
the easiest way to do the healing energy is once you gesture a hug or you can do it without putting
your hands in front of us, get that rise, that emotion to come up. Imagine that person, whether
you know them or not, to for their body to be back in a more perfect state as they were when they were
18 years old. This is where it comes in, where you have there's work involved. If you know the person
75 and they broke their hip or whatever, you say, well, I'd like to bring this person back,
demand that towards them, towards where you heard this or where this person is while you're in that
emotional state of giving that they are, their body is back to how it was at 18. But if you know
more about it, and let's say they had a hereditary thing, they weren't good at 18 back to the womb,
how they were when they were just born their body renewed. Right? The what I hear very often in the
community is they mentioned the ailment, that it should go away. And I would suggest stay away from
all of that. And just have a do a replication or a past condition this person when they were more
perfect, be evoked towards them, you see? Now, what if it was something that they had when they were
born, then you have to go back several generations to before it showed up in the family line. So this
is where it becomes very specific. You see, just like the health thing, what do you want to do?
When do you have the pain you see? So this is where the the email work is very is a very big field.
And it's very practical. But essentially, the the giving feeling is when is the giving is when you
would send out and broadcast coherently and directly towards the subject, whatever it is,
it can even be a group of people. Okay. And that is the carrier wave. If you once the body is
in the condition of that particular emotion, then it becomes very effective, really,
really effective. And I could sit here for the next four hours to give examples and, you know,
real stories and things from myself and other people. So I think at this point, maybe we'll
give another example. What do you think? Well, I was going to just ask you about the the inverse
of that sentiment where and this this might touch on something that you don't want to go in depth on
right on this episode. But let's just hit it anyway. You tell me. But fact is that people
also in the airy fairy community will talk about when you need to do, let's say, balance things out
or do some harm to someone who's harmed you. Right. So what do they do? They say, oh, well,
picture them in your mind. Right. Having a problem, say. Right. But that but how many times has that
been done and it doesn't work? Well, and how many? And again, when it does work, it's over amplified
safe. Well, that's I was just trying to point out that it's about the same thing. It's just
that it's in a different direction. But some people think of it as a completely different thing.
But isn't it virtually the same? It's just, you know, objectively.
You're sure it would still be the giving energy. Yeah. But it would be technically it would be.
Sorry. Yeah. I was just saying you're giving something bad instead of good. But still,
it's the same. Sure. Sure. You can heal. You can kill. You can make sick. You can make happy. You
can. Yeah. This has been by the way, there is a guy named Samuel Chong. He translated a book
called 334 Lies out of German. It's very hard to get get an Amazon. I haven't read it yet. I might
get it about the confessions of an Illuminati or whatever. But listening to Samuel Chong talk about
it, he said, basically, they have superpowers. Basically, they can mind control other people
and they could make people they could do all kinds of things. And they're trained from a young child.
And I'm like, well, what could it be? It has to be an emotional carrier that they're trained in.
You see the same with the Jedi in Star Wars. Right. They're trained from a young child. And
they in the movies and in the books, I guess they portrayed as a feeling of the force and all that.
What I'm trying to do here is show that there is a point of discovery where how the emotional
the existence of emotions attached to the mind have led to super physical and supernatural
possibilities and events taking place. Right. So. Well, no, it does. It does happen. I was
just pointing out that there's you know, this thing can slide in all directions. It's still.
Oh, yes, it has. And to publicly get into showing both directions is really the objective way to
do it. But but don't you know, I mean, that's why they have guns, right? Or whatever. And this is
in the mind in all of the mind. It's in the field of psychology. But this would be like
ultra psychology, let's say, because it's not discussed in open circles.
But the each emotion has a different carrier for a different objective. Right. Give another example.
How many times do you hear again in the airy fairy community guard yourself, protect yourself, right?
Oh, yeah. A lot of stuff about protecting yourself. And it goes everywhere from the
physical gesture of, you know, a circle assault, which is the most common trope I can think of
on Yeah, go ahead. Yeah, that's very powerful. The circle of salt because it's a Yeah, that's a
pretty big discussion. I don't know much about it. But when we get into gesturing,
it is really the gesture. Right. And also what salt does the properties of salt, right? Why not
a circle of gold coins, or urine or whatever, because it's what salt the properties of salt?
Oh, not as though all those things don't have useful purposes. But go ahead.
Yeah. So yeah, so the protect yourself is a major Well, you know, what I hear, I'm addressing the
main like tropes that are out there, which is give healing energy. Other one is regard yourself,
protect yourself. Okay, so what I've discovered with the guarding yourself, this is going to
maybe shock some people. But this is what I've discovered you if anyone has any other ideas,
I'd like to hear them. But you're you're in the it's the form of protection. The most mild one is
you're in grade school, and you haven't done your homework and the teacher calls on you
with a question regarding the homework. You're like, Oh, no, I knew I was going to be called.
And now I don't know what to say. And I'm caught. Right? Right. Okay, at that point,
it goes both ways, it goes into protecting yourself, but you're extremely vulnerable.
So the next level to evoke is denial. We've always been told, don't deny it. Or,
you know, actually, in the legal system, if you don't deny something that's accepted as true.
Right. So the ease just like the hug was the gesturing forgiving the protection emotion to
clothe oneself in would be the denial like when you are accused of doing something,
right, you took the cookies out of the jar, and you deny it. As you're here, as just as the
accusation stops, and you're ready to produce the denial, there's an emotion that comes over. It's
almost like a slick feeling like a, like a taut sheet of plastic. It's kind of cool. It's thin,
but you know, it will stop many things. It's a denial. There's many, I'm just giving you like a
tactile feeling of that emotion, right? It's a stillness and almost like not a coldness,
but a cooling down a very even feeling when you deny something, right? So when you set up that
feeling of denial, that actually is a protection, then ask for yourself to be protected,
generally from other incoming things, even physical, right? But you maintain that motion
of denial. It sounds bizarre, doesn't it? Because we're taught denial is a bad thing. But I'm telling
you, in the legal community, denying things is okay, right? You hear it all the time. Right.
So, so the interesting thing, so imagine actually in to make it even stronger, which goes into
almost the falsehood aspect. Imagine that you're accused of something that you did actually,
but you're still denying it, right? Because you don't want to suffer the consequences
is also similar, because some people have been in both worlds where they've been,
they've done something and denied doing it and haven't been falsely accused, let's say,
didn't really do it and they but they have to, as a defense produced denial, there's an emotion
that comes when you are denying something, opposing it, that emotional state is the protection state.
So if you're going into a situation where you know, you're going to be either verbally,
emotionally or physically attacked, you bring up that emotion of denial, like no,
right, you're warding off that there's an emotion to it. I'm actually trying to gesture right now
as we're speaking. And I feel it. But typically what you feel it's, it's a very even this,
it's a cooling down and almost rigidity, but you're still can move. Are you with me on that? Are you
getting something like that? Yeah, no, I understand what you're saying. I'm not different than the
hug. Very different, right? No, I get that. What are you getting from it? Well, I'm not getting
anything from it. I'm just putting the idea in my mind and observing that, that that's a
possibility, but I'm not actually getting anything from it at the moment. Honestly.
Okay, so if you were to gesture, okay, so okay, so I see it's subtle, it's more subtle than the
gesturing the hug, but that would be the general emotion state to produce the protection layer.
Because think about it when you're accused of something and you're denying it, whether you did
it or not, that is a level of protection, just like in the legal system. If you don't deny it,
then it's accepted that you are guilty of it or have committed that, right?
Right. Well, denial, denial is definitely important. And that's the thing. So denial
is protection. I, I get the concept. No, it's not protection. It's, it's what you're,
you're bringing up the thought of denial to evoke the emotion that when you are denying something,
and that is the emotional field where one carries the protective layer on, you see,
but you see, this is a, this is all, I'm using terms that we're all familiar with,
but the application of them are very unfamiliar. You know, the application is completely unfamiliar.
That's why I'm, I'm trying to reassemble this in my mind. Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
Yeah. So like, like Chuck, you know, we're, we're thousands of miles apart, you know,
you stole my calculator, right? What do you say? Well, I don't know how I could have done that.
Right. Or no, I didn't do it. I don't know how I could. Yeah. But you'd be more firm with it.
You'll see there's a feeling when you bring that up, that emotion, right? Yeah. Okay. Okay. I get
it. Because when you're denying something, it does create a, yeah. Okay. It's the, what is evoked
emotionally? Just like when you're gesturing a hug, even if no one's there, it brings up this
rise. That's the giving feeling. That's the giving feeling, but I'm giving a feeling of deflection
really, where it's like, look, that can't touch me because that is, yeah, that's what I'm feeling.
Right. But you're doing this as a general setup, almost like a four field, because we don't know
what that is usually like going back to the airy fairy comments, just put some guard yourself.
We don't know what that is yet. Right. So this is a very general non-specific state,
but it's even better if you're going into a very specific state, you see,
like, for example, people that are going into a debate are ready to deny what their opponent is
saying, right. Or counter it. This is a little different than that. This is very simple.
Well, no, no, no. I, I, that, that's a different state of mind. I'm saying that though my reaction
and I'm having a reaction as opposed to preparing myself, which is a different thing.
Uh, so. Well, it's more than a reaction. It's the emotional aspect of it.
Yeah, no, but that's what I'm saying. The emotional reaction. I'm trying to describe it,
but I'm, I'm, I'm apparently not communicating it too well, but what I'm saying is I'm having a
reaction as opposed to preparing myself, which is a different emotional state. I believe if you feel
prepared, I mean, and you'll note that if you go into something fully prepared, as opposed to not,
uh, you, you have a different emotional state that is generally noted all around, right?
Uh, if you feel prepared, you come in kind of confident, you're a little more relaxed,
people would say, right. So there's a difference there. Now, simply reacting to something that's
happening as it's happening creates a different emotional state, right? But then you're not,
you see, when you understand the power of the emotions, then we go into the realm of the
supernatural and the super physical, like the 90 pound soccer mom that flips the van over.
Here we are continuing with the second sonic event. And, uh, I, I gotta say it was a fascinating
point. We stopped at because we had gotten into denial. And I was mentioning that there is a
reactive denial and there's a prepared denial. And the Greek was talking about, well, if you're in
court, right, and you're being charged, or if somebody accuses you of something, you have a
reaction. Now that's a good way to relate it to, uh, to one's own experience. But is there a
difference here? I mean, how, how, how do we continue to, yeah. Yeah, we're, we're basically,
it's an element, let's just call it an element, meaning it can't be broken down any further,
even though it can be changed. The element, one of the elements of the spirit and the mind
is the emotional component. And by the way, uh, different, uh, spirits and different beings and
creatures come pre-downloaded with knowledge. We don't, right. We have to learn everything as we
come into this world because the knowledge is in the spirit, in the mind, but not to mistake the
brain for the mind either. Okay. So this is the, that brain is solely part of the body. But again,
the emotional component is attached to the spirit and there is no reason that has been discussed
of why it's there. I mean, of course it's in literature, it's in romance, it's in culture
that, you know, we're emotional beings and also that the Vulcans and other cultures in fiction
try to eliminate it because it's potential irrationality. But what I'm saying is that
there is no reason for why we have emotions that's been discussed. And I, through experimentation and
thought experiments, of course, and practice have figured out that it is a way to actually
manifest things into the physical reality, manifest them through a form of movement.
So we discuss movements. There is a psychic movement that we hear about and there is the
emotional movement that sets up the environment to accept what we want to project into it. So the two
examples was the giving and the other one was the protection or the, which comes through the emotion
of denial. There are many, many, many, many emotions. You know, after we spoke a little bit,
I looked up online the list of emotions. They give only six emotions. How ridiculous. And then they
give lists of feelings. So whenever you see something as prominent as the emotional body
of the spirit, not to really say that it's a body, but it's part of the spirit. And it's almost
obscured in the information or the data packets that they give online or reference material.
Again, I think that's deliberate. Something is being hidden. A lot of the ancient cultures,
you'll find that in there, either we want to call it mythological or religious texts or whatever,
the gods have the potential of manifesting things in various states of emotion.
So just to add that in the sonic event is very important because we can, we have talked about
spirit, soul and body, but never really leaned heavily on how the emotional function works.
And this is a special project, by the way, because we can discuss just the emo work for eight hours.
I just wanted to bring this up because many people are affected by it. It goes both ways.
We were speaking about when you gesture a hug, it sets you up for giving and projecting,
which also being very happy sets that up. Then the protection, which is the next most typical
one. If you understand the feeling that you have of emotion when you deny something, that is the
protective emotional carrier. So then you put out what you'd like to be protected from,
or a general protection, almost like a force field. But most people are aware of,
through especially since the 80s, there was a book called Subliminal Seduction
on how the advertising industry manipulates the public through advertising, right? Like drink
Coke, between every 15 frames in the film, they'll have a flashing image and your mind picks
it up, right? Right. Also, when a clock is present in a public space, it makes you conscious of time
and makes you more conscious of what you're doing. For example, if you have a small business
and you have a problem with point of sale theft, petty theft, people just pocketing stuff and
not being able to find it out, you thwart that by opposite the entranceway, you have a very large
clock. So you enter the space, the store, and you cannot help but notice the clock in the back. That
will thwart petty theft, believe it or not. Another emotional thing that's used, and by
the way, the person is not really aware of it. They might come in thinking going into a store
to hawk a candy bar, but because the clock is there, they say, it doesn't feel like the right
place to do it, and they leave, right? And I've done this with maybe two dozen businesses that
I said, put a big clock there. We just go and get the biggest possible clock. It doesn't matter if
it's four feet in diameter. If it fits on the wall, put it there. It's really gaudy. And they all
reported the theft went down every single time. Another one is fast food restaurants. They don't
want patrons sitting in a small space after they have their burger or whatever, and sitting and
lingering. So they paint all the colors that are chosen are these gaudy greens and oranges,
right? Very unappetizing colors, right? To deflect the patrons from spending much time there.
This is also part of the emo. So it's colors, it's shapes, it's devices, and the subliminal
seduction, right? Where you're subject to a microsecond or a millisecond flash of something.
You don't cognitively see it, but it's there. That affects the emotional body of the spirit
or of the mind. So this is an entire special ops project, call it Greek-speak or it's only in the
Greek special ops, and it's a study that I'm kind of going back and forth. Maybe it should be
in a book where it could be referenced or sonic events that could be referenced.
But I felt like this had a very, very prominent part of the way we exist, the emotional body,
that is not discussed in this way. Well, it certainly does. And you know, look,
it requires examination because it is key to so much of what is done. And I was thinking about
this, the why. You know, like you said, nobody talks about the why. And I was thinking, well,
perhaps because it should be self-evident. And maybe this is, again, one of my juvenile ideas.
But it seems to me as though the why this is there is about, well,
how do you call the species to propagate, right, to continue to breed? I think a lot of these
triggers have to do with that. I think a lot of these emotional keys have to do with that. So
you're encouraged to go back to that, Chuck, to propagate. You know, you're going to propagate
more readily when you're enamored, right? Well, you're turned on emotionally in a positive state.
As a matter of fact, if you're in too much of a negative emotion, the sperm and the ovum
stop being fertile, right? It literally has a physical element to it. It plays out physically,
just like, you know, not just you react and by gesturing, but your body will change based on
your emotional state. Sure, but stay with the propagating. What is that formative? It's
creation. So like the gods create when they're happy and they also create destruction when
they're not happy. So it is part of the formative, creative aspect of the spirit.
So, yeah, propagation is a great example on that. Well, propagation in itself, you know,
anyway, is one subject that again... And self-preservation too. Both of these things
are essential, right? Because look, if you can't continue the species, there's not much history to
discuss. If you can't protect the species that is there, if you're not triggered to protect your
children, yourself and everything else, you're going to get eaten. I mean, even if we go back
to the caveman example, so to speak, right? You would say, well, look, if you're not encouraged
by your emotions to protect the family, the core, the tribe, whatever, you know, the other animals
are going to come along and pick you off, right? Yeah, so that's the conventional. Let me just
expand that a little bit. When you start noticing that we're in a waiting room situation,
we're subject to all these anti-human forces here since the beginning in this epoch,
and you realize the difference between the spirit, the soul and the body. And, you know, the way you
pay rent is by food, clothing, shelter, right? You have to maintain the food, clothing, shelter
for the spirit to be animated. When you ditch the body and the soul, let's say at death, the spirit
is still there. I mean, it's disanimated. It can be destroyed by special means,
but essentially you go on. Now, whatever existential belief you have, I assure you the spirit goes on
unless it's thwarted and hampered not to. So, are we really the species? We're not.
We're manifesting in this particular thing. So, one side of me is like, screw the species,
let's get this over. As far as Greek-speak goes, I tell people not to propagate. By the way,
the worldwide strike, just don't do anything for three days, you know, don't work, don't use banking,
you know, don't turn on the electricity, don't use banking, don't turn on the water,
right? Don't turn on the TV, don't use banking. You see what I mean? If you stop all that for
three and especially don't have children, you know what the elites are going to do? They're
going to perk up, right? Especially no children, right? They're going to listen. They're going to
say, okay, what do you guys want, right? But from the formative and creative perspective,
what I'm suggesting is once the emotional state is recognized that's appropriate for what you
would like to do, that carries that energy and manifests very much like, again, the X-Men or
the hero type thing. You notice before they perform whatever special function they can do,
they either cringe or yell or they get into a Mr. Freeze state or fire state or whatever.
There's an emotional reaction there and also it's used against us and we can use it for us.
Right. Even the Hulk has to get angry before he turns green and pops up, right?
There you go. Yeah, you'll see it. That's the thing they all have in common. Even
inanimate in a pathetic fashion in machines also tend to exhibit some sort of pre-reaction. So,
in art, in literature, cartoons, whatever, anime. So, here's the interesting part.
We've been bouncing around the metabolism, which is the soul, the breath, the body and the spirit
and kind of lean heavily on the emotional part because when you say emotion, it goes into the
airy-fairy category and I'd like to filter it through that category and make it usable.
What all this talk essentially is about is so you can view the parade from a helicopter
instead of on the ground. I think I've given the analogy before, a helicopter is a time machine.
If you're on the ground viewing a parade and you want to find out what the last float is,
especially in a big parade, you have to wait four hours. But if you have a friend in a helicopter,
you give him a call and he sees the parade, the front and the back of it all in one time
and he could tell you what the last float is and to everyone else, you seem like you know the future,
but you don't. So, not necessarily for knowing the future, but you're going to rise above,
you're going to have a high vantage point. So, again, with the body, we spoke about
how if you look, download a cross-section or bring up a cross-section, put in steel-belted
tire cross-section, automotive tire cross-section and just study it. You'll see layers and rubber,
it's thick, whatever, whatever. And then do a cross-section of the human intestine or lung
tissue or whatever. It's like as if the same engineer put that together and neither one,
anything is absorbed or passes through unless there's a failure. So, we know the body is a
complete sealed system. So, when you have a cut in a tire, what's the first thing you want to do
or puncture? You want to seal it up. So, it could go back to its function. Now,
the same thing with the body. You notice even a child will tell you or anyone young will tell you
if you have a cut or a puncture in your skin, you put a bandage on it, but it's almost like a custom.
But really, what you want to do is maintain that pressure difference from the internal body to the
outside body and the only way you could do that, I mean, can you put a loose piece of duct tape on
a car tire? No, because it can't handle what? It can't handle the pressure difference.
Right. Same thing with bandages and wrappings. You make them as tight as possible
without cutting off all the circulation and if it's a severe injury, you want to make it so tight
that you monitor the extremities and when they start to go numb and turn blue or purple,
you release it so the flow returns and then you again make it tight and then you release it until
you'll see the wound starts to close and heal. Now, I mentioned I don't like to give personal
stories, but I had a very sharp axe. Anything that I have that cuts, a scissor, an axe,
a knife is all razor sharp. I maintain them very, very well. I'm holding a log with my left hand
leaning over and I'm shaving and gleaning the little branches off before I start chopping it
with my right hand. I go a little too far and the axe swings into my left thumb that's facing the axe
and it slices the entire below the nail down to the palm open to the bone.
The blood is instant and all that. You have a pulse in your thumb, right? It looks like
who are those Monty Python guys, right? You're losing quite a bit of blood. Anyway,
I go in a little bit of a panic, but I know what to do. I need to seal that up.
If I gave you an image of what it looked like, it would look totally normal,
but if I outlined where the injury was, you would see it like a palm line. I've done nerve damage.
My thumb is numb. You know how the feeling you have when your leg or hand falls asleep or your
arm falls asleep? Well, my thumb is asleep. I have an acquaintance who is a neurosurgeon. He
says, well, I could probably come back. If not, he'll deal with it. I'm like, no, no, no. It's
too obtrusive, right? So what does this mean? Well, first of all, if this happened to your
normie, you know what would happen. Not only would they say you have to go to the hospital,
they would call for an ambulance, right? Which is a $1,000 cab ride, right?
And what happens? They have you sitting there. They wrap it real loose and in two hours later,
they might give you a bunch of stitches, which will look like, you know, you're not going to
go to a plastic surgeon for that. It's not going to heal well. It's not going to look like it
ever happened. They might even offer you neurosurgery. So I just gave this example because,
by the way, I've also done a tibial compound fracture. That's all. I'm going to stop right
there. And the person was able to walk on it in two weeks, where if you had gone to a hospital,
they put pins in it and you'd be on crutches for six months. This is all by wrapping it really,
really tight, but being smart about it, right? And I'm talking tourniquet tight in the beginning
because you're sealing it up. What happens is with the physical body, there are impulses in
the brain, the management system, and in the heart. By the way, when you have a cut, you know,
there are platelets that come through the blood to seal, supposedly. They don't really do that,
but they do a little bit more. Those platelets are shed from the heart. So when people are losing a
lot of blood, they literally can go through a heart attack because the heart is trying to
shed all those platelets to send. You see what I mean? Okay. The other thing is when blood tests
are done, they look at, oh, these are red cells. These are white cells. These are this, this is
lymphatic fluid. This is right. You know, they just, whatever. Okay. Well, what they don't see,
which is a study is when you see a red blood cell, do they see that this one is for the ear?
This one's for the big toe. This one's for the liver. No, they don't. No, there is a way to
discern that though. It's actually very simple. So once you start studying this, the human body
and seeing that it all relies on a pressure differential in order for it to work right,
just like a car tire, then you can go to the stuff that I just discussed. Where do we know? How does
the wound heal from platelets? What the different types of blood and all that. So it all gets
wrapped up. But no matter what you study about biology, you must understand that there is a
pressure differential. It's called a, well, I like to call it a biological vacuum. Anything
that's alive forms a vacuum, right? So now we understand that, right? When you eat seasonally,
you're taking in food that will regenerate the body based on the environment that the body is in,
right? I think we've gone over this. So if you, if it's cold outside and you eat tropical fruit,
what happens? You're going to be adjusted to a tropical climate. You're in the cold.
What's the first symptom? Well, you're going to feel colder. You're going to feel colder. And
then the next symptom, you get congestion. Your nose starts running. You get mucus children,
especially, right? Right. Okay. More quickly. All right. If you understand when a woman is in
gestation, she has a baby right at the cervix. What keeps the baby from falling out and all the
liquid? You could look it up and you look at the drawing and it says, it's a mucus plug.
Just like you have a plug on a bottle of wine or something or something to keep it closed.
Okay. So the mucus developing in the body is a signal that you're losing what? You're losing
vacuum. It's trying to plug up and it's trying to tell you, look, all these holes you have in
your body, I'm going to start plugging them up because you're not working with me here. So I
need to a signal you that you're, um, I'm plugging up your holes because you're not
be getting the hint that you're losing vacuum. So when you switch back to eating food,
the biological food, uh, that is, uh, within the same environment, the vacuum will be restored.
It's very, very simple, but it's so simple. That is a complete, imagine a fork in the road.
You have the materialist takes one fork. You know, the, the main, the main road is
what makes our bodies work health and all these other things. There's one fork in the road.
That's the materialist. It's all chemical. And the other fork in the road is the biological
vacuum and it's energetic and the chemicals are also included in that. So this is a huge study.
And by the way, I've been leaning and hammering on this publicly with people locally on the
internet, on the phone for over 20 years. And I, no one's ever come back and said, Hey Greek,
we need to start a study and Institute something around this. Right. And it still hasn't happened.
So it tells me it's not, this is not the right planet, the right society or whatever for this,
but it doesn't mean we can't talk about it on the Sonic, these basic things.
Well, right. Which leads me to a question by the way, because I understand the,
the concept of look, eat the thing that has grown locally at that time. Because
if you eat with the season, then it makes sense that that's what would be
created by induction in your body. It would be natural in the environment,
in the atmosphere of your body and in the atmosphere that your body is in.
But you can, but yes, you said something very important, but there are exceptions
that are also inclusive. Okay. So let's say we go out, Chuck, you want to have some burgers?
Well, let's go have some burgers. That was the thing I wanted to get to is the meat
because okay. Wouldn't that mean, hold on for you. Remember, hold on. This is very important.
Eating seasonally, things that are grown. All right. We're going to burger. I'm going to order.
Do I say I want mine with milk and cucumber, or do I say I want mine with a pickle and some cheese,
pickle and cheese, right? I didn't say, I didn't say cucumber and milk. No. Right. If you tell
someone you want some cucumber and milk on your burger, well, what's a pickle? The pickle that
they serve traditionally with burgers is a cured cucumber, cucumber. Okay. So when you cure it,
you change it completely. If you take a slice of cucumber, fresh or in the fridge or whatever,
and a slice of pickle and they're cured different ways and preserved different ways,
they taste completely different. Might as well be a completely different animal. Right.
Right. So when you have a cheese and you have milk, there's almost no similarity unless someone
tells you they both come from a cow. Okay. So when the milk becomes cheese, it's completely
transmuted. I mean, it becomes a completely different. So cucumbers are grown seasonally.
Right. But when you pickle it, we just, right, you can have it off season, but you shouldn't
have the fresh cucumber brought over from a warm place when you're in a cold place.
Do you see, you see how the exceptions work here? Look, the people that lived out on the range in
the country or whatever, what do they do? The farmers, they, in the winter, they, they pickle
everything, right? They preserve it. They canned and pickled one way or the other. Canned and
pickled. And they eat that in the winter and they're still doing fine. So there is a natural
system here. So yeah, it's, it's, so it's the change that makes it. The same goes for many of
the tropical foods, but it doesn't hold true when you refine it. They say sugar rots your teeth.
Bologna doesn't do that at all. What happens is the sugar that you add to foods or the sugar
itself, because they talk, let's talk about real cane sugar here or whatever. It's separated from
the plant, which, and when it's in the plant, it's attached to minerals, water, protein, fiber,
and refined when you put it in your body. Okay. Well, when it's refined, it's in a,
it's in a dry package. It's not attached. It's just itself. And maybe it touches the
wrapping or the container. Once you put it in your body, the sugar from an energetic point of
view says, Hey, look at all this water. I remember being in water. Look at all this protein and all
this starch and all this fiber. I remember being around that. Let me grab some of that. You see,
and attach to it. And that you see, so now it's robbing you or attaching or depleting you of all
the other things that it needs when it was not refined to be itself. And that's why it rots your
teeth. You see, so the refined foods. So the same thing happens with medicine. See,
if someone has a illness or an ailment and they find a plant that treats it or cures it,
you give it to a materialist or actually just most people. And they'll say, we need to, we need to
do an assay, break it down and find the active ingredient. Does it work? No, very rarely. What
it'll work in the way, the same way fertilizers do on crops. You know how they use the nitrate
based fertilizers and farms, the chemical based fertilizers. They think they're getting more
growth. All it's doing is getting the plants high. It's not creating more growth because,
you know, if you use that same system for more than two or three years, what happens,
right? The crops do not work, do very well. So they blame it on their formulation. It has to do
with it being synthesized. So in essence, when you understand this, you don't have to even be
in the study of it. Just the sonic is enough that if you understand this and comprehend it
even better, you'll be able to apply it. You see? Well, see, that's why when they say a naturally
occurring sugar in a food already, it has all those other things attached to it. So it doesn't
seek to rob the body in order to recreate itself effectively. I mean, from a certain point of view,
that's the way it could be described, right? Sure. I mean, look, for example, even in a car,
they have carbon buildup. It gets dirty when they burn clean gasoline. Well, what does clean
gasoline look like when it's in the ground? It's brown and black. That's why if you run a car long
enough, the inside where the gasoline is supposed to be, it turns brown and black. Everything wants
to go back to that. So anyway, there's an old lascivious joke. All the men, they come out of
it and they try to spend their whole lives to get back in it, right? Oh, yeah. Yeah. So, you know,
it's this really strange. And it's not duality. It's all about direction and pressure and all
this. When you have two things next to each other and there's a pressure differential,
they want to equalize the one with the high pressure is going to go to. You could either
raise the pressure of one to go against the other, or you could lower the pressure of one
to go against the other. Right. So this is basically the the crux of all this, because as we continue
with sonic events, people are going to be, you know, we'll make a comment or a remark
on something and it attaches to this very thing that we've been discussing on this particular
sonic. We have brought this up before, but you cannot separate the the body, the health of the
body, which is the metabolism and the mind. But they must be known as separate things. It's really
the original trinity. You see, all of these religions are allegory. You know how they have
Trinitarian based stuff. It's it's no, we do have a it's not a duality. It's a it's a three part
that makes us. But the thing that is that the three parts are working, actually, two parts are
working to preserve the spirit, the mind, because the mind can be transferred. Right. And this
sounds a little crazy, but we give many fictional examples. So the the soul and the body are not
important. It's the spirit that's important, not because we make it important, because it's what
the soul and the body, you know, the breath and the body are there to animate. No, I understand
all this. But back to the one question I had about the meat, right, which is, wouldn't it be more
proper than to consume an animal which is freshly killed? Because, again, look, people often say,
well, I'm a carnivore. You're not a carnivore. You're you're you're a carry on eater because
you're eating something that's dead for a bit. OK, carnivore eats things that are alive.
All right. So that's right. But the bottom line on this is, doesn't it make more sense not to
freeze? Now, does that change it? If you freeze meat? Probably getting into preparation.
Overall, if it has eyeball and a heart and lungs, you're it's a it's a different type of being. It's
to a certain way. What law form do you function in? Because, by the way, cannibalism is alive and
well. And I would I would tell you that maybe two to five percent of the world population is
engaged in cannibalism, at least two to five percent. And it's not really well known. And
I mean, straight up cannibalism. Right. OK, so. What I mean by your law form is just that
a food preparation is a whole different thing. Like it give you the eating. If you can avoid
like, for example, in the biblical text, it indirectly promotes vegetarianism indirectly.
It doesn't tell you you shouldn't eat meat, but it says that if you touch the flesh of a of a
dead animal, you are in an unclean state until noon, you know, the next day when you wash.
Right. And most people say, well, I'm not going to be touching any unclean animals while they're
eating a chicken sandwich. If you're eating a chicken sandwich or a fish sandwich, are you
touching the flesh of a dead animal? The answer is yes. So. Yeah. Yeah. So if the biblical text
actually promotes indirectly. Indirectly, I mean, doesn't come out and say it in many ways to be
to eat vegetable, but there is a certain hierarchy in the animal kingdom and the biological kingdom,
like each what we call lower life or manifestation aspires to be the next. So if you go into the
kingdom, the plants want to be like animals and the animals want to be like humans and the humans
want to be like gods. Right. You see how each one aspires to the next, like a child wants to be
like the parents. OK. For example. OK. Now, plants are the most readily available to be eaten. Right.
By every everything and everyone, let's say they're always constantly in this dream state.
So imagine you're dreaming as a human. Right. And you're a plant. And, you know,
here comes this thing and it bites off your arm, starts chewing on it. You're like, oh,
man, that was really that wasn't too cool. You're OK with it. Right. Because you're in this dream
state. By the way, when people take all these naturally, if you indulge in that kind of thing,
hallucinogenics or whatever, where do those things come from? Plants. Interesting. Right.
So then you have the animals, the animal state. Right. You know, at one point,
animals were not afraid of humans. Actually, if you go to certain parts of the world, they're not.
You know, if you go down to Antarctica or North Pole, penguins, seals,
polar bears on the other end, they're not afraid of humans. They don't run away. Right. Certain
places, they're not. But at that point, they feel like they could relate. And only other certain
places they run naturally, like deer in the forest. You know, you have a certain innocent demeanor
with some people, you know, when the butterfly lands on a little girl's nose and there's a wild
bull or a bull in a ranch that will just gourd anyone except for this little girl's best friend.
You know, there are these spiritual connections also. But the the animals, by virtue of them,
let's say, meaning to be domesticated. You see, and working with humans is the next level.
And then the humans wanting to be like a godlike state or whatever, even when
in certain religious practices, when they say they want to ascend, you hear that a lot,
that ascension stuff. Well, what they don't know is if when you study the text that actually it's
a very selfish thing to do, because in the in the Buddha's Sapa, when you do approach nirvana
and ascend right before you're ready to enter, you're supposed to say, out of selflessness,
I need to go back and not ascend myself and help the others. So you never really do ascend. I mean,
a true master would not do that. It would be selfish, you see. So anyway, I think that's
pretty much the, you know, the wrap on this particular sonic, because I've always wanted to
say the same thing different ways, but also implore the listener that how important this is to myself
and to them has yet to be realized. An example of that is if you injure yourself physically
enough, you go into a panic, you may not do what you tell other people, do you have to actually
make a very big concerted effort to remind yourself, hey, dummy, no matter how bad this
looks, you know what to do, do it. It's kind of hard to do it. That's always my first order of
business upon an injury to myself or someone around me is is I first have to shut that down.
That that panic reaction, that's my first order of business, right? You know, because otherwise,
I'm not thinking clearly, and I'm not going to do the right thing. And I might just react. And
yeah, no, like like you said about the personal story about splitting your hand.
You know, the first thing to say is, I know that I need to take care of this a certain way.
You know, and you don't do that if you're going, oh, I'm bleeding, I'm bleeding, you know, it's
it's kind of hard to do, you know, the worse the injury, the more easier it is to go into shock.
And, you know, when someone has a bad injury, the last thing you want to do is let them see
the injury because they'll go into shock and you can die from that. But it wasn't that bad,
but borderline, but but also, you know, eating seasonally, you know, when you're,
you might have a craving for something and it's out of season. Learn in the beginning,
train yourself to, to not, it's difficult in the beginning, like with anything until you
until you it becomes natural not to. Like, for example, there's many people have heard me speak,
and I'm like an Old Testament kind of guy. And I don't know pork on my fork, right?
And let's say you enjoyed pork products before and you decide that you're not going to do that
anymore. Right? Well, it's in everything, by the way, if you see gelatin on an ingredient,
if it doesn't say bovine gelatin, it's pork gelatin, right? And even Altoids, breath mints,
candies, right? Oh, yeah, there's pork in that. So So anyway, in the beginning, it's going to
be difficult. But once you train yourself, and it's also like shrimp, lobster, clams, oysters,
right? Because if it comes out of the water, it should have fins and scales.
And I'll say that again, if it comes out of the water, if it lives in the water, it has to have
what should have fins and scales. Right? So obviously, clams don't know these other, you
know, and catfish, shark, well, they have fins, but they don't have scales. They have a skin
eel, right? Well, so in the beginning, you might have enjoyed these things before. And in the
beginning, you're it's going to seem like you're depriving yourself of something that you enjoyed.
And then you're living in a world that you want to enjoy as much as possible when you know,
it's opportune to Well, I noticed that after a few years of not doing this or less, I didn't
even view it as food anymore. Well, see, there's an interesting thing too, because
Alright, so I think this is a helpful hint, but maybe it's not you'll correct me.
When it comes to candy, though, somebody might say, well, that means I can't have a lot of candy
things that I enjoy. That's not necessarily true. Because I've seen things that are, you know,
they're just fine as far as the, the Orthodox are concerned, because they have like one of the
rabbi symbols on it. Oh, no, no, no, that's totally different. Remember, I assure you that
there's no religion on the planet that knows or does anything that's in the text that supposedly
is supposedly subscribed to. Well, I understand that it's the opposite, just just like if you go
to a lawyer, you think he knows the law, he doesn't. Well, I understand that. But what I'm
saying is that I think they try to avoid all that stuff, though, when it comes to the,
well, first of all, the pork product, but oh, yeah, yeah, well, that's they have a,
they have the haraka, which is an excessive law where where if the law says you got to be in by
six, they tell everybody to be in by four. So if you're running late, you'll still be in before
six, right? So what they do is they ban pork to come in from coming into a certain city.
You see, and pigs, by the way, just the people, you know, when they're running in the what pigs
like, you know, when you hear about tuna or sharks, if they stop moving, they die.
Yeah, right. They have to keep moving. Pigs are like that. They never stay in one place.
But when you put them in one place, it psychologically damages them. And they're
rolling around in there, right? They're constantly pooping and digging up stuff constantly. Right
there. They trench. That's where these pigs to find truffles in the ground, right?
They scoop down into the ground to find something to eat and they keep moving.
So once you try to farm them, they get very, very messy because they they're always pooping
and they're always digging. Right. OK, so in a nutshell, people say you're dirty like a pig.
Basically, if someone's you hear someone saying that what you say is, well, a wild pig or one in
a farm because wild pigs are very clean, actually. Right. I was just going to say the wild the wild
pig or the wild hog or whatever that you say is actually not the same as the one on the farm.
No, they're they're the opposite. So the thing it's the same thing with the religious people
or the attorneys or the doctors. Look, how many times more than a dozen times with people that
are in the medical profession, I've pulled out a cross image of a cross section of a tire and an
image of a cross section of the lungs, the any organ in the body and the intestines. And I
explain this to them. What do you think they say? I can't acknowledge that. I'm not saying
what you're saying is not true Greek, but I can't I can't go that route. They all say that or some
variation of that or that's a very they're very or they could be very dismissive. They say
that's an interesting way to look at it, like, you know, little boy, pat you on the head. Right.
Well, it's so funny because that sounds like conversations I used to have with rabbis,
actually. Exactly that kind of conversation where it's just ended on that either not the
pat on the head for the little boy. But, you know, I'm not saying that what you're saying is wrong.
It's just that I well, you know, when you approach an authority figure, by the way,
you have to speak their language out of respect. Right. You know, like, for example, I have I there
was a client that someone recommended I work with and he's from Korea and he was highly bred in
Korea and he came here want to do some things. So I learned a little bit of Korean. So so,
you know, it comes to the door and I say, I'm young as hell, you know,
John, but I'm going to let me die. And, you know, I started speaking mild conversational. So every
white guy that he saw that he knew by facial expressions had a hard time with his English
accent because very, very little English, but he was educated in English. When I saw that,
I wanted to meet him there halfway. It was not to impress him. It was to say, I want to I want
to work with you and to prove that I'm going to meet you halfway by by learning how to communicate
the way, you know, you see. Right. So when you run into a rabbi. And he sees that you're a Gentile,
you know, you have to be able to tell them that, you know, suffer better. She's better. She's
better. He touched me in the head to audits. Right. And which is I could keep going on with
this, but that's basically you have to memorize the first chapter of Genesis to be bar mitzvahed.
So I basically have passed all of the requirements to be bar mitzvahed. So what is you know what I
mean? I basically tell him I have all the I can be you could bar mitzvah me right here on the spot
right now. I have all the requirements. What am I saying? I'm not I'm not saying I'm like him,
but I've met him halfway at least, you know, I've done work on my part, done work on your part to
meet him, to say, I'm going to meet you. Yeah, I'm not somebody down here on the outside giving
you a hard time. If you don't try to make an effort into that person's life, whether it's
language or knowledge or whatever, it's no different than being a salesman knocking on
your door or Jehovah's Witness. Hey, do you have a moment? I want to talk to you about something.
You see now with doctors, you they have a particular language. Right. And, you know,
you learn a little bit about that, too. You know, if I basically said, you know, epithelial
apoptosis, all it is, it's when cells are replaced in the body. That's all it is. You know how the
cells replaced, you know, drop off. Right. And and grow back. OK, that's epithelial epithelial
tissue cells that are replaced. And apoptosis is the removal. So you get into all this, by the way,
the epithelial apoptosis, I've been hammering it for a long time because that's what the AIDS
thing is about. So I think we've covered this before. You know, all the people, you know, there
is no AIDS test, by the way. It's demographic, right? Just like PCR doesn't work. Right. That's
where really part of it started. And they went after certain groups, the needle, the people
with needles and drugs and the homosexuals and the low, the ghetto and other. Right. OK. They
targeted those people with this thing called an AIDS test. And they said it's very serious.
So if you got positive on it, which is like there's no positive or negative PCR test, by the
way, if you eat raw meat or rare steak steak and you have a real PCR test, it'll show that you're
positive every time because of the blood tissue stimulant hormone in the blood. But the way the
AIDS scam worked and they've killed like 50 million people this way, it sounds very nefarious.
How could it be going on? Right. It's kind of like Santa Claus can't be a hoax Greek because
you know how many people would have to be in on it. You know, AIDS can't be a hoax because I mean,
a lot of people are in on it. I've been to a graduation party where someone had just gotten
their Ph.D. and the older doctors are going on saying you should just do a AIDS test. You know,
you get paid five hundred dollars up front. And then if they follow treatment, you can get up to
twenty five hundred dollars. It's all about money. Right. OK, so I mean, I was really I just wanted
to tell the guys, all those doctors to go outside so I could back up. Don't move. So I could back
up my truck over them. But anyway, what what they do with the AIDS test is they come up with that
you're positive and then they barrage you with literature and phone calls. Do you know that you
might have tested positive, not tested positive, you know, Santa Claus shoe size for a very
serious disease? You should consider treatment what the treatment the AZT is. It's a drug that
when you put it in the body, it tells the body that the cells that were are that are being
replaced have already been replaced when they haven't. So epithelial tissue, some of it only
like inside of your mouth, the cheek tissue that only lasts a few days. It comes off. Right.
You know, they do a scrape on the inside and that's the easiest tissue to get. Right, right.
Uh, well, there's a particular is a series of hormones, let's say, and proteins are more
complex than proteins that call them hormones. Let's say that the body releases once the cell
has grown back. The AZT is that hormone. So your body is still shedding. But your body is not
regrowing because it has an abundance of the hormones that said it's grown back. So you end
up looking like you're starving to death with body sores and you can't breathe because the lung
tissue is very important. Now, what when they show you pictures of AIDS victims, what do they
look like? Skin sores, skinny, can't breathe. Right. Right. That's what the other thing it
could do is develop these fat like tumors. We're talking about a criminal cabal, like criminal
group locked into the medical because what I just I just broke it all down how it is.
Now, if you bring up what I said to any medical person, they're going to deny it.
Remember, we talked about they want to. Why? Because they want to protect themselves.
Right. Yeah. And this is a fact. There are actually several people there. I remember not not anymore
on YouTube, but there were people that were explaining this this condition. Right. It's a big
scam. And, you know, whose fault it really is. It's the people's fault, because I put out the
information. Other people have put out the information where, you know, the end of the
Frankenstein movie, where the villagers find out what Frankenstein was doing and they show up
with torches and pitchforks. Right. Right. How many people does it take to tell the public this
before the people pick up their torches and pitchforks? Only one. Right. Only one person
should be right. It should be enough, but it does. It has not worked because I heard about this
many years ago from someone else. And it sounded crazy to me, to be honest with you. It was just
like, how is this possible? And they basically said almost verbatim what you just said. Okay,
good, because I've never heard anyone else say it this way in two minutes. I mean, I mean,
I could get it down to 30 seconds, but that's good if there are others out. I know there's
others out there. But the thing is, you got to be able to communicate in a neat little package
that is not intimidating and people can remember and repeat it. Yeah, but still,
but still I was taken aback by it because it was like, look, I saw people that seemed to be dying
from this. I mean, I saw, you know, people that had been in this condition. I mean,
sure, anyone can be positive for it because there's it's like Santa Claus shoe size.
Who's right? Who's wrong? Right. No, I get it. But it was just like,
see, that was the evidence to me that that meant that this was a real thing. But
you know, it was a real thing that people dying or the AIDS. Well, no,
people dying was a real thing. Oh, yeah, yeah. It was real because they were being
executed slowly by their own. Every time they receive treatment, they have to sign a whole
new set of contracts, which, by the way, are monetized. They they're 50,000 a piece. Like
when you get the Vax or by the way, not you, but whoever the paperwork is good for 50 grand
a pop, your signature right is like a gold bar. Right. So this is pretty this is very well known.
But the thing about this is I have seen people say, oh, I got tested for AIDS positive and I
have a girlfriend want to get married. I'm going to get treatment. So you're going to die.
They're going to kill you. Right. So in six months, you'll be dead. Well, I hadn't heard
from him again. But two years later, I asked about it. So he died. Yeah. Right. And with the new
thing now, there's a woman very fit. Well, she had a thing where her fingers and toes were really
cold and they were turning like a bluish color. And they said, yeah, it's because you just got
a new job and your stress goes. No, I got tested positive for this and that. I said, if you go to
the hospital, you're going to die. She was dead in a week. Right. Totally fit woman. So just like
9-11, if the buildings came down and no one died, it would be people would be so relaxed and say,
wait a second, there were no planes in there either. Right. You know, if you ever see a
video of the plane going into the building off a street view, everyone is looking across and down
until the building explodes. Now, that that plane was put in with CGI. Very obvious, because I don't
know about you, but if you go by an airport and a plane is coming in, not even as low as it was to
come into the building, everybody looks up. They would have looked up. But you know how loud that
is? Instead of coming in at maximum whatever, that would be so loud, it would be shaking the
ground. You would have looked up way before every film that they show of someone on the ground.
Pay attention. No one looks up until after the building has exploded. No one heard the air.
Right. That's your psychological thing. But if no one died on that day, people would be talking
more about what I just said. But because they allowed those people to get fried in there,
how many it was to be vaporized. By the way, you know, the original coroner's report,
the New York City coroner, state coroner for the people that died in the buildings,
you know what the cause of death was listed. They were vaporized. Right. And a lot of the
family members, what do you mean? What do you mean? And they and then they just redacted it and
they never replaced it because the coroner really shouldn't be lying, you know. So anyway,
what happens is we are mucked about with the people dying. So if you bring this up,
the AIDS, you know how many people have died? How dare you, Greek? Disrespectful,
right? You see, this is always brought up, right? Right. The Ukraine war thing. Oh,
what about the children? What about the children here? You see, so when you're you know that you
are really a spirit and I don't want to go with the airy fairy say this. So you're just a spirit
having a human experience. You hear that all the time. I think the stuff we spoke about on this
broke it down. So you have technical access to who you are. Technical access means if I have a
problem with this, this is a mind spirit problem. Or if I have a problem with that, that's my soul,
that's my breath, my metabolism. Or this is a physical body problem. And by the way,
whenever you're doing anything with the body, it's the soul because it's alive.
Right. So as long as the body is alive, the soul is part of the body.