So you wanna be hardcore, with your hat to the back, talkin' bout the gats and your rats,
but I can't feel that hardcore appeal that you're screamin', maybe I'm dreamin',
this ain't Christopher Williams, still some MC got the feel one, cats I got the feel some.
So Sonic 1-22, and uh, yeah, you didn't, you didn't press play on the wrong thing, just so you know.
Rated Y, and uh, little, little bit of a different start, but here we are,
Greek, uh, you wanna explain that clip at the beginning there, or?
Well, if anybody likes to hear the rest of it, just uh, send me an email or a Skype and I'll send you the file.
I did that about seven years ago.
It's uh, Christopher Williams, Biggie Smalls over Grammatic Beats.
Yeah, I think it's well done, it's only a minute and a half, the whole thing.
Some people out there have it, from a while back, and some other stuff like that.
Yeah, and it's uh, it's a really interesting mix, uh, it's slightly compressed here,
so, you know, you'll get the full experience if you get the file from the Greeks, so there you go.
Anyway, Greek, speakin' of files, and weird stuff that goes on, you know,
I was lookin' back at somethin' that we talked about before, and it's always relevant,
because death is a constant, and it used to be, you know,
because I spent a lot of time lookin' at autopsy reports, right, for various studies that I was doin',
and they have changed in recent years, but they've changed over time, several times.
Let's just hold on, an autopsy report is not the autopsy, it's a report of the autopsy, right?
You get it?
Yes, absolutely.
But that's usually what you end up looking at, unless you can get into the materials themselves,
and that's past the report, that's your photographs, your collection of stuff, your slides,
and that's a whole other area of interest.
But just lookin' at the paperwork, they've changed that too,
which I imagine means they've changed all the procedures.
Anyway, forget all that, problem is the alternative.
By the way, hold on, everything's about procedure, there's no law, there's no medicine,
there's none of that stuff, right?
If you know a doctor that's tryin' to be, to improve the procedures,
he gets reprimanded because he's supposed to follow those standard procedures, right?
It has nothing to do with whatever.
Oh yeah.
Okay.
No, being taught by forensic pathologists, right?
Look, what do I need to know in order to interpret things properly?
What word comes out of their mouth first?
Procedure.
You need to know the procedure, what procedure, you know, what was performed,
here's how you do the Y incision, blah, blah, blah, all these different things.
But what's fascinating to me is the ultimate conclusions, right?
People talk today about, gee, there's a lot of people droppin' dead of heart attacks, Greek.
Well, that's been the case since about, I don't know, the 1960s to the 80s.
Well, why in the 60s?
Because that's when they introduced, they had a big, big push to get people to start eating margarine.
Ah, yes.
Believe it or not.
And the way, yeah, there was no standard way of making margarine,
they just made margarine and a lot of the chemicals in there.
And we'll get into that because most people don't know what a heart attack is, and I'll simplify it.
Well, yeah, but what is a heart attack?
Anyway, they got a lot of different words for different cardiac events, right, that they say caused death.
And what's funny to me is I would sit there, you know, novice, reading it, going,
well, that's not the cause of death, but that is something that happens.
I mean, if you die, the heart stops workin'.
And I'm wondering what order they're puttin' it in.
Now, you and I discussed before that there was a point in time where people were dying from all sorts of dental issues
because their teeth would rot, they would get infections, they would spread, and it would kill them.
Right?
Right.
And two research that I've done from the 1890s to 1920s was death certificates that listed the cause of death was poisoning of the teeth.
And there was another term, I feel bad, I can't remember it,
but basically it's shock and trauma.
Like if you were hit by a horse and run over, and you went into shock, right, basically from pain, you died from that.
I've seen people go into shock, it's quite a thing.
And, yeah, so.
And that allegedly started the movement to, you know, give opiates to everybody, to reduce pain, and so on and so forth.
Because up to that point, believe it or not, pain was not an issue in medicine.
It was like a, yeah, pain is just something that's there.
We're not trying to deal with the pain.
Yeah, so the reason people are not dying as much as they used to back in the day is because of the tranquilizers, anesthesia, painkillers.
The water is separated.
What I mean by the water is separated, your freshwater and your sewer is separate, right?
Right.
And because, by the way, years ago when you had a freshwater source, people dumped their sewage in it,
and then they stopped drinking it when it got too much sewage in it.
I know it sounds crazy, right?
Yeah, so it's completely separate.
And also dentistry is what, and by the way, most, you know, the easiest way to access dentistry,
other than having an acquaintance that's a dentist, is to go to a dental school.
And most people will find a way to be accommodated.
So, but let's just jump right into the heart attack thing real quick, because there's no such thing really.
First of all, it's been very well known, the heart doesn't pump the blood.
It's physically impossible, right?
It's physically impossible to do that, just no matter how you look at it.
The quantity of blood, how thick the blood is, and how much linear,
or like some places in the country they don't use, they say linear, they say lineal,
feet of, or meters of blood vessels you have.
It's impossible to pump anything through that.
So it has to be self-moving.
And I've described, we'll do a quick recap.
It's the capillaries that cause what we call blood movement throughout the system.
The Greeks, ancient Greeks, they said the blood moves in the body like the waves in the ocean.
It's very accurate, actually.
When there's a transfer of nutrition, nutritive and eliminative matter,
on the capillary level, what's a capillary?
Go look in the mirror, if you have an organic eye,
and you look at your eye, you'll see these very fine blood vessels, right?
That's what I, that's the level, that's, in other words,
that's a good demonstrative example of the size that I'm talking about.
Because they are small, and they can be smaller than that also, and larger,
and still be classified as capillary.
But in other words, all of the blood movement in the body is caused,
well, originated on blood vessels that size, right?
So, which you have the most of.
And it goes around a circuitous path, branches off,
and goes into different parts of the body.
You could research that anatomically, what they tell you in the coacademic books,
it's fairly accurate.
And when it gets to the heart, it's not about mixing or anything,
even though there is, the heart's job is to slow that down.
So, let's use an analogy of slowing something down.
Can we think of anything that slows something down in the world that we live in?
Brakes, right? Oh, yeah, brakes. Very good.
So, you have brakes on cars and things like that, right?
Automotive, motorcycle, trains, planes, and automobiles.
Okay, so, what do we know about brakes?
Well, anyone who's been around before anti-lock braking
was more aware of how critical it is to brake.
So, with anti-lock braking, that spoiled everyone, right?
Years ago, before anti-lock braking, you were concerned about skidding,
you couldn't stop in the rain, right?
Yeah, you can read that in the old driver's manuals.
They would tell you, look, in these circumstances,
you have to actually pump the brakes.
Stuff like that. Right, go ahead.
So, it's been more of a concern on the older folks.
They know about it, but these days, it's been very automated.
And by the way, if you want, just since we're on the subject,
because I also work with high-performance automobiles, or used to,
they found out that if they remove anti-lock braking systems
from high-performance cars, they actually go faster,
and have better braking. Go figure.
So, what goes around comes around. That's another subject on why.
So, what happens?
So, think of a heart attack as being your brake failure.
Because the heart, let's just say it this way,
if we view the heart as its mechanical function,
it is a brake, not a pump.
I couldn't make it any simpler than that.
Because what we're told in the simplest mechanical form,
the heart is what? A pump.
Wrong. It's not.
So, if we're going to simplify it as a pump,
why don't we simplify it down to what it really does?
It's not a pump at all. It's a brake.
Okay, so, if you have a heart attack,
it's a failure of the pump to be working properly, according to them.
But if you find out that it's not a pump at all, and it's really a brake,
a heart attack is what? Brake failure.
Right.
Okay, so, when you don't have resistance, you have no braking.
Correct.
Simple as that.
So, if the heart cannot get in alignment,
mechanically, electrically, flow-wise, hydrodynamically,
flow, you know, purely on a fluid level,
purely on a mechanical or electrical level,
and it cannot slow down the blood,
what happens when you start losing your brakes?
It gets worse and worse, right?
Right?
Back in the old days, if you lean on your brakes,
and they're not doing good, and you keep leaning on them,
they're not going to do better, they're going to get worse, right?
Oh, yeah, absolutely.
So, once it starts, the blood flowing through the heart system,
you know, what we call the heart,
because it says ventricles and chambers, right?
And it cannot basically apply the brakes to the blood flow,
is what they're interpreting as a heart attack, right?
Okay.
So, what'll happen is it'll create too much, okay, what is,
when you don't have brakes, you can't regulate your speed.
True.
Right? Very simple.
So, when you, the heart stops acting as a proper braking mechanism,
it cannot regulate the speed of the fluid in the body.
Right.
So, it'll pull too far away on one end,
and clog up too much on the other,
and that just makes the recovery even harder.
Now, this has been in many medical circles,
and I just did this from understanding Yin and Yang,
but this is actually applied therapy.
So, without even getting into my personal experimentation,
right now, they've found that most effective treatment
for someone who is experiencing a cardiac arrest
is throw them in an ice water bath.
Mm-hmm.
Right? Contraction.
So, it's based on that.
But part of the shenanigans of what's going on now
with people with heart failure
is the same people that are writing all the shenanigans
with the COVID thing, right?
Right.
Now, if you've been injected with what they call a vaccine,
by the way, I think I've gone over enough.
There's no such thing as a vaccine.
They call it an injection, a vaccine injection, or whatever,
but there's no such thing.
You cannot give someone...
It sounds rational and logical,
and it might be effective if done right,
but you cannot give anyone part of a pathogen,
even if it's not live,
and their body develops an immunity to it.
That's a fallacy.
That's not true at all.
Right.
It's a subject that sounds reasonable,
and they're perpetuating this now for over 200 years.
Well, right, but that's the problem with it
is that it does sound reasonable, but...
That's right.
Yeah, go ahead.
That sounds reasonable that also when you eat food,
you absorb it, right?
Well, you know, you think to yourself...
And you're getting energy from calories.
They keep it going.
Right.
That's why I said, you know, I brought up archaics.
People look at that.
People also look at Brandon Joe Williams.
He's doing some stuff with law.
He's pushing it, you know, and it's the same everywhere.
It's funny.
With Brandon Joe Williams,
I don't endorse either one of them, though, by the way,
but they're fun to look at,
and I can tell you what they're not doing as well,
better than they should be.
But the Brandon Joe Williams guy,
recently I've been putting some stuff on
in the background while I'm working.
By the way, when I say recently I read a book,
I do not sit and read a book.
I have audio books playing audio,
so I could do other things.
I'm always doing at least two or three things
at the same time, right?
I don't sit and read anything, unless it's specific.
But he's been coming out lately
and making statements like,
attorneys don't know any law at all.
None of them.
I wonder where I've heard that before.
Yeah.
And he's only been saying this for a year.
So he's, in other words,
if you hear people saying that,
that means that they know what they're,
you know, they found out.
They know it now, right?
They know that.
And just to add to that,
if you're an attorney
and you decide to learn some law,
like, you know, remember the juice?
They have pulp and then no pulp,
and then they have some pulp, right?
Okay.
On the orange juice.
So if you're an attorney
and you decide not to learn law,
but some law, a little bit,
a little bit, a little bit,
like De Niro would say,
just a little bit, right?
You start talking that you're doing that,
you're going to get disbarred,
which is not a license to practice law,
I assure you.
And this is a phenomenon.
When you're a lawyer
and you become disbarred
or disenfranchised with the bar
and you decide to do something else,
they always work in the car sales industry.
Now, I didn't say used,
so much as, yeah,
they become used car salesmen.
I never said used car salesmen.
They could be used car salesmen,
but you'll find them
in new car dealerships as well.
They somehow, it's a phenomenon.
It's a phenomenon.
So I'm bringing these guys up
and that's just to interject,
just a reminder,
if you look at archaic stuff
and look at Brandon, Joe Williams,
this little recent guy
that popped up on the scene,
yeah, they've got good stuff going.
But what I'm trying to say is
when you learn a little bit about,
well, where have you heard this before?
All fields are wide open.
Every subject under the sun and moon
and stars is completely wide open.
So whatever you start finding out about it,
stop reading stuff that's recent.
You've got to read stuff
that's before World War II,
preferably 1890s.
People that are familiar with Greek speak
that used to hear me back in the day
in 2010, 11, and 12
when I was just on call in radio.
Even American Freedom,
I was going to say American Spirits,
that's a cigarette.
But American Freedom Radio,
I used to call in
and have long conversations as well.
What I've said is everything
and everything was already known
by the late 1800s.
Everything.
And archaics also says that,
also, similar to it.
Everything that, yes, everything.
Just about anything that we could.
And right now, okay,
back in those days,
they used to put out future,
the World's Fair and all that stuff
that by the 19,
say in the teens and 20s,
1970s we'll have a hotel on the moon
and everybody will have jetpacks
and flying cars, right?
By the 1970s.
The world of the future, yeah.
That's right, yeah.
And the Jetsons and all.
The Jetsons are supposed to be
like 2100.
But anyway,
you're never going to get that.
But they had known enough technology
that that stuff was not
pure fantasy to them.
They already knew it was plausible
and doable, right?
There's a couple of futuristic stuff.
Actually, futurism was a big deal
in France and Paris in the 20s.
There's a lot of illustration books.
You can get books online
and look up futurism from France
in the 1920s and you'll see
1980s flying cars,
1990s this and that.
It's not because they were
super fantastic imaginations.
They had the technology to do that.
And I think as we speak,
it would not be impossible to have
flying cars out there, right?
Right.
Well, it sort of depends
on when you say flying.
It's because birds don't fly.
Birds are flown.
They set up their bodies
so the environment lifts them
versus thrust where an airplane,
right?
It's different.
Things in nature,
they don't thrust.
There are things like
certain kinds of shrimp
and things that do thrust,
squid,
but most things that fly
just to manipulate
their immediate environment
to create loftiness.
How about hovercraft?
Is that a better term?
Yeah, you could,
but not by thrust and propulsion.
Yeah, but there are other ways.
Okay, so what I'm trying to say here
is you're not getting
any kind of talk like that anymore
because you're never going
to get flying cars.
You're never going to get
a hotel on the moon.
That stuff is never...
So what I'm trying to say,
the 20th century was stalled out.
They stalled...
Nothing happened in the 20th century.
When you think of the 20th century,
what did you get?
Okay, you got airplanes
and whatever,
but there's all these big wars,
financial situation, right?
There's nothing.
It stalled out the whole century.
It stalled out.
And it's still stalled out,
but now it's becoming different.
Now it's cultural
because they know
you don't have a lot of time left.
So my point here is
if you want to learn
about all of these things,
first thing to learn,
I assure you,
is what the public knows
about the subject is false.
Even though it looks workable.
And it happens...
This happens in cultures constantly.
In other words,
the corruption of information
increases in proportion
to the technological advancement
that's available
to the general society.
So when you see
the society at large
is becoming more technologically advanced
where devices in the homes
and all this stuff,
the information that they're getting
about everything else,
even that is corrupted
more and more and more.
So in other words,
the people that relied,
that had a more natural environment
without all this technological stuff,
that relied on signs
and superstition,
were better off in many ways
and less corrupt, right?
Like if you look at
one of the most corrupt times in Europe
is with the Inquisition
when the Vatican took over Europe.
That's the initial major corrupt,
horrible shit, right?
Other than the Mongol invasion
and all that, right?
And that was a lot
based on superstition and all that
but it was based on
creating a political body again
which is part of technology
because as technology gets stronger
you'll notice the state gets stronger
which is a political body
not the government, right?
The state.
So just like 1984,
the whole premise of 1984
was based around a state
that had a lot of power.
Right?
Right.
So this is the situation
that you're in
and your information
is all corrupted
no matter how many people think
the corrupted information
is usable or correct.
This is on every subject.
So if people are having heart attacks
and they go to a medical quack
that, by the way,
people tell me they have
a certain condition
when I meet them
and I say,
did you go to a medical technician
known as a doctor?
Did he ever engage you
and say,
I gotta take your vitals?
Does he put a cuff on your arm
and inflate it?
He says, yeah, yeah,
blood pressure.
I say, it's a quack.
Anyone who does that
is a self-proclaimed quack.
But they all do that.
Thank you very much.
Right?
They're all quacks.
Because it's procedure
like we started off early.
Yes.
So these people
that have heart conditions
they go and they supposedly,
oh, the doctor helped me
get better and all that.
Yeah, you actually survived
the heart attack
and survived that treatment.
Right?
Right.
So you're a pretty tough individual.
Don't think that they helped you out at all
unless they gave you some pain relief.
Because pain, by the way,
is circuitous.
In other words, pain is like,
what do you call it
when a dog chases its tail?
It's a compounding.
When you have a little bit of pain
it gets worse.
It makes it even worse.
Right?
It's cumulative, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
So relieving pain
is a very, very big,
it's a bad,
over-signaling the body,
the nervous system
can actually create shutdown
of other systems.
So what does that mean?
Okay.
It means that
if you're talking about something
like heart attacks
and whatever,
are they misclassified
or whatever?
Yeah, you know,
it doesn't really matter.
Like, I started,
this is a big tangent
because I got into this tangent
because of the vaccines, right?
Right.
The people that are dying
from, let's say,
side effects of the injection
they're calling it heart failure.
We're talking like 19-year-olds,
30-year-olds, right?
Athletes.
Yeah, people that you would not
normally expect
to be suffering
from such a thing are.
Is it possible?
I don't need to study
what they inject.
Because no one really knows
because the information
is corrupted.
Is it possible
that there are constituents,
even technology
in those injections
that would prevent the heart
from acting as a proper
breaking mechanism?
And the answer to that
is yes.
Yes, of course.
Of course.
But also, those people,
could they be monitored
and then hit with
other types of things?
You know, the phone
and devices
has enough energy
to induce biorhythmic signals
that can induce that also.
And here's the thing
about this concept
of a nanoparticle
that they introduce
into this thing
is that that is now
another receptor,
not one that is native
to the body.
Well, they're not that mystical.
Now imagine, okay,
take a piece of sheet metal,
very thin piece of sheet metal,
very small,
bend it in half.
But you know when you have
a sheet of paper
or a piece of sheet metal,
it's even thickness throughout?
Yeah.
But imagine the paper
or the sheet metal,
it's not an even thickness throughout.
And depending where you bend it,
at that bend,
what the thickness of it is
at that bend point
will react to certain radio frequencies.
It's not that mystical at all.
This is what I'm telling you,
remember,
the simplest technology, right?
Right.
So they make these
little nanoparticles
that are asymmetric or symmetric
in a certain way
and they're folded up.
And based on how they're made,
whatever frequency
they are activated with,
they will unfold
and open up.
Okay.
So it's the opposite
of a bear trap.
When you get caught
in a bear trap,
the thing is open,
you step on it,
it closes and it clamps
on your foot, right?
Or while the bears paw away.
It's like the thing
in the Saw movie
where they put the bear trap
on in reverse
and it pries the jaws open
radically.
This would be more like
a jack-in-the-box
that's folded up
and it's folded across
certain lines of thickness,
nanometers, right?
That's why it's nanotech.
That when it's succumbed
to a certain amount
of amplitude and frequency,
amplitude meaning volume, energy,
and frequency would be
where in the band it is,
the thing unfolds.
Okay.
So it'd be like, you know,
opening a jackknife
in your pocket.
Right?
Let's say it's an analogy.
Okay.
This is what nanotechnology is.
It's nothing mystical or magical.
This is like 1930s technology,
by the way.
You know, the idea
of having something
like that activate.
Yeah, but clearly, again,
that's not something
that is native
to the capillaries.
No, no.
It would be something
that would be easily
put into an injection.
Yeah.
And easily activated
with a specific frequency.
You know, there's no,
everybody's talking
about these nanoparticles.
They've been talking
about it since
10 years now already, right?
And I've never heard,
I don't spend that much time
on the Internet, of course,
but I've never heard anyone
explain it so simply
like I just did.
No.
Why?
Because maybe
it's a planet of morons?
Anyway, did I just say that?
Could be.
Okay.
Yeah, so, yeah.
Yeah, so all of these things,
you've got to somehow
relax about the whole thing
because let's go back
to the idiot that went
to the medical professional.
By the way, there's so many
people that I've known
even in the neighborhood
or whatever,
maybe let's say 60s or 70s.
I said, I haven't seen you
in a while.
Yeah, I have a doctor
who says I have
a heart condition.
I said, you know,
you'll be dead in six months
to a year, right?
You look fine.
You watch them degrade
and then you don't see
them anymore
and you see the other wife.
Oh, he died a month ago.
And everybody's okay with that.
I said, you know,
there's nothing wrong
with him in the first place,
right?
So anyway, at all.
But look, if I call
that medical Darwinism,
if you're so stupid
that you actually think
what they're doing
is helping you,
you shouldn't be procreating,
even though it's kind of late.
But remember,
if you have a male American,
65, 70, totally fine.
He's told that
his blood sugar is off,
which there's no glucose
in the blood anyway.
If you read,
I'm not going to go over
that again,
but if you see how they
determine blood glucose,
you're like,
wait a second,
that is so far off.
It's by analog, right?
And they tell you
you have a heart condition.
They start experimenting on you
and you die.
Is it possible at 65
that you could still have babies?
Yeah.
A man could have babies
till he's 90 or whatever.
I think the sperm hang around
pretty long in a male.
Yeah, the male can go
all throughout their life.
A woman loses it
between 40 and 50 years of age,
but the male, no,
they can keep going.
Yeah, the women
really get the bum deal here
because after menopause,
their brain can shrink
as much as 30%,
physically in size.
You know about that?
That explains a lot,
but no, I've never heard that.
It does explain a lot, yeah.
Maybe it does.
It explains why
a lot of these women
become interior designers.
But anyway,
you ever notice
the most interior designer women
are over 50 or 50?
I call it a post-menopause career.
Yeah, definitely.
But anyway, yeah, yeah.
So I would, well, anyway,
it's not the size of the brain.
Is it working or not, right?
True.
So here's the point,
which is pointless in a way.
The Darwinism part for the women,
I don't see it,
but for the men
because they could have babies.
So these older men
that believe
what the medical idiots
are telling them
and they are killed
by the treatments,
it is a form of Darwinism,
so they can't procreate.
I call it medical Darwin.
I'm totally okay with it.
It's like a test.
You know, when you're taking a test,
you stand up during the test
and let's say
in one of these public schools
or private school
and you start walking around
and telling other people
they did this wrong,
they did this right,
they did this wrong.
What are they going to do to you?
Throw you out of there.
Kill you, right?
Guaranteed.
Yeah, it's academic suicide
as a fifth grader
if you do that, right?
Right, exactly.
It's the same thing
here in this society.
You start going around
telling people
what you're doing
is absolutely asinine,
it's suicidal.
It's socially suicidal.