Ah, Rated Y, 2-2-1, that's the
sonic event number, and anyhow, Greek, how are
you on this fine, what is it, Saturday,
or whatever?
Fine day, yeah, what they call Saturday, I
was having a conversation with someone recently, and
the more you use presumptive terms, the more
accurate you are, you know, like what they
call Monday, I remember once calling someone a
minor, and I said, I'll be there what
they call Friday, what do you mean what
they call Friday, Friday is Friday, right, and
so when you do stuff like that, you
get a reaction, you see if they're listening,
where they're at, you learn a lot about
people, but by the way, my thing about
learning about people is not asking questions, but
like recently, about four times this past week,
because I'm trying to expand into luxury business,
and I don't want to be the one
that does anything really, I want to be
the driving force behind it, right, so whoever
deals with whoever develops their own rapport, because
all the businesses I did before, people would
call, you know, someone answer is the Greek
there?
No, he'll be in tomorrow.
All right.
I'll call tomorrow.
Wait, what can I do for you?
No, no, no, no, I don't want to
talk to you.
I want to talk to him.
Right?
No, no, no, I don't want to do
that.
Right.
So I've been, and it's really hard to
get a feeling of what someone is about
on a basic conversation, but you can't by
using how the term they use, but you
can't condemn them for it, because words are
one of the easiest things to be changed,
right?
So yeah, you can change that in an
instant, really, once, let's say someone becomes aware,
you know, I've made people aware of lawful
timekeeping, real timekeeping, and most people don't care
but those that do it just kind of
like oh my gosh I got it no
more I got to do this you know
you know I got a really deadly right
so by the way who I'm looking for
to work with me on the various things
with the scalerator is when they see it
get the idea oh I'm gonna quit my
job I'm gonna leave my wife leave my
husband I'm gonna quit my job this is
what I want to do that's I feel
it okay great great great one thing you
are getting some electronic interference so watch whatever
it is you're going near yeah it's like
actually actually not much actually I just I
held up a metal device maybe that will
do it near the phone so anyway so
this is one of the things I do
for character you know I think I went
over a job interview a job interview right
yeah sorting out coins and you learn a
lot that way from people also especially when
they walk in they drop their resume and
tell them to sit down on this table
and sort out coins like oh I'm not
gonna do that I'm out of here my
favorite my very favorite little test of your
you know let's see if anybody's listening to
what the hell is being said was a
phone message you had for a little bit
where yeah you called a certain number this
message sounded very much like the usual numbers
you get this numbers been disconnected but that's
not what the message said that's it's a
lady's voice which I'd always used to be
I don't know what it is anymore but
you know you get a lady's voice that
used to tell you this number has been
disconnected anyway it sounded just like that except
the lady says you've reached the number that
you dialed if you believe you reached it
or hang up and dial it again yeah
and people kept hanging up and redialing basically
it says you have reached the number that
you have just dialed it's an English accent
you have reached the number that you have
just dialed if you believe you dialed in
an error hang up and dial it again
and people and so I see someone hang
up a delegate I'm like oh this never
never spoken before a referral or whatever oh
this guy's not paying attention so what do
I do should I fuck with him you
know I mean mess with him a little
bit I mean or they're easy to mess
with or to educate him or what I'm
just gonna watch this character yeah so most
people fail most people fail tests especially with
criticism I recently spoke to someone oh it's
hilarious oh it was hilarious oh because you
gave me the the number I called it
and then hooked back up with you and
I said that's the weirdest thing it says
I reached it's a psych test it's a
psyop it's an operation to psychologically look at
a distance you can only spiritually or psychologically
it's the same thing filter yeah of course
right that's the only way you can do
it but when we meet in person I'm
listening about criticism if you give criticism you
can't just say it sucks and stop a
five-year-old can do that right you
should prepare when you give criticism say what's
wrong with it and the to fix it
so you get three parts to a criticism
I've spoke to someone recently said oh this
sucks I'm like okay how do you fix
it looks they were silent I'm like okay
this person's eight years old so you know
basically it doesn't matter how old they are
but they stopped at around eight or nine
you know their function yeah so it's kind
of like you know I had an old
member of the early 2000s computers you try
to update them and it took like all
night and then you're like then you're like
hit fuck it cancel just hit the cancel
button no more but then it would still
be there but not do you want to
finish downloading it no yes yeah so it's
dumb stuff so I like the computer analogy
because it's supposed to be the mental mental
machine right there you go a mental machine
well they tell you the brain is the
body's computer or you know yeah they always
try and do that sort of yeah so
essentially what I do now it's sort of
the coin thing for an interview as I
hand someone a camera and there's something in
the room I say take a picture of
that object for me would you and then
when you think you've got a good picture
you can take as many as like just
present me with one right and when they
show me the picture I'm like it'll be
a flower with a vase and the lights
coming through the window and they show me
the picture and I'm like what's that big
black thing right there and that's the first
thing I see and I'm like oh that's
the shadow I'm like you know that because
you're in the room but if you show
this picture someone's gonna wonder what that big
black blob is right there first thing you
see right so you know the first thing
you see second thing you see so I
learn a lot about people by having them
take a photo and by the way I
have still to meet anyone who can take
photos up to where the photo is well
communicating right still I haven't seen anyone coaching
I coach people on it years ago there
was a photographer I'm not gonna mention his
name Chris Gimarae he used to photograph for
Buick General Motors and we go to the
football games giant stadium and anyway he hired
me says I want you to work in
my studio I was like but I don't
know anything about photography and he says you'll
do great you're smart I'm like what what
did he just say yeah so anyway so
I'm trying to focus where you know the
games are going right so I'm trying to
focus and take a shot focus take a
shot he grabs the camera he grabs my
camera and two cameras he holds him three
feet ahead of him he goes pop up
up up up up up up up up
up up up up unloads them it says
take the film out new film I'm like
holy shit you know so we put it
we went through 40 rolls of film and
then what you do you develop everything because
I was used to like everybody line up
say cheese okay right you know that's not
how you do photography it's all about timing
you take hundreds or thousands of pictures to
find one it's all about timing and it's
not timing that you create it's a timing
universe that whatever happens right you know how
that developed in the photographic industry that sort
of attitude which was correct where they just
threw a net and hope they captured the
great image is because two different photographers captured
Lee Harvey Oswald getting shot in the gut
by Jack Ruby and yeah I've seen that
and it's that action shot yeah and one
of them got the Pulitzer and the other
one got nothing and it was just a
very slight deviation in the photograph but it
was like hell this is like a split
-second difference in the photograph and one worked
one didn't because one conveyed the actual incident
and the other did not and it was
like a baffling thing it is 1963 folks
that this is when that changed and photography
is like that though yeah you know that's
why people and the worst thing it's like
you know I was talking to someone so
you know who really about financial business on
it so that's really messed up I didn't
know that so you know don't blame the
government or the schools it's your parents that
screwed you up they're the ones that made
you stand around on holidays says cheese for
photo they have no idea what's going on
it's your parents so if you're gonna blame
anyone it's your parents that messed you up
I don't care how you think they good
parents they were I could show you there
was pretty shitty 500 different ways and I'm
not saying go everybody go after their parents
no but you have to put them in
their proper perspective ones that messed you up
yeah but they may have indeed done with
the best intent they could and everything else
with their heart doesn't matter it doesn't matter
but the fact is they did the best
they could but don't forget they were screwed
up by their parents so yeah and so
and so so that's why people harkin on
the halcyon days I think we're better well
if they were so much better than they
wouldn't have allowed it they would have put
guidelines and enforced you know guidelines so we
wouldn't be where we are to people we're
actually better today believe it or not there
goes that electronic jump again whatever is in
common with the last time I said it
you're doing it okay you know by the
way this whole time you have a major
echo but I've learned how to deal with
that so if you have something like that
I can't really pick it up but I
sound pretty clear and you do pick up
a distortion every so often is what you're
saying no no no it's not just a
distortion though it's literally like I can hear
a break in the interference yeah it's it's
a different thing I'm talking about a little
distortion I could even factor out I wonder
if it's the whirlygig stay away from it
whirlygig anyway for those that did the weather
yes webinar know what that is so it's
amazing how completely passive device I've had several
people say do you know the weather devices
mess up a compass I'm like yeah is
that cool so and there's nothing you know
right electronic or magnets or anything so well
because it doesn't generate an electromagnetic field it
guides them so it actually messes with the
field that makes electric magnetic fields it's a
yeah so by the electric magnetic fields of
perturbation and the static it's so funny when
you talk about the ether you know how
it let me just go over this I
don't want to get in something you know
this thing is with a motor you see
it our construction sites emergencies and what is
that say it's an electrical generator right it's
a generator it generates electricity no it doesn't
generators right it does not generate any more
electricity than a water pump generates water go
out and buy a water pump leave it
in the box just plug it in you
expect water to start coming out of it
no no you have to connect it in
water pump is designed to take something that
is static static keyword yes and and depending
on the design of the pump to give
it a certain pressure and rate of flow
it's exactly what a winding and a generator
does and or the commutator however you want
to do it a magnet and a coil
let's say it's a simple one you can
use as many different ways to do it
when you start rotating rotating that it takes
the static body of electricity and then starts
magnetically pressurizing it just like the pump with
the impeller pressurizes the water and it make
that magnetic repressurized ether or static electricity likes
to run along metallic what we call conductors
and that's what electricity is has nothing to
do with electrons I've talked about it for
years I've done experiments with my very powerful
microscopes where I have a high current high
voltage wire and I have heavy rubber gloves
and I cut the wire and I pointed
towards the ground and I come back with
the microscope looking for the electrons to scoop
them up right right of course yeah that's
how you make fun of these or maybe
more and they're moronic the scientific people so
anyway yeah all these things it's like no
one is paying attention it seems like only
like the 15 subs that we have do
though when you go out into the world
and you see what's going on it's a
miracle you know I was speaking to an
engineer I said how many tens of millions
of people drive a car you know operate
you know machinery like that like oh you
know where they could put themselves in something
that looks like a projectile that's going down
across the surface of the earth at 50
or 70 miles an hour right that's what
I mean by that right a lot millions
like tens of millions maybe more no one
really knows but it's it's tens of millions
okay but if you talk to these people
and see where they're mentally at and their
perception what they know what they perceive it's
a miracle any of them return home alive
it's a miracle right there should be like
you know millions of fatalities every day just
from putting ones in itself in a heavy
metal object and projecting it at high speed
across the surface of the earth you know
known as a car or whatever well they're
based on their mental state they should be
half of them should not be coming back
alive but they do well there are there
are tens of thousands of accidents every day
anyway so I mean I'm talking about like
terminations you know yeah I mean so there's
something that's got like autopilot that's protecting people
keeping them going like someone working at a
quote-unquote job they hate it they're there
for 25 30 years they hate it the
whole time yeah and they're and they get
their retirement and then they hate the retirement
because they got nothing to do you know
it's but if at any point at that
in their lives if you tell them to
break away from this all you need is
food clothing shelter they don't want to hear
it at all but they'd rather be so
they're like this is autopilot protection kind of
thing where people normal normal and above normal
people are begging begging they're begging and asking
to be messed with guess what that's why
they are you ever heard of something called
a government agency you ever you ever you
heard of something called a you know a
large corporation you ever heard of a critter
called an attorney you ever a critter called
medical doctor those are all there to mess
with you because the state that you're in
you're in a stupor so this is the
majority of the people yes your parents are
like that too here's the thing and I
got a thing for parents so could they
got to stop messing I'm messing up their
children I'm really big when a child is
born to be taken away from the parents
and raised in a situation kind of like
what the dictators did in Thailand and Soviet
whatever they take the children away and they
raise them so they're raised according to the
narrative right right and the narrative here would
be perception reality real science real medicine real
education real language all this stuff and here's
the thing people you know I used to
say you know law like who decides what's
wrong and right I say you do it
has to be voluntary you decide what's wrong
and right all right so all this stuff
so anyway but one thing that I have
an itch on parents is you always hear
oh it's like how mom used to make
it tastes real good it's like my mom
used to make and I'm like oh I
don't want that I have never been to
anyone's house whose mom was even remotely a
good cook or grandma so you notice they
stopped doing those ads years ago in the
70s as I was five just like mom
used to make right oh my gosh terrible
terrible food I have never been to anyone's
house actually it's not true there was a
I remember a Japanese family that invited me
over it was food was very good and
a Persian family okay the food was very
good but there was only two occasions where
it was a family invite the food was
actually palatable so when I started documenting all
these events and what people say what they
say and think has nothing to do with
what's really going on that's what I mean
take the children away so what they say
and think has is tangible to reality right
like for example I'm studying the economic stuff
and you know mortgages are considered intent and
car loans and bank loans are considered intangible
debts because the bank never let you anything
it's actually in the paperwork intangible means what
you can't see it you can't smell it
you can't touch it right it's something for
you to touch tastes yeah it's intangible so
yeah it's it's amazing the stupidity so smart
question because you know somebody who is not
just looking to be on autopilot asked a
question in the chat and we'll start there
when do you switch from new moon eating
to more full moon light question mark is
this still new moon time for heavier and
baked items question just curious thanks that's the
full question there and what they're asking is
because you've talked about this before the timing
in which you eat if you are pay
attention to your you know lawful timekeeping you
will notice there is a difference of things
there are different cycles or different portions of
the cycle of the moon so yeah go
ahead don't take it so narrow though let
me just first make an adjustment to the
question let's call it dark moon full moon
okay dark and all the ancient texts the
new moon is the full moon right in
the Bible if you'd say I think it's
Psalms 81 the new moon is the full
moon should in the book of Enoch the
new moon is the full moon well you'd
figure that if something is brand new it's
still in one piece none of it has
been sliced away none of it is hidden
whatever you want to say so therefore that
makes the most sense doesn't it I've heard
pretty strong arguments against it because it's gone
and then it's back you know when the
moon is dark and the sliver comes back
that's a new moon so both argue so
let's just call it what it looks like
a dark moon and a full moon right
yeah but that's a sliver of the moon
as opposed to the moon so I would
argue yeah it's just for communication it's it's
better that way because when you say it
doesn't matter either way as long as you
know what you're talking about right the reference
for in terms of time here okay so
let's put the moon aside the reason I
brought that up is because it's a predominant
condition in your environment give you an example
you must always give you a way to
think about it it's always take consider consideration
the predominant forces in your environment okay so
what would be the predominant force would be
seasonality so when it's winter winter yes that
winter season takes predominance over day and night
and the moon because it's predominant then the
next thing most likely would be the moon
and then this and then the sun because
you see the moon changes very gradually but
the Sun changes twice a day right right
so right and and then there's in between
things like people who are prone to being
seasick or sick in an airplane yeah that
being on that ship or be airship or
naval ship or whatever you are that is
now the predominant influence in your environment for
you right being in an office cubicle with
fluorescent lights on eight hours a day that
might take predominance right messing you up right
so you have to decide especially again I
mentioned how dumb people are most people don't
even look up they don't even know what
what you know they just know it's light
or dark out they don't know the positions
of the Sun what it means they don't
know what the moon means at all just
like zero full moon people go crazy right
so yeah so it's not really about the
moon it's about assessing the predominant influence in
your environment right like the best example I
could give for the predominant influence of your
environment that is very personal would be being
seasick okay when you get seasick you don't
care what position the moon is if it's
day or night man you're see that ship
just rocked you you got rocked right I
get so I get carsick I don't give
a damn about anything about being familiar with
emotion helps by the way so so here's
the thing tell her that but anyway what
I would suggest is let's stick to the
question in the moon so the full moon
is the most expansive okay and the dark
moon the new moon here in the question
is the most contractive so you want to
be whenever you have a predominant influence on
your environment you want to be in sync
with it so back to the being seasick
the reason you get seasick is because you're
not paying attention to the motion of the
boat if you know you're prone to seasickness
pay attention to the motion of the boat
don't just fix yourself on the waves or
don't fix yourself on the boat you have
to look at how the boat is moving
contrary to the waves and all that get
her get that rhythm going in your mind
even if it's not smooth and you usually
don't get seasick you see what I mean
okay so pay attention to how that goes
so same with the moon so when the
moon is full or approaching full becomes fall
and then just after it was full that's
when everything is the most expansive on that
influence so you want to have foods that
are expansive so it would be salads light
foods not heavily cooked maybe more sweets than
usual not don't go for sweets but you
know save you know you want you craving
blueberry muffins save it for that week right
something sweet or whatever pancakes or whatever okay
so now as the as the moon starts
to contract and go towards what's called the
new moon or the dark moon that's most
contractive so that's when you would have a
little more salt that's when you would eat
have your meats let's say something more baked
that's when you have your beef stews your
barbecues blah blah blah blah blah okay and
then and you focus so you know a
few days the rule of thumb for me
is three days before three days after so
if you start transitioning into the moon three
days before and then it happens whether it's
full or dark and then three days after
and then you have like a neutral point
which is still a transition point so let's
say you the you know the new the
full moons be coming in three days you
start transitioning to lighter foods you may not
even have to eat when the full moon
is around you'll notice your appetite is lower
and then you will find go ahead and
eat yourselves for one or two or three
or the light foods two or three days
and then you could start introducing the slightly
heavier foods and I like between the dark
moon and the light moon that week you'll
probably be doing 50-50 so introduce the
upcoming change keep the existing status but it's
a transition you know because the moon doesn't
do it abruptly it's gradual so get her
feeling it has a rhythm right the same
with the same with the daylight when the
Sun is up it's very expanded and when
the Sun is down at night it's everything's
very contracted it just doesn't it's not like
hitting a light switch on the wall you
know the Sun is going down you know
it's sunset you know it's early evening and
then you know it's midnight right right everything
so the transitions are to be smooth now
that depends on what finesse you have what
planning you have what abilities you have so
and the same thing with the daytime the
night is the most contractive it's so contractive
that it knocks you out usually right so
you fall asleep in other words right right
and and the the daytime the Sun is
so expensive that you want to be up
and you want to be out right it
really has oh it's the sunlight Greek you
know it's the light rays well no there's
a lot more than that because you could
have someone that is not exposed to the
light indoors and they're more active during you
know noon than they are at midnight by
the clock let's say right no matter what
your sleeping schedule is people that work at
night I have a rough time like people
that have a career to work at night
have a rough time after 10 or 15
years you know they have health issues or
whatever mental issues fatigue issues you know fitness
issues I meant say not health issues and
they have to be very careful and have
to restructure themselves because they stay up all
night let's say on a job right or
a job right yeah you know you know
I would explain I need to go there's
a job and then there's a job but
anyway there's there's a finesse personal for this
but here's the thing this should have been
in your culture and I'm pointing a finger
at your culture man right this should have
been already implanted just like you know you
know bacon and eggs for breakfast you know
and yeah for lunch and dinners meat and
potatoes you know how they have these cultural
things they put in your face right why
didn't they put anything benevolent or useful why
do they always put malevolent stuff and harmful
things yeah so now you're good you're living
in a world that pretty much all your
cultural stuff is malevolent not outwardly completely but
if you do it you'll be it's not
not good and no matter what it is
that's in your culture usually the Western culture
especially you're gonna have to it's not just
how do I do it with the light
moon or the dark moon it's actually a
cultural thing because not only do you have
to figure it out and finesse it but
the people around you also how do you
deal with them right right so this stuff
that I'm bringing just to preface again I've
said many years ago this stuff that I
talk about is not for this society it's
for the next society or let's say it
is not for this society but if you
want to know I'll share it but I'm
just telling you how screwed up things are
over here but I'm not just gonna say
things are screwed up yeah they are okay
next subject an eight-year-old can do
that true I'm saying it's screwed up and
this is this is why it's screwed up
and this is how you can do it
so it's not screwed up right that's what
I'm all about I've been doing that since
at a very young age people didn't like
that they would say Greek I ask you
for the time and you tell me how
to build a watch I don't want to
know you know so there's those they're not
skeptics or naysayers there's a difference between a
skeptic and a naysayer right yes so skeptic
entertains the information sorts it out sees its
validity naysayers is that you're not saying what
I'm used to you know I mean Jack
Fresco had an analogy about a normie and
someone who is not a normie if you
have a little here a little tiny flashlight
says a million lumens and you bring it
to an army right but if you take
it to someone who's rational I say a
million lumens in that size well how do
you power it how do you keep the
temperature down how did you figure out how
to do that you know you know he'll
ask logical questions right right so you're not
gonna run into people like that I don't
care if it's your spouse your children your
parents your people at work do not expect
them to react favorably if you're listening to
me for more than what do we call
episodes or you have an episodic trip here
I guess where you've been with me for
a while you know this or tell people
right yeah this is you're not in a
good place it doesn't mean you're not right
but you're not gonna have a you won't
have the best make the best possible like
when I used to travel often especially working
with the mines and doing the engineering and
stuff for them you're on the road you
eat like highway food right yeah and after
a while you know I still had a
little camping set where I could pull off
and I made rice and beans you know
wherever I stopped you were like God this
guy's cooking smells good and but if you
go to a McDonald's yeah right get a
fish sandwich in an apple pie and a
sprite right that's the best choice you can
make right so you got some how are
they gonna screw up the fish all right
they might spray some chemicals or whatever and
then you got an apple pie right instead
of the French fries right well I always
roll the dice on the fries because depending
on where you're at even though it's supposed
to be universal and they are all McDonald's
is dog food I recently had it about
six months ago and I said this is
dog food man they don't really care about
that now it's real bad but the French
fries used to be take a roll of
the dice because most places would be okay
but a lot of them screwed it up
and if you had a dog well they
would eat them anyways that's why I mean
it's dog food I mean when I say
dog food literally I just said I gave
it to my dogs they'll fight you for
it they'll take the fry and growl you
know they will they'll fight each other for
them they'll get mad at each other for
snapping them yeah I got another one now
this is a combination between two people and
I'm gonna put them together and kind of
bring this so so you guys know this
came from two different people I had an
experience one time where a young man who
was staying at our land got possessed by
something his voice changed he was talking nonsense
he was referring to us as stupid humans
it was a very creepy experience I moved
away because I was feeling a sinking sensation
in my stomach while being next to him
really creepy stuff half an hour later though
the guy was normal again now hold on
the other question that goes along with this
is short how do you know if you've
been cursed and how can you get rid
of it now I think this opens up
a whole wide subject for you if I
give you both I think he just met
possession is real okay with with the spiritual
entity or an entity messing with you have
influence which 99% of the people I've
ever met are influenced then you have a
oppressed we hear these mental disorders schizophrenia depression
whatever that's called a spiritual oppression then you
have the first two that I just mentioned
the people still retain their personality and name
and all that identity let's say self-professed
identity the third one is possession and that's
where they that's not them like if the
episode is for a day they don't remember
it if it's for an hour they don't
remember it that's possession possession is where your
spirit is replaced with another which is very
rare by the way and what this person
laid out sounds like that the third the
third you know third degree there and I
have no answer other than you know it
is what it is and curses can be
lifted by appealing to your higher power to
do that for you or having the person
who put the curse on you amend it
now that's what I know about it I
mean yeah and some people have brought up
you know like this what they used to
call split personality it's now described as a
dissociative identity disorder where literally there are different
personalities that seem to present themselves from the
same you know corpus if you will yeah
I wonder sometimes if this is not being
confused for exactly what this guy's describing sometimes
that's but I would rather here's the thing
this is not related I've been really I
don't endorse him but I've been hammering a
lot on look out for Charlie F look
out FA Charlie yeah because he's showing you
how it's in tech it's sound it's not
intangible let's say or spiritual it's just sound
and who's one thing he doesn't get into
is who's doing it he says it's humans
or whatever but yeah it's always been going
on always that we were subject to this
stuff there's stuff underground up in the sky
or whatever that they're beaming us with and
it hasn't stopped it's been around since the
beginning or whatever you want to believe the
beginning is and rather because that's tangible and
that makes it seem a little more pulp
pulp how would you say you can do
you can deal with it better because literally
if you put yourself in a soundproof environment
you might be away from it who knows
but then we could work backwards from lookout
for Charlie and go back to the spiritual
stuff there's a lot of stuff in the
biblical narrative about that even with curses by
the way there's a lot of stuff in
any I mean you want to go the
pagan route you want to go the eastern
route Western route is the worst you could
do I consider the biblical narrative Eastern by
the way it would be South West East
so in other words it would be Southwest
Asia is what I consider the biblical narrative
once you come over to Europe let's say
or whatever you know you could go to
old druid stuff see what they say but
stay away from what's called psychology those guys
are morons even yield when recently I put
on an audio book by by you'll see
but wrote a bunch of stuff and I
was like this guy's a moron no wonder
they they made him popular you know Freud
was even more of a moron like oh
my gosh you're really as I'm getting older
I'd argue with you that's a race between
the two of them as to which one
is King moron because I mean it's yeah
yeah and the people just adore likely Einstein
is another one right I said wrote really
good personal letters I had a book personal
letters of Einstein that he sent to people
and stuff he had a pretty good mind
in a for communicating you know various things
but the way they put him up is
doing this who's plagiarized but anyway yeah you're
pretty much stuck and also by the way
people that are confused or not all the
classics they told us to read in elementary
school in high school that's all garbage most
if you read Emerson and O'Mellville and Mark
Twain you know all these guys they're idiots
they're not good writers I recently I picked
up Samuel Clemens book margins this is so
poorly written it can't be by him yes
it is oh my gosh we were so
hyped up told that this stuff we should
read they made us read garbage and yeah
so what do you read then well you
still have to read it because when you
come across something good you know what good
is right oh so yeah I was bored
to death by that book the the pearl
or whatever it was who wrote that was
that the Simpers are at the girth also
wasn't it a Steinbeck maybe it was another
idiot oh my gosh oh but by the
way I want to bring up to something
I was mentioning to someone these Ivy League
colleges you could look this up we're started
back in the 1600s or whatever 300 years
ago 250 years ago 180 years ago my
families who became mega wealthy during the opium
trade and they wanted to keep that going
so they said you know people might see
what this this does to people when they
use it habitually and they might come after
us so we need to make a cultural
change why don't we make these colleges and
start changing the culture their point of view
and the narrative about what we're doing right
and he could put out the rest so
you had a bunch of rich scumbags that
basically drug dealers that opened all these Ivy
Leagues and they're still do you right so
this is where this is when I say
you're in a bad place it's not because
who's a president who's who's the current occupant
of the White House or whatever pedophile you
have in the parliaments wherever you are or
whatever no it's always been this way since
ancient times and there were city-states and
groups back in ancient times that wanted to
fight to clear the air you know and
they always failed you know it's this is
a scumbag planet or realm whatever you want
to call it make the best out of
it just like when you go to McDonald's
don't order the greasy stuff or try to
make up the best decision or hold hold
out part of the thing about holding out
here is just focus on food clothing shelter
you know I'm not saying do what I
do I constantly remind myself look I was
sent here by accident right so I'm not
gonna act like I belong here right no
way in other words when it's cold I
just want to be warm when it's hot
I want to be cool when it's raining
I want to be dry if it's too
dry I need some moisture if I'm if
my belly's making noise and I need nutrition
I'd like some right that's it you know
if I don't want to be wearing rags
and tatters right I don't want it right
so but I really don't want anything here
it's the absolute minimum but if you're gonna
do the absolute minimum do it really well
do it really well so you know that
balances everything out and then you could point
the finger and say hey you know better
than that or you don't care or whatever
and you'll always be in the right fair
enough so uh what do you think I'm
changing this question a little bit because I
think they mean to ask you what do
you think about this substance they call beyond
meat like the vegan thing because okay okay
that because that's been I it's going away
thankfully yes it's it's really an unclean food
from a spiritual point of view what they're
doing is growing hemoglobin they're going blood in
a laboratory using algae that mimics that and
they're putting they're making this vegetarian blood it's
no longer vegetarian if you're making blood right
right so it's really a bad cocktail the
level of gmo and preservatives that are in
there is it's toxic you'll probably well there's
that but they want to know your liver
and kidneys with it yeah they want to
know if there's any human elements in it
like if it's uh yet another like sort
of cloaked cannibalism yeah they they could do
that just like I wouldn't be surprised if
they're using the cloning technology which has been
around since the 30s by the way yeah
the biggest problem with the clones was by
the 1950s they had them walking around but
they didn't have them in public because the
whites of their eyes were brown that's why
you hear the black eyed children and all
that that's they're not from outer space but
anyway true um no they're horrible uh horrible
people uh uh doing all this stuff and
I think those that support them are horrible
also um and eat a piece of meat
like for example right now it's dark moon
time and it's like well I'll roast a
chicken I'll do it uh I call it
the one two three one two three chicken
I get an organic chicken uh scotch babbit
or babscotch I forgot which one you cut
this cut it right down the spine yet
most people can't do that they don't have
the a sharp knife but you could use
a butcher a strong scissor also and make
sure that when you do that with a
chicken right about an inch or so above
where the pope's nose is the tail of
the chicken stick your thumb in there where
the kidneys are right by the spine and
you'll see a kidney pop out you can't
see it when the carcass is open but
stick your finger and you you want to
get all the organ meat out because organ
meat doesn't have a good flavor most people
don't know how to do that that's why
I can't eat chicken up because it's not
clean they don't know how to clean them
then what you do is you you blend
liquefy that this is why I call it
one two three water uh uh with a
mixture heavy salt like a brine very salty
not as salty as the ocean but really
salty with garlic and ginger if you don't
have fresh garlic or ginger you could use
a powder of each quite a bit of
it uh cover the chicken in a bowl
or a pot put a plate on it
with a weight or whatever three hours that's
okay and that's why I call it the
one two three one two three because the
brine is made of salt ginger and garlic
one two three and it's one two three
hours in other words one two three hour
brining marinate then you take the chicken and
you hang it up if you can't hang
it up outside put it in a colander
you know the one you use to drain
your pasta whatever and put you know a
towel or something over it and then you
got to wait for at least two or
three hours again for it to drip dry
you want the skin to be dry to
the touch almost to the where it looks
like it's sunburned on its own I hang
it up in 100 degree weather in 20
minutes the skin is crispy just hanging in
the sun and then we put it in
a 700 degree mesquite oven for about 20
minutes 25 minutes 30 minutes it's completely done
rested not an hour or whatever and and
it's it's delicious and okay when we did
this yesterday we do this in the middle
of the month typically let's say and it's
the dark moon it's just chicken so two
people sitting down ready to eat we got
lime and juice you know whatever just chicken
dig in chicken good you know it's just
chicken that's it no sides no salad no
you know yesterday we had a kimchi cucumber
side some kimchi from Trader Joe's and I
sliced some cucumbers with rice vinegar and sugar
and put that around the kimchi and I
did make rice but the majority of the
meal is just chicken typically when we do
this broiled chicken in the middle of the
month it's just chicken we just sit down
just chicken and a beer some wine or
whatever just like you know when you have
meat in the middle of the month don't
worry about the sides you must have a
condiment though to make it digestible in this
case it's the kimchi and the lime right
now quick question you know I appreciate all
kinds of cucumbers but do you have a
particular favorite or one that you would savor
the standard I used to grow the Armenian
ones which are like the skinless they look
like they don't have a skin oh those
are weird yeah yeah okay yeah they're really
they grow really large you know cucumbers you
don't want them growing too large because then
they get air pockets where the seeds are
they're not as flavorful as cucumbers are in
the melon family yeah by the way so
look at whatever is good for melons is
good for cucumbers you know if you someone
cuts a cantaloupe in a room and you
walk in you can smell it someone cuts
a cucumber in a room it smells just
like a melon but it's not you know
a cantaloupe it's a different right right just
like onion and garlic you know if you're
processing onion and garlic in the kitchen you
know it's like one of those one of
those right so yeah so it's a melon
so consider that it should be eaten very
sparingly should be treated because remember melons either
eat it alone or leave it alone cucumber
tends to be one of the exceptions that
can be eaten in a salad and with
foods with other things but always in minimal
that's why when they when they you know
when they serve burgers with a pickle that's
a cucumber but no one ever asked for
do you want a cucumber with your hamburger
like hell no give me a pickle because
it's changed because it's it's cured now it's
a completely different animal just like whole milk
and parmesan cheese is not the same thing
it's completely different you know you can't even
consider parmesan to be dairy anymore literally it's
completely different just like that heavily processed cucumber
sauce that they put on a lot of
greek wraps is uh is is pretty good
but it's because yeah but it's been processed
with garlic and salt and pepper so it's
and it's minimal yeah right it's called tzatziki
yeah uh and they don't really make it
anymore because it's gotten popular so they yeah
it's mixed with mayo and all kinds of
but it is good it is good it's
uh there's also an there's an indian one
similar with a very watery yogurt sauce some
carrot and fennel but i just gave you
the rest of that for people you want
to dry your meat before you cook it
doesn't matter what it is because when you
put it in the flame if it has
any water on it any moisture it will
not go above 220 or 212 degrees until
that moisture is gone so you're literally steaming
the meat that you want a nice roast
on right because i remember mostly white people
when i tell them dry the meat or
if it's a turkey a chicken a steak
hang it up so it's dry to the
touch when you touch it there is no
moisture it's actually dry like a potato would
be dry right or you know and they're
like i want my meat to be moist
i don't want oh my gosh they don't
understand because when the meat is wet when
you put it in the fire it will
be dry when you're done because you're boiling
it you're not roasting it or broasting it
so uh the same goes with veggies if
you're going to uh want to get a
nice color i do like what i call
a veggie roast with various sliced vegetables and
uh i put a little salt on them
and i put them in a colander to
air dry so when they hit the pan
and the pan is at 350 400 guess
what the vegetable goes to 400 right away
it gets a beautiful golden caramelization if the
vegetables are wet they you know you can
have a hot pan with one drop of
water in it and it will not go
above 200 degrees or 220 until that drop
of water is gone it's a phenomenal thing
about water also so learn how to dry
your food if you want to roast broast
saute years ago that's why when they did
a roast in the oven you know uh
you you rubbed butter or oil on it
on the surface right yep so it wasn't
water that was that hit the meat met
the heat it was butter or oil to
get that uh and when i cook these
the stuff out on the mesquite grill there's
nothing dripping on the grill there's it doesn't
need maybe one drop of liquid you see
white people grilling and the chicken is running
all the juices are going into the fire
everything's catching fire i'm like oh my gosh
you're not doing that because if you're grilling
properly nothing you don't have any drippings coming
out of it so if you're used to
grilling or roasting and drippings coming out you're
not doing it right or i wouldn't say
you're doing it wrong but you're definitely not
doing it right you know if it's edible
it's not wrong uh so