The sonic entity known as Ocelli is here to greet you.
Today, we're going to be talking about Ocelli, the sonic entity known as Ocelli.
with the patriot movement de facto du jour.
Du jour means by law, by how things should be done, and de facto is by force.
But it ends up being done that way anyway.
You know, like a stolen election, for example, would be a de facto leader, right?
Because a du jour leader would be, you know, the votes are counted and blah, blah, blah, right?
See, I always took du jour to mean, look, you have a choice.
And I always took de facto to mean, this is just what ends up happening because this is the way things go.
Either one, you don't have a choice.
But no, actually, de facto, you have more choice because this is how it works.
Du jour just means by the book, by the law, by the day, like soup du jour.
That's how I learned about du jour.
When I heard de facto and du jour, I said, I know about soup du jour.
You know, the sandwich boards, you know, at the diners or whatever.
And then I said, well, what's de facto?
And if the people don't go along with it, it won't last.
You know, here's the thing.
They give you this false history about all these dictators, right?
In other words, they're painted in a bad light.
And no dictator, no matter how powerful they seem to be, will last more than a week if the people don't want them there.
This is just how it works.
And the people, you know, the military come from the people, right?
Conscription or whatever it is, whatever kind of military you have.
And, you know, by the way, you know, the modern militaries are not really du jour militaries.
They're all contract militaries.
And there's a movie called Jarhead, which I enjoyed because of that,
because whenever they were questioning orders, they'd be told, you know, you signed a contract, right?
Well, I always found it interesting, the people that told me about getting out of the military,
even when they were, you know, drafted, because I always thought of drafting as one of those things that you can't get out of.
But apparently you still require consent, right?
I mean, that's the word I always think of is, you know what, it still requires your consent.
And a lot of people say, well, look, there's no choice here.
And I always say, but at some point, they do require the consent of the people, otherwise they can't operate, right?
I mean, or am I crazy?
No, that's right.
You are crazy, too, though.
But let's just say the de facto part, anyone who's hanging around with me long enough has to be crazy.
But the de facto is by the people allowing it or a significant portion.
By the way, it's not 51 percent.
Anything more than 10 or 15 percent of the people or definitely more than 20 or 30 percent can rule the rest.
You know, it's not that much.
You know, that's the funny thing is everybody seems to think that it takes an actual majority.
Now, that may be the way voting goes in Congress or whatever, supposedly.
But truth is that when it comes down to it, it's a vocal minority.
And I think you're exactly right.
It's about 30 percent.
If you get a very vocal and active minority at 25 to 30 percent, game over.
It looks like everyone's in step because then they can cover up any dissent very easily.
Well, yeah.
And you also have just the general apathy, too, where, you know, there's plenty of people that it's like, oh, today it's a dictatorship.
Tomorrow it's a benevolent dictatorship.
Whatever.
You know, like they don't engage.
Well, a benevolent dictatorship would be a benevolent monarch.
And that's the best government for humans.
Yeah, you said that.
Because they form that anyway.
Look at Lord of the Flies or Animal Farm.
You throw a bunch of people on an island or an isolated area, they're going to form.
They're going to get the alpha dog up with his cohorts and, again, 30 percent of the group.
And they're going to make them the rulers.
That happens every time, everywhere.
So that's how you know there's a real revolution, when you have a group of people, not just one leader, you know.
So it's always done by council.
But, again, it's a very small – Animal Farm, Lord of the Flies, you know, is a group.
You know, you'll have the alpha pair or a single, and then he has his two or three sidekicks.
He's number one, you know.
Well, and some people say, look, you need administrators to, you know, exercise authority, right?
And I get that, and that's true.
I mean, one man, unless there are people that follow his orders, can't really do much, right?
I mean, what do you think of that?
I think it's – well, you don't want to do much.
You can't do much.
I was having a conversation about this with someone, and it's like, man, you could do all this stuff.
How come you're not like a billionaire, or why aren't you so successful?
I mean, define success, right?
I don't want to do anything.
Because I know, like, for example, personally, whenever I get into a project and I put 150 percent into it –
and by the way, if you, let's say, start a business or do a project, you can put 150 percent into it.
What that means is 100 percent is all of your time now,
and the other 50 percent you get from planning on doing stuff next week.
You know what I mean?
That's how you could put 150 percent.
So if someone calls you and says, hey, you want to go fishing next week?
No way, man.
I got things I got to do.
So that's how you put in 150 percent, right?
By blocking out your time.
You've already allotted all your present past time and your future time to it, right?
But it always gets very successful and prospers and does all this well.
But the moment I decide to take a day off, and even though everybody seems like they're running fine, everything falls apart.
So the thing is, no, I'm never going to do any solo projects again.
Whatever I put out, solo sonics are different, but a solo project in any field is not for me,
because it means that it's going to take up 150 percent of my life or the life that I'm living, let's say.
So I'm always looking, putting out stuff, and then trying to find other people that are interested.
Yeah, I'll guide them.
I'll be the alpha for a while, whatever.
But don't get it running and then step back, take a day off.
Start taking days off in the beginning, right?
So this way you're not surprised, you know what I mean?
So that's how I've been functioning.
Yeah, you find out really quickly how the people that are working under you are functioning.
If you take your days off early, that's for sure, right?
Yeah, so that's the way that these administrations are run, because there's no way –
that's what the administration is, basically.
It's always a group.
Now, it's all paint by numbers.
They tell you directly that you've got plenty of, quote-unquote,
in a lawful sense, subversive organizations like the CFR and the Council of Foreign Relations
and the Trilateral Group and all that.
They make no bones about it, about the State Department and other branches of the government.
Let's say State Department is not a branch of the government, it's part of the executive,
but agencies and departments, they make no bones about it
that they take orders from these other organizations, right?
You've heard this, right?
Oh, yeah, and I don't think I've ever actually asked you about Bilderberg.
I think they're meeting sooner now, right?
I stopped paying attention to them a while ago, but I know that that's what they're meeting.
Yeah, Bilderberg is just the extension of the National Socialist Party of industrialists.
The Bilderberg – when I say National Socialist Party, it's the Nazis, right?
It's just their political group.
The people that propped them up, like the King of Belgium and all these other groups,
they were all forming these other sidekick groups known as the Bilderberg.
There's more.
There's other groups, actually.
I don't have it off the top of my head, but years ago I used to show this to people.
You know the United Nations, right?
Before the United Nations, it was the League of Nations.
Well, there was one that was formed even before the League of Nations that still exists.
You can look it up.
What is the oldest international administrative group?
It still exists, but no one talks about it, right?
Then there's the Vatican, where the state – not the Vatican, where the Pope is,
but they used to have a website and it says we're an 800-year-old red building behind.
We're in Vatican City.
We have nothing to do with the religious part of the Vatican,
but all state departments of the world subscribe to basically what our policies are,
and they can't appeal them.
You know what that means?
They tell all the state departments what to do, and you can't say no.
They used to have a website.
If anyone wants to find them, they were calling themselves something Vaticanus,
nothing to do with Catholicism.
So there's all these groups.
So that's what I mean by paint-by-numbers now.
You don't have to do much anymore because it's all international.
I've also been saying for a very long time there are no national enemies.
Everybody's in the same boat.
It's just like you have the NFL and the whatever, and then the other league,
and the baseball, they have the American League and the National League, right?
Right.
Well, at the end of the day, they're all under the banner of Major League Baseball, right?
Sure.
The divisions, right?
So each team is part of a different – they play the Super Bowl and the Stupid Bowl
and all that stuff.
Well, they're not really enemies because they get traded, don't they?
Players get traded from teams and all that, right?
Oh, yeah.
But it seems like they're having a war when they're on the field.
Get it?
You know, the theater?
Oh, sure.
A war.
So they're all the same.
They do – you can catch what I'm saying behind the scenes.
Like North Korea is supposed to be bad, but who's that basketball player, Rodman?
Rodman, yeah.
He goes and has dinner.
They love him there, right?
He has dinner with them.
But anybody else, you're a spy, right?
Mm-hmm.
Well, he gets sponsored by PotCoin, you know, so it's helpful.
You have the nuclear – you have the real Manhattan Project on 9-11.
So what does Iran do?
Because they're – you know, Obama gives them like $800 million in cash on a private airplane.
I don't know if you remember that.
That kind of went under the radar.
And they – what do they do?
They have the tallest building in Tehran, the PLASCO building, P-L-A-S-K-O.
Okay.
And there's a fire in it for three hours, and it suddenly collapses.
And when they go to clean up the debris, there's molten iron underground as they're digging it.
Right?
Get it?
You know, it's justified.
So they say, we have nuclear devices also, you know, but not to tell the United –
the United States knows that.
They're not enemies.
There are no national enemies.
There is no – China is not a national enemy.
The current CCP was set up by the people who set up Roosevelt,
and the people who set up Roosevelt set up Stalin.
The people who set up Stalin set up Hitler.
You know, the New York Jewish accent, Hitler.
You want to talk about Hitler?
Anyway.
Well, I always find it funny when they bring up Mussolini, too,
because Mussolini is a little bit different.
But, you know, because he actually had this idea about unifying and creating –
because Italy, again, is a fabricated country, right,
which Mussolini is partially responsible for.
Yeah.
You know, but so he has –
Duque, right?
Wasn't he El Duque?
Well, El Duque, yeah.
But the thing is, he was part of fabricating that country, though,
because initially it was the kingdom of Sardinia, the kingdom of Sicily,
and what was left of Rome, right?
So you had these three things come together that were just battling city-states,
and he said, well, why don't we just, you know, form a cooperative here?
And they even instituted the Italian languages,
even instituted through the military.
It's funny because people think of it as, you know, this very ancient thing.
Italy has been around forever.
And I'm like, no, it hasn't, actually.
It's only – it's actually a younger country than America.
And they change their government every three years.
They've had like 50 different governments in the past 75 years since World War II.
But here's the thing about him.
He was a fall guy.
No one wanted to get in that power seat, let's say,
and declare the Vatican City a sovereign state.
Then whoever would do that would take a lot of flack for it, and he did it.
That was his job, by the way, to declare Vatican City a sovereign state.
So that's all he was good for, basically.
Yeah, it's –
But if you study it, I'm just saying it still stands, at least,
that unified thing that he created that people think of as Italy.
And, again, even the language was not something – because if you know about it, right,
Sardinians and Sicilians did not speak the same as Romans, okay?
They just didn't.
But they blended their language together.
And so you know about the Italian language, right?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, so they –
Not in great detail about those differences, but, yeah,
I know that the North and the South are in a big contention always,
politically, culturally, and so on.
Well, right, but that's more of a monetary problem
because the South never was permitted to prosper under the same rules as the North did.
And it didn't matter if the country was unified or otherwise, right?
I mean, look, you've had enough Italian friends.
I'm sure you've heard a hundred different stories about this.
But, you know, there were a whole bunch of wars and things that nobody puts in the history books.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, they call them civil wars.
They call them whatever – yeah, divisions.
Right.
Spain had similar stuff.
You know, like recently Catalan wanted to declare its independence, which is –
Catalanese is not Spanish.
But Franco here, we're talking about all these leaders.
Franco, you've got to really tip your hat off to him.
Yeah, there's an interesting –
Because he –
Nobody talks about him, by the way.
Nobody really –
Yeah.
You never see –
He gave everybody the finger.
After World War II, he says, look, I've got the best German technology,
and I know you guys want to do cessations of hostilities,
but if you think you're going to come over here and mess with me,
I'm going to give you some demonstrations.
And he used electric rockets to blow out – blow some American transports out of the air
that were crossing Gibraltar into the Mediterranean.
He radioed them and says, I know you've got a couple of transports with troops.
I want you to watch what happens.
And electric rockets from the Germans, not –
you know, so they're not powered by rocket fuel, you know,
chemicals coming out the SN.
These are powered by electricity.
Right.
And, you know, talk about hypersonics.
And so they said, okay, let's leave this crazy guy alone.
Well, that would explain why Spain was one of the only major nations in –
you know, there's been various skirmishes all across Europe constantly, right?
I mean, you can't even keep track of how many different little, you know,
civil wars and international, you know, one nation slugging it out with another one
for a couple of months, a couple of years at a time, left and right, right?
But you ever notice that Spain is like the only major country that nobody steps up to attack?
Nobody.
Yeah.
I mean, France is invaded constantly.
They still have enough of it.
Enough of it is dug up underground that they've got a lot of goodies that are 50-,
75-year-old ordnance that still rivals anything the Americans are telling you
in public that they have.
Right.
I mean, it's just – so that explains that.
Hey, you know, speaking about things that have been dug up,
and you were talking about, you know, how you sort of become the alpha
and inspire or, you know, give a few pointers to people and see where they go,
I did note in the chat that there's a few people starting to work with magnets a bit, huh?
Yeah, that's a good thing.
It's impressive.
Even if they don't do it well or right, according to what I've been professing lately,
it still works.
But what I'm really leaning on very heavily is when you pass the fluid near the magnet,
don't pass – make sure you're not passing it anywhere where everyone else is passing it,
like not where the magnet is reactive, right, or the center, the outer edge,
where nothing's going on is where you want it to be.
Right, not where the pole is, not where you're trying to actually –
you keep bringing it up, stick it to the refrigerator.
Yeah.
Oh, that sticks really hard.
That must be a strong magnet.
No, no, no, no.
Go exactly in the opposite direction.
Not there.
And I haven't defined the block wall.
I just say put it on the block wall because, you know, enough people can look up what that means.
It's the center point where nothing – if you hold any shape magnet to the refrigerator,
you'll notice that there's part of the magnet that does not want to go to the refrigerator.
That's where you run the fluid.
Right, and I have several other ways to do it because some of the really large magnets
that I've been using lately, they're $500 magnets, right, for one magnet,
and it's not really cost effective.
I have a photo of one in the chat.
No, but if you want to spend money, you know, they make – you've heard of the band Monster Magnet, right?
No.
Well, there's a band called Monster Magnet from New Jersey,
and they got the name because they were UPS delivery guys
and they were delivering what was referred to as a monster magnet in the early 90s.
And I'm giving you this weird back story, but the thing is –
Yeah, they couldn't get it out of the truck.
Well, it was funny because it had to be handled just a certain way and all that,
but those magnets, if you want to spend a whole lot of money, you can.
Back then, those were the magnets for what they call MRI machines, right?
And they called them monster magnets.
And you don't need a giant expensive magnet to accomplish most things like that.
I mean, you know, what are you doing?
You're picking up cars?
You've seen the wreckers that pick up the cars, right?
Well, you do what's called a Halbach Array with small magnets,
but the thing here is there's a way to do it with any shape magnet.
You just stack them like they normally stack together
and then bend them around the, let's say, pipe if you're doing water.
And if you show it to an engineer or a scientist, they'll say,
that's not going to do anything.
That's not where the field is.
That's exactly how you want it.
But the thing that I'm excited about is there is a major reduction in mineral content
with no loss of volume.
What that means is this.
When you have a liquid and you have something diluted in it,
it affects the volume of the liquid, right?
To a degree.
And when you remove that, whatever is diluted in the liquid,
you should have a change of volume and weight, and there isn't with this.
So where is it going?
Where are the minerals going?
And when I first started measuring this,
I noticed a 40 to 60 percent decrease in mineral content.
And I thought, I've got to go buy a new meter.
There's something wrong, right?
Then I get a report back from someone else.
They noticed the same amount of decrease.
I'm like, well, a meter is just fine, right?
And then someone else noticed the same kind of decrease
and said, wow, this is really playing with the ether.
So this is even more exciting.
Yeah, I want to ask a couple of stupid questions, if you don't mind, about that,
because here's where it doesn't make sense, right?
I mean, literally speaking, if I was to think, okay, you have mineral content in water,
and if the mineral content is removed, if it's no longer present,
then that means you must have removed a substance from the water.
If you didn't remove it, and it appears to have the same exact volume in whole, right?
The whole thing has the same volume, whether it has the minerals present or not.
Where did it go?
And in fact, what is actually keeping the content of the water at the same volume
if you didn't remove anything?
So here's my stupid question.
Doesn't that mean that you've literally come up with a way to have something be transmuted,
turned into something else?
Into water, yeah.
If it spends enough time in the water, those minerals are water-based, right?
So the minerals become more water.
Yeah.
Okay, I know it sounds like a dumb question.
It's not a big deal.
They don't want to, the establishment is, they're morons, right?
I mean, you know how I've said this.
If you spend more than, by the eighth grade, if you haven't realized you've been bullshitted to,
and you're going to be bullshitted the rest of your life,
and you continue past the eighth grade and get university,
you deserve to be bullshitted to even more because it's pretty obvious.
So these guys, you know, they're in bad shape.
But transmutation is a bad word.
Ether is a bad word, all these things.
So you don't have to use those words.
You can use other words.
What's the use of transmutation?
I mean, because that's all I can think of.
That's what would happen.
If you turn something into something else, I mean, other people would say,
Oh, that's alchemy.
But no, that's not alchemy exactly.
It is.
It is alchemy because alchemy means you're using the spirit, you know, the essence of the human.
And by the way, you need to be like a, quote, unquote,
a special person spiritually to be an alchemist, just like to be a shaman or a magi.
By the way, it's funny, I put sorcerer in a translate to see what it was in Greek, and it's magi.
Okay.
Magus, right?
Right.
Very interesting, right?
So you need to be above the rest.
In other words, lesser people can't do this kind of stuff, alchemy, you know, in the traditional form.
Like when you read about, like you watch Lord of the Rings, they show the wizard.
He's a higher being, you know, as terms of humans are concerned, right?
They have to be very sensitive and sensible and very much aware of their own stuff.
You know, they've already learned to cancel the voice in their head, which we could get into a little bit.
I've been getting a lot of feedback on that.
And people are starting to talk about it more and more, by the way, I heard on the Internet, synchronicity.
Well, actually, yeah, that's funny because people totally separate from you or people that I know listen to you.
I have taken note that a few people are talking about this now.
And, you know, look, not the same way you are.
But they are beginning to mention it.
And that was not present even a year ago, I'm sure.
No, not even recently.
It's because you have to be in tune with there's a collective, but you don't want to be part of the collective.
But you just kind of look, you're a cattle rancher, right?
You're not a cow, you're a man.
But you have to be in tune with the herd, right?
There's nothing wrong with being a cattle rancher and being in tune with the herd.
It's totally fine.
But once you become part of the herd, well, now you've got a problem, right?
Well, look, it's good to know when a stampede is coming.
I mean, you should be in tune enough to know that, right?
Sure.
And you also want to know what calms them down, too, right?
Oh, yeah.
Just for your own self-defense, right?
Yeah, and also it doesn't have to be cows or sheep.
It could be fish and birds.
But, yeah, so where are we going with this?
There's no national enemies de facto and du jour.
You live in a de facto.
Okay, it's a de facto world, but it's not like they're imposing things on people.
The people want it that way.
They're accommodating the people, right?
I think I've mentioned to you before, I was at the pharmacy, drugstore,
one of these big chain ones getting various sundries, gauze and things like that
to re-up a first aid kit.
And there was a man, a tall, skinny, white guy in his late 70s, probably 80,
yelling at the pharmacist about why they're taking so long
to get his blood pressure medication, right?
Because if he doesn't get it, he'll die.
And I was like, oh, my gosh, oh, my gosh, where do you start with that guy?
What did you decide to do with that guy?
I'm curious because I know you probably sat there and said, oh, my,
and shook your head at least.
He's a goner.
He's dead.
He just doesn't know it.
He's one of those, like the Christ said, let the dead bury the dead, right?
See, I don't know.
When I hear people uttering things that are completely ignorant, though,
I often feel obligated to step forward and see if they don't want to be ignorant
for a moment.
I don't know why.
He was enraged, and he was one of these nuisance individuals
where you need one of those bug zappers, a big one, like an eight-foot one
that you'd slam him with.
But anyway, that's not my job.
That's public service that someone else is going to have to do.
But here's the thing.
What I do with the pharmacists is I always go, when they're not busy,
I get their attention, and I point to the blood pressure machine.
You put coin in it, right?
Oh, yeah.
You sit down.
You put your arm in it.
You put the coin in it.
Where do I get one of these?
I need one of these.
And he's like, well, why do you want it?
He says, I don't know.
We just rent it, you know, or we share, you know, whatever.
They pay or we pay to have it here.
I said, well, why do you want it?
And I said, because I'm starting a museum on medical quackery and fakery,
and this is going to be one of the displays.
And they kind of looked at me, and they nodded their head.
None of them defended.
You know, you could say they're busy and what they're doing.
But one day, one guy, when I said that, I went around.
I did some more shopping in the store.
It's one of these large, you know, grocery stores or like a Safeway type thing.
And he was leaving.
It was the end of his shift.
And he says, so really?
Is it medical fakery and quackery?
And I went over, and he just agreed with everything I said.
I gave him five minutes of Greek speak on how the body works, and he says, yeah, that's right.
But he just goes back and does what he does, you see.
So his moral and ethical content.
Anyone who is moral ethical will say, I better quit my job.
This sucks, right?
So that's the de facto.
The people, they know what's wrong.
This is, you know, and they just keep going along with it.
That's why I keep saying it.
You cannot have a better society with the people that are here now.
So you don't think it's moral or ethical to sit there and leave it there and tell people maybe, hey, look, you know, let me enlighten you to something here.
You know that that's a bunch of bullshit sitting there, right?
I mean, you don't think that that could be a useful thing to do to try and get people to start to think about it, that at least maybe there's something to.
Not these people.
What you would do, let's say you told me tomorrow the population will be down to just a few million across the world.
Then you can travel and every hundred miles you see a dozen people.
You could talk to those people.
Oh, OK.
Right?
But not the masses that are here now.
They're goners.
They were goners a long, long time ago.
They were goners when the World War started because they would have never gone for it.
And by the way, you don't hear about the call about World War II, the Great Generation, all this bullshit.
All the protests against fighting the Pacific and the European theater, there were huge protests and they've been completely scrubbed from history.
The only way you can hear about that now is if you talk to somebody who was alive then who remembers because that's it.
There's no books on that.
Even up until the Vietnam War, a lot of people were jailed, especially of the black community.
Directly?
Hell no.
Yeah.
Muhammad Ali was one of them, right?
They call them protesters.
How many people went up to Canada, right?
And all that.
Even that was covered up to a degree.
But, yeah, so the de facto and de jure, I've revisited this because it's all de facto.
But when enough people, we're not talking about just the 20 or 30 percent, let's say sort of a requirement to keep the entire population in check.
But it seems like everyone, if you're going along with it, right, you're still part of that de facto system.
So is there really a de facto and de jure?
I think it's all de facto.
I think the last time I kind of ranted about no one is following anything that they have memorialized in their reference books at all.
That's why it's interesting if you read old encyclopedias, let's say the authors or the compilers of encyclopedias,
there were companies that hired people to do research and compile encyclopedia definitions and stories about the subject matter.
You look up in an encyclopedia.
Yeah, they just aggregate all kinds of information.
Yeah, they were not part of the standard academic community.
They were encyclopedia compilers, right?
And they weren't invited to the same parties that the academics were in all this.
So when you read the old encyclopedias, they put little digs, especially with scientific stuff.
When you read in an old encyclopedia, they'll put a little dig against the academic community if you know how to pick it up, right?
It's kind of funny if you're reading it with comprehension.
Like we look up water, they'll tell you, you know, one cubic centimeter or one gram of water is supposed to be one gram of water.
But it's really not because when they took the measurements in the reference books, it was at room temperature, not at 39.
So it's really 0.99994, right?
So it's like a dig, you know, that's basically telling you that, you know.
There's lots of little digs that you'll see in old encyclopedias against the academic community.
So I feel like the sentiment that I have against academia is not I'm not against academia.
I'm just against what they're doing, the same with the attorneys and the doctors.
It's not I'm not against attorneys or doctors.
It's just that the ones that we have worldwide are not doing what they're supposed to be doing, right?
So and there really are going to movies on the job.
You know, imagine going to work in a factory.
You put the punch card in and then you go to the movies.
That's not what you were hired for, right?
You know, but maybe it was actually because if you're supposed to do nothing and make nothing move forward, make nothing be accomplished.
Well, then you are doing your job, aren't you?
Yeah.
You're doing the job you were given anyway.
You know, that's what it's like.
Yeah, I actually thought of this last week because I had somebody on my show that I had a thing that went on where people could sign up to volunteer to be guests on the show.
People I've never met before, you know, didn't encounter on my own.
And the one guy made a documentary, which I don't know.
I don't know what you would think of it.
I actually meant to pass it by you, and I don't think I've gotten to it yet.
But the premise of this, he starts, you know, he talks about COVID and all this and how it's a big scam, right?
But he's coming at it from a slightly different angle, and I'm sort of surprised that this has been allowed to even exist.
It's been out for a couple of years now.
He attacks the whole thing about virology and how this is like just quackery and that, you know, viruses are quackery.
And, you know, look, at a certain point, there was just this ridiculousness where they started agreeing that viruses are what's making people sick.
And I said to myself, you know, that is vaguely what the Greek has kind of said.
I know it's not exactly the same, but it's very similar to a lot of what you've said about the medical community and the things that, you know, on and on.
I mean, when we touched on COVID on here, you pretty much said very similar things.
But he was breaking it down and showing people that, like, even the concept of this is a virus and everything else is all a bunch of fiction.
It's garbage.
Well, I've been saying the same things.
If you took a transcript of what I said about the medical community in the 1980s, mid-'80s,
and you took a transcript of what I've said about it recently and you held the two transcripts up to the light, it would be identical.
I haven't really changed because I've been watching it closely and studying it.
I stopped studying it over a decade ago because I found out that they're no longer doing research.
Well, nothing new.
There's no reason for it.
It's so funny, though, because I think you would find it interesting.
This is weird.
I don't think I ever recommend a documentary to you, but I think you might want to look at this one.
Okay, well, are you familiar?
There was a major lawsuit.
Well, it became major sort of in the 1990s.
A group of doctors in Germany were suing the textbook companies and whatever for writing down viruses.
It went on for about a decade, and at the end, in a little court date thing, they said, well, it's inconclusive,
so the doctor that's suing the textbook companies for talking about viruses and the health authorities has to pay their legal fees
because you can't conclude this case.
So that's how they shut him up.
Yeah, he touched upon that in the documentary but didn't really give us the conclusion to it
because the whole thing ends up being kind of tossed aside as inconclusive.
And the medical establishment, yeah.
Well, the medical establishment just basically said, look, it doesn't matter if it's real or not.
This is the direction we're going in.
I mean, that was the general point after an hour of listening to this whole thing.
And he was going to people that were scientists and stuff going, you know, look, here's what the scientific method should be,
and here's what they did, and they were trying to illustrate it.
So I just, I don't know.
I found it interesting.
Well, you're not.
Title 12 U.S.C. 411 says it all, you know, about the lawful money.
Right.
The Federal Reserve.
You're not authorized to use the money, so everyone's using it, so you're a scofflaw.
Your scofflaw means that you know the law, you just don't care about it, right?
So, yeah.
Speaking of medical, I want to throw in something on the cancer thing we did last time.
A while back, when you study just a segue in a way, people fear it, right?
And, by the way, most people that I diagnosed with cancer don't have cancer.
They get sick from the treatment, just like AIDS or whatever, right?
You know AIDS is completely fabricated, right?
I think just to recap.
Another thing that was in that documentary, by the way, is how that was all a complete hoax as well.
It's just like 19 Arab hijackers vaporized the World Trade Center with box cutters.
It's that stupid.
You know, when I tell this to people, they say, that's not how the story goes.
Oh, really?
Well, tell me the official story then and compare it.
It's so stupid.
So, the AIDS thing is that first, they always do propaganda.
You know, get the test, get the test.
And once you get the test and they decide to make it positive, just like the COVID, by the way.
I met a nurse at the smoke shop.
Because I was talking in Project Event 201 in November.
Oh, yeah, right.
In 2019, I was telling people, watch what they're going to do with this because they're ready to lock down 100 million people in China.
There's an example that you could lock.
If you could lock down 100 million people, you could lock down 500 million.
If you could lock down 500 million, you could lock down a billion.
If you could lock down a billion, you could lock down 5 billion, right?
So, I was saying this before it all started.
And it's all a fraud.
But I met a nurse and she says, yeah, we got 10 COVID tests.
We put on gloves.
We went into a clean room.
We took them out of the delivery package and just opened all the packages and then put them back in the send-back packages.
Nothing touched anything.
And seven out of the ten came back positive.
Right?
It's all scam.
No sample whatsoever.
You're telling me no sample whatsoever in a clean room and they just send them back?
Because when you get the box, it has the tests and then the package you're supposed to send it back.
And all they did was transfer it out of the new, open the package and transfer it into the send-back package without touching anything.
And sterile.
Nice.
In a clean room with gloves and masks and everything to, you know, a nurse-type setup.
Make sure it doesn't touch anything.
Very little contact with the air.
And 70% came back positive.
It's complete fraud.
And they do that.
And when people working in the hospital say this is a fraud, the administrators will say, well, you know, you know, you know.
That's all they would say.
Right?
It's about money.
So the AIDS thing was very similar, actually worse.
What they did is once you got the AIDS test, which was not a test for anything, actually it was like a PCR-type test.
I told people if you take an AIDS, if you want to test positive on it, eat a raw steak, like rare steak or a couple of hamburgers.
And four or five hours, the PCR will always show an explosion of those mucus in the blood, let's say pus in the blood from eating meat.
But what they do is once you test positive, they have your information, contact information, right?
Because they won't test you.
How do you know you got positive?
Because they contacted you.
They'd send a barrage of contacts.
Well, you know, they don't say you have AIDS.
They said you tested positive for a very serious thing.
You should consider treatment.
Three days later, you get another envelope.
You tested very serious for this.
If you really want to continue in your life, and they start telling you about yourself, you have two children, this and that, you should consider treatment.
Well, once you start getting the treatment, then you come down with AIDS, right?
Basically, the AIDS treatment is a hormone that the body naturally produces when a cell is replaced, epithelial apoptosis.
Apoptosis is when the cells are replaced in the body.
Some are replaced daily.
And when the cell falls off and goes out to be distributed, turns into energy, and then it's excreted, again, as material, a hormone is produced.
I forgot.
There's three or four different hormones stemmed from the same thing.
So what they do is that AIDS treatment has that drug, that hormone in it.
So when you take the treatment, it tells the body that the cells have been replaced.
But they haven't been.
So your cells start falling off internally and externally, but they're not replaced because the body's been tricked thinking that they're replaced.
And you start looking like crap.
You get all the sores.
You whittle away.
Children get these big tumors of fat under the skin, and you die.
And, of course, everybody claps their hands because you died of AIDS.
Stay away from whatever, you know?
It validates it, right?
Just like the people who were put on ventilators during COVID, and they were not given any water for a week.
They jam the ventilator.
They sedate them.
Make sure they give them extra sedation.
No water, no food, very little.
And they adjust the mixture just right until you cease to exist.
And I know two people that have gone that way.
And I have no pity for them whatsoever because I told them, you go to the hospital, you're going to die.
So, you know, that's the thing.
Actually, their family didn't either.
They said, we knew that was going to happen.
That's really interesting, right, how humans really work.
It just shows you you're just passing through here.
Death is not as big of a deal as it's been made.
You know, in ancient times, the more people cried for someone when they died, the more honorable they were.
So what you did is you went and hired mourners, professional mourners, to come to the funeral.
And what they did was they stood around where they were in high visibility areas, and they cried and cried and cried for hours.
Talk about vanity.
That's the kind of vanity that, remember when the cell phones came out in the 90s?
Right.
It was like, oh, wow, you know.
Well, China made like 500 million fake cell phones, passed them out.
So in China, people, you know, they were walking around like they had a cell phone.
It was a piece of plastic.
Vanity, right?
It was a marker of prestige.
Yeah, exactly.
So this is what, you know, the play on death is, is they see, oh, I'm so sorry.
That's why it's like don't ever invite me to do a eulogy or whatever, because I'm going to tell you the truth about the person.
You know, I've been, even with family members, do you want me to go to the eulogy and actually stand up and tell everyone what a scumbag this person was?
No, no, don't do it.
You better not come.
Yeah.
Right?
So, yeah, I'm not going to mince words on that.
Just tell them what should be said.
So let's stop.
You know, it's very simple.
So that's how that works with the AIDS thing.
And, actually, there's a lot of medical people that know this, but they just go along with it, you know.
So what do you call it when you're an accomplice?
That's a criminal thing, too.
Right.
So, yeah, cancer, one of the things that I spoke through about it was tagged on with the allergies and all that, is that in a complex way, this is very advanced, by the way,
the material that you find in these tumors is either a biogenesis of the body reproducing teeth or hair inside of a tumor that's under, like behind someone's kidney, let's say.
How can you have teeth and hair in it once they remove it, right?
The body is just flipping out, and I'll talk about that.
But in some of the fluids, when they're tested, it's plant matter, right?
In other words, it's not like chewed up plant matter, but it has the same material that you find in pre-digested or semi-digested plant matter or meat.
The food that goes into the body, that energetically goes into the blood by the intestines through induction, reverts back to food.
So if it reverts back to food when it's in the blood, it's very, very dangerous, right?
You know, you don't imagine injecting someone with spinach juice, right?
You don't want to have, like, a steak, you know, a purified steak in your blood injected, and that would be messy.
Yeah, so this is what's happening.
Now, from the other hand, what they call a cancerous tumor or malignant and all this other stuff is the body is in such disorder that, for example,
I have a hazmat manual somewhere, you know, the hazardous material.
And a lot of the stuff is very practical, by the way, the hazmat manuals, because it's about spillage control.
Usually with hazmat, it's liquids and gases, mostly liquids, and how to stop.
So when the liquid spills, the first thing you've got to do is stop it from spreading.
So they have, like, these tubes, like sandbags, right, like these 10-foot-long sandbags that you lay down on the ground, and they're heavy.
They prevent the liquid from spilling, right?
Well, that's what the body is doing with cysts and tumors.
There is an energetic flow in the body.
The left side, the energy flows down.
On the right side of the body, the energy flows up, both men and women.
The way that it works, the difference between men and women is from the top down.
When you're looking at the crown of the head, one is counterclockwise, one is clockwise when they're standing up.
But the energetic flow, the general major flow in the body, the entire left,
you just draw a line through your nose and center your head down through the groin, between your legs, your left leg, your whole entire left side.
Energy goes down, right side energy goes up.
So you'll notice that these energy points, where the tumors form along the body,
is what level of energy is either being blocked or is deficient.
So when an energy needs to be blocked, and let's say you're eating foods and chemicals and things,
that the energy is always rising and it has to be discharged.
When it gets to the left side of the body, that kind of energy needs to be discharged upwards.
But the side that discharges energy upwards is completely saturated,
so it starts to go on the side that wants to go down.
Let's say the left side, and it doesn't want it to go down, so it puts a tumor there to block it.
So the tumor kind of, it's like the hazmat sandbags, right?
So what it's telling you is that you've got a messed up energy flow.
It's all energy because there's no absorption, right?
So when you take nutrition in the intestine, it's broken down into energy,
just like you would transmit a signal, and it's received on the inside of the body,
and then it rematerializes like the Star Trek beaming up into the material that the body needs, right?
Okay.
So that energy, even when the cells can't use it or don't want to use it,
once it gets until the wrong, if it's an energy that's supposed to go down,
and you have too much of that, once it gets to the right side,
which is where all the energy goes up, it'll form a tumor.
So it's very interesting when I've spoken to oncologists and this and that,
what side, where's the tumor?
Is it on the left side or the right side?
And depending on what side it's on, it's, oh, this person's doing too much of this.
You found this in their blades.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
How can you figure that out just from the side of the body that it's on, right?
Duh, you know?
But they're not taught any of this.
So what these tumors are and these cancers that form that are measurable tissue,
it could be on the skin anyway, internally, it could be external,
they're blockages just like the hazmat sandbags to stop,
and it has to do with up and down, right?
The left side going down, the right side going up.
Very, very interesting.
I just wanted to mention that's what it is.
And, by the way, let's go back to the hazmat.
If you've got to call a hazmat crew in to come and put leak or spillage protection down,
that's pretty serious stuff, isn't it?
Well, it is.
They make you do it, though.
Okay, so I told you I ran gas stations,
and allegedly we were supposed to do that if one gallon of gas hits the ground,
we're supposed to call in a hazmat crew, right?
Yeah, they got the absorbers and all that.
Yeah, but I mean, generally speaking, in a practical sense, look,
I mean, I could keep a bag of kitty litter around and control small spills.
You know what I mean?
Not that big a deal.
But that was the general consensus is that you had to call them in,
and every industry like that has a level that they determine,
okay, you know, you've got this dangerous whatever,
and you have different ways that you're supposed to act,
and eventually, yeah, you call in a team that's dedicated to dealing with it,
and that's that, right?
Sure, it could be over, but that's a good point you made.
You know why?
Because a lot of the missed, no doctor will say you have cancer and sign to it.
They'll show you a lab report,
and it says, oh, because it has a presence of this and that,
and it could be one cell, right?
And a lot of people go under therapy and they, you know, whatever.
So, yeah, it could be over, like you said, one gallon.
It could be one cell on the test, and they say you have cancer, right,
which was just something that appeared and disappeared.
Well, that's why I found it interesting that people started just getting, you know,
like these melanoma, they were calling it, you know, being removed from the skin,
and it's like, okay, so you got rid of the cancer on the skin,
and then that's the end of it, right?
And, no, it's not because, you know, they have to actually cut around
and take away some healthy tissue and this and that,
and the next thing you know is then they got you in treatment,
and then the treatment makes them sick, and I go, oh, man, you know.
Yeah, I wouldn't remove it like that.
It depends, because when they remove the healthy tissue,
see, the reason it's there is to block an energy,
and when you remove the extra tissue around it, now it's like, wait a second,
we need that to block the energy, so now we got to spread more in a bigger area.
That's usually what happens.
I've heard many people whose parents go to a medical technician.
Calling them doctors, they're not deserving of that.
But you would have a spot on their ankle, and they remove that,
and it gets infected, then they have to remove the leg,
and then they get cancer, and then they die, right?
So if they left the spot there, it would have fallen off in a year or two,
depending if it's on the left or the right.
Usually the society that we live in, it's eating chemicals and expansive things,
what's called the yin type foods, expansive, very fast-moving,
high-dispersing energy, chemicals, plants that are from the tropics,
out of season, all that.
It's mostly too much yin.
And it discharges on the right side of the body,
but if you have too much of it, it has to go over to the other side
and discharge from there, right?
Just like if you put too much gasoline in the piston,
it's going to come out the exhaust, raw gasoline, right?
That's where you get that backfiring, right?
So it's going to backfire to the left side of the body,
and the body's like, we don't want this upward energy, only downward energy,
so it forms a tumor on the left side, depending on what height of the body.
Usually it's center mass.
If it's legs or arms, it'll be on the skin.
So basically eating a holistic diet, fasting first,
and we'll normalize the body.
Some things that get stuck inside the membrane of the body,
literally like World Trade Center,
if you were there that day, you breathe that dust in.
If it happened to be from deep underground,
it's going to be irradiating you from the inside out
if you have the physical dust in your lungs, right?
If it goes through the body, your intestines, and you swallow,
it'll come out in a few days, and you might actually feel better from it,
give you a little boost.
But if it gets stuck in the lungs, it's microwaving you,
irradiating you day and night, day and night, day and night,
and the body needs to block that, and it forms cancers.
And it's funny, there was a fireman that, before the towers came down,
he was running towards the building,
and about 20 feet in front of him, the sidewalk exploded,
and a stream of hot steam went up about 50 feet in the air.
And he kind of, even though he was far away from it,
he got blasted by it, and he had to have his nose removed
because he had all these melanomas developing on his face.
And he still didn't, you know, you told me it was nuclear.
He said, oh, no, they never told us it was nuclear.
And he's having all these cancers that are only caused by radiation.
So, you know, you can't help people like that.
And that's why the truth will never get out to the masses.
Well, you know, because Christy Todd Whitman would never lie to anybody or anything, right?
Right, right.
But it's all, look, Napoleon lied.
Everybody, they go all the way back.
Caesar lied, you know.
It goes all the way back.
It's just the way business is done.
So, yeah, so the cancer thing is really your body's trying to block it.
Now, here's, I've been getting some messages on food.
The last time I did discuss one way to, a healthy body, healthy mind, right,
and healthy mind, healthy body.
So if you have a healthy body, the mind will function better, right?
Well, one assists the other.
And if you have a healthy mind, you keep the body healthy.
Well, one will assist the other anyway, right?
I mean, if you physically feel better, your mind is clearer.
And if your mind is clearer, you'll physically feel better.
I mean, it's just simple.
I mean, that's observable, right?
I mean, that's, I don't know how much more to simplify that.
And the easiest way to do that is to put what the body works best with, which is whole food.
And it could be, I kind of talked about macrobiotics because of the analogies.
Like I said, when they first started introducing,
I knew Shizuko Yamamoto and Michio Kushi personally.
And when they first came in the crew, when they landed from Japan and California,
like I said many times, it's worth repeating,
they would do these public seminars, invite the public in to introduce them to eating.
It was basically a modified Japanese diet, right,
but with whole foods and no meats, no four-legged animals generally.
And the only repeat people that kept coming back were the hippies.
And they stopped one day and said, okay, no one else is coming back but you guys.
Why do you keep coming back?
It's because when we eat the brown rice, we feel high all the time and we don't have to buy drugs.
So what's wrong with that, right?
And it's true.
Like for example, I suggest people get some Lundberg brown rice.
It's the only, okay.
Let me just do a little diversion.
You've heard of Goya Foods, right?
You're from back east.
It's all over the country now.
Of course.
Okay.
There was an interview a long time ago on NPR, not NPR, KXCI,
which is a private radio station in New York.
It's like the super leftist, but anybody will get on there, right?
Okay.
It's kind of like American Freedom Radio or something, right, back in the 90s.
So they had the great grandson of the Goya Food Company, and he gave the history.
He says when the Latins started coming over to the U.S. and they wanted to buy beans and rice,
it would be like basically a white people market.
So you buy the beans, you bring them home, and some of them are the wrong, you know, mixed sizes.
Some are broken.
You get the rice, it's kind of like dusty, and some of the grain is broken, right?
So they're used to, they're very prideful on their food.
So they started that based on that, you know, so good quality.
By the way, when you buy like Nishiki rice or Lundberg rice and you pour it out of the container to prepare it,
you won't notice one broken grain of rice.
When you buy like a can of Goya beans, whatever beans, and you pour them out,
there's not one broken bean where you could go to Trader Joe's or whatever and buy their best black beans.
You pour them out, there's like broken beans, they're different sizes.
What is this, right?
There's some loose water that might have used to be a bean, but it's not anymore.
Yeah, yeah.
So I like the Nishiki because it's good quality, best quality for the price.
It looks like when you break open a 20-pound bag of rice, sushi rice, that they actually chose each grain with a tweezer.
There's not one broken grain.
The same with the Lundberg.
That just means they take pride in what they're doing, and it's very high quality.
Well, if you know how to make the brown rice, by the way, don't buy food that you don't know how to cook well.
If you don't know how to cook something well, why bother?
You're going to be wasting the ingredients and not having a good experience.
You do need a good pressure cooker to cook any good rice, any good rice.
It's gotten to the point where this was very well known, but people didn't know how to use a pressure cooker, right,
even though you need one to make rice, so they would destroy the rice again,
so they did converted rice, right, to make it more uniform.
By the way, if you know how to make perfect – I've done – back in the days, I always talk about food.
I talk about how to make perfect rice and just about it.
I've got – and potato stovetop cooking.
You don't have to fire up an oven for all kinds of things, and people have gotten back to me.
So I know I've gotten hundreds of people to making perfect rice.
If you go to like a white Midwestern family and they make rice, it was like, you guys made rice.
Where is it?
They won't even look at the rice pot.
They'll just point.
It's over there.
They'll look the opposite way.
They'll point, it's over there, and you go and you open the lid, and it's just like a big ball of starch.
You can't tell what it is, right?
There's no reason for that.
But anyway, you don't need a pressure cooker either.
If you have a high-quality pot, you just need to be able to put weight on the lid, right,
and as much weight as you want to put.
I have diver weights.
They're made of lead, and so they're like three inches square by one inch thick, and they're four pounds,
because lead is very constant, very heavy.
You could use gold bars too.
It would be a little heavier even, but anyway.
If you have enough gold bars laying around your house, you know.
Yeah.
You just hide them in the brick.
You just paint them red and put them in the brick wall, right?
Right.
That won't help you, by the way, the gold and the silver anymore.
Even scripture talks about that.
So my point here is the easiest way to get some good whole food in your body,
if you're in this world that you're probably listening to me,
is to get some Lundberg organic brown rice, short grain, not the long grain,
and it's more young, right, and it'll cook better and more consistently.
Make that and eat that for a week.
Get some umeboshi plums, umeboshi plum vinegar.
Learn how to roast sesame seeds and grind them with some salt.
Get some sea vegetable, seaweed, right?
Eat that.
Don't switch over.
This is what I tell people about food.
Oh, you've got to change your diet, they say.
What do they do?
They change their diet.
How do they feel?
Like crap.
Right.
You incorporate it.
Look, let's say you're eating McDonald's for breakfast, Burger King for lunch,
and Wendy's for dinner.
Okay, you need to change your diet.
Everybody would pretty much agree.
Right.
Don't stop doing that.
Get the McDonald's, Burger King, and Wendy's for dinner.
Get all that, but don't get as much, and make the brown rice.
Have a pot.
So when you go to McDonald's, instead of getting all this,
just get one little thing and have some brown rice with sea vegetable
and some green tea or something with it.
Do the same, right?
And then what you do is each day you eat less of the McDonald's,
less of the Burger King, less of the Wendy's,
and you eat a little bit more of the brown rice.
You see it?
Right?
That's how you switch your diet.
Don't stop cold turkey.
You know what happens with anything, right, when you do that.
Yeah, you end up on some sort of withdrawal, but, I mean,
it's fairly accurate because your body goes, hey, where the hell is this now?
Yeah.
That I'm used to.
It's like your computer, because it's all electric and information-based.
Your computer, you can go somewhere and get a few cookies and maybe a mild virus.
It still works.
But what if I put 100,000 cookies and five viruses on the computer right away?
What happens?
It stops.
Yeah.
So you just transition very gradually.
Now, I'm not promoting macrobiotics.
There's two reasons.
One is it's a modified Japanese diet.
It's not fair to push that on anyone if you don't have preference for it.
And the other thing is there's very little information.
As time goes on, there's less good information online about it, right?
And the really good books that are out there from it before are too Japanese-centric.
But there's a dichotomy and a duality of the yin and yang that's very evolved.
The basic stuff is good to know, but you will not know how to use yin and yang by going on the Internet either.
That requires, again, maybe a Greek sonic solo just to explain a few examples, right, in a Taoist way.
The Taoists tell stories to make a point, right?
So you don't have to do the macrobiotics.
But if you eat seasonally and cross-lateral, like if it's wintertime, don't eat food that's grown in hot places at the time, right?
And also eat locally and stuff that is extremely fresh.
So let's say you live in Holland, right, or the Netherlands, and you go out and the what they call street vendors,
they have this pickled fish and roasted fish, right?
I forgot what it's called.
It's a herring, a type of herring, I believe.
Right.
And that's local and all that.
It's very fresh.
Eat it.
That's fine.
Wherever you are, there is some local produce or something that you can acquire that's fresh, that's grown locally, hopefully, right?
In New York City, believe it or not, you get some of the best produce in the world because of the farmer market.
It's a real farmer's market.
Real farmers come in, where if you go to L.A., the farmer's market, it's just a bunch of guys unloading, like,
Andy Boy tomatoes that they got at the terminal market, you know what I mean?
Right, right.
It's not a real farmer's market in L.A.
So if you can get some real food that's seasonal, right, that's what I'm talking about.
But you will get the boost of energy from the organic brown rice.
Another way to get a boost of energy for the body is something called kombucha, right?
It's kind of one of those illicit things that the scoby could be considered a mushroom.
It is.
It's not.
It's more of a fermented thing.
But I'll tell you personally, if I drink some kombucha, any kombucha, there's some various qualities.
I feel invigorated, like a high almost, almost like eating the organic food, right?
I mentioned the Barrio Bread Bakery here.
We have a bakery where they locally grow the wheat organically, dry it, grind it into flour, and bake bread out of it, right?
I mean, in other words, you go to most bakeries, they're buying from the big distributors, right,
bags of flour that are mixed from various co-ops.
That's where they came from, yeah.
Yeah, it's not going to be the same thing.
So when you read in ancient times, we need bread to eat, when you ate that bread, it was like steak.
It's not like the bread now.
I mean, it gave you a lot of energy.
So when you go to Barrio Bread here and you get a loaf of bread or a roll, he'll give you a roll sometimes your first time there,
you bite into it, you feel the sensation of love.
I mentioned this the last time we spoke, I think.
Right.
It's like, you know, when you're a teenager and you see someone and you're infatuated, you get that, wow, you know, that feeling, that invigoration?
That rush.
That's what it feels like, that rush, yeah.
Imagine you're getting a rush when you eat.
Here's the thing.
Imagine that every time you ate something, it gave you a rush of energy and it was euphoric and invigorating.
How many people could say that about their food?
Very few, at all anymore.
This is how it should be.
So you limit your diet to things that are very high quality, but don't limit yourself where you don't have variety.
Here's the other thing with cancer also.
If you don't have variety, you'll end up having a very narrow spectrum, right?
And then you'll overdo it and the body wants to block that, you see?
I discovered, especially moving to the southwest, because when I was back east in New York, I associated mostly European people, you know?
And also New Yorkers, which if you live in New York, you're going to be influenced by European, you know?
Right.
The easiest takeout is pizza and Chinese food, right?
And it's good pizza and good Chinese food.
Well, guess what?
That's not New York.
That's not New York food.
That's European and Asia.
But when I came over to, you know, when I crossed the Midwest and came to the southwest, I noticed some people I ran into,
I said, well, how about you want to come over for some dinner or I'll make something?
They said, no, I only eat hamburgers and drink milk.
And I thought they were joking, right?
And I was like, what do you mean you only eat hamburgers and drink milk?
Yeah, every day I eat hamburgers and drink milk.
That's my diet.
I'm like, what?
Do I need to get my ears cleaned out?
Am I dreaming?
Stuff like that, you see?
So, yeah, so the good food is something that is easy to talk about but difficult to do, but it's so worth it.
If you're not getting a euphoric feeling from the meals that you eat, you should try to get, you know, aspire to it.
And the easiest way to do it, again, is get some Lundberg brown rice, learn how to cook it, and move on from there.
And that's basically the cancer aspect of it.
It's just a blockage.
None of these things are for fear.
They're all inadequacies based on neglect, you know?
And everyone wants to do whatever they do in their life.
And let's say you're a bus driver or whatever and you want to learn about astrophysics.
Well, you're going to find someone who that's their job, astrophysics, and listen to what they have to say.
But if they're misleading you, what happens?
You see?
Right.
And that's very easy.
So all the specialists and professionals, if you want to take over a country or whatever, you take over the schools,
you take over the professionals where people look up to, and you have them all doing the same stuff.
I think it's called WOKE now, right?
Here.
Which is so easy to see that it's fake.
And the people that go for it are really inadequate.
In other words, you have a tremendous amount of people, well, not tremendous, but enough people you can see in a local whatever,
depending on where you are, that are for it.
You know, that WOKE stuff and the LGBTQ, RSTUV, whatever.
Before this, they were degenerate in any other way, you see.
I mean, how many stories do you see about some man that dresses like a woman?
He's going to a preschool to pick up children, right, that are not his, right?
So this is just another outlet.
But what else?
I think we pretty much covered that in a roundabout way.
What else did we want to maybe get into?
What did we start off with?
We started off with de facto, the cancer, the water.
De facto, the cure, cancer, water.
We covered everything I thought we were going to cover.
Yeah.
The transmutation thing is a really big deal because it's really hard to get people's minds outside of how elements exist.
And real short, I wanted to get into this a little bit.
Everything is hydrogen, right?
Very easy.
Hydrogen is one.
Helium is two.
Lithium is three.
You go down.
So when you look at something like 16, right, it's just 16 hydrogens coupled together.
But the problem is, you know an element, right?
The problem is if you take the type of hydrogen that you go and get industrially or laboratory grade or whatever,
you can't work 16 hydrogens together and get oxygen.
It doesn't work that way because what people don't know, and it's not talked about,
there's many types of hydrogen just like there's many – it's an isotope, right?
For example, when you get gold right now and have it tested at a lab,
they can tell you where it was mined because when the gold is mined in different parts of the world,
it has a slightly different isotope, right?
196 point whatever, 196 point something, 197.
So when you manufacture gold in your kitchen and you send it to be tested,
they're going to see – they know right away that it's been man-made,
and they're going to tell you that it's not gold, it's iron and copper.
And then you ask for can I have the sample back, and they say we lost the sample.
And once this happens, all of the laboratories are certified.
And how do you get certification?
You have to fill out government forms, right?
Right.
And once you're a certified lab, all the lab computers are connected, so all their database –
You know, now, by the way, a flip phone went through the wash for the second time.
I couldn't revive it, so I have an Apple phone now.
I just – I don't know how people carry these things around, man.
It's like a brick.
When I have this Apple phone, I'm thinking it's like why am I putting this in my pocket?
It's like am I going to go into a fight where I need to hit someone over the head with something?
Why am I carrying this thing?
You know?
If you know you're going to go for a fight, you better start carrying –
strap something around your chest, you know, grab something.
We're going to go fight, you know?
Okay, you know, what am I – this is a weapon.
What am I doing with this thing?
Anyway, so the way that these – let's go back to the elements.
I don't have a flip phone anymore, and I kind of regret it.
I just wanted to bring that up because I don't know how many people are listening
that still use the old style phone that you put in your pocket, smaller than a wallet and all that.
I really miss it.
So there was a little movement there for a bit of people trying to get those
and find them refurbished and stuff because they wanted to go back to them,
take their SIM cards and stick them in.
Yeah, so I'm going to have to research and get it because the Verizon doesn't want to do it.
But anyway, so once you get the laboratory test that you – that they don't see an isotope,
they're told to tell you that it's not gold, it's iron and copper.
And by the way, before you send it in to get it certified,
you went to all the local pawn shops and they told you it's gold, right?
Because they have the XRF tester and they have the touchstones and the acids and all that, okay?
All right, so once you get in there, you get into a database.
And so we found this one lab in Swastika.
There's a place called Swastika, Canada, right?
Right.
And we sent it to them.
And this is typically what happens.
And so we send in a sample.
Here's the name.
It says – I don't know.
I'm looking for it.
I don't see the sample.
Let me look on the computer.
Oh, we haven't gotten to that one yet,
but it says here that it's iron and copper and we lost the sample is what he's reading on the computer.
But he said we haven't gotten to that one yet.
So they were totally busted.
I said, so if you haven't gotten it to you yet, how do you know it's iron and copper and you lost the sample?
Yeah, right.
So there is suppression.
So when people say you're a conspiracy theorist, there's no suppression.
It's total bullshit.
Sometimes it's very obvious.
And I think when you're doing the JFK research,
you've discovered some of the suppression and the diversion and all that is so obvious it's cartoonish, right?
Yeah, so this is the world you live in.
But here's the thing with transmutation.
Someone once emailed me, how do you turn copper into gold?
Right?
Well, that's more complicated.
And the reason why you want to do copper to gold is because it gets closer to the gold that you know
than growing the organic one from the yeast.
What you might want to do is turn lead into gold by removing the hydrogen atom from it.
Well, what do you mean?
If I have pure lead, where's the hydrogen to remove that?
You see, that's where the macrobiotic yin and yang approach, right?
So the hydrogen is the most yang element, the most compact, right?
And as you go down past the radioactive ones, they're the most yin, right?
Most expansive as the numbers get bigger.
So how do you convince pure lead, Chuck, if I have pure elemental lead, 99.49 pure lead,
how do I remove a hydrogen from it when there's no hydrogen detected?
I don't know.
Excuse me.
Honestly, I don't know.
See?
So that's where the alchemy comes in.
That's where the spirit and the mind.
It's the same mind that you use that inventors have, right?
And most inventors, by the way, when you ask them how they invented that,
they said it was by accident or I had a certain need and the idea just came to me out of nowhere, right?
Right.
So that's the technique.
Well, how many inventors actually said, well, how often do these big consortiums
and corporations fund something to be invented and it never quite works out?
Like the Post-Its, right?
It was supposed to be a super powerful glue and what happened?
It didn't stick to anything.
What do we do with it?
And the secretary said, I love this stuff because I could stick it on anything.
It doesn't leave a residue.
Right.
So what happens is you have an intent that doesn't work out.
Sometimes it's the opposite, but someone else finds a use for it.
You get it?
Right.
Or it just comes out of nowhere unexpected.
So when you have a deep understanding of the yin and yang,
not only will you understand how to treat and manipulate the body,
you will also understand how to treat and manipulate the elements
based on how everything in the universe shares these factors.
If something has a front, it must have a back.
If something has an outside, it must have an inside.
If something has a top, it must have a bottom.
If something is hard on the outside, it must be soft on the inside.
If something is soft on the outside, it must be hard on the inside.
You see?
Okay.
Or how about some, when I was, a few days ago I was going over this
and someone said, what about a rock where it gets hard on the outside
and hard on the inside, right?
Good.
Good question.
It means you're thinking.
That's more advanced.
Actually, yes.
Physically it seems the same way, but energetically it's not.
The rock is hard on the outside, but less hard on the inside.
Think of it, you know how an egg is broken?
You know, egg is very hard on the outside, very soft on the inside, right?
So the yin and yang works well.
You know how an eggshell is broken?
You don't get a big saw to cut through the whole thing.
All you've got to do is break the shell, right?
And it cracks open.
Okay.
If you ever watch a bricklayer cut a brick in half, what does he do?
He holds the brick in his hand, which is hard on the inside, hard on the outside.
It breaks just like an egg.
They mark where they want to cut it, and they tap, tap, tap with the claw
or the back of a claw or a chisel, just a score line all the way around,
and then they just hit it once, and what happens?
It snaps off.
This is how rocks, this is how they work in a quarry.
You have a big slab of stone.
How do they cut it?
How do they break it off?
They just tap it.
They score a line, and then they bump it, and it breaks off.
You kind of cut a guideline, and then you just kind of give it a little bit of force,
and boom, it comes undone.
Yeah, it's called notch.
It's not notch-resistant.
Like glass is the same way.
It has very low notch resistance.
Once you make a notch in it, it breaks on that notch.
Well, I thought it was supposed to be hard on the inside.
Doesn't it act just like an egg?
It behaves just like an egg.
You just score the outside, and the whole thing breaks open, right?
Right.
So this is where the energetic part overrules what you see physically.
In other words, what you're seeing physically going on matters.
Yes, it does.
But when you start reacting or working with the object, the yin and yang works.
So in other words, you cut the stone just like you break open an egg.
Because to break open an egg, you're like, oh, I just need to break through what?
A half a millimeter of some substance, right?
A half a millimeter, like a sixteenth, not even a sixteenth of an inch.
Same thing with a brick.
When you want to cut a brick, which you think is hard on the inside,
you just score it a sixteenth of an inch and tap it.
It breaks off just like an egg.
But wait a second.
See, because this is where the energetic principle overrides what you think is the physical principle.
You see?
Okay.
And this is how you start off with alchemy.
And by the way, just like with many things, there's nothing on alchemy on the Internet.
I've looked and looked and looked.
And there's the closest you're going to get.
I have a book here.
Let's see.
I think I might have mentioned it once before.
It's the Pyrotechnia.
It's from the 1500s.
It's a reprint.
If I could find it here.
I might have put it in a way.
But it's the Pyrotechnica.
It's 1500s.
Let me turn on a light.
This should help on alchemy.
And it's not purely on alchemy.
Basically, this was on the FBI confiscation list for a long time.
You know the FBI has a book confiscation department, right?
Back in the day and still after 9-11 with the dictionaries.
Because on the last chapter of this book, it tells you how to make various types, not just gunpowder.
Various types of cannon gunpowders.
And if you run out of gunpowder, you had to make it on the fly and all this stuff.
They don't want people to know anything about that, right?
The high-speed chemistry.
So here it is.
I think this is a soft, so you can probably still get it.
It may be where it's called.
The Pyrotechnia of Vannaccio Beringuccio.
The classic 16th century treatise on metals and metallurgy.
It's about 400 pages, 450 pages.
It's border on alchemy.
This is like a very high-level technical science book of the day.
And today it would be called alchemy, but it's not.
Because the practices in there are still functional and relevant, right?
And especially the part where they're looking for gold and making gold.
Well, refining gold and all these other things.
Another thing about the transmutation of elements.
Once you start viewing it from the something is hard on the outside, it must be soft on the inside.
That's true for an egg, right?
But not true for a brick.
But the way you interact with the brick to manipulate the brick is just like as it was an egg, right?
Very similar.
Okay, you understand how the hydrogen is.
What is hydrogen?
Gen means to generate, to bring forward, like Genesis, right?
And hydro means what?
Water.
Right.
So hydrogen generates water and water generates hydrogen.
It's not that water is made of hydrogen.
Just like when you remove hydrogen from the lead, it becomes gold, the portion of it does.
Does that mean that you're cracking the lead?
No.
So you have to somehow make the part of the lead.
I haven't thought about how to make a presentation on this yet.
And it's going to be a lot of thinking because when you speak on these things,
there's a lot of parallel things that have to be considered at the same time, right?
And there's really no direct introduction to how to manipulate the physical world, the elements.
There's no direct way.
It's all these indirect ways that you have to contemplate.
And the way to finish off is if you want to work with transmuting elements or making other elements,
you have to understand the air and the water and electricity and magnetism very, very deeply,
especially the water.
So I think we covered enough and we had enough tangents for today.
Fair enough.