Sonic Event 19. Yes, it is 19. That's right. You never know quite what you're going to get.
And it's certainly not Forrest Gump's world. Welcome to it. And here we are. Greek, how are you doing today?
I'm doing all right. I wanted to say, you know, anybody who's been here for more than 15 minutes
should figure out what's going on here, meaning Earth, right, this world.
You ever hear me? I think I've that's part of the later Greek speak when I came up with the why bother model.
Right. You know, when I'm out in the public and they bring up a notion, you know, whether it's banking,
human body or, you know, any of the Greek speak points, all like 17 of them or whatever to someone in the public.
And they give me that look like they're contemplating. And before they decide too much on how much to contemplate,
I'll say, well, you know, anybody who's been on this planet for more than 15 minutes knows this. Right.
You've been here more than 15 minutes. And they're like, oh, what, what, what?
Is that the point at which you get the the the dog turn?
What I mean by that is, you know, the head kind of goes sideways and they, you know, did beers.
Yeah. But but here's the thing. I said, hasn't anybody have anybody use when they're older?
I always underage them. So when they're 60 or 70, I said, you're older than 35.
Right. And when they're, let's say, between 20 and 40, I said, you're more than eight.
You're older than 18. Right. The younger people, I don't mess with them that much.
And I don't get off on this, by the way. It's a part of my study.
You know, it's kind of like when you go out in the jungle and you study plants, you break off a leaf, put it in a book.
Right. You fold it to flatten out the leaf. Right. Preserve it. Dry it out.
So it's kind of like they cut their head off and I put it in a book, flatten it out.
Anyway. Well, that's one way of doing it.
You know, I was taking a look at something my son was watching and he was watching a guy allow things to bite him and was a little confused by that.
And I said, well, you know, people always ask, what is the first thing they ask when they see something that's kind of dangerous or that they think is dangerous?
What happens if this thing bites me? So the guy showing you what else can you ask for?
And here's the thing is what I was going to address tonight is when you said your son, that's the sun in the sky. Right.
You get it. And you know how they say the son of God is the sun in the sky.
Anyway, you know, Maxwell, Bonacci, all these people, not to mention names. Right.
Talk about that. Right. You know how the diversion. Right. I get what you're saying.
Well, I do mean meaning Frankie, the child. Yeah, I know. But this is what people are being told.
You know, you meant no. Chuck really meant the sun in the sky. Right.
But you see what happens when you when you get people's attention.
You kind of manipulate it in a way that is not good for them, where I don't feel so bad telling people, you know, anybody who's been on this planet for more than 15 minutes knows this.
Right. You know, they're like, well, obviously, the guy, you know, they never say I'm crazy.
Sometimes someone will I'll catch them for my you hone in your peripheral vision from the side.
They were next to the person I'm addressing and they kind of walk behind me and they do the cuckoo thing with their finger around the head.
You know, I haven't seen that in a while. Yeah. Yeah. And the older usually the people that are older than 35 and I'll turn around.
I said, no, I'm not crazy. It just sounds like it. If you if you don't know.
Yeah. And the thing is to hone in your peripheral vision, because when you see magicians, you know, ledger domain, press the digitation.
It's even before you know how they do the trick, whatever the trick is, rabbit out of the hat, sawing a woman in half, whatever, whatever.
Yeah. Yeah. You see that they're overly gesturing for your attention in one way or another. Right.
With their hands and their body, the way they look, their facial expressions, it's like an over gesturing, like, look here.
Well, and here's the thing. If you don't look where they want you to look, you're still not going to see much.
But the whole thing is to keep you guided. So in case things don't go perfectly right.
Right. What I mean by that is if you look at how the news is being projected the last time, something that's still echoing, by the way, we're not going to go off on a tangent.
Like I saw I just went to the chat today. Sham on me. I haven't been there in about a week.
But you mentioned that Tucker boy or whatever, the 9-11 conspiracy denier or whatever, he he didn't get another job or anything like that.
It's all psyop. Right. You think I think you already know that. But he doesn't need another job right away.
Look, but here's the thing. He doesn't even exist. Him and his boss and everybody and all the computing, they all eat from the same dog bowl.
You know what I mean? So literally a dog bowl. So when they're and here's the thing, if he decides to go against whatever he'll when he goes to sleep at night, he's going to wake up somewhere else, if you know what I mean.
Yeah. So that's the thing. I don't think he's against anything. I think this is part of the plan.
Yeah. It's also it's all. Yeah, it's all. It's amazing. Where was I somewhere yesterday? I ran into a place that CNN on. I was like, oh, my gosh.
It's it's it doesn't matter. MSNBC also was in another place. I think it was a smoke shop or something. They put it on for a moment. It's and there's something that comes in.
You know how they say, be a good listener when people speak. Here's the thing. That's that's OK. Let's follow that real quick. Be a good listener.
So when the person speaks, you don't speak and you wait for them to say everything right. You just listen. Right. Supposedly. Right.
You know, that's like they talk. You talk. That's what a conversation is. Right. So but they want you to focus on what they're saying more.
Well, I when I say be a good listener is you have to be a good listener before they even open their mouth. In other words, reading people. Right.
And here's the thing. When you see what they put out in the public right now, it's so diversion and so far away from anything that makes sense.
It would be like someone doing hard drugs for the first time or a child puffing on a cigarette for the first time. It would be completely vile to them.
You know, right. They'd spit it out right away. So when you start to see things for what they really are, you you you start to see where you got to.
How did how did you get to that point? How can you see things for what they really are? Remember, it's still in time.
So when you start and as you progress, you get better and better, like going to the gym, right, or developing a muscle.
But the same thing, like the first day of the gym is just as important as where you are now. Three years later. Right.
It's just a everything stacks up one on top of the other. So when you look at all these subjects that are being brought up and one of the things I want to bring up, like I said, you mean the sun in the sky.
You're talking about the gods. Here's it in a nutshell. And this is this is where it's at. And this is where it's important about it.
So we're going to the more important part in the cell phone. So that in case we lose the signal later. Yeah.
OK. The most important part is it's part they're part of your education.
So if someone tells you to bow down to a statue that does, you don't get anything from other than bowing down.
Well, they've the next thing is, you know, it's like eating out of a spiritual doggy bowl. Right.
Basically, you know, but even the dogs, then they know you make that can, you know, the can popping sound.
They know they know enough that. Right. Or a certain bag crunching sound or whatever. It's it's on that level. Right.
So here's the thing. Who are the gods? Very simple. They they they each each group of gods has a name of their race, literally.
Right. And these were people that were around the everyday common or to met too many degrees.
They were sequestered. And just like a race that's gone away. Right.
When you say dodo bird or you say giraffe, you get a totally different feeling.
Yeah. One's a bird. One's a long necked animal that's still around. Right. There's the key point.
The dodo bird you get. Right. There's a certain tiger. There's, you know, the duck bill platypus.
I think they're still around. But some some just, you know, when you speak of an extinct animal,
you have a different feeling than one that still exists. Right. It's regardless of what kind of an animal it is.
So now I'm not saying that the gods are extinct. They're still extant, meaning around, but they're not mingling at all.
So the only thing that you have left is what do you get from them?
Now, if someone tells you to bow down or the Christians cross themselves, kiss an icon, light a candle, that's that's doggy bowl stuff.
You know, open the can, put it out. The dog eats it. You go out. That's basically how humans have, you know, from that perspective.
But in essence, what the gods are, they're in a systematic sense in human society.
They're part of your education. They're part of your legal system, meaning law.
Legal is all fiction, by the way, and presumption, which is OK to have, but it has to be substantiated in law.
And anyway, so so here's the thing. Your university, your education, your right or wrong morality,
which is your law and legal, basically presumption. If someone says, what if I do this?
You haven't done it yet, so it's not in law. Now it's legal. You know the ramification because it hasn't happened.
Right. It's in the fictional realm. That's what I mean by legal.
Your aspirations, where you draw your hope from and towards. Right.
It's called faith or the faith. Each religion has its own faith.
So you would say the Christian faith is the faith. The Jewish faith is the faith.
Right. Each one has the faith, not just faith. Right.
So where we're left right now is with a series of memorializations.
You'll pick your format, print or digital of certain information. Right.
Now, when you go to certain faiths, it'll be commentary by what people think it should be.
Right. Actually, all of them do that. The imams have the Muslim.
There's a there are more writings about the Muslim faith, let's say, that you're supposed to do as a Muslim in Islam.
Then you get out of the Koran. The same with Christianity.
I don't see anything the Christians talk about in the Bible at all. Nothing.
Zero guys. Zero. And if you don't see that, you're you're still doggy ball conscious.
There is in the Jewish faith, I would say one percent of what they do is biblical and close to zero.
OK. Islam as well, especially Islam.
But you've got to give more, quote unquote, credit to the Muslims than the Christians easily,
because at least the Muslims think you need to have a certain laws to follow, you know, permissible, not permissible.
With the Christians, anything goes right. You're washed in the blood of the lamb or you could do anything you want.
But, oh, you don't believe in that or you're going to hell. OK.
All right. But nothing. No reason at all. Right. Or just cross yourself, kiss an icon and whatever.
Eat a piece of bread, drink some wine and you're good. Yeah.
Is it Alpo time to even still have Alpo these days?
I don't know. I think so. You know, I got a quick question, though, because you said it's part of your education.
OK. The gods are part of your education. But that's a kind of a general sounding statement to me.
What do you mean specifically by that?
OK. You're breaking balls now, right?
No, I'm not trying to break balls. No, I got you. All right.
All right. What you eat. OK. What you get from your old Greek speak, old like from charity level Greek speak, you know,
would be what you eat, what you wear, how you keep time, how you do business, how you enter a relationship,
how you keep your house. All that comes from your God.
And the state and the colleges are going to provide that for you.
And they have a big statue of a goddess there to tell you where you're going.
They sure do. Yeah. So each one, everyone does.
So, yeah. So your education basically is all that.
Just like, for example, if you were raised by primates or apes, they would educate you very well.
This is how you scratch. You know, this is how you eat. This is how you sleep.
This is how you fight. And if you take that from your formative years to an adult, you will act just like they do.
Right. You got to groom each other. And this is how that's done.
Sure. So let's say education in a formal sense means some kind of formal training usually applied to animals.
What I say is your formative knowledge to your functional knowledge based in developing into your moral and ethical life.
OK. OK. What does that mean? You hear about these people that are like philanthropists.
I don't believe any of it, you know. But anyway, they make more money being philanthropists.
Anyway, I think I let me just say this is a slight tangent.
A billionaire wants to increase his business on a particular holding that he has.
So he's going to take a hundred thousand dollars out.
I'm saying, you know, credits to get a full page ad in The New York Times, which is, I think, two hundred thousand.
To promote his business. And I say, no, no, no, don't do that.
What you do is you make a big hoopla that you're going to show up one day and give a hundred thousand dollar check to this orphanage.
Right. And not just in New York Times, every newspaper that will get a hold that, sir, will print something.
May not be a full page, be maybe half a column, quarter column or whatever.
Right. OK. Two things will happen. You'll get in all the papers.
And the second thing is you're going to get more people thinking about you a certain way.
Because when you take out the full page, yeah, they're going to be some, quote unquote, people.
They say, look at this bastard, how much money they have.
You know what a full page ad in The New York Times costs. Right.
And they'll ignore everything you're doing.
So you'll actually get more profit, quote unquote, out of being a philanthropist, throwing away a hundred grand toward.
Right. Towards the orphanage, then towards the.
So that's what I mean by the moral and ethical life.
People, your moral and ethical life doesn't develop until you become like you go on your own, whatever that is,
until you're accepted as an adult, let's say, on the with a career.
When people ask you, when you see someone really young, they say, what do you don't say?
What do you do for a living? Right.
You presume they're in school, they presume they're living with their parents, you know, whatever. Right.
But when you meet an adult and more mature, you get to know them eventually.
What do you do? Right. You know, I mean, I'm in this. I'm in that. Right.
OK, that's your moral. That's where you that's when your moral and ethical life develops.
OK. And I mean that directly. So that your basic, basic, basic.
Hopefully you have humans that are well-cultured that show you how to wipe your bum when you're young.
Right. You know, girls always front to back and all that. Right.
As a child, potty trained, tie your shoelace, how to act at the table. Right.
On and on and on and on. How to act amongst others within your culture, because it's different in every culture.
You have birthdays here where everybody goes and brings a present or a gift. Right.
Other birthdays in other countries and other cultures, you open your doors on your birthday, let's say,
and the village comes in and takes anything that they want from you.
Your house is. Are you familiar? OK. Right. I've heard of this. Yeah. Yeah. OK.
I don't think it's done anymore. But there's several cultures on the continent of Africa.
Yeah. Very different. Yeah. I was going to say, I'm not I'm not sure that's a current practice, but.
Yeah. Because they don't want their. You know why? Very simple.
One of the reasons would be that you could go and see these places.
Let's say they call them third world countries or whatever.
Or your ex-president called the third world shitholes or whatever.
Dirt floors, whatever, you know, they eat off the floor with it, you know, but they have stupid rectangles.
They literally do. Right. So I don't think, you know, hey, you got the latest iPhone.
Let me take. Right. They won't. You see, they're not going to give it up that easy.
So what the purpose of the gods is, is part of your education.
Now, also drawing faith and drawing hope on what you where to put your hope is another thing.
Right. And all these things. So all of the formulation that one can come up with has already been done.
When you have a comprehensive God that provides most of that. Right.
The problem with that is, is let's say you're not going to find more on this than in what they call the scriptures of the Bible.
More information on qualitative and quantitative application of everything I just said than the scriptures.
Now, if you go to, let's say, Tibetan Book of the Dead or something, there's quite a bit there to do on to help people pass to the other side.
Right. Well, you know, all these ceremonies all the way to a sky funeral. Right.
Would basically lay the body out, let the vultures eat it and the Bardo. Right.
All this other stuff. Steiner wrote some things I cursory went over about, you know, when people die, they're still kind of around, you know, a little bit.
You know, they're fading out. Right. It's kind of like burning on a TV.
You turn off the TV and the room is dark enough. You can still see the last image that was on there burned in slightly. Right.
Yeah. Old TV used to do that. Yeah. Yeah. Sort of like that. But that's another discussion.
So the ultimate thing here is to understand that you're dealing with a culture.
And by the way, they're people. Right. People have a hard time. Right.
When I say the gods are human. Right. But they're not human as you consider a human.
Just like how many people would consider someone that was raised by gorillas human. Right.
Most wouldn't believe it or not. You know, if you got to know them, of course, you don't know them.
You say, of course, they're human. But when you got to know them, they would be more happy if you kept.
You would be a lot happier if you just put a leash on them and kept them outside for a few days till you figured out what the hell you're going to do with them.
Yeah. Because they're going to come inside and jump on the table and poop and hang from the chandelier.
What you decide to call human is based more on the way they act, I guess.
Yes. OK. Got you. Exactly. Civil. Because they'll get.
And this has been justified. Just genocides have been justified this way, that they're not human anymore.
So it's OK to gas them or kill them. Right. Right. This is how you justify an illegal system.
You know, if you don't have attorneys, it won't happen. So here's the thing.
Many people are curious about certain characters in the Bible, the Christ or Yahweh or whatever.
You know what? Put that aside. What are you going to this because you think there's some like playing the lottery or something?
Or are you going to this because it's in vogue, because it does get in vogue every 40 or 30 years as a movement, right?
Biblical, conservative, biblical movement. Right. Right. To use the names and, you know, church is bad and all this.
Right. Or what? Right. What why are you going to it? Right.
If you're going to it because you are looking for, you know, they say there's got to be a better way.
Right. Yeah. Then you're on the right track. But then you have to get how are you going to get something out of it?
Because you're not going to see common modern things in society in there.
Generally, there's no iPhone in the Bible. Right. There's no airplane in the Bible, directly speaking or anything like that.
So it's going to lean more towards your basic formative way of how you keep time, how you live, what you eat, how you keep a house,
how you do business with who you associate with. And then it jumps over to your moral and ethical stance in life.
Right. Not in between, you know, stuff and your technology. OK.
The other thing about the Bible is it's very egocentric. It speaks from the God's perspective and it's mostly about the gods.
Right. So when it says knowledge will increase, people think, oh, yeah, knowledge because we have the Internet.
No, no, no, no knowledge. It's about everything's about the God. So it says knowledge will increase.
It means the knowledge of the gods will increase. Right. So when you have these nouns and what do you call pronouns that seem general?
They're not. There's no generality there. It's very specific if you understand it's about them.
Right. So the best example I give is people will travel to and fro and knowledge will increase.
Oh, that's happening because of the Internet. No, no, people are actually less knowledgeable because of the Internet.
Sorry. Unfortunately, much dumber. Yeah. Less literate as a mass, as a group.
You could see that by all the reports they do with what they call public schooling, which we know has an alternative agenda.
But yeah. So. So they're not. So it's knowledge of the gods.
So whenever you see these general words, right. Hunger, knowledge, hate, good, love.
All that has to do with the gods, not with each other, unless it's not paraphrasing and it's more direct.
Right. It'll say like the the Hittites are back in there and they hate the the other guys, whatever.
You know, if it's specific like that, then it's specific. So when you start putting these things together,
what you're going to get is who are the gods? Is this God better because he's a redhead?
Right. Versus this God who's short and fat. Right. That's not.
No, it's what they're telling you to do. Right. And does it qualitatively get better to make your life better?
Just like the previous examples about the actions you're taking. It's about the things you're doing. Right.
I mean, yeah. So. So like let's say you spend like I spent 20 years knocking my head against the wall like everybody else.
And I read this thing in scripture and it says, don't knock your head against the wall.
And now I'm not knocking my head against the wall. You know what? My life is going a lot better.
Better. OK. OK. You see the example. Oh, come on, man.
I think you read it wrong because everybody's knocking their head on the wall for eight hours a day or 10 hours a day.
What's wrong with you? You know, you're you're you're one of those extremists.
I'm telling you, man, it really means don't knock your head on the wall and you'll feel a lot better. Try it.
You know, I don't know about that. You see, I'm giving that analogy because that's how simple it is. Right.
So who are the gods? It doesn't matter until you get to where you're putting your hope and getting your idea of what you should have hope in.
Then it starts to make a little bit of a difference, but it's still based on your what they're giving you to substantiate as base knowledge.
Now, I call it doggy bowl. Consciousness is in the world right now.
All the way across with anything. Right. Science, religion, everything.
You know, I was talking to someone recently about relationships. Right.
About one of the most ridiculous is they have these relationship therapists.
You go to as a couple. Yeah. Whatever. Yeah. No idea what they're doing.
Not a one of them. Not because they first of all, it wouldn't make sense to tell people the truth of how to be in a proper relationship.
Right. It's very simple to do, by the way. I think we kind of went into it in a lengthy thing.
But basically the one you're equal in a relationship, not one over the other.
Sometimes you might want to be because let's say the guy is 250 pounds and 2 percent body fat, which means he's like built like Arnold Schwarzenegger and the woman's 90 pounds and a big couch needs to be moved.
He's going to do the brunt of it. Right. He's going to be carrying it from the middle and she'll be balancing the end.
It wouldn't be fair to have them do the lift 50 50. Let's just say the fitness level corresponds with their size.
Right. Right. So in some cases. Right. But the people in a relationship must have the ability to objectify is who is better at what within the relationship and not trying to one up each other.
Right. Right. So and to confide. So in other words, you have instead of carrot soup, you've got carrot and celery soup.
Tasty. Much better. Good combination. Right. You see. So they come together to to become greater than than they were apart.
So that instead of one plus one to make the relationship, it's not two, it's four, five, six, seven.
But if you come together, what I see is people you have one and one come together to make two and then it becomes one point eight, one point five, one point three.
You see, because they're not adding up. Well, but that's the thing. Look, it's by addition.
I've tried to have this conversation, had this conversation many times in many different relationships where it's like, look, this is something that I'm better doing.
So therefore, this is the thing that I should be doing. You know, it's just that simple.
And it's almost confusing to some, you know, look, if this is naturally, it just makes more sense for me to do this part and more sense for you to do that part.
OK, you know, I've got the visual problem, so it doesn't make any sense that I should be relying on for transportation to drive a car.
It's not sensible. So a partner of mine knows that they're going to have to do that part, you know.
No, no. But it's more than that. So you said doesn't add up. But you see, nature doesn't add.
Nature multiplies. You notice I didn't go. I said one plus one is not two. It's four, five, six, seven.
Yeah. So it multiplies. Think about cats and bunny rabbits. What do they add up or do they multiply?
I mean, like crazy. Right. So the intent and the workability should do the same.
But here to go back to the gods, it's also I'm going to say it's a personal relationship.
What are you getting out of it? Oh, I just believe. OK, doggy ball time. Right.
Yeah. The big kennel, the church. Right. Whatever. And they know this, by the way.
They the the mid-level is their academia, priests and all that.
They're there to protect what I'm saying. In other words, the leaders of these organizations, governments, science or whatever, deplore the people.
They hate the people and they have the mid the mid-level group, mid-level management to be a buffer between them.
Right. But when you're around, let's say a high level, whatever, bishop or finance person or whatever, they'll tell you.
So, yeah, people are basically stupid. They'll tell you that.
But, you know, when they're on CNN or Fox News, they won't say that.
There was a time when do you remember when Obamacare came out?
The guy who head off the committee to structure it. So why so complicated?
Why? Why so much? Why is it so expensive? It's basically the American people are too stupid to understand this.
He wasn't talking about Obamacare. He's talking. This is a financial, the financial system thing, you know,
because people don't understand that the money comes from your signature.
And when they want to do things to for the interest of the United States, which is not United States, it's not what you think.
Right. So in Mexico, when they say Mexico, anyone federal says Mexico or anyone federal says Russia, Putin or anyone federal says United States.
It's the district within the country, a foreign district. Right.
So basically what he meant by the people are too stupid.
So they don't know that the money is drawn from their signature. And we as a corporation, which is that capital, they believe they worship us.
How do we know? Well, look, we need a bunch of their funding, their credit, and we need to get their signatures.
And we're just getting creative on how to get their signatures. Right. The IRS is the same thing.
You know, people say, oh, you pay taxes. I don't know anyone who's ever paid taxes.
Never. But I know that if you endorse credit instruments, you're going to have to file a report and then give a return.
Oh, yeah. That's paying taxes, is it? No, that's not paying taxes.
You're using private credit. You're going to make a report on how much credit you use and then file a return.
Isn't that the same thing? I said, no, if you go and borrow a tool rental tool from the tool rental shop,
you just bring it back a few days and wave goodbye. No, you got to pay a fee for using that.
Right. That's what it is. I don't understand. Good. You'll be a good citizen, good resident.
Pat him on the back. Have a nice day. You know, this is this is the same thing with the gods.
Right. And here's the thing. You know, I say the anyone who let's go back to the scripture for a moment.
I've been saying this for a long time and I wasn't saying it public.
Like I wouldn't say a guy nailed to a cross wearing a diaper is what they show Christians, you know, because it sounds kind of crazy.
But no one ever said you're insulting my God, you know, because I'm not saying it to insult.
I'm just saying it to awaken you. But here's the other thing that I've been saying.
The most hateful bar none bar none. Most hateful character.
Literally what's written, what he said in the Bible is the Christ.
And all that lovey dovey stuff is all in private.
A lovey dovey stuff would be like you recording you and your best friend from the third grade and your wife.
I'm not talking menage a trois, but I'm talking about like someone you really, really care for in private.
In a relaxed sense is what people are taking applies to the public at large.
Where if you take what the Christ said to the public at large and the general groups around him is so hateful, so hateful and so dismissive.
And it trumps anything, anything I've said anywhere else in the Bible.
So we're talking about the population is completely demented to think the opposite.
Right. And where does it say that? Sometimes people say you have to show me more.
No, I'm not showing you anything because if you're not going to do your own research and if you don't know it well enough, then there's no reason to talk about it.
Well, a suggestion about where somebody could find that, though.
Oh, every all the red letter, all the red letter.
A suggestion would be all of the read all the red letter in the King James.
But when you read the red letter, read do me a favor and read a few verses before for the setting.
Right. Not when he's sitting in there in his cozy little room in a house.
They were in a house here with his disciples.
No, that doesn't count. That's the lovey dovey.
Read about where he was around the groups of people.
Right. And we're not talking about the beatitudes where those are.
Those were different. That's a very small exception.
You know that the meek will inherit the earth and all that. Right.
OK. OK. Even then it's like, oh, wait a second.
You know, those are pretty strong.
But the personal ones, the woman at the well, the rich man, the Pharisees, all these things.
Oh, my gosh. No one's ever said anything like that to anyone in Scripture.
Very, very hateful. And I mean, hateful.
All of the everything that he says in public and private is completely misunderstood by ninety nine point nine nine nine nine percent of the people have ever read it.
It's it's unbelievable how this has been misinterpreted.
Actually, not interpreted at all. It's been opinionized because it's good for business.
You know, I had the Jehovah's Witness come to the door and she had a Bible out.
And I said, oh, it's like a baseball bat. You know, are you playing baseball?
She goes, well, you know, I said baseball's baseball bats.
Ninety nine percent of baseball bats sold are not playing baseball because they make a good club.
Right. Everybody's got one behind the seat or behind the cashier.
You keep one next to your door just in case. Yeah.
And so that Bible is not being used for a show talking about what's in it because you don't know a thing in there, do you?
Right. You know, as a response, you know, sometimes you got to do that once in a while.
And there's sometimes say no one's ever told me to tell this.
I'm not saying I'm saying this to help you because I know you're not going to hear this from anyone else.
How do I know? Because the planet full of morons with little exception.
The exceptions are so little. It's a real teeny, teeny, tiny bit.
The exception is so small that you won't even you won't see it.
So anyway, I like when people tell me. So are you.
So you're saying you're not a moron. I said, well, what do you say?
And they never say you're a moron to none of them. So anyway, that makes me feel feel OK.
That's where people challenge. You just pull what the Christ said.
What do you say? I am. They say that you're king of the Judeans.
What do you say? I have no answer. All of these things.
So so here's the interesting part about all of it.
Have you ever heard of. Well, the one room schoolhouse, we suggested that the biblical text was a book that was already available.
Books are still very expensive, especially in a rural community.
You know, when I ship something, I guess I'm naive when I ship a pair of loudspeakers to someone.
It's like one hundred and fifty or two hundred bucks. Not that heavy. Twenty pounds.
OK, like, oh, my goodness is so expensive.
But it's not really because think about driving them over the fifteen hundred miles, how much gasoline and time.
It's cheap, but it's still expensive when you think about it.
You know, an insurance and all that. It's like a ship out of Paris.
Two hundred bucks. Oh, my goodness.
Well, it's a lot cheaper than if you had to go through all the process yourself, you know, and actually, OK, I'm going to take this.
You get books to get books to a rural area.
No matter how much you thought was expensive at the post office,
it took a long time and you didn't have access.
The post office refuses it. We don't ship this because we don't have them.
We have a carriage. It's muddy. It's raining. And we have a horse.
You know, when it's raining, the carriage can't carry that much.
Right. You know, the wheels will sink into the.
So it was very, very, very, very, very, very good at a few more varies expensive to move things around.
So when you had these Bibles in one room schoolhouses,
it was not only the education because it was the written word, as they call it,
but it was also part of the context and the subject matter as well.
You see. And right now it's not being done that way.
Now it's all about you got to believe, believe, believe, believe in the doggy ball.
So and, you know, very, very interesting.
So who are the gods? Irrelevant. But if you decide to focus on one, just like literally taking a picture, what do you do?
Oh, it's out of focus. No, put it. Let's focus. You take a picture. It's out of focus.
Reject. Reject. Right. Right. OK. Well, once you get it in focus,
you better figure out if you're focused on which which got which version of that God.
Are you getting the misidentity? Are you getting the Osama bin Laden who's been killed two or three times already?
You know what I mean? Right. You get it. Or the guy who was the CIA agent.
And the reason he died of kidney failure is because he got Western medical treatment that his family advised him not to.
Which one? You know, you see what I mean. And the one who was interviewed after 9-11,
he says, this is not a terrorist act, as you're being told. This is some group that runs your government.
Right. That made it to the news, by the way. And also, you have a lot of fake news.
Do you know? I don't know if you remember. There were reports that an airplane crashed into Camp David on 9-11.
You know, do you remember that? Oh, yeah. Well, Camp David.
Plus, they said that there were bombs that were set off on the ground in different places.
Yeah, there were that were that were found later. But yeah, exactly. So where's the one?
So they had it all pre scripted, ready to go. Many, many things. So what are you focusing on?
You see, or do you see 9-11 as a textbook nuclear reactor, which it is a textbook?
You know, there's nothing to ponder textbook, basic textbook physics, but not the textbook they have at college, by the way.
So so here's the thing. When you when you focus, let's say, let's look at the Buddhist genre.
It was a skinny Indian guy, man. Right. From India. Right. Not this fat guy. Right.
You see what I mean? And he had followings and disciples and all this stuff. Not this. Right.
That's another one. That's another. So you keep going on and on and on and on and on.
You better identify and figure out what your identity, what you're what you're looking at, you know, because it's not going to be served up to you.
And that's the that's the easy part. Believe it or not. Why is it easy?
Because whatever you're being, whatever they're telling the masses, it's not for sure. Right.
It's the opposite. But which opposite. Right. And then you've got to focus in on your own.
And this is the part that the let's say, again, I always compare religions and the biblical stuff to any stuff to 9-11.
It's perfect because it's backwards. So what they do is they set up alternative groups right away to mislead you.
What is it called? Counterintelligence, whatever coin Intel program.
So if you know there's going to be a counter group to something, you set up the counter groups and have them fall into the predetermined package.
Right. So you control your position because you control it all that way.
Because someone who does have the proclivity to go into an opposing viewpoint.
Well, they already have some of these groups available to them.
So, oh, well, that's all right. Then we'll go. Yeah, exactly.
They're total cookie cutter. Yeah. So the people will say it on the surface.
Oh, yeah. They're opposing the official story. So do I. So they're going to go with them.
Oh, I don't think they're right. Maybe this other one is. None of them are right. None of them. Zero.
So the easiest part is to figure out that what they're telling the masses is not true.
That's the easy part. But then it gets easy again.
Once you see the alternatives are also part of the same thing. Yeah. Right. Yeah.
All right. And then it gets easier because you're doing process level elimination.
So the alternative group says it was a super weapon from space.
Oh, great. It's not in the official story. But that's bullshit, too.
So now we could scratch that off and on and on and on.
So this is how you look at biblical stuff, Quranic stuff.
But by the way, you know, 99 percent of Christians, if you tell them you're a staunch literalist of the Bible,
they they don't like that at all. Right. The same with the Muslims in Islam.
They actually have a term for it. I forgot what it was that if you if you do what's in the say what's in the Koran,
you're like you're actually it's punishable almost to the point.
I don't know about now, but mid 20th century, it was almost to the point is if you were Protestant in a Catholic Europe.
Right. You know, it was punished. Right. Also. So, yeah, it's really bad.
But it's not so bad if you're going for it for the right reasons, which is to get knowledge.
Right. And what I'm talking about applies to point zero zero zero zero zero zero zero one percent of the people.
So that's OK. And I don't think they've all subscribed here yet.
But either way, it applies to those people. So it's all about knowledge.
When you get knowledge. Here's the thing.
If someone gives you an idea of what to put your hope in, meaning future,
and you have no knowledge of them, the subject matter or anything, how and you you you think you're well invested in that.
How well is the turnout going to be? Well, it's 50 50, isn't it?
Well, it's a lot more than 50. It's more complex. Look, how reliable is the individual anyway?
You know, how about you know who the individual is and what where this is coming from?
You know, so you got to know what what what what their proclamation is based on, don't you?
You got to know what it's based on. So, yeah. Let's go back to the biblical nomenclature.
OK, there's a lot of knowledge in there. It's about knowledge. He gives knowledge.
There is. It's about knowing. And it's also about knowing.
And did I mention it's about knowing. Right. Yada Yada.
It would be Hebrew for knowledge or knowing. It's here.
Let's just say even though the Jewish culture is one percent biblical or two percent. Right.
Do you know that one of the main things in, quote unquote, Jewish culture is it's very important next to food and water,
food, clothing and shelter isn't is to be educated, but not what what the collective is getting right about their own culture,
but specifics on how to do business, how to keep a house. Right.
You know, we think we brought up to the Syrian Jewish in Deal, New Jersey earlier.
Very much so. They're orthodox, but they don't appear to be like, you know, the cultish black and white.
We weren't recording at that time, but yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
So but the education, in other words, going to even today, what they call yeshiva or shul. Right.
The education is far better than any of the private schools that you get otherwise.
But here's the interesting thing. They're still teaching a lot of BS, 98 percent BS.
That's not you won't find in the Bible.
I've run into some people that were when I was living out in California for a short time a decade ago,
there was a very religious Jewish man, his wife and a newborn baby.
And every morning he would see him running down the steps, going to the temple,
which was a block or two away to to pray for an hour and then come back.
And I said, well, you know, my prophecy is, oh, yeah, prophecy.
Yeah. Elijah is going to come down from heaven and he's going to bring the temple, the temple.
You mean the building? Yeah. From heaven. And they're going to land it right on your head.
Right. I said. And before he finished saying that, I said, right on your head, that's not in Scripture.
Oh, it is. It's in Isaiah. So it's not it. Where? Where?
Well, you see, this means that this means, oh, I see, because the car is red and the apple is red.
The apple is a car. I get your I get it.
So so this is what they're this is what their strong education system still leads to crap like that, you see.
So I'm not I'm not condoning and saying, yeah, the Jewish people know they don't.
I feel sorry for the efforts that they make to stay.
So let's say rigid within the confines of excelling scholastically,
because they are very rigid about excelling scholastically.
By the way, the Asian, the Asian-Americans that come here are like that with their children.
You know, if you're there's a lot of funny car stuff on YouTube, you might find the Chong brothers or something.
What's it like growing up with Asian parents?
If you could catch that video, it's kind of funny.
You know, they come home and it's look at the report card.
A, A, A, A, A, B, B, this one you got B.
You disgraced the family. Right. You know, it's like they're very, very harsh.
Right. Also, but even then, scholastic with all that.
That's what I mean. Rigid like that.
But it's still a waste of time because they're telling you, you know, to go into medical school.
They believe actually the body is absorbed.
They don't even see what's in front of them.
They're still in this, but it's in their culture to be rigid scholastically.
You know, so you see this in every culture.
So, again, to go back to the gods, whichever religion, quote unquote, you find rubs you the right way.
Go see what it's based on and what that's based on and what you're supposed to do in there and how much information is there.
And you'll see there is a group of beings in there.
If you can properly identify them.
It's in the text, by the way, just like 9-11.
It adds up, for example, it's called Ground Zero.
Look up the word Ground Zero.
What does it mean? Right.
Just look it up.
It has to do with nuclear atomic.
And then start looking at, you know, how is it 3000 degrees underground for so long?
Molten rock and molten steel for a month.
Oh, OK.
So everything adds up.
Right. So when you start.
Let's say you find a religion that rubs you the right way.
Find out who the gods are and see.
Forget about what their little pictures and things are showing you.
What are the characteristics of this entity?
Add them up.
Right.
And then you're going to have to do it from your peripheral because what's easy to focus on is some picture or icon or image in front of you.
So you've got to do it from the peripheral, you know, which is what your safety relies on.
And then see what kind of knowledge base.
Does it tell you how to keep time?
What to eat?
What to wear?
How to do business?
You see?
On and on and on and on.
How much stuff can you find in there?
And if the answer is no, it's none of that Greek.
It's about faith.
I got alpo.
I got purine.
I got dog.
I got dry.
Someone says, you know, their cat ran away.
I said, your cat ran away?
Why?
What did you feed him?
Good cat food.
Dry or wet?
Dry.
Ah.
That's why they left.
You got to give them wet food, man.
Right?
So they have the wet food version is, yeah, we have really good prayer session or really
good Bible study or really good festival.
The Greek churches do the festival.
Right.
Whatever, right?
You know, that's the wet food, you know, part.
So, you know, here's the irony of it.
The local Greek church, they have a raffle, right?
Okay.
And it's a statue of Zeus they were raffling off.
And my wife and I were cracking up.
I wouldn't go there.
It's disgusting.
Go to a place.
It's perfect.
That's hilarious.
It's priceless.
These people are so stupid.
Don't even bother with it, you know.
It's that they all had stupid tattooed on their forehead in white or whatever color skin they
had.
You know, you couldn't see it.
You needed the glasses to see it, right?
Okay.
No statue of the guy in the diaper.
Yes.
No, no, no.
Well, they all wear one on their neck.
Right.
But here's the thing.
And oh, my goodness.
This is not just them.
It's all of it.
Go down to any government building, right?
Even the attorney general.
Have a discussion with the attorney general about something.
You know, if you keep talking about this, you're going to go to jail.
That's all you can say.
He doesn't know anything about law at all.
He can't.
They're just there working for the bankers to intimidate people.
None of it.
It's a shithole of a place when you try to put things together with rational logic and
people saying, oh, the recent thing with the pandemic with science.
Well, science is based on logic and reason.
And when you have a science with no logic and reason, it's not science.
Right.
Very simple.
You don't even have to go.
So you live in a situation like this, but take advantage of it.
Here, I'll give you an example.
Okay.
You have the moral.
I've mentioned this before.
You have a moral and ethical decision on what you're going to do.
Now, there's something in scripture that says if an animal dies of unknown causes, I'm paraphrasing
here, don't eat it.
You know, like roadkill or sick animal.
Right.
Because you have no idea what's wrong with it.
What's unclean.
It has to be killed.
You know.
All right.
So if it dies, it's more than just pathological.
There's a spiritual element to this.
Right.
Just like water.
But what you do when you find the animal, you sell it to the pagan for a profit.
Let him eat it.
Doesn't say give it to the pagan because he's hungry.
No.
You sell it for a profit.
Right.
Let him eat it.
Okay.
I could see that.
Right.
I wouldn't do it.
I can opt.
It doesn't say you have to do it.
But I'd rather bury the thing.
Right.
You know.
It should be buried.
Or whatever.
Or actually feed it to other animals.
But I wouldn't really go that route.
So you also have that route.
You see.
It's voluntary.
Right.
You see.
You can pick and choose.
But you can't cherry pick.
You can't insert things.
You can't insert things that are not in there.
And you can't fragmentize it and change it.
So now it becomes something else.
Right.
You can't just take a part of it and say this part of it says this.
Now you've twisted it into something else.
Right.
You can do that with a chocolate chip.
You can take a chocolate chip recipe out of Betty Crocker recipe book and turn that into a Bible, into a religion.
You just take pieces out of it.
Right.
It's got the hot fire in there.
Doesn't it?
It's got the hot fire.
Right.
It's got the heavenly part.
You know, the heavenly hot.
Right.
They've got all these.
You just take words from here and you piece it together.
It sounds like something out of the Bible if you do that.
Right.
So you can make the.
You've seen the edits years ago.
I remember the first one with Reagan.
They did an editing with his voice.
I forgot.
It's Air Force One.
It's a disco group from very obscure underground.
They took Reagan's voice and it started with a heavy, like 120 beat per minute house beat.
And it goes, I've got my finger on the button.
Feel the heat.
See the light.
Nuclear war with Russia.
I've got my finger on the button and it's Reagan's voice.
They just kept editing and splicing it until they got him to say what.
You see what I mean?
There's a whole bunch of YouTube channels that do that with all kinds of stuff.
Yeah.
It's been done since the 60s, 70s, 80s.
It was kind of interesting.
So this is what the religions are doing.
Away from all of it.
Once you understand what's in the text.
Now, here's the thing.
There's another thing about the veracity and the origin of all this.
It doesn't matter at this point.
Do you know it?
Like, for example, if you switch over to fictional genre.
And let's say we're going to do a study on Moby Dick.
Okay.
We're doing the purpose of the investment of time and effort is to study this book.
It's Emerson, I think, right?
Moby Dick and all the grammatical and mechanical mechanisms used.
And now let's say we want to create a screenplay or whatever.
And you have some idiot in the background saying, but it's fiction.
Oh, yeah, we know that already.
We're not here to get that it's fiction to the public.
We're here to get the story out to the public.
Right.
So when someone says, well, the Bible was really written by  that's okay.
We just want to see what's in it first to criticize it.
Right?
We want to see what's in it.
Is it usable?
Is it substantial?
You see?
And if it's usable, it's usable.
If it's not usable and it's not  then that's the second part.
But you have to know  right?
There's Gulliver's Travel.
When he went to the Lilliputians, one of these little people
Well, there's many  look, there's actually more than one story in Gulliver's Travels.
But the most famous one is when he goes to see the Lilliputians, which are small.
Lilliputians.
Well, they tell him about the moons of Mars, which were not yet formally discovered.
Right.
Are you familiar with that?
Yes.
They described the two moons of Mars in detail,
but yet they were discovered 20 or 30 years later by the scientific community, let's say.
Right.
Yeah.
So you have stuff embedded in there everywhere.
The thing is, do you know it?
And the thing is, I don't need to know it.
I just believe.
Well, there's lots of dog chow for that.
And you think about dogs.
You know, they fight.
They pee on everything.
You know what I mean, right?
Yeah, yeah.
And actually, I'm denigrating dogs, too, by comparing these people to them, by the way.
Nothing, you know, but anyway.
Gulliver's Travels is interesting, though, because here you go,
a lot of people reference it and have never bothered to read it.
Anything.
Yeah.
And that's just typical of the whole thing.
This is exactly what goes on.
I mean, look, I'm willing to bet that the majority of people that are listening to us right now,
don't remember who the Ho Hoiams were in that story, right?
My memory serves.
That was the horse people.
He ended up with horse people, too.
In what context?
Well, he ends up on another island, another place, another travel, and yeah.
Oh, that's right.
That's right, because he's going.
It's more than just three places, right?
Yeah, but during his travels, he encounters really interesting, you know,
people that are completely different.
And people have gotten into the metaphorical reasons for it and whatnot.
But the point is that, yeah, okay, it's a fictional story.
But at one point, he comes across a society of horses, basically, that are, you know,
able to speak and this and that, right?
Mr. Ed.
Well, kind of like a Mr. Ed sort of thing, but.
Yeah, but not in a stable.
They had a formed society.
Yeah, a whole society.
Yeah.
So just to go back to the gods, it's a matter of preference in what you get out of it.
I've run into a lot of people.
That's why I'm diminishing on the discussion of the gods more and more on them specifically.
And I'm more focused on what people have gotten or what they think they can get out of it, right,
from a knowledge base that they could yet use.
Because I recently had a Skype discussion in a private, small Skype group.
Okay.
And I was like, I want to talk about how Yahweh is a man.
But he's not a man as we are men genetically also, but he is human.
And the conclusion at the end was that he's not.
But the hour that we spent bringing it up is all of the points, especially like in Exodus 15.
Yahweh is a man.
He is a man of war and uses the word ish, right, which means man.
It's not metaphorical.
And I kept bringing up all these other things, you know, like all the visitations
and how he has doppelgangers and on and on and on.
And suddenly, no matter how what you show or talk about,
it still goes back to somebody like Zeus sitting on a throne.
It's very hard to break that, right, that image.
Which, by the way, Zeus sitting on a throne was a man, by the way.
It was a group of the Olympiads, right?
They were descendants of the Titans.
If you want to get a cut and dried version, which I don't really endorse,
listen to Jason Breshears of Archaics on what were the ancient gods from the Greek and all that.
And I said similar things with Seth Michael 13 years ago on Revolution Radio late at night.
You know, these were kings, men of renown, right, these Greek gods.
They would be considered like Elvis Presley, you know, kind of, but not a musician,
but a physical prowess, mental capability, you know, far superior.
They were men.
There are many places where it's documented like they didn't know if Zeus was a Minoan king
or he was a king of some other extraction.
But he wasn't a king because he didn't sit on a throne.
Other people said he sat on a throne.
Other people said he tried to live in his own settings.
So there's much on that, but Jason Breshears of Archaics,
but he puts out things that are not where they're not really so.
He's borrowing still from religious BS and making it a fact.
So I don't endorse it, but it's fun to look.
Here's the thing.
If I'm in the shop or I have speakers wired here everywhere
and I want to put on a YouTube about something, history, whatever, and I have them on,
it's a lot better than most of the others that you have out there, not to mention names,
and I won't mention names, which I end up yelling at the speakers.
I'm like, I'm not that stupid.
So at least get some chronography correct.
But I don't endorse them by any chance.
I don't subscribe or I wouldn't send any newbie there.
I mean, go ahead and enjoy it.
It's fun to listen to.
It's Texas country meets the Internet.
Have a good time.
Yeehaw, and it'll be fun.
And you'll get some good stuff.
What I got out of him is a 138-year cycle.
Close enough.
It winds up pretty well.
So if you want to get a roundabout thing, he's got a thing called the dark scriptures,
which I don't endorse.
The stuff that he talks about is just not found anywhere.
It's just commentary that someone wrote, so so what.
You can take a commentary on a movie review and make that as gospel.
That's fine.
You watch the movie and you're like, I don't know what movie that reviewer watched.
It's similar.
So either way, we're in a tough spot with all that stuff.
But when people say, give me your statement of faith, I'm an Old Testament kind of guy.
Write me down your statement of faith.
Somebody wanted me to do a talk show once because I called in and broke down the nail to a cross,
wearing a diaper, that didn't happen, and all these other things.
But if you're acting like your kindergartner is eating from a doggy bowl, you're never going to see this.
You're going to have to grow up to eight or nine or 12 maybe years old, clean yourself off,
brush your teeth, and then go back into the text as if you're reading your older brother's college book,
from that mentality, and then you'll see it.
It's in your face.
So I want a statement of faith, so I'm an Old Testament kind of guy.
And I just put in writing, I'm an Old Testament kind of guy.
They never got back to me.
I was like, no, I don't sit there and say I believe in one J-E-S-U-S and this and blah, blah, blah, blah,
all that stuff, two old beef patties, special sauce.
It's a mockery.
Have you accepted Christ as your one true Lord and Savior?
Which one?
Because even if you read Scripture, there are many.
Some are false and some are minor.
And then there's one that is claimed to be out of a certain lineage.
When these Christians come to me and say, do you believe in J-E-S-U-S?
I'm like, you mean the one that was talked about by the prophets, the Psalms, and Moses?
Huh?
What?
I mean, that's what the Christ said.
He says, if you want to know who I am, read Moses, the prophets, and the Psalms.
So I just use that on the Christians.
You mean the one that, well, there's only one.
I'm like, oh, okay.
There's only one for everyone, isn't there?
Yeah, anyway.
So, yeah, it's pretty interesting.
What do you get out of it?
It's all knowledge-based.
By the way, you know, just about every story that you see biblically done in any movie,
biblical movie, is false, every single one.
I think we, just real quick, you know the woman being stoned,
the Christ is sitting down and he's writing with his finger in the sand,
and he says, whoever is without sin throw the first stone,
and they all drop the stones and walk away.
And the Christians think, oh, he's so kind and loving.
No, nothing to do with that.
You could take it that way.
Take it that way.
You get some candy, too, if you take it that way.
Right?
Good boy, good girl.
But actually he was a stickler about the law,
and in the law you need two witnesses.
There are obviously more than two.
But in the law, you know, the two witnesses, you have to be a qualified witness.
So what I mean by that is like if you have outstanding parking tickets, right,
or a warrant, you can't qualify.
I'm using modern-day legal terms here.
Right.
With the temple, you don't qualify.
So without sin, right, meaning you don't have any warrants or outstanding tickets,
and they all said, oh, we all have, you see, so they all drop their stones.
And also the ones that witness against throw the first stone,
that's what he meant by the first stone.
You see, you have to have a qualified witness.
So twice, without sin, meaning you have no outstanding warrants or tickets,
and in order to throw the first stone, you may have to be a witness, right?
Okay, because the witness has to throw the stone.
Okay.
Strictly from the law, if they did, okay, stone the bitch.
If they did, you see what I mean?
If it was the other way around where they had no outstanding parking tickets or whatever,
you see what I mean?
Because he said sin no more.
So actually people see the biblical law as being harsh,
but it has a lot of loopholes.
In other words, you could be seen by a lot of people doing something,
but if they had outstanding warrants and parking tickets, you can't be stoned, you see,
according to the law.
So you had a lot of people actually, people thought it was brutal.
Yes, it is brutal once it is, what's it called, procedure is applied.
Right.
But it was very difficult to provide procedure.
You could actually set it up.
You want to do something.
Let's go here where we know these people have outstanding warrants and tickets.
Let's do it right in front of them.
They won't be able to stone you later.
Okay, bet, let's do it.
And guess what happens?
You get off scot-free because those people get checked out and they know they can't stone you.
They can't throw the first stone.
They can't commence.
You can't have somebody willy-nilly say,
if the people that witnessed against you don't throw the stone,
it doesn't matter how much the others want to stone you.
You see, according to procedure it won't happen.
So people don't understand this.
They don't get it.
And don't ask me where it is in the scripture because you're just disqualified just by asking that, right?
It means you don't know it.
So step off.
Watch Netflix.
Right.
What I would suggest, also, do you know when there was no witness and a woman was accused,
you wrote the law down and you put it in water and some bitter water.
It was called dust from the floor.
Okay.
And if she drank it, this is like a sorcery, right?
This is in the law.
And if she drinks it and loses the loss of her legs, she's guilty.
But if she drinks that and she's accused, this is the accused,
and she still has power in her legs, she's innocent of the charge or the accusation.
That sounds like magic to me.
It does.
Yeah.
It's in the Bible, right?
Okay.
But it's approved, right?
Here's the thing.
If you are to slaughter a lamb, a goat, or a pigeon or a dove at the temple
and pour its blood, et cetera, et cetera, if you don't know what I'm talking about,
you could find it in there just like you find everything else I'm saying.
Right.
Right?
What's the difference between that and some voodoo lady cutting the head off of a chicken, whatever?
What's the difference?
It's an animal being slaughtered, right?
It's who you're doing it for, right?
Right.
You see?
It's the same thing.
When you see there's a bunch of references, too.
You know, okay, so you're supposed to offer up a ram and this and that and the other thing.
It's an animal being slaughtered on an altar.
It's voluntary.
Well, here's the thing.
Okay, what do we see objectively?
Let's say you're up in high altitude and you're looking down with a camera.
You see some people slaughtering an animal here in a ritual in the temple, let's say, for Yahweh,
and over here you're seeing a bunch of people slaughtering an animal for some other whatever voodoo thing.
What's the difference?
The only difference is slight procedure difference and who they're doing it for.
Right, but if you're misidentified, okay, so all of this stuff comes together based on how you want to live your life, basically.
It's very simple.
It's very, very simple.
All of it comes together when you go on your own search.
There's so much.
This is a little bit of synchronicity.
You know what's been coming up to me lately a lot?
On the radio, on the computer, in print, being out.
I even saw it on a billboard about five times this week, maybe more.
I have to say it.
It's not getting there.
It's the journey that matters.
You know that, right, the clich?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It keeps popping up everywhere around me for the past, let's say, week.
What does this mean?
Everything that I've said is paraphrasing that.
You better find out what you want to do.
By the way, there is no conversion in the Bible.
There's no missionaries to go out and convert anyone, and there's no racism either.
In other words, it states that if some foreigner, sojourner, whatever, not you, your people, come in amongst you.
I'm paraphrasing.
Your camp or your nation.
And they become educated on these things, and they want to do it, right?
And they pledge to doing this, let's say, have allegiance to this way of life.
You treat them as one of your own.
It doesn't say just because they're this or that or whatever.
There's no conversion.
You don't go out and tell people, come here, blah, blah, blah.
They have to be free.
They have to pick it up on their own, do it on their own.
You'll offer if they ask, but you don't put it on them, right?
Right.
You see, Christian missionaries, what the hell?
Where'd you get that?
It's totally separate.
Completely different thing, right?
The Mormons, they send out missionaries.
There's no missionary work.
None, none, none, none, none.
And then they say, oh, based on the Christ, you know, after the Pentecost, which is not Pentecost, by the way, right?
It's seven weeks plus 50 days, by the way.
Anyway, to the 3,000 people, that was to let them know that the Christ has come to spread the news that the resurrection has been proven.
Not to start a religion or anything.
Why bother?
So, in essence, it's all about knowledge.
Why do you think, here's another description, another sideline comment.
Ready?
Okay.
When education is removed from society, I'm not talking about BS education, but real information.
Real information.
It's a society unto godlessness, meaning they're removing knowledge, meaning they're pulling you away from, quote, unquote, the gods.
Right.
The society that goes closer to knowledge gets closer to the gods.
Very simple.
Has nothing to do with faith or religion.
Those things exist just like anything else exists, any other social mechanism, right?
And it's the journey.
I give hints, and I'm not reading into it.
I'm reading out in a purist form.
So, you know, it's like when I go buy certain supplies and the supply is out.
I'll ask, when will you get it in and can I order some before I go for an alternative?
Right?
You see my point?
Because there might be a compromise.
I'm not familiar with it.
So, the more you get familiar with it, the easier it is to get familiar with it.
In other words, when you start going into a gym or any exercise, even mental, if you're not used to reading, when you start reading again, it's difficult and it's slow.
But the more you read, the faster you read and the more you can read, right?
You go to the gym, it's difficult.
But the more you go to the gym, the more you want to go to the gym and the more you can do at the gym.
You see?
It becomes easier.
The spiritual stuff is the same and it all has to do with knowledge.
And, yeah.
So, if it says don't bang your head on the wall and you stop banging your head on the wall and tell other people you don't bang your head on the wall anymore and they laugh at you, well, you're going to have to make up jokes about banging your head on the wall.
I don't know.
Everyone's got their own thing.
But, again, paraphrasing, it's the journey.