Okay, I'm gonna give the Greek a call.
It looks normal, right?
Yeah, it does.
Not even a coloration difference or anything.
Alright, so I was looking at 67, and 67, what it was, is stress in the atmosphere.
Now, I started talking to you about the general condition of people, and the mentality that
I was noting among people.
And then you started talking about stress in the atmosphere.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Okay, that's why teenagers stay up late, because the air is clear.
There you go, right.
And then we got into that whole thing about why it is that people stay up late, because
that's when other people are sleeping, and therefore, there isn't that in the ether.
So, and that's the way that one went.
Mm-hmm.
Okay?
Alright.
I'm just reminding you, because it's 76, so I went to 67.
So, next one we do, let's see, 77.
87.
77, you know, 77, well, 77 is a 77, right?
Palindromes are stops, but when you subtract the palindrome of a palindrome, it goes right
to zero.
Right.
2178 is the only number that doesn't collapse.
Any other number, you subtract its palindrome, so, you know, 1 through 11, 0 through 11 doesn't
work, right?
Right.
Because if you subtract 9, it doesn't have a palindrome, 9 from 9, it goes to zero.
Right?
Any number, you leave the integers out if it's negative, and you keep doing the palindrome,
they go usually to 9, and then 6, like Tesla was saying, 3, and then 0.
All numbers within two or three operations, when you subtract their palindrome, it doesn't
matter if it's 49,999, right?
Right.
It will go down to zero after just a couple of operations, and from its palindrome.
But palindromes disappear right away, not double numbers.
Great.
So, what's the palindrome of 77?
77 minus 77, boom, that goes right to zero.
So, we live in a synthetic environment.
The only one that doesn't do it is 2178.
It becomes 8,000, whatever, and you subtract it, and it becomes something, and then it
becomes a little bit bigger, twice, I think, 2178, and then you subtract the backwards
of that, and it goes back to 2178.
And then you do the palindrome of that, and you're back to where you started, where it
brings you right back to 2178.
It just loops around.
It's the only number that does it.
That's the fine constant.
137.84 or whatever also is the fine number constant they use in physics, right?
Pi times 5.
All right.
Okay, let's get into it.
Let's just start making a short one.
Yeah, no, absolutely.
I just wanted to let you know where we were at.
All right.
Let's start.
Sonic event 76.
Okay.
I almost tripped over that.
It was funny because I had a bunch of other numbers just floating in my head due to the
fact that we were having a little conversation before I started recording, and I was going
back over some things and trying to follow the Greek.
He's very, very quick, obviously, with the numbers.
Anyway, it doesn't matter.
How are you doing tonight?
Quick with the numbers, yeah.
That would have been good back home, so to speak, in Jersey.
Remember the guys running numbers?
Handle the books.
You can make book, right, as opposed to handling the books.
Right, right.
Anyway.
We were talking about, well, sort of, let me just get into it because I had a little
chat, a text chat with someone recently on what they call Christmas Eve, like what to
do and this and that, the energy.
I said, listen, take advantage of it because, you know, we got into why teenagers stay up
late.
Well, not why, but I would suggest that the reason teenagers like to stay up late, to
recap, is they've gone from a young body to an adolescent body, and they're developing
a larger body looking more like an adult.
So as the body size changes, just like any ham radio antenna person will tell you, change
the antenna size, change the frequency, receptability.
So as they get more into the adult frame, the mindset can pick up more of the adult
mindset during the day, all the radio waves that the brains are transmitting and receiving.
And guess what?
In the collective, in normal society, it's really fucked up.
But this is new to them because they've just, you know, formed this more mature body.
Well, they didn't have the antenna before, so they weren't able to pick up as much.
I mean, it's that simple.
Well, yeah, it's when they just got introduced to it.
Right.
That makes perfect sense.
I mean, I can think back to when I, I mean, I don't know about you, but I virtually did
not need sleep as a teenager or as in my 20s.
I mean, I did my best stuff basically when everybody else was sleeping.
Right.
It's, this is an interesting, and I'm really sticking with this description or this reason
because once you understand, you know, the brain receives and broadcasts, right?
It's spiritual stuff, meaning mind technology, mind science, mind tech.
Well, I'll tell you something else, too, is you'll note a difference.
Okay.
Now, where you live now, it's not, I don't think the population density is super high.
It's not like the Northeast.
But when you're in a place like New York City, right, you know, they always say the city
never sleeps.
It really doesn't.
There's people on the street, no matter what time you're out, no matter where you go, you'll
find people actively moving around in New York.
Now, other places, your city totally sleeps.
It stops, you know.
There's no nightlife.
If you, I went down, someone wanted me, I dated a girl and her dad worked one of these
jobs with all the bennies, they call them benefits.
When someone says you got to do it for the bennies, that's like a total slave, right?
Get a job with lots of good benefits, right?
And I was like, all right, I'll check this guy out.
He worked in maintenance.
You know, when they hit the brakes too hard, especially when it's raining, you get a flat
spot on the wheel, on the train wheel, right?
The subway.
Sure.
So they have to machine those to a certain degree and then balance out their height and
all that.
So that's what he did.
And he was getting like 50 bucks an hour.
This is the 1980s, you know, which now would be equivalent to 150, 200 an hour.
Yeah.
It'd be really good pay, actually.
But yeah.
Yeah.
And he said, I don't think they're making that much because the salary is actually going
down, right?
So comparatively speaking, it did.
So probably they're making 100 bucks an hour, but really they should be making 200.
Yeah.
Gotcha.
In other words, at 50 bucks an hour in the 80s, you could buy a Cadillac, right?
No problem.
You can buy a house in a year.
Pay off the house in a year.
Yeah.
Right.
So anyway, I went down there, checked it out.
It was busy.
It was really busy.
It was fun.
You know, it was like these big toys, you know, cranes lifting all these things.
You can't move anything on your own, right?
Everything's so heavy.
Right.
So there's machines everywhere.
And it's crowded.
You know, we're talking like three in the morning, right?
Well, and your work is important because, look, you're balancing thousands and thousands
of pounds on these little wheels.
Okay.
So you don't do that correctly.
You know, you got problems.
Well, it's not even that scope.
In other words, the city never sleeps.
I mean, I went in there.
It was like another city within the city functioning, right?
Yeah.
Of course.
24-7 they do this.
And then all the other stuff.
There's the nightlife, they call it.
And when I say nightlife, literally nightlife.
So, I mean, there are places that open at 2 a.m. or 10, actually 10 a.m., 10 p.m.
Yeah.
And then they carry over.
All the way to dawn.
Yeah.
The bars were normally open until 4, but it's still dark out.
And then what could you do if you walked out of a place at 4 is usually somebody knew where
an after-hours place was, and those would go on until well into the daylight hours for
sure.
Yep.
And you could go back around to the legitimate establishments reopening, really.
If you wanted to drink 24 hours a day in a bar in New York, you can do it.
At least quite a few bars, yeah.
Everybody knew a place you could go.
But that's not the reason why.
The thing is the quality of the thinking, again.
The teenager analogy that we've given many times is the quality of thinking.
It's messed up, the collective.
So, okay, going back to the text that I was doing with someone, it's like, you know, he's
kind of perturbed.
Everyone around him is doing that holiday thing, and I'm saying, listen, take advantage
of it because it's really quiet right now.
In other words, they're all in this mindset, mostly.
Some people are very depressed or very sad during that time, right?
You know, I take advantage of that, by the way, by going to the secondhand stores by
the Golden Ghetto.
The Golden Ghetto is like the edge of the rich neighborhood.
There's a secondhand store.
And I buy brand new Nordstrom shirts, which are $80, $90 shirts for five bucks.
They still have the tags on them.
Why?
Because these old people, they get these $30,000 a month pensions.
They retire to the big house in Tucson.
They got nobody.
So what they do is they walk in the malls.
You know, they even open up the malls in the summer real early so the old people can walk.
Right.
Yeah.
And they do the same.
He goes to the mall every day, whether it's, you know, whatever, BMW or Rolls Royce or Cadillac.
And he goes in shops.
He doesn't wear anything.
He's got a walk-in closet full of, you know, expensive shirts and suits and all that.
So he passes away around Christmas.
They usually die between Thanksgiving and New Year's.
And the family comes from back east, New York, Chicago, Jersey, Massachusetts.
And they look at this big house, $2 million house, and it's full of stuff.
They don't.
Selling the stuff and all that.
It's like, ah, we want to sell the house and get them break, you know, separate the money.
So all the stuff in the house gets pulled out and sent to a secondhand store.
Like a half a million dollar wardrobe gets sent down to the secondhand stores, getting
a lot of these, you know.
So they want to sell them.
Right.
So they mark them.
But I used to joke around with the wife.
I had a bag.
I spent 20 bucks and I had like three, four shirts and a couple other things.
And I pulled a shirt out of the bag, Nordstrom's, Calvin Klein, all the stuff.
And I go, I think this is this is a little worn out.
And the tags are hanging.
And she looks at me.
What do you mean?
It's never been worn.
You know, you know, it's kind of being, you know, funny, you know.
So this is the time for me to go do my shopping because these old parts die around this time
between Thanksgiving and January is when I go to this particular secondhand store.
It's called Speedway Outlet.
Well, and what is is, you know, what's funny is that I guarantee you there's a couple of
people that are in business around that area that are just doing liquidator work where
picking up this big business this time of year.
Right.
And that's all you do is you go in and look, you got three, four kids, whatever.
They want to divide up the money.
Like you said, they don't want to bother with this.
They're not going to the secondhand store.
They don't know where it is.
But you do.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I'm not going to liquidate his closet and his furniture and his piano.
You go to Craigslist and they have a grand, not a baby grand or a grand piano free.
You know, it's a thirty thousand dollar piano.
Just come take it out of here.
Right.
And I'm like, what the hell?
Is this a scam?
No, it's not a scam.
No.
But the thing is, somebody was paid to get rid of it.
And now they're just looking for somebody else to do the work so they don't have to
go get a truck.
You'll go get the truck to go get rid of it.
Yeah.
And also the Tucson is a retirement city.
It's a retired like Palm Springs, Tucson, Phoenix.
Right. Those places are known to be retirement cities.
Yeah, of course.
So this is what's going on here right now.
And it's because, OK, it's not because they're having happy thoughts.
Some people are actually kicking the bucket.
Right. Right.
And so this is the time of year to go to retirement cities and buy secondhand stuff
because you'll be surprised what you'll get for secondhand.
You know, it's you know, and they upkeep it.
You know, when I saw a couple of grand pianos already and I'm like, oh, my gosh,
that's a 50,000, you know, a piano moving is very expensive.
They don't just don't move a piano.
They have to disassemble it.
Right. Yeah.
Usually. Yeah.
Yeah. And it has to be, you know, you don't want to damage it and all that.
So it's very expensive. So anyway, I'm looking at all this stuff and it's well
maintained. It's just because they're giving the stuff away doesn't mean it's
junk. It's actually because they're liquidating some wealthy retirees.
Estate. Right. Right.
This is what's going on. And this is a time of year.
OK, so that aspect.
But the other aspect is most people are typically happy.
So what's going on there?
I told this person in the text, take advantage of this.
All right. What does that mean?
The airwaves are cleaner than they usually are.
So take advantage of it.
Like if you have something you want to rehash, like a previous problem
or like a solution to something or you're trying to invent something
or you're trying to create something, if you're a writer or anything.
Now is the time to be creative because the coast is clear.
The air is clear or clearer than normal.
Right. You see, because they're receiving gifts.
They're happy. They're going to travel.
Right. You know, blah, blah, blah.
OK, so now the airwaves are a different frequency.
Take advantage of it.
Don't sit around and mope around and say, oh, fuck,
I don't do these pagan holidays and they do them.
What am I supposed to do?
Do what do whatever would work best with this cleaner air quality,
meaning radio frequency air.
You see what I mean?
If that makes any sense.
Take advantage of the circumstance.
You don't have to participate.
You can just take advantage of the circumstance,
which is funny because I actually got, you know, I hadn't gotten emails
for a little bit, which, by the way, the only time I'll see an email
is if you send it to me at my website, because that's the only place
where I control the emails.
Otherwise, we've given you the Greeks email address before.
And obviously people can email the Patriot.
Yeah, let's do them again.
Uncommon sense.
Radio one at Gmail dot com.
One is numeric one.
Uncommon sense.
Radio one at Gmail for the Greek.
And Chuck is blind JFK researcher at Gmail dot com.
And if you if you can't remember that, you can go to my website,
click on the little email icon and I'll get it from there.
But either way, it's fine.
But I did get one.
And it's funny, it kind of dovetails exactly with what you were talking about,
because they had asked about these pagan holidays and also about the cooking.
What do you do in the case that you have a partner already?
OK, now say that again.
A partner with a partner where you've already got a wife, a spouse, whatever.
I won't even give a gender on this.
It doesn't matter.
You got a wife, you got a husband.
I don't care. OK.
You got a partner. OK.
So that's your partner in life.
You live together. You work together.
But now you're changing.
This is the question from the email person. OK.
I'm rephrasing it a little bit, but it was like a very long winded sort of thing.
But yeah. And these holidays come up.
You're changing stuff.
And now you're noticing that originally the two of you did have an agreement.
The covenant you talked about earlier about relationships,
how you have the same covenant, et cetera.
But now, because you're learning and you're changing.
What do you do?
Because you still kind of want to maintain that partner,
but they might not want to come along with you, even from the kitchen.
Well, hang on from the kitchen to the pagan holidays.
They might still be stuck in the other stuff.
What do you do with that?
You know? Yeah, I got it.
It's very, very short.
Way back in the day before Ocelli in the Greek and at Ocelli in the Greek,
I said this will break up your relationship if you start looking to live a better life.
Ninety eight.
Ninety five.
Ninety nine percent of the time it will break up the relationship.
Maybe not right away, but definitely within six months to two years.
Right. If you're going to live well now, that is the actual spirit.
We're having like a spiritual mind experiment here.
Let's go back.
This material world and your physical body belongs to the earth.
In other words, when you're conceived sperm and egg,
if the mom doesn't eat earth material food, right?
Vegetable, animal, earth material, whatever.
She won't grow the baby and you won't be born.
And when you're born, regardless, you know, let's say after you're weaned away,
if your breast milk, hopefully you do have it.
You still need earth material to live.
Food, clothing, shelter.
This is everything that you see and touch with most of your senses.
Actually, all of your senses is earth belongs to the planet, the earth,
this existence, whether it's flat or round or whatever.
So the other stuff, the personality, the behavior,
the intellect or lack of is your experiment here.
Right. Your experience here.
But so let's go back to the question.
When you have these holidays,
they're very much expressed through materialism.
Yes. Right. Yes. And and OK, now let's go back to the other side.
They're expressed materialism.
But what is expressed mentally, spiritually,
you know, intellectually, that pretty much nothing.
Because even if you watch a documentary on the holidays,
they open up just like with dinosaurs, everybody's, you know,
66 million years ago when they start Christmas documentaries where they say,
well, he wasn't really born on December 25th.
They always start the documentary that way. Right. Always. Right.
Yeah. You know, but see, this this this adds a weird question to the mix
that the email person didn't ask. OK, but I'm going to ask it.
And it's it's pretty weird because, look,
if OK, you're doing things differently
and you have this partner, maybe you want to keep that partner.
Isn't there a way to kind of participate?
Yeah. Then let me let me continue. OK. Yeah.
Let me continue, because OK, so the mental thing, right away,
you see all the signs.
And if you do a little more mental work, all is everything.
It's acknowledged that this is not really accurate.
They go further and acknowledge that it's actually sat on the schedule
and on the days of the traditional Saturnalia,
Mithra, Mithraism, Simiramis, all this other stuff that goes back.
OK, so that's the mental.
The the rather mental is what?
Singing songs, getting drunk, giving gifts, feeling good, endorphin, dopamine.
Right. So there's no mental aspect to it. Right.
Really? I mean, with any kind of depth or substance.
So if that's so, in other words, OK, OK, how do we make this?
Let's not spend too much time on this.
And let me get to the point.
It's like not you, but, you know, to myself here
in the third party, get to the point, Greek.
Just like I said, I wasn't you notice I didn't coach or pad
the part about relationships, 95, 98, 99 percent of the time.
That's not going to last. Right.
Notice I didn't give any other.
I didn't make that too soft.
I didn't. There's no soft landing on that. Right.
No, there's not much margin for. OK. Yeah.
Different. All right.
So let's let's do the same with the mental part.
OK, this is real stupid shit.
So how well the answer then is, how do you handle it?
If one does and one doesn't in the relationship?
The question I would ask myself or ask that person,
how well do you deal with, quote unquote, stupid shit?
How well do you deal with stupid shit?
Let's let's say the time I would say, you know, personally,
no matter what level it's on, most stupid shit, I just stay out of it
and let them do what they're going to do.
You know, that's probably what they're trying to do.
They're probably trying to do that. Right.
There's other stupid shit people could do.
What if one spouse,
let's say, forgets the baby at the grocery store?
Where's the baby? I don't know.
Last time I saw him at the grocery store. Oh, shit.
I thought I left the baby.
I think the baby's at the grocery store.
This might sound funny, but it's happening.
It does happen. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
OK. Or or, you know, I got why is the back of the car
on the driver's side rear fender all crushed in?
You know, like, you know, while we were at the grocery store,
somebody backed up in the car, took off and the person got in,
didn't see it, got home and then you saw it when you got home. Right.
Yep. Stupid shit. Right.
That's why whenever you get to your car, do a little walk around.
Right. The whole thing.
Well, that would be smart.
But look, a lot of people don't.
And this is going to happen at some point.
Stupid shit is going to happen no matter what you do.
If we're going to make a list of if we're going to make a list of stupid shit,
there's enough there's not enough time on the whole Internet.
Right. Cover it. Forget about Sonics. Exactly. OK.
Yeah. So how do you deal with stupid shit?
There's no soft way.
Look, if you're going to land, if someone if you're taking someone out
on an excursion and you know that they're bumps and they could land hard,
you tell them that before they get get into it. Right. Let them know.
Of course. Right. Yeah. It's only fair to warn them. Yeah.
Yeah. So I think we've done that.
And look, I'm not taking responsibility.
Look, I can take responsibility with you and you can take sort of responsibility.
You know, I know I've gotten at least
500 people in the past, let's say, decade told me that they
drifting away from the standard collective stuff. Right.
So is it because of me?
Yeah, they actually told me it was because of me.
So am I responsible for it?
No, because I didn't do I just told them they they're the ones that do it. Right.
If I told them to go get a gun and shoot themselves, would they do it?
Right. It's my fault. Right.
Well, we've spoken to thousands of people and 500 of them actually drifted away.
I mean, that's pretty good.
And it is, you know, the thousands of people that didn't.
Are we responsible for them as well? No, we're not.
You know, but I know.
But there's a certain amount of responsibility,
because when a question like this is brought up,
you don't want to duck and run away and, you know, you want to cover it. Right.
So and there's no it's a hard landing.
So, yeah, so it's going to break up.
Ninety five, ninety eight, ninety nine percent of the time.
The reason I broke it up to ninety five, ninety eight,
ninety nine percent of time to separate, because as you do more research,
the chances of breaking up is that the ninety nine percent,
if you don't do a lot of research, but it makes you you don't want to.
It'll be ninety five percent. So. Right.
OK, so there's no that's not a that's a hard landing.
And the other hard landing is how do you deal with stupid shit?
So it's stupid shit.
You're going to have to deal with very simple.
Well, there you go.
And, you know, the same thing goes for toxic shit as well.
And I'm going to tell you what I mean by that is that, you know,
there are people that get together and in their relationship,
something new gets introduced and it's destructive.
And sometimes they share it.
No problem.
They're both perfectly, you know, perfectly capable of being self destructive
and therefore being mutually destructive together.
You see this with people that are drinking different stuff like that.
And they drink themselves into the stupidity.
And that's when you're introducing something.
This is more like a withdrawal, like you're withdrawing from a certain aspect.
But either way, you're changing the equation.
You're changing the initial agreement. Right.
I mean, yeah, I've known of a couple that drank a lot
and one decided to stop and they broke up because one wanted to continue.
And the other one wanted to stop.
Well, either that or they'll just descend into it
and, you know, drink themselves until their liver dies.
And then the other one dies to not too long after.
I mean, I've seen them defend and, you know, descend into darkness together.
And I've been a participant in some of that mess myself.
No, I understand me, too.
But here's the thing. You can't bring the OK.
Ultimately, you know what these holidays are.
It's an intelligence op to see who will go along with it
and those that don't go along with it.
And I'm not talking because you're Muslim or a certain sect.
No, they got other things for them.
They got other things for them, too.
I'm talking about if you're not going along with it,
because you've actually, quote unquote, researched it
and you have a fundamental understanding of what's going on.
It basically you become you go on the list now of those that could be watched.
Right. Yeah, exactly.
You know, because if you're a Muslim, you're just going to do Eid day
or you're going to do the.
Yeah, you're still in the same stuff. Something.
Yeah. I like what Archaic says about Jason Boucher's.
It's dungeon programming, he calls it.
You're still in the program.
Yeah, they offer you.
It's kind of like the the vending machine, you know, with the chips at the hospital
or every, you know, the convenience.
You know, like they got all these rows, you know, they got the Funyuns
and the Doritos and the one and the potato chips and the other one.
They got the multicolored ones and they got the candy bars.
As long as it doesn't.
The reason they have all these offerings.
The thing is, when you go within five feet of that vending machine,
you got to put money in and pull the lever.
They don't care what you take.
That's what all these religions are.
All the religions, by the way, I've got the seal of approval from the pope.
All of them. Right. Don't believe the fight.
Yeah. If you start a religion or there's a religion that doesn't have
this, the approval of the pope, I'm talking about the past 500 years
approval of the pope. You are done.
They will come in and clean you out.
Literally, you know, take you out.
So, yeah. So all of them are a form of that program
and an intelligence op because. Yeah.
So that's very simple way to put it.
And look, the this is an apologetic,
you know, apologetic means to defend one's position.
Right. Right. So the thing is, look.
No, I didn't hear any offense here.
I heard you just say, look, this is what will result if you do this.
That's not apologizing for it at all.
That's just telling you what's this is the logical conclusion to this action.
I mean, I think that's reasonable.
Actually, everything here belongs here.
The mental stuff is open.
You want to imagine your imagination is unlimited and it's also infinite.
I think I've talked about the capacity of the human mind.
Everyone can memorize everything.
We just taught that we can't and then we're limited. Right.
And we've also been downgraded as time goes on.
So and if you don't think humans have been downgraded as time goes on,
go watch some old black and white films and look at the facial features of people.
Look how prominent their features are.
And then switch over to a modern crowd,
you know, like people walking and there's people with cameras, you know,
doing walks in Fifth Avenue in Manhattan or any city in the world.
Look at their facial features.
They don't. Yeah. What are we looking for?
Is that this is typically we see the brows are smaller.
The eyebrows. Right. The brow bone.
The ears are smaller, which represents the overall constitution of the individual.
And the nose is much smaller and the faces are much rounder.
In other words, they look less developed.
This is just from a phrenological point of view.
Phrenology is the Greek phrenosis, the face, right.
Knowledge of face reading. Yeah.
By the way, all the phrenology books were on the FBI capture seizure list.
You know, the FBI has a book seizure list. Right. Right.
And it's not so it's not that programs aren't running so hot anymore
because now they just digitize it and take out whatever they want or get it lost.
Right. Yeah. But but the phrenology, I found some
there was a used bookstore here. I should have gotten it.
But phrenology book, it was under it was a National Socialist Party, 1937.
Nazis. Right. It was a Nazi book at a swastika and everything on it.
It was for the officers that when they ran into people and they wanted to
judge them, you know, their their racial purity, let's say. Right.
They went through this manual. Right.
And I was paging through is all in German and very well printed and all that.
And it was interesting because one of them, one of the faces,
the profiles was like almost like the gangster type that you see in a cartoon.
Right. And it's in Germany. It was dangerous.
This individual is dangerous.
You know, it was kind of trippy.
Yeah. So but anyway,
yeah, phrenology has been really banned
for some reason, because maybe it's true.
By the way, stereotype, the reason why it's called a stereotype,
it's because the word stereo means solid.
Right. It's a Greek word for meaning solid.
You know, we use it for, you know, the left and right speaker,
make a stereo solid image and type means type.
Right. In other words, categories.
So stereotypes.
The reason they're called stereotypes is because it's pretty solid.
And now they've turned it around and made stereotypes
something that should be what dismissed. Right.
Or not taken into account for.
Then why are they called stereotypes?
They would be called elusive types then.
Right. Or maybe types.
So, yeah, these things are not absolute,
but they are pretty general guidelines.
If you don't go to the more ridiculous end of it.
I mean, that's the truth of it.
Yeah. A stereotype.
Once you understand the validity of it.
Miles Davis, the horn player jazz.
When he lived in L.A., he bought a Ferrari.
And when he was still at the Ferrari dealership, he told the
the dealer, I want you to call the LAPD and tell him that Miles Davis
just bought a Ferrari. Right. Yeah.
Right. So, you know, you get it smart. Yes.
Yeah. Because he understands stereotypes. Right.
Absolutely. A black guy in a Ferrari is going to get pulled over.
You know, this is talking about 70s. Right.
A hundred percent of the time.
So, yeah. So he understood stereotypes.
So and so does the LAPD.
Hmm. No, definitely.