The Sonic Event 116 rated Y, and a little bit of a break, but did you notice?
Did you miss us, Greek?
How are you?
Okay, I think I could speak a little bit tonight.
Excellent.
Yeah, it's interesting.
It's not physical, as we were saying, losing one's voice.
I think it was energetic, and mental, and a bunch of other stuff.
I've got a lot of stuff going on.
Actually, I've got the least going on that I ever have, but the stuff that I've got going
on is the most that I've ever had.
You know, a lot of the woo-woo people talk about your chakra, your throat chakra gets
blocked and whatnot, and I've got a couple of messages recently about the difference
between superstition and maybe the vagaries of the way things actually function.
How true is that kind of stuff, where your voice gets silenced because everybody with
the whole karma play, right?
Oh, it's just karma coming back.
He's getting silenced because he said bad things.
It's mythology.
Yeah.
Mythology, but no, it's fine.
It's like a runner that has his knee, because I don't write.
I've discussed before why I don't write, because if you're writing and publishing, you're presuming
that people have comprehension, right?
It also adds to your participation in the culture, which is usually what superstition
is built on, right?
It's about culture, because you and I have talked about this, where people from different
parts of the world have similar ideas that are superstitious, right?
You know about the evil eye.
You know about the curses.
You're Greek.
I'm Sicilian.
We've both heard about curses at some point in our lives, right?
Well, here's the thing.
The Greek-speak stuff is just based on factual stuff.
Then there's the personal, what you do with it.
For example, with Greek-speak, what got you here ain't going to get you there.
In other words, if you listen to Greek-speak because you found out about it, you better
figure out what you want to do with it, because just listening to it and hearing it, whatever,
ain't going to get you anywhere, right?
It was like the confusion that people had years ago when you said, look, I'm not advising
anybody to do any of this, because here's what I guarantee you.
Everybody around you.
Yeah.
I wouldn't do what I would do.
I wouldn't do what I would do, especially if you value the people and things you have
around you right now, because if you do, you're going to lose them, most likely.
No, we're not losing them.
What will happen?
Well, yeah, you will, in a simple term, perhaps, but what happens is, okay, if you understand
what's going on, in big air quotes, and you want to be a part of it, fine.
But this is what I want to say.
Some people think it's kind of negative, angry, or whatever, but if you have a positive attitude,
you'll be rewarded.
And the best positive attitude is the giving attitude, right, just to help people for the
sake of helping.
I've spoken to people that did things, they went on projects, whether it was a week long
or seven years or 10 years, that they would be rewarded.
The universe will reward them or the gods will reward them.
No such thing comes about, right?
And I said, of course, it's not going to come, the chances of doing something good, right,
so you can have good done to you is nearly null, you have to do it in a in a sensible
way that that's part of your character.
And then your character, it's a character gets rewarded, not your actions, but your actions
are based on your character.
Again, what got you here ain't going to get you there.
You know, in other words, listening to Greek speaking, ain't going to do much for you unless
you know how to use it.
But I just got someone, I get messages, by the way, I get someone messaging me, emails
a long time listener, and he just did some black car wax on a black, a black shoe polish
on a black car.
No one does that.
Right.
And it's great, because it fills all the scratches and everything, right?
It's like, it's amazing.
Works great, you know, because you know, you've ever pulled out years ago, I don't think people
polish shoes anymore, maybe they do pull out some old pair of shoes, put some shoe polish
on and you're like, damn, they look just good.
Just as good as new, except for the, you know, the wear on the heel or whatever, right?
Yeah, on the bottom, like everything except the bottom of the shoe looks great.
Yeah, same with a car.
So you know, stuff like that.
By the way, here's another little tip.
If you have laundry facilities, and even if you don't, most people have a refrigerator
with a freezer section.
I noticed like some older clothes or while as your body chemistry changes, I get bo and
I can't wash it out of t shirts and things like that.
I once heard, you know, with real expensive jeans, because some jeans go for, you know,
the Dolce Gabbana is right, you can imagine, right.
And don't wash them, because you'll wear them out, put them in the freezer makes the smell
go away.
So let me try that.
So I've been doing that.
And it works really, really well.
So if you have body odor on something, especially things that would be dry cleaned, or you don't
want to wash, put it in the freezer.
They say it's the bacteria that freeze that cause the odor.
It's a yin and yang thing also, by the way.
Yeah.
So that's another tip.
I've been practicing that this week.
I've got half my closet in the freezer.
I happen to have a freezer chest.
But I didn't use it.
But in case you want to start a laundry service or you freeze people's clothes to get the
smells out.
Quite interesting.
That's interesting.
Bring that up.
But yeah, one thing I wanted to just tackle a little bit is there was, you know, the Trump
verdict thing, right?
Oh, boy.
Yeah, I can't.
I'm not going to talk about Trump, but I just want to talk about how something like that
is so obviously whatever, kangaroo court, and obviously a show, but it does pertain to
how what's going on.
It's very important that people understand this.
And what I'm going to say is understood by less than 1% of people working in the Department
of Justice.
Probably Supreme Court judges know this.
Some judges know this.
Almost no attorneys know this.
So what I'm saying now is the kind of stuff you get for like $1,500 attorney stuff, you
know, $1,500 an hour attorney stuff.
So this is what's going on.
People don't know is there, you know, they're fake courts, you know, they railroad people,
they charge people with all these things like something very loose, and they serve time
in prison and all that.
All of this is because of the minister, a series of administrative procedures acts passed
by legislation.
And also a landmark case in 1938 called Tompkins versus Erie Railroad.
Okay, so the administrative procedures acts for like 1887, 1946, 1966, 1982.
I know them all, by the way, and I could talk and lecture on them because that's what everything
is based on administrative law.
In administrative law, it's basically commercial, like the first one 1887 was interstate commerce
and all this other stuff, right?
But what happens there is in administrative law, the law gets so glorified that any proceeding,
legal or otherwise, is always putting the actual regulations codes in question.
And because you can't question them because they're a fact of legislature, right?
They're infallible.
And everyone in the courtroom is an offender.
And a payment has to be made and bonded.
This sounds like some crazy religion.
Bear with me.
And by the way, it is.
The Bar Association, Segway, is in every country in the world.
North Korea, Iran, all these enemy countries, they all have the same bar association with
their country's name in front of it, the American Bar, the Russian Bar, whatever, whatever.
It's a group that comes out of England.
It's kind of modified.
Nobody knows.
They deny what it means and all that.
And there is no legislative act that ever said the bar can take over the court system
of the world, of every country in the world.
There's no legislative government.
Legislative act means, you know, enacted in law.
True.
But if you want to freak out a barrister, just bring up the phrase to them, Temple Bar
Association, and they'll cringe.
Right.
But the thing is, do you know how it works, you know?
Right?
And the answer is no.
Most people don't.
I kind of want to break it down.
It's a private organization, just like all the money is WEF, right?
Right.
And so everything is already new world order for a long time.
But there's no tell a lawyer that, you know, there's no legislative act that enacted the
Bar Association to run the judiciary because, you know, you can't be a judge or a highland
lawyer or high end lawyer or attorney general without being a bar member.
And there's no by the way, there is no license to practice law.
It's fictitious.
They're calling a bar card, right?
A license to practice law in a way it is because a library card is a license to take books
from the library.
Well, it's membership or approval by the organization in order to participate, which is the bar,
which is not there.
Again, there's no understanding.
Underscore.
There's no legislative act.
OK, so back to Administrative Procedures Act.
The laws are infallible.
They're sitting there.
So any procedures are going on as an offense to the regulations.
Now, you might say, well, Greek, well, you know, here's the plaintiff.
He's been, you know, and then you have the defendant and there's an offense by the defendant
against the plaintiff.
Right.
No, that's OK.
That's what that's what people say in law.
But once you go into the administrative procedures side of things, which is everything, right,
the law is no longer competent.
The law is no longer competent.
In other words, it doesn't hold anymore, because if you the the the the logic there is that
if you were observing the law, you wouldn't be here.
OK, so this is what's going on.
How does someone get guilty on all 34 charges?
How does someone get guilty on whatever?
It doesn't matter.
You want to run the whole gamut.
There's I think worldwide there's over 20 million different things, illegal offenses
you can be charged with in the United States, over 14 million things you could be charged
with.
Sure.
OK.
All right.
So this is what's really going on.
And this is the intent of the administrative procedures.
And this is what's going on.
How are you guilty on all 34 charges, especially let's let's fast forward to oral arguments
with a jury.
When the jury goes into deliberation to create to bring forward the verdict, what they are
told specifically is the entire case.
This is what a plea does.
Also, if you put in a plea guilty, no contest or not guilty, it's the same thing.
By the way, if you don't show up for a court date, the judge puts in a not guilty plea
for you.
Right.
Because people think, oh, I'm going to plead not guilty has nothing to do with the plea.
By the way, putting in a plea and this is the punchline, this is where I'm going to
finish the thing off.
When you enter, when a plea is entered of anything, it means that the charges are true.
So when someone is guilty on 34 charges, when the jury goes in, what the jury is told, what
you are going to decide on are the charges true?
Not whether they don't say not whether the person committed the crimes or not, but whether
the charges were applied correctly and whether they did it or not is irrelevant because this
is administrative.
Right. So the only evidence that could be looked at is, let's say
they have several, you know, they call them star chambers, pre-trial stuff, right?
Indictments that are done without, you know, in secret.
OK, when that's the most important part, when you're charged, you're indicted, those things
are structured in a way that once they get on, once you're charged with it, you're stuck
with it, whether it doesn't matter if you're guilty or not guilty.
So what the jury is asked.
Was it was he charged with this number one all the way to 34?
Right. You know what I'm talking about?
Yes. Was he charged?
He was charged. OK, let's go 34 counts.
Right. So first count.
Is this charge true?
Obviously, yes.
Second charge. Is this charge true?
Yes. Third charge.
Is this charge true?
Yes. Not whether he's guilty or innocent of it.
Is the charge true?
And then the whole thing is the indictment.
If you read indictments and things before they arrest someone, they set up the charges in
a way that it seems like you're guilty, but it's irrelevant because does the charge fit?
Right. It's like this was the crime fit with the glove.
You must. Does it?
Yeah. If the glove don't fit, you must acquit Johnny.
Right. It doesn't matter.
So in other words here, let's go back with something.
Go, Jay Simpson. Is it true that you can be charged for murder?
Yes. Is it is it proper to have charged him with murder?
Most people would say, yeah, but he's innocent.
That doesn't matter that he's innocent or guilty.
I know this doesn't make sense to the this is this makes just as much sense to most people
as the money system does.
How I know what you can do when the government wants to make money, they send you a check.
And then when you sign it, it becomes ten times that value.
Right. Right. People don't understand that this could be looked up very readily and charged.
If you're charged with something, it's always pointed out.
Well, he was charged with that. He's not guilty.
All things with O.J.
He was found not guilty.
Remember, right? It doesn't matter somewhat.
OK, what happens administrative?
It's shipping. It's commerce.
All if you look at it, I forgot which code it was in the title.
All crimes are commercial crimes.
I think it's Title 28 or Title 18.
Title 18. Either one.
Title 18, 28 or 50.
But anyway, or the shades of it in there.
So, OK, so this is what's going on.
Once the charges are put together, bonded, they have a case number and there gets they sent over to the Chris system.
C.R.I.S. Are you in front of a computer?
Yeah, I put in Chris.
C.R.I.S. It's an acronym system.
Federal Reserve.
And it should show it's the Court Registry Investment Service.
It's part of the Federal Reserve Bank.
And it's in Dallas.
Do they still show that on the Internet?
I'm just curious.
Let's see.
Christopher C.R.I.S.
Christopher J. Walker, Federal Reserve.
So here we go. Chris.
No, Chris Barker.
Put in Chris Court Registry Investment Service or Chris is part of the Federal Reserve in Dallas or Chris Court C.R.I.S.
Court Investment Federal Reserve.
Anything come up?
OK, hold on.
Court Investment System, most likely.
Anyway, look, years ago you would find it online.
I mentioned this to someone about a year ago.
I said it's nothing.
There's nothing online on the search.
Chris Court Registry Investment System.
Oh, you found it online under the United States District Court, Middle District of North Carolina.
Court Registry Investment System.
Chris, what is the Federal Reserve?
It's out of Dallas.
They show that the course registry is, let's see, interest bearing cash management tool administrated by the administrative office of the U.S.
court that provides clerks with an easy, efficient court now and safe way to apply.
It's part of the Federal Reserve System out of Dallas, Texas.
Now there's now they're shrouding it in the state court.
Let's see. How does it operate?
How is money deposited?
How does money get?
It has nothing to do with that.
I'm just telling you what's listed as, you know.
Yeah. OK, well, it's in Dallas.
It's a Federal Reserve.
All court cases run through there and they go through the window.
They become monetized.
Well, you know, I can add Dallas to it and see if that's what it does.
There's a lot of long winded stuff there.
That's it. So if it's a traffic ticket in Podunk, Idaho or a big case, they all go through the Chris system, just like everything goes through the DTCC.
Right. It's all financial.
This now can only be found on the Internet Archive, looks like to me the original listing, which, let's see, Attribution
non-commissioned. OK, there's something about the court registry investment system now online.
Yes. But it doesn't go directly to Federal Reserve Dallas, Texas.
No. General order 24 court registry.
I mean, it's bad that it doesn't because that's what it is.
But yeah. Yeah. But this is where it mentions Dallas is in the Internet Archive.
OK. General order number 24, court registry investment system.
Dallas, also known as Chris, which stands for court registered investment system.
This is a system used by the judicial branch.
Read judges who often misallocate justice to the interest of continuing the transfer of wealth from the defendants that would be actual people.
Most of the time, nothing has to do with monetizing the court case.
Well, I'm just reading what it is.
You know, I could stand up and talk about the legal system, how it works and the history behind it.
As a lecturer, a professor type lecture on another planet, not this planet.
You know, I mean, they give another acronym here, by the way, which is what they give another an acronym here, which is OK.
The bonds are indexed under a system known as CUSC, CUSC bonds.
Real quick. Every case, even the bonds are short.
2003 was the Paperwork Reduction Act.
A lot of things have changed since then.
But what I'm going to talk about is before that there's something called the Miller Bond System.
Construction companies use it.
So there's no money.
So they want to rebuild that bridge that the boat hits.
Right. All right. About a month ago.
OK. Three billion dollars.
So they put out a couple of contracts.
They figure like everything underwater is going to be 300 million.
Everything above water is going to be, you know, about a billion.
And then they have to do this other stuff.
Half a billion. So they put it out for bid.
Right. And that's why, you know, people cry when there's a no bid contract.
It's corruption. Right.
So the government puts out stuff for bid.
So you're a construction company.
When you put in your bid, you have what's called a bid bond and a performance bond.
And it has to be signed by flesh and blood being an executive.
And you have to be vetted.
So when the government gets those bids, they take the bond that the construction
company put in. It's an executive bond, right?
An executive, not an executive.
Right. Trix is the female executor.
Yeah, gotcha. All right.
Let's say tricks. OK, so.
So the government says, oh, I want to get that government job.
I want to get the government's money. Right.
The government has no money.
What they do is when you put in the bid for the job,
they take the bond and they deposit in the Federal Reserve
and they get the money off of your own bond.
The construction company funds its own
construction fund. It's crazy.
And then you have to pay for it twice.
So then you have to put in a performance bond.
So give a shout out to Alberto.
He's a old OG here in Tucson.
While back, went down to court building anyway.
His son was going to jail for whatever.
So we go up to the court clerk and we say, got this case number in your computer?
She goes, yeah.
And OK, so we'd like to sign off on the bonds.
And she goes, what did you say?
Can you present the bonds to us so we could sign them off and have the case
discharged? I can't do that because if I do it for you,
I have to do it for everybody.
Now, the big bond is what's in other words, once we a second party
signs those bonds, they can cash it out and the boy doesn't have to go to jail.
Done. Everything's paid for.
OK, so the big bond is up to three proceeding up to what they calculate
to be three hundred thousand dollars from what I understand.
But, you know, there's unlimited.
It goes to like 60 million now because it was up to three hundred thousand
some years ago. I know that for sure.
That was. Yeah.
So but all you got to do is sign it and then you got to do some verbiage
and the money comes out of your signature.
But anyway, here's the thing.
The big bond is the court case.
OK, the performance bond is the fines that you pay or the jail time.
You have to perform time.
OK. Right. So there's always two bonds.
There's more bonds to it.
But it's called if you put in the Miller bond system,
does anything come up on the Internet or they kill that, too?
Well, I'm going to try that.
But you know what's funny?
I just entered the cussing thing that I was telling you, which was the.
That's different.
That's the Convention on Universal Security Investment Protocols.
Yeah. Yeah.
But what's funny is that that is the first time ever
that I put in something that's, you know, a letter standing for a word
that I have gotten absolutely zero.
It tells me that they're they're blocking it.
Yeah. OK.
You know, when you go to a government officer's school, they have your name
and these little has to be spelled out in individual boxes for each letter.
Many forms are like that, mostly school forms.
You'll see it. Yes. Right.
And they'll tell you that's for the computer.
No, that's a QCIP.
That's part of the QCIP convention. Right.
So when you go to Ace Hardware or a supermarket
to get one of their rewards cards, it's just like that.
It is. I said, my gosh, how much do I get for fillings?
I'm giving you guys my credit.
Yeah. What are you talking about?
People don't know they have no clue.
That's why this is the kind of stuff I could lecture on.
I could do a full semester course on how the legal money system even helps.
But on another planet, right?
Not here, because people are going to hear this.
They're going to say, first of all, I don't understand what you're talking about.
Second of all, it sounds so outrageous, even though I can look it up.
I still don't believe it.
Just like the college professor.
So he told him that, you know, even if all the astronauts said,
even if all the astronauts confessed that they never went to the moon,
I still believe they did.
OK, well, here's a funny thing.
When you put in the Miller Act payment bond claims, right?
All right. Well, here's the thing.
The American Bar Association is the first thing that comes up.
Second is the G.S.
When you do a search for the Miller bonds. Yeah.
The bars come. Oh, perfect. Perfect. Good.
So they're telling you. Good. Yeah.
So they come up.
But then the second thing is funny to me because it's under the GSA dot gov.
OK. Yeah, that's right.
Government services.
And they give you the Miller Act, which is right. Yeah.
So they show you the Miller Act.
But the Bar Association does something different.
Now, let's go take precedence over the GSA government.
And then they have the G.S.
So and then there's the there's all these they're they're all they're all corrupt.
Like, for example, you know, the coroner,
the coroner was no one messed with the coroner.
He really had the highest office in the county. Right now.
He's just nothing.
They've dragged him. They pimped him out like a crack hole.
Or oh, yeah. Years ago, the coroners would refuse to
if it was a suicide and the sheriff or the police said it was not a suicide.
If he was murdered and the police said just to say, no, I'm not going to say
it's a suicide because it's not.
And they would, you know, honor him and whatever.
So they got rid of all the good corners and everybody that's in there now
is just a puppet. Right.
Well, that's why they also downgraded the requirements in most places
in the in in this place they call America.
People don't know this.
They're not even required to be doctors anymore.
Yeah, that's right.
You're supposed to have at least a graduate or doctorate to be.
In other words, it was the most respected.
He had the highest office.
Like, like, for example, he's a piece of trivia.
When you go to become a paramedic, EMT or you're going to drive
in one of those emergency vehicles that one of them in the test,
they tell you who has jurisdiction and they give you like police sheriff.
Right. Whatever.
And then postal police, you know, it's the postal police
have the highest jurisdiction, the federal postal police.
And then it's the yeah, then they're.
Yeah. So anyway, yeah, the coroner had, you know, had was the most respect
had the highest position really in the land and on the county level.
Right. And they've gotten rid of all that.
So now these government agencies like the GSA and all that
that used to be very respectable, you know,
they've been also trashed completely, just like the Treasury.
Right. We've been completely trashed.
There's just trash, trash, people, trash system.
It's just so secondary.
It's just a formality now doesn't even do anything anymore.
Has no honor and no, no, no teeth, no bite, no bark and no bite.
Well, see, I want to know something, though.
But, you know, as you go through all this, right,
because there is the Trump thing and OK, there's the court system
and how that actually functions. And what's the truth?
Yeah. This has to do with traffic tickets, too.
Yeah, there's nothing to do. I'm not talking.
I just wanted to bring up the fundamentals of it.
Don't of course. Yeah.
So when you hear someone been railroaded, he didn't do it.
It doesn't matter. It's the charges is administrative of the charges.
True. Was it right that he was charged with it?
Whether he did it or not is irrelevant, because now there's a debt
that has to be run through the system and bonded.
Right. In other words, here's another way.
That bridge that fell in the Delaware hit by a boat.
It doesn't matter if it was, you know, set up to do that or what.
Is the bridge there? No. Do we need a bridge? Yeah.
Yeah. Why it happened and whatever and who did it where.
Right. That's how the courts work.
Every you know, so basically when you say guilty means you're going to pay for it.
When you say not guilty is the charges are true, but you don't want to pay for it.
That's why they do, please.
Well, fair enough, except in the case of where you plead no contest,
which means, you know, no contest means that whoever can pay, step in and pay for it
should pay. You know, I hope someone comes in and pays for it for me.
Otherwise, I'll get stuck with the bill.
I'll have to wash dishes. OK, fair enough.
What I find interesting, though, is that this is a two pronged purpose.
You have the functionality of this system,
but also this is really just for TV.
This is made for TV. This is made for video content.
No, no. But I'm saying let's say it wasn't.
That's why I said I kept emphasizing here.
Right. Even a traffic ticket works this way.
Right. Yeah. Yeah.
So I just want to bring this up because that was in there.
And it seems like nothing can be done about it other than an appeal.
But people don't understand.
They understand like back in the days, cops were good
because they had Barney Fife and all these cop shows. Right.
And then they did the the court TV.
So they have several court justice shows even now running, I think, probably.
Until recently. Sure, sure.
Actually, not until recently.
People think that's how it goes.
No, no, I get it.
And that's the funny part about this is that, look, my spitting on the sidewalk
ticket or whatever that they decide to issue me.
Nobody wants to watch that on TV usually.
But since this is this, you know what I'm saying is
stuff they're showing you on TV and telling you in school is completely false.
Right. It's just like, you know, jet fuel doesn't disintegrate steel.
Right. It's a powder.
No, definitely not the powder.
No. Yeah.
Anyway. Yeah.
No, it's just to me, it's interesting that, you know, there's the other side of this,
which is how it's useful as content
and how it's useful to leverage everybody's emotional reactions to something.
Oh, you mean the case with Trump?
Yeah, they completely don't understand any of it.
I brought that from any saw that.
I know what's going on.
And it's like, you know, 99 percent of the people, if not 99.999999 percent
of people watching a Trump case will say it's just a show or whatever,
but they don't know how it really works.
What they showed with the Trump case is actually factual.
In other words, because that's how the system works.
But people, if you ask 99.999999, even law professors, they'll say,
oh, yeah, that was because it's a liberal judge and blah blah.
They're trying to railroad them.
You'll never mention.
That the administrator proceed.
It's an administrative court.
And it's a matter of there's no competency in law there.
The law is not competent to be brought in there.
They don't know that it's whether the charges are true, not whether he did it or not.
This is what I'm trying to say.
It sounds bizarre.
So the takeaway from all this stuff is when you're being charged with a crime and you
think you have a strong evidence and a not guilty plea, it has nothing.
That's a show.
That's the real show, even if it's a traffic ticket, right?
Any plea.
Here's the thing.
You could find this in the Administrative Procedures Act.
I don't know about online.
Any plea entered into a case is admitting the charges are true.
You're screwed.
And this is how the system works.
And people, just like banks, banking, right?
If you get, I don't know if you were, we were speaking out there early on in 2019, 2020,
when they started 2021 sending checks out, I said that if you get a $1,000 check from
the government, you're going to pay for that.
It's going to cost you more than $10,000 in the next five years in inflation.
That's what I kept telling people.
Oh, yeah.
Someone in the car washed it.
If you, for every dollar that you get from the government for as a stimulus, it's going
to cost you $10 later.
Is it worth?
That's terrible.
It's terrible.
Even compound Warren Buffett, you know how Warren Buffett makes his money is by weighting
compound interest.
Right.
He makes his money by waiting 20, 30, 40 years to get a return.
And that's how compound interest works.
$1,000 invested, actually $10,000 invested in 40 years becomes over half a million.
Right.
So if you're investing $10,000 a year in your 20s, by the time you're 65, you'll have several
million dollars.
And you can afford, you know, working 50, 70, $80,000 a year job.
You can do that.
Right.
It's.
Yeah.
So, boy, putting $200 a week away in your 20s would make you a millionaire when you when
you're in your 60s, multimillionaire, just simply by compounding.
Right.
You have to know how to do it.
I'm using the index and all that.
But OK, so what I'm trying to say here is that whenever there is a case about law, that's
how it works.
And also, just like the money, people don't understand.
It sounds bizarre.
If I went in public and started telling people we're under credit based and right.
And if the government wants to create a lot of money, they send you a check.
And when you sign the check, it becomes 10 times or nine times face value.
They give you whatever's on the check and they split the rest with the bank.
And that's how they create money.
That sounds absolutely bizarre.
And what I'm telling you is exact.
It's already printed in the Federal Reserve manual.
You could look it up yourself.
Right.
No, it's so.
Yeah.
The whole concept that it does appear out of thin air is true.
It's just that the way it's created is not.
Yeah.
But there has to be.
They have their own internal auditing.
So they try to stick to accountability.
And most of it is accountable.
That's why they have the IRS and big again, Warren Buffett's company as a you know, the
IRS is a money laundering operation.
I don't think you most people know it is that they just see it as the tax man.
It has nothing to do with that.
It's when they want to move funds to create, let's say, overthrow a government.
They move it through the IRS.
Right.
No one's going to say, hey, look, they moved this money through the IRS.
Anyway.
So this is it's bizarre, but it's true.
That's what I'm saying.
This the Greek speak stuff is super effective.
If I can get on a flying saucer and get to another end of the solar system or another
galaxy, maybe people eat it up.
Don't be like, holy shit, we were really waiting for a simple explanation on how this
works.
But if you try to do this here where it's happening, crickets, it doesn't really work.
It doesn't have much impact.
But the whole thing is whoever's listening can understand it.
I think I dropped a lot of detail on this one.
So it might be worth listening to again, if you're interested in jotting down some notes
and looking up a bunch of stuff like that.
You know, by the way, when we're on a sonic and I say, Chuck, punch that into the Internet,
what do you get?
That's a that's a hint that see what's online because it's just not that it makes it more
real because the Internet is alive.
Right. You know that digitizing a book is no longer that book that was digitized.
It's the digital version, which means whatever can anything can be put in and taken out.
Well, it's what I call the digital book burning.
And you can either do it a sentence at a time or you can eliminate the whole thing either
way or just alter it so that it's still under the same label.
People go looking for something that they think was there and they find out, guess
what? Oh, Mandela effect.
It must be. No, they changed it.
Well, it's the end of the cosmic editing of the Mandela effect is real.
Yes. But when you start over applying it.
Right. Right.
Well, it's just like anything else.
Look. And the funny thing is, a lot of people think this might be exclusive to the American
system. This is not.
This is a global system, even since the 30s and especially after the 50s.
Oh, yeah. And look, it took them a little while to figure it out in the communist world
there for a moment. But, you know, when Vladimir Putin, Putin took over Russia, what did he
do with the oligarch that complained?
He charged him with tax evasion and stuck him in prison.
I mean, and it was it was for a penny.
It was for nothing.
And what was he complaining about?
You have to show something, a penny, a stamp or a stamp is even worse.
Oh, yeah. Because Russia stamps are very important.
Yeah. Like if you stole a stamp, it's like 30 years in prison, you know, in Russia.
Yeah. I mean, you know, that's almost like getting your hand cut off in some other places.
But yeah, people don't know that years ago stamps were very important.
Not anymore. But anyway.
So, yeah, I agree.
This is a yeah.
This is what's going on on this planet.
And no one's going to change it, but you can weaken it and you can affect the change.
OK, so if everybody stopped using the banking system, right?
Yeah.
For just three days, just which is palatable.
You can do that because people stop doing things on a three day weekend.
Don't they want to that they normally do?
Right. They go on their three day weekends that are like a big deal.
Yeah. Look, you could literally get away with not doing anything except breathing for three
days. Almost anything in your life.
Whatever.
That's right. Especially if eating and drinking.
That's right.
If you don't want to eat, you don't want to drink.
You could do anything except breathing.
Breathing is the only thing that's true.
If you were locked up in a box.
Yeah. What do they call it?
The box in the southern prisons where they put you in the hole.
Yeah.
Whatever. Yeah.
OK, so you can live there for.
Yeah, definitely.
Three days.
Anybody can do three days without anything.
Yeah. Right now the system is set up to do be able to handle billions of transactions per hour.
And just like anything, there's but you look computers buffer in the handle and they stream
and do that. If that's if that goes down to near zero instead of billions of transactions per hour,
the thing will not the analog, the the what do you call it?
The when a computer has a metric, what do we not the analog, the algorithm will shut itself down
because it'll think that something's disconnected and it'll say I'm broken.
You get it?
Exactly.
The algorithm will be because the algorithm with a is just networking with algorithms.
Right. And the algorithms that people call it is going to shut the thing down.
Now, can anyone shut it down?
No. But if you get the thing to passively shut down on its own, what's better than that?
That's like amazing.
Right. That's like beyond Neo and the Matrix.
Right.
Exactly.
So, yeah, and it's so simple to do.