Technically, this is event 234, but you know,
we're gonna we're gonna do this real short
and just attack the one issue that came
up between a few people.
And it's just real simple.
Look, Greek, they're complaining about the chat tango.
And like, you know, and I've heard this
before, you know, they don't like that.
Some people don't like chat tango as a
place to be.
And so they're saying stuff like we'd like
a forum where we could have, you know,
different subjects and this and that.
And I said, Well, look, you know, there's
lots of platforms, but I want to get
your feedback on that.
You know, if somebody and by the way,
we didn't build the chat tango, somebody else
did.
And people well, I suggested the forum Yeah,
well, here's the thing.
I just where people can meet when we're
when we're not doing our thing.
And to talk about what we're talking about,
and back and forth, I'm open, but I
don't I can't dedicate any time to it,
you're, you'd have to take that on.
And maybe anyone who else wants to help
out?
Well, I say, I'm down for whatever.
Yeah, I say, let me put it this
way.
Let me just say this before you go
on.
I can't really, when I go into chat
tango, it's like once a week, sometimes once
every two weeks, sometimes every other day, I
my time is really taken up at this
point.
Because I want it to be focused where
I'm focusing it.
I wouldn't say the Sonics are low priority,
but they are.
And I can't I can't go go beyond
any, any, any more than I'm doing right
now regarding Sonics and all that other stuff.
Right.
But here's the thing.
If these guys, I'm open to it.
Yeah.
If these guys want to build, okay, something
on a platform that you know, that they
prefer that they like, that could be accessible,
you know, and all that I say, good,
do it.
Show me the better spot because to tango,
we just used it because it was familiar
and it was open for anybody to go
to, you know, and accessible from any device.
But you know, some devices vary in experience
when you do these things, right?
So anyway, it would be good to have
a space where you can comment under different
topics.
The space looks like a big soup.
Yeah, this is them complaining again.
One is commenting about whether yet it does.
And that's the way it is.
It is a big soup.
And look, you, you have discernment and the
Greek, yeah, by the way, it's linear.
If some, if I tell someone that was
posted and should tango, like I've been scrolling
for an hour, you know, I've been scrolling
for weeks here and it doesn't go back
that far.
I'm like, okay, yeah, I get it.
It's cheap.
It's well, it's cheap.
Not meaning cheap.
It's low quality.
Yeah.
It is.
And so if somebody has something, I mean,
you know, yeah, linear, we can go to
a date though.
Usually if it's recent and find a comment
or find a response or find a video
or a picture or whatever.
And if somebody has a better idea, I
say, sure, show us, tell us, you know,
but let's not get into, you know, everybody's
got to sign up for crap and whatever
else.
Like in other words, build it, build it
and he will come despite the Mandela effect.
Sorry.
Yeah.
We did.
Well, we did.
Sorry.
We did set up the tango.
You do have to sign in.
It's not public, but it's like, you know,
today I kind of like, it reminds me
of the old HTML days when websites were
very plain and simple and there was a
lot, the heydays.
That's what I should say.
It reminds me of the heydays of the
internet right back, back when it was more
whatever.
But yeah, I can't get into, I mean,
like I just said on the earlier previous
Sonic, I heard about the archaics underground and
he's talking about it and he said, there's
a health and wellness.
All right, let me go check it out.
And I signed in.
And like I said, I just can't, I
don't know where to start.
I looked at whatever else was posted as
my stuff.
This stuff is so contrary, even though it'll
be helpful.
I just can't sit there and type all
day or whatever.
So no, but it's something like that.
You want to do something, something more elaborate.
Most forums tend to be category based and
member based and blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Someone wants to set it up.
It's fine.
Yeah.
Because look, either we could use the facilities
on Patreon and do something similar to what
it is they're asking for.
Or if you have a better solution, look,
build it.
No, I don't.
No, not you.
I'm saying you, the listener, you, the listener,
have a better solution.
Do me a favor and go ahead and
show me what it is and I'll work
with you on it and we'll develop it
and we'll just give Greek, you know, the
password or whatever.
And Chitango, you don't even need to sign
in.
You can go in anonymously.
But right.
Right.
Sort of.
We changed it because someone was posting porn
or something and yeah, well, I don't know.
I like to see more progress, progress in
what we talk about and if a forum
is the way to do it, fine.
Yeah.
No problem.
But like I said, you're not going to
build it.
And like, you know, if somebody else establishes
it, though, show me and we will integrate
it into everything.
I don't want to have 80 forums though.
So let's, you know, be selective.
You agree?
Hmm.
What do you think?
We have two right now.
The Patreon.
Yeah.
Well, there's the Patreon, the Chitango.
So the rest is, I don't know.
I mean.
Well, yeah.
But, you know, I see when you start
getting into people's preferences, right?
Somebody might say, well, I'm comfortable with Facebook.
Well, I would rather work in a, you
know, what they used to call Twitter X
spaces.
Somebody else might say, well, look, we should
use Reddit where you can do different subreddits,
you know, and OK.
And only people that are going to want
to find the Greek subreddit will find the
Greek subreddit.
But, you know, it's up to you guys.
If you have a better way so that
we can do this better.
Look, I'm not saying that I'm 100 percent
familiar with forums and obviously the Greek doesn't
do that all day.
Yeah.
You know.
Look, these these social media are like you
got mall security, you know, the malls, shopping
malls have mall security.
I'd rather hang out at the park, you
know, you know what I mean?
Like a public park that's more open.
So the more open, you know, like I
said, you know me, I'm going to read
the back in the day when I was
on Revolution Radio 15 years ago or more,
I started telling people, start reading terms and
services of anything you sign up for and
everything.
And, you know, I was explaining to them
is where did you get that Greek?
It's in the terms and services.
So, you know, you got to read.
So unfortunately, I've read Twitter's services in terms
and legal and all that.
I've read Facebook.
There's no way I'm going to sign up
for that.
Right.
And we have you read what they're what?
Yeah.
What they're lauding over your head.
No way.
Some so no.
Some of them, they tell you all about
taking your data and all that.
And the worst, by the way, is the
YouTube community.
So don't even suggest that because that's why
I never went there.
Yeah.
Right.
And even worse than that is the comments
on YouTube.
Worse than the communities before they even built
the communities.
The comments showed you what the communities are
going to look like.
So no, I can't read comments, but fortunately,
we have a pretty good group comment situation
with Chitango.
Like they're pretty cogent to the subject and
fairly well, let's say, educated.
Right.
So it's it's linear and it's a fairly
decent except for that one porn poster.
But but then again, look, you open up
your phone lines, you know, publicly on the
airwaves, you're going to get prank calls, too.
So, you know, it's just a way of
things.
There are clowns.
Yeah, that's fine.
I don't know, man, I'm putting the time
Greeks time is going towards developing projects, tech
projects, which include weather and biology.
And I give an example like today, it's
it's even it's like seven or eight ish
for me here.
And it's my day is at noontime.
Like in other words, I still got another
three or four hours of stuff to do
as if it was, you know, as if
daylights burning.
Right.
And it's not because I don't have time.
This is where I want to dedicate my
time.
There's a difference, right?
You know, people say, I don't have time
for that.
Well, all you have is time.
So manage it.
Parcel it out.
Put your time where, you know, when someone
tells you, I don't have time means it's
just not important.
Just like when someone says, I can't afford
that, you can afford anything.
You can you can afford a billion, a
billion dollar yacht.
If you know how to work the credit
system, it's all everything's affordable.
It's what you want to afford, because if
you get that 200 mile an hour Ferrari
or that billion dollar yacht, once you got
it, can you can you keep it?
Do you know what kind of uptake it
keeps?
Right.
So same with the forums and all that
stuff.
They do need maintenance.
They do need adult supervision to a degree.
And they do need input.
Right.
Last thing you want is, you know, I
went over that forum.
There's nothing really there, you know.
So you want to kind of keep it
interesting, but it needs to be supervised and
all that.
Someone wants to take that on.
That's fine.
Right.
I'm not.
I elect not to put my energy there.
The most I elect to do is to
is to show up and do these Sonics
and keep that going for whoever is interested
in it, because I know it's helped quite
a few people because I do get not
often, but I have gotten a 24 page
email.
Right.
I don't know how many words that would
be.
I get 10 page emails and I do
read them.
Some messages when I'm busy or too long,
I'll just say I'll have to go back
and I see I acknowledge that I got
it now.
I'll read it again and comment later and
it might be two months before I comment.
And I've had at least 100 people since
I've been doing Sonics say that it's changed
their entire life.
Right.
For the better.
I really haven't anyone say it's changed their
life for the worst.
By the way, if if this Greek stuff,
diatribe stuff that we talk about and before
has made your life worse, let me know
because it's you're right.
I'm not saying difficult.
Yeah, we'll be more difficult, but better qualitatively
and quantitatively in many ways also.
Yeah.
So I think that's worth doing.
Right.
I think, in other words, keep keep going
on.
And as new people come on, we don't
have a good historical category where they can
go back and listen to, quote unquote, health
or fitness and or tech stuff or like
some people interested in the water.
Where do I find about the scale or
eight or tech?
Right.
We don't have categories like that.
So when there's new enough new people, I
kind of have to start over at square
one.
Right.
Well, kind of.
But then again, there is somebody working on
a transcript of every single one of these,
in which case you could make it.
So and that could be something uploaded to
a form.
But, you know, these forms require administrators and
even Bashir's has people administer, you know, take
care of the commentary.
He's got a whole thing.
He's got a whole thing going.
He's got an entire year.
He calls it the archaic empire.
And he and I, I'm not a social
person like that.
I'm very social on the engineering tech stuff.
Like I said, I want to advance certain
things to help whoever wants to use it.
But my thing is not sitting in front
of the computer and writing papers or books.
Right.
But that's another thing.
Yeah.
The final write a book.
I'll never do that.
Exactly.
The final thought here, though, just I want
to get this across is that I think
very much in the spirit of everything that's
been done on Rated Y is, you know
what?
If you see something that doesn't exist that
you think should, why not build it yourself
and make it happen?
Because isn't that the way of things here?
Look, you need to get something done, figure
out how to do it and do it.
I mean, is that not really one of
the general through lines here that we see
throughout all these Sonics is that, you know
what, if it's not there, make it be
there.
Create it.
Well, yeah.
One of the things that somebody asked me
before, Harry, if you're listening, how are you
doing pretty well?
He said, so what do you want to
do, really?
What do you want to do in life?
It's about a year ago.
And I said, you know, I really want
to help mentor young people because they're not
getting it from their parents or not getting
it from school.
Like, you know, when you sign an application
to go to college, that application actually paid
for the tuition.
Then they ask you to pay for it
again.
Any application, how the human body really works,
biology, how it works, weather, work, water, work,
just you want to talk about ancient texts
like the religious texts, just the basics, you
know, just the basic, basic fundamentals.
They're not getting it from anyone.
And I know there's still a communication issue.
Years ago, I laid into the Skype group
was 15, 20, 30 people.
I laid into them.
I said, shame on you guys not networking,
because I remember back in the day, being
on the East Coast, NYC, Park Slope, Brooklyn
and all that.
You run into people on the sidewalk, having
a conversation and you're with someone that they,
you know, you introduce them to someone else,
you know, for the first time.
And then you come to find out a
month later, they got together.
And then, you know, one guy does this,
the other guy does that complimentary.
You know, he met his sister, got married,
whatever.
And he's like, wow, this is great.
When you introduce people to each other, they
network.
They, you know, it's not just a shallow,
you know, greeting.
You know, you say, hey, what are you
guys doing?
You know, what can I do to help?
You know, you know, you know the Greek.
Hey, I know the Greek, too.
OK, why do this?
You do that.
OK, good.
You know, whatever.
Like some real simple would be the guy
had a pizzeria.
I introduced him to someone that I knew
who was an AC guy, gave him his
card.
A week later, the AC wasn't working in
the pizzeria.
Guess who he called?
The guy introduced him to.
Right.
Fixed his AC.
And I found this going on constantly.
It's like matchmaking and all that.
And I get on the Internet and you've
got audiences of, I don't know, half a
dozen people to 50 people.
And no one is.
What do you call it?
Networking.
What else would you say?
You know, I mean, they're not getting together
and doing anything, even regionally.
I remember we have people on Skype and
regionally like four or five of them were
in the L.A. area and not even
it's like, damn, man.
What?
Where are you?
You know, get together, you know, even if
you're not like exchange ideas.
Like, what do you do?
You know, what is what I do?
Hey, go work with it.
You know what I mean?
That's what a real community does.
And I was shocked.
I think it's an Internet phenomenon.
Maybe, maybe not.
But I remember again being in back in
New York City, you know, when I over
the years introducing people come to find out
they worked with each other or did, you
know, exchange.
It wasn't more just, you know.
Right.
You know what I'm talking about, right?
So look, I don't see that happening.
No, that's that is the trouble here.
Look, you have every opportunity to build a
community.
It's kind of a natural thing that you
can do where you, yeah, begin to interact
with people.
OK, we both see something the same way.
I mean, it's like meeting somebody at a
baseball game or something stupid because, look, you
both enjoyed baseball now build and you can
build.
Oh, well, this is more.
Yeah, this is more than that, because they're
being introduced to coming to a common thing.
But here's the thing.
Maybe that's the natural way of things.
Maybe the Internet, the cyber thing or whatever
is unnatural.
It's so unnatural that people just don't do
that.
You know, once the terminal or whatever device
they're using is is off or they're away
from it, everything that went transpired on it
is forgotten.
I don't know.
I just found it to be a very
frustrating phenomenon.
Right.
But there's nothing.
There's nothing stopping that.
That's my main point.
Yeah, there's nothing stopping people from interacting with
one another, though.
And look, the community, the community thing on
Patreon.
Look, build, build this other thing and show
me another community that we could build that'll
be better.
That's fine.
You know what?
Yeah.
Now, as a as a rebuttal.
But as a rebuttal to what I said,
I've recently come to find out by just,
you know, not tapping into it, but just
hearing crosstalk in the past year or so,
a lot more people have, especially from the
older Skype groups from 10 years ago, whatever,
till recently, the more people are getting to
know each other.
So I'm taking a little bit of it
back because I'm finding out behind the scenes.
There's a lot more networking, you know, people
that have come to the rated Y are
networking more than ever before, which is good.
But initially, my I was in shock years
ago when I found out that was.
I don't know.
I just like to see people benefit from
the meeting.