Rated Y, number 95, and here we are, Greek, how are you doing?
Oh, I'm doing, doing as I'm swallowing a big gulp of coffee and lit a cigarette, yeah.
Usually I'm better at that timing, I usually know and give you a minute to breathe before
I ask you a question, but that was a bad timing on my part.
No, it's fine, I got caught out here with Daylight Savings, which I kind of knew,
someone asked me to meet them on Skype the other day, and they gave me the time,
and I looked at the time on the Pacific coast, and it was the same as Tucson, so
I was like, oh, okay, it's happened already. I once missed a bus trip
because of the Daylight Savings. Sunday morning, we were supposed to meet up,
go somewhere, and I go there, and no one was there, and it was back in the days of payphones,
and I was like, I only have one phone number, but that person is not the one to call,
so the person I needed to call, I didn't have, and I was looking for a payphone,
and I asked around for the bus. I didn't ask around for the bus, I was just wondering why
they weren't there, and then I asked around for the bus, and they're like, oh, that left an hour
15, 20 minutes ago. I was like, what? How is that possible? And that woke me up that changing time
and people's perception of time is a big deal, right? You can really miss the bus, right?
No, fair enough, and it's an odd thing, too, because Arizona, I think, is still the only
place where they don't change the clocks, even though they constantly...
Arkansas.
Oh, Arkansas, too?
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
This last time I checked, yeah, it's wartime. Basically, this was done World War I and then
definitely in World War II to increase productivity and delay, because most raids,
aerial raids, would be done at night, right?
Right, right.
So they increased productivity to keep people out more and walking home during daylight,
you know, because of the natural light, let's say, and it's called wartime, and it still is,
in effect. A lot of countries, just about all the Western, what they call them, allies had it,
and most of them stopped it after the war, but the Americans did not, because you're still at war,
legally. What's going on in the state that we're in with World War II is just cessation
of hostilities. Germany has an interim government. There was never a treaty with
the legitimate German government. They went into exile, right? So you can't have a treaty
if you can't find the people to have a treaty with, right?
No, that's for sure.
So they put an interim government in Germany. That's why one of the Olympic gold medalists
from Germany, he has a seed oil company, and whenever we talk about anything politically,
he says, I don't want to talk, we haven't had a government in 80 years, you know?
In other words, more educated people know this, kind of like Iraq. If you go to Iraq right now,
it's an interim government. The Iraqis don't have a government, it's an interim, you know,
puppet put in by the, right?
Yeah, it's been that way for quite a while. What was it, Afghanistan was the same up until
very recently.
Yeah, they got, yeah, the Taliban is not what, you know, we've been propagandized that they are.
But they are, they start, are an intelligence operation. And the Americans have an interim
government since March the 9th, 1933. So, you know, anyway, pretty interesting.
That's the receivership you talked about.
Yeah, yeah. And if you put in March the 9th, 1933, in a search, Google will provide you the,
it's just two paragraphs of the act that did that. And when you read it, it uses pretty simple
terms, but you got to find out what those terms mean. Right? So, you know, it's pretty interesting.
I mean, yeah, it's the credits. Yeah, well, you know, yeah, don't expect, I've heard someone
call the 20th century a stalled century. It's like the century where nothing really
was allowed to happen, right? Because when you stall something,
it implies that it's not functioning as it was intended, right? You turned, basically
turned it off, right?
Well, that's the funny part, because they will tell us that this was the time of change. This
was the time of upheaval. This was the time that the world wars happened. This was the time that,
et cetera, et cetera, right? I mean, the rise and fall of the communist block,
everything goes on during the 20th century. And what you're telling me is in reality,
nothing actually happened.
Yeah, well, no, nothing much happened in terms of what you would sum up for the total of
happening in a century. Anything scientifically, philosophically, medically, whatever,
was already known by the late 1890s, right? And it's kind of hard for people when you say, well,
we didn't have cell phones back then. Well, actually they did have wireless. But what I'm
seeing and anything that could be known was known, right? In terms of scientific, you know,
the people, when they talk about technology, they're really, they've been misguided by the
process of miniaturization, right? Everything that's in a cell phone was around back then
in principle, right? In principle, you know, micro semiconductors, you get it, micro,
you know, the average cell phone has 16 billion transistors in it, right?
You know, that's with a B might be more, some of them could be up in the in the 40 to 50 billion.
What I mean, we're back in the days, you would need a 10 story building that took up an entire
block, if you can use vacuum tubes for that, right, right. But the principle is exactly the
same. So in principle, but when you brought up the communist capitalist, you know, the main
difference with that, if you study, by the way, if you study communism, none of Lenin and Marx's
ideals, which is use that word where have ever been implemented, by the way, fully,
they just say they write, they just say that they do, right? I've always said that. And I've had
people argue with me where I say, Look, you know what, I've read their work, and it actually has
not been implemented as described. So yeah, they just show you the planks of communism, which is a
derivation. And I said, Lenin, I didn't mean Lenin, I meant Marx and Engel. I liked Engel a
lot more. But the whole idea with communism was that each area based on its geography and culture
would be optimized, and there's no central government, right. But they do have a central
central government with centralized power, they still have a central government, but not
the power is not centralized. So the same thing here, like the United States of Mexico, you know,
Mexico is also United States, right? They just people don't call it that they just call it
Mexico. But politically, it's the United States of Mexico, right? I think that 28 or 26 states,
America is 5051. Maybe if you count a few other places, but their territories, territories,
which is not part of this country, but I wanted to just harken on something that people do,
you know, how do you define the difference between capitalism and communism? Well,
when it comes to the country, the I've defined capitalism before capitalism is just when you
when you can't acquire something, or if you have acquired it and stop using it, you destroy it. So
no one else can use it. That's capitalism. But But the difference between capitalism and communism
is very simple. Once you study what was implemented, it's very simple. And capitalism
you can make fun of the national leader, but you can't make fun of your boss.
And communism, you can make fun of your boss, but you can't make fun of the national leader.
Right? Okay, you get it is a big difference. So you know, everyone can make fun of the like,
no one's ever been arrested for, you know, saying they hate the President, right? No one. No,
no, we're not talking about, you know, whatever else assassination threats and threats and
intimidation. But if you said something like that, in communism, you're immediately, you know,
they sent you to Siberia, let's say, no questions asked, where, you know, you know, the United
States, by the way, since we're going back and forth, or in China, a couple years ago,
they sent people to prison for comparing, what was it using ping to Winnie the Pooh, right? Sure.
Or sitting on miles picture, right? Back in the days. Yeah, they're very much similar to that,
because the same people had set up. So right. So So the difference here is that in America,
if you speak bad about your boss, you're in trouble, you can speak bad about the national
leader. But in communism, you could speak bad about your boss, right there, where you work,
and they wouldn't have any effect. But I mentioned Siberia, as a place of retribution,
in the Soviet Union. We have one here, too, in the US, you want to guess where it is?
It's in the US, not Alaska. It's not has nothing to do with North.
No, it's got nothing to do with colder North, right? What is it? Where is it?
It's in Kansas City, Missouri, is the Siberia. And from a corporate perspective, if you if there's
if there's a corporation that has an office, or an adjunct or an annex in Kansas City, Missouri,
and they don't like you, that's where they send you. Anyway, it's I've heard this over and over.
This is from the I used to hang out with industrialists. I don't know if that makes
any sense. They have their own years ago. I sense of humor. I thought they sent you to Scottsdale.
That that's that's probably an annex to Yeah, very much so. Okay, which is which they're trying
to turn. I heard there's going to do is an I 10 that goes to the east west major thoroughfare down
here in the southwest. So it goes all the East Coast. Yeah, they're gonna do an I 11. And they
basically want to turn southern Arizona, you know, between Phoenix, Scottsdale and Tucson into
another like Orange County, California. All these places that are, you know, you could have bought
40 acres for $5,000 are going for a million dollars now. Yeah, so yeah, it's interesting.
Well, you know, there's a big exodus from there. But anyway, all these things that are changing
are not really changing much. It's very easy to predict, you know, politically, socioeconomically,
and all this other stuff. If you just look at, you know, what's been served up versus what you're
being told, what's being served up is right, right, right. Well, it's weird. You know, I was
looking at the trend. You mentioned the trend of people leaving California. Actually, I read
recently that they're now returning, because they want somebody because they're reactionary, right?
The reactionary responses. Yeah, they react. Yeah. That's why I recently got an email, which
was followed up again, I need to check it out a new person in the mix. And they basically stated,
they heard Greek speak on a podcast, they didn't say which, but they were listening to various
things on the internet. But when they heard the Greek speak, they're like, you're the only one
that's not really just reflecting mainstream occurrences. Like all the alternative media
just keeps referring to the flavor of the week, let's say. Well, that's the thing is they go,
Oh, what is the main almost every single one of them? What is the mainstream doing? You know,
and it's like, if you're basing it off of their information, and you're calling them out as a
liar, okay, but you're still starting with their starting point. So you're letting them dictate
the beginning of your script. I've never understood that. And it's all confusion. And you know,
no matter how true they try to be in the mainstream, it's always going to be false,
because they're not filling in the history that changed that perception. You see?
Of course, like, yeah, yeah, like, recently, I've been watching a lot of the stuff comes up,
I'm looking up, I'm making these molds, right. And to cast certain things, you know, it's still
water related. But in other words, I, you know, there's the device that I make, and then I need
to make tools to make the device. So it's consistent. So I do some reference, you know,
like specific materials and things like that. And then they'll, the the algorithms like this guy,
maybe he's trying to start a business, right? So they start giving me all these business YouTubes,
I put a couple on there's this chick, Claire Sanchez or something like that. She's like,
in her 30s. And she's telling everyone, you know, fuck Walmart, fuck Starbucks,
we need corner stores, start buying businesses, open small businesses kind of thing, right?
Okay. But she has no idea how fiat currency runs. She has no idea what taxes really are. It's
there's no text, there's no taxes. How can you tax when there's no money, it's basically a return,
right? It's in other words, the public money is in is private property. That makes any sense,
right? And that whenever you use private property, you have to go on conditions that they set up,
right? Just like if you go over at the tool, like you've given the same analogy,
you bring it back to the rental shop, you leave it and you wave goodbye. No, you have to pay a fee.
And if you don't, you know, they basically come after you as a form of theft, right?
Right. That's exactly what they're calling these. And these taxation agencies are not
even governmental, their franchises of another, right, but they're in partnership with the
government. Okay, here's an example. If you work for the CIA, this is a fact or the Department of
Agriculture, any of the agencies, how many there are like 170 of them, right? But there's like
10 major ones, right? You know, FDA, Department of Agriculture, Department of Energy. By the way,
Department of Energy is the one that runs shit, by the way. Okay, you can go on government property.
And they have signs, you know, like Area 51, you can get shot, whatever. If you go on Department
of Energy property, they shoot you and then get show you the sign. It's they're very, very serious.
Right. In other words, like when you talk, this is out of tangent. But when you talk about 911,
Department of Energy had to okay the trigger devices, right? Because the devices don't
have triggers built in. It's kind of like you have guns, but no bullets, right? Right. Okay.
Yeah. So they so when when when a certain nuclear demolition is approved,
through the Department of Energy, and you know, a small group or whatever, you know, back and forth,
they provide the trigger device. And basically, the device looks like an eight foot fire
extinguisher has an access panel and you install the trigger device and it runs a rudimentary How
do I know all this stuff? Anyway, anyway? I wonder if anyone's asking that question,
because I won't tell. But yeah, so they run a rudimentary startup thing. And it lets you know
if it'll work without, you know, anyway. Now, when the Department of Energy sends the trigger devices
to these nukes, they don't call a courier and they don't have someone in house, they call the OST,
which is the Office of Special Transportation. You might have seen something like that in some
of the movies, Close Encounters of the Third Kind, where they want to transport things and
they put like a McDonald's as a trailer. And it says McDonald's on the side or Piggly Wiggly or,
or, you know, Target, you know, right. So they Yeah, so they're on the film. Yeah. You By the
way, if you know what to look for, if you're on the highway, you can tell if it's an OST
transport or a real McDonald's truck full of buns, but I won't get into that. Okay. Yeah. And you
think about it, because someone if someone finds out and they want to, let's say take that McDonald's
truck, because it has nukes inside of it, they have to be able to protect it. Right. So when you
look at some of these trucks on the highway, I've spent a lot of time, you'll see some of them look
like normal trucks, but they're extremely unusual. Things built into it that it looks like you can
hit it with a tank round and it would survive, right? So anyway, so why wasn't all this alternative
media? Why didn't they say anything about Department of Energy, the Port Authority and the
OST, Office of Special Transportation, which, by the way, is a part of the Secret Service?
Oh, boy, I can keep going. You know, why? Because none of this is mentioned ever. Okay. But you
could everything I said you could look up. Pretty much as time goes on, you it'll be harder and
harder. But let me go back to these agencies. If you work for the CIA, and you're going to be,
let's say doing something with the Department of Agriculture or the FBI or the executive
office of the President, when you start filling out paperwork, you know, to start whatever they
requested, you know, that agency goes under a heading as a customer. Right? Yeah. So when you're
Yeah. So when let's say Department of Agriculture, let's say the FDA wants to investigate someone,
and they call the FBI, right? That's pretty normal, right? FBI raids.
So the FDA wants an investigation, they call an investigative agency, the FBI. Okay,
yeah. Now, when the FBI starts filling out the paperwork, the paperwork clearly states who's
the customer. And they write FDA. So in other words, all the agencies are viewing anyone that
any action they do as a customer, who's the principal, who's issuing this request? Who is
this action for? It's not like agency or government authority or order its customer? What does that
tell you who has customers businesses? Right? Do you get this? And you right? Give me an example.
The IRS has like 100,000 plus people on payroll. This was true up until the early 2000s, right?
They couldn't do payroll for their own people. Oh, well, they didn't they had the Department of
Agriculture do the payroll for the IRS employees. And someone asked internally, why is the Department
of Agriculture doing payroll for the IRS and the IRS head honchos in the admin group said because
they have better bookkeeping than we do. I'm serious. You can't make this stuff up. No,
that's hilarious. But yeah, it is because the IRS is not based on but it's based on legal
presumption to send you a bill. For example, like, I know someone that they did some stuff
and say, all right, so you owe us $1,500 from 10 years ago or whatever. Right? Because it's a 10
year limitation, by the way, for them to class. So she sent them a check for 1500. Three months
later, he gets another bill for 1500. And why am I getting on the bill? Oh, this bill is for
processing the 1500 that you sent before. And then while he's arguing that he gets another $500 a
day, it just never ends because there's nothing to do with what you think it is.
Right? You're the one people if you can, if you're a living, breathing soul,
with blood running through you, and you have a pen, you have unlimited credit, there's unlimited
credit. They don't none of the agencies, you know, the corporation, they can't let you know that you
do so they want to get as much out of you as possible. And they don't need to, by the way,
when you write them a check, you don't need to have the money in the bank, they could just use
the signature off of your thing, but your bank will complain and they'll still complain to make
it look like you know, you didn't do the right thing, right? That's why they when you look to go
to certain shops, you turn your Attorney General says prosecutes bad check writers. Yes, you've
seen those signs. There's no such thing. They can't say they cannot use legal terminology.
They cannot they have to use what they call common parlance. Because in legal terminology,
in Title 12, I think it's 95, or 95 B. No, not 95. It's just prior to it might be 92. It states that
there's nothing anyone could write that can be held against them in a financial instrument. So
basically, you could write a million dollars on a piece of paper and sign your name and have
someone else sign it, you should literally go to the Treasury window, it'll be good.
Right? This is in the codes. But you can't let people know this, because suddenly, what will
happen? Right? Everybody will show up signing a paper. And yeah, yeah, they'll say, screw you.
Why do you leave the door open with the heat on and the water running all day? Screw you.
Right? You see, this is because Yeah, so I'm not blaming the agencies or the attorneys or
everything. They are scumbags. But but the blame is not on them. You know, news and mainstream media,
who do we blame? Right? It's the people. You know, the people need to write be more.
I don't know how you'd say it. They're basically savages that need to be
monitored. And yes, monitored and managed. Who is it Nietzsche that said the common man is best?
These aren't the right. But these aren't really the right people to be monitoring and managing,
though, are they? I mean, or are they? But here's the thing, like someone says, Oh, he's a good
doctor. So what do you mean? He's from Jupiter? What planet is he from? Like, you know, if you
say someone is a doctor, well, how did they become a doctor? There's a school requirement.
Go look at the school that he went to and go look at the syllabus and the curriculum that he was
trained under. Is that syllabus or curriculum reflect what he's supposed to be doing? No,
it doesn't usually know, right? No, it doesn't teach. Right. So what's going? So I mean,
there's so much to collect on what's going on here to piece it together. But you know,
one thing that I'm proud of is, I'm able to do okay, I've spent countless of for not countless,
because it's limited, but many, many, many, many hundreds, if not 1000s of hours doing a lot of
boring, really boring, dull drum footwork to present what I've talked about. Okay, right.
So when I say that, you know, all this stuff that they don't know what they're talking about,
I didn't read it in some book somewhere directly that what I did is I started going through
everything that they're supposed to be doing and everything that's written that they're supposed to
know, and it doesn't correspond. So but I said, Why isn't anyone talking about this? Right?
No one's talking about any of this stuff. So like, Oh, my gosh, I mean, I'm the one that's
gonna have to start talking about it. Yeah. Yeah. Well, because it seems to me as though
people just react based on their feelings. They don't bother to find out how anything works.
No, I agree. They just look the people that they trust, who's the authority that's supposed to know
are not doing their job either. So it has to be right. So it's, it's all about trust. Look here.
Let's see who's more to blame. Look, if you put an idiot in charge of things,
and it doesn't go well, you know, who's more to blame the idiot or you put the idea,
but they're not in charge. It's just a puppet show. Because very clearly, we know that
all the you know, the script, basically, who's writing the script, it's not the actor.
Yeah, they're just they're called actors anyway. But But here's the thing. Yeah. When you
when you look at the situation, and what's going on, and what's available to people,
you know, and they're not and they don't go right. So let me give you an example.
This, I've heard this indirectly a couple of times already with medicines, especially with
the vaccines recently, that killed all these people, supposedly, or they're still sick from it.
The answer now that's being given is, well, no one forced you to take it.
No, no, I'm serious. But they did. But they someone says, well,
right, so the coercion, what is it? Yeah, but right. So yeah, it's it's not.
Yeah. But see, you're not gonna have a job. But see, you're not going to be allowed to go to
school. But see, we'll put you in jail. Send your kids to school. No, but you know what I'm saying
is that all these preconditions, then the intimidation comes in, we're going to take
all these things away, right? That's right. But if you're weak enough, right? Like, here's the
thing. This is what I say. You know, you've heard about people taking advantage of others, you know,
or could by controlling them and whatever, people that are easy to take advantage of are not worth
taking advantage of. You get it. But here's the problem. If someone is so weak that they
can be manipulated, those people are not worth manipulating, because they got nothing off. Or what
could they possibly do? Well, then next week, that week, you know, the only good for your skin,
right? Well, I got you. But explain to me the world around me, then, because all I see are people
that are really, you know, not worthy. Much higher. We've got into that. That's the cosmic
censorship. That's the much higher realm. Let's say, oh, the how would you say a blanket statement
would not cover that, right? Because as you go higher, it gets more dense. And the more dense it
gets, the more simple these principles get. And then when you go down, they seem to disperse and
become more complicated. But essentially, the human perspective is basically how it's raised. It's
based on its culture, not not on the individual, not on the Jack Fresco has gone into this a lot,
there's no human nature, it's human culture, you know, what, what upbringing you have,
it's not specific to, and I've gone into it a lot with the, we don't come with a pre downloaded
operating system, right? You know, reiterate, yeah, no puppy dog, a puppy dog raised by gorillas
will always act like a puppy, like a normal dog at adulthood, but a human raised by gorillas will
act like a gorilla when it's an adult. Right, right. No, true. And that's, that's no question.
I mean, there's no doubt about that. Right. And look, frescoes most interesting in that he takes
a step back, and kind of says, Look, in perspective, what is all this crap worth? You know,
all of this? I mean, what is the famous line? Yeah, he got really? Yeah, but go ahead. All this
shit has to go. You know, yeah, I like that. I love that. But he doesn't have a vibe. His viable
replacement was these concrete centralized cities where everything was very efficient,
and organic looking, let's say, but he didn't give too much of a structure for the raising of a
individual, right, let's say, or the collective, because the collective and the individual are the
same, right? Well, no, you pull an individual out of a collective, they still reflect, right,
you can take the man out of the street, you can take the street out of the man, and whatever,
whatever, I get that man out of Jersey, but you can't take Jersey out of the man.
Fair enough. But what I'm saying is, it was an interesting perspective to me, because
look, you take away all those things that are major struggles, right? You take away,
you don't have to go ahead and struggle or do a job or do this or do that, because
there are a bunch of self sufficient mechanisms that are available to the community. Now,
if you do that, then what do you have left, you have the ability to expand, why not learn a craft?
Why not develop those things that could be part of the culture, as opposed to wasting your time in
a bunch of repetitious action to collect the fiat currency? It's not a waste of time. Here,
like, to give you a perspective, sometimes you hear people, you know, in a relationship for a
few years or many years, and when they decide to separate, they'll say, well, I wasted 10 years
with you or whatever. No, because was the years before you met that person wasted? Right? You see,
what's waste? You know, what does that mean? What's lost? Like, I lost this time with you.
Okay, so what about the time before you even started? What was that lost to?
Where does it add up? Where does it lead to? Where is it? It doesn't.
From that perspective, you must go to a higher perspective to see what's going on.
In defense of that, right? I think it comes from the idea that, look, I invested this amount of
time, I invested this amount of energy. And here's what I feel like I got back out of it.
I think they're looking at it as a transactional. Sure. But again, it's cultural. It's cultural,
right? Because from, again, the culture on the ground boots on there. But if you go to a higher
perspective, you see above the culture and you see that how many times have you heard like,
well, it's meant to be right. And I've had a lot of meant to be moments where, you know,
like, for example, just something simple as what's called driving, someone cuts me off,
I couldn't go into the lane that I wanted to go into. And I'm like, shit, you know,
I got to go around, you know, another block now and make a U-turn. Well, when I'm sitting there
saying shit, you know, that guy cut me off, I didn't make it to the lane. I hear a loud boom,
man, if someone was not paying attention on their cell phone rear ended the car
that was supposed to be me. And I'm like, Oh, that wasn't so bad that getting cut off
you see what I mean? Well, and that's always another perspective there. When you're talking
about somebody says they wasted 10 years, it could be that they were with that person. So
they avoided something else because they were tied up with that person, as opposed to getting involved
with, you know, the person that's going to cut them up into dog food and feed them to another
victim in a basement somewhere. I mean, you know, by the way, I'm tired of hearing you hear about,
you know, the guy chops up his girlfriend, right? Yeah. Oh, he's an evil guy. Or and then you got
the other one where the woman cuts off her husband's dick, right? Oh, she's bad. No, no,
you got to look at the other side, what would have driven even if the person's unstable,
another person to the point where they have to chop up their spouse or girlfriend or mate,
or cut their dick away. You know, everyone always goes to the automatic simply like the victim,
right? All the victims, right? Whoever did it is wrong. What no one ever starts and thinks like,
wait a second, let's look at it from the other perspective. What kind of a rotten ass
would have drove driven another person to do that today?
Look, you know what? You know why I'm laughing? Because I've never heard you say this before.
And I think you and I are the only two people that I have ever heard articulate something like this.
I swear to you, this is exactly what I think about. There was a story recently that I was
reading about and somebody I don't know why people sent it to me repeatedly. And this woman cut off
her boyfriend's head, okay, and stuck it in a bucket and put it in the bottom of the steps
for his mother. I guess the two of them were living like in the upstairs.
Oh my gosh. Yeah, but since the detail, it sounds like the guy in New York had cut off
girlfriend's head and even cooked it and served it to the homeless in Thompson Square Park. It
goes on and on and on. Or there was the guy who was walking around Penn Station,
just carrying his girlfriend's head. I don't know if you remember that one from.
Yeah, that's right. And but but this is very not not to not to mix this up with serial killers,
which are military operations, by the way. Oh, absolutely. But no, I also real killers that
you've been made aware of, even the Russian one who did like 300 people is part of the military.
There's active military while they were doing it under orders. Right. So anyway, no, no. And you
know, that guy that was walking around Penn Station with his girlfriend's head. I missed
that guy by 10 minutes, literally. No, I got you. But what I'm saying here is the victim.
So everyone's like, oh, if she cut off his dick, she's terrible. Well, what drove? No,
I think the guy, the person who got their dick cut off must have been worse because what would
have driven even someone who was even considered unstable to that point to do that, because
humans are not really like that without even a judgment. I don't even try and go for the
judgment part of it. But no one's ever even looking. No. But when you're saying, oh,
they must be terrible and forget that. I ask the open question. What in the hell
got to a certain point here, regardless of if they're out of there? Like I'm asking the open
question, what actually inspired that? You know, that's right. Well, I can tell you very simply,
it was constant and very high level, whatever to get that, you know. So right. So the guy
cut the girlfriend's head off. She must have been really horrible because, you know,
then I heard of bad things happen to good people. But, you know, something that extreme. And just
what was the famous one where she used Bobbitt? Yeah. Yeah. He got a silicone penis and it was
all famous and all that. John Wayne. But I think he actually got it reattached and then did porno
movies afterwards, if I remember. Oh, my gosh. Or whatever. Yeah. So, yeah. But, you know, it's
yeah. That was the only one that I've seen where the sympathy didn't go extreme in either direction.
No, it was kind of weird because it was Lorraine Bobbitt on the other side. And what came out is
like, well, he was beating her and he was doing this and he was doing that. And then she was
right. Exactly. That's the point, you know. But this is very different from what you hear of
put out there. But this is OK without belaboring it anymore. This is the culture. Again, no one
is examining anything. So once it's examined, opinion aside, you'll be able to see a little
better until people are able to see things aren't going to change. But fortunately, we don't have a
lot of time. So.