Rated Y Sonic event 126 or 126 however it is you want to count it here it is and it's
a happening. Greek, how are you? Hey, I'm you. You're me. Now that's kind of a male sheep
right? Is it you? Oh, no. Wait. Yeah. Is it you? I knew it was you. Yeah. What is a ute?
They said in the movie Cousin Vinny, my cousin Vinny, right? Okay. Anyway, did you say you
eat? What is a you? What is it? Center? Are you? Yeah, I like that. Because I came from
that sort. But my cousin, it's Jersey. That's not Brooklyn. Jersey. Yeah, but I don't know.
That's not really they don't really talk like more Brooklyn than Jersey, though. He mixed
it up. It was all a mix of like, you know, New York, New Jersey and some other gutter
mix. I mean, some Philly, Philly. That's what it is. You're right. Okay. So tri state area
gutter talk. Yeah. Yeah. Vernacular. And of course, a little bit of Italian stereotyping
or not really Italian stereotyping, but Guido stereotyping, because there is a difference.
Anyway, forget about all that, because you could hear that kind of thing. Well, almost
anywhere. Let's talk about some messages we've gotten recently from rated Y listeners. Okay.
So I got somebody who basically gives a whole long wind up about how he's surrounded by
people that are, you know, very Baptist and religious, and he finds himself coming to Greek
speak and a few other things. It's taken him a couple of years, but he's been listening
to come around to some of these ideas. Right. Because he's steeped in Baptist stuff. And
his friends, his brother, I think girlfriend, too, but he didn't want to admit to it. Altogether
seem to have this idea that there's really a black and white world. It's either things
are godly and good. They're just godly or they're the work of the devil. There's no
in between. Okay, no, that's that's a good way to carpetment called part of it. It's
a hard word for me to say. compartmentalize your lives. Yes. What you're striving for
when in reality, it's not give you an example. This is parallel analogy. So so this is aspirational
as opposed to descriptive about the world around you. Yeah. So here's a way to look
at it. So I'm many, I designed something and I decided I want to put it out in the world.
So I start manufacturing, I make them, I have some people help me make them very high
quality units. And we idealize we idealize the perfect unit that should be when it's
made to perfection. Will we will write so that means that everyone that we make will be exactly
the same and perfect. So it's functionality, it's appearance, everything. Everything will
be perfect, right? So okay, so just let me let me finish this point. Sure. So we're manufacturing
something and I have some helpers and we're working and we're created the perfect of who
this is what we think the perfect device is. Okay, so let me when we're done at the end
of the day, a week, month or year, if they were all perfect, they would all be identical
and they would have have a be without flaw on any level of scrutiny. Is that ever going
to happen? No. So what we do we strive for that? Yes. Right. So when you strive for a
black and white, yes or no, you know, just do just simple duality. That's, that's fine.
But you will find that you won't achieve it. Right? So it's kind of like the thing, if you're
going to go for 100%, the best you'll ever get is 95. Right? So if you want 99%, you have
to go for 150%. Right? If you want 99.9%, you got to go for 200%. It's a diminishing returns.
So what they're doing is they're getting diminishing returns. If they're looking back at
what they're doing, making a change or making any progress or, or, you know, anything like that. But
now this doesn't go for being Baptist or whatever, like this, you know, I understand that I know what
they talk about what they're into, right? But they still don't know. Okay, just all right. Now,
I hope you got that analogy, right? So it's fine to know this is good. And this is bad. And that's
fine. But you can't live that way. But you keep it as a, as a standard as a reference, right?
But reality can never be because it can never be exactly like that. Because no matter what you do,
and you know what, they always say accidents will happen. So even if you do everything, right,
something will be faulty at some point. Nobody is called tolerances. But again,
just to comment directly on the, on the, what would you call the, let's say the pedigree,
right, which would be Baptists, they are still deceived. So if you were to be
an ardent listener of Greek speak, you would know that very simply, the Baptists are works of the
devil. Very simple. So that kind of flushes out the whole thing. But within the Baptist sphere,
being within the understanding within the using what the through Baptist eyes or whatever eyes,
yes, it's fine to see as good and bad. This is the devil. This is not this. That's fine. But I'm
telling you, if he's an ardent, if you really know what's going on that clearly that baptism
is the work of the devil. Why? Very simple. They are also deceived by the counterfeit Christ.
They believe in a counterfeit Christ. They think he was crucified on a cross, Christmas, Easter,
the law has been done away with, right? So that's 100% work of the devil, right? So yeah, so,
so on one end, I was more addressing, is it all right to be black and white, good or bad? You
know, no, no leeway? Yeah, of course, because I do that when I make things. I want them to be perfect.
But are they perfect? No, but everyone else thinks they are. So that's good enough.
Same thing with baptism. Everyone thinks they're, everyone else thinks they're righteous or
whatever. It's good enough, but I'm telling you, it is demonic. So it's like Catholicism,
Protestantism and whatever Mormonism, they're all demonic. So it's okay to aspire to having
a circumstance where everything is, you need a reference, a base reference point to start your
life with. And it absolutely, there's clear cut, good and bad. Absolutely. But you see how I gave
you the one was the worm's eye view, then the airplane view, and now like, high up in space view,
when you go away, it's all demonic. Right? The people that know the real spiritual
characters, the ones that you depict in the Bible are on the run on the go, they don't talk about
it, in terms of, like, I talk about it, but I'm not gonna, I'm never gonna do a website on it.
Right? I'm never gonna go ahead and write a book about it. And I'm not going to write
someone, send someone, I've been on years ago, 20 years ago, or 10 years ago, 15 years ago,
call in on these calling groups, 70, 80, 100 people that capture their attention. I just
lead them into showing like, Hey, why are you doing this one? Right? And they all stop right
here. Stop right there. I before this guy continues speaking, I need for him to give me a letter of
faith, you know, like statement of faith, send me a statement of faith. And then I'll let you talk
here, you know, so they're like running administrative stuff, you know what I mean?
So and I can't even write a statement of faith, because they won't understand damn word in it.
Right. So. So when I say they're on the run, whoever knows, that's what I mean. They're not
literally on the run. But they're on the run from avoiding. Let's say, what would you do when you do
a form of public publishing, which is however you're going to publish,
you're doing websites publishing, putting these things down about the Bible that you hear in
Greek speak is a complete waste of time. So what you do is you do it in passing, like we do on
Sonics. And whoever's meant to hear it, hears it. And even further, whoever hears it, if it's
meant they can tell others and they can and so on and so on. And that's it. That's the maximum
within my discretionary ability, using whatever wisdom I have that anyone any of these things
should go. It's like the new whenever you hear about Christian, I think about 911. It's a perfect
example. It's exactly the same thing. Okay, what really happened on 911 was a nuclear demolition,
not like your day, right? Okay, so the underground boom reaction, everything turns to dust based on
the yield. You know, if it was half the yield, only like, you know, a third of the building would
have turned to dust and the other bit would have just fell on top of it. So right. So it's new.
It was 36 2600 degrees for three months underground, you know,
just for just FYI 2000 degrees melt steel 2150 depending on the hour, but around 2000 you'll
melt iron somewhere. So it was six or 700 degrees higher above the boiling point of
melting point of steel. Anyway, very simple. Alright, so you go ahead. Good luck doing a
loose change or Alex Jones or mass alternate me on that. First of all, I have people tell you nukes
don't even exist. Right? They don't as they as explained, you know, but no one's ever split an
atom. I can assure you for sure has nothing to do with splitting out. You see how waste of time you
can project with something's gonna be a waste of time or not, right? But you still put it out there
to the people like Dimitri Kalasov. I've had some really good. Well, one really good discussion
with him. He brought up some things he didn't bring up, but he never added them to his repertoire.
He doesn't have to because it's already a thing. But there's a lot of people talking about
alternative Christianity and all this stuff. So I'm telling you, they're all wrong. All of them.
So why just like with 911, all these alternative theories are all wrong. It's very simple.
What it was and it's textbook one on one. The biblical stuff and all the religions is biblical
one on one is real basic. It's it starts off and it ends off exactly the same way.
And there's no religion on the planet, or no Christian on the planet that knows what I'm
talking about, unless they, you know, break away. And there are, you know, and there are many that
do, but they don't talk about it. They're smart enough, right? No, just like that wave that book
around and they've never even read it. They have no concept. Yeah. And even though I knocked the
knock worthy, you'll see that there's no crucifixion, no matter how many times they
use the word crucifixion. So and on and on and on. So yeah, so B is Baptist, the same as Muslim is
the same as Catholic as the same variation. Yeah. And is it satanic or demonic? Absolutely.
Well, from a certain perspective, it's all just noise distracting you from the reality.
Yeah. And the reason if you want to discern anything, it's just like, especially Christians,
very simple. If they show you crucifix, they talk about Christmas. That's the imposter. It's 100%
the imposter. So the Satan put puts the Satan, the adversary puts the put something completely
false as you're chasing that. And you're done. Have a nice day. Well, that's one of the keys
in every single story that repeats as something about the adversary arriving and implementing
a plan. What do they always do? They claim to be an agent of peace, of goodness, right? And
denying the existence of the adversary, right? For themselves. Of course. Well, a thief would deny,
right? You know, someone gets caught stealing. Did you recall? You said, No, I didn't steal
denial. That's the legal thing to always deny. The legal thing is in denying and then intimidation.
So yeah, speaking of which, I'm getting some feedback from people dealing with attorneys
and how they get angry when you ask them questions about law, and how they come back and say,
No, that's not the law. And but if you ask them for the law, they don't know anything.
It's very typical, right? So Oh, by the way, the comp one of the common answers by your segue,
with the attorneys is very simple. When you start bringing up certain fundamentals of law,
which they cannot answer. They say, Well, I don't do that kind of law. I do this kind of law,
right? Or, or the another wiggle room is as if the laws in question, we have a jury trial,
those are the two answers they always always give is that because if they're part of some
pre recorded message, it's it's the funniest thing in the world.
It's funny, I love how the grand deception is always preceded by the you go to see the doctor,
you have to deal with law, you have to you know, the government,
grand deception, it's all deception, all of it. Well, what I think I brought up scale, you know,
yeah, the ancient Greeks believe we've already died in another world. And this is the in between
time here, this life here. Right? So you're already dead, as has been spoken of in many
ancient texts, the walking dead and whatever, you know, right? Yeah. Well, did you have another
question? Well, yeah, there was this other one. And let me let me just get to my reference here
to make sure I got it straight. Let's see. All right. You know, here's, let me boil it down real
quick. Okay, because again, it was a long convoluted, like, da, da, da, da, da, da.
Anyway, they're looking at Biden, and they're looking at him being dysfunctional. And they're
looking all around them and seeing other dysfunctional old people. And they're saying
Greek, is there a way a fit and proper spiritually, you know, according to the way things should go?
Shouldn't we, you know, do something with our elders? How do we treat those that have become
old and infirm? What is the fit and proper way to deal?
Well, I before we go, yeah, okay. But But you mentioned Biden twice there. So look,
sorry, keep bringing the pieces because Biden is not Biden is a clone. I think they're on like the
second or third one right now. Right? Really? Okay. Yeah. And then say, well, this is a clone.
And then another one will emerge. I'm not saying hack of pieces because of the
presidential whatever, I couldn't care when a clone is a clone is a clone. It's a copy.
So when you hack a clone to pieces, its consciousness gets transferred immediately back.
And they put it in another one or in the original body. The clone is doesn't have any
rightful ownership of the body. I don't believe that murder and all that other stuff and torture
applies to clones. Okay. Right. But the torture and the murder experience will,
will could damage the mental capacity of the one that's in it.
Well, it'll still get carried as an abortion argument, because you need an abortion argument.
Well, you need the spirit or whatever to animate Yeah, is it the original spirit,
then it would be just like hacking or killing the person. But clones are in my book,
if I were to start a religion or an abomination, when they're done secretly. Now you could do it
ritualistically, where we have someone that we need to keep around. And when everyone knows,
on this day, we're going to transfer him to his clone. And it's approved that you have a synthetic
human, right? But then the the original body, what happens to that? It's just a shell. No,
and then the spirit transfers over and then you're just as good as gold, you know,
if it's a good enough clone. Yeah, but once you buy it, and whether they're at least on the second,
more than the second, third or fourth one right now,
but once the original is gone, you can never redeem and replay it like you can never actually
restore then Kenya. You probably could you would use the same DNA to grow the clone.
cloning is a very simple process, folks. I'm not going to get into it. But there's secrets,
you need certain kinds of salts, and they're on the market. Should I should I disclose that? I
forgot what they're called. But I know I know how to find them. Go ahead and take up this time. I'm
going to research right now. Well, the reality, excuse me of salt and water, excuse me, seems
to be a constant, right? Where a lot of things and different types of salt. I got it. Good. They're
called cell salts, cell salts. Okay. Yeah, they're available. They're expensive as hell. Highlands
makes them. They're the homeopathic type salt. Those cell salts here, homeopathic cell salts.
They're started in Europe. I believe that they leaked out from the early
boys from Brazil. Right. Okay. Anyone? Okay. Yeah. Yeah. And of course, I don't sell salt.
All right. Okay. That's that's what you need. And you need a certain kind of water. So I wouldn't
you would have to use spring water. You know, you wouldn't you wouldn't want to go.
If you got distilled water, you have to know what it was distilled from.
Right. You know, you would use spring water. You don't want to just source straight from tap. Yeah.
Right. But you could if the tap was from a spring, but it's tortured already.
Speaking of which, let's bounce around here. I got a message today is the follow up six
month on a scalarator plus. Okay. Six months plus. Victoria White is her name. And I'll mention her
name because she's a public person. She has a Web site. It's called Structured Air and Water
dot com. I think. All right. Victoria White. She's outside of Tucson. She got she has a
scalarator and I could read it's a long text. Why don't I just read the message?
It tends to have better so I could get it on a stupid rectangle. Sure. Why not? I mean,
if you can, you know, if it's OK to disclose, why not just relate it? Yeah. She's a public
shows a Web site about water. So, OK, might as well. It would be seen as a promotion.
Right. All right. So good to hear from you. Let's see where I'm at. Oh, my gosh. Because
I'm thinking it's salt, you know, back to the salt. OK, here we go. Yeah. Cell salts would
be C.E.L.L. like like a cell. Yeah, right. Right. Got you. I think there's only. Yeah,
there's also S.E.L., which is in commerce, but no cell salts. Right. So there you go.
Cell salts. And then you need to move it. Oscillates. OK. Anyway, here's the Victoria
White. She has a Web site. I think it's called Structured Air and Water dot com or something.
OK. She has she pedals. She traffics mostly in the natural action technology guys. By the way,
everybody now that's left in natural action technology is just punching in and punching
out. They couldn't make these. I call them and I do mean it a little facetiously.
What's his name? Nolte, the guy who made these balls and all these balls.
OK. It's like golf balls in a PVC pipe, supposedly structures water. Nobody there.
If they're making that or golf club equipment or condoms or working in a tractor factory,
it doesn't matter. So Jonathan Butts, who was the leader there, passed away,
was the last person there knows anything about water. I'm not knocking natural action tech.
And if it sounds like I'm knocking them, maybe they deserve it. But I'm not. My intention is
not that I'm just telling you guys what's going on there, because if you call them with a question
about water, they're going to tell you to go watch videos because they don't know anything.
But she traffics mostly in their stuff. Structured Water and Air, by the way,
does have a Web site, Structured Water and Air dot com. Is that is this the one? Let's see.
Victoria White. Yeah, it's kind of a blue background, Tucson. It's the
address is Tucson, Arizona. It's more close, closer to Ohio, Arizona. But
so here's our message. Sure. We also recently had a little talk about animals in the Garden of Eden,
you know, turning into a food forest now. But OK. Yes. Right. We also recently had our well
die. It was in the ground almost 20 years, so it was ready to be replaced. When they pulled it out,
they commented on what exceptional water we have, unlike other wells they have seen in the area.
And that pump still looks shiny and brand new. No buildup on it at all. It hadn't been if it
hadn't been for freezing up. You would think it was new, meaning the motor stopped working.
Sure. I'm wondering if our structured water may have been trained all the way back to the
source. Interesting, given the fact that this was a family business and decades of working on wells
in the Tucson area. We're so blessed to not have a scale problem like many others. I'm so grateful
to you. Thank you again. Wondering if the water had been trained all the way back to the source.
Water. That's well, that's what I mentioned with the scale orator works backwards and forward.
OK. Yeah. So, right. That's I mean, that's pretty. It's just like a power line. If it's on the ground,
it doesn't matter where you grab it. I got you. I'm just pointing to the word trained,
though. It's interesting because trained and trained and trained. OK. And trained means,
you know, infuse or whatever. So now this is a good six month testimonial because I did mention
to her. See if you can. If you were in contact with others that are from the same water source
and see if they're noticing a change. And she's never responded to that.
And the answer will probably be less or no. I mean, less or no. I mean, not that much information.
But I don't know if anybody is familiar with how well pumps work. You know,
they're submerged. You know, they're well pumps that are not submerged.
But any well pump, anything that's been in the ground for 20 years in water,
you pull it up and dry it out. It doesn't look very happy. It doesn't look like a clean machine.
Not at all. No. Yeah. This one looked like it was just in there for a week
and it was just burned out, meaning the froze, she said, meaning that the motor stopped. Right.
So it's working constantly because she has that. She's got four acres of apricot trees,
apple trees and all that other stuff, which I enjoyed quite a bit of apricots,
a few hundred apricots this year and all that. And but anyway, I just wanted to put that out
there because you just keep adding testimonials because this is new. I mean, it's not an airplane
where you have to fly it around for, what, four years before someone, you know, boards it as a
passenger. The sclerator has only been around for a year and two months. Right. Or three months.
So you're two months, let's say. So it's still very new. But the predictions that I made based
on the early observations are starting to hold hold true, which is pretty good. Pretty good.
So she's not offering the sclerator on our website or anything. No,
no one really is. And that's by my decision. Also, if someone said I want to do that, I said, no,
it's still too soon. I think I need to get even more. You really won't know until you get 100
units out. Right. Or so. But from the what can be surmised. So I just want to put that out there
because I did the seminar on the sclerator with over 40 people. And if you're still planning on
building them or whatever, I hope it just adds more confidence to what you in the mix,
let's say, you know, to what you're doing. So, you know, how would it work in a well?
Well, water and what would you expect? There you go. So, yeah, I just try to pull up some emails
and I just signed out so I could do that again. But basically the questions, one of them was
fellows name is an alternative guy talks about more gallons.
Oh, yeah, that that weird thing that looks like one of those creepy crawlies that flies down a
wall file for bio farming, archons and all that stuff. And I did watch a little bit of this stuff
once before. And this his name brought it up again. And I'll just tell you what very simply.
It's a Harold Cox Vela cut. That's where the k a u t z Vela transhumanism or gallons,
archons, quantum dots, AI, black magic, black goo, money, and healing for the love of truth.
What's his first name?
How Harold, Harold, all A's, Harold, all A's, couch Vela, B, L, L, A, and Harold is all A's,
a, h, a, r, a, l, d. I saw some of his stuff. He's seen his well intended. He's been
doing some a lot of public stuff for quite a while. But he thinks the body absorbs
things. So he doesn't show. Okay. I'm not saying he's on the wrong track. But I think his work
would be far more refined and far more accurate if he got some Greek speak, right?
And this guy's written a few books, right? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. He's been, you know,
it's the alternative, whatever. Yeah. Okay.
Well, no, what you'll do is you'll group all these topics that I just mentioned.
But if you have, if you have Greek speak under your belt, you'll be like, dude,
I like what you're saying, but you got to get to get, you got to look, you got a dozen points that
you need to revisit. So gotcha. It's not impeccable. No, I'm just looking at impeccable,
but valid topics, all of them. Right. And I'm just looking over his little Pinterest. Actually,
he's got a little Pinterest. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's just, there's no, yeah. Yeah. You know,
the whole thing about the relevance of caloric intake for food, the relevance of high blood
pressure, the relevance of blood, you know, there's no blood glucose or blood sugar level,
you know that, right. There's no such thing, you know, that's created by an algorithm.
Right. You don't have to mix your blood. Yeah. They make certain things in with the blood sample
and then they measure how much hydrogen peroxide is created in the blood. And that is an analog
for how much glucose is in your blood. Oh my gosh. Oh my gosh. Yeah. It's got nothing to do
with what you just added. Nothing to do with glucose. Yeah. They'll just make shit up. Like
my favorite one is AIDS auto immune, whatever deficient, what immune there is no,
I think Harold brought to the immune system. You know, there is no immune system, right?
When you ask these morons the doctors to explain the immune system and pretend you're taking notes,
have a notepad there. And when they go through everything in the immune system,
you make some points. So, so you just said it's elimination of this white blood cell elimination,
elimination of that elimination. Oh, so you're talking about the eliminated system. You still
haven't brought up any evidence of an immune system. It's all elimination. There is no,
there is no immune system. It's the elimination system. Okay. The immune system. Okay. You live
in a suburb or city. Okay. You know what the immune system is? You take the garbage out for
garbage night pickup. You take the trash out and put it out in the can in the alley. And then that
goes to the curb to be picked up by the truck. And then the truck takes it to the landfill where
it's, does that sound like a new system? Or does this sound like an elimination system?
Sounds to me like a filtering system, actually. It's a matter of what you're getting rid of,
right? So total elimination filtering would be that you have a mix and agglomerate and you want
certain things and you don't want others. Segregation is filtering. Well, that's what it
sounds like. You're taking out the garbage. So you're deciding to take contents away.
The bad stuff, maybe from the good stuff. Yeah. Right. Sort of. Yeah. No, not even. Well,
okay. So no matter how they explain the immune system, it ends up being the eliminative system,
which is very well known and discussed for a hundred years prior to the invention of the
immune system. I haven't never, I hammered calories. You know, there's no calorie caloric
relevance to food at all. Unless you're, unless you're pooping charcoal briquettes. Now, if you
go number two and you get charcoal coming out every time, well, you better watch your caloric
intake. Yeah. Right. But if you're not pooping charcoal, you know, like black carbon briquettes,
you know, that you could go out and put on the fire. If you're not, if you're not pooping that
caloric value of food is completely moot. Right. And then if they strap a cuff on your arm and tell
you that you have blood pressure problems, that is like tying a string on the end of your finger
and saying, you got purpleitis, stupiditis, blueitis. Right. What kind of shit is take the,
never put the string on your finger and you don't have any stupiditis. Don't put the cuff on your
arm and guess what? Bam. No blood pressure. Go imagine. Right. What I always thought was weird
about the name aid, you know, when they named it AIDS, cause initially it was called grid,
but it's acquired. The first word in there is acquired. Yeah. Yeah. You acquire it because
you believe that you've been diagnosed. I've seen the stuff, by the way, I've seen it, what they do
ensure it. Life insurance companies, very, very thing. You need a postcard. You put a
blot on there. If they tell you, you have a, they go tested. Right. And when you get tested,
they said they no one knows. They'd never said anyone had AIDS. You got to read it very carefully,
not so carefully. They say that you have been tested and could have a possible diagnosis for
a very serious illness, or you might've been diagnosed or you might, the most severe they're
going to get is that you show that you have been diagnosed with what could be a possibly severe
illness. And then you start getting letters. You should consider treatment. Now, anyone who's
gotten that letter that they were diagnosed, not that they have it very carefully,
like no one has cancer. You've been diagnosed with cancer. No. Ask any doctor that tells you
you're diabetic or high, but you write it down on a piece of paper. I have it. They will not do it.
They know that much. They're not that stupid. They will never write it down and sign it ever.
So it's all presumption. Now, anyone who's gotten those letters who just threw the letters in the
garbage is still alive and fine. I'm talking about the eighties and nineties, right? When it
was big promotion, the only time people come down with AIDS is when they put these billboards up,
go get tested for AIDS. And then a year later, you got a whole bunch of people dying from it.
Isn't it funny? This is, this is by the way, being made what everything I'm telling you is
being made fun of by X hospital administrators and doctors. I've heard them are retired. We'll
laugh about it. The same with the diabetes, the same with the high blood pressure. They laugh
about these things now. Uh, maybe they should be cloned also, but maybe they are ready. I mean,
maybe they are. I think they would be. That's how you have an alien invasion.
You have, uh, look human and they do make humans do really stupid stuff.
By the way, when you've got treatment for diabetes or AIDS comes down and it gets worse
and worse and worse and worse. And then you die, you pass. I've known several people and, uh, like
someone who knows it's all in, they won't get it. And I said, well, they're going to die. Well,
you know, they're like, Oh, really? I'm like, yeah, watch. You know, they're going to get,
you know, they're going to kill them. So this is the stuff that I'm talking about. Someone's saying
that doesn't make any sense because that sounds like Nazi Germany, concentration camp, doctor type
shit. Yeah. Yeah. Fool. That's right. That's right. That's exactly what's going on. You have
an open hair concentration camp, Mengele type motherfuckers running at, uh, at, um, they're,
they're running about 10 to 50,000 deep, maybe a hundred thousand deep is how they roll. What,
what do you mean by that? Dr. Mengele types. Dr. Mengele was a boy scout compared to these people,
right? Cause he was, you could say that he was doing valid research. You know, he was cutting
people in half and sewing them back together. Right. Right. So, uh, to see how they would heal
and to advance that these people just say, come here, take our drugs so you can die.
See Mengele when he did his stuff, he's, I'm not doing this so they could die.
I'm doing this weird shit to see if they could live or how to make them live.
These doctors are doing it so you can die. Right? So these doctors, they run, they could run up to
half a million deep. They could be running up to half a million deep mean a half a million of
these motherfuckers running around. And they're usually put into administrative situations,
meaning that they run the whole department of the, what the doctors do. Right. So they
get the guy who doesn't know what's going on to do their dirty work. This is the reality
of, um, uh, American medicine predominantly. It's also going on in Europe because you can't say
there are no cases for AIDS or diabetes in Europe. There are not as many, but the most of it,
you know, just like I mentioned to someone in the medical industry,
is it only countries that have treatment for diabetes? Does the population have diabetes?
Only countries that have treatment for AIDS? Does anyone in the population get AIDS? And they're
looking at me like, what does that mean? The treatment is the disease, right? So now, yeah,
these are like what you call Nazi type, you know, concentration camp people. They're still bragging
about how many people they killed over COVID on, on the ventilators would sit, you know,
with, uh, they sedate them and starve them to death. Right. And the families come in and thank
them. And you got to admit that was efficient, you know, that was pretty efficient. Yeah. So
the whole thing is just, it ain't going to get better. I think unless you start seeing, like,
they line these doctors up and like, they just clear out, imagine like a big football field.
And what are those big machine guns called? Those, uh, 50 caliber or whatever, and just start,
you know, make a big ditch Gatling. Yeah, yeah, where they dig the ditch, and they have them
stand over the ditch, and then they shoot them all. Then the next run comes in. This is the human
history. So when you look at how could they be doing this to all these people, these mass executions
and all that, you don't really know the whole story behind that. Right. And you see, so in other
words, if that starts happening, again, don't be surprised, don't be shocked. Right? Give me an
example. You know, the whole woke thing that's going, I did some research on this about two
years ago, and I was shocked what I could find. It's really hard to find, but you can find
literature, what was going on in Germany between the 19 after World War One in the 1920s, early 30s
is exactly what's going on with the woke regarding, you know, cutting your dick off,
men dressing like women and women dress like men. If you go start looking at the literature and the
publications in Berlin, and other parts of Germany, not Germany, mostly not Austria.
They were telling you were encouraging young boys to get a sex change or dressed up like girls.
They were encouraging women. It was like one out of three women in Berlin were prostitutes.
They're encouraged women to get into the sex trade. And remember, this is post World War One,
where they got the German Chancellor to agree to reparations and destroyed the country, right? The
you know, the story of post World War One. Yeah, the destruction of it. Right. So they were doing
all the woke stuff, or all the perverted shit you see going on with the woke stuff,
not so much with the racist stuff. But what they were doing was they were making popular all the
debauchery in early Germany. And so when the Third Reich came in, when they did the book burnings,
that's what it was. They were burning those publications, telling boys to cut their dick
off. And I'm serious, it's pretty harsh. And they were cleaning up like, why is this, you know,
woman, three children prostituting herself, you know, because the periodicals and the professors
and the academia of the day, were backing all this up. So the the gray shirts who came in,
then they became the brown shirts. We got to clean this up. Right. So hint, hint. Right.
You know, go try to do some research on you know, you know what the woke movement how it is,
well, the sexually or cut your dick off, right? Yeah, all that stuff. Yeah. And or put a dick on
if you're a woman. All that stuff was going exactly exactly was going on in Berlin in 1920s
and 30s. Very hard to research. I came across some German video might have been on video or
something. And very poor translation about prior third. So basically, the prior Third Reich,
post World War One prior to Third Reich, what was what was put on Germany was the same stuff
that's put on the Western nations right now. And I only I'm bringing this up because,
you know, Dr. You know, the the atrocities of the German doctors, you know, what you're
actually doing tests for high altitude, you know, right, if you lose atmosphere and a high altitude
airplane, what happens? So they put you in a vacuum chamber, right? Right. You know,
prisoners and slaves and, you know, concentration. How long do you stay conscious? How long is
Yeah, but but I'm telling you, they're not as bad as these bastards hospital administrators now
that are actually, you know, being incentivized by the Department of Health and Human Services.
There were letters posted in November, people in the medical industry. Why are why I work in
the administrative hospital? Why are we getting letters that if someone gets put on a ventilator,
we get 150,000? Why are we getting letters that if they get a vaccine, you know, and they die,
they get 50,000? Why are we getting these letters? This is like six, four months before,
five months before the COVID thing, right? You know, memo, right. So the other thing is,
when you have a big machine, like the medical system, and the government agencies and all that,
they work very slow. So when you're in the system, and you start getting these odd letters,
you know, about changing what they call policy and things like that. It's quite a fair warning,
you can imagine like four or five, six months ahead. Right? Just like colonels in the in the
military, we're getting briefed on a 911 type of event six months before, right?
Yeah, two years before, actually, two years before. Yeah. So you have plenty of heads up
up to two years. Yeah. Well, if you know, what is it Project Northwoods? You had 4050 years?
Well, yeah, that that's the, you know, part of the stuff with the remote planes. And it's like,
oh, gee, they didn't have technology do that. Well, then why did the Pentagon propose doing
it in 1962? You know, 61? Because they had the technology to do, you know, the military doesn't
volunteer to go do something, if they don't have the equipment to pull it off, is all I'm saying.
Right. So, you know, when they said we could take a remote control plane and fake an incident
and blow it up over here, we don't even have to actually have the students on it,
we could have them on it. But all we got to do is tell them that after they see a blown up plane,
yeah, and you know, they wanted to keep that thing going, where they crashed a small,
supposedly a small plane in the IRS building. Remember that? Years up? Yeah, no one saw a
plane or anything. They hired people to say that they saw a plane, but no, but they didn't get
their script right. So they didn't include that. No. And at the end of it, it was supposedly one
guy decided to commit suicide, right? Yeah, but it wasn't Yeah, it's just bizarre. So it wasn't even
that it was the whole thing was completely staged. I don't know how they staged it. But I'm just
saying that was the story they ran with. I'm not Yeah, right, right to cover up the mess. Yeah.
I don't know what else to say that, you know, it's just about covering up a mess somehow.
There you go.