Sonic Event 35, Ocelli in the Greek, rated Y.
You know, it's almost got a rhythm to it, probably because I'm making that happen.
But anyway, it is as it is, and here we are in the evening when we record or after the
sun goes down where I'm sitting.
But what day is it?
What day is it?
That's always a large question.
Greek, we could start there.
I also always ask you how you're doing, but how are you?
And what about this day, this time, this moon that we were just talking about before we
started recording?
Well, look, we've been over the lawful timekeeping.
If there's a better way to keep time, I'd like to know.
In other words, you don't have to subscribe to something that is commercial.
So what do they call those ring binders, loose-leaf paper, punched in there?
Well, they got a three-ring binder, and then you could have loose-leaf paper that goes
into it.
Some people don't have that anymore.
But if you have one of those around or a reference circle, I'm not going to tell anyone to really
go and cut a perfect circle.
But those little ring binders line up with the cornea and all that, the paper, just hold
up paper with a hole punch in it to the moon and move it back and forth and see if it fills
the hole just right at the edge.
And you'll notice that before it's full, it's very evident to see that it's not full.
Slightly usually between 7 and 10 o'clock on the face of a clock would be slightly flat.
Now when it's full, most people mistake the biggest moon to be the fullest moon.
It's always larger the night after, let's say, or even the pre-dawn after.
It's not a matter of the biggest moon, it's the roundest and the brightest luminosity
for its size.
So you can have a really small moon that's full, you'll notice that it's very round and
very bright.
The next night after a full moon, you'll notice that it's much larger, 30-40% larger, but
it's not as bright.
It's like you got closer and you turned the dimmer down, right?
The night before the full moon, it looks very bright, but it's not round.
So you'll notice, look at a clock face, between 6.30, 7, 8 o'clock, depending on where you
are on the earth, until about 10, 11 o'clock on a clock face, the left side will look a
little straightened out, the curvature will be slightly different.
So that's pretty much, I got all this from an oldest farmer's almanac from the 1800s,
by the way.
It was not a farmer's almanac, it was a little pamphlet.
See, they made, people wore vests and they had vest pocket books, this might sound foreign
if you're not in your 6th decade or 5th decade, they had, I don't know, you probably remember
vest pocket edition books, right?
Well, I've seen those, they're kind of like skinny, you know, the rectangular shape is
that the vertical is much more extended than the horizontal, the aspect.
More like the proportions of a pack of cigarettes or something.
Yeah, I've seen them, and you know what, it's funny, things like bus schedules and what not
are still designed this way when they make them on paper.
Sure, for pockets, yeah.
It's really out of habit, but it's just because that's the way it's always been done, this
is why they do them.
I don't think there's an efficiency reason for it, but I think initially it was designed
to fit in those vest pockets when they were doing these mass transit schedules, yeah.
You wore a vest, you know, with clothing, we'll one day get into clothing, but you wore
several layers, not because it was cold, even in the summer you wore several layers for
protection.
Just like today, if you go through certain Asian cities, you'll see white gloves, people
wear white gloves.
You don't know what the person was touching before you opened the, touched the handle
or whatever.
That's the first place I saw the masks, too, to be honest with you.
People just wearing what I used to call a surgical mask in the street, it just sort
of emerged in Asia first.
It makes sense because they use a lot of small engines, not anymore, but places, other more
Pacific Rim countries, they use these little tiny scooters, and they don't really run,
the engines don't run hot, and they burn oil, and there's particulates in the air, literally,
if you wear a white shirt, you take it home, if you're walking through the neighborhood
for a couple of hours or even an hour, take a white shirt off and hang it up in the light,
you'll see these little tiny black spots all over it from the oil coming out of the exhaust
of the tiny little engines.
The smaller the engine, the less efficient, by the way.
But there's actually physical particles, you know, it reminds me directly when, again,
you and I, similar age, when we were kids, there was a popular commercial on TV where
it was for smokers' tooth polish, right?
And what they would do is, you know, toothpaste for somebody who smokes, they would take a
cloth, a white cloth, and take a hit off a cigarette and then breathe through the cloth,
like, you know, breathe out through the cloth and then show you what was deposited on the
cloth.
Anyway, it's the other way around.
This way, it's like what's going in as opposed to what's coming out.
I mean, I remember in New York back in the late 70s or so, I would experience that.
But yeah, they wear all the masks and all the clothing and the protection.
Back to the Vest Pocket Edition, it was a small little hardbook, hardbound leather book.
It was about how to use a farmer's almanac, right?
And that was quite interesting because, you know, you have books written about books, right?
So how to read a book, basically, a certain book or a manual or whatever.
And it was quite interesting, and it kind of all came together because I was studying
scripture at the time, and I knew there was no Pope's work schedule and all the religions
and from whatever, they're all on the Pope's work schedule except for certain things they
might profess.
And you have then the very religious people, whatever.
You know, yeah, it's a very duality.
When I say very religious are the ones that use the dark moon, right, and sundown.
You know, let's say the Jews, the Karaites, you know, I think, admit it's the full moon, perhaps.
They still do sundown.
I said, all this confusion, you're either keeping...
If you're keeping time or measuring, any kind of measuring system has to have accuracy.
In other words, it can't be ambiguous, right?
Even when, back before they had tape measures, they would use a finger width, a hand's width,
or an elbow, right?
No, the reason why a foot is called a foot.
Sort of, yeah.
And that's close, but yeah, whose foot, whose elbow, whose finger, whose hand?
Right.
So when you do sundown and all these other things, oh man, is it vague?
Like the dark moon is super vague.
You can't use it for measurement.
So I said, there has to be an accurate way to...
And there you go.
I think I'm the only one that's put together noon and full moon as the terminal points
for the day and the month.
And then there's the year, which is a little more expanded, but works on those luminaries as well.
You know what I'm thinking might work better than the loose leaf paper hole you were talking about,
but a similar idea, is they make clear plastic pages that go into those loose leaf books, right?
Oh.
And if you were to take a Sharpie, say, you know, a black Sharpie,
and color in the edges of just that particular thing a little bit,
you'd be able to see on either side, and that way you would know if you're centering that thing
and you're having some of it hang over on one side or the other
to see if it fits into the perfect circle, so to speak, right?
But if there's no loose... I was pondering.
Yeah, I think the white paper looks pretty dark.
Remember that it'll illuminate.
It doesn't have enough illumination, but that's...
In other words, anything prefabricated,
in other words, something that's made by a big honking machine
that they guarantee or they're looking for good tolerances
of something round and small like that.
But the reason I was concerned is how many people still have loose leaf binders
or three-ring, four-ring, five-ring, whatever binders and, you know, access to them.
I mean, I'm thinking, you know, all this paper stuff is gone by the wayside.
No, they exist. I mean, they're still out there,
and schoolchildren still actually use them.
Oh, those blister packs, I got...
Oh, no, they're not really round anymore.
You know how they punch a hole when you buy an item hanging on a hook?
Yeah, yeah, right.
They're not really round any day.
Sometimes they... because they're made for double hooks also,
so it's a rectangular slot.
Yeah, sometimes they make them sort of universal
because there's like a two-level thing.
No, but the loose leaf, like you're talking about,
I mean, I have some of those binders,
but then again, I have a bunch of things that are like older school in nature.
But spool people, yeah.
A small spool like something, a thread that's used for spooling up on a sewing machine.
Oh, yeah, the ones that go in a sewing machine, perfect.
That would be...
If they're round, yeah, clean out the hole, whatever,
a piece of tubing or something prefabricated that's laying around.
You might even find it in the bin or the trash, something.
Just be aware.
Speaking of being aware, I wanted to talk about...
Maybe talk about heuristics, discovery of things, ideas.
Because I said I'm working on a bunch of stuff
and I had some ideas and hunches and whatever,
and I built it and it works really well,
better than I thought it would.
And it makes me feel like it's surreal, right?
Imagine having an idea of something that doesn't exist
and you put it together in the mind, right?
You know how they do it on a computer,
CAD computer, and they rotate it and all this?
I could do that in my head.
It's just practice.
You know, some people have good memories
and some people are visual kinesthetic.
You have to show me.
Some people, telling them is enough, right?
You got to put it all together and use that as a model.
Like, for example, if you see when they design something
and they CAD and they show you the different views
and they rotate it and all this,
see if you could do that in your mind.
It saves a lot of time.
And Tesla did stuff like that.
He would design things in his head
and then come back a month later to check it for bearing wear.
So he would be running it in another dimension, right?
Why not? Sure.
Yeah, so I've been practicing that for a couple of decades now
and I'm getting good at it.
Someone asked me,
how did you design that on a CAD system?
Which one do you have?
The one in my, the biological one.
And he's like, huh?
Again, goes back to the loose leaf paper, you know?
Right?
So, you know, right?
See, it's not the way things are done anymore.
And here's the bottom line, okay?
How you conceive of something,
how you construct it in your mind and everything else,
you have different points at which,
and then you have to articulate this to someone else.
You have to communicate it.
And this is where communication becomes an issue.
And I remember in the very first early episodes,
after you and I did some basics on what time it is
and stopped looking for Atlantis,
I think was one of the very first things, you know,
because you're standing on it,
stuff like that, after we got through that.
One of the versions of it, the main version of Atlantis, yes,
but then there were many Atlantises.
But yes, go ahead.
Well, yeah, but again, you know,
study for another day.
I'm just referencing it.
But the point is...
It's just like New York and New York, but...
Yeah.
Let me just stop you short right there.
So if you're trying to communicate an idea,
and I'm trying to say this while you're speaking,
and I want to just say this.
Go ahead.
Do not try it across the board.
Okay.
There's probably one out of 50,
one out of 100 would put it at 1%,
one out of 50 is 2% of the people
that are actually communicatable
on the heuristic side.
In other words, Chuck, you got a new idea,
you want to go communicate a totally new idea
that's new to that person,
and it's new to you.
And even though you're a good speaker,
a good communicator, they're not going to get it.
It's not your fault, right?
They're just not here for that.
I mean, I think a while back,
you and I, maybe eight years ago,
we were on a Skype call,
and we had a bunch of people
that I wouldn't normally do Skype calls with,
and this one lady kept butting in,
and I said, what do you do for a living?
Oh, wait, don't tell me.
I bet you wear a reflective vest
and hold a plastic broom, huh?
Is that your job?
I don't know if you remember that.
I intentionally wanted to tell her,
like, grab your vest and your broom
and get to work.
Skype calls about these things
is not your cup of tea.
Really rude, in a way,
because that's, you know,
I let her speak her mind
for so long, I said,
this has got to be cleaned up.
Most people don't do that.
Most people will go along and yes you to death
and whatever, right?
Yeah, and some people would say,
look, you're just being rude if you do that,
but in a case like this,
it was about, look, let's be efficient.
Let's be efficient about this discussion.
What she was doing was throwing a bunch of things
there that were not useful.
Yeah, but I do that often
and the reason is because
the percentage of what is out there
in terms of bipedal,
vertical, surface-toiling earth inhabitants
are not for,
they're programs
put here
to do things, right?
Like if you were designing a video game of a city,
you wouldn't do an empty city.
You would have people walking around, right?
How do you put those people walking around
in a video game? You program them in.
Yeah, of course.
If you start looking at them like programs
and you're looking for another player,
versus an NPC,
that puts the communication aspect
more in perspective, right?
The other thing is a sense of immediacy.
If you're trying to communicate with someone,
this is my advice,
yes, I do give advice,
and they don't get it,
you show it another way, just like different facets
and if they just leave them alone, that's it,
they're done, finished,
off to the side, next, who's next?
You've got billions of people to go through
and that's harsh, right?
Otherwise you're just going to be spinning your wheels,
oh, let's just spend time together,
oh, whatever, I enjoy your smell,
or I enjoy the way you look,
or whatever, that's fine too.
Yeah, there's something to be said for that,
it's not like that's never to be done,
but, you know,
in the proper timing,
when it's time to do that, do that,
but when it's not,
the biggest lie is that
you've got rights and we're all equal
and this and that and whatever,
that's total rubbish,
the stuff that's put out by the authorities,
you've got rights,
when you speak to
any of the authorities,
an attorney general, an attorney, a judge,
a police, military provost,
whatever, marshal, whatever,
in private,
they'll say, no, you don't have any rights,
at all, you do what you're told,
but in public, on TV,
they're constantly telling you,
so you have this schizophrenia,
where I totally agree
the structure is
the way it is,
I call it a digital colony,
where there's an empire
and we're colonialists, colonists,
and a digital empire
is what they're transitioning to,
it's still physical, but the control
is digital, right?
And
there's no
aspect of what they're saying
that holds in reality,
what's in reality is humans have always
been futile, it's a futile system,
you have the slaves and the serfs,
right?
There's a slight difference between slave and
serf, like you could sell a slave
as property, but a serf is more
like a very
strict work contract, right?
There's a difference, right?
And then you have the real
menial aspect of population,
which is about 95%
of the population, you know, that's why
people complain, I was having a conversation
with someone recently, oh yeah, we don't have
a lot of this and that because of
compartmentalization, everyone said
yeah, that's what they do,
that's exactly how
they should be, compartmentalized, they can't
think outside of,
in other words, there's a deep
aspect of the hybrid,
the human hybrid that exists right now,
was severely dumbed down
a long, long time ago.
And until
that gene dies out,
unfortunately, the dumber they are, the more children
they have, so it's the opposite, right?
The ones that can handle
the more evolved spiritual
awareness, remember,
there is a limit to hardware,
in other words,
you try to put Windows 10 on a Windows
95 machine from 30 years ago,
it's not going to do it, right?
So there is hardware, I don't know exactly,
I definitely can tell you it's not DNA,
it's not DNA based, it's much more
on how the human body
relates to the cloud, the network,
right? Just like if you try to put
a 35, 40 year old computer
on the internet, what will happen, right?
Won't work. So you're
stuck with this population
that's here now, but
you know, I always talk, it's going to be cleaned up,
it's not going to be
pretty, but you know, I don't know if you've ever
been into a place like a junkyard,
cleaning it up, it's not pretty.
So in a sense,
back to communication,
do a rough
evaluation, a snap judgment,
snap decision making, and hold that as a
reference mark, I've always talked about
this,
you know, the alternative media, all the
new age people,
the love and light, or this and that, that's
they're completely, everything
they say is the opposite, right? Especially the health
people. You take these herbs,
it'll lower your blood pressure,
has low calories, excuse me,
what did you just say?
Ridiculous, right? So
the whole thing
about that is
how to keep people distracted,
and they do it themselves, just like we
had an idea of
let's say
we go into the, even
JFK research, a lot of people are
putting out false information, they think
they're doing the right thing,
they don't know that it's false, so they're
like useful idiots, but they don't know they're
a useful idiot, right?
So there's this thing that keeps going
on and on and on, and it'll change,
but again, back to
communication and heuristics, if you
are operating on a certain level, you must
find people that are operating on that level.
A very simple
analogy is when you play in a
band, right?
When you say you play in a band,
what do you play, guitar? Okay, that
doesn't mean, that says a lot,
because if you tell me
you play guitar in a band and how long you've been
playing, I know you didn't get guitar
lessons a week ago, right?
It is highly unlikely, right?
Highly unlikely, yeah, so
there's certain things that, metrics
you can look at people, you know,
and very quickly make snap decisions,
very quick judgment calls.
That's why I just did a tangent
about the new age people, I said, don't be judgmental,
don't be judgmental, I said, it's amazing
you said, do you drive a car?
I was once on a Skype call with a radio person
when he was new age, a while back,
you're so judgmental,
I said, do you drive a car? I said,
yeah, do they have stop signs there?
Yeah, I said, it's amazing you're still alive
if you're not judgmental, because you're supposed to
stop at a stop sign, make a
judgment call left and right,
should I go or not? Do you just drive through a
stop sign or a light, see someone
crossing, you just keep going, because you don't
want to judge what you have to do?
What are you talking about? Condemnation
is the point, right?
So, if you use good judgment
you never have to condemn, because
the good judgment, you walk away from
the situation that will
eventually lead you, either through
anger or whatever, because anger feels good, by the way,
it's a release, it's an emo, right?
To condemn someone, like, go to hell
or whatever, you know, you hear that often, right?
Well, it's good
in its proper time, okay?
If you're constantly...
I don't think we're here for that, there's too many...
But somebody who's constantly angry
is not doing themselves any good, if they're
constantly angry... Oh, yeah, it'll affect the body
Yeah, I mean... But it is a release,
it is a necessary release, I mean,
even the quacky
therapist, it's like, go punch a pillow,
that's Reikian, by the way,
you know, they get all these things from Reikian therapy
and they never, right, admit them.
By the way, William Reik, the reason, one of the
reasons they punished him, not the reason, is because
he lived during a time in the 50s
and... well, actually, in the 50s
and 40s, where they were starting to narrow
things down. If you got an education
and a degree as, let's say,
a psycho-psychiatrist,
you cannot do biology,
you cannot do engineering, you cannot do
meteorology, right? If you get a degree
as an architect, you cannot do
oceanography, you have to stick in
your field.
The authorities
do not want to show multi-talented
people that you're,
like a Walter Russell type, who was an architect,
a scientist, an alchemist, you know,
did 14, 15 different things.
They don't want that, so if you
get a degree from them,
and let's say
whatever the degree is, you better stick to that field.
You start operating as an expert
or professional outside of that field, uh-uh,
can't do that, because what you're doing
is setting an example, right?
Right. Well, when you do that,
that's a very bad thing. A specialist is
fine, because they stay in their
lane, you know. Well, it's actually a good
thing, because we can do anything. People
say, oh, Greek, you're a jack of all
trades. No, no, excuse me. No, I'm a master
of quite a few trades,
right? I'm on a master level
of quite a few things.
Not a jack at all.
You know, if I
appear to be a jack of a trade, it's very
temporary, because, I'll tell you
why. I'll either
start advancing towards mastering
that technique, or I will abandon
it, because it's not something I want to dedicate time
to, and have someone who is a master fill in
to do it for me, or with me. Right. You see?
That would be the most intelligent thing to do. So you don't want
to stay as a jack.
So, um,
but anyway, they borrow from right, they tell you
to punch a pillow, the anger and all that,
all the emo thing,
any emotional carrier
will always result in a
physical manifestation of your actions,
your speech, and then
eventually manifestations
in the body, right?
The body's formation, health, all this other
stuff, in terms of the
anger. But it is a
necessary,
I wouldn't say necessity,
but it's there as a
necessary aspect. In other words, to tell people
they can never be angry,
right,
is harmful.
But to manage it, and to
keep it, it's not
a necessary thing, right?
But it is a necessary part
of the toolbox. It's just there.
It's kind of like... Well, you don't fix everything
with a hammer, but sometimes you damn well need
a hammer. Yeah, or the fire
extinguisher, you know, in the building.
I remember going into buildings for years, and the same
old fire extinguisher's sitting there. It's there.
No one uses it, right?
You don't need it.
But essentially, back
to the heuristics and communication,
do a snap judgment.
If this person, for example,
you know, I play guitar
in a band for five years. Well, you know
a lot.
Not how well they play,
but you know that they consider themselves
an expert, enough that
other people...
There are many metrics you can use when you're speaking
to people, even if they're not
present. A lot of people say, yeah, look at their eyes if they
glaze off. Yeah, but sometimes with
the digital age, you don't have the convenience
of looking at their eyes, right? You could be just on the
phone. There's a certain... There's different types
of silence, by the way. You know, when
you're speaking to someone, let's say on a phone or
a device, and
they're silent, and when
you would expect a response, there's different
variations of that silence. How long
it is, how deep the silence
is. Sometimes you could feel people drifting
away on the phone.
It's a feeling. That's the emo
aspect of it.
Yeah, of course.
It goes beyond the audible.
But you'll notice
the different silences that
people give.
It's
almost as...
It's almost as...
When you focus on that, it's
almost as evident as when people can
raise their voice in laughter, they could
raise their voice in anger, or they could just raise their voice
because they think you're not hearing them. Different
elevated voices,
different levels of silence.
The
heuristics and the communication.
Heuristics
is basically discovery heuristic.
Eureka means found it.
And heuristics
is basically based around discoveries
and finding things, usually
things that are there always.
If you look at most inventions
and most contraptions or gadgets,
it's a combination of geometries
and materials and shapes
and functions of other things put together
to do something different
that makes it new. But nothing is
completely original.
They might look completely original, but obviously
you're going to have to build it from common materials
that are accessible or not so
common. Something that you can access
that anyone else can access.
The way of putting things together
when you're, let's say,
making a prototype of something
that you think doesn't exist or really
from searching notice doesn't exist,
and then trying to communicate
that to someone
is really the
point of the
communication of
the heuristics.
Otherwise, they have common communication.
Hello, goodbye.
My favorite is, have a nice day.
I'm sure you certainly will.
So,
speaking of having a nice day
without getting too deep into other things,
in America here, it's
the 4th of July. They're celebrating. You said
there might be fireworks and dogs barking or something.
It could be.
Do you think they're going to...
Notice how it's backwards.
March the 9th, 1933 passed
already and it wasn't a peep.
Nobody talked about it.
That was the day the country
died. But they're still celebrating.
Oh, but wait a second.
That seems to be part of the custom because
they have George Washington's
birthday and whatever, right?
Don't they celebrate birthdays still of people
that are long dead?
Of course. There's still holidays built around it.
We have President's Day now, but at one point
there was celebrating what?
Washington's birthday and Lincoln's birthday too.
Yeah, right.
But they tend to forget that
it's really strange
that they're dead. But does anyone
know when they died
or remember that day? That seems to be customary.
I can't fault them too much for not knowing
what March the 9th, 1933
means. Maybe that's why
they just, if you ask them what the 4th of July
Independence Day for the Americans is,
what was that guy that goes
on the beach with a microphone? Dice?
Mark Dice?
Yeah.
Dice, right? What's the
July 4th mean? I don't know. It's a day for
hot dogs and fireworks.
Mark Dice.
I was going to say Andrew Dice Clay, but it's not
Andrew Dice Clay. It's Mark Dice.
Andrew Silberstein, the Andrew Dice Clay character.
That's a stand-up comedian, but it's very funny
to watch him ask some common questions,
and sometimes he does things like, you know,
can you find this place on a map?
Sometimes it's the place they're standing in.
I don't think
he ever did it in Jersey, but one time
he did it in a place where it was like, can you find
this state on the map?
It's the place they're supposed to be in, and they
cannot find it.
Most Americans, if you show them a map
of the world to point to the U.S.,
90% of the time they point to
Australia.
It kind of sticks out, right?
I've never seen that.
They always
point to Australia. Not always, but the majority
of them, yeah. 90% point
to Australia. It's the world map, you know, the flat one, right?
The Mercator
or whatever it is.
Strange.
I thought it was crazy that people would not be able to
find the state. Because I remember, again,
being taught, even the things
that we were taught in school at the time that you and I
were of school age, one of the things
they always made sure we knew is where the state
was that we were in.
I just thought it was...
You could at least find that.
You might not know where Wisconsin is,
but you knew where...
Here's the state for the Americans.
Have you seen the film Goodfellas?
Of course.
If you remember it?
There's a whole part of the
film where the mobsters go to a
restaurant and they keep racking
up the bill, the tab on the liquor and the
food, and they never pay it.
The restaurant owner goes to one
of the mobsters and says, look, I got this big bill
or whatever. He's never going to pay it.
He says, all right, make me a partner.
I'll take care of it.
As soon as he makes him a partner, the other guy comes in
and sells everything that he has,
all the liquor and whatever on the black market.
He can't pay the bill. They have to torch
the place for insurance,
right? That's exactly what's going
on in America.
By 1933
is when they went into full
partnership with the other mobsters
full on.
Before that,
it was just a group
that was sick, private bankers
and others that were put on the Americans,
the government to
change its policy, 16th Amendment,
all this other stuff.
When they bankrupted it on March 9, 1933,
if you go read the...
They prominently post it on Google,
by the way. It's only like two paragraphs.
You can read it. You won't understand what it means
unless you start defining what
the word discount rate and all these things really
mean legally.
That's when...
If you remember the restaurant scene,
that's what's going on
in this country right now.
It's going on in other countries
in a different way.
Hollywood showed...
You know how they showed the movie The Matrix?
The Goodfellas restaurant escapade
is exactly what's going on politically
and lawfully
with law and money.
If nobody ever saw it,
to summarize the whole thing, by the way,
he's got a problem getting paid from one guy.
He goes to somebody to,
help me solve this. I want to get paid for this one bill.
He goes, okay, I'll come in
and be a partner.
He reluctantly says, I don't know.
I don't know about the restaurant business,
but okay, I'll help you out.
He comes in and now the next part is
every week this guy's got to come up with his money.
He pays his new partner
every week, but any problems
he has are now supposedly solved.
However,
the problem
is that during all this, the bills are being
run up, stuff is coming in the front
door, going out the back, being sold at a discount
rate, on and on.
Sure, he got his problem solved,
so to speak.
It's kind of like if you
bump your shin and it hurts, then you get
punched in the nose. That hurts a little more, so you
don't feel it on the shin now, right?
Right. It's the whole, well, let me, what was it?
The movie Major Pain.
Somebody hurt themselves, they fell on their face.
Oh, my nose is, exactly.
Here, I'll fix that for you. Let me see. And he breaks his
finger.
You don't care about the nose anymore
because the finger's busted. That's what you're paying attention
to.
All of this is where it all started.
I mean,
it's kind of like a long story made short.
Is that people
came over to this side of the
world to get away from what was going on
on the other side of the world, but it followed them, right?
Yeah, of course.
So that's essentially what's going on.
But back to heuristics and communication.
The snap judgment,
a very rapid, quick judgment
of the situation.
Just like when you stop at a traffic light
or an intersection in a car, or walking
even, right? Let's say you're crossing the street.
I'm not going to judge.
I'm just going to keep walking.
You stop and you look at if it's going to bring
any danger to yourself.
You can also judge on what brings
pleasure to you.
We've given the analogy
often the lunch menu.
You go to have lunch. You look at the menu.
You're going to pick what's going to give you
the most pleasure at that time.
That's a judgment call.
It's the same thing I told this
Love and Life person. When you go to order food at a
restaurant, do you
make choices?
Do you make those choices using judgment?
Right?
I had him say,
this guy's the most judgmental.
He's telling me that I'm too judgmental.
I just showed everyone on the call, this guy's the most judgmental
guy who's making judgment calls all the time.
I've only
ever known one guy that was weird
like that, who basically
would pick exactly, no matter what restaurant
you took him to, the very first meal
on the menu was what he would buy.
That was it.
Sometimes it depends on the house
special. The house special
is usually
whatever.
Whether you took him to a diner or a burger joint
or whatever, what he would say is the first complete
meal on the menu, that was it.
Whatever that is.
Maybe he just had two brain cells
to rub together.
I don't want to know.
I'm saying this
was a guy who was a very good specialist in one
particular area. He knew exactly what he was
doing with one particular thing. When it came
to food, though, very arbitrary.
The first full meal on the menu, that's it.
That got to be
strange at diners or whatever.
We don't have those
here in the Southwest.
I missed that, by the way.
You're ready for this. There were Greek
diners.
The Greek
diners were the best in New York.
Cheeseburger Deluxe was the way
to go. It was just five bucks
and you got a fairly decent meal.
That's when I ate meat.
I went several years,
from 1988 to 1993,
being
what they call macrobiotic
or whole food
and mostly veggie, some fish.
No dairy, no eggs.
Which is good because
I adjusted
very well to it.
I learned how to cook it properly. That's the whole thing.
Again, with heuristics,
if you discover something
you want to cook at home to make
for yourself, don't just
try to make it. Try to figure out what is the
best way to prepare it because you can have
a really good ingredient and make a really crappy
meal.
It doesn't work the other way around.
If you got crappy ingredients, it's hard to
make a good meal.
That's what ketchup is for.
Or hot sauce.
Hot sauce. A lot of people
just drown things in hot sauce.
In the military, army, infantry,
the hot sauce is used as money because of the
MREs. Everything starts
to taste the same. Chicken a la king
and burritos and all this. They give you
these little bottles of hot sauce.
If you don't have that or the more you
put, the better it tastes, they trade
that as money. I got three bottles of hot sauce
for a cigarette or something or a couple
of cigarettes. Yeah, I'll take that.
Have you ever actually eaten MREs yourself?
Yeah, I've had a few.
Yeah, I mean,
I even got a hold of some of the older ones
that literally still had the cigarette in them.
At one point.
Very interesting.
Steve1989, I used to
like watching stuff. He would
pull out 70-year-old
MREs and taste them. I think he ended up
in the hospital several times with food poisoning.
I did that a few times
in the 90s just to see what it was like.
It didn't send
me to the hospital.
You have to use
the sniffer test, by the way. If it smells,
there's a reason why things smell foul.
There's a reason why.
Well, there's certain types of
fruits and foods.
I like
natto, which is fermented soybeans.
When I go to
a hardcore Japanese restaurant, not here,
but there aren't any, but sometimes
I'll order natto and they're like, oh, not for white
people, not for white people. I'm like, no,
I want natto. Give it to me with some green onion
and mustard. Oh, really? You like it?
I say, wow, that's great. It's fermented
soybeans and it smells like old, dirty
gym socks. It's
really sticky and kind of
gross-looking, but it's full of
positive intestinal flora and fauna.
People that have problems with digestion,
if you eat some natto,
it will reset
your entire digestion. In other words,
number two
will reset for
what it should be for you. It's got
this interesting
quality where
it's loaded with intestinal flora and
fauna, the microbes,
but it
adjusts itself to the individual. So if you
need more or less of another
thing or more of another thing, it will do that
naturally. It's amazing.
Better than yogurt. You know how the people
who are antibiotics, they have some yogurt
or something to get the
acidophilus. That's
nothing compared to certain fermented
foods like natto. Another
really funky, bad-smelling
food is fermented
tofu. That's really stinky.
I can't handle that. But anyway,
there are certain things that
smell foul if you understand
that they shouldn't be and you shouldn't eat them.
But if you think you have
food poisoning, by the way, it's the same thing
that was used
during the Spanish
flu, the American army flu
in 1918, that people
that knew was coming around because it wasn't
like anything experienced.
You could
get up in the morning and be dead
by the next morning.
It was hemorrhagic fever.
In other words, you basically got
a really bad fever and pieces of your lungs
broke off and you coughed up your lungs.
But the people that didn't get sick
is where the mom
would give everyone
in the morning a glass of water and soda
and soda is baking soda.
She would put a teaspoon
of baking soda in a pitcher of water,
stir it up, and then
maybe dilute it again and give it to
whoever was in the family. Whoever took that
didn't get the
hemorrhagic fever.
Which is what they're trying to do
again, by the way, but the people that are
in the, I think I've said this before,
they're morons.
They killed off all the really
good ones, by the way. I don't know if you remember
during the Obama years, like every
week there was a microbiologist that was found
dead, right?
Every week, crazy stuff
like he tied a noose
around his neck, around a tree
and then drove the car to break his neck
but he also had a bullet wound in the head.
Anyway, crazy stuff.
So they got rid of all the
ones that are left are idiots.
So when you hear about someone that does
microbiology
research or whatever, they're morons.
All they do is they play video games,
watch porn or
tell them to go over experiments. There's nobody
left, really. They don't know how to do it.
They really don't know how to create
plagues anymore.
I'm sure someone will pop up.
I don't think it'll be in the
recruitment center of any government
office, but someone will pop up
because they're trying to work on hemorrhagic fevers
again, by the way.
Hemorrhagic fever also is relatable to the
Ebola's and the Hantavirus and that kind
of stuff anyway. I mean, that's what I thought of immediately.
That's what they're calling it, yeah. They've experimented
with how to put it, but they don't know how to do it.
It's a combination, and what you were talking about there is like
a combination of tuberculosis and
Ebola together.
It's that sudden hemorrhagic thing
that you're talking about.
Most of them don't understand.
The thing is, once you understand
how the body works and how these diseases
really work, you won't
see anything that they're telling you or teaching you
in school or even
in industry as being relevant. It's not,
right, at all.
But anyway,
the soda water is the simplest
way for food poisoning also, if you
have an inkling. By the way,
I think I might have had it once, maybe
40 years ago from eating
something, and you feel this
thing like you just ate something
and it's not really, it went down into
your stomach, but it doesn't want to stay down,
and you're not sure if you want to throw up
and you're kind of gurgly or whatever,
and you kind of get this
wet feeling inside
and you just don't feel it. It zaps
your energy immediately.
And throwing up doesn't always
prevent it. If you have
that situation, a little bit of baking
soda and water should knock it out
and prevent it, because once it sits in the body,
you know, your body
will reproduce it in the bloodstream,
right? And then
it could kill you. It could be from
several days' illness to several
weeks' illness, and even when you
recover, you're not right for another few weeks, right?
You've got to get your digestion back up, or it could
kill you. So,
baking soda and water, go figure, right?
Yeah, well, that's been offered
up as a solution to a bunch of things, actually.
People have talked about fighting cancer
with it, too.
Well, look, the cancer thing I've brought
up, when I hear someone's got cancer
the first thing, I'm like, okay, your body's
working well. It's working right.
Right? What I mean by
that is like, you know, when there's an accident
on the road, and within five minutes
the police are there, and they start directing
traffic, and they block the road with the
cones and the flares, but
you know, nothing's, the streets, hardly
anything's moving anymore. You can't get through.
Right? That's what cancer is.
Right. You get it?
Mm-hmm. Instead of the
wreck being there, and everybody driving around
it and making more of a wreck, or a
mess, right? So, cancer is
actually a block.
You know,
the body regulating and saying, hey,
this is getting so bad that if we don't make a block
here, you're going to die. So, you know what?
We're going to make a blockage here.
Right? Okay.
That's why, years ago, when I was
speaking with people, I've said this before, as you got cancer,
I was like, oh, good. And they're like, what? What do you mean, good?
You're wishing negative? No, no, it's the connotations
that you have. That's why there's never going to be a
cure for it.
Oh, if you want to know who you're
going to communicate with, by the way, they have
this thing like breast cancer,
fight for the cure, or run for the cure,
or walk for the cure. Yeah, of course.
Millions of people show up, or thousands
of people. Each one of them is an idiot.
All of them, with no exception.
Oh, there might be someone there
collecting,
counting the cash, obviously,
right? And might
know what's going on. But, yeah, if you
want to know who a moron is,
yeah, the fight for whatever,
the cure, you know, look for the cure. There's no
cure for that.
There's never going to be a cure for it
because it's
like curing
accident recovery. It's not
ever going to happen. So people that
think about it that way,
you know
how to think about them now, very, very
easily, right?
See, we're actually
talking about heuristics without even
talking about heuristics, generally.
But the baking
soda and water
is the easiest
to acquire if you can. Now, I'm
not so familiar with other
alternatives if you can't get baking soda,
but certain
things
might be similar. That
would be independent research. I have not gone down
that road because I'm kind of spoiled.
You know, I'm not living out
in the jungle, right? I know I can get
baking soda pretty much anywhere.
Okay,
so what do you think?
Where should we go?
Well, you know, I'm thinking that
we're still striking on
this whole thing about communication.
You brought up NPCs.
I think it's interesting
the idea that, you know, look,
just because it stinks doesn't necessarily
mean it's not a good thing.
It could be a good thing that has a powerful
smell, but there are certain
types of powerful bad smells that
are directly indicative, and that's
one of those things that's built in,
just like
the emo stuff is built into everything,
right? Well, yeah.
Like I said, there are certain foods
that should smell bad, and that's
what they're made for, but if you know that it
shouldn't smell bad, then, you know, it
shouldn't be taken.
Yeah, but okay.
Communication. Very simple.
You're going to be wasting...
If the person doesn't get it within the first
three or four minutes or show signs
of extreme enthusiasm
or eagerness, you're wasting your time.
You're wasting your time.
Unless you want to practice.
I've gone through many years
of having conversations with people,
Skype, fortunately, and I don't have to be
face-to-face, but face-to-face,
pressing on certain matters
that they may or may not have been
interested in, and I kind of
read that, and I was like, you know what?
Just keep talking, because you could practice.
Practice your oration skills.
You know, how are you going to speak?
Right? You've got an audience, because you could
practice being an orator
on your own, but it's always easier
when you have someone else there, right?
And once you notice that they're
not paying attention or they're
just yessing you to death, because some people
want to be polite, right?
Or whatever,
just keep speaking if you plan
on speaking more and more and more on things,
right? If you want to be a communicator,
you must speak, and it's easier to
speak when someone's there or
other people are there. Well, I've always thought of it this
way, too, is that if you can't elicit the
enthusiasm from the
person that you're presenting to,
sometimes, you know,
you go through a few different things, and you'll find that
they pick up on one out of ten things that you
were speaking about, right?
And you
start to learn, oh, well, if
this person can pick up on that
and actually understand it, even though they're
not enthusiastically seeking the knowledge,
you're not getting through because they're
not really open to communication, they're not
able to understand
what you're saying, for the most part.
You come across a couple things, and you're like, but they
got that. Hmm. Well, they
all have, okay, most of, okay,
let's say it's the MPCs, like the lower tier,
which is 90% of the population,
the base,
let's say.
They already have been shown
all of the choices of the things they can do,
and they have decided
on being
a certain way. And what
happens then is it becomes habitual,
right? And
that's why you lead,
well, you lead to the conclusion
that humans are futile creatures, right?
You, proof
of, when you think of your average
Joe idea,
blue collar
or whatever, I don't think the reason is blue collar
anymore in the U.S.
It still exists, it's just not
as popular as it once was. Yeah,
they told everyone in the 60s and 70s
they were going to shut down all the factories, but no
one listened, right?
Yeah, it was actually, there's plenty
of articles and people speaking about it,
pre
what is it, programming or
predictive programming or whatever.
It's not even predictive programming, it's just flat out tell you, right?
When
you look at the actual life
of how it's portrayed,
almost like a Homer Simpson type thing, so
you work at a job that you hate,
you do the absolute minimum,
you try to do whatever you can get away
with, right?
There's no consciousness there.
And when you're not at work, you're either
watching sports, drinking beer
or thinking about sex.
We just narrowed it down
to about 90% of the population.
I had
once met a woman
a while back and she
said she was psychic, right?
And she actually was pretty good.
She said she doesn't like it
because most people's thoughts are pretty
bad thoughts, you know?
And
it's pretty interesting and I kind of stuck
with this back almost 35 years ago
and it kind of stuck with me and
when you start
learning how people think in private
or when you get to know someone, let's say like a roommate
or a co-worker,
let's say a co-worker situation, they put on a certain
facade because they're at work, right?
But then you get to know them,
you go to the bar, you have a few drinks
after a few weeks or months, they start
telling you things of what they think about you.
You're like, wait a second, I would have never...
Wow, you know?
Things that are just
very unusual or immoral
or unethical or
not fitting that type of person, right?
So whenever
I would hear that from people,
yeah, I used to...
I hung out with a co-worker a few months, the guy's a real
sicko, but he seems... everybody loves him at work
but in real life, his personal life,
he's a sicko. I'm like, yeah, that sounds about right
for most people.
And they were like, what do you mean Greek sounds about right for most people?
Yeah, yeah, don't be naive.
I know, the private thoughts that most
people keep to themselves are
far from what it is that
they present, you know?
Exactly. Regardless of whether they're
the Homer Simpson type and they seem pretty
simple and you go, okay, I got this guy
all the way around. The twisted
and insane things that could be going on
inside of that skull.
And usually, for the majority,
that's what's going on. But they have it under
control, they call it repressed whatever
to a certain point and they go
to their grave with this duality,
which we've talked about. They think, you know, they're being
led that way. But here's
the interesting part. The
real interesting part is there's a
filter that has to be employed
both ways. In other
words, with those really bizarre
thoughts, whatever you want to call them,
that people have, they have to filter that when they're
at work and the facade they put on.
Right? But also
when they're not at work, they have
to put a filter because they have to
go back to work. They don't want to be seen
somewhere by a co-worker out in public
doing something again.
So there's a two-way filter. So they're
using so much energy
just by filtering the different
aspects of their
thoughts. Well, it goes to different levels,
right? They behave a certain way in front of, say,
their wife, but when they're out with
their buddies, that's a different person.
Yeah. You have to filter it both
ways. Because when
they're out with their buddies, if they start acting like
they do with their wife, oh, you're a real pussy, man.
What's wrong with you? Right. But if he acts the
other way, so it's like a
two-way filter. So think about all the energy
that people are wasting just by not, quote
unquote, being honest with themselves, number
one. Number two, not
being honest with anyone else.
Right? And
number three,
what do you think they
would do if they were actually found out that
that voice in their head is not really them, and it's
an external influence? Well,
I've tried to explain this to people, and they
don't like it at all. Where I say,
somebody will tell me, well, this person's very
honest with me all the time. And I go, no, they're not.
They're not.
I guarantee you they're not. What do you mean
you guarantee they're not? Think about this from
your side of it. All the things that
go on in your head. Do you speak every
single thing that goes on in your head? Do
you communicate that at all?
Well, yes, I do. Well,
okay, good. Yeah. To communicate
it, like you said, to communicate
it is people say, what do you mean?
That's not my thought. I think about these crazy things
or whatever I say, but check it out. I'll show you
how it's not your own head.
We said this before is all you do
is when you have that crazy thought, whatever it is
as the thought
is in the head,
tell yourself,
okay, this is this crazy thought
coming. Tell me more like anticipated
and it'll stop.
It'll stop.
Because it's busted, right?
You see what I mean? So
if you have a, let's say you,
anyone, these thoughts that
are unusual, you shouldn't
you morally or ethically, civilly
or whatever, shouldn't be thinking about this about another
person or situation or whatever. Anticipate
the thought. Ask yourself
to, okay, I see the thought.
It's not very good. Tell me more.
Ask the thought to continue.
And if it stops
and pauses,
you just busted
the outer voice
on outer voice. Yeah, because there's
there, they don't want it. They
want to have you convinced that it's your thought.
You see, it's kind of like
the clock in a retail
store, right?
It's a, it's very
subtle. It's actually, it's not very subtle to tell
yourself continue
internally with a thought. It's not very, it's not subtle.
It takes quite a
quite, it's
pretty overt internally.
But the clock, by the way, on a retail
store is, these, a lot
of small, I've mentioned this many times, I think
it's pertinent. Yes, Ivan, I'll let you
out.
It's very pertinent because let's say
in, you'll see the analogy.
Small retail shops, they
have a problem with point of sale items being lifted,
right? Right. And they rely on those
to whatever, because they're usually high
markup, whatever, you know, you don't want anything lifted
in a store. And I remember
having a meeting with all the shop owners, let's say
on a block or two. And
the thing that came up is how do we stop this
whatever
shoplifting is, oh, I put them behind a glass case,
but I don't sell as many when they're like that, right?
Right. Well, but none of
it gets stolen. So I'm like, yeah, okay. So it's
what you do. When someone, most people
I'll give you a good
for instance, convenience stores
used to put lighters right on the
counter. And in a lot of places
they would just be there and people would just grab
them as they were going because they were there to buy cigarettes
and they would sell a lot of them because it was
right there. It was a good
point of sale. So
percent got lifted. Seventy percent were
sold. Yeah, something like that would start
to happen. One out of three were lifted.
Okay. So I said, well, instead of you have
to do it psychologically. And what that is
is that when someone's going to
lift something, steal something
they're conscious of time. In other words, they
want to do it as fast as possible and not be
seen, right? You
cannot really do
much about the not be seen
part, right? Because I've seen some shops
where I drive by or walk
by and there was no one in the
shop. I mean, there was no customers and no one
minding the store. It's like I could walk in. Still
no one came out. I could have picked up the
cash register and walked out, right?
Because the person was
on a break in the back on the phone in the
back in the bathroom and they didn't lock the door, right?
That's the physical aspect.
You can't do anything about that.
But the time aspect, what you do is
right opposite the entrance door
when the first thing you see when you walk
in the shop, put a big ass clock, the
biggest clock you could fit in the wall
space or whatever. And
at the time there was like a
deco movement where these fancy old
antique clocks were being sold real cheap.
You know, like a foot, two foot diameter
clock, doesn't matter, a functional
clock. Put it right opposite the door
and what that does subconsciously,
I don't even like the word subconscious, Freudian
stuff, but what it does is
it gives everyone
who comes into the shop the impression
of time
signaling. And it messes
up the one who's coming
in thinking that they're going to lift something.
It really messes them up and they don't
know why. This is actually
why you'll see in a lot of stores, they place
a screen so you can
see yourself on camera.
So that you're aware that you're
being seen.
But that's the other aspect of it. You said
time and being seen, these are the two aspects.
This was before, because back in those
days, if you wanted to do a security system like
that with the CRT TVs and all
that, it was real expensive. Yeah, it was a pain
in the neck, but they did it in some places
because it was worth it. And if you
put up that screen, it would automatically
reduce the shoplifting because people
were now being shown that
someone is watching. Yeah, but the
thing is, some people don't give a
you-know-what and they'll do it anyway.
That's another thing. Yeah, it's the
subtle psychological part. So anticipating
the aspect of time. So there's
something about filtering out
a lot of the external
influences if you anticipate them.
If you know what I mean.
With the internal thought.
In other words, if you want to judge
the thoughts that you're entertaining,
when the thought comes up,
assess it out. Is it
something that came into the mind?
Is it really running a thought pattern
right now? And then ask it to continue.
Simple.
And then you'll see
what's really going on in the head.
not much about heuristics on the
material end, but I guess we talked about
enough about heuristics on various
other things.
And we'll continue that.
Fair enough.