Colds and naps and medical malpractice aside, here
we are, Rated Y, once again.
Greek, how are you?
Oh, much better on the laptop.
I'm using an old wireless Logitech wireless headset,
chilling in front of the laptop.
Can't run away, it's too far, but yeah,
just telling you, it's funny, they do an
article once in a while that Hulk Hogan
might have died because of malpractice, they didn't
even use that term, but yeah, him and
like 4,000 other people in the USA
that day.
This is common, this is so common, and
Ozzy Osbourne and all these guys, so you
could live to 100 pretty simply here if
you're like them.
In other words, if you feel you belong
here, you're part of this system, I saw
someone where trust the science means trust the
system, right?
You could live pretty long, but the problem
is you won't be much better off than
you were in the 19th century, you will
be, because you want to avoid all the
stuff that everyone else is taking in, including
the food they eat, very, very important.
Years ago, even in the film, it's shown
in art, you go to a weird town,
and people say, must be something in the
water, right, oh hell yeah.
You notice that's never making it anywhere, even
the alternative, alternative is a waste of time
too, they're not talking about what's in the
water, right, at all, anymore?
Well we have, I mean, over the years,
there's been a lot of people like myself
who've talked about the water and how people
don't understand it, and of course, but the
crap they're pumping into the water is a
problem, and the containers they're putting the water
in is a problem, I mean, it took
some of us a little longer to figure
that out, but I mean, it's just obvious,
and now there's so much plastic in everybody's
body, I don't know if that's, you know,
I don't know what your view is on
the plastic situation.
Plastic is not an issue, well, there's seven
types of plastic generally used in industry, and
we'll go through it really, really fast, so
fast I'll be done before I even say
what the plastics are, one of the plastics,
if not two of the plastics, have these
things called plasticizers, and one is a BPA,
the other one is a phthalate, I like
that word phthalate, it's spelled P-T-H
-A-L-A-T-E, and those two
plastics, yeah, yeah, those, one is PVC, the
other one is polycarbonate, so with the BPAs,
it's funny when you see like a polyethylene
and it says no BPA, I'm like, of
course, it's polyethylene, but those things are gender
-bender chemicals first, they dump them in the
river, you know, the factories that have the
BPAs and the phthalates, when they have a
runoff, the fish, all the fish are female,
regardless of how many male fish were there
a month ago, right, and then you have,
and then what it does is it does
accumulate more like toxify the liver and the
kidneys, and now 99% of what people
complain about being lack of fitness or health
is liver issues, and there's no discussion, but
by the way, I was driving here in
Tucson recently and it said center for liver,
medical center for the liver, I think it
was something like that, I was laughing, like
you're gonna go there and these morons know
anything about the liver, right, I wanna go
in there and ask these morons, if you
go into surgery and you have a procedure
where half of the liver is removed, how
long does it take for it to grow
back, and half of them say, oh my
gosh, oh, I don't know, I'm serious, right,
I think we went over this, I don't
know if anyone looked it up, there's maybe
some scant information, it'll grow back in like
two weeks, yeah, so I don't know, but
anyway, you're in really bad shape, people, humans,
you know, it's still a fact, not really
well reported, they shut down major funding, by
the way, in the 80s for Red Cross
medical research across the world, like doing profiles
of societies and all over the world, they
used to go to, you know, as many
countries as they could, spend time there and
document what, you know, quote, unquote, the health
of the people, and they shut that down,
you know why, because they found out the
more, quote, unquote, poor the country was, the
lower the infant mortality rate was, for example,
the lowest infant mortality rate on the western
hemisphere is Cuba, most likely today, they found
out that the people lived an average, you're
ready, 17 years more, not five or 10
or two, right, that's a lot, right, so
if you live to 100, 17 years is
17% more, if you live to 80,
it's 23% more, and so on and
so forth, so they lived 20 double digit
plus times longer, infant mortality was down, quote,
unquote, health issues, disease, cancer was non-existent,
right, non-existent, yeah, and yeah, this is
what's great, this isn't, in other words, go
to the pot, everyone knows, has heard of
someone that's got some ailment, I see them,
I'm in a neighborhood, I haven't moved from
this place in 25 years now, almost 24,
and I've seen people just a year or
two older than me walking with a cane
in this neighborhood, right, right, and they're being
killed slowly by the medics, you watch it,
you know, they go, how do I know
they're being killed by the medics, well, they
have a job, or a job, not a
yob, a job, I think I've explained the
difference between a job and a yob, right,
like, hey man, I got a yob, that's
different than, hey man, I got a job,
so anyway, when they have these jobs, they
have to get what's called a yearly or
biannual, what do you call it, medical exam,
a physical, they always call it, physical, yeah,
yeah, and guess what, they fall for the
high blood pressure, they fall for this, the
cancer screening, I've read cancer screening stuff, and
I said, go back to the doctor that
tells you you have cancer, and have him
sign an affidavit swearing that you have cancer,
he said, I wouldn't do it, he won't
do it, I called him, hey, they won't
do it, of course, none of them will
ever do it, because you don't have it,
do you know how rare cancer is, by
the way, it's extremely rare, well, it used
to be, you know, yeah, no, no, in
other words, people are dying from, they're dying,
in other words, right now, one out of
two people will die of cancer, just like
one out of two people who are married,
one out of two couples that are married
are going to divorce, that still holds, in
other words, half the people, more than half
the people are dying of so-called cancer,
right, so, but there's no such thing, really,
as they portray it, that, no, my gosh,
have I confused everyone right now, so, anyway,
yeah, probably, yeah, what is the thing, as
you thinketh so you are, and your beliefs
become your reality, right, oh, yeah, there's so
on and so forth, many different philosophical stripes
that basically say that, you know, you create
your own reality by your own perception, and
how you interpret things is exactly the way
they are, so, the Agregor thing, well, enough
people believe in something, yeah, that emerges as
real, or manifests, let's say, I've been doing
some, well, for a while now, engineering consulting,
various subjects, I mean, just stuff, just drop
that a thin air on me, and coming
up with solutions and stuff, and it's funny
when you hear these quote-unquote people are
supposed to be learned in the art of
engineering and all that, believe even the medical
stuff, one guy says he wants to take
this, these, when I say dealing with engineers,
these guys are raking it in, right, I
mean, like, four guys making 100 million a
year in engineering, I didn't know it could
be, like, a drug cartel or something like
that, you never hear, when you work as
an engineer in an office, you know, you
get a salary, right, and you get paid
well, I think it's 100k plus, 120k plus
out of college now, something like that, and
someone, you know, should get raking a quarter
of a million a year, but, like, 30
million a year, I don't know, these guys,
what the hell are they doing, but anyway,
it's good for me, though, because, you know,
when you're making 30 million, 40 million, 50
million a year, you know, handing someone six
figures is like a candy bar, right, so,
$50,000 is not a big deal, $100
,000 is not a big deal, yeah, yeah,
because you're doing all, you're doing 2 million
a month, right, so, personally, and, yeah, it's
quite interesting to see that, and the ignorance
abound, but I'd rather be speaking to engineers,
though, because, you know, they have the training,
you know, you can actually get into, when
you explain something, you can actually say, well,
this thing moves left and right, and goes
up and down, and it's made of this,
and they're not like, huh, right, they kind
of get it, right, so, yeah, interesting, anyway,
I just want to bring that stuff up,
because I don't know how much to overstate
humbly, the relevancy of what we discuss here
is so effing relevant, right, that it should
make, I mean, I don't know how many
of our subs have ever heard more than
10 Sonics pour gasoline on their heads, set
it on fire, and ran down the street
naked, how many have done that, I don't
know, because this is how, this is the
urgency of what I'm saying, right, yeah, I
look, I understand that, you know, and, in
fact, somebody asked a very long, convoluted question,
I'm going to break down for you fast,
that, you know, like, why don't you just
simply create an entire new exchange out of
the credit system, you could literally create the
credit, you know, utilizing the credit system, create
something that does have tangible value, and then
literally create a collective that would be, in
and of itself, a profitable venture, like a
new bank, almost, but I hate to use
the dirty word bank, he says, yeah, go
ahead, no, that's fine, no, you could, but
you can't have it defined as such, the
moment it's defined as such, then you get
a knock on the door, this goes against
the United States, and then you're at war
with the United States, basically, when they tell
you this goes against the policies of the
United States, it's an indirect way of saying
that we're declaring war on you, right, so
that's why, when they go to other countries
to wage war, they're, why are they going,
what do they say, to defend the interests
of the United States, right, you've heard that,
right, literally, an interest is exactly what they
collect when they make loans, so, you know,
yeah, well, they don't really make loans, they
use your credit, and in order to get
into that agreement, you make them the trustees,
right, is the main way, and then the
other way is that you give them also
security interest, if you didn't know, if you
didn't recognize that you were making them a
trustee, because a trustee, for example, when you
have a trust, a trustee could sell everything
you got, and legally, that's why, here, I'll
give a little legal secret out, when I
set up trusts, I've been doing this for
20 years, not setting up trusts, but consulting
on them, it's like, oh, man, I'm setting
up a trust, you know, my sister's brother,
my wife's, my brother-in-law is going
to be trustee, I say, oh, brother-in
-law, oh, I've seen that go sour sometimes,
you know, I don't care if you're married
for 30 years, that could go south, right,
and I say, listen, this is what I'd
like for you to do, whenever you set
up a trust, I want everyone who's going
to sign on as a trustee, sign something
else first, and that something else is a
resignation letter, have them sign the resignation letters
first, before they sign on as trustee, get
it, wink, wink, so if they turn out,
whatever, you just go record the resignation letter,
and they're out of there, now, some, now,
here, if you really want to know what's
going on, if you ask them to sign,
what's this, it's a resignation letter prior to
signing trustee, it's like, screw that, I'm not
doing that, well, they kind of exposed their
motive, didn't they, right, so, yeah, so, by
the way, it's $1,500 an hour attorneys
that don't know what I just said, and
I have spoken to some of them, mentioned
that, and they're like, that's a great idea,
and I, wait a second, you're charging $1
,500 an hour, and I'm giving you great
ideas, yeah, well, this is kind of backwards,
this is kind of backwards, isn't it, yeah,
oh, well, you know, how about this one,
a retired New York attorney wants to write
a book on how corrupt the Bar Association
is, but he can't, because he doesn't know
any law, that's almost verbatim, I'm kind of
paraphrasing what he told me, yeah, by the
way, the reason I knock, quote, unquote, doctors,
or medical technicians, that's what they are, and
attorneys, is because I know so many of
them, right, people that knock these other things
hardly have any first-hand experience, I'm like,
oh, my gosh, right, and priests, right, rabbis,
whatever, they do nothing, they're fun, I love
those guys, though, they create all kinds of
weird stories, and then they create their own
little offshoot of the story, it's just, you
know, rabbis, you mean rabbis, yeah, they're the
funniest, they're hilarious, they could be the, you
know, they'll sit there telling me about their
last steak dinner, you know, instead of, you
know, telling me about something in the book,
you know what I mean, it's hilarious, it's
very much like, I don't know if anyone,
if you guys are familiar with Guy Ritchie
films, Snatch, S-N-A-T-C-H,
you know, go watch it, the beginning, when
they go in to get the diamond, and
they're dressed up like Hasidim, right, and what
they're discussing, right, give me the stone, where
is the stone, yeah, anyway, so, all right,
let's go, question.
Yeah, that is a key, so somebody wanted
to know if you were involved in the
recent dust storm in Arizona, or if you
were affected by it, one or the other,
because it did make some headlines, and it
seemed to be a strange weather event.
We've been getting a change in the jet
stream here, and I finally said, listen, I've
got to do something about it, for the
past couple of days, I altered the jet
stream, the jet stream here should be coming
up through Mexico, like the west coast of
Mexico to us, bringing what's called the rainy
season, and what's been happening is, we've been
getting a jet stream coming down from Seattle,
swirling in the midwest, clockwise, across central Texas,
and we've been getting what's going across central,
you don't want anything from central Texas, especially
the jet stream, very hot and dry, I
said, this is really screwed up, I did
about 20 hours of ops, and I got
rain to come here from the south, and
it's a lot of work, it's very sensitive,
right, it's like, I don't know, it's kind
of like between dialing a watch and scratching
your butt, but anyway, so, yeah, so anyway,
I'm just joking, people, I have to laugh,
because I don't know if they'd say this
everywhere, but on the east coast, it's definitely,
I don't know whether to scratch my watch
or wind my ass, you know, when you're
confused, yeah, that's why I said it up
that way, yeah, you got it, so anyway,
so anyway, that's it, and we had some
rain today, a slow drizzle, those are called
Haboobs, or Habeebs, or something like that, sounds
a lot like friend in Arabic, and it
went around us, it forks, there was one
coming, you could see it, it's really ominous,
it's like that movie Scorpion King or whatever,
it's a wall, a tan wall that goes
up to about the low height of airplanes
before they land, really tall, 700, 800 feet,
1000 feet, and it moves towards you very
slowly, completely engulfs all the traffic lights, come
on, you have a visibility of anywhere between
10 and 50 feet, and they always go
around us when I know they're coming, obviously,
because I've mentioned, when you set up these
devices, you create a force field or a
bubble, it's amazing how when there's lightning, you
know, get inside, like that's going to help,
right, so you don't get hit by lightning,
right, and the first thing I do is
start activating devices, it forms a force field
around you, right, so no, I saw that,
I had nothing to do with it directly,
I didn't, you know, but it went around
us, because we usually get it, and if
you study the jet stream, it was going
from west to east, which it shouldn't be,
it should be going south to north, but
thanks for asking, yeah, and it went over
phoenix, I think, so, you know, yeah, it
shut down, they lost power, a couple of
the counties there lost power, right, so here's
one about pets, by the way, I always
like these questions, why do some humans experience
a loss of vacuum from cats, has anyone
found ways to bypass this experience, short of
maintaining the cats and humans general hygiene, how
should we go about remediation, now, really quickly
on this, I lived with a friend temporarily,
when I was getting a divorce, and I
had nowhere to go, and he had a
cat, and I was like, dude, I can't
stay with you, because cats just blow me
up, you know, and he's like, well, look,
cat scratch fever, if they scratch you, you
get a rash, like that also, yeah, plus
I just get the runny eyes, runny nose,
I mean, just my whole vacuum goes out
of whack, that's because the cat has a
case of cat psoriasis, it's, you don't see
it, it's very small, very fine, and energetic,
it's because of the quality of life of
the cat, most of the time, in other
words, I found out that most people that
have adverse reactions to being around felines, if
they're around a barn cat, in a barn,
with the doors closed, it's not so bad,
but when they're in an indoor, near an
indoor cat, meaning it doesn't get to go
outside, apartment house, what have you, they have
that issue, yeah, well, typically, yeah, my friend
was one of the most incredibly clean people
ever, and so he kept it at a
minimum, but I couldn't escape it, and I
happen to know there's a lot of people
that like, I know you say it's a
matter of psoriasis, but it seems like everybody's,
everybody's indoor cat is a problem, everybody's, you
know, really, yeah, for some people, yeah, now
here's the other thing, I'll take this, we
all take interest in things that affect us
personally, if something doesn't affect us personally, we
very rarely take interest in it, unless it's
an occupational thing or whatever, and you have
to know, so I've never had an adverse
reaction to cats, I've remotely, and not been
around people, had an adverse reaction to cats,
but I've heard people say that I have
adverse reactions to cats when the topic came
up, and those people are actually hypersensitive, or
very, you have, you know, you have sensitive,
very sensitive, then hypersensitive, right, but I would
say they were sensitive to, very sensitive in
hyper, all three, I don't know, I think
that there's been a lot of stuff about
cats have special, you know, bacteria, quote-unquote
things that in their gut that go into
your gut, if you just touch them, you
know, like 30 seconds handling a cat, you
get it, right, Richard Allen Miller is big
on that, and starts taking over your brain,
some shit like, I just, am I on
point with that, or am I off?
Richard Allen Miller says a lot of things,
you got to decode, so, you know, who
knows, but people have talked about that, what
is it, tox, toxus plasmosis, whatever the hell
it is, I forget how you say it
exactly, but you know what I'm talking about,
where they say this thing gets in your
brain from the cat poop, and maybe it
does, I don't know, but you know what
is funny to me, is that when I
was young, the first pet I had was
a cat, and my cat used to go
outside, inside, he was outside a lot of
the time, and he didn't make me sick,
but only these indoor cats, yeah, that's what
I mentioned, yeah, it's, yeah, that's right, there's
a certain stress, certain element that they change
the environment, now to me, if you really,
you know, everybody cover your ears, I think
cats are visiting here to monitor us, if
you guys know about John C.
Lilly, did a lot of research with dolphin
brains, and psychedelics, and all that, right, he
talks about echo, ECCO, ECCO, which is Earth
Coincidence Control Office, it's like one of God's
field offices, if you want to understand more
of what he meant by that, it's the
Adjustment Bureau film, he says that's real, well,
he died before the film came out, more
than 15 years, or 10 years before, 15
years before the film came out, that's based
on John C.
Lilly, there's an Adjustment Bureau, and they control
large, long events in people's lives, in society,
and you're sort of controlling the small events,
and they do make adjustments in the small
events, so the big events happen, and when
he was tripping enough in isolation, they approached
him and said, listen, we appreciate what you're
doing, but don't do it anymore, we want
you to go back and learn what it's
like to be a human, you know, like
be a screw-up, right, so, but they
did tell him that if you figure out
how we do things, you'll never have to
come back here again, you're done here, so
I thought that was interesting, and I think
cats play a role somewhere in that, well,
they would be excellent monitoring devices, because, I
mean, they seem to be everywhere and nowhere
at the same time, yeah, yeah, yeah, there
are other people said, if you don't put
a probe, or a, what do you call
it, a chip, though, one of those sensors
in people, put it in their pets, right,
right, so, yeah, because their pet's not going
to be able to communicate that it has
something like that, so, yeah, and cats, by
the way, it's very well known, they're not
evolved from, someone was talking about evolution today,
I had to interrupt very simply, of course,
but cats did not evolve, domestic cats, small
cats, from large cats, at all, they're very
different, just like dogs did not evolve from
wolves, just look at a wolf paw and
a dog paw, and they're internal, they have
different aspects to their biology, they're independent, what
happens is species don't evolve, species are injected,
they're introduced, right, yeah, so, when you have
like a small looking canine, large canine, medium
canine, oh, they didn't evolve, you know, in
any way, they were, it was time to
bring in this size and this type, and
they just put it in, you put it
into our reality, you know, there's no evolution
at all, as a matter of fact, the
food industry is wholly and solely dependent on
the lack of evolution, like long-term canning
stuff, right, you're gonna, this is a Chuck
Missler thing, if you can peanut butter for
a fallout shelter, it's supposed to last for
25 years, yeah, yeah, I was shocked when
I found out some things were designed to
last 25 years, you know, food stuffs, right,
wet, yeah, it's, they're relying on there's no
evolution, right, right, you get it, so no
change, yeah, what else you got?
Okay, so, on the topic of acoustic counter
space, I'm thinking the most important factors in
the material used for the barrier, in quotes,
the size of the hole and the amount
of space between the barrier and the back
of the speaker, could the Greek elaborate on
these factors?
Oh, wow, who, I wonder who wrote that,
email me, email me, sounds like you got
at least one or two sharpened pencils in
your pocket, you know how to listen and
communicate, thank you very much.
This is a long-time listener, I know
the handle they're using, this is a long
-time sonic observer, let's call it.
Well, either way, either way, what you wouldn't
believe, I've had long, long, long, long time
listeners that couldn't structure a sentence like that,
but anyway, no, that's great, there you go,
the false back, imagine a false back, it
doesn't have to be a false back, per
se, in the enclosure and when you successfully
do this, you don't need all that volume,
there's something called Thiel's small parameters, T-H
-I-E-L and small, now you ready?
Now, I forgot Thiel's first name, but small,
his name, there are two Australian guys that
came up with speaker parameters, like how much
volume need behind a certain driver when it,
when you measure its parameters, you know how
flexible it is, dimensions and all that, electrical,
mechanical, anyway, I just want to play on
this, because it's funny when you find that
most people have been in audio and know,
use Thiel's small parameters, but they don't know
about small, small's first name is Richard, now
what's the, what's the nickname for Richard?
I'll leave it at that, so yeah, you
got it, all right, so yeah, the Thiel's
small parameters fall apart, that's why someone kind
of gave me an elbow and says, no,
they're never, industry's never going to use this,
because it destroys Thiel's small parameters, and his
entire business is based on Thiel's small, right,
it's kind of like what the acoustic counter
space is like, oh yeah, cars can run
on water, right, or guess what, the periodic
table doesn't apply anymore, they're going to let
you get away with that, no, never, right,
their entire system is based on that, so
it's based on Thiel's small parameters, they fall
apart, so the question, I guess, was materials,
the barrier, the barrier is the same, you're
using the actual structure, the baffles, let's call
it, they're all, they should be made, or
can and should be made of the same
material the loudspeaker enclosure is, so if you're
working with an enclosure that's half-inch particle
board, make it out of half-inch particle
board, right, I tend to, okay, also these
things could go behind drivers, there's a patent
on, someone did a patent on something similar,
and it was called embedded transmission line, and
I got in communication with them, and I
gave them all these drawings, and how they
can improve their patent, and when they got
the continuance, they put my drawings in the
patent, oh, did I ever show you that,
all my drawings are in somebody else's patent,
you never showed me that, you got permission,
okay, yeah, so when I show these drawings,
I said go to this patent number, and
you'll see all my stuff there under a
different thing, right, I give them permission, because
you know me, I like to give pretty
much whatever I can away to help people,
I wouldn't do it anymore, but not because
of that, I think, I think it's just,
what is it called, Bob Pearls, right, so
yeah, the answer, I guess the answer I'm
getting here, just make, just use whatever materials
you have, now the gap inside the counter
space changes depending on the driver's side, if
you're doing it for behind a tweeter, a
very tiny speaker, it's much proportionally smaller, for
a large woofer, I would make the gap
quarter inch of air space, quarter inch of
absorbent material, all right, and I'm still developing
this, and it's unbelievable, especially when you do
an isobaric setup, I have a speaker that
is 9x7x10 dimensions, small, you can put both
of them under one arm, and when you
play these with a, they're not very efficient,
because I just use drivers, I find, if
I use really good drivers, they'll be more
efficient, but I'm more sensitive drivers, but you
crank these things up, and you think there's
like big old JBL towers, or those big
-ass Sergo and Vegas, or huge rock and
roll speakers, that are as tall as your
brother was, whatever, when you're growing up, oh
yeah, Ben's, yeah, that's what you think is
in there, huge speakers, and the base extension
goes down to 20 cycles, like really 20
cycles minus 60b, but pretty flat down to
28, a little tiny four and a half
inch woofer, it's like, how is that possible,
every time I listen to it, I'm like,
no, we don't live in a real world,
no, not at all, you know, this is
not real, this is not really happening, yes
it is, yeah, so, have you ever tried
to apply that, yeah, have you ever tried
to apply that kind of stuff to instrument
cabinets, because part of what you're describing vaguely
sounds to me like what they did with
Laney for a little bit, when they were
actually concentrating on their construction, once they went
into like mass production, it was over, but,
well, when they do that to an instrument,
it will change the resonance, see that resonance
you have in a guitar, whether it's acoustic
or not, right, or any instrument is the
characteristic of it, and by the way, you
know that bullshit about the Stradivarius, where it's
three million, because no one knows how to
duplicate the sound, it's total bullshit, I know
how to duplicate, I can build you a
Stradivarius that will sound exactly like the original,
except for if you, actually I could, I
could, that sounds, I'm saying this humbly, and
it's based on this theory, I'll give this
information out, it's very well established, I'll give
the information, it's a German guy, again from
Snats, you know, where'd you get that for,
who's going to get you, protect yourself from
who, it's the Germans, right, it's here, I'll
give you this guy, it's a C37, C37
acoustics, here, I'll click on it, look it
up, it's, the website is enemoza.com, it's
C37 theory English, this is in English, by
Dieter Enemoza, not a good German accent, E
-N-N-E-M-O-S-E-R,
it's called C37 theory English, what that means,
C37 is the 98.6 blood temperature, and
basically what gives that Stradivarius that sound is
the, and tonality is the coating, the lacquer
that they used, it's not the wood, it's
the coating, so I'm very big into natural,
if you're going to have a hi-fi,
a hi-fi, you know, for, you know,
music is wonderful, but it gets more wonderful
when you have a nice high, a really
good hi-fi to play it on, right,
and everything blooms, the sound just blooms, and
everything just sends, usually if you have a
good hi-fi, it's better than what they
had in the recording studio, and then you
get into the problem of, I can't get
recordings that sound good, right, so you can
have a very revealing system, because, yeah, so,
yeah, so check them out, C37, he's got
some pretty good articles, all very German, so,
yeah, that's, so I apply a lot of
that, for example, when I do coatings and
things, I use natural shellac, which come from
the lac bug, yeah, it's actually a bug,
right, they make a resin out of, and
alcohol, I use lacquers, I got away from
acrylics and all that, you can hear the
difference, yeah, you want to use natural sustained
materials, in other words, they're not modified with
too much plastic, yeah, so anyway, about the
counter space, let's do a get-together on
that in the next couple of weeks, I'll
announce it here, just to discuss it, the
sooner we discuss it, I'll do, like I
did the weather and other stuff, I'll pop
diagrams, drawings, photos, maybe a video, I have
sent people videos of what the little speakers
sound like, I know, whatever you have, but
if you play it with headphones, you'll be
like, oh my gosh, that's a lot of
sound, right, and it's coming out of this
little tiny thing, I wouldn't say they're tiny,
they're small, so, you know, probably smaller than
the sound, right, okay, so the Greeks, oh
my gosh, yeah, the Greeks said in one
podcast, that what they're selling as AI is
not really AI, now that I, no, understand
some technical stuff, and having worked with it
a bit, I get it, it doesn't have
its own memory, and it can't retain any
information, it just gives the output, and then
drops the whole thing, so there is no
AI, just a more advanced algorithm, so somebody
was testing what you had to say there,
and I wanted to let you know, and
networking, and it came about, I don't remember
in the heydays of the internet, there was
a lot of talk about that, that's when
Snowden, that was the heydays of the internet,
when Snowden was in the news, that was
the end of the heyday, right, yeah, the
end, remember all that stuff, that they're spying
on us, and whatever, I actually looked up
what the, what was disclosed, the, versus what
everybody was talking about, what was disclosed is,
now they finally have enough computational power and
memory to make a transcript of everything, right,
what they're doing is, every phone conversation, no
one's listening to anything, I shouldn't say that,
but what's really happening is, transcripts are being
made of everything, transcripts of all your transactions,
your movements, your, in other words, your map,
you know, have you ever seen the maps
in Wile E.
Coyote, but anyway, all your conversations, your emails,
transcripts are being made in a file, like
just like years ago, that was it, what
do you say, 99% of US citizens
have an FBI file, right, was it something
like 87%, 97%, I don't know, whatever, you
get it, yeah, there was, so it's a
very high number, proportion, right, some people, like,
they don't know how to label you, but,
but now it's 100%, yeah, now it's 100%,
because the fact is that the, the goal
of the NSA, which was stated, was to
capture every conversation they could, so they did
that, by transcript, yeah, no one's, yeah, and
that was the thing, though, but back then,
people said, oh, that's radio, that's telephone, that's,
yeah, but that has now gone further into
the rest of it, so that's everything now,
yeah, that's all it is, they bottlenecked, they
bottlenecked everybody into using a device that, that,
look, recently, I hate the voicemail thing, recently,
the voicemail shows up as a text message
now, yeah, right, and voicemail, you can hear,
why, because they're trying to tell you, hey,
look, this is what we're doing, look, pay
attention, I'm fine with it, because, whatever, not,
well, I'm not fine with it, because it's
not going to be used right, but if
you know your rights, you can make sure
that it's being used right, because you signed
them, your permissions to do that indirectly, it's
always indirect, but what I just want to
bring up, we brought up the, I dropped
an article, by the way, speaking of reading,
in the Ocelli, it's called, I think, ocellianthegreekchitango
.com, it's an NIH document on the history
of glucose measurement, blood glucose measurement, and that's
how you catch these assholes in telling you
the truth, well, Greek, why would you call
them assholes, telling you the truth, always look
up the, how many times you heard me
say, if you, in order to understand a
thing, you have to know the history of
that thing, right, yeah, I mentioned once, there
were some young twins always watching TV, and
they thought, I asked them how long the
TV's been around, they thought it was around
since the dinosaurs, right, they didn't know the
history, it's a recent development, so, but I
put that article up, and whoever can read
it with comprehension, you go ahead and read
that and tell me that there is such
a thing as blood glucose measurement, there isn't,
it's an attempt, so, yeah, and this goes
on and on and on and on with,
when you read what's going on, and you've
got to know your rights, by the way,
just like I've said many, many times, there's,
I assure you, no one in prison right
now, today, is there lawfully or legally, no
one, because if you know what lawful and
legal is, you wouldn't be in prison, oh,
by the way, I did find that Judge
Bork interview on PBS, the confirmation, with senator
questions and all that stuff, and they spoke,
the part when they asked him, what are
you going to do about the growing prison
population, he said, I'm not going to do
anything, because everyone in prison has volunteered to
be there, they dubbed the hosts of PBS
speaking over that, so you can't get it,
you can see his mouth moving, but you
don't hear it, so, shucks, wonder why they
did that, wonder why, I'm sure that was
just an editorial decision, you know, for the
sake of appearances, you know, right, oh my
gosh, yeah, aesthetics only, yeah, aesthetics, right, that's
what I was looking for, aesthetics, correct word,
thank you, hey, here's another interesting question, a
question to the Greek about living lawfully and
separately yourself, uh, discernment, okay, bank account, uh,
that would be unlawful, does the Greek have
a bank account, now, I know you've answered
this, it wouldn't be unlawful, it wouldn't be
unlawful, no, but go ahead, well, I knew
you answered the does the Greek have a
bank account question before, no, right, uh, but,
so, it's not unlawful for you to have
a bank account, no, it's not, it's just
like it's not unlawful to go and sell
heroin in your neighborhood, well, no, it's illegal,
it's illegal, but that's only because you can't
pay the taxes on it, um, there's no
law that, yeah, there's no law, well, you
shouldn't have to pay taxes if you were
born in the USA, anyway, on anything, and
that can be proven out, your passport makes
you tax exempt, by the way, if you're
a national, but, um, if you have a
passport, you know, they bring something up, and
you give them the passport, you say you're
tax exempt, they give them the number and
name of organizations, the name on there, and
it takes off the taxes every time, so,
but here's the deal, there's no, um, unlawfulness
on growing, selling, or processing anything that grows
on an animal or a plant to anyone,
well, nothing unlawful on that at all, ever,
but is it illegal, in a lot, many
cases, in a lot of places, with certain
things, yeah, so, yeah, the reason I don't
do it is because I don't, it's like,
okay, let's do our banking, let's go find
the Zeta cartel, it's a cartel, all right,
and I can't sleep at night knowing that,
uh, what I signed on to as terms
and service, terms and conditions, and they don't
want to change it the way I want
it done, no, they don't, what I want
them to do is, I want to hold
them to 12 U.S.C. 1431, go
ahead, pull that up, 12 U.S.C.
1431, Chuck, 12 U.S.C. 1431, pull
that up, and read it, just the first,
like, 30 words, or 20 words, oh, yeah,
no, I just said, I think I know
that one verbatim, had to pull up a
browser real quick, so I think I know
that one verbatim, all right, that's fine, no,
I know that one verbatim, but I'd rather,
it's got more impact when you read it,
okay, if you say so, uh, let's see,
okay, so, 12 U.S.C. code, uh,
funny signo thing there, uh, 1431, yeah, section
1431, powers and duties of banks, that's what
you want, yeah, yeah, okay, borrowing money, keep
reading, 20 words, A, borrowing money, issuing bonds,
and debentures, general powers, each federal home loan
bank shall have power, subject to rules and
regulations prescribed by the director, to borrow and
give security, therefore, and to pay interest thereon,
to issue debentures, bonds, or other obligations upon
such terms and conditions as the director may
approve, uh, good, that's it, you could stop
there, because it just continues with more, a
list, laundry list of the same, right, but
if you were to, if you were to
break that down, the powers and duties of
the bank is essentially to borrow money and
pay interest, debentures are unsecured, unsecured instruments, like
credit cards and stuff like that, similar, so
where does it say, but you could keep
reading the thing, and they'll give you a
thousand dollars every time it says they give
loans, you know why, I still have that
thousand dollars, and I always will, because it
doesn't say anywhere that they have the power
to loan anything, how many times have you
seen a billboard, we lend money, how many
people have said, I went in banking, got
a loan, you did a big switcheroo, right,
it's right, so why would you want to,
yeah, now here's the thing, I go and
speak to the banks, and I'm like, I
need to speak to your senior banker, oh
yeah, okay, come in on this day, going
on that day, and they give you the
senior banker, he doesn't know what the hell
you're talking about, I said, who's your senior
banker, oh well, he'd be in on this,
you know, you got to go to this
other branch, I go to that branch, and
he doesn't know what I'm talking about, who's
your senior banker, and they give me an
address, it's an office building, whatever, and then
completely outside of a regular bank setting, and
you go talk to him, and all he's
interested in is how many people you talked
about these things or asked prior, and he
doesn't even know what you're talking about, because
they don't, he knows a little bit of
it, a little bit, he wants to, he
was so curious of how many people I
brought this up with prior in his organization,
do you think you're going to be working
for the IRS or bank for whatever, 30
bucks an hour, I don't know what they're
paying, I don't know, if you know how
the hell the money system works, you can't
sit there in good conscience and work there,
no, I couldn't, right, so anyway, it's not
unlawful, what they're doing is even legal, because
you agree to it, constitution says there'll be
legislature will make no law that interferes in
the agreements of contracts, but they're doing a
lot more than just making a contract, but
anyway, well, go on, what's the question, I
don't even think we breached the question, oh,
well, back to it, let me see if
I can get it, I was doing other
things here, yeah, let me see, where is
it, Greece said, what's a pocket selling in,
no, no, that's the wrong one, hold on,
I know it's here, it's in one of
these, let's see, that's fine, let's do another
one, and we'll come up to it again,
okay, well, this is the only, this is
like the last one that I had in
mind, anyway, I wanted to see if we
could end with this, because this is a
little bit of a winding road, Old Testament,
King Nebuchadnezzar was cast into the wilderness and
became as a wild beast eating grass, because
he didn't recognize the Most High, and the
Most High said that he controls the affairs
of men and all the kingdoms of the
earth.
In the New Testament, Satan takes up Yeshua
up to the highest mountain and shows him
all the kings of the earth, and Satan
said to Yeshua, worship me, and I'll give
you all these kingdoms, are we dealing with
two entities that rule the affairs of men
and control kingdoms?
Two entities, the same office, if you look
at the New Testament Christ says, I'll protect
you from the evil one, one who does
evil, if you look in Jeremiah, Yahweh says,
has evil ever fallen on a city that
I have not brought?
Yeah, they're the same one, essentially, it's the
same office.
In the book of Job, in Yahweh's counsel,
who do they see walking around, and they
ask him, what are you doing?
Who, who do they see?
Satan, right, yeah, he's hanging out, same office,
like the bankers, right, or whatever, so, yeah,
you got a problem with that?
Now, most people will say, well, that sounds
like Satanism, then, no, it's not, and you
should understand, like, for example, Satanism is in
the same category as Christianity, what a joke,
what a joke, you know, Christianity is a
joke, by the way, right, it's a joke,
it's the kind of joke that doesn't even
have a punchline that people sit around and
listen to, right, Satanism is the opposite of
Christianity, they'll tell you that, yeah, they make
a little more sense, actually, I don't endorse
that, because it's dumb, just like Christianity is
dumb, I mean, really dumb, and it's actually
dumb, which is like, you know, third level,
so, but it's there to flag you, once
you pick one of these religions, they know
that they don't have to invest in a
control apparatus anymore, and you cannot pose a
threat model that they can't overcome, right, so,
no, I would say that once you understand
the office of the Most High, you understand,
because look, let's go back and let's massage
this, right, the fallen angels, why are they
fallen?
Because they left their original habitation, what was
that?
Right?
So, it's a political thing, if you're politically
favorite, you're a good god or an angel,
if you're politically, you did something that made
you politically unpopular, right, you're a demon, so,
yeah, stay away from politics.
Yeah, that's what they do now, I mean,
there's, you know, no longer any nuance at
all in political discourse, it's just, nope, they're
the enemy, they're evil, that's it.
Well, just like John C.
Lilly said, he said, don't get into the
super pleasurable, because then it'll grab you, and
you want to keep doing it, right, because
it's pleasurable, and don't get into the really
negative shit, because it's just negative, right, it's
just destructive.
Somewhere in the middle, there's a Buddhist principle
on that, or some ancient philosophical principles, in
Greek, parmetro ariston, like median, be in the
middle, and do it well, and then you
can, right, so, yeah, I think people, I
think I've given enough on this stuff, you
know, like people, I'm a Yahwehist, right, I
do use those laws, because any law you
want to follow on the surface of the
earth is based on that Old Testament stuff,
or similar to, right, so, if you understand
law, you know your rights, right, then you
can operate here, and when you have to
apply force, you know why you're applying force,
because everything else has been exhausted, right, so
I think it's worthwhile knowing those things, but
I never said Yahweh was a good guy,
I never did, when did you ever hear
me say that, right, I just know the
rules.