Sonic Event 44 and here we go, straight to the chat and straight to everything else,
Grieg, I know you're in an interesting mood tonight.
I love it when you're in an interesting mood.
Anyways, let's get straight to it though.
Some people were asking about certain times and I guess a time of atonement might have
just went by.
this was what somebody mentioned in the chat.
By the way, moods, Frank Herbert book, dude, gurney, how like
moods off of children, women and child's play. So anyway, guys
like reading, dude, I think I paraphrase that might have
botched it up, but get it. No, no, I looked at the chat. It's
great that it's active. I like that stuff gets turned inside
out. I'd rather have it jumping around. I been I read some of
it. It's fine. You know, some people voice quote unquote
opinions stronger than others. And that's, that's all cool. I'd
rather have that than even keel lukewarm. What is it called
lukewarm? Right? So, well, it gets pretty stupid when all you
hear is Oh, thanks. Thanks. Glad. Thanks. Great. That's not
all that. I mean, look, it's nice, but it's not how I
specifically tell people don't send me emails, thanking me
before it send me something else and you know, real, you
know, reciprocation. Or don't tell me this stuff is great
because I already know that otherwise I wouldn't be saying
it. Oh my gosh, the Greeks got such a high opinion of himself.
Oh my gosh, can I even hear that? It's not me at all. It's
just the reason I say the stuff I do is because it hasn't been
said or isn't being said. It's so blaringly obvious. Basically,
the whole thing is, if you're going to talk about a subject,
but what is no, what can be known about it conveniently, I'm not
saying be an expert on it, right? But have you as as anyone
in the population, at large, even conveniently, conveniently
look back, you know, at anything that they're talking about, you
know, in terms of what has been referenced or memorialized about
the subject? The answer is no. Right? Which I want to interject
something. I put stuff on the background archaics did a pretty
good video today about he doesn't really have a handle
because he thinks the king he well, doesn't have a handle on
the language and the culture and and other stuff that you guys
could see better in Greek speak. He did a pretty good video on
the Phoenix and the horsemen and all that. He's stretching it a
bit. But I, you know, again, I don't endorse.
No, I know. Just for a point of reference here. Pope's work
schedule. It's what the 15th of August, right? But what is the
actual day, by the way? Well, it's the it's the six month,
right? It's a six month. Yeah. It's about a day off. Yeah.
Okay. So yeah. Well, that's the seventh or eighth month,
according to the Pope's work schedule, but it's a six months
a day. In other words, right now, it's it's smack in the
middle of the month, like if you wanted to split hairs about
it, Monday, Tuesday, right, of August was the first at noon,
right? solar Monday at noon. Yeah, yeah. Or Yeah, Monday,
Tuesday, actually. Monday, Tuesday at noon, Tuesday at
noon, it was over. So it's so funny how you can't just say
that you have to give a denomination, right? So the
first day of the of the sixth month was between the 31st and
the first, right? Okay. The second day is between the first
and the second, I just tell people, if you have the regular
calendar grid, just put a line in between, they actually give
you lines right where the boxes, you know, where one goes to two
and three goes to four, that that's noontime. Right? It's
like they almost do you see just count the lines between there,
right? Yeah. So so if you're looking, for example, on a
Sabbath, kind of idea, the Sabbath just finished at noon
today, right? So the Sabbath was between the 14th and the 15th. So
it's a day off really, sort of. It's it's every seven years, it
lines up pretty close for one month, by the way. It never
really lined up because it was three days off last month. Now
it's a day off. So it never really lines up very rarely,
right? Well, let me push this question, then what about
atonement and a time of atonement? Okay, it wasn't the
time of the holiday. Yeah, go ahead. The 10th day of the
seventh month, 10th day, the seventh month, so that hasn't
come up trick or treating. Okay. You know, I mean, that's
wait, wait, wait, Greek, you could. Well, actually, I went to
a dollar store recently, and I got Halloween stuff up. Yeah,
yeah, of course. How is that possible? It's isn't it like the
end of October, but yet, you know, they keep doing that
earlier and earlier. Now, you know, yeah, it's one of those.
So what I mean, that's why I brought that up. Yeah. Now, now
there's a real hard thing about the other side of the world, you
almost have to do double time on that. Because this seems to be
very agricultural based. The reasoning behind the first month
is the what's happening in agriculture, right? And the
lower half of the world is is backwards in winter. So I
suggested that when their spring comes, that's their first month.
But actually, in terms of like, for time for the what events
happen in the world, it's going to have to go from this part of
the world, you see. So for example, if you're living in
Australia, right? It's the 11th month, or it's the sixth month.
Right? Just in other words, you would take up for our time. But
because it's the 11th, you see, they're going through winter,
right? So in other words, when they they do Christmas in
Australia, it's suntan oil and going to the beach and ice
cream, right? It's the middle of summer, right? Well, since your
law is partially based on the conditions, I mean, obviously,
you can't have a law ascribed to something, they can't tell you to
grow things when it's the dead of winter, lawfully.
It's no, no, you could you do is winter, right? No, no. Okay,
there's, there's stuff that I've come up with, because it's it
follows the logic and the reasoning in a text, right? So
if you have a book on electricity, or an electrician's
handbook, okay, let's sign an electrician's handbook, what
electricians do, right? Okay. And so as you're going through
this book, you see things, if you just page open to a page and
read it, it's sort of going to be out of context, if you don't
know the preface, or the premise of the book, right? Right, you
have to, right? Because like, imagine you have an
electrician's handbook, and you just open it and start reading
it. Yeah, no kidding. It's not going to make a lot of sense.
But you have to remind yourself, this is an electrician's
handbook here. It's talking about number eight wire needs to be
stripped this way. And you have to get this kind of, but what the
hell is number eight wire? It's no, it doesn't really define
maybe in the appendix, maybe it's not in here. You see, so
the context of these things are cultural, they're scriptural as
such religious in a way, yes, because you do it regularly. But
I want to just instead of getting into this, I'm glad,
you know, we, I had a feeling we're going to be focusing on
the chat. Now, here's the thing I'd like to say, and I'm going
to keep giving an analogy. And then I'm going to get to the
point. Here's an analogy, like I do this with the wife, it never
works. I do this with other people. It never really works
very rarely. And this is what it is. You ordered what's called a
flat pack piece of furniture. It's more than a piece of
furniture. It's something that has a device built into it,
right? Okay, flat pack is like Ikea, you know, you look at
stuff, and it looks like nice in the catalog or pleasant in the
catalog, and you go to buy it, it's in a flat box, you got a
lot of assembly to do, right? Okay. And then there are things
that, you know, you get four or five boxes, like if you order a
roll top desk on Amazon, a given example, this is a, there's
something like that, or utility, kind of industrial kind of work
table. Okay. And it's got all these other parts to it. Well,
everything comes in boxes, flats, all the drawers are flat,
it's each drawer has to be assembled each day, you know,
the mechanisms are to be assembled, and the whole thing
has to be assembled. And the whole thing has to be assembled
again, because it takes, you know,
yeah, you put together the drawers, and you put together
the tracks, then you put together the sides and slide the drawers
in. Yeah, of course, right. Yeah. But what if it has other
contraptions inside that articulate? Okay, so this is the
this is what never works. And I've been doing this for decades.
When it because this is before the flat pack phenomenon. But
I've done it with other things that required instructions or
whatever, like cars or whatever. You're with two or three people,
let's just make it simple. I'm with someone else. We've got
this as a project. So I take the instruction manual, and I cut it
in half. If it's 10 pages, I take the first five pages, and
I give the second person page five to 10. I said, Okay, I'll
read the first half, you read the second half, and we just
separate the parts. So I'll build everything that's in the
first five pages, and you build everything or getting in the
last half, and then we'll meet in the middle. Yeah, having done
this, I already know why it doesn't work. But it doesn't
work at all. But you have to do it in a way where, you know,
they don't overlap, right? Yeah, no, this is the section. So So
in other words, what ends up happening is, whoever is working
with me stands, there's looking at me asking questions all the
whole time, or can't figure out what they agreed to do. And, but
here's the part where that really pisses me off.
Because they're part of the book, in fairness, they're part
of the book already says, Look, take the take the completed
drawer and do this with it. And you're like, Well, you got to
complete.
That's that would be the presumption you do need to spin.
You can't just randomly cut it in half. Well, but that's what
you need to spend a few minutes. But here, this is what pisses me
off. Okay. So I'm working on the side that I've agreed to do and
the other person's supposed to be working on the other side. And
when I go over, all right, I'll take a pause because nothing's
happening. And by the way, they tell you, you're in trouble. If
it tells you the assembly time is two and a half hours, it's more
like six hours, right? Right? Because remember, unpacking and
all that and finding laying out all this stuff, right? Yeah,
right. Okay. So I go to the other what the other person's
supposed to be doing. And it's just already there. And all I
start doing is let's see your problem. Okay, I don't know,
don't why you're asking me I'm this is foreign to me. It's in
the manual, right? So we go back to the instructions. And we look
and I say, well, the question you're asking me is right here.
When you have everything you need right there. So what's it?
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah, that's right. Right. And then it goes
on. So it's like, okay, let's put them out. Let's just work
together. You hit, you know, whoever, right? Okay. So now
instead of having parallel production, it's one person with
a helper. And half the time, the helper doesn't have a lot to do
they start losing interest, and they don't follow what you're
doing. And they're not much of a helper. So that makes any sense,
right? No, well, that's not like you're doing heart surgery, you
have two nurses handing you an implements, because usually what
happens, you go, look, I got to assemble these six things before
I can put them into the woods. So do you put them those
together, and I'll work on something else. And then yeah,
by the time you get back to it, it's like, did you put those
together yet? Or someone, here's another analogy, someone
sends me a link regarding an event or something. And I'll ask
later on, I'll ask about it was all in the link. I said, Well,
why don't you How about this when you send a link on the
internet? Okay, don't be so super lazy. I understand that
you just copy and paste and whatever. That's okay. I get
that. But go ahead and type out the most important thing why I
should watch it or what's important in that, right? You
get it? Go ahead. And if you care about me enough to send me
a link, why don't you show that you care a little bit more. And
say at this time here at this time marker or something. This
is an important part of the video, right? So guide me along
a little. Okay.
You know why I'm laughing? You know why I'm laughing, though?
Because I do show notes all the time. And I put a headline over
the links. I don't just usually give you a bunch of links. And
I do show notes, I put a link and I put a headline or the
important part of what you
this is not about. These are just analogies. I'm giving here
on things that I've been noticing. Oh, yeah. But screw
the analogy. I'm telling you, I do this. And then I still get
people mail to me. Where is this? And I'm like, did you read
we have, we have a human problem. Yes. Okay. So so the
analogy here is that any subject matter is the same. Right? It's
the same formula. Like a lot of times I'll, I'll ride someone on
something. I mean, my riding them. It's like, it's called
yelling at someone right about whatever, right? And I hate
riding people that way. That's a street term. You don't think I
like riding you like this, you know? People keep asking and
I'm very generous with my time and my effort, whatever. But when
I start seeing that it's beyond the subject matter, and it has
nothing to do with the subject matter, but has to do with basic
function. Now, we have to start weeding things out, which leads
to the next point. Now we'll get more of the juicy stuff. So
spiritual, everyone still is stuck in this thing about
spiritual. So when you look at some of the definitions that
I've put out, actually, heaven forbid, you look at the
definitions that are put out by others on spirit, soul and body,
because it's, they're just following the confusion, right?
Yeah. And sidestepping. You know, it's like 911. Oh, yeah.
Yeah, it was a weapon from space. Yeah. But you know, I
could be a technical witness. In other words, if I went to a
court, I could be a technical witness and sit at the stand and
tell you technically exactly what happened, just like you
know, the higher technical witnesses for in court, right?
I can do that for 911. I could tell you exactly what happens
with the atomic or nuclear demolition that was thermonuclear
everything to look for. So I had to be that right? Technically,
I could do it any day of the week, even in my sleep, but
people still insist that it's a space weapon or dynamite on all
the floors, which is impossible and all that stuff, right? So so
there's that aspect to it. So what I mean about definitions,
I've gotten to the point where I've been a technical witness to
the definitions of spirit, soul and body. But it sounds easy to
break up those three things into three compartments very neat and
tidy. But this is the but when you describe someone when you
judge someone when you interact with someone when you have a
feeling for someone, that is mostly with their spirit. When
you hear someone say something when you see someone's behavior,
when you have someone approach you or depart from you, that is
mostly their spirit animating all that. The part of the soul
that is animating it is basically are they breathing and
walk and as their heart beating and their nervous system and
elimination working and metabolism working and the body
well, the big but again, anyway, did I say big but okay, but the
body part? Yeah, the big but but right, yeah. Okay, the body is
the butt, right? Anyway, is the body and that has a strong
effect also, but it has effect on what your spirit and then
your body, right? So the majority of interactions that people have
actually animals even more in some cases, right? Is with
someone else's spirit. What someone says what someone does
what someone how someone behaves, how they dress that
morning, and how they how much cologne or how little cologne
or they put on is based on their spirit, their mind. So when
people say they want to have a spiritual discussion, or talk
about the spirit, if I'm in a mood, certain mood, and I say,
Hey, moron, right? Am I addressing their body? Am I
addressing their heartbeat? Or am I addressing their spirit?
When I say that their mind, you see, I think on some level, it's
coming from a place where you're interpreting all of that
combined. And it's about your reaction to that. No, no, no,
listening. No, I'm not listening. Okay. The spirit. Okay, if you
look at the body, the butt, anyway, and if you look at the
soul, which is the metabolism, literally, at this point, we can
have people that are all comatose, laying down, imagine a
football, a big room with 1000 beds, and everyone's not hooked
up to IVs, but they're all sleeping or in a coma. They have
a functioning soul, because they're alive and breathing,
right? No, the metabolism is working, and they have a body.
Does that make it more clear? You see? Now, anything else
beyond being comatose or catatonic or asleep? Right? You
get it is a reaction to the spirit, and driven by the
spirit. I hope that made it more clear. I can't I don't know, I
could I'm trying to think of stronger analogies. So the
analogy here is this anything, anything, any form of
communication between two beings, appearances, again, judgments,
desires, repulsions, repugnance, hatred, love, everything you can
imagine interacting with something, someone else is a
spiritual interaction. So when people say, Well, I'll talk
about the spirit. I'm like, Okay, let's go the other way. What is
not spiritual? Well, if it if it's deciding on how do we make
a description of 1000s of people laying down asleep or in a coma
that are still alive, that would be the only thing that would
solely basically encompass the soul and the body. The moment
there's animation, and distinct personality and distinct
behavior, or even if they all act, you know, what is it called
synchronistic swimming or synchronically cheerleaders use
synchronous actions, right? Yes, you're synchronistic. So you can
have synchronistic actions also, right? That is all spiritual.
And otherwise, it's driven by the mind. Give me an example. Let's
say the the synchronous, what do they call those things? pom poms
that they move the cheerleaders, they do the kick does, you know,
they do a dance. So synchronous routine. Sure. routine. Okay.
Let me ask, let me say this. If one of their souls and body
become corrupt, let's say one of them suddenly has an epileptic
fit. Right? That is so overcoming to the spirit that
they that will they'll just collapse and fall over like a lot
of these vaccine videos are players. They don't know why
they're dying suddenly, right? kind of thing. The body and the
soul are overcome. They no longer no longer functions and the
spirit can no longer function. Again, it goes back to the
original definition. So when people want to have a spiritual
discussion, tell me what is not spiritual. Basically, it's
people in a coma or sleeping. So when you say you want to have a
spiritual discussion, the only thing that gets ruled out of
that, as people that are in a coma or sleeping, everything
else is included. Holy crap.
Sounds to me like everything that involves interaction is
therefore spiritual. Yeah.
And I've been saying this for the longest time. And years ago,
when I started interacting with people on the internet, and
well, specifically, they bring up, oh, he's so spiritual. I'm
like, that doesn't tell me. But spiritually, in a good way, bad
way. What? What do you mean? It's a good thing to be
spiritual. I said, Well, demons are spiritual.
Yeah, that's a very dumb dad. Exactly. It's a very dumb dad.
That's like saying you're very political. So what does that
mean? You know, it means nothing business of the state. Yeah,
it's the business of the state. Right. But that's but you give
me no idea about the character of the individual when you say
they're political. You know what I'm saying? You have no idea
what it is they're actually involved in or what it is.
So it's very so I don't know, I feel like this. You know, this
is like something where you need to shotgun it. You know, I don't
know if you guys have been around hunting. You go out with
someone hunting and even if they're 20 feet away, and they
have a shotgun rifle to depending on the caliber, then
they shoot it. And you're not ready for it. Oh, crap. It's
just really shocks you. Right? It's just so it's, yeah, it's
power. It's very dynamic, right? Like you've been near a car, two
cars crashing at speed, you know, stuff like that. And this
kind of stuff needs to be transmitted that way. So it
sticks. And what it does is it raises the person's
consciousness of their awareness of everything that they're doing
around them. Now, I don't know how to emphasize it. If you want
to emphasize it, can you give a key? Do you want to take the
credit? I'm going to toss it over to you. Well, I'm on the
subject. How would you describe? No, that that that sounds great.
And look, to say that it's just you know, a spiritual that that
is too general. Again, it is not a specific thing. Like I said,
political. So, you know, when you were or the idiotic
compliment given where somebody says you're, you're very
intellectual, you know, give another analogy regarding the
spirit, because it's basically the mind and anything that the
mind is guiding and behavior or community or anything is the
spirit this right? Well, there's no way to separate those two
things. So the mind and the spirit, it is the same thing.
It's like kind of can you separate them two equals to how
do you separate the two? Well, that's what I'm saying. It's
like, exactly. Look, you can't separate these things. They're
not separate components. Well, it's just different words for the
same thing psyche, right? There you go. psychological PSY
prefix is the spirit. And they've just split they've,
they've, it's this has always been done. This has been done
throughout history, where all you got to do is mess up the
definitions, right? Well, pranks are based on that, right?
When you're going to prank someone, right? Of course, the
prank, the actual prank itself, right, is a duality that is not
recognized as such. It's recognized, you know, here's a
chair, and there's a thumbtack on it, right? You don't know, you
didn't say here's a chair with a thumbtack. Did you? No, you
just said, here's a chair.
No, you let them run into the problem. It's just like throwing
the firecracker in the crowd is same kind of thing.
Where the other day I was a woman says, Have a nice day. So
you do, by the way, there's no ticket, it's a time to check
out. Do you know what the word nice means? She had to look at
she looked it up. I said, Look it up. You have a stupid
rectangle. So what's that? Oh, my gosh, you've been a victim of
it then. Anyway, she looks it up. It takes me like, oh, quite a
while to walk her through Adam. She reads it. Because Oh, that's
very interesting. Well, have a nice day anyway.
etymology. So she goes to etymology online and looks at
it. And it basically, you know, is
sending so many people there. Now they're starting to put the
geography on the stupid rectangle. They put the
geography for nice the place, right? Yeah, France, right. They
put that first to kind of throw people off, you know, good. All
right. So. So here's the thing about that. All right, let's
jump over to the gods. Let's jump over. Let's make a jump
here. Okay, so
want to spend two hours repeating,
I'm sorry, I'm not gonna let you but I'm not gonna let you get
away without addressing the word atonement. But go ahead, go to
the gods. Because just look it up. It's actually keep putting
which means to cover in the Hebrew, the word is kippur, which
means to cover. I don't think atonement is a really good
selection to translate.
Okay, well, that would be the reason why they use Yom Kippur
as the right for the name of the holiday.
Yeah, there you go. Kippur is a cover. Yeah. Okay. And it's a
cover like the cover of the box, you know, the Ark of the
Covenant, right? I probably just butchered which, by the way,
doesn't there is no image, public image of what is directed to be
built in the Bible in existence, by the way. I've never found
one. No, if you in other words, if you study how to build it,
make it draw have an eight year old or and then have a
professional artist, as you're giving the description of what
it should look like, they'll both come up with the same thing.
It's very simple. And you'll and then you'll look at the images
online and nothing looks like it. And you're like, well, is it
so easy to deceive people?
Yeah, none of the artists and none of the artists renderings
or whatever, are anywhere near what should be no, no, not at
all. Yeah. So okay, so yeah, let's let's drop the Day of
Atonement thing. I didn't see that up there. But okay, so
you brought it up enough. Let me just say something in terms of
timekeeping appointment times and all that. Let's say we're
going to be lawful in terms of the not in the strictest legal
sense. But let's say we're going to be lawful. Because when we say
that in these in this type of forum, let's say, with Greek
speak and stuff, I'm referring to biblical stuff. It could
also sometimes be other stuff. But it doesn't work when you go
out into the world. Because when you say lawful, they think
you're talking about the legal system, right? You know, which
is not lawful, right? And they tell you that it's awful. But
anyway, okay, so we're going to be lawful, even from a loose
point. I've been saying this for three decades. Now, I do not
really announce things that much, because I'm not a priest. That
was a priestly function. Okay, so let's dumb it down. Let's dumb
it down. Let's say we're Catholics. And this is a
Catholic forum. And we're talking about butts. No, anyway.
So not the first thing I look at personally. That's the word of
the night. Okay, so children's butts, of course, for the
Catholic priest. The cardinals. Yeah, yeah. Get it. Anyway.
Let's say we're talking about that. Am I fit to baptize? Am I
fit to give communion to Greek for talking about it? Am I in a
position to do that? Well, no. According to their creed? Yeah.
Right. Who does that? Right? The priest has to do that. Yeah,
right. So when when we're going to adhere, I'm not saying
dogmatically, I don't really get into Oh, it's the Sabbath. Oh,
it's this holiday. Oh, it's this. Well, you know, I'll
occasionally do that. I'd like to see what other people do with
it. Because I'm not a priest. And actually, I'm going to stand
that. Well, am I a teacher? Well, once you find the
principle, and all that now you can teach it. So if you can
teach it, why am I the teacher? You get it? Well, again, at any
given time, as we've discussed before, anyone can teach you
something even. And we get enough information from them
where you can teach it now. They're a teacher. So there's a
level here. It's kind of like splitting the instruction
manual and half thing again. Right. So here's the point. I'm
not adamant about doing these things. I do practice I do
observe, right? Because I've noticed there are very subtle
changes that happen when you do that. In other words, when you
when those appointed times and days come around, there are
changes in the natural world, believe it or not, that you can
focus on and spiritual, you know, the very subtle, subtle
doesn't mean weak, by the way, subtle could be strong. Okay, all
of the high level energetic work doesn't blow someone waves their
hands and knock someone down. With that power. It's subtle,
strength is not obvious at all points in time, you may not be
aware that somebody like you've seen the guy who doesn't look
like very much, but winds up being able to kick the hell out
of some bigger guy. And nobody knew that he had those skills
until right. So the reason why I observed the law and do all of
that is because in the beginning, three decades ago,
when I was made aware of it, I said, Well, how can I knock it if
I don't try it. And when I tried it, I saw it was subtle, but
powerful. So I decided to make it my law form, and the way I
function, but I'm not a priest in any capacity. Neither do I want
to be. Right. So that's why there is not now the rest of it,
there's no problem in discussing it as a forum. But when someone
comes to me with it, like I think Randy did about the months and
all that I said, it's really both and I have to think about
I've always brought it up. It's both because the the the the
world the alarm as it is in Hebrew works around that part of
the world where right now it's the nearing summer end of
summer, not quite but late part of summer, where the other part
of the world is in the late part of winter. So I would say that
world events and all that will be based around what's happening
up here, right versus down there. But because it's
agricultural, you're, you're, you're double timing it, right?
You see, you're gonna have to do both. I don't know there. It's
never been addressed. And I can't again, I think that would
be a priestly call. Right. So, okay. So
it seems to me it could be equally logical that in that
part of the world, it just the world flows differently. Okay.
And therefore, events could be it's, it's reverse. Yeah. So
it's viewed in that way. So therefore, you know, this may be
the time when harvest has already occurred and all that
stuff, because it's winter, it's winter. So the end of winter
renting, entering probably the Yeah, it's not spring is about
more than a month away. That's why I've never been dissatisfied
with the title of pagan because I assert myself as someone who
was doing his best to be ignorant. No, it's all believe
believe it or not, it's all the same. It's just what level
you're functioning on. Right. But I am doing my best to adhere
to the world around me. Now, if I was in Australia, I would do
my best to adhere to that, you know? Well, no, it's what level
you're operating. Okay, it's for example, like a pagan knows you
shouldn't murder, right? Someone who's a biblical lawful, you
know, as you shouldn't murder. Well, why did why did they both
know the same thing? Somehow? The ones that pay any other ones
that was just different levels. Well, even if you don't know how
to read, you may be aware that there is a book that says you
shouldn't do that. And you might be aware that it's not a good
thing to do. Yeah, but it also gives you a lot of other reasons
on what happens if you do and how to remedy and yeah, pagans
don't have that. And they might do an extent depending on what
level you want to see my posture isn't even about it's wrong to
murder. It's wrong to do harm. You're not supposed to seek to
do harm. That's all there is to it. Harm is not something you
should be seeking to do. This is not your place in the world.
Okay, that that is as simple as I can bring it down from a pagan
philosophy. And that that is accurate to me, don't harm. And
that covers all that other stuff. You see if you steal, I
guess, but what I'm saying is, it's different operates on
different levels. Okay, maybe I'm operating on a technical
Yeah, well, maybe I'm operating on a very, you know, limited
level there, but I still stand by it. Because I mean, not you,
but that's typically what I seen. And now if we went back or
in private circles, paganism is very different. I got pretty
familiar with a lot of the practices. And there were not
really that difficult from biblical, it's just but the
direction was different. Okay, so let's get into the gods.
Let's get into the gods real quick. And okay, so when you say
the gods, that's a various sundry term, a various garden variety
term, very garden variety term. So specifically, you'll see
there are various various pantheons, right? Throughout
throughout history. And there haven't been too many pantheons
created recently. I mean, in the past 2000 years, not
officially, no, there's no official canonized sort of like
here it is the pantheon of because supposedly, we're in a
time of the individual, the singular God. Well, there might
be sort of religion religions that have been created, like
from Muhammad, peace be upon him. After that, but I wouldn't
consider that a pantheon because it actually refers, by the way,
in the Quran, I think Syria 26 or 28. It says that if you want
to know the law of Allah, it's was given to Moses. Yeah. So how
many Muslims put the Quran down right there and then go read? You
get my point, right? Okay, so
now some of them do exactly that.
None of them. I've never run into anyone who's done that.
I'm not saying some, there might be some Yeah, it's like, but
it's some like, you know, they when you buy orange juice, they
got oranges, then they got oranges with pulp, and then they
got oranges with some pulp. Anyway. Okay. I had to
trivialize it. So it's fine. It's fine. It's Yeah, you get it.
Get the point. That would be something in the middle. The the
not Pope, Pope. But anyway, various sundry, various sundry
gods and all in the pantheons. Okay. So here's the point. How
do you make a judgment? Well, the ones giving you the most
information are probably the more higher order ones. And the
ones that give you the least information are the opposite of
higher, right? Very, very simple. Now, I don't believe in
any of this. Right? I've come to the point where I begin to
know what's been memorialized, whether it's actually done or
written by Moses, or this was fake or that way. That's okay.
I know the text doesn't matter. It's like if you want to have if
you want it, someone wants to say that it's fictional, and
whatever it says, that's okay. So if we have a discussion on
Moby Dick, we really can't unless we read the book by
Melville, right? So do we want to argue that we can have a
discussion on Moby Dick without knowing anything that was
written by Melville? Can we can we do that? Should we do that?
Would that even sound right? No, it doesn't. Right? Well, it
doesn't accomplish much. That's for sure. You actually, that's
the whole world is functioning on that premise, by the way. So
so I found the there's lawful stuff in the Bible, the guides
and histories and things that pan out, they pan out reality,
if you do them, and you study it, right. So that's where I'm
at with that. Right? It's it's better than what in the 80s. Oh,
red meat is bad. Here's pork, the other white meat, right. And
then it was that it was all grilling is bad for your causes
because shit carcinogen, you know, cancer carcinogens, right
in the charcoal.
He everybody drink a gallon of milk, every everybody drink a
gallon of milk a day. Oh, wait, don't drink the milk. Oh, wait,
eat, eat 20 eggs a day. Oh, wait, don't eat eggs. Yeah, I
know all that.
Yeah, I'm not gonna Yeah, I realize that's a farce. And by
the way, you know, I think I brought this up before you drink
you drink, you take dairy products, some people could be a
piece of cheese causes depression in humans, by the
way. I wouldn't say that emphatically. But now that I've
said that, and if you can remember that pay attention, do
you hear about people being depressed? So yeah, on a side
note, do you consume dairy? How much dairy do you consume? Oh, my
gosh, you're gonna be shocked to find out.
Well, anytime I get tired is always when I've consumed either
a some dairy or be some bird.
I'm talking about the psychological aspect of what
people say, I'm depressed, you know, I'm feeling, you know,
low energy, the world sucks, this and that, right?
My association with being tired.
The psychological aspect of label, which is all whatever,
but I'm just saying, right, right. Because that's still a
big deal. What that was a big deal in the 90s, depression,
number of pills and all that. So of course, 2000s also. So I
function on that level. And I consider myself normal, the high
functioning human, right? I mean, above normal, high
functioning. And I think anyone can be it's just a choice. And
it takes extra work. It's just like if you go to the gym, you
have high funk people that are high functioning in the gym. And
you got people that are not so high functioning, right? It's
very simple, right? You know, you play tennis, this guy's really
high function, right? Look at your ass, right? If you play
them, right? And there are people that are not so high, but
because they just need to practice more, spend more time,
you see, that's what I mean by that. So this is the whole
aspect of everything. So let's say we have a discussion like
we've had on whatever various topics, even when it gets rude,
crass, and lascivious, guess what, if it has anything to do
with people behaving in any way talking, or doing anything at
all, that is a guess what, this type of discussion, it's a
spiritual discussion. You want to discuss what you saw on TV
last night, on cable, whatever. Guess what? That's a spiritual
discussion. All of it is spiritual, although it's rather
shallow, because you're not actually interacting with an
individual, you're actually interacting with the
representation of an individual, and therefore things shift a
little bit. But still, it's a shallow spiritual discussion,
right? Yep. So here, let's go back to the gods. I haven't seen
any gods around lately, tell me they're gods or anybody with a
t shirt, I'm a god. No, the only thing that I can interact with
that is the information based on how I should live my life, and
tell others if they want, if they want to hear it, right? If
they want to hear it. And, and I never tout the benefits of it.
Never, because it's not about winning or losing or benefiting
or worsening oneself. It's a it's a choice that you make based
on how you want to function. I find personally, there are
benefits to it much more. The benefit for me is you have a
very well organized system that actually works. You know, so
let's go back to the gods. There are various sundry guys. I mean,
I mean, there's got to be at least 10 Jesus's, right? I don't
even like using that word. I mean, maybe I know there's like
three or four major Jesus's, right? Okay. None of them are
biblical, by the way, you know, the one that, you know, if you
don't follow me, you're gonna burn in hell, the one with the
bleeding heart. The other one that says everything's been done
away with the blood of the lamb, right? Okay. If you don't believe
in me, whatever, you know, this is so many different types. They
got the black one, right? They got the white one. They got the
Middle Eastern one, they got the one with dirty blonde blue eyes,
the one with curly brown, brown eyes on Hollywood, right? So
which one is none of them, right? And when you say God, I
say dog, I mean, either way, because you're not saying
anything. When you say that there's a you have to be more
specific, more specific. Yeah. So on that case, it would be our
way of the Bible. Now he's got a lot of friends, he's got a lot
of enemies. So that's your pick. That's what you what you're
going to do, who's your deity, right? So it's very simple. But
there are so many of them. And I ain't running into any of them
lately. But what's interesting is that on whatever level you
want to function, you're going to need an operating system,
some programs and files to run off of, right. And if you don't
have someone, you'll get them. Even if you don't have them,
you'll still get them, you just will be it'll be unawares,
right. So in essence, what I have to say about the gods is
very simple. When you approach the subject, of whether it's a
pantheon or a single God, what are they providing for you in
terms of instruction, let's say there are higher functioning than
humans are. So don't you want to kind of kick back something to
the lower creatures, you know, the humans about, hey, this is
about, you know, this is how you eat, this is how you do this,
this is how you do that. Right. And if you look at the gods, see
who's kicking information, what are they trafficking in? Right?
What are they selling you? What are they giving you? That's
that's it. Basically, that's the entire discussion. You know, the
you know,
well, the weird thing is that, honestly, though, and to my
horror, I discover over the years that people hear exactly
what they want to. And it is usually they only hear the
things that they want to hear. It doesn't matter necessarily
what you've said, what you've tried to impart, what you've
tried to combine into a discussion. It can be most
profound when you've said very little, because they heard it
that way.
Well, that's just like sex, the type of sex and how much sex and
who to have sex and this and that is all based on how you were
raised. And the culture that you live in. Right. And even if
they want to hear what they want to hear, that word want is
kind of funky, because they're actually told what they should
want. Think about it. Right? Look at children. When you ask, I
don't know, let's say, girls between six and 12. Ask them
what they want. I bet you 99% of the time, it's something that is
in vogue, trendy, whatever that's targeting that age group
in the kids culture at the moment. 99% of the time. Most
right. No one's gonna find a six to nine or 12 year old girl
say, ask her what he wants. I want a unicorn or I want a pink
elephant. Never. It's always going to be something that they
saw. That was pushed to them. Right. So how do they know when
they say I want this particular doll or this particular
fashionable whatever shirt? How do they know about that? How do
they how do they know that they want that? Well, it was what they
found about right? It was pushed up.
So it was either pushed on or yeah, or at some point, it was
pushed on them. And they had a minor experience like, you know,
they've decided they want cookies and candy. And the reason is
because they've had some cookies and candy because that was
pushed on candies, it's going to be something that they was made
they were made familiar with or promoted to them anyway, of
course, and they're not going to say, like, for example, you know,
you have, you know, the little crispy snacks. They get the
crisps, they call them in England, they do call them
potatoes, always crispy side. Okay, if you go to Asia, when
children get crispy snacks, it's dehydrated shrimp and fish.
Okay, right. There's the pork rind thing. Also, I know that's
popular right here. But that would be the closest. But you
don't see Westerners saying, Oh, I want a bag of chips or a
bag, you know, give me the dried shrimp. They would say, Oh,
that's gross, right? Because anyone who's had fish food, you
know, that, you know, the little dried shrimp, you throw in the
fish tank, whatever. Okay, so it's your culture. And how you
were made to want to believe things. That's why it's more
important to develop the individual well rounded. Right?
Before they start wanting like I have no wants, I have needs. And
my body knows I like when I use the stomach kind of feels kind
of tingy, it's making a really loud noise. And I've been
telling it to go away. I did the email work after a while it did.
But after a few days, Chuck, I found out that need has to be
satisfied. You know, right? It's stomach's making noise, and
it's distracting. Right? I could I could keep it off for a while.
Days even. But after a while, I got a sad, you know, I have to
fulfill that need. You see what I mean? But it's not like, I feel
a slight hunger or I haven't eaten in eight hours, I better
eat something has a big difference there. Right? So
there's an interesting point there where look, spiritual
things are a need of and a function of the being. And the
fact is, if you don't seek them out and decide what to put in
there, at some point, you'll be directed to put something in
there anyway. Regardless of whether you chose it, it might
just be the thing pushed on you as well.
Yeah, well, most likely, that's actually what you're being not
only what you're being made aware of, but what you're being made
aware of, and you consider to be important, which is different
for everyone to a degree.
So there you have