Rated Y Sonic Event 105, it almost rhymed and we're definitely not live because you're
hearing us due to the fact that you are subscribed. I don't know, that sounded like I was gonna
make some poetry and then got lazy about it on the way, but isn't that the way the world
works? Anyway, Greek, how are you doing this, uh, Tuesday? It's supposed to be at the moment,
according to the works. Yeah. We started talking. I said, hit the record button because I'm not
familiar with what's going on in the news. Can you do give me a, uh, you said bit something
about Bitcoin and something with the Middle East. So it was, let me just preface. If I,
if you don't follow current events and you have a pretty good foundation in the way things are here,
you'll be able to explain them much better. I'll tell you why, because if you follow current
events by the hour, by the day, there's programming in there. In other words,
about 20 or 30 years ago, more like 25 years ago or so, it was decided with TV commercials that
people get up and walk away. So they started designing the TV commercials to be, to be more
penetrating and more effective on the mind. If you weren't paying attention to it. Now that's some
crazy subliminal shit that they're into. Right. So, you know, uh, there's a few acts that were
passed that it's okay to use anything on the American public. Right. So, well, right. Cause
there used to be bans against doing the subliminal advertising where you were, you know, you insert
a couple of frames, chemical warfare is on biological warfare is on, uh, what is it called?
Psyops is on. It's all on. Oh yeah. But at one time there was that idea, just like people talked
about in the movie theaters where they would insert the picture of a popcorn and then people
would want to go back. Yeah. There was a book called subliminal seduction that I read partially
in the eighties. Uh, no, no, no, no. Uh, what happens is the residue from things supposedly
not being the way they are is, is still there. Right. The residue meaning like if you go out and
you don't say, well, you know, you can't use the military against the U S public, you know,
that's right. That's possible. That's right. Bullshit. So the residue people don't understand
the fine points. Right. And it's all open. It's all fair game, but it's much more interesting to,
okay. To do what they're doing. You've heard of the silent, uh, weapons for silent wars or
whatever. Oh yeah. Of course. Yeah. That's exactly what's going on. But okay. So when you're up on
current events, there's a trickle in, to accept in the mind, to accept what you're hearing,
whether even whether you think it's bullshit or not as something real. Now it's not much of a
task to convince the people who believe everything that something's real. The task here is how do
you convince the people that radio TV print say to themselves, oh, here's some more bullshit,
right? Though that's the system. So it's very, very nefarious. So most people,
especially the patriotic type that approach anything that say, oh, this is all bullshit.
Cause it's the media. They wholeheartedly take stuff more seriously than the people that don't
say it's bullshit. Think it's real. Well, right. Because there are, they take offense to the
idea that they're being lied to supposedly that that would be a normal reaction. I mean,
I get mad when people lie to me about things that are important when I want information about
something. Right. But here's a question I have for you. Actually, that occurs to me,
forget about the emails or anything else lately, but I know you say, look, there's no such thing
as general health, but what about mental health? Because there is a constant state,
same, same, same, same. Okay. But what would you call the perpetual state? The almost constant
condition that somebody is in mentally? Because when it comes to TV shows, like if you notice,
someone who is oppressed or possessed, oppressed or possessed. Yeah. Very,
there's very little possession. If you, no matter how bad someone mental state is, if you ask them,
let's see for the name that they're given as a child, wherever they could still recall that
they're not possessed, but they're heavily oppressed. Right. Yeah. No, no. It's a mental.
Uh, well, look, so you get impressed to be oppressed basically. Right. You get an impression
laid on you that becomes oppressor beings. There are more beings than there are people
in this realm, but they're not material. Right. So, but, but back to this constant state idea.
Right. I take note that when, you know, people that, uh, get obsessively, like they,
they constantly watch like crime shows. I took notice of this a few years ago because of the,
uh, law and order SVU, very popular syndicated show. By the way, that's a typical newlywed
problem. When newlyweds or people get into a relationship, one of the main things is the
guy trying to figure how to get the chick off the crime shows. The crime show thing is a chick thing,
by the way, but mainly, yeah, especially the true crime, you know, where it's like,
here it is. Here's the husband. Here's the matter. Well, the fictional one because crime shows. Yeah.
Most, most new relationships are married. It's a, the guy's like, how do I get her from stopwatch
cop shows? Yeah. Well, the cop shows, especially when there's a constant feed, right? I mean,
today you could create a constant feed any way you want. It's on demand. But a few years ago,
when people were still dependent on broadcast TV, law and order SVU was on seemingly 24 hours a day.
There were people that pointed this out and there were people that I swear to you, that's what they
had on in their homes, right? Now, I took note of the fact that since they were constantly being
exposed, even though it was fictional, they were constantly being exposed to the concepts of
violence, especially sexual, intimate violence. Look, look, I enjoyed this thing fall out on
Amazon Prime recently, right? And the level of detail and duration of the Gore, meaning like a
gunshot wound with an exit and splash on each violent scene was overly enhanced to get you used
to that, right? And that this has been going on since the eighties, by the way. So it wasn't like
Quentin Tarantino where it's cartoonish and over-exaggerated to be like, it was actually
what these guys did. They actually studied safety films. You know, when people get turned up or in
a real bad accident, occupational hazard, they're, they're usually filmed and also photographed very
well and also in the military. So, and I've seen a lot of it by the way. And it's, it's pretty
accurate. It's not, it's not just like it used to be where just all the fake blood everywhere,
whatever they're showing, like the edema on the tissue, the different, the details of the
different types of tissue, how the body reacts after two minutes of being injured. Yeah. They've
got that down like a swelling collar around an entry wound from this kind of thing. So all that
they're really super detailed. Okay. Well, fair enough. Okay. Let's okay. Hold on. The violence
is not a big deal. I'll tell you why, because the result of violence is around us everywhere.
Just like there's a saying, their power is not given it's taken. So for example, when you hear
about the bullshit they give in the Western governments, while the people give power to
the government through democracy, that's bullshit. It was taken from them and they're given a, a, a,
and they think that's why, you know, the, the they can vote, whatever the only way to make any
changes by taking it. And it's usually violent because that's just the way it is. It doesn't
have to be actually, but the people are not intelligent enough to do it nonviolently.
So in the, by the way, the way you take power back nonviolently is by not participating in the system,
uh, but you participated in it as, as you, uh, as you need to, but then you have these, uh,
you understand of, of rapid trades, right? How it works. So, uh, years ago they did a strike for a
week or two or three to make an effect. If you do a boycott or strike of the banking system for three
days, it'll pretty much cripple it. Right. Cause they're, cause they they're used to doing billions
of transactions per hour or per several hours. So if you stop that, those computers don't know
how to run anything else. And what it'll cost to adjust for that is massive. And they will listen
to that, right? The same, like with court, nobody show up to court. And if someone does, well,
you see, there's a thing. Well, I'm going to be arrested. No, but if nobody shows up, you won't
get arrested. Right. What will happen is, uh, these, these are not courts, by the way. I hope
you guys know that by now. Right. They're just, uh, yeah, it's the bar association. It's like
McDonald's or Walmart has a, uh, whatever, you know, uh, imagine like, uh, Amazon or like the
Italian pronunciation. I'm awesome. Uh, opens up a court system and they, uh, they don't even,
there is no license to practice law, by the way, it's just a bar card. It's all bullshit.
Um, but it has to be that way right now. Cause the people are so incompetent. They don't know
what, how to mitigate or legislate, not legislate, but, you know, perform a, uh,
what's right or wrong or arbitrate. Yeah. Thank you. They don't know they're too ignorant,
but if no one, here's the same thing with voting the same with court. If no one, absolutely no one
showed up to vote within a few days after that, the buildings would be emptied out. There'd be
no one there. Why? The only thing that would function with nobody showing up as the stock
market, because they have these computers that are preset to, as soon as the market opens,
they make a million trades in three seconds. Right. But they do require a human element
on the other side because the stock market is where the stock guy rings on the stock market.
That's why a guy rings a bell. That's why a guy rings a bell and another guy pushes a button next
to him. That's why there's two guys. It's not about the machines are not there yet.
They're machines. You'll know the machines are there when they start doing automatic abortions
and killing people. So here's the thing, OK, because every advanced planet, every other
advanced world doesn't have animals on this planet, by the way, it's just the beings. But anyway, here
let's let's just say it this way. If no one shows up to court for a traffic ticket or whatever,
whatever, you know, they're not incarcerated. Zero attendance. Zero. And no one votes.
You will go back to the court building government and they would be emptied out because the people
that are there will say, oh, no one's showing up. I guess they found out and they figured out what
we're doing. We better run. We better run and hide because when they do show up, it ain't going
to be good. So it's their own guilty conscience that will shut it down. Right. But this will never,
ever, ever happen with the current stock that you and breed that you see, whether it's the person
sitting next to you while you're listening right now or the person you see at work or on the street.
This current stock and breed of people that are here are not they ignore just like the commercials
are designed to impress the mind when you're not paying attention to them. The people do not pay
attention, do not pay attention to any of these systems. Right. And there are horrible systems,
by the way. The actual virtue of having, quote, unquote, a law system or a government system or
a health system or whatever, there's no such thing as a health system. That's ridiculous. But,
you know, medical system is fine. But what it's turned into is so horrific that, you know,
we could actually do three or four sonics just on the legal system in the banking system. I know we
did quite a few on the Federal Reserve on fractional reserve banking and how the system works
a while back. But the next run and the medical system, we've done a little bit of that. I think
the next run we should get into the banking, legal, the medical and really talk about how horrific it
is and try to objectify it. And it's way more horrific than anyone I've ever heard out there
talk about it. And I'm like, I need to start piecing this together because it's really, really bad.
Well, instead of using their language, shouldn't we use the proper terms and describe, you know,
use proper adjectives for descriptions? Right. Wouldn't that be more accurate instead of calling
somebody a banker? Call them what they are, you know, instead of calling somebody a lawyer or an
attorney, depending. There was a bit. They're not lawyers or attorneys. Yeah. So attorney is just
attorney is like a babysitter or a guardian that brings you to somewhere where you're not allowed
to go without. Right. Which, by the way, is what if you read things properly, you will see that
that's why the attorney is OK. There is no reason you will not find a government form in any country,
any municipality, federal, local or that in any language that's done in proper grammar.
Why? Why do they deliberately do that? Because if there is a Nuremberg style thing in the future
where these people are, let's say, brought that, you know, they're going to say that we're just
following orders. Right. Right. But if you bring them to a place, a trial, they will say, well,
these cannot be admitted as evidence because they're not in proper grammar and you're being
set up so you cannot be done using the current system. There's an old thing like you cannot
use the devil to exercise the devil. Right. So a new system will come. But unfortunately,
I don't see it with the current stock and breed of people that exist. And I'm not talking about
some people far off. I'm talking about the people next to you right now, wherever you're listening
to this people at work, people when you open your door, just look around you, look around you.
These people will not participate in any kind of clearing or cleansing or whatever. That's why it
requires a mop up crew, an external force to do it. And they're and they're very, very brutal.
But the the the violent aspect of it is what people are used to hearing. So I'm tying this
back to what you're saying about all the violence. What's more violent? There's an old Buddhist way
of thinking about it, where you have, let's say, someone, two people, they're both going to take
someone else's money through violence. The first one points a gun at one person to take their money
and says, Give me your money. The second person befriends the person who was money they want.
And as they're befriending them, and they establish that then they take their money
in secret. They are both forms of violence. So right now, the medical system, the legal system,
the government system, the health system is that second guy. Right? It's just as violent as any
other violence. Now, you can say, well, it's a hell of a lot more uncomfortable for someone to
put a gun in your face, right? Or live in a dystopic kind of dictatorship. But I'm still I'm
telling you, the end result is the same. And right, and, and they're both based on ignorance.
Now, the first one, with the gun pointing at the victim is also ignorance, because if you are fast
enough, and skilled enough, you can take the gun away. Right? And the second, right, so and the
second one's based on ignorance, because you cannot discern what's going on. So I'm telling
you that the system of violence that's being put on people, especially in the Western world,
is far more violent than they imagined by watching cop shows or Holly water, it's far more violent,
because it will persist. For example, if someone puts a gun to someone to take their money,
that person may net may be changed forever. For the rest of their life, it might want to carry
a gun down this next time it happens. The success rate of the assailant might be 50% instead of 100%
because the person's packing, right? Right. But if you condition somebody incrementally,
you're not going to have that rubber band snapback effect where it's not going to be so sudden. So
you're not going to have a sudden reaction, right? It's the slow roll the mission creep,
if you will, it's a one way conditioning. Okay, if you're born into slavery, and that's all you know,
just like when I get puppies, I always raise them in the kennel, I have a kennel,
and they kind of eat by it, I always put them in there, show them love in there, whatever.
And then I train them with a certain sound. So they go into the kennel, right? And you can only
do that when they're a little puppy. So when they go to sleep, they want to go to the kennel, right?
And you close it and make you know, safe place for the dog. Yeah, because they're used if you
tried. Yeah, if you tried, but you're raising, that's all they know. So what's going on if
you're raised in slavery, and that's all you know, okay, it's, it's not a one way street,
you're standing on a dot is no movement. But if you take people that are like that, and you try
to make them into become free to live in freedom, which you have to, it's very difficult to be
living in freedom, by the way, they cannot do it. Also. So that's kind of like a halfway street
instead of a one way street. A one way street also is when you have people that are free,
and you enslave them, they cannot go back. It's a one way street.
They don't know how to get they do not want to get out. Because it's very, very, very comfortable.
It's people don't understand, like, for example, if you hear of super wealthy people that have
mansions everywhere, right? If those mansions are not lived in, and I mean, lived in, they fall
apart, right? Or they could be vandalized and squatters or whatever, right? Doesn't matter what
kind of security you have, they have to be lived in. So someone's got 10 mansions. They can't live
in all of them at the same time. Right, right. So people are living there, their slaves are living
in there, and their slaves are living in splendor. Now, if you take that person based on the salary
they get as a slave, and get them out of the mansion into the real world on that salary,
they'll be on like public housing. They'll hate it. Right? You see what the because they're in
other words, they will not up their what their earn more, if you keep them at that earning and
have them go out on their own, quote, unquote, more free, they will not like their living conditions,
I assure you, they want to go back and be a slave in splendor. Now, most people that are free live
in squalor, by the way, because for the whatever time you're using, to not gain whatever you're
going to earn in food, or whatever you're spending on protecting yourself and your family from the
other violent ones that are not so free. Because free people do not bring violence onto other free
people. This is the opposite of what you've been told. Well, that's why anarchy, you know,
when when people discuss anarchy, I say it's not an idiotic thing, right? Anarchy is when free
people meet the non free people. Well, but no anarchy in and of itself. That's that's a problem.
That's a question. No one will mean no one at the top, right? So if you have a castle doctrine,
each person, the anarchy actually was Switzerland up until 2002. Like, they could not send,
they could not be part of the United Nations, because they could not have each person,
each man or woman that lived in especially men that lived in sweet, Switzerland had to decide
who would represent them was impractical. So they had to bring them all in under a corporate umbrella
and have them agree to it so they can send a representative, right? So the thing about free
people, you very difficult to have someone represent you. That's why they're always put to
the side. As those people are like this with a you know, they don't have ambassadors, they don't have,
right, right. You see, this is something that's been taken out of history completely. For example,
when you look at the quote unquote, Roman citizenship and the and the hierarchy of
order of social structure, they had problems with the the Britain, the Britain, or the
not sort of the goals also, when they went into what's known as modern day England,
because they didn't, they, they, they did the people that lived in modern day England back
then that fought the Romans did not have a concept of sending a representative to negotiate each
individual person or man or woman that lived there had to be dealt with individually, where the
Romans, you know, they had a council and they had a representative just like the Greeks and
every other country did, right? Yeah. So it ended up being a mismatch, and they fought.
So until they picked up the traits of the, of understanding the concept of council
with foreign relations, no pun intended there.
Well, and the only way that that was actually normalized was through creeping in. And then
what happened is that both societies affected each other at a connection point. And then you had,
you know, the alleged Romans going, I said earlier, those some of those early Brits
saw how much more splendor they could be living in, if they just followed the Roman rules, right?
And they adapted and became enslaved by the Romans. So when I say it said, you know, is
when you join that society, now you're subject to the rules and regulations. So if the,
if the council, the legislator says no shirts on Monday, or you go to jail for three days,
right, you have to follow that where it was absurd. So yeah, so they just figured that
it's in the Bible, in the Bible, also a lot of criticism of ancient Israel about, you know,
you left, you know, me meaning Yahweh to go and pursue these fine things that they had, right,
like the trinkets and jewelry and all that you were impressed by how well, you know, fashionable
they were and all that, right. So that's one of the things that is part of the dressing.
So if you're going to have a society of slaves, you have to always make sure that there's something
to aspire to, that they cannot make on their own. Like how many people these days, for example,
this, I remember this from many years ago, but how many people these days want to build their
own car from scratch, like a kid car or build their own quote unquote vehicle? Nobody, nobody.
You know, and they tried to roll that out, by the way, about 15 years ago, where, you know,
when they started doing the, you know, 3D printers and all that stuff. And they said, look, we can
send you directions and a kit and you could build a vehicle, which would be, you know, and they
tried this. Yeah, but also here's the criticism I have on that. I said a kid car, whatever.
Don't copy that. Okay, start from scratch, new design, new everything, you know, like the easiest
thing to do right now is these electric cars, because it starts off with what's called a
skateboard. It's just four wheels for motors, basically some controllers, and on a flat
platform that the batteries are hiding in. And it's there's almost no engineering once you these
are all off the shelf parts, you get you in Tesla, all off the shelf stuff. It is so simple and easy
to build. I mean, if I started this morning, I'd have most of it done by this afternoon, just using
hand tools. And you can build it's going to bring back the coach body works. Years ago, you bought
the chassis and then you went to a coach. That's why if you're a coach builder to build you the
outside, right? That's why years ago, if you saw a GM car from the 60s, or 50s on the running board,
when you open the door, even the 70s, it said body by Fisher, all the GM cars, you remember that and
had a stagecoach wagon on the emblem? You know, I remember body by Fisher. I remember that I don't
remember. So joined with Jeff. So anyway, right now we had a point where you can buy all the guts to
make an electric car, right and build your own outside, but don't start copying the way they
build it and make it the way they do it. Because it's very inefficient. If you try to do it that
way, you know, one at a time that when you look at production items, it's efficient when it's
mass produced. So this is the problem. The ingenuity and the creativity is is gone in the
toilet. I don't see much. I mean, I know if you do some research, maybe online, you'll find people
doing that. But it has not hit home that there's so much accessible right now, because everything
is so sloppy. The the your freedom within the slave system is maximized right now, by the way,
like you said, with the 3d printer, there's a thing that I saw recently about, you know,
where guns, certain types of weapons are banned, people can 3d print a one shot gun.
Oh, yeah, they go in the ghost guns and the plastic guns. And yeah, yeah,
yeah, you just need one shot. I mean, that's a talk to anybody in the CIA,
they make they put them in umbrellas and all kinds of James Bond stuff, a cigarette lighter,
right doesn't matter. Just one shot pens. Yeah. Yeah. If you're if you're two feet away from
someone, you point it right at their neck, you know, and it's only 22 round is very small.
It's no bigger than a barrel of a pen. Honestly, you know, yep, I've seen someone catch a 22.
Remember the bomber jackets in the 80s with the fuzz brown with a fuzzy brown collar and the
leather jacket? Oh, yeah. Yeah. popularized. Yeah. popularized after what do you call it?
Top Gun came out? Yeah. Yeah. Way before that. But yeah, the 70s. Actually,
they're called bomber jackets at a police line that the cheap version of it, whatever.
Yeah, I remember another two. Yeah. There was the local weed dealers like 1978. Right.
And he couldn't zip. It was really cold. He couldn't zip up his jacket. He says here and he
points the top of the zippers. I can't zip it up. And it's shattered, right? It's split open. He
says that that caught a 22 bullet. So someone shot at him and the zipper caught the anyway,
long story made short there. No problem. So I mean, that's how small the projectile is. But
if you do a hollow point, it'll work way, way better. Well, because because of the sheer Yeah,
it's shot. And also when it hits a bone or something, it just it's it shatters and sprays
about and creates a whole bunch or the other thing is a tumbler. If you can make it tumble,
then it'll just rip every you know, right? It's but here's the whole thing. We're going back to
violence and projectiles and all that. Totally unnecessary, totally unnecessary. All you need
is everyone. Here's the thing. The more people that participate in withdrawing from a system,
the less time you need to do it for. Right. You give an example. Remember that stupid protest
about the 1% back in 2011 occupy this and that? Yeah, that was stupid. And they went on for weeks
and months or whatever, because there's a small group of people, right? You know, look, even now,
they they'll have like, what, 2 million people marching and was it Argentina, Venezuela recently,
or somewhere? That's still not enough. You have to have everyone and that's not going to happen.
Do it for a day. That's enough to really change the system. It's so simple. No violence is
necessary. You know, mathematically, I think one third of the people really if one third of the
people collectively did that, that would probably do it. No, it wouldn't do it. But it would
definitely, it would definitely have enough of a result that if the result was not hidden,
or covered up, it would inspire more. And the next time it would be half of the people.
Well, I don't think you could you could hide a one third action because you could hire the
no, you would hide the results of their action. Okay. Right. That's what's always being done.
Right. Well, just like we talked about any terrorist event, you see, it's publicized is not
a real terrorist event. There doesn't mean that there are no real idiots trying to do terrorist.
There are no but when that happens, they'll call it a drill. No, yeah, it's completely blacked out.
Yeah, because it's not in their control. Everything you see is in their control. And the same thing
here, like, for example, we're doing this rated y sonic or whatever. Let's say it was the old
telephone lines were memory to be on a conversation, you can hear someone else speaking. And yeah,
let's hang up and or sometimes you can participate in the dialogue, right? You know,
crosstalk or whatever. Yeah, they used to call them party lines at one point, because you end
up with a phone that would just somehow connect to another phone. And this is before the days
when you can do it intentionally. But yeah, so we're doing the sonic now, let's say we connected
to some other thing. And they started speaking over us or with us or whatever, it would be like,
wait a second, Chuck, let's know, let's let's stop this, right? Yeah. Somehow. Yeah, we're
connected to somebody we didn't ask to be connected to. Yeah, right. So the whole thing
here is about we are all guilty, potentially of it. That's why you always have to mind yourself
and be impeccable and very intentional in what you say and do. I mean, sometimes people say,
oh, you're very harsh. And the things you said, and I'm like, you know, before I say something,
I think about it a lot. You know, I think about it a lot. So if I said it, it was there was a
very strong reason it was for your benefit. Well, that's why I find it very weird that you say that,
power is always taken, it's never given. Because here's an interesting part of that to me,
is that all along the way, you're telling me about a lot of choices here, where it seems like
consent is given. I mean, it's not given freely, where somebody is allowed to consider what's
happening. It's what they called an unconscionable contract, unconscionable act. It's done
unconscionably. Right means that you're right. Yeah. Okay. So this is this was very popular,
you know, one name signature, two name signature, unilateral contract, unconscionable contract,
all those things were very popular in the common parlance. Boy, oh boy, what would be the 1930s?
That would be 90 years ago. I wasn't around then. But I was surely was around a lot of stuff that
was going on there in print and more stuff that was written about the big stuff going around back
then was unconscionable contract, unilateral contract, and all this other stuff. And there's
no talk about that. Most people don't even know what the hell that means. So because yeah, that's
why going back to what I said earlier, the current breed and stock that you see around you, pretty
much everyone cannot do this. That's why they're going to have a quote unquote, calamity that
they're going to have a series of them. And that's why they're going to keep going, you know,
with the current systems, no matter what they are, which are going to get worse and worse. And
why is the current banking system, medical system, legal system getting worse and worse,
because the general stock and breed of the people is going down the quality of the people. And when
they get in there, now, it's just like, we've been doing it this way for so long, no one cares.
Just you know, let's let's let's have some fun. Because if you keep a system that is perpetuating
fraud long enough, it's a thrill to do that. Right? So the medical system, the legal system,
governmental systems, scientific, they've been they know they're perpetuating frauds,
and it's a thrill. But after a while, the thrill wears out, it's like shooting fish in a barrel.
And now they want a little bit more risque. That's why when you watch the media,
or current events in any way, the stuff that's going on with all these systems is so outrandish,
outrandish, outlandish, and whatever that would have never been even 10 years ago,
wouldn't be accepted. So it's going to get much worse from that thing. From that perspective. But
is there a reason? Okay, like a lot of relatable, even if you go back to what they call obscenities
on TV, or whatever, you can literally use the F word on broadcast TV, so long as now that you know,
you know very well that people used to get thrown off the air, their businesses taken away,
all kinds of stuff, people lost jobs, when somebody dropped an F bomb on on TV or radio,
right? Well, so tell me that they're dropping F bombs now on TV. Nowadays, you can Yes, as so long
as it has a certain context, or the other thing is, you can do it once a season you're allowed.
I mean, it's just weird. Like they've made up some weird random rules about it. And somebody
can literally say fuck on TV books that they're putting in elementary school and all that. But
look, yeah, up until the late 80s, early 90s, toplessness for women was allowable on Italian
television, Italian and British. I remember watching stuff from Britain where they had to
put black bars over it when they sent it to America. And they go, well, in America, we can't
show nipples. You know, the only thing that's still offensive is the bucket, the middle finger in
it's an offense, right? And it's a justice gesticulation in the towards a victim.
In the Middle East, it's the bottom of your foot, the bottom of a shoe. That's why, for example,
I'll see a clip from a film. There was one recently I pointed out to someone and it's
Nicolas Cage in the movies laying on the bed and the camera starts zooming in past him and his feet
take up half the screen and then pass the feet up his leg and you see him there on the road
laying down. So that would have to be edited out for Middle East countries. They do cannot show.
Well, you know, when you have, for example, a talk show host and they cross one of the guests
crosses their legs and the bottom of their shoe is showing that would have to be edited or they
have to change the angle because they would find it offensive. So when they let the the F-bomb
or this or whatever, it's it's OK. If if I hear that in the Middle East, they're allowing the
bottoms of feet and shoes to be shown, then I will see that as a worldwide trend with the F-bombs
here. You see what I mean? OK, well, two quick questions. Well, one observation and one question.
How about this? First of all, I guess Quentin Tarantino movies never get shown in the Middle
East because he's got an obsession with with with showing feet in his movies. Weird bear.
He likes cute women's feet. Yeah, he's he's very much about it. It's the bottom. It's the bottom.
But often that's what he shows. So the solely the sole of the foot. Right. And that's what he shows
often, usually a little dirty. And that's what he does. And he does it in every movie. If you if you
check. Yeah, he's got a foot. He's got a foot fetish for sure. But why is that? I mean, look,
we know about the middle finger, right? We've talked about it. Feet are very important,
especially with women. Yeah. But we've talked about the middle finger before and why that's
offensive. Right. It just became that way because it has to do with not having it amputated. You
could pull a compound bow from back in the French wars. Right. So historically, you waved it at
somebody to show you I still got mine. You could in other words, if they started running, you
could hit them further than they can hit you because you have a compound bow. Right. And
you should only have a compound bow with the middle, because if you use any other finger,
you could tear your forearm off because you're the maximum amount of clearance. Right. You know,
when the the bow, the cord goes back and by. Right. I know. I know. I've hurt myself. I don't
know exactly the mechanics on all that, but I know I've hurt my hands before pulling a bow with other
than the middle finger being involved. But anyway. But why is the foot so. I don't know why.
You don't know why. Well, because it's tread. It's tread. Right. Well, I'm just thinking where
you tread. It's the lowest part of the body. And you would just gesticulate that towards.
I'm doing it because it represents the dirtiest things, because everything eventually that is
dirty. Left hand would probably be dirtier, I think, in that culture. The left hand would be
dirty. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Well, even in Latin, the left hand is sinistro. The sinister sinister
means left. Yeah. Left is always seen as the matter of fact, they call it a path when it's
about the dark side of things and etc. Yeah. Well, it's Spanish. It's asked, you know,
which is askew. And in Italian, it would be sinister. I think Latin, it's also sinister.
Yeah, it is. No, fair enough. But yeah, so that was a yeah, that was that I wouldn't dive into
why things are they, you know, offensive or whatever. It's just that things are it's part
of the programming. And by the way, it's very, very easy to program people. I think it's good
to know why people react because as I as I started out with the whole TV thing, right?
It's because I took note that when people choose to when they consent to expose themselves to
certain things consistently, it creates very I've seen negative effects to this and other people
claim positive effects, right? If they expose themselves to if they constantly play, you know,
positive, light feeling music, you know, very yin sort of music. It makes them young, right?
It makes them feel stronger to deal with this lighter music.
And what will happen is, let's dabble into this and we'll call it a night. Absolutely.
When you dabble in a particular, let's say, force direction, we are young.
When you start exposing yourself to yin, you will become yin also. It's when it you cannot it's
when the system that's exposed to the yin cannot take any more yin that it flips and becomes its
opposite to bring balance again. You see? Well, that's why the constant exposure, I think,
works that way. Right. So if you listen to music, you will not become automatically young,
you will you will become yin until you're over and overly yin and then
young either external or internal will manifest. And this is why there are no laws of physics.
They're merely observations in physics. Right. But like that constant exposure,
though, to I'm telling you, the deviant acts and the ideas and the negativity,
I think that does cause and people start, you know, they call it.
It won't make them positive, right? And they have to cut it off
before it makes them positive to keep them. It can go either way.
See, it almost looks addictive, though, in the way that people behave,
they're almost seemingly addicted to being oppressed by the negativity. It's like
if I don't have my negativity, I don't know what to do with myself.
When you say people, though, they remember that it's a current breed and stock.
It's very, very downgraded. Well, without a time machine, I can't really.
Well, without a time machine, I can't directly observe people from other time periods,
except the time periods I lived in. I can observe them from the since I remember being young.
Well, that's what I'm saying. From memory, I can think back and people are different,
even in this space of our lifetime, 20 years ago. Yeah.
They were already softened and ready, but they were not accepting of would not be accepting of
what is happening now and what will be happening. I've talked about this in the past.
But essentially, they they are like chihuahuas, meaning if you imagine a what a dog would be
like in the wild. Right. You cannot take a chihuahua and put it out in the wild.
They won't live because it's bred to be a chihuahua. Right.
Just like what came first, the chicken or the egg, the chicken farmer.
Because if you ever found a natural wild chicken and wanted to have it for dinner,
you wouldn't do it again because there's no meat on it. Right.
So it had to be bred for that. So the current breed and stock of people,
I cannot compare and say with what I consider, let's say, to be a proper more proper breed and
stock, you see, with to them, you know, chickens, chickens are the only birds, quite frankly,
that I have never seen an example of. Here's a wild chicken.
I don't think I've ever seen an example of it. Really? Where is their genetics?
If there's well, if there's no people around and they end up staying in the wild long enough,
they will revert back to their. Yeah, theoretically. Sure. But have you ever
seen an example of that in the wild? Like I know you've watched nature shows. You and I
talked about watching nature shows years ago. So I know you've watched them. I don't think
I've ever seen an example like you see wild turkeys, you see wild ducks, you see almost
any of these birds that are bred either for pets or for food or whatever.
I see examples of them in the wild. I don't recall ever seeing a wild chicken.
No, you won't. You won't. Because the current iteration,
just like you'll see, you won't see a wild chihuahua. Right. Yeah. So they go.