Rated Y Sonic Event 92, and here we are. And it is yet another one of these events.
Greek, how you doing tonight?
Doing okay. You know, I got a pretty lengthy email, various sundry questions.
I skimmed the email, and I want to read through and answer it because it covers many, many topics.
And it's even prefaced that some of these might be a dummy load, or let's just start here.
Hey, Greek, here's a rough list of topics, questions for Sonics.
Of course, feel free to go into what you'd like, all, some, or none.
I'm aware some of this could be dummy loads. It would help to clear it up if possible.
Quite an interesting start, right?
It's been, yeah, and you know what, it's been quite a long time since you were using that term, dummy load.
That was like a constant from you when we first started doing this, pretty much.
So, yeah, but I haven't heard of it.
Yeah, well, that was back when I was more militant.
Now it's, my give-or-should factor is going lower every year.
You know what I mean by give-or-should factor, right?
Oh, yeah, absolutely.
So the more you care, the more upset you get sound, or the more heated and the more passionate.
When you don't care, it's like, ah, so what?
Well, what's funny is the audience has changed since then a bit, too,
because I don't know if it's their give-or-should factor that's changed or not,
but the reality is a lot of people, when they heard that term, they didn't like it.
They thought you were calling them dummies, and meanwhile, take two breaths,
and you would be saying that most people were effectively space eaters anyway, which...
Yeah, but if you hear the word dummy load and you think you're being called a dummy, guess what?
You are.
Yeah, well...
So go away. Watch Fox News, right?
Okay, yeah.
Or CNN, whatever.
I don't even know if such a thing exists anymore, but...
Yeah, they do.
I heard they do, yeah.
They have to because it's part of the intelligence apparatus.
Well, and as per usual, if there is an audience, someone will show up to deliver what that audience wants,
which is precisely that.
Advice first.
They want to be lied to, yeah.
Yeah, it's a dog chasing its tail, you know.
Yeah, that too.
Anyways, so what is it?
Let's start with what is a dummy load, by the way.
This person is obviously somebody who has heard you in the past because, like I said, you haven't used that term in a while.
Yeah, I've used dummy loads often.
A dummy load, a simple way to give an analogy for it would be running on a treadmill.
So you could run on a treadmill and say you ran two miles, right?
On a treadmill.
Right.
But where did you go?
On a treadmill.
Nowhere.
Right?
Right.
So that's basically it.
The dummy load definition, let's just give what anyone else can access to.
Let's see if it's meaningful, right?
Let's do it that way.
What is it?
Why use a dummy load?
Okay.
Dummy load, Wikipedia.
A dummy load is a device used to simulate an electrical load, usually for testing purposes.
Right?
It's a simulation.
A simulated electrical load.
So a simulated transfer of energy, which means…
Yeah, like a simulation run around the block would be running a half a mile on a treadmill.
On a treadmill, yeah.
Or riding a stationary bike.
You didn't go anywhere on a bicycle.
Yeah, same thing.
That's right.
That's what's out there.
So here we go.
First question.
These are bullet points.
Psychedelics.
Very high usage throughout history.
In almost every culture.
Secret societies.
Do you have any opinions?
Experience.
Knowledge.
Including states.
Attained through other means.
Dancing.
Sensory deprivation.
NDE.
Meditation.
All right.
First half, yes.
I do have experience with it.
I don't feel like I ever had anyone coach me through it, so it was pretty much like,
I think, 75% of the people that have experience with psychedelics are not coached.
Right?
I'd say maybe 20% or 25% or less do it on a ceremonial basis.
Well, it has changed a lot in recent years because people have decided to access information,
and there's a lot of books on it and videos on it and stuff like that, which means they're
kind of getting a secondary coaching.
That didn't used to be the case, like say, again, when you were a kid or I was a kid
and we probably first ran into this stuff, and it was about, let's see what else we can
do today.
But the reason I brought that up is because in a secret society situation, for example,
you're prepped and you're coached.
Right?
Oh, yeah.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
So what's it for?
I think it's just part of adjusting the perception, but also it does trigger things that are there
that normally wouldn't be triggered.
Right?
You don't need any of that at all, but for the average person, I would definitely recommend
it.
But for someone who's well-versed, seeking knowledge and wisdom or wisdom and knowledge,
hopefully, seek wisdom and then knowledge.
Because knowledge is kind of hard to attain.
It's just knowledge would be the independent files, and wisdom is what to do with those
files.
So get the wisdom before you get as much knowledge as you can.
Because wisdom lets you know how to manage and use it.
Right.
But sadly, no matter how much knowledge you give to someone, wisdom still remains unattainable
to some.
Right.
And that's how it's made to be.
Yeah.
I think there's a selection process, not as a terminal thing where someone is selected
and an outcome, but just like a film, you have the main characters, secondary characters,
then you have the backfill people.
What do you call them?
The whatever, the standby people or the backfill.
In a movie, the extras.
The extras.
Yeah.
Yeah, the extras.
So that's, I think, part of the manifestation here.
It's what it appears to be throughout history as well.
But do you...
Well, you know, you make a lot of references to movies as if this whole thing is like a
big, giant movie.
Sure.
Well, it's not a movie.
It's an analogy, just like the treadmill is an analogy.
Well, right.
But in the analogy...
They both exist, but you can crisscross them.
Right.
But here...
Okay.
Go ahead.
Let's just give an example to a book, the Carlos Castaneda books, right?
Ultimately, well, it starts out about how to use the psychedelics in the way the Toltecs
did, but he says you don't need them.
You really don't need them, right?
So there's no need for them, but they're available, right?
So I would say that scratch it from a wellness point of view, but if you're in like, ah,
fuck it.
Let's try it.
It's fine.
As long as you don't have a very bad trip.
It depends on how strong the psychedelic is.
So I'm not for it, but I'm not against it.
But I'm more against it if you want to maintain perfect wellness or not perfect.
Perfect is not...
Perfect is a terrible thing to try to put on anyone, right?
It's just good enough and better than good enough.
But yeah, I've done them.
I knew what they were, but I didn't know what it would be like.
So I kind of figured it out as I went.
If I had to do it over again, would I do them?
Yeah, absolutely.
Because the memories that you have from that are very distinct from anything else.
This is all true.
I would say, though, that just on a personal level, they were extremely helpful to me.
At a certain point, it gave me greater power to reorganize myself.
Yeah, and you could still access that state of mind,
which you would never be able to have if you never did it in the first place.
It takes much longer to do it without it.
But again, you need someone.
You're not going to figure this out on your own unless you happen to be someone who does.
It's very rare.
But yeah, you can get into altered states.
How many times have you heard people...
Someone tells someone, in part, a new idea or a concept,
and what does the person say?
That's really trippy, man.
That's like an acid trip.
Or, let's say Chuck and I went to this place,
and it was like being in an acid trip, right?
So yeah, why would you say that if it wasn't?
And were you tripping on acid?
No.
But it was just like one?
Yes, pretty close.
But it also shows you how you can't trust...
No matter how much you want to trust your senses, you can't.
Right?
Unless the senses, the things that you sensed under, let's say, an LSD trip were real,
and now the senses, again, can't be trusted.
Right?
Because you perceive things in a different way.
All right, so the next one.
Animal-human bond.
What is the significance?
Do they raise our life force energy?
Yeah, anything can raise your life force energy.
I think, just a segue here,
most people that practice acupuncture don't know why they're doing it.
It's just a tradition.
The life force energy is also around the body.
So what the needles represent is a lightning rod.
So the body can be adjusted by borrowing energy that is in its field around it,
in its atmosphere, and driving it, sending it back down to the body, or vice versa.
Right?
If you can send the excess energy into the body, into the atmospheric shell,
without discharging it, shorting it out, to help the body,
you do that as well.
So it works both ways.
I have to harp on them because most of them don't know why they're doing it,
don't know what the purpose is.
It's just basically a lightning rod.
So when you say life force energy, it could be that mechanical.
When you get to the bonding of humans and animals,
I can't really consider that much more,
other than I know cats are some kind of alien species sent here to monitor us.
Right?
Yeah.
I mean that, by the way.
That's not a joke.
Yeah.
I'm more partial to dogs myself.
Well, dogs are actually, you know, there's no parentage for dogs and cats.
In other words, they did not evolve from wolves or tigers.
They're independent.
They're just as unique as anything else.
Right?
So, yeah.
But dogs are dogs and cats are cats.
Yeah.
Okay.
What is fire?
I don't believe you've talked too much about it,
but considering how much water is discussed in terms of sacrifice,
what is the significance or importance of fire?
Okay.
Leave the sacrifice part out, because that's a big term, really,
and it's very subjective.
But fire is – here's the thing.
I have mentioned this.
I've done a lot of speaking with Seth on Revolution Radio back in the days.
It was called – what's the – Isaac Asimov Foundation.
Yeah.
Back in the 2009, 2010, and 11.
Spent four or five hours on the weekends there speaking on the radio.
And I did get into what fire was more on itself,
because at the time I was doing alchemic stuff.
The other day I found some heavy copper strips that are wrapped up real tight,
and I haven't opened them, but I was like, this is not labeled.
What is it?
Ah, this is when we're transmuting,
we're turning basic oxidized minerals into gold on a copper strip,
on a copper, let's say, plate.
That's what they are.
One day I'll open them up and photograph it doing alchemy.
So fire is very important, right, when you're going to reduce that.
So in essence from a chemical point of view, what is fire?
It's oxidation.
That's all it is.
Think about it.
How do you stop a fire?
Deprive it of what?
Oxygen, right?
Typical fires we're talking about, right?
Yeah, but it seems like you're explaining the chemical aspect of it.
Right.
That's the chemical.
What is fire?
Yeah.
That's basically what – all it is is oxidation.
For example, hydrogen peroxide is a very strong oxidizer
when you get it above 20%.
Thirty-three percent hydrogen peroxide is basically rocket fuel.
They use them – when a C-130 is too heavy for takeoff,
they have these six-inch cylinders they attach to them,
and they fire them off to help the plane take off when it does an airdrop.
Okay, if you put that strong hydrogen peroxide on a piece of paper towel,
what happens?
It starts to smoke and what?
Catch fire.
Any strong oxidizer concentrated will start a fire.
So fire is basically oxidation.
Now there are other fires that can happen like sodium in water, right?
If you take pure sodium strips – this is the pure chemical stuff.
That's what it is.
In terms of when you say fire, there are fires that don't burn hot.
It's in the biblical text.
By the way, you hear a lot, especially Jason Warwick,
so funny that he talks about Yahweh and the burning bush and all that.
You know there's no burning bush in the Bible, by the way?
Here, let me harp on our cakes a little bit.
He says he's read the Bible 40 times and he has the notes to prove it.
Okay.
I don't think – he read it once 40 times because if he did that,
you would have seen that the bush is never burning.
It was an angel that was emitting fire, scared Moses,
so the angel decided – because he had to deliver the message,
how are you going to do it if Moses is going to run away, right?
So he stood behind a bush, so the bush was between him and Moses,
and his fire did not consume the bush.
So where's the burning bush?
So if you've read it at least once with comprehension is all it takes.
But anyway, there's that type of fire as well.
I have witnessed fire that doesn't burn.
Anyone can if you work with a very high-quality HHO torch.
They're called HHO torches.
It's an intelligent fire.
It will burn through fire brick.
It will burn through four inches of steel.
But you put it on your hand, it barely singes the hairs on your hand or your body.
When you put it on a live plant, it doesn't hurt the live plant.
If you put it on the brick, it will cut right through the brick immediately.
Interesting, right?
Very intelligent, right?
It doesn't hurt things with life.
But essentially it's an – most fire is an oxidizer
unless you start going into the intelligent fires,
which is the HHO or angels that seem to be emitting flames that don't burn bushes.
Okay, so that's all I could get into with that.
And I'll unwrap – well, I don't know.
It's kind of like the Scalarator thing.
Sometimes when I show things that I do, I don't really want to post them
because it's kind of look what I could do, look what I could do, right?
I don't like doing that kind of stuff.
But I found out that when I do do that, it inspires certain people.
So in a sense, it's good, right?
Right.
Yeah.
Can you speak about the Nazis?
Oh, the Nazis.
That's the National Socialist Party.
Nazi is a derogative term, by the way.
There was some New York Times writer that made that up, right?
It's like calling Asian people gooks, right, or nips.
But it's totally acceptable, right?
In academia, they use that term.
So can you speak about the National Socialist Party and what's actually going on?
Not just the Holocaust, but more importantly, their search around the world
of whatever they're looking for, knowledge of Aryans, life force, energy engines,
inter-Earth groups, interdimensional communication, Tibet's 20 years with monks.
Not 20 years, but yeah, I'd say so.
It started in the 20s, so yeah, you could probably say 20 years.
Aryans, okay.
Do you know anything about this?
Yes.
You go online and there's about the Germans visiting Tibet,
and there's a sketch of it from a book that's been redacted,
which was online in the early 2000s, not anymore.
All there is online right now is how the Tibetans lifted heavy stones
up of a cliff face using drums and trumpets, right?
And that was a sketch from a book from one of these Germans
that had gone there and spoke to them.
What was redacted, not shown on the Internet anymore,
is when the Germans asked through a translator, the Tibetans,
about their history.
They went into some satchels and came out,
and they had these things that looked like glass pads,
and they would pass their hand over it,
and it would give the entire video and audio history, right?
This is in the 1920s.
I don't even think we have iPads and tablets, but they're not like that.
It's not like a clear piece of glass that you wave your hand over, right?
The Germans ended up around a lot of wild stuff.
They had basically Skype in Germany.
Guess when?
Around that same time period.
Perhaps, yeah.
Where you had video conferencing.
I've never heard of that.
Yeah, no.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Video conferencing, yes.
That's right, and they even had advertisements about that.
Yeah, yeah.
Small tube, yeah, and you would, yeah.
Yeah, and you could literally make these calls like you do on Skype,
see somebody on the screen, they see you, the whole thing,
and people act like, oh, that just came out in 2010 or whatever.
It's like, no, you know, or 2001,
or whenever it is they first decided to tell people it existed.
But it existed before that.
There's a crazy question about that, by the way, about Nazis.
I found that to be very similar to the Hebrew title
they give to the president of Israel.
The Nazi.
Yeah.
It's like it's.
Yeah, the Nassim, like Nassim or Nazi, yeah, that's a Semitic term.
Yeah, and it's a N-A-S-S-I.
Well, that's the Jordan Maxwell stuff.
Yeah, no, but I'm just saying it's very weird to me that that is.
Like the sun in the sky is the son of God, it's not.
But, yeah, I don't stretch things that far, but I get you.
I get you.
I try to stick more to the etymology.
Nazi is a derogatory term.
It should be National Socialist Party, but I get it.
Okay, the Aryans.
The Aryans, you know, Iran formally changed before the Shah or,
yeah, before the Shah, it was called, they switched it to Iran
because they were professed to being the legal descendants
of the original Aryans, the original humans, let's say, right,
of certain types, hybrids.
If you want to get more into that, you can listen to Archaics on the Anu.
And you do mean before the first Shah.
Shah, by the way, is a term just meaning king.
But Shah.
Before the Shah, that was put in the 50s.
So around the 1920s or 30s, they changed it from Persia to Iran
because they were legally Aryans.
Yeah, because the one that was installed in the 50s there
when they got rid of Mosaddegh, that was the son of the original Shah,
which was installed before that.
Yeah.
Right.
Yeah, the one that was, because remember, the Iranians, Persians,
are not Arabs.
They're not Arabs, right?
Right.
So they're much closer to the Afghani people.
They're Farsi, right?
So, yeah, I would say with the Aryans and all that,
there was a lot of exemptions.
They worked, again, with the Germans and all that.
So is there significance to that?
It goes back, again, Archaics has a lot of stuff on that,
on the Anunna and how the people that came after the main cataclysms
and mixed with men, you know, that were on the surface,
the primitive people.
I think the stuff that he's dug into really deeply on that,
it's undeniable.
You could go look at something he's got called the Anunna files.
It's about five or six hours of stuff he gives you.
He just likes to, just like I did for a long time, and still do,
you've got to get some source material, right,
if you're going to bring something as history.
Then you have personal experiences,
and then you have social experiences and comments and all that.
But essentially, if you're going to get information on history,
it would be good to cite some kind of source, and he's done that.
So the Aryans, again, all we have, we're hybrids, right, from that.
Okay, life force energy, the more research I do,
it seems that it was some of the most important knowledge
held by most secret societies.
By the way, most secret societies that you know of,
let's say Masons, those are all buffer zones.
Those are all intermediaries.
They really don't know much.
If you know any Freemasons,
99% of them are joining it because of business opportunities.
They help out each other.
Yeah, mainly.
And the parties.
Networking, basically.
Networking, yeah, they don't know anything.
What's funny about that, though,
is that there are various sort of suborganizations
which they confuse the histories of and all that,
like, say, the Knights Templar,
who are pretty much almost like a subset of the Masons at this point,
and all these things, and you can chase it around,
like, again, a dog chasing its tail.
Yeah, but again, it's not put out to them.
Right, right.
They're like, what do you call it when you set up a group to attract attention
so the real stuff is not, you know, no one looks at the real stuff.
They look at where you, I don't know, like a decoy.
They're decoys.
They often talk about common usage is like false flags, right?
So it's almost like the existing secret societies,
the guys with the big old, you know, lodges and all that.
They're decoys, yeah.
They're the decoys.
I think by the time of the Golden Dawn, you know, the 1890s,
that was the – let me just rephrase that.
Prior to the 1890s, the chances of getting real stuff
and having real, you know, within the surface of that building,
it was probably more like it.
After the 1890s, for sure, it's all just a decoy, for sure.
You can get more.
I've run into people that have been studying it,
and they thought I was in those secret societies
because of the stuff I was talking about.
I was like, no, no, it's just out there right now.
It's just – all right.
So, okay.
And it gets a little bit more into the Kundalini transmutation,
all this other stuff.
That stuff is another decoy, another distraction.
All that tantric stuff, transmutation, okay.
All that stuff, that energy stuff, if you study its roots,
it's all emo work, all of it.
All of it is emo work, including yoga.
When you say yoga to a westerner,
they think it's bending your body in uncomfortable positions, right,
where a real yoga master would say don't do it if it's uncomfortable.
Yoga is only 10% exercise and physical stretching, right?
90% of it is state of mind, right?
It's emo, believe it or not.
So we've gone through the emo and the importance of that.
From private messages and emails,
there are still quite a few people working on the emo with success, by the way.
It's been a couple of years, and, yes, it does take that long, right?
But they're glad that they're doing it.
It's much like martial arts.
The majority of that is not about the stances you take
or the defense postures and all this kind of stuff.
Yes, indeed, those things can be useful,
but the truth is that the majority of it is internal and it's about control.
Yeah, a short way to say that is the martial arts that are taught,
especially to westerners, to put your key, your life energy, outside of yourself.
Right.
Where the higher schools are to keep all of the energy inside of you,
not in a detrimental way, but to contain it and use it from within
and also use the energy of others.
Yeah, so if you want to, by the way,
even the highest form would be Qigong, Tai Chi, right?
Qigong, Qigong.
But even that has been, you're not going to get.
That's emo work again.
That's emo work, you know.
Yeah.
Okay, what does fear do to the energy?
Okay, well, it seems to be important in sacrifice ritual society, hungry entities.
Yeah, fear is a very simple way to think of fear is two ways.
One is, okay, the way that most people use it is to disable you, right?
It's disabling.
What does that mean?
Okay, just that, it's disabling.
Yeah, no, it disables and disrupts.
If you think about that, just no matter what the circumstances,
when you're in fear, you're not able to make as clear a decision.
You're not able to function as well.
It's just that simple.
And then there's another one, another type of fear, which is not discussed,
which is in the higher spiritual circles.
And I've brought it up, but I've not discussed it.
And I won't discuss it here much, but I'll bring it up again.
When something is of so much utmost significance to you,
it's a fear energy that there is no option but to proceed.
So, in other words, the disabling fear that makes someone a coward
that cries in the foxhole, that same energy, just slightly focused
in a different way, like low pressure water versus high pressure water,
in a high pressure fear, that's the one that drives the guy
on the front line to run into a stream of bullets, right?
You see?
The bravest guy in the army is driven by fear.
And the weakest guy, the yellow belly, the guy that gets shot
for whatever is also fear.
One aspect of fear, like two sides of a coin,
heads or tails are black and white, one is very yin, one is very yang.
The disabling one makes you very yin, scattered.
And the inspirational one, I'll give you an example of the other fear.
Soccer mom, minivan full of children, coming back from a soccer game
or softball game is actually more popular, right?
And she loves her children, she's having a conversation,
car accident, car flips, minivan flips, 90 pound, 110, 120 pound,
5'3", mom gets out and she flips the van back up that, you know,
two or three power lifters would have a hard time doing.
What made her do that is fear of harm coming to those children.
You see?
So when fear is blanketly used one way, whenever you're just shown one thing,
like, you know, in politics they do that.
This guy's bad, this guy's good, well, you're on this side, right?
That's why, no, it's never one, right?
It's the same thing, right?
It's the same thing no matter who it's politics.
Fear is kind of political.
You can go one way or another, right?
So one group might want to instill the disabling fear on another group,
but the other fear is more individual,
the one that focuses and brings inspiration and you have no option.
These 100 pound soccer mom that had to turn the minivan over on her own
to save the children did it out of fear of what?
Fear of harm coming to those children.
You see?
So that's never discussed.
Yeah, even if you take a look at the run speed on somebody, you know,
when they're truly focused by their fear,
they can run at a much faster rate than they ever could in any other circumstance.
It would be the fight or flight.
The fight or flight is that fear we're talking about now.
So if you stay and fight, it's not because you're cowardly.
And if you run faster, it's not because you're cowardly either.
I mean Bruce Lee said run from a fight first if you can run, right,
instead of fighting.
Fighting is the last option.
But, okay, so that's about the fear energy.
It's a duality there.
And one is bad, one is good, yes, depending, right?
So and that ties in with the animals also, right?
It's a very primordial, very deep because dogs could sense fear.
I'll give the analogy.
One person is a dog lover.
The other person is afraid of dogs.
They both walk up to a junkyard dog by a fence.
Neither of them say anything.
Who is the junkyard dog going to start barking at?
The one who is afraid of dogs, even though they haven't exhibited any fear, right?
They can read that in your aura, let's say, in your being.
Okay.
Any information you're willing to share about underground people?
That would be more on the archaic side and Donald Marshall's side.
Donald Marshall talks about the Saurians.
The Saurians were an old race, a reptilian race, upright.
They speak and all that.
And the underground people.
Underground is something that everyone always goes to.
And given the analogy that, you know, I built a new house.
And I'm having new furniture for the new house.
Makes sense, right?
Furniture company delivers the furniture.
Do I tell them to put all the furniture, bedroom, living room, kitchen on the roof?
Or do I tell them to put the furniture inside each corresponding room inside the house?
And if I lived on the roof like that, all the neighbors would be saying, what an idiot.
What's wrong with him?
Right?
Something wrong.
So if you see, whenever you see people living on the surface, they're subject to weather events, cosmic events, right?
All this other stuff.
An advanced society, all advanced societies live underground inside the dwelling.
The earth is the dwelling, right?
That's all I can say about the underground people.
Far more advanced.
Way more advanced, right?
I mean, put it this way.
Let's say you do find a neighborhood, one of these ticky-tacky neighborhoods, suburbia or whatever.
I'm not talking about Appalachian crazy people, but suburban neighborhood.
You drive down the street.
Everyone's in their houses.
Let's say it's dusk.
You could look inside their homes.
They have their blinds drawn.
They're having dinner, watching TV in the living room.
You could see inside, right?
And here you come upon a house with all this furniture and all this stuff and tarps, and they're living on the roof.
And the house is all boarded up down below.
Wow!
What's wrong with that picture?
Right?
You see?
That's basically the point that I'm trying to make.
We should have taken advantage of it.
It has been taken advantage of.
And I think if you try to go down there, you're going to get in big trouble.
You're not allowed because you're one of the surface dummies.
There were laws passed, I think, federal laws, that if you go more than, what, eight feet underground, you know, without – or if you find a cave, you can't go more than ten feet inside of it.
Otherwise, it's like ten years in prison, right?
Something like that.
They made it very serious now.
They really don't want any mingling.
What role do these underground societies are playing with the world today?
Well, those are the ones running the surface.
Very simple, right?
Are they working with surface groups to keep things hidden?
Absolutely.
For benevolent or malevolent reasons?
Both.
Are they physical beings in that or perceivable world?
Yeah.
Because you can go into certain parts underground.
It's provable that the densities are so high that you cannot have any physicality.
Okay.
So I found most myths, stories, and symbols in all religions, and even Disney ironically, are actually stories that are at least tens of thousands – at least thousands of years old.
Not tens, just thousands of years old.
Everything is just retold in different ways, but it's clearly all the same.
Yes.
Whose stories are they?
Well, again, you just tie it into the people.
It's what we're permitted to, right?
We live in a society where information and what people talk about is permissible or non-permissible, right?
Hey, I'd like to add into something here a question because nobody ever answers this one for me.
There are parts of the ocean that we've never seen, depths that we're not able to get to.
Yeah.
Well, they have been seen and they're very well known, but they're not discussed again.
Well, the general public does not know and we're told if you go down too far, we're just crushed and we can't get any further down, right?
That's what we're told.
But one would think that would be an even better place to conceal things than …
For temporary.
Yeah.
Because oceans change very quickly.
That's been scrubbed from our history.
Archaics, again, will give you a lot of that.
In the future, even in the biblical in Isaiah, we won't have – the earth will no longer have oceans.
It will have seas and lakes and rivers, but not oceans.
OK.
Yeah.
In other words, we won't be 70 percent water on the surface or 80 percent.
It will be the other way around.
It will be 30 percent water and trillions and hundreds of billions of people could live here easily.
I mean right now, I think everyone on the planet, if there are – I don't believe that there are seven or eight billion people because the bankers are keeping those records, right?
Those are World Bank numbers.
Right, right.
And bankers keep double books and they lie and it's in their benefit to have more people that create more commercial paper.
I think it's less than half of that.
I think I gave the analogy.
They say that 80 percent of the people in China have cell phones, but there are only 300 million cell phone accounts.
So if you do the math, there's only six or – right?
700 million or something?
Yeah.
Or less, 600 million, not a billion and a half?
No, the thing is if you've got a billion and a half people in China, then that means you would need a minimum.
One point something billion cell phones and there aren't that many.
Right.
So the cell phone records audit, oops, that got out, right?
Yeah.
So there's not that many.
So if you factor that in, there's probably no more than three billion people on the max, right?
But even at the seven billion number, everyone could live comfortably, comfortably like in a tight suburban setting.
In Texas, all seven billion people.
Anyone that's driven around – I mean I've gone – when I go from here to Tucson to California, there's stretches of I-10 that I go on for an hour and a half and I see nothing, nothing.
I mean there's of course service stations, but if you pull over from the service station and decide to get off I-10 and go north or south, there's nothing there for hours.
Right.
We're not overpopulated.
Yeah, no, not at all.
That's the other funny question because even if you just look at what they call the United States, right, and they tell you how many people are supposed to be here, I don't think it's that many and it seems to me like there's a whole lot of land that's not really being used by people.
All of the land is not – like if you could fit everyone in what's called the Texas state, it's very insignificant, especially if you factor in that there are really not that many people as they say, right?
Right.
We don't have any independent consensus of how many people there are, only the banks, right?
And the reason they tell you there's shortages is because they don't know how to handle the monetization, not because there's shortages of water, gold, food or anything, right?
I do have a problem with like five billion cattle being slaughtered in America alone or something outrageous like that.
We don't need to do that at all, right?
That many animals – animal factory farming, right?
It doesn't have to be done and all that.
Yeah, there are issues, things that are overdone, right?
And the use of petroleum products as they're being used as fuels.
We should have a hydrogen economy, not a petroleum, right?
And it's been proven that the best lubricants are not petroleum-based.
They're plant-based, right?
There's – it's Mobile One which is a very good mobile – a motor oil.
Right.
And their highest research laboratory is constantly – they don't do it much anymore.
From their research labs, when they did publish papers, the oils that lasted the longest with the most heat and the most – less viscosity breakdown were plant-based.
Go figure.
So we don't have – yeah, it's just certain things need to be adjusted and not done as much.
And when you do that, then we're on our way to let's say more than sustainable, right?
So – and start doing commerce without money.
Well, the banker's money that they use.
Go back to where a nickel bought you a steak dinner.
No pun intended.
I just mentioned cows.
Too many cows being slaughtered.
But you know what I mean, right?
If you look at old movies, it was what?
Five cents, ten cents for dinner?
Steak dinner, right?
Right.
So if you go back to that, so you don't need all that monetization.
Yeah, it's pretty easy to fix the world.
Most attorneys and doctors and whatever will meet their demise.
But before they meet their demise, what you do is you give them an option.
You know how they have those weed killers that are toxic?
You have the doctors and attorneys pull the weeds and they herd goats and sheep.
That's what people used to do before, goat herders and sheep herders.
The farmers would welcome them before planting to pass their herds over the fields to eat all the weeds, right?
Right.
And if you don't have enough sheep or goats, you have attorneys and doctors picking the weeds.
Or, you know, the terminate them with extreme prejudice.
You know what that means, right?
Of course.
Because most of them are responsible for killing people.
At least every doctor is responsible.
I would suggest average doctors, if they practiced, you know, 20 years, has killed at least a thousand people directly.
Each one.
So over a 20 year period.
So we're talking about Charles Manson being a Cub Scout.
So we're talking about the average practitioner now.
They do it through prescriptions and whatever.
Okay.
So that's not opinion, by the way.
So all these adjustments can be made pretty simply.
All right.
So here's one.
Was lead paint in buildings more beneficial than harmful?
No.
Yes and no.
Not necessary.
The original paints were calcimine.
Basically, when you hired someone to paint your home, they showed up with a wagon with all these powders.
Right.
And they mixed the paint on site using linseed oil and various other things.
When you call a paint contractor now or you want to paint, you go and you buy these liquid paint.
It wasn't like that back in the day.
We were talking about using big, expensive brushes before we got on.
So the lead paint is a factor of the oil industry again.
And the scare about lead paint and children eating them was overdone because when lead is added to paint, it becomes encapsulated.
It's very – you can eat as much lead paint as you want and will not come down in most cases with lead poisoning.
It was done from other things that they've experimented on people.
They had to blame it on something just like they blame lung cancer on cigarette smoking.
When it wasn't, it was actually all the nuclear testing they were doing.
People were breathing the air down.
No one in California got lung cancer unless you were a black woman or a Jewish woman.
Anyways, read the stats on what I mean by that.
So it's encapsulated.
Recently I heard a short part of an interview with Philip K. Dick's wife.
She was talking about her childhood and how they were trying to eradicate polio by giving everyone, the young children, polio vaccines every year.
There's no such thing as polio.
That was from the DDT spraying of flies, nervous damage.
But anyway, she said that every year after the polio vaccines, only half the classroom would be alive because they were killing off – right?
Right.
Every year they were killing off half the people with these things.
But again, where's the outrage?
So I'm not saying lead paint is good for you, but I'm saying that it was blamed for many other things that were being done.
In terms of energy, Faraday cage blocking signals radiation.
Yeah, Faraday cages work in most cases.
I have seen where they do not work.
That's another discussion.
That's when you're using a Tesla-based – let's just say with Tesla coils.
I'm not into directing people.
Yes, it's technology that's worth looking into.
But if you go on YouTube or whatever, it's everyone making sparks, and that's because they're not adjusted properly.
It's kind of like saying we're working on our cars and all this black smoke is coming out.
That means like something's wrong with your car, right?
So if you're working with Tesla coils and making sparks, there's something wrong with your coil, right?
Okay.
But if you can create a circuit where you generate – it's going to be 1.6 or 1.8 times the speed of light going through the circuit.
The Faraday cage will have a hard time blocking that.
That ties into the previous conversation we've had with an alternative Internet powered or carried by ham radio type.
But not through the air with ham antennas but through the ground where you'd be propagating through the ground at twice the speed of light.
In terms of what they tell you, the upper limit is just a constant in a vacuum.
All right.
Carl Jung, what do you think of his work, especially his idea of the collective unconscious?
Is he correct?
Dummy loans?
Yeah.
Anything that's been put out that the mainstream knows is a dummy loan unless you pick it all apart and pick the corn out of the poop.
I haven't used that in a long time.
Yeah.
I don't know much about Carl Jung.
There's something about him that didn't ring right with me.
It's just like Freud.
All I know about him and Freud, for example, is what everyone else knows from reading comic books.
Okay.
So empathy, what's the significance of – by the way, I have not read this email like I'm reading it now.
I just skimmed over it.
Okay.
So empathy, what's the significance of empaths?
Why do things touch them so deeply?
Well, who's them?
We all have the ability.
If one person can be empathic, everyone is empathic.
It's just whether or not they've taken control.
It's just like saying I know someone who plays golf.
Well, anybody could play golf, right?
Yeah.
Or try to play it.
It's the same thing.
It's just a skill.
Whether they do it badly or not is another question.
Yeah.
It's just like – well, yeah.
It's just like the – but it's a terrible – you get yelled at.
If you go to a golf tournament and your guy let's say does well and you – let's say a small crowd of people start clapping, they'll throw you out of the tournament for doing that, right?
You're supposed to be really quiet.
Talk about a solemn sport.
There's no cheering, right?
Aloud.
Okay.
Should there be transforming or control of these energies?
It's like emo work again, right?
Sending and receiving.
It's all emo.
We're never told what the purpose of emotions are.
I feel like I only heard part of the question because – what energy?
Oh, empathy.
What's the significance of empaths?
Why do things touch them so deeply?
Should there be transforming or control of those energies?
Oh, okay, okay.
I didn't –
Yeah, absolutely.
Controlled by first of all realizing that we're all – could it – let's look at it this way.
Could it be possible that we've ignored and left something so unacknowledged that we could now deny its existence?
Yeah.
Yeah, of course.
Pretty much.
That's pretty much what's going on with it.
I think maybe though the question there is more about is there a purpose for – okay.
How can that be used?
Let's say – I mean empathy is informative, right?
I mean that's really what it is.
It's how much you're allowing yourself to be informed through the emo.
Yes, of course.
It's the two-way street on the emo.
Yeah.
What are you picking up?
We do it – you know what?
You can be – and time and distance doesn't matter by the way with empathy, right?
You don't have to be even near the person.
But we have so much filtered out with that stream of information.
It's a very subtle information.
That's a big subject but it's emo.
Emo.
Learn how to set yourself up for receiving, right?
You know the thing about giving energy?
I've always given the metaphor.
When you give someone a hug, that's the giving energy.
You feel a rise, right?
Right.
So if you want to receive something, that would be whether it's a surprise or not.
Let's say a party where you're given a present or a gift.
There are lots of holidays for that.
When you see someone saying, hey, I got something for you.
They're going and getting let's say the present or the gift.
You know that feeling you have?
It's kind of like the hug but it's in the opposite direction.
You're waiting to accept something, right?
Right.
Do you remember like someone saying – or a very simple way to remember this is if you
receive post where you live, the postman comes to the front of your house, gets out
and starts walking towards the mailbox and you now anticipate going to the mailbox and
getting what he's putting in.
He hasn't put it in there yet.
He's on his way putting it in there.
That feeling right there, that's an empathic feeling.
You're receiving, right?
Okay.
So anytime you anticipate receiving something is the emo.
Well, you can – it doesn't have to be that way.
I like giving these examples just to set – so look what is he talking about, right?
Like the dummy load being a treadmill.
So the giving would be the hug and the receiving would be anticipating receiving something.
Not – but still in the phase – okay.
This is the detail that I can't – I have to underscore.
When someone says I'm going to give you something, it's in the car.
When they depart from that point and you're waiting for them to show up again, before
they show up, that's the feeling.
Once they show up and they're carrying something and you see what they're carrying, the empathy
falls away.
It starts to fade away because now you know – you start to form the construct.
Oh, it's a small box or it's really small.
It might be jewelry, right?
Or it's something that's really heavy.
Oh, it might be some stereo, right?
Or something, right?
Or TV.
So it's the open-ended reception.
It's not about the focus on the particulars.
It's about –
Exactly.
It's the notion of knowing you're going to receive something and you don't know what
it is.
Otherwise, you're not really an empath.
You're coloring the situation, right?
Okay.
So it would be like also receiving a guest.
You come over at 4 o'clock.
4 o'clock comes around and you know they should be here but there's no sign of them
here yet at all.
No sign.
Like they haven't pulled up.
You looked out in the distance.
Where are they?
That is also you're trying to receive, right?
But once you see them in the distance, the empathy then now becomes colored, becomes
constructive and it's no longer empathy.
Now, you're relying on your eyes or your ears or your previous experiences.
The thing about being a good empath is not putting any conditions on or attaching it
to anything that you've ever had before or accepted as a thought before.
It's completely new thinking, completely new thought, right?
Okay.
That's the cleanest, right?
Otherwise, you're coloring.
Otherwise, you're overlaying what you think it should be and it's not.
It can be but you're not an empath.
And you're narrowing it down at that point, right?
Because now the anticipation before also involves a lot of unexpected things that could occur.
Yeah, there's no presumption.
So there's no – yeah, there you go.
There's no presumption.
Yeah.
If there's any presumption, there's no empathy.
There we go.
Okay.
That's why the legal system is based on presumption.
Okay, views on cannabis, so many types, so whatever.
It's not for me.
Is it a positive thing?
Yeah, I would say so.
I think it's one of those things that – you know how they say if voting did anything,
it would be illegal, right?
So cannabis was made illegal.
Guess why?
Because it was good for you, right?
Like raw milk is illegal, right?
Right.
So just from a political, administrative, governmental, societal point of view, if
it's made illegal, it probably has benefits to it.
Personally, it's not for me.
There are certain things that are not for me.
It's just not for me.
It turns me into a piece of the furniture.
So but yeah, if you use it well, yeah.
That's what I see.
I think what I would like to start experimenting with is since – if you go to a smoke shop,
it's all these cannabinoids now, right?
Yeah.
There are even drinks like sodas, like little $5 sodas with – I don't know, all kinds
of stuff.
I'd like to try it out.
I haven't.
We'll see.
To be continued.
Use of liquid mercury in ancient structures.
Well, not only that.
It was medicine.
When people had some kind of food poisoning, they drank a half a cup of mercury, believe
it or not.
Okay.
Back in the days – and it makes you think about these things.
Well, remember like you experienced it growing up roughly when I did.
When you had a cut, you went into the medicine chest and you put what on it?
Mercurochrome, which was chromium and mercury, which are two like class A hazardous things
right now.
Yeah, you can't get it.
It was very effective.
You can't get it anymore.
No.
What they did was they decided to ban it because they dipped the baby in it, an entire infant
and the baby died from it, of course, right?
So you could have just drowned it in water and banned water but they would love to do
that but they can't because that will be a revolution.
Right.
Okay.
Use of liquid mercury in ancient structures.
Yeah, it's a dielectric and a conductor.
It's both.
It's very yin and it could carry a lot of yang energy.
I'll just leave it as that.
Of course, most of the areas in South America where they suggested there were people being
sacrificed, which they did also, these rock structures that were carvings that look like
someone would lay down and have their heart removed, was actually they're finding evidence
that they were just pouring mercury down these pyramids.
So, yeah, lots of mercury.
It's, yeah, lots of myth about it because, again, it's considered a hazardous substance
now just to keep it out of people's minds, right?
But, again, it's not something that's easily available.
Okay, thoughts on people like Ram Dass, Terence McKenna.
Not much.
Don't know much about him.
I have been exposed to them.
Didn't do anything for me.
Different pathway.
Too much presumption.
Too much carryover from formal academia, I guess, which is toxic, right?
It's been too adulterated.
There's some people out there that are on the alternative fringe on different things
and they start making...
I'll give you an example.
Alternative medicine people.
Oh, we found that this herb lowers blood pressure.
Oh, my gosh.
It just destroyed you.
Oh, my gosh, right?
Or this will help you with diabetes.
Oh, my gosh.
There's no diabetes.
By the way, dementia is now considered type three diabetes.
Yeah, well, okay.
It can't get any more in your face than it is.
There's no such thing.
It's a liver dysfunction and it goes really...
It's just like AIDS.
You start taking our treatment, you will get worse and worse and worse.
You go from insulin shots to kidney failure to death.
And parts of your body, you get arms and feet cut off, right?
Usually feet, right?
Yeah, feet.
The yin part, yeah, feet.
It's always the lower part.
Yeah, because the yang energy runs away.
So, yeah, if you are getting treatment for diabetes or whatever,
you will get worse and worse and worse because there is no such thing.
It's a liver dysfunction.
Same with AIDS.
If you get tested for AIDS and get treatment, you will die for sure.
If you say that you've been tested positive for AIDS,
you laugh and say there's no such thing.
Bye.
It's just like saying stay home because Santa Claus is coming, right?
This is how we do it.
It's in your face.
It can't be any more in your face than it is already, you know,
about all these things.
And high blood pressure, there's like what,
40 million Americans on blood pressure medication,
which destroys your liver.
Statin medication destroys the liver, right?
They're all, right?
You know, if you're that.
Here's coming like I did the credit card analogy, right?
Most people who use credit cards don't know how the money system works,
but if you do and you use it, you're an idiot because basically
you're destroying the system.
Here's the thing.
If you're that stupid that you think you have AIDS or diabetes,
you may be deserved to, you know, that kind of,
I'm not that type of person because if I ran into someone like that,
I'd say stop what you're doing with them immediately and show them it
does.
I don't care about what they're giving you.
It's not, you shouldn't have never believed it in the first place.
Right?
Right.
So, but if you do continue down that path and you don't have a way out,
I don't know, call it natural selection, whatever.
I don't know.
I can't,
I can't go down that route because the outreach,
it's so obvious that what this is medical fiction, you know,
they've almost put it out there without saying it.
It should be obvious at this point.
And the constant is they always have something new and then they reinsert
opium into the equation.
And that's,
what do you mean by opium?
Well,
the,
anything that they,
you know,
is an opioid derivative,
whatever.
Fentanyl stuff.
Yeah.
I'm all for fentanyl by the way,
but not the way that it's gotten the rap.
If you can have create something as 20,
30,
40,
50,
80 times stronger than heroin or morphine.
Well,
now you can have these tiny little,
like if someone's in an act included in a,
in,
in a medical kits,
because when people get into a really bad accident,
right.
Most people will die from trauma when they don't have to from pain,
take,
you know,
make a tiny little pinprick that will numb it out until you can get
the proper alignment or,
you know,
treatment.
Right.
Instead of dying from pain,
make it available,
but in a very respectable,
responsible way.
Right.
Well,
yeah,
exactly.
But that's the thing.
I have no problem with opium in and of itself,
but the thing is they keep reintroducing these different derivative
products.
And that's,
but it's part of the cycle of the popular,
like right now there's this thing called Ozempic.
Have you heard of it?
No,
no,
I tried it years ago.
I might've,
if it was new now,
I try to just to look the other way.
Cause it's just so ridiculous what they're doing.
No,
I think we did mention anything that's come out less than 20 years is void.
Yeah.
No,
but,
but the thing about this is that,
you know,
every,
every 10 years or so,
there is a brand new look.
This is the miracle drug,
right?
This is the miracle drug.
And I mean,
I'm talking about for the,
for the existence of this thing called the United States for the past
coming from the medical morons.
Yeah.
People don't know better because they spend most of their effort that you
trust them and no effort on quote unquote science.
Right.
But the thing is,
but the thing that is noticeable is a continuous pattern of here's the new
miracle drug.
Here's the new thing.
And it's always,
and constantly the thing that really ends up killing people.
Yeah.
That's the idea.
And that is the idea,
but it's just amazing to me that it's like,
you know,
no matter what,
nobody ever picks up on it.
Even afterwards they go,
well,
that drug was bad.
We got to get rid of it.
Here's your lawsuit.
Here's the,
this,
here's the,
you know,
it's job security for the attorneys.
Right.
And that's all it is is continuous job security for the attorneys,
but also security for the,
you know,
the two main companies.
Cause believe it or not,
there's only two that actually handled the distribution of drugs.
You know what I mean?
And it goes above.
It's the,
who holds those companies?
Probably the,
you know,
what we're told Vanguard,
black rock and all that.
Right.
And that's,
and that's the beauty of it.
But what I find funny is that there's always a miracle drug,
you know,
like in the nineties,
the psychotropic,
they say there's a miracle drug.
There isn't.
Well,
but in the nineties,
the miracle drug would be pristine food when there wouldn't be a drug.
Exactly.
But actually,
you know,
I needed oxygen about 10 years ago for a water processing.
And I called around,
they're like,
we,
you can't buy oxygen without a license.
Cause it's a drug.
This is how brainwashed they are.
I think it's,
yeah,
it's time for the mop up crew.
You know what I mean?
It's,
it's going to get a lot worse before it gets any better.
That's why they introduced the term controlled substance,
you know?
Cause yeah.
And classified it.
Yeah.
But look,
if people are going to accept that,
maybe they deserve the side effects of it.
Ah,
understood.
So do you have anything else left in that email?
No,
that's it.
Yeah.