Sonic event 20 rated Y and here we are again, my apologies right out of the gate for my
voice tonight.
But then again, who knows what day it is, what time it is, as you hear us because they
are recorded for later listening.
Anyway, Greek, how are you on this wonderful occasion of Sonic event 20?
Yeah, 20.
Ecosy, right?
Ecosahedron.
That's one of those weird platonic solids.
Have you ever heard of Ecosahedron, which is 20?
It resembles water, supposedly.
I have a bone to pick with all that stuff that they've pushed on the public because
there's more to it about the ether.
They're supposed to be ethereal shapes.
But anyway, that's another Sonic probably.
I wanted to bring up an email back in the day a few months ago when I started putting
out notices that we're going to be doing rated Y.
I got an email from someone and it was like it would be aired as being sarcastic and fiery
and forward, but I did enjoy it.
And it started off paraphrasing something like, yeah, I see you're going to be speaking
again.
That's great.
What are you going to be talking about?
How to make perfect rice and everything else that's going on?
I don't know if you're familiar with it.
I did a couple of either private, semi-private public Sonics on Common Radio back in the
day about cooking.
I think we have Joe, I think.
I'll mention him by name.
He doesn't mind.
He really liked the potato recipe for baked potatoes.
Fire up an oven where you can do it stove top, right?
Right.
No, he still loves that.
He does that.
He mentions it to me all the time.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, the thing is, the point of that is Native Americans said white man, racist voice, white
man, big fire, a lot of smoke, little heat.
Indian, small fire, no smoke, a lot of heat, right?
Right.
So being efficient is really where it's at.
So the email went sort of fiery like that.
Anyone else, I think, could have taken it like as a sarcastic, but I like that kind of
stuff.
I like fire.
I mean like people on edge about a subject or an approach.
Not that they are on edge as a character, but it's fine to have edgy talk, right?
Let's have edgy emails.
So start off, I thought about that because I've kind of reflected on several things
that this is pertinent.
Why?
Because first of all, I want to mention again, when you're making rice, folks, I've talked
about pressure cooker is the way to go.
No matter what rice, you just have to know how to use a pressure cooker if you don't
have one.
Anything with a pot with a really tight lid.
If you buy Allclad, it's a brand.
I'm not sponsored or anything, but the Allclad, all their lids kind of fit inside of the pot,
most of them, and they kind of like with a nice tight fit.
Not quite a press fit, but a very tight slip fit.
And if you put a weight on it, a coffee mug turned upside down over the handle.
If it's a strap handle, you have to grind it out so the strap fits through.
And a brick wrapped in aluminum foil, because you know how bricks like to give off sand
even if you clean it.
They're soft.
And keep the lid on really tight.
It is a ghetto, I call, on the make improvisation cooker, rice cooker.
And the other thing that's imperative, which I've always used, but I haven't for a while,
and I've gone back to even making more perfect rice, is one thing that's indispensable in
a kitchen, especially if you understand the subtleties of cooking, which is management
of heat, is what's called a heat diffuser plate.
You can get them anywhere.
I mean, they're really, really cheap.
I remember back in the day they were a dollar in Chinatown on Canal Street.
Boy, I'm giving too much geography here.
But meaning like, I mean, if anyone's been lower Manhattan, Canal Street, you can pretty
much get anything there.
Yeah, pretty much.
It's real inexpensive.
So, I mean, you've got those places, parts of town in most big cities.
So, heat diffuser, you won't get that crusty burn on the bottom and it just cooks more
evenly.
You just got to give it a little more heat in the beginning, put the diffuser under the
pot once everything comes up to temp.
So, these are all very subtle, subtle things to manage.
By the way, one of the most difficult, not daunting, it can be based on the person's
character and skill level.
Again, that's why I keep insisting through Sonics that people need to increase their skill
level on anything.
But cooking is extremely challenging because there's no limit on how fine and how perfect
and how delicious it can be when you think about it, right?
If you ever remember, I remember when I was young, there was the Abbott Ice Cream Company
under the 86th Street subway and we'd go there with our bikes.
This was back in the mid-70s, early 70s actually.
And you know those Abbott, I don't even know if they're in business anymore, the little
ice cream sandwiches for nickel, they'd be in the freezer, you'd go to the newspaper
stand, right?
And you get the little ice cream sandwich wrapped in wax paper.
It was like the cheapest thing to get.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I don't know if Abbott still exists, but yeah, of course.
Yeah, it was Abbott or something like that or Clark or something.
We knew where they were making them and we would go knock on the door of like four or
five of us on our bicycles, right?
Training wheels that come off like a month before, right?
So when I say bicycles, you get the picture here.
Kind of like E.T., the movie or Stranger Things.
Anyway, we knock on the door and a guy comes out.
He's got the big plastic rubber apron and the galoshes and the boots because it's all these
machinery.
It's cold and wet and all that.
Oh, you guys.
So he comes out with a cardboard box.
How many are you here?
All right, here, here.
And he's handing out these fresh ice cream sandwiches and they tasted nothing at all
like the ones you bought in the store because the ones that the wafer was soft when you
bought it in the store, but when you got it initially at the factory, it was very crispy
and crunchy.
Right.
The reason why later on I found out is because water evaporates at a higher rate once the
temperature goes below minus 20, right?
And it goes even, that's why you get freezer burn, right?
The evaporation water rate starts to rise very fast.
That's why, for example, you'd see people in the mountainous areas, let's say northwest,
they saw a Sasquatch footprint, right?
Well, a size nine foot overnight, if the temperature drops, that snow evaporates and now it's a
size 16 or size 18, right?
I don't know if you've ever noticed that.
Only happens when it gets colder, though.
It's a phenomenon.
Well, I can tell you, you know the Carvel ice cream, right?
For the whole northeastern area.
I got to tell you the reason why people love those flying saucers, which is what they call
a round one, is exactly this reason.
The cookie is still crisp because-
That's right.
If you wrap it, later on when it was wrapped in plastic and put it in the freezer, it was
not.
Right.
But the thing is, but still you stand a chance, even today, if you go and get them, if they
freshly made them.
See, that's the thing.
It hasn't had time for this other stuff to happen.
So, in a lot of cases, I don't know if Carvel still exists, but maybe about 10 years ago.
Yeah, I think they were absorbed.
There was an old Greek guy who did it.
He wanted soft serve ice cream.
You know that motion, that motion that you, you know, when the soft serve, you have to
move a cone a certain way when the soft serve's coming out of the machine, right?
To make that swirl?
Yeah.
That motion you do with your hand?
Okay, well in the fourth grade, I don't know, back in the elementary school days, right
before classes started in the homeroom or whatever, the principal or notary would make
a speech.
You know, you do this Pledge of Allegiance and then the, on the PA and all the classrooms,
there's this important things or whatever.
It was the assistant principal or principal.
I don't know if you remember that or they did that.
Yeah, they did that in high school, yeah.
Okay.
Well, when the assistant principal came on, he sounded just like the owner of the Carvel
ice cream company on the TV commercials.
Exactly.
So, when his voice came on, I started gesturing that I was making an ice cream cone and the
teacher points me out and sends me to the principal's office for being rude.
So, I really know what his voice sounds like.
True story, you know.
So, I just wanted to, you know.
Yeah, no, look, and if people are not familiar with the Northeast, he did have a distinctive
sound, the guy's voice on the TV commercials was.
Right.
Very distinctive and of course, my favorite is when they introduced cookie puss, which
And they made fun of it.
Yeah.
It was good.
It kind of sounds like you if you had a really bad sinus congestion.
Yeah.
And went maybe half an hour, a little bit lower.
Anyway.
So, I want to bring up food, food, food, food.
What's that we're going to be talking about?
What I wanted to get to was basically back the feeling in that email was kind of like
excitement that there's going to be more sonic events, but you know, like what are you going
to talk about?
I make perfect rice in this world, you know, meaning in this world, you know, however you
want to take it, right?
It's pretty shitty, right?
So, I want to attach this also to the topic that I've been bringing up, which is the
email and clearing one's mind and all that.
But before we get into any of all that directly, I'm going to do this in real time.
Hopefully, my memory serves me right from what I've been doing and walking around here
in the office.
Let me pull this book out here.
This is a – I got an Aramaic English New Testament recently.
Thank you very much.
Let's see.
And I'm going to do what I normally don't like doing, but it's important because it's
the most poignant way to describe what I'm doing with Rated Y with you as well.
And so – and what's coming?
What's this all about?
And it's poignant, meaning it's a lot.
It means a lot.
It's very much encompassing.
And also, I want to use it to correct the context that many, many, many, many people
use a particular term, that the kingdom of heaven or kingdom of God is within you.
And you hear all of these people constantly saying, not that they're religious, God
is within you.
How many times have you heard that?
It just makes me – yeah.
Okay.
Now, here's the thing.
You can say that.
You can say anything.
But once you start – let's say that God is within you, kingdom of heaven is within
you, extended a little bit more in the conversation, they'll say something like, yeah, Bible,
whatever it is, it's got some good stuff in it anyway.
Right?
So they always reference that comes back from the Bible.
I want to know where they got the license to use it out of context.
As far as I know, there is no license to use anything literal out of context, as far as
I know.
It can be done.
Right?
You know what I mean, using it out of context.
And I always made the analogy of, you know, you can take a chocolate chip – you want
to start a religion?
Real simple.
Don't think about it too much, because the more you think about it, you're going to
screw it up.
Keep it really the KISS principle.
You get a chocolate chip cookie recipe and you rewrite it a certain way.
You get it, rewrite it, and you make a cookie.
And one of the cookies eventually is going to come out looking like the Virgin Mary.
And you put it all over.
You show the cookie, right?
And you have your recipe rewritten.
And you know how many people – you're going to get thousands of people asking you,
how'd that cookie crumble, man?
Right?
You get it?
It's kind of like – it's so simple to do this.
So where do they get license to take things out of some place and apply it to however
they want to use it?
That's the baseball bat principle again.
So what I want to do – what I don't like to do is read from what they call the Bible.
This is – I like this because it has a better texture than King James.
And it actually – a while back I did look at the Aramaic on this, and it was pretty
clean.
And this one is pretty clean.
So I'm going to start sort of in the middle of chapter 17, because it's chock full of
stuff.
It's got about five different subjects.
But this is the important part.
Now, keep in mind, as I'm reading this whole thing, the reason I'm bringing this
up is because people – I hear people still, videos or whatever, say that God is within
you, the kingdom is within you.
And I'm going to say a little more after that.
Right?
You ready?
Sure.
This is the context, okay?
Okay.
And when he was near to entering into a certain village, ten men who were lepers met him,
and they stood from a distance.
And they raised their voices and said, Our Master Yahshua, have mercy on us.
And when he saw them, he said to them, Go show yourselves to the priests.
And they were cleansed while they were going.
But – I'm going to stop right there.
So you'll notice he doesn't heal anyone, right?
Every time that people – it's – right?
All these miracles, you know, when he – the water to wine, he didn't turn the water
into wine.
He told the servants, Do this and do that.
Right?
Remember?
The loaves of – all the fish and the loaves of bread to all those people.
He says, Just grab those baskets and do this.
Right.
You ever notice that?
It's all third – people think he did these miracles.
He was a component, the catalyst of it.
Right.
Okay?
But one of them, when he saw that he was cleansed, returned with a loud voice, giving praise
to Elohim.
And he fell upon his face before the feet of Yahshua while thanking him.
And he, this man, was a Samaritan.
And Yahshua answered and said, Were there not ten who were cleansed?
Where are the nine?
For what did they separate?
There's – actually, there's more in there in the Aramaic.
But for what should they separate that they should come and give praise to Elohim?
Only this man did, who was from foreign people.
And he said to him, Arise, go.
Your faith has given you life.
And when those from the Pharisees asked when the kingdom of Elohim would come, he answered
and said to them, The kingdom of Elohim, or God, does not come by observation.
Neither will they say, Behold, here it is, nor behold, there it is.
For the kingdom of Elohim is within you.
I'm going to stop right there.
I should keep going to keep the context.
But if you remember, I said, I'm going to start in the middle of chapter 17.
And the first thing I said, and when he was near to entering into a certain village,
ten men who were lepers met him, right?
Okay.
When that statement is used in context, that the kingdom of Elohim is within you,
he's referring to the village, not the individual's body.
You get it?
You ever hear about, What the hell's going on in this place?
Right?
Someone walks in here, in a room, let's say, What the hell's going on in here?
Right.
Does he mean like in your body, or does he mean in the room?
Within the place, yeah.
The approximation.
Yeah, it's an approximation.
Right?
Yeah.
Because the whole context here is about him going into a village,
and the setting are the lepers and the Pharisees and whatever.
Later on, the village is identified.
Okay, so when he says the you part, it's because the group is asking him.
You're in the village too.
He's asking him.
The group is asking him, so he's saying it's within the group there.
It's within you, where you are.
Yeah, exactly.
It's the same thing as saying you walk into a room right now,
wherever there's something strange.
It's like, What the hell's going on here?
Well, where's here?
Well, the easiest way to define it in context would be,
is it the house?
You walked into the house or a room or a town, right?
Can you say that if you just drove into a town?
What the hell's going on here?
What's going on with you?
No, you're looking at the one area of observation,
the one area that's being addressed.
Yeah, it could be a room.
Okay.
Yeah, it's not a spiritual.
In other words, the point is that it's within the village context,
because he is there, wherever he is representative of the kingdom.
Okay, so this is very simple.
People want to think about it.
Actually, I can continue,
because the rest of this is important to what I wanted to discuss,
including what goes on in the mind.
Yeah, you said the rest of it would set the rest of the context.
So please, yeah, go ahead.
The context of more of the sonic.
Yeah.
But I just want to bring up,
there is no license for changing or reapplying things, right?
You know, they call those memes and things like that, you know,
urban myths, urban myths or falsehoods, right?
Okay, so this was pretty easy.
But to continue, and he said to his disciples,
now this is where I want to get in,
this is what the sonic is going to be,
and basically what I've been discussing indirectly for all these years.
Okay.
The days will come when you will covet to see one of the days of the son of man,
and you will not see it.
And if they say to you, behold, here it is,
and behold, there it is, do not go.
As for flashes of lightning from heaven,
and all that is under heaven is lit,
such will be the son of man in his day.
But first it is necessary that he suffer many things
and be rejected by this generation.
And it is what is in the days of Noah,
likewise it will be in the days of the son of man.
For they were eating and drinking and taking wives
and giving them to husbands until the day of Noah
entered into the ark and the flood came and destroyed everyone.
And again as it was in the days of Lot,
and they were eating and drinking and buying and selling,
planting and were building.
But on the day Lot went out from Sodom,
Master Yahweh rained down fire and brimstone from heaven
and destroyed all of them.
Thus it will be in the day of the son of man as revealed.
In that day he who was on the roof
and his possessions are in his house,
don't let him come down and take them.
And he who was in the field, do not let him turn back.
Remember the wife of Lot.
He who desires to save his soul will destroy it
and he who destroys his soul will make it live.
So all those contexts there cover up on very, very heavy stuff,
even to the point where, you know,
don't come down and get your stuff when you see this
because, oh, my stuff, right?
My stuff, are you sure?
So I'm going to close this.
That was a very poignant, that's been buzzing around,
bouncing around in the head for a little while
because it covers so many things.
Internally, I stopped myself a few times
and I said the next time I hear on a video
or someone say the kingdom of God is within you,
meaning that, you know, we're not in that village
and it's way past gone, so you really can't use that properly.
You can use, you can say anything you want.
You could say you're the guy who started the Carvel Ice Cream Company
if you want, right?
But guess what?
It's not true.
Right.
So if you notice, the rest of it was about catastrophism.
He brings up Noah.
He brings up Sodom and Gomorrah.
Right.
Those were local events, except for, well,
the flood of Noah was a global, but it went across the planet, right?
And if, again, Jason Breshears talks a lot about the vapor canopy.
I started talking about the vapor canopy in the mid to late 2000s,
back in the Revolution Radio days,
about how we had the canopy theory, right?
We were completely covered.
The sky was nothing like this.
But Jason Breshears would be the vapor canopy guy to go to.
I don't endorse him, but he has good info on that.
Okay.
Okay, and that's the thing.
I'm always looking for people that put out good info,
and if I find them, I'll tell you, hey, this is what I think about it,
and yeah, definitely, right?
Okay.
Now, it's interesting.
You say, well, someone might think, well, Greek,
there haven't been any catastrophes since then.
Yeah, there are.
They're always local.
Back in 2004, what was it, a quarter of a million people,
some tsunami, some island got washed over.
Remember in 2004?
Right?
So for them, that was really bad.
So you have these very localized events.
There were many worldwide events that had been redacted from history, okay?
Because remember, they don't want to advertise.
The forces, the human forces on Earth don't tell
and don't want memorialized in history things that they did not create
or have full control over.
Right?
So that's why I say when there are real terror events,
you just never hear about them as such.
There are military exercises, they call them, you know.
Everybody's wondering what the hell is going on here,
and there's no answer until the next day.
Oh, we were just doing something.
Sure you were.
Right.
Some idiot got a hold of something, usually idiots,
and they found out, well, this is too dangerous.
We're going to look bad if it goes off.
But what they call terrorists are just basically exercises,
most of them nuclear.
And when you say nuclear, people wonder, you know.
Hiroshima and Nagasaki, you know, they're so small
they could basically look like the older cell phones.
Right?
That's how small they are now, 15th generation.
So the catastrophe element is what Earth is about.
You know, okay, it's the blue marble, beautiful Earth, Mother Earth.
It is a sentient being, by the way.
All these other things, we are on the catastrophist planet.
Meaning, I once was discussing this with someone on Skype
invited me years ago, and one of the women started crying
because she was actually from Jersey, had a real heavy Jersey accent.
Yeah.
And she was crying, I don't know if I could take this.
I was like, oh my gosh, you know.
So it's not for everyone.
Right.
What I see the catastrophism that comes in the 500, 1500, 2000,
and then 6,000 years, it's like blinking an eye.
You know, when I say not blinking an eye in terms of time,
but you blink to clear the lens, right?
Yeah.
And to moisturize, right?
Yeah, it does many, many things.
So it's basically a dog shaking off, right?
And the value of humanity is as high as you want to consider it,
but like I've always said, most of the population does not matter
to the powers that be, both human powers and non-human powers.
Right.
And you know what?
It never did.
Most of the population, it was always a small group.
Just like you have a seed bank to store seeds,
that's how the society has always been running, as long as there's a remnant.
And the thing is, what do you do here while you're here?
To a certain amount, you have more choice than you think you do
once you know more about things, let's say.
That might sound confusing.
Right.
So, okay.
You ready?
Yeah.
If you hear a lot of Greek-speak, or since I've been doing Greek-speak
on the Internet or whatever,
because I've been doing it for more than a decade and a half before,
you hear a lot of things that you don't know about things you already know about, right?
Right.
Like the body induction, the money system, the government doesn't exist.
Those are a lot.
I really talk about a lot of things that most people don't know,
but it's about things that they know.
Okay.
How about talking about things that people don't know about things that they don't know?
Oh, my gosh.
Then you have no place to start.
You don't have a point of reference.
Right.
Now, the problem that I have with that is when I start to get into that zone,
because there are things that are not known,
using language and means of communication that are known,
that were designed to communicate known things,
how are you going to use that toolbox and apply it to things that are unknown
and not known that those words don't really do, let's say,
quote-unquote, justice to describe?
You need new words now.
You need new words.
It becomes a challenge because the old words don't match the new thing.
It doesn't.
Right.
Exactly.
It's not a matter of square peg in a square hole or round peg in a round hole.
These things, there's no pegs.
There's no pegs.
There's no holes.
This is a completely different setting.
And when something new is introduced in general, right,
it's usually because it's an adaptation from the language.
Okay.
Technically speaking, right, at one point there was a clock.
At another point, there's a wristwatch.
Okay.
Why is that called a watch as opposed to a clock?
Right.
Okay.
Well, computer.
Yeah.
Well, look at the computer language.
Why do they call it Windows?
Is it a name?
Is it a window?
Why not just call it an operating system?
Well, there you go.
But they do.
But the thing is, operating system.
Even again, it's still not, you know, here we go.
They usually build off of something that's semi-familiar and then sometimes, you know, like an airplane.
Okay.
There's a good example.
There were not airplanes for a bit.
Right.
So how did we build an airplane?
And then how did we name it?
Well, it had to be named something that was semi-familiar.
So you have to build off of it somehow.
But until it's done, until the new thing is there, I mean, you bring up that word to somebody 100 years before it showed up.
They don't know what you're talking about.
Most didn't, but it was already known.
Everything was already known by the late 1890s.
Okay.
But if you went to somebody in the 1890s and you said cell phone, they'd say, what?
What is that?
But, you know, there were cell phones that existed since the 40s.
Truckers had them, right?
Because they had the cell towers along the highway.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It looked like a regular telephone, a wooden box.
Yeah.
So they kept that name, by the way.
Cell towers.
No, the thing that I'm trying to pertain to here is that one way, okay, it's episode 20, which is kind of funky.
It's a funky number, by the way.
Yes.
You're in a place, on a place, near a place that is reset by catastrophes.
More than you believe to know and know, meaning you, as it's discussed in society,
the thing is most of these things have been brought down to myth.
You know, a myth is designed for a society.
For an individual, when an individual has a story or an idea, it's a dream, right?
Or it's a fantasy.
But when you have a dream or a fantasy applying to a society, it's called a myth.
It's interesting how this works.
But here's the analogy.
The analogy is you're in a place, one of the things they used to say, it's very, very violent.
If you woke up this morning and you hadn't had someone crawl into the room while you were sleeping
and try to rip the liver out of your body or your kidney, you're fortunate.
You're fortunate.
You know, they say you should be appreciative, right?
But here's the thing.
If you're not so fortunate but you're fortunate enough to hear me means you survived it
and you caught the guy or the gal and you said, why are you trying to do this to me?
All they do is say, because I feel like it.
Right?
You see what I mean?
This is the type of world you're in.
So how does anything else matter?
Well, the only way things matter is if you create a very organized structure of thinking and perception,
a box, and you keep people in that box, right?
Kind of like a pet, but not really a wild animal, but a pet.
You put them in a box, and that's where it gets used to being, right?
It's a very small box that has been made for society and the individuals within it
regarding any field, any topic.
But when you understand that the earth goes through a series of catastrophes, minor and major, on schedule,
and it's to reclaim the setting, meaning like there are people here and now there are not,
and we start all over.
Yes, that's where you are.
Just like think of this world as when you go to an amusement park, you go to one particular ride,
that ride has its own attributes, right?
Whatever it might be.
So the ride you're on is called earth, and what is this ride about?
That's the ride.
That's how it works.
Resets, wipeouts, and then you start all over.
Very little remnant.
Right.
Now, some people call these epochs, right?
Or ages.
Ages.
Okay.
Right.
So the whole thing now, how are you here?
Most people don't give this, and I'm not saying that you should lean on this and make it an obsession.
You can, but you have to do it very orderly because it's kind of like I give the analogy,
could it be one of the last things a fish realizes right before he dies is that he spent his whole life in water?
Right.
The obvious, right?
They don't think about it, but fish drink water.
They do through the gills.
The water passes through the gills and osmosis, right?
That's why when you poison a lake, not all the fish die at once.
Eventually they all do.
The fish that were drinking water at the time early on die first.
The ones that weren't thirsty die a little later.
Greek, that doesn't make any sense.
They're in water.
I know.
Think about it, though.
Right?
That's how things are.
Okay.
It's kind of like someone goes and gets a boat loan, and he says,
a bank just gave me $40,000 for a boat.
I said, but bank doesn't have any money to lend anyone anything.
He took your signature amount.
I don't know, Greek man, you got that weird sense of where do you get that from?
Nobody talks like you.
You know what I mean?
I said, yeah, go ask them.
Show me the money.
They don't have any money.
It's very easy to start a bank.
All you need is a room with a ledger and a computer to some Fed window, and that's it.
We have loans.
We give loans.
Come in.
All right, boom.
You just get a transaction number.
You're done.
You don't need any money.
Anyway, this is bizarre compared to how people think.
But when you see people who study fish know that the fish that die first are the ones that were thirsty.
The ones that died later were not so thirsty, you see.
So it's them not being in the poison but drinking the Kool-Aid, so to speak, right?
Okay.
That's what the punchline is.
So they make this very, very little narrow box.
Now, you don't feel like you're in a box because you're not in a physical box.
It's a mental box.
The topic, and let's just say, when you're listening to what I'm saying,
even now you're referring to the words that I'm using by whatever definition you apply based on previous thinking and your current thinking.
What I wanted to do is go back to the previous sonic or two about how emptying the thought is not really a good way.
Like the voice that you have that you think is you that sounds like you in your head, I'm telling you, is not you.
Right.
It's not you.
It's playing you.
In other words, you wouldn't listen to it if it didn't sound like you.
Well, that's the thing.
If you heard a strange voice in there that didn't sound familiar at all to you, you'd be disturbed by it.
I mean, well, most people would be.
Exactly.
Now, that's the interesting thing.
You know, there's a thing about the silence between the notes makes the music because if there's no silence between the notes, there's no music, right?
Of course.
So you're going to find out who you are when you make it quiet.
Now, here's the other thing.
The perception, whether you view the world as being a series of catastrophes, oh, no, what do we do, or this is where we are, let's make the best of it, is based on your thinking.
But when you're thinking, you're placing these things through various conditions within the box that you were born into, first started with your parents.
You know, I used to go on calls, by the way, years ago.
People used to blame, you know, it was the blame game on the politicians.
What was the alternative?
Whatever alternative or mainstream was talking about this week and everybody gathered on a Skype call and talked about it.
They said, oh, how screwed up Soros is or how screwed up Bush or Obama is, right, all this other Trump or whatever.
I'm like, oh, look, okay, okay.
I've been listening to you guys for a while now.
You're looking to blame.
You know who you've got to blame?
Your parents.
Your parents screwed you up, right?
Did Soros put the little pacifier in your mouth and change your diaper and say mommy, say mommy, say daddy?
Did Trump, right?
No, none of those guys.
Those guys don't even exist as they are.
They're puppets.
Your parents screwed you up.
So if you want to call someone an asshole, call up your mom and dad.
You see, that's where it started, the position you're in right now.
They're the ones that actually built the box for you, right?
Well, they're the ones that introduce you to the world, right?
They're the ones that initially provide you with everything that is required.
They're the ones that begin to teach you how to relate.
As they know.
They're the ones that teach you what the name of everything is, where things are, how things work.
That all comes from them to begin with, doesn't it?
Right.
Now, if you're in a society where you're not complaining and everything's fine, even if it's worse than George Orwell,
you thank your parents, right?
Because everything's going fine.
You know, it's all a matter of how it is.
But here's a point.
If you, Steiner, Rudolf Steiner, talked about a lot of stuff about thinking spiritually.
It's a little too airy-fairy.
The thing about studying or reading Steiner really pisses me off because you've got to go through a lot of lengthy stuff to get something.
It's kind of like, you know, when you're squeezing a lemon and you don't want to throw it away.
You want to get every last drop out of it because it's wasteful, right?
It's kind of like that.
It's like everything's been squeezed out.
Anyway, it's too airy-fairy for me.
I'm not saying it's not good.
It's too airy-fairy for me.
But one thing that I got from Steiner was that if we really cleared our thoughts and we didn't have thoughts
and we got into this world without the box, without the overlay, the brainwashing and the convention,
we wouldn't see anything as we see it.
Everything would appear to us.
And you can do this now, by the way.
If you didn't have any thoughts and you really cleared that voice, you would see everything as shapes and colors.
You wouldn't say, oh, look, I'm in the room.
That's the chair.
That's the speaker.
This is a microphone.
This is the computer.
This is the fan.
You wouldn't say that.
You would just see colors and shapes.
You would not acknowledge them.
And you wouldn't call it by a color, by a name either.
It would just be what it is that you're interpreting.
Right.
When I say color, it's because there's a variation in the frequency, let's say.
That's why.
And the shape, there's a variation in the plane, whether it comes towards you, away from you, is it curved, flat, whatever, pointy.
All you would see is color and shape.
And there would be no, this is not a book, this is not a chair.
It would just be the color and shape of each item.
And you would not acknowledge it as, yes, the book, of course.
I'm not saying not acknowledging its function.
If you can do this, by the way, if you can just see things.
This is what inventors and designers do, by the way.
I'm giving away a big secret.
I took a, well, when I was in, I was trained as a designer years, years ago.
I was very, very young.
And I was, people, anyway, my history, I was very advanced.
And they put me in places where when I hung out with other people, it's a student body.
They would come to those other people and say, hey, did you bring your little brother to school?
How cute.
No, he's not my little brother.
He's here with us.
I'm like, oh, okay.
That's my young life situation.
But I had a really good designer teacher, and he said, the first day in class, we walked in.
He introduces himself, says what the class is about.
He says, everybody in this class gets a B automatically.
And we're all looking at each other like, whoa.
He says, don't think you can't show up because if you don't, it's based on attendance school policy.
I'll have to give you a failing grade if you don't, if you stop showing up, right?
But everyone here does a B, and you're going to think it's not fair because somebody might do better work than someone else.
But everybody gets a B.
The reason why is because this is design, and I want to bring out the most fundamental creativity that I could possibly get out of you.
Leave everything you've ever forgotten, anything you've ever learned or seen or thought before.
We're going to start new.
Sounds like what I'm talking about, right?
And then someone says, well, why does everyone get a B?
Why?
The reason why is because when you go out into the world and you're a designer, no one looks beyond five feet in front of them.
You'd make a beautiful building.
No one notices it.
You make a beautiful teapot.
Very few people will ever notice it.
So no one's noticing anything.
You're going to put your whole life in there, just beautiful stuff.
So I'm going to give you a taste of what it's like.
See, because someone might want to get a higher grade, and someone might slack off and get a lower grade.
And the person with a higher grade wants to feel the reward of a higher grade, right?
Right.
But he's telling you, don't look for rewards in this world.
Do you see what he's saying?
Mm-hmm.
And he basically is telling you the slackers are going to get rewarded just as well as the overachievers.
Right?
How many times have you heard that, right, in an office situation?
The guy's a total slacker.
He's making more money than me, right?
Right.
So he actually set up a real-world situation within a situation within the real world,
which is to really break out of design and how to look at things.
Just forget it.
I'll give an example.
This is very pertinent.
This was architecture.
So what do you do in architecture class?
You draw buildings, usually, right?
And there's industrial design, like Frank Lloyd Wright.
He did furniture and down to forks and knives and lamps, chairs, right?
From what I understand, you draw a lot of stuff is what you do.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
And it usually has to do with building stuff, right?
When you start, there's typically buildings.
Right.
You have landscape architecture, there's parks, you know, all forms of it, down to furniture.
Yeah.
All right.
So, see, he really got us on this.
So he says, I'm going to give you three pieces of paper, no, five pieces of paper.
Mm-hmm.
And you're going to go home with these.
It was a two-hour class.
We're 15 minutes into the class.
And he says, take these five pieces of paper.
He gives us these five pieces of blank paper.
So I want you to mark them one through five, and I want you to take them home.
And on each page, I want you to draw five lines, three intersecting or two intersecting,
on each page that are aesthetically pleasing to you, however you want to put the lines, you know, on the page.
Okay.
One through five.
All right, go home.
Go to the lunchroom.
He's like, oh, what do we got, another hour and 45 minutes?
Ah, just go to the lunchroom.
He was so cool like that.
You know, in a two-hour class, they want to keep you there for two hours, right?
Yeah, well, not in this case.
Okay, just go ahead.
Yeah, in this case, he's like, go to the lunchroom.
So we're like, this guy is so fucking cool, right?
Right.
So we go home.
I draw the lines.
The next day we go in, or two days later, he says, take out those five pages.
We got them.
We're like, oh, this is so great.
He's such a cool teacher, right?
So he says, out of those five that you have aesthetically pleasing lines,
I want you to pick three out of the five, put two away.
All right, we do that.
And he says, I want you out of the three, pick the two that you like the most.
Right?
So he picked the two, put the other ones away.
He says, right, mark one of them letter A and one letter B.
All right, what the hell, where's he going with this?
Where's he going with this, right?
You know?
And he goes, okay, letter A is going to be the floor plan of the house you're going to design,
and letter B is going to be the elevation.
We're like, holy shit.
Because I've got lines here that are like really, really skinny lines close together, two of them,
and three of them are off to the side.
Okay.
What the hell?
How are you going to build a house with the interior floor plan with these two little skinny lines
with the rooms three feet wide and 40 feet long?
What are you going to do with that?
Mm-hmm.
Right?
And then the elevation, you've got like three skinny lines close to the bottom,
and this big square on top, so you're going to have three floors with each the height
and the floor to ceiling is three, four feet in each floor.
And the other one's got a 30-foot ceiling.
How are you going to build anything?
How are you going to make that usable?
So he screwed us.
You know?
Mm-hmm.
But he says you made your own bed, right?
But he didn't tell us why we were drawing lines, you see.
Right.
So now we're spending, we're racking our brains for three, four, five, six months.
How the hell?
You know, because when you have those lines, those are your floor plans and elevations,
you do a scale to it, right?
So you can imagine some random lines on a page.
If that's a floor plan, it's like you can imagine one room being 20 by 30
and the other room being four feet by 30.
What are you going to do with that?
That's your bedroom?
I mean, how are you going to live in a room that's four feet wide and 30 feet long with two people?
Right.
How's that possible, right?
So we started making these things where you, like these archways that you have to walk over the ramp.
So when somebody's coming this way, you can't pass them.
You've got to walk over.
So we started designing all this weird shit, really got out-of-the-box thinking, right?
And the whole time, no matter how frustrating it is, you made it, right?
You made it.
You're the one that drew it.
So he was really cool.
Then he became a real asshole.
He was like, I can't figure out how we're going to make two bedrooms in a four-foot-wide by 35-foot-long space
with a 25-foot ceiling.
That sounds like the back of an accessory in an industrial place.
You know, you can't use that.
What is that?
That's not usable.
You made it.
You drew it.
Don't look at me.
You got to do it, right?
So I was like, that was the most frustrating six months or five months of my life.
I was around 15 at the time.
So at that point, I started picking up on other things, and I always referred to being so frustrated,
but being reminded I made it, I made it that way.
But I made it that way because I didn't know what the hell, what it was for, what I was doing, right?
So I'm in this place where I have to blame myself,
but I can't blame myself because I didn't know what I was doing, right?
You get it?
How many times have I gotten messages about people saying, I didn't know what I was doing.
I went and got a bank loan.
I heard you talk about how the money works, and now I feel like shit
because I thought they were lending me money.
Right.
Right?
You get it?
No, if you don't know in the first place, I mean, yeah, I got it.
I got it.
But you're stuck with it.
Okay, so here's the thing.
There's a level of creativity.
The whole class was not about sitting there and being frustrated about it,
but what are you going to do about it?
And the only way we could have do something about it is by seeing what needed to be done,
having it all preplanned as much as possible, and then having it executed
because the whole thing was we were just designing.
We're not executing anything.
We're not building anything.
This is all specifications for someone else to build, let's say.
That's what architects do.
Right.
So that's what they're hired for.
By the way, if you know any architects, the more, let's just say,
cerebral ones are really weird people.
I worked for some of them, for actually pretty famous ones.
One of them, their dad comes from a very famous art family.
We visited this one house that he had.
It was on the Hudson Valley, right?
Okay.
And I'm on the second floor bedroom, and he's like,
be careful when you open the sliding door.
It's like a cabin-ish kind of wood.
They never built the balcony.
So you're up like on a cliff.
You open the sliding door.
You look, oh, man, oh, shit.
There's nothing here.
I could fall down and kill myself.
So they left things like that really strange because it wasn't – anyway,
very odd stuff going on.
So anyway, you end up making – you end up – even though you don't know –
look, here, most of the people listening to me,
I know you don't have to tell me.
You don't have to agree.
I know, like, your parents didn't know what the hell was going on.
Nobody around you knows what's going on.
I usually – when people come to me and discuss a problem,
and it usually errs on their personal – it sounds like it's a personal problem.
I say, well, first of all, you know that everyone around you is a moron.
You're completely surrounded by idiots, right?
I've been saying this for about three decades now, and not once, not once,
has anyone stopped and said, Greek, how dare you say that?
I'm not surrounded by idiots.
No one.
Everyone acquiesces to it, right?
Everyone.
Okay, that's how I start off because it's the same thing.
Yes, you're not in a good situation, but you know what?
You're in that situation, so no one put a gun to your –
somehow you got yourself into it, and you're in it now, and if you think about it – right?
Right.
Okay, so you don't want to think about it in the way that they tell you to think about it, right?
How many times do you hear people, oh, go to a doctor, go to the hospital, or get a lawyer, right?
Worst thing, worst thing, worst thing.
So the whole thing is how do you pull back enough and balance the blame game,
how am I in such a shithole situation or not such a shithole situation?
For me, I think on the cooking thing, I said nightmare hell for me in a twilight zone
would be living with a white Midwestern American family.
Right.
That would be like hell, a twilight zone hell for me, right?
For other people, it's fine.
That's what they aspire to, but I'm saying personally, right?
So everyone has their own personal adjustment or view,
but what I'm saying here is if you can eliminate all –
just look at the shapes and the colors and not what it really is.
It takes on a completely new meaning.
Not always, but usually does, but how are you going to do that?
You know, when you think of a situation, whether it's good or bad,
you know that little inner dialogue, that little inner voice pops up in your head
and starts making chitter-chatter, doesn't it?
Yeah.
Right?
Either making you feel self-important or making you feel like crap.
Right.
Or second-guessing or whatever, whatever.
Or it wanders off.
It tries to wander off so you don't address the problem.
Don't do it again, a whole other thing, right.
Yeah.
I mean there's so many possibilities, but typically that little voice,
what it's doing to most people, if not all people, believe it or not,
it's putting in thoughts of food, thoughts of sex,
and thoughts of play as priority every single time.
Right?
You can go and – you've seen this even in the media.
There's nothing to do here today at work.
Oh, let's go play.
Right?
First thing.
Let's not edify ourselves.
Let's go get that Soros or let's go get that Trump guy, right, whatever.
You know, I'm just saying, right?
Right.
Like it matters.
You see, so that's why getting – people say,
don't you get into people's – it's easy.
You don't even have to get into people's head.
You could predetermine what they're thinking about,
and it's usually sex, food, or play or combination of that, right?
Very, very simple.
And then you have the other group, which is obsessing about things.
They have this tape that's running, like background, like elevator music
or music running constantly about some problem that came up.
It could be a consistent thing of how am I going to pay the bills kind of thing too or whatever.
That's not you.
None of this is your voice.
Now, here's the thing.
I'm not saying it should be eliminated because it will be eventually as we transition,
but give yourself a break from it, and how do you clear the mind from that?
The easiest way to do it is to start attaching however – some people have –
they're called visual kinesthetic.
You show me versus linguistic tell, right?
I put in the chat recently about someone who had gone through a Qigong or something,
Tai Chi meet, and there was a negative energy no matter – it was the people, right?
And I said just when you pick up on that, it's a feeling.
It's very internal, let's say.
It triggers off chemical things as well.
When I say it's internal, meaning it has a physical manifestation and emotional
because feeling and emotions are different.
But just if you could visualize them as soap bubbles, they're harmless, right?
They could be a pain in the ass, those soap bubbles too, right?
Because it's soap, right?
Yeah.
But it's not so bad.
Just like soap bubbles.
So you're going to get hit with those thoughts and you're going to get hit with soap bubbles, but so what?
If you're wearing a tuxedo, by the way, and you get hit with a soap bubble, it will leave a mark.
So depending on the fabric, right?
Something that's, let's say, fine clothing.
All right.
So the way you do it, again, think about – don't think about the voice, but if you don't think –
how do you talk about not thinking?
We're using the word thinking.
If you had no thinking, again, this is the premise.
If you have no thinking, which is, by the way, not you, that little voice,
everything would be perceived as colors and shapes and textures and temperature, right?
Right, right.
You wouldn't say, hey, it's hot in this room, right?
Look, here's the other thing.
You could be in an office doing the recording, whatever, windows closed, doors closed.
Somebody walks in, says, hey, Chuck, it's hot in this room.
Another person walks in and says, hey, it's stuffy in here.
They didn't say it's hot.
They said it's stuffy, right?
So everyone's got this slightly different variation of it.
But how about getting rid of all that and just feeling and perceiving it, being in the moment, right?
Yes, of course.
Yeah, but then again you have to understand there's another level of danger,
and that's something I've never really discussed in all this.
There is an innate sense of danger, and I've never really got into it.
This is more of a protocol.
I don't think we'll do it on this sonic.
Okay.
But you know how these preppers talk about stuff?
Usually you watch a prepper thing and they show you knives and guns, right?
And bottled water.
Always, yep.
Yeah, it's like, no, no, no, no, no.
You don't prep for that, right?
You need to be prepping every day for everything that's going on every day is a different kind of prepping, right?
An example of that is electrical tape, always at arm's reach, in the car, at work, at home, in a drawer.
It's a flexible binding, just what I mean.
It sticks to things, right?
Imagine you could use it, a hose, your arm, a broken bone, right?
It's flexible.
Yeah.
It binds, multipurpose, right?
That's what I mean about doing a thing on things to keep around that you're going to be using.
And you have to know how to use it also.
Like a sharpening stone, for most people, has no use for them at all, right?
You know, you go to most people's kitchens and they have all these gimmicks.
They don't know how to cook.
They think if they buy these, right, kitchen gadgets, not gimmicks, yeah, they're gimmicks, they'll be better cooking.
No, it has nothing to do with it because a really good chef just has three knives, small, medium, and large, two pans,
small pan, big pan, and two pots or three or four pots, small, medium, large, and extra large, and that's it.
And a cutting board and a sharpening stone, that's it.
No, right?
Everything is done with that.
So we are taught to buy all the gadgets and gimmicks and this and that, Band-Aids, all the way to whatever, right?
That's one aspect of how to deal with things that are dangerous.
But when I mean danger, there's another aspect to it that you have to mitigate within yourself,
and that little voice rarely helps, by the way.
That little voice that you think is you confuses that.
There is an evil behind that.
Just put it this way.
You'll never catch me amongst a group of a large crowd of people.
Why?
Potentially dangerous, always, especially morons, right?
Yep.
And by the way, if you had a crowd of people that were not morons, there wouldn't be a crowd.
There'd be like two people there.
Anyway, that was a bad joke.
Yeah, well.
Hard to find people that aren't morons anyway.
Well, the thing is, are you looking?
You'll be looking for a long time.
Here's the point.
There are general things also discussing danger that that little voice –
I wanted to go to this because it doesn't help.
That little dialogue that's within the self that people think is their own self, right?
You don't really get to yourself until you get the silence, but the thing is to maintain the silence.
That is one of the important factors of avoiding danger, right?
I'll give you an example.
You're, let's say, well-to-do, upper blue-collar, middle-class, white-collar guy, whatever,
and the bank is offering you a loan at whatever.
They'll even pay you to get the loan, right, a certain amount, give you a toaster.
It sounds like a good idea because you might want to go.
You think the bank is lending you.
Your little voice inside says, yeah, go do it.
It sounds good.
It's a good deal, right?
It's a good deal.
There's no deal there at all.
It's so backwards and so upside down and not so that you can't perceive it
because that little voice is egging you on and saying, oh, that's a really good deal.
I never saw a good deal like that before, right?
Many times you hear people saying stuff like that, right?
The same thing works with avoiding danger.
I think we were discussing the sound.
People say, hey, Greek, do you want to come to a live show?
I'm like, is it really live?
Well, you know, it's going to be at that venue over there.
It's this band.
Are they on stage?
They're like, yeah, of course they're on stage.
I said, do they have a PA system?
Of course there's a PA system.
Oh, no.
That's not live music.
The moment you put something through speakers, it's not live.
I can't stand it.
When I do go, after like two minutes, I get up.
I'm going to go outside and have a cigarette, walk around.
So I walk around the whole neighborhood, see what else is there.
So if it's late at night and they're doing the day, I might want to come back.
They're like, hey, you were gone for an hour and a half.
Are you okay?
I'm like, yeah.
Are you okay listening to this crap?
Right.
They have a little voice inside of them telling them that that crap sounds good.
Do you see my point?
Yeah, I can't help it.
How can you sit there?
Right.
And listen to that.
Something inside of you is telling you it's good.
And another part of you is telling you, sit down and enjoy it.
And the part of you that is like, this is bad for me, you don't even hear.
You know why?
Because it doesn't make sound.
So you see how we were speaking earlier about how do you explain,
how do you talk about things that are typically not known about things that are not known
with words that are used to only describe things that are known?
Very, very difficult.
So this is a point of mastery, I would suggest, that if one follows what I've been saying,
if you can, bless your heart as the Catholics say, right, on this level of Greek speak,
then what am I supposed to listen to?
It's not a problem, but let's just say there's nothing to listen to.
It's all feeling.
There isn't going to be another voice, getting rid of the voice that sounds like you.
Are you going to get another voice that sounds like you that's you?
No.
No, you just have to be open to the experience objectively.
Exactly.
It's so objective, it's totally quiet.
And once you understand the sound of silence, you're going to go to a different level.