Rated Y, Sonic Event 127.
My voice is a little weak today, but that's okay.
You didn't tune in to really hear from me.
How you doing, Greek?
All right.
We're doing.
You messaged me that there was an attempt on Trump.
You're supposed to bring that up, but I'm bringing it up, and I saw something on YouTube
right before we came on.
Yeah, they got it on YouTube pretty quick.
They killed the shooter instantly.
I was about to say, yeah, this is standard stuff I've talked about.
There's going to be either an assassination attempt, a flash economic disaster like 2008,
but a flash one with no reason, reasons that didn't make sense, right?
Because they're Ukrainian war.
This is all just showmanship.
How about all of the above, Greek, because I'm thinking, you know, this is still early
before the election.
People's memory holes are big enough that this stuff could disappear by then.
Look, there's no economic ... 2008 was an economic crash.
I remember it was an election with Bush, and I think it's when Obama went in, right?
That's when Obama went in, yes.
Yeah.
Okay.
So all this is the corporation, Title 28, Section 3002, Subsection 15, the United States
defined as?
A corporation.
A federal corporation.
Yeah.
So it's all just corporate magic, corporate junk.
It depends on ... watch the movie Founder.
Founder.
Okay.
The guy who played Beetlejuice was in it.
Michael Keaton?
Yeah, Michael Keaton.
He does a great job.
It was about how McDonald's came about.
Two brothers with high integrity, he takes it, steals it from them, he says, you know,
competition, competition.
If I saw my competitor drowning, I would stick a hose in his mouth.
Okay.
This is the story of corporatism, and that's what you're under ... see, I'm in total, utter
disgust of just about every human around me for a long time.
That seems to be a newly emerging thing.
People are telling me about this all the time, that they're actually sick of everybody around
them.
They're sick of ...
Yeah, but this has been going on for decades for me, and now it's easy to speak.
Well, that's an odd question.
Wait a second.
Before you get there, there's an odd question that came in that links to this perfectly,
so let's hit it on your way through.
Because somebody asked, were you always like this, with this unique perspective, or was
there an event that caused you to see it, and if so, when did that happen?
In other words, like I'm 12 years old, this changed for me, I realized this, or I'm 20
years old.
Is there an event?
Is there a time period?
Is there something in particular that made the guy who was you before the way you are
now, with the kind of perspective you have, is there a difference?
Well, when I was two years old, I was sitting up in the crib, the adults were in the other
room, the room that I was in, the door was ajar, the lights were off in the room that
I'm in.
Not two years old, I was probably less than a year, because I remember at two, the other
sister came, and I was already running around in sneakers, or shoes.
So I was very young, and I realized, why are these people so dumb?
Now there's a difference between being dumb and being stupid, right?
Okay, so toddler you, says, looking at the adults, these people are kind of dumb, but
that doesn't mean that you have your perspective yet, but that means you're...
Right, no, yeah, but as I was getting older, I noticed that, why did these adults seem
so juvenile?
Okay, so they were more immature than they were dumb, or were they, is there a difference?
Juvenile, just like you, okay, so I was learning that pretty soon I'm going to be going to
school every day, right?
Oh, wow, great, finally, a change.
So I go to school, whatever, kindergarten, first grade, and I'm like, why are these people
so fucking juvenile?
So acting really like, you know, why, these are adults, you've got to be joking.
So the adults at home are juvenile, you go, okay, I'm going to go to school, there's going
to be other adults, maybe they won't be as juvenile.
Yeah, maybe they're a little quote, unquote, grown up and got their shit together, they
don't have it either together.
Then I started getting out in the world, and I hear about stealing, and lying, and fighting,
and fraud, and you know, the world is full of that, right?
Of course.
Yeah, and I was like, oh, that's what they're into.
That's what I want nothing to do with that.
Okay, so you really have always been from that perspective.
Now, I did learn your prime, your prime is like between 15 and 25.
Okay, what in age what I mean, that's when you your body recovers very quickly from everything.
And anything, usually, we're talking about a fairly healthful individual, myself being
that.
And also anyone who is healthful, if you're sickly as a child, you know, it's a different
story.
So, or, you know, whatever.
So I feel like that's the time period where you have a sign.
That's the time.
15 and 30.
Really?
But it's because I like to have endless energy, right?
Because that's right.
You're not easily exhausted.
Isn't that the key to that time period?
And if you happen to be good looking and smart, at the same time, you have more advantages,
right?
To a degree.
See, I don't know, good looking people, it seems to me get off easier and don't get challenged
as bad.
Right.
And you know, like, just like rich people don't pay for anything.
Yeah, right.
Exactly.
Like, you know, you go to a restaurant, they won't let you eat for free.
But in comes like, chef Elon Musk, and he gets to eat for free, right?
Yeah, the guy who's getting paid $7 million a movie, they give him a free meal.
But yeah, okay.
Okay.
All right.
So, so I started, I got very social, socializing various aspects of many, many different societies
all the way from the basically homeless, I was homeless for about a week.
And I would in the way you do that would staying on the subway is you write it to the end of
the line in New York City.
And then what happens the doors open, and the guys come in with brooms and mop and they
clean up, right?
Right.
And they kind of ignore you to tell you that I got to get off to get a cop.
They don't they don't have their own security, right?
They have the transit police, basically, which is like a New York City cop.
Yeah, to tell you to go get off, so you can't be here just anywhere, and they make you leave,
so you have to pay another ticket to come in, but it doesn't matter another token or
fare.
And you go back on the subway, and you keep writing after a while, you know, you get used
to it.
You know, you read the end of the line, sometimes they leave you alone.
After like three or four days of this, and other places, there are places I could stay,
but I decided to see what it's like to live out in the wilderness, right?
Okay.
Just like when you read about lost hidden tribes, you know, sometimes, you know, Native
American and Native tribes all over the world, when they get start to get killed off, there
might be one tribal member left, and they make it on their own for years and years and
years.
So totally by themselves living in the wilderness, right?
So that's the idea.
You know, you've heard of, like, the last man of this tribe was, you know, finally encountered
in Australia or whatever, and he's, you know, they said they killed all of his tribe, he's
the only survivor.
And he's been living in the mountains for 30 years by himself, you know, usually preceded
by a bunch of sightings, the legend of the one guy in the wilderness or whatever.
Yeah.
They seem to be okay.
So I've tried that.
I've gone over to the high society and all that.
I said, wow.
So how old were you when you went out into the urban wilderness, so to speak?
How old were you?
17.
So you're at your peak mentally, you're inexhaustible.
You're in good shape.
And I wanted to try it.
Let me try this.
Okay.
Yeah.
Give me an example.
I had 2000 bucks access to 2000 bucks and what they call a bank account, which in those
days was be like six or seven thousand, eight thousand now.
Right.
Well, yeah, that's a lot of money.
I might be more.
Yeah.
Right.
I would have had access to it.
But I didn't.
You know, it's you know, I didn't use it.
It was long.
Sorry.
It's a cosign.
You know, you have to get someone else's signature to get the money.
Yeah.
No sweat.
But you could easily access enough money.
Yeah.
I didn't have to.
So I tried all of a sudden.
I tried this, tried that, even like some people said they were.
Let's go skydiving.
And like, oh, yeah, this is crazy.
And you know, why do I want to do things that make me miserable, like riding a roller coaster
or whatever?
Right.
It's just it makes me miserable.
So I started realizing that sometimes you do have to do they call it a compromise, right?
In a relationship, at work, whatever you compromise.
But deliberately, when I started seeing people doing things that made me miserable, like riding
a roller coaster, that G-Force is not makes me miserable.
Skydiving makes me miserable.
All the all these thrills.
It's like these things are really through.
Why do they seek these things?
So, OK, when I say I'm disgusted by the humans around me, all I do and want to do now is
just take notes.
Like I say, I'm just visiting, taking notes.
I sit back and I watch how they behave and how they're being ruled, right, which is actually
a very loose hand.
Now, I'm for all for Nietzsche, the common man should be ruled with an iron fist.
Like I'm 100 percent for a real war, a good war wipes out 70 percent of the population
or a real pandemic, a real one that wipes out 70 to 80 percent of the population.
What that'll do, it'll give you some more breathing room, right, and a more organic
organization.
Right.
Now, these things I'm saying are coming.
But, you know, I'd like to see that, you know, sooner than they are.
Right.
OK.
So, you remember, you only need two people to survive, to keep things going.
So and there's plenty that will.
But these types of resets are necessary.
I believe the last one that happened was when we were shown the orphan trains, civil war.
You know, people don't talk about the the Civil War period starting like in 1840, something
maybe six or seven, the Crimean Wars.
Everybody was at war.
There were revolutions and civil wars and country wars all over the world in the 1800s.
Yeah. In the 1840 to 1870, it was it was rocking.
It was worse than World War Two.
Right. In terms of number of conflicts and even France.
I mean, even France, where they, you know, they just seem to be perpetually protesting.
They even went to war for real.
Sure. And civil wars and revolutions in Central Europe.
Yeah. Just everything going on.
Yeah. OK.
So and then what's all we hear about?
We just everything's kind of been made minimal and they call it civil wars, civil war
here. But, you know, civil war wasn't adopted until 1920s.
Before that, it was called the War of the States.
And before that, it was the War of Northern Aggression.
But and before the Civil War started, there were, quote unquote, terror cells going around
killing people right in the farms.
Right. Yeah.
So what's interesting is that all that's been downplayed, including the orphan trains.
Where are these children come from to the adults?
A lot of those killings on the farms were actually corporate backed, you know, mercenaries
that were sent in to destroy competition, like in the tobacco wars in Kentucky, which
nobody ever talks about. But a whole lot of people were wiped out.
Farms were just, you know, literally taken over physically because they would literally
walk over, beat the farmer to death with a shovel and declare their farm to be part of
this other farm. That actually went on a whole bunch.
And again, they don't call it a war at all.
But that's what the civil the it was about the basically Lincoln, who was a total punk
ass. He got visited, you know, OK, you know, the Constitution, this is really hard to
find. Let me just say it and maybe I'll bring it up again if I could find when the
Constitution was written, like 1779, 1780, whatever it went to Europe, it went to the
Vatican. It sat there five or six years.
OK, they got it back and then they sat for another year or two and then they did the
U.S. Constitution. Most people don't know that.
Why would you send it to the Vatican for approval?
Right. Also, there's some doublespeak because a lot of doublespeak and federal stuff.
Right. Is that before or after the Vatican declared every soul on Earth to belong to
them? Is it that was that's around that time or actually the Vatican did that about
four or five times since then.
But yeah, I actually popple bulls started in the well, you know, people first century,
first millennium and popple bulls.
Right. So anyway, it's a mess.
But let me just go back to what I see.
I just watch people's behavior.
Sure. And then I watch how they're being ruled and how they do self-rule and how they
manage themselves, you know, and, you know, and how they catch themselves and how they
inspire themselves.
And it's it's not fascinating.
It's actually boring as hell.
And it's really dumb.
And I just watch just anybody, everybody, anybody and everybody.
And I'm like, we are just here to waste our time.
This is just a waste of time.
And it goes on and on and on.
Most you're giving example, most people, especially working class Americans, whatever
that is, if you say you have a class in America and you have a caste system, right,
they look forward to wasting their time.
It's called Super Bowl sports Friday night, Monday night, whatever, going on vacation,
but all these nonproductive things that they look for because they know it's a waste
of time. Everybody's wasting each other's time.
Right. So getting this message out could be a waste of time also.
Well, universally, it just used to be the television.
Everybody would gather around that.
And that was it. Time would disappear.
Well, that yeah.
The television is what rules you.
There's still people, for example, I heard this thing the other day.
Someone being here. He's really upset at the no plane.
The people in the 9-11 conspiracy movement that say there were no planes.
And I wanted to put in the comments section.
You're both right. Meaning whoever saw the event, witnessed it on television, saw
planes. But whoever was boots on the ground that day saw no planes.
He just saw the side of the building explode.
So you're both right.
You see, you don't say one is, oh, you're an idiot for believing there's planes or
anything. There's no place. Just say, give the facts.
It's a fact. Right.
So, you know, that's how you move it and move ahead.
You know, you know, like I had a neurosurgeon I was speaking to and so many hours.
It's like I kind of told him he doesn't know what he's doing, but he's a neurosurgeon.
He kind of got the message.
He's like, well, I guess as long as people get run over by trucks, they'll need a
neurosurgeon. Wow.
You know, so it's just so ridiculous.
It is so my favorite thing that, you know, in the movie Idiocracy, watch it again.
Yeah. When the lawyer finally starts to turn around because he's declared the
smartest. He says they're in Costco.
This is where I studied law in Costco.
Perfect. This is exactly what's going on.
These idiots. What I would suggest is since it's a fact for me and I could
disclose, I would stand on this issue.
Welcome to Costco. I love you.
Yeah, I would stand on the issue that everyone's here to waste each other's time more
than anything else I've ever said.
OK. Ever. It would be the paramount.
So what you're telling me is that that Sonic that we did on the meaning of life is the
pinnacle of the pinnacle.
That would be if I had to send that put in a time capsule.
If you had to place to another galaxy, that would be the message.
So if you had to boil down Greek speak to one particular sentiment, you would say
that's it. That's it.
Oh, for sure. I've been thinking about this for more than 30 years.
When I started the bike shop in New York City, I was like, you know, the reason I'm
doing this is because I once said I wanted to do it.
I know, you know, it's not what eventually I'm not going to sit in retail.
That's stupid. And you deal with the public.
Oh, my gosh. Whoever comes through your door, you know, it's scary enough.
But fortunately, we were blessed with good people most of the time, if not most of all
the time, with few exception.
But I was like, let's just do it.
It's another way to just spend time, you know, do it for two years and then leave or
shut it down or whatever. But so.
Yeah, everything you know, the fun you want, here's a real funny thing and it's still
perpetual. That's why the insanity university college going after high school is a
waste of time. And everyone other than the people who had good parties and got fairly
good grades would disagree with that.
But pretty much everyone would disagree.
It's a waste of time yet.
They still do it. You know, we can go through the full spectrum, right?
And look at it that way.
Funerals. I was once asked to go to a funeral of a relative and I said, I'm not going.
He says, why not? I said, did you want me to stand up at the eulogy and tell everyone
what a scumbag he was?
Oh, yeah. It's best that you don't come.
No one does that kind of stuff.
Right. You know, everyone said, oh, he was this.
He was that the guy was a scumbag.
We're better off that he's gone.
Everybody lighten up.
You got to go to Italian funerals.
And I'll tell you, because there's always to kick your ass if you say that.
Well, no, there's always two rooms.
And they don't. Yeah, there's one room that boxy.
I know. Yeah, there's always the same with the Middle Eastern stuff.
And the second room is always a bunch of guys standing around talking a little more
quiet, usually smoking cigarettes, going, I don't even understand why we're all here.
This guy was a jerk off.
I mean, yeah, exactly.
This is the reality of reality.
Now, one thing I didn't talk to us about older people like Biden.
Well, Biden is a woodchipper material because he's a clone.
Just like the thing with Trump today.
He's a clone. He's not a good thing.
Anyone of notoriety up there is a real human being.
You got something coming for you.
Right. For example, when I heard the clone stuff, I knew it was real.
This is how I knew.
I had seen some UFO pictures, you know, people to snap with the thirty five
millimeter pictures of flying disks.
Oh, yeah. Well, it was it was taken in nineteen sixty six, nineteen sixty seven.
And right. Chasing the flying disk was the what is that?
That's not the stealth bomber, the stealth fighter plane.
What's that one called? The one twenty one or something like that.
Well, you got you talking about the triangle shape that's black.
Yeah. OK. Yeah.
That was chasing exactly that plane was chasing the UFO.
And this is twenty five years before they released it to the public.
Right. Right. All right.
So. So, yeah.
So cloning was a big deal in the late 90s, by the way, with Dolly, the sheep and all
that. They can't tell you.
Right. So if you think anybody, Elon Musk, anyway, any of these people go listen to
Donald Marshall, you know, and you'll get it.
I mean, even if you think that Donald Marshall stuff is off the hook, that's mild.
That's mild compared to what's really going on.
Very mild. It's much, much worse.
So you'll never see a political politician being assassinated because it takes the fun
out of it. Right now, he could be it could assassinate the clone and bring another one
back. I think I've told you about some security people that I knew that actually they
were high up in the army and they left the U.S.
and they live in other countries.
I'm not going to give up the countries like Colombia or Romania or anything like that.
Anyway, and they get involved and they just couldn't stand in the U.S.
because they found that these are people that would have first name basis with presidents
like Reagan. Right.
And they left the country because it's just disgusting to them.
They saw what's really going on.
Anyone listens to the Brandon Joe material, Brandon Joe Williams, who I've been
bringing up serially, you know, just about every sonnet past five sonnets.
I'm very impressed with that young man.
It's much worse than what he's saying.
You know, so what they basically mentioned is that from a security point of view,
what's going on, the word on the street is when you're an ex special off special ops
guy, your name gets pushed around various organizations, drug cartels, industrial,
whatever. You get put on a list and you can get approached for a project.
You've got skills. You know, people will find you a job.
It doesn't. Yeah. And they're all, you know, all the corporations are corporations.
There's no good guys, bad guys.
Right. So so basically he found out there was no more market for kidnappings of
high profile people.
The reason why is because when you kidnap a high profile person and ask for ransom,
someone pushes a button a few miles away and their head explodes.
The person, you know, the rent, the person is being ransomed.
Right. And then you see him on TV the next day.
And you're like, how could that be? Because his head explode.
We had him here in the room and his head exploded.
And how could he be on TV the next day?
They never went around saying they're all clones.
I'm saying they're all clones from that account.
Right. Right. That's why you don't hear about kidnappings were big up until the 70s
and it went away. It's a high profile piece.
Another one. Yeah. Another weird question.
Like they asked somebody asked me not too long ago, how come nobody hijacks planes
anymore? Really? You know, and what I learned is that because they can be remote
controlled anyway, there's no point.
You know, it's like if you go and you take over from a pilot, you take over the
cockpit, you've done nothing.
That's what it comes down to.
Rebecca Roth got into that pretty well.
Yeah. And they were landing when it's slow at major airports.
They they they test everywhere.
They tested one coming down and one came out a little too hard.
American Airlines back in the 90s.
Right. And yeah.
So this is a by the way, if you want to know what happened to the planes that took
off that morning, they landed at Westover Air Force Base, which is 20 minutes from
New York City. It's in Massachusetts.
And if you think not, if you know anyone who was in the Air Force Base, but why
Westover? Because it has a like a five mile long runway.
Right. I think it's a it's like 15000 feet or something, three mile.
And so you could land big planes back to back.
Now, if you don't think you think that's a conspiracy theory, why did they tell
everyone, all personnel on the base to stay in a hotel locally on
910? The whole base was evacuated a day before and everyone was supposed to be put
up a hotel. Since when does an Air Force Base put up everyone in hotels?
Right. The only time the only time that's ever occurred.
And it's funny. It was a chemical spill.
Yeah. Right.
Right around that time to remember when they had the anthrax attacks.
They actually did that.
Yeah. You know, and that was a whole event.
This was a day or two before 9-11.
Oh, yes. You don't want people.
So it's so ridiculous.
It's so ridiculous.
The whole thing is so absurd, meaning all the way back, you know, talk about the
history that we get, which, you know, I say question the history.
No, don't question the history.
Do your do your own restart from scratch.
In other words, don't don't see.
Don't take what they give you and start questioning it.
No, no, no. Put it aside.
You know that. Don't even look at it.
That's the main body of work.
Now let's see what we could find out on our own.
Right. And then then compare notes and then obviously one will completely shred the
other. In other words, first construct your own history from stuff that you can prove and
you can find proof of.
Then that's right.
Go and look at what it is they wrote about it after.
Yeah, that's right.
Like, for example, I lived through the 70s and the 80s and half of the 60s.
And from what I recall, especially, you know, being a young adult in the early late
70s and through the 80s and what I see recounted now about those times is very
different, very close, but very a lot of things are left out.
Right. The sentiment and all this.
Right. So you can pick up on that, you know, if someone is a good communicator, which is
another thing you brought up, something that I.
Well, but anyway, this is the second time I derailed myself on what you do lawfully for
older people. I jumped to the cloning thing with Biden.
He's a clone. Trump is a. They're all clones.
Yeah. Congress, the whole Senate.
Yeah. There's millions of them.
And we still didn't finish with.
Was there a particular event that turned you over?
You gave us a progression.
We got up to you experimenting with the homeless killer event.
No particular event.
But during that time period, you realize how stupid you are now.
Yeah. It's a series of events doing sonics.
Right. That allows me to hear myself, not hear myself speak.
But I'm very serious when I say something or I say it.
I thought of it four or five times before I say it.
Right. And it allows me not not speaking to hear myself.
I'm speaking to put it out there.
And when you put it out there, the power of those words reflect back that when
people think about what I'm saying reflects back, it's like the silver cord, you
know, saying we're all attached with a cord and we could we could break
attachments and create attachments.
And the feedback is very, very neutral along those lines.
So there is no that I would say doing sonic events has put even more life into
these thoughts. And because most people that do
hear the Greek speak are glad for that, that they can hear it.
You know, it's like because I never talk about anything cryptic or anything that's
out of whatever we used to do a Skype group.
And this guy, he was an IP intellectual property
agent. He would find cool ideas and market them to big companies.
He always tells us a great thing.
Build this, build that. In order to build this device, you needed like a three
million dollar machine. I said, listen, have you got any IP you could share with
us that we could just go down to Ace Hardware or make with things we already have?
Why do I need a three million dollar laser to make this?
This doesn't make any sense.
Don't you have anything practical like putting dish soap in a spray bottle so you
don't use as much dish soap? Come on.
Well, that's a hell of a fact. And I've heard back from people about that.
And quite honestly, I implemented a bunch of those things.
They won't be buying you by dish soap once or twice a year now.
It's a lot on laundry soap, too.
I've got to tell you, laundry soap.
I'm not spending nearly as much at all.
And it's just as clean.
Yeah. So these are very, very simple hints.
I used to do Skype calls and give every every time I did a Skype call, these two or
three different simple things to do.
And I could still do it.
And I still do it.
You know, I'm constantly coming up with stuff.
Put it this way. Not a day goes by where I haven't made something improvement on
something or something new.
And that would be three hundred and sixty five short YouTube's right a year.
So that would be an interesting way to go.
Like Chris Fix, you know, you don't have to show yourself or give any names.
Just stay anonymous.
And a million subs and a million views, you know, type thing.
Yeah, it can easily all this stuff can be used.
Mr. Mr. Hands Practical Fix YouTube channel.
And it's just your hands doing stuff.
Yeah. Yeah. How to fix stuff and what stuff is and what's going on with this and
that. I'm talking about just practical stuff.
Just put it on a table.
So again, what lawful way to deal with old people is what covenant you live by.
For example, if you are an old person, a man, a woman, and you're dying in a
remote African village that's in the southern, let's say, areas where
cannibalism is still fresh in their minds and acceptable, they ask you permission.
You're considered. They say you're an honorable man of society.
Is it OK if we eat you when you die?
OK, this is a common question.
I know most Westerners, especially white people, or it doesn't matter what level
of melanin you have or whatever in your skin.
Most people are not aware of the prevalence of cannibalism in places like Asia and
Africa, those continents.
Right. It's very normal.
That's part of the ancient past.
But yeah. Yeah.
Like, for example, if you're in places like Liberia or whatever, all the way
across, if you see food vendors, street vendors selling meat, it's probably not
what you know. They don't ask.
It's human meat most of the time because people always die.
Right. So is that how you treat old people?
Ask them if we eat. You see, depends on what covenant you live by and what laws you
live by. Now, OK, what I see, you're typical American.
They're doing the right thing.
They slap some diapers on them, keep them full of drugs and throw them in a nursing
home. Why?
Because I say they're doing the right thing.
Usually when you went for many generations to the older people, they were bastions of
wisdom. They can give you good advice, usually based on their education.
They promoted things that would better your life.
Now they have nothing to say at all.
So why not fill them up with drugs?
And by the way, I found that most of the senior living starts at 55.
I'm more than four years into that.
Yeah, that's a new thing.
It used to be, you know, the 55 was introduced.
Yeah, like Agenda 30, 2030 Agenda introduced that with 15 minute cities.
But if you had the 55, it was usually for the spouse of the older person.
Right. Like so if you moved into a place and you had a husband or a wife that was a
little older than you, it wasn't directly for 55.
Yeah, that's the way it used to be.
And now you're right, though.
They start going, well, you can start living here at 55.
Not your spouse can come with you if they're close enough to your age.
But 55, I don't know when that change happened, but it is fairly recent.
Well, I feel I'm going to be 60 pretty in another year or so.
And I feel like I still feel like I did when I was 35.
Yeah. So I'm 52.
I'm probably 10 years older than you in real life.
But yeah. Yeah.
And at 35, I looked like I was 25, you know, and that would be easy to get a 21
year old. So at this age, can I still get a 21 year old?
That's the other point. But anyway, I got you.
I hit the wall when I was about 35, though, I think 35 or 40.
I just kind of went, OK, I'm old now.
So anyway, what you do with the old people is based on the covenant that you live by
strictly. When you read the biblical stuff, forget it.
That has nothing to do with anybody you know.
All that biblical stuff has something that you can ascertain is useful or not and put
it into effect and see what it's like to be live with real law.
Right. Which is not about control or motivation by penalty, but how to open up
yourself to a world where things fit the way they're supposed to.
Let's say that does not what you read about that.
It does nothing to do with the elders, you know, unless those elders understand what
I'm talking about. Right.
You know, the law also.
Right. So, yeah.
So when it speaks about treating people a certain way in the Bible, it's people that
are in the same covenant with you.
It's actually very harsh about those outside of your covenant, like the pagans, like
you don't find if you find an animal that has died of unknown causes, do not eat it,
i.e. roadkill or wake up in the morning.
And it's got what's called in the former funds, a dead cow, you know, supposed to put
it in the food supply. Downer, downer animals.
Right. But it says, but you sell it to the pagan for a profit.
In other words, don't give them a discount and make sure and have them eat it.
All right. So all these examples are the people living in the same covenant as you.
Right. So it says respect your parents.
Right. You see in the in the spoken commandments, the oral ones, not the written one.
Yeah. Honor them. But father.
Yeah. But in other parts, it's like, oh, my gosh, get away from these crazy heads.
Right. In other parts, like Abraham.
And it goes on and on and on.
You got to think this guy was an evil.
You know, his son didn't want to be evil like him and whatever.
On and on and on. So it has nothing to do.
With a general, it's not a broad brush application.
So what's lawful is based on the laws that you live in.
Right. Or how whatever the covenant that you all agree.
So, for example, you can have a different covenant than the people around you.
But so then that's where you come in and you do what they do in their own government.
Not for yourself, but allow them to do it to themselves.
If you're, for example, living by a higher covenant.
Yes, there are higher and lower covenants.
And those people live by a low covenant.
You cannot go in there and start commingling.
It will not work.
You you you either avoid, you know, so not partake in what they're doing
or allow them to do what they're doing, but convincing anyone or changing anyone,
especially now, forget it.
It's it's been that time has been over for a very long time.
So anyway, good. We didn't skirt that.
That's what you do.
But you see, we did bring in the clone thing again, the clone revival.
And again, if I hear about something,
I tend to poke around and see if it can be validated,
if you can't get validation or verification.
You still keep the material aside.
You don't have to deny it.
That's one of the signs of intelligence, by the way,
is being able to entertain a thought without rejecting it. Right.
So you know what?
I saw something in there real quick about something about speed reading.
Like I've done a tangent.
I haven't talked about that.
Let's we want to get into that.
Well, yeah, because, OK, maybe somewhere in the 40s,
it was pointed out to me that you had said
you were going to give people a really easy method.
Yeah. Yeah. Whoever. OK.
First of all, you have to be a good observer.
Second of all, you can't allow that voice to dominate in your head. Why?
Because when you have the that.
OK. Why do you have to be a good observer?
Well, obviously, you know, this is very mechanical.
If you can't read visually, you need glasses or help. Right.
And also be a very good observer of many things,
of the setting of the book, the type and all that. Right.
In other words, right.
Is it easy for you to acquire the information? Right.
So and then
the voice in your head, because when you're reading,
if you are reading the words aloud in your head, like most people do,
you will never do speed reading ever.
When you find yourself alone reading silently
and you notice that you're trying to read those words aloud in your head,
you hear them in the voice in your head.
You're not going to be a speed reader. Guaranteed.
That's the voice in your head. Also reading it.
That's another proof that you there you're walking around.
You know how there's you and the corporate you.
They call it the straw man. Yeah. It's always denied.
If you're reading something silently and you find yourself voicing
that in your head, that's the other being reading also with you, along with you.
Which we've covered in previous sonics where you talk.
That's right.
Voice in your head is not actually your voice.
Yeah, it's not. It's another being that's, yeah, keeping you along.
You know, just like, you know, you know,
capital letters is not you on the government paperwork, right? Right.
Yeah. So if you still have that voice in your head when you're
especially when you're reading, it'll jump out.
It'll be pretty obvious that someone else is reading.
You sound like you're voicing it off.
You're not going to do speed reading. Put it aside.
Now, if you can conquer that and just look at the words as if they're hieroglyph,
forget about what the words, what language it even is.
You can do this with even with a language you don't know.
And start seeing words like for the, you know, all the basic
where they go conjunctions, you know, in, out, only in and out might be important
because put the clothes in the dryer, put the clothes on the dryer.
Is it very important? Right.
Positioning logistically.
Yeah, that is all for, you know, all these things here.
You have to group those together.
Right. And start looking for things that add more meaning, more like it was.
I've never got to David Wynn Miller stuff, but syntax, proper syntax.
Well, let me ask you this quick question,
because when I get a good pace going reading and I've read a lot,
I get pictures that will go by like a motion.
Like, OK, so let's make a movie of what you just get.
Yeah. Let me stay on this roadside picture.
OK, so what you're actually doing is you're when you looking at the page,
you're photographing as you're progressing along.
You know, let's say imagine someone's reading
and they're moving their finger along the pages very quickly.
That's another good way, right, to do it.
And it's like it's like someone looking down the scope of a rifle
when you put your finger or ruler or paper on the page.
But OK, so let's say you take a three sentence chunk.
You have a book open, three paragraphs, you know, medium font.
You read you take a chunk of the first three or four sentences
or half a paragraph skim through that.
And as you're going to the second chunk,
which is the other second half of that paragraph,
you have to also visualize what you just looked at
and see if they overlap and if they follow through.
So your eyes, your eyes are picking up what you're now seeing.
Now, below, you're still reading
as if you have another window open on your computer, right?
Another tab, what you just read
and comparing it and seeing how it ties in.
And the thing that just starts to you start seeing
how unnecessary most of the words are.
And then you can get through.
So, for example, I'll be sitting and we watch informational YouTube's,
you know, in the living room or whatever.
And there'll be a movie, right?
And they have a paragraph description, you know, like Star Wars a long time ago.
You know, some films open up, give you the setting.
And it's about three or four sentences.
I'll look at it. One, two.
OK, I read that next.
And the other person is still reading and reading and reading and reading
and reading and reading and reading and reading and reading and reading
and reading, just look at I read that. Got it.
It reminds me of the infographic shows on YouTube
where they have a very basic, you know, graphic going on
and the words go by on the screen at the same time.
And if you do it that way, it gives you a basic understanding of what's happening.
The crawl, you mean like a crawl?
Well, there's a lot of words different.
Well, not on the bottom, like along with it.
In other words, like I said, I create pictures.
So you end up with not a caption, but you're reading the words.
And as you're reading the words, they're sort of being created
in a visual form over here.
OK, so yes, I get you. Yeah, that's very important.
OK, so another way to think about this whole thing is very simple.
The most simplest, the absolute simplest way is what images are you getting
when you see the words that you know, like the Scientologists are big
on definitions, and I give this to them when you're trying to read fast.
You if you understand everything that's there, all the definitions
of all the words you start to see pictures and you start to form the story in 3D.
The moment you hit a word that you cannot define it, that's it.
You're fucked.
You cannot continue that anymore because it just broke the chain.
It broke the rhythm.
It's kind of like you're going on a run and you slip and fall.
And now you have to get up.
You're not running anymore, right?
You brush yourself off.
You're still not running.
And now you start your gate again.
Takes a few seconds to get up to speed.
So you got to get back into the flow of things.
It's a trip.
It's an imagine you're running with a group of people and you slip and fall
and they keep running.
By the time you get up and start running again, they're way ahead.
You got to catch up. Yeah. OK.
Yeah. So you just killed your entire.
So you're not going to be running from that point on.
The moment you hit a word that you cannot define,
even if its definition is in doubt and you're not sure how it's being used,
that will kill that completely.
So what does that mean?
You have to understand also that many people
authors, if not all of them, do not know how to use.
And you're reading a book that mentions soul and spirit. Yes.
They do not know what those words mean.
Do you know that most people that write even authors
do not know what the word nice means?
Yeah, I know that. Right.
OK, so once you pick that up, you continue along the context
that it's written, but you remind yourself the author is an idiot.
Right. OK. OK.
Now, do you want to speed read through something
that the author is an idiot? Absolutely.
Why waste time?
You want to get the needle out of the haystack.
So that's where the speed reading comes in.
Right. You're already caught.
Like, for example, I know an author and he wanted me to read his stuff.
I'm not going to mention his name, Bruce McDonald.
And he started writing about the soul and the spirit.
He wanted to argue what it meant.
I said, listen, your stuff, you keep interchanging these things.
They're totally different things. Yeah.
And, you know, so I'll read through it, but I'll tell you right now,
it's not good, no matter how good you think it is.
Bruce, generally, I like Bruce, but I get your I get your point.
Yeah. So, you know, he tried.
So and this goes on.
I was interviewed, Dean Romania, the other author, hours and hours.
To write a book together or for me, whoever, about all this kind of stuff
is based in like China, ancient China, some Chinese sage and all that.
I said, no, no, no.
You first of all, like half the words that come out of your mouth.
You don't even know what the hell you're saying.
You know, so what are we going to build it?
Guess what? We're just wasting each other's time, aren't we?
All right. We're just wasting time.
All right. What else?
The speed reading thing.
Look, there's plenty of classes, just like language.
OK, this is a parallel to the language thing. OK.
Now, I believe in learning languages organically.
Now, what does that mean?
You know, you run into someone
that looks Asian.
Let's say you find out they're Korean and they speak Korean.
And, you know, you're young and at school.
And the reason why they speak Korean is because their parents
immigrated to America and they speak Korean at home.
Right. You get it.
Well, how did they learn that?
Well, the shorthand is you use the words.
Look, if you use those words in action,
you can connect them to those actions.
It becomes a lot more of a natural thing.
OK, that's another language example.
Let's just say you just know one language.
How did you learn that?
They put a coloring book in front of you.
If you pretty much grew up past the 1950s,
you had what's called a primer.
Yeah. Where it was a book where there was a letter on each page
and then maybe an object. Yes.
Right. And you studied that.
Apple, so on and so forth. Right. Right. OK.
So now you studied that with an inexperienced mind
that was still developing.
So this is the way you learn an organic language.
And you will learn so fast.
People won't believe it.
Let's say you want to learn Hebrew right now.
Give me an example. You know, absolutely nothing.
None of it. Right.
It all looks like whatever.
Go online and download from a Jerusalem publisher
a coloring book in Hebrew
for ages four and under or five and under.
Start downloading those coloring books.
Print them out and you will see all of that gumbo.
Right. You'll see all these letters and you'll start coloring them in
and it'll have, you know, like for bet it'll, you know, or this.
You'll have write a house on it. Right.
You go on and on.
So you're going to get the letter you color in.
You're going to show they're going to show upper lowercase, let's say.
And they're going to show an object with a short word.
Now, you're an adult.
Don't even force yourself.
Right. Even if you did one letter a day,
there is no way you will not remember, not not remember any of that.
You will know that you will know it for sure.
And you will have a primer.
Then you move up to the first grade, second grade stuff for Hebrew.
There is no way you will not not remember it.
In other words, you will learn that shit fast.
Right. You will learn it so fast.
As a matter of fact, you will go through the
the primer first and second and third grade in less than a week.
Yeah, no problem, because you'll be working on the boy lives in the house.
There'll be a that's right.
So let me just mention this way.
If you're a Hebrew speaking boy and you're five or six or seven
and you're left alone, can you communicate enough about who you are,
who you are, where you live in this and you're hungry or you got to go to the bath?
Of course.
So within a very, very short period of time, you will have
the communication skills of a young child. Right.
Organically. Now, if you start doing the Rosetta Stone, all that other bullshit,
six months later and a thousand dollars later,
you might think that you can speak like a tourist
and you're going to forget all of it.
I assure you, you're going to forget all of it
and you're going to be stuck there like a cripple.
Oh, I once could walk, but now I can't walk.
When you learn organically, you never forget it.
It will always be stuck there organically, meaning the way children do.
Because remember, you are conscious.
And as your brain grows, it tunes into different stuff.
So as you know, I've always said a superior mindset
will always overcome an inferior mindset.
Always. Right.
That's why they are the professional people.
Lawyers, doctors, priests, rabbis, accountants,
consultants, whatever that deal with the public.
They always put inferior characters, their inferior minds.
Right. Because two reasons.
If people notice that that person, the lawyer, the judge, the doctor
is a superior mind, they want to emulate that.
Right. Right. And now what are you doing?
So you got to make sure doctors, lawyers, judges, Supreme Court, prejudice,
presidents, congressmen, accountants, consultants, business leaders are dummies.
Now, this has been certified fact
that this is one of the big filters that's been going on for since 9-11,
because during they really stepped on this really hard after 9-11
because they had this thing called the 9-11 Commission.
Yeah. And even before it was done or afterwards,
a lot of those people that were part of that were interviewed.
And boy, oh, boy, the Freudian slips or the slips that they have
about the bombs in the building and the missiles.
And they're like, oh, from now on, we've got to make sure that
anyone that interacts with the public does not know.
Ergo, Brendan, Joe Williams keeps saying
you go to the State Department, they don't know anything.
I think at one point a long time ago, we had someone in the State Department
in the chat on the hotel.
And I kept bragging on the guy, like my brother or whatever
works in the State Department, like everyone's like, oh, wow.
So if he works, the State Department knows nothing about the State Department.
Absolutely nothing. Right.
So because someone who has no knowledge
cannot possibly make one of those Freudian slips
because they don't have it in their brain to slip. That's right.
And so it's been made the upper.
So if you go to the State Department, they know no one there knows anything
about what the State Department is supposed to be doing.
That's been memorialized for 200 years.
No one. I assure you that because the moment they find someone
who knows what's going on, they're going to pull them in the back room,
double his salary and says, shut the fuck up and go work out of your house.
Yeah. Right.
Go put him somewhere where nobody can find him.
I know someone who went down to Congress and kept showing all the emergency
acts and all the bankruptcy and all this other stuff.
No one. None of the car knew.
None of them knew any.
And I'm open to this.
And the aid comes out, you know, aid that works with the army.
Right. It's also a congressman.
No, no, no. You don't need to look at this stuff.
Right. They're flagged.
So this is the situation you live in right now.
So a higher consciousness will always overcome a lower consciousness,
whether it's intelligence, spiritual worthiness or anything like that.
But the problem with subjecting the common folk to a superior
human mind is that they want to emulate it because that's what humans do.
If humans didn't want to emulate, you wouldn't have trends in fashion.
You wouldn't have Hello Kitty and tick tock.
And you wouldn't have. Right.
You wouldn't have any of these things.
So, yeah. So it goes on and on and on.
And you're really, really stuck.
But look, there's nothing you could do to change anything
at this point other than within your own sphere.
But just keep in mind that everyone around you is there to waste your time.
And they perceive you as you're supposed to waste their time.
This is not how they're saying it, because remember,
they have a voice in their head that blocks them from this.
Here's proof.
Let's say you go learn about how the human body works
or how the quote unquote government works or how this works
or the Bible or whatever.
Like basically, you've been listening to Greg speak
and you go to coworkers, family members, associates.
No way, dude.
I don't want to hear that because you're supposed to be wasting my time.
Why are you going to give me information that actually binds itself to reality?
I need stuff that will not bind itself to reality, not bound to reality,
where we just don't know.
And we're all just blowing around or maybe even blowing each other,
a circle jerk. Right.
So this is what's going on and it's not going to change.
And this is it's been this way for a long time by design, by the way.
And certain things by design, just like addictions become perpetual. Right.
So you can reach your next level of Candy Crush or Black Ops,
you know, Soldier of Fortune, whatever on your PlayStation.
You know, that would be interesting.
So anyway, there's a lot more.
There's someone more to come.
I don't know if we'll do it now, maybe next time we meet.
What are the loose ends of Brandon?
Brandon, Joe Williams or Williams, Joe Brant, whatever.
Brandon, Joe Williams is.
Yeah, Brandon, I keep I'm like he gets a serial mention even more than archaics
does, because I'm so excited that he put it all together using just the codes.
Right. Right. And I'll just give a preface to that.
It's the title 12, section 411, because in order to succeed.
In other words, you know, the IRS is there to support your faith
in credit, full faith in credit.
The reason you're taxed is because, oh, the money must create scarcity.
They need the taxes. So the money's worth something.
No, they don't need that.
There's no no one has any accounting for where any taxes go anywhere.
No one does.
The building, some of the governments give a little card as well.
It goes some of it goes to the jurisdiction of the schools.
It goes to the jurisdiction of the roads.
But OK, OK, that's fine.
All right. But where and how? Show me.
No accounting, zero accounting.
OK, everywhere. So so if people get away from the taxation
legally by, let's say, revocation of election
and doing conditional endorsements in many ways,
the money system will the faith in the money will collapse
and they have to do something else, which is happening slowly.
But Brandon Joe Williams thinks that you have to get rid of all your contracts.
Right. He does. He endorsed things a certain way.
But it's shown that even endorsing them without recourse,
which basically doesn't make you liable for what happens after
is still endorsing it as something of value.
And the IRS wants that's a liability, right, because you're adding value to it.
Right. They basically told it's in the 16th Amendment.
You know, the same verbiage that's in Title 12, Section 411
is actually in the 16th Amendment.
They pulled it out of there.
And that's your remedy.
Now, you don't have to do any of the cancellations
or anything like that to use that.
You could be a total citizen slave and do that endorsement.
And that particular instrument that was endorsed.
So he is not does not rise into a liability column ever.
Right. Unless you want to, of course, you know, then you could say,
well, I'm going to donate it anyway. Right.
So what he's talking about on and on and on and on is fine.
But if you do his contract killer course and still still endorse
without a demand, yeah, that's a tax liability, dude.
In each individual thing, someone that was once scrutinized by the IRS,
he actually called, says, I want you guys to audit.
He says it doesn't work that way.
But what we look at anyway, he showed all the checks,
all the things everything was endorsed that way, you know,
with a conditional endorsement demand for lawful money, USC 12, 12, USC 411.
And the IRS guys looking through it.
And he says, well, do you have anything that's not endorsed this way?
Is there's no I've been endorsing everything like that for decades.
Well, then, goodbye. Have a good life.
They don't.