The Sonic Event 25, Ocelli in the Greek, there I go announcing it again, here we are.
Greek, how are you doing tonight?
Oh, busy, busy, busy, but rested.
You know, we were going to record another night, and I just walked in from doing labor,
like masonry, plumbing, complicated stuff, and I knew you were calling without knowing you were calling.
So, here I am. It's good, it's like a different pattern.
I'm usually prepared for doing a recording.
Tonight, it's just I walked in and I'm numb from using a brick hammer and wrenches and torches,
and I was thinking I'd just come home and have some leftover pizza that I made last night,
and hit in the sack, and we're recording. That's great.
So, let's see how I do. Let's see how you do.
Why not? Let's see how this rolls.
Yeah, yeah.
I was scrambling around the house taking care of stuff.
Just so you know, weird things happened just before this.
I was running around the house trying to figure out why I had an internet connectivity problem.
I reset everything. It seems okay now.
I also had to get rid of a mouse, so that was my fun.
A mouse apparently found his way into the house.
I do live with a lady, so you can't have that.
Okay, you're going to do limericks? You could rhyme every other sentence.
Why not?
I don't think limericks are rhyming every other sentence, but yeah.
You mentioned something about more prophecy, and I really got over that in the public forums.
What to expect.
The only other specific thing I can say is, look for, this is way down, but this is a sign.
The Palestinians and the Israelis will become united like allies.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hand in glove.
United?
Yeah, politically, militarily, economically.
It sounds really crazy.
Israel is going to give up a lot of land along what they call the Gaza Strip.
The Palestinians will get Jaffa back, the ancient city of Jaffa.
Now wait a second, let me just say it so it's more pertinent.
This would freak out the people that don't know what I'm talking about, about prophecy.
Jaffa is Tel Aviv.
What's Tel Aviv?
It's the capital.
It's kind of like the U.S. giving up Washington, D.C. to North Korea or Iran.
Wait a second, they already did that behind the scenes, but you know what I mean.
Yeah.
So you'll see.
It flies in the face of all conventional reporting at the moment, right?
Well, so do airplane, well, so do steel skyscrapers vaporizing from jet fuel.
Of course.
Magic bullets.
Lots of other things like three shooters disappearing into one guy.
Things like this happening all the time, yeah.
Or a dollar bill.
Who's going to pay that bill?
Good question.
It's all bizarre.
But this is not on my own.
A lot of people that are on the fence about it and don't like the Bible because it's religious to them.
Where do you get this?
It doesn't matter where I get it.
Did you hear it and can you file it away?
It's kind of a diversion tactic to let them be open indirectly.
It's kind of like making children eat their vegetables by tricking them.
Well, here's a funny thing, right?
Even people that swear by the Bible in the most pedestrian way.
I mean, somebody in a piece of feedback recently brought up how you were talking about the Bible guru and that guy.
People of that ilk who absolutely say, I swear by it.
This is absolutely what I swear by.
And they're really swearing by what their pastor told them or what their pastor has always told them.
Okay, fine.
That's like paying your taxes.
You've got to pay your fair share.
Well, yeah, of course.
There's no way to pay taxes.
They're not taxes.
You have to file a return for using private credit.
So all this stuff has gone away and become something else.
In other words, all these things you just mentioned have gone away from what they really are in a du jour world and become something else, but they're using the old language.
Right.
But I've taken note that people that have gone away from what the original is and what the intent is and what the book is, it doesn't matter, right?
The people that claim to cling to their book, they don't even read it.
It's just the way it is.
It changes.
Yeah.
The Mandela effect also.
I don't like using it.
Well, come up.
See, I don't think about the Mandela effect enough to come up with another term for it, but yeah, temporal edit.
Temporal edit.
Okay.
But the thing about it is that if you present to somebody who absolutely staunchly tells you, look, this is the beginning, the ending, the alpha, the omega, everything,
you present to them something else, though, that will make sense, and you prove it out.
You say, look, here's what's going to happen, and it happens.
Well, next thing you know is they don't care where you got it from.
They'll hear it.
Oh, yeah.
That's how the money system works.
Right.
Well, not money system.
It's called speculation.
Okay.
Right?
So a successful speculator is not really speculating because he has some inside knowledge.
Yeah, yeah.
So we'll see.
I've got either good or bad.
I've got a really good track record.
I got that cartoon hand on a stick.
I pat myself on the back, so I'm not looking for approval.
Guys, don't worry about it.
You know, people like to get feedback.
You know, I've talked about this.
Don't send me an email that I've got good stuff because if it wasn't good, I wouldn't be saying it.
Don't send me that.
I know it's good, and it sounds really cocky, right?
But if you contact me, it's because you've got something to share that moves everything forward, whatever that everything is.
Speaking of which, what's been moving forward in the chat is people taking interest in magnets and water.
And I'll tell you a quick story about this magnet and water thing.
It's recurring.
It's with the car stuff.
It's with the audio stuff, most of the health stuff.
I tell people about something in passing, and I meet them again later, and they have time to come and see me demonstrate it.
Okay.
And when I demonstrate it, it's like, this is unbelievable.
I know you told me about it, but, you know, it's unbelievable.
You know, I'm like, well, if it wasn't so, why would I tell you it was so, and now you're surprised because it's so?
I mean, do you get people telling you things that aren't so, and then you go, and it's not so?
I mean, is this how people operate?
Yeah.
A lot of people do operate that way because they know that a majority of individuals that they're trying to trick, quite honestly, will not follow up.
They'll just either take their word or not, and that's the end of it.
So, yeah, there are people that constantly work on exactly that.
I mean, I know that's ethically unsound to you, but, yes, that is what we're confronted with, you know, among the poor.
Or live with, in other words, because this was very natural.
This was not – I've heard this before, not just with myself, but with others.
It's actually been portrayed in film also.
In movies or TV, they use that kind of scenario.
Right.
So, yeah, so at this point, you know, with the scale or the reduction of minerals in water, conservatively 30% to 40% is very accurate.
It could be 50%, but it's not.
It's just about between 30% for sure, 40% for sure.
That's a good thing.
I keep messaging when I put comments about what's going on with this.
Anyone who's enterprising will recognize this.
This is like – if you're into finances, this is like – there's this thing called Bitcoin.
It's 20 cents a Bitcoin.
Anybody who's enterprising will know what this means, right?
Okay.
So this is similar, but you have to be involved with water and fluid treatment technology, right?
Because this also works with gas, you know, like natural gas, propane.
It works with any fluid, but it'll change things on a different level, fuel.
So without getting into that, we've had – I'm very actually pleased by the feedback,
because it actually shows people still know how to operate a screwdriver, hammer, saw, zip tie, other than the popo,
because I know the popos use zip ties now.
And people don't know what the popo is.
It's the fuzz.
That's from the 70s, right?
So what's the fuzz, right?
So anyway, yeah, people are – I could see people have proficiency with hand tools, right?
I mean, saying like – I used to ask people, do you know how to operate a screwdriver?
And the response is very wide.
It could be laughing, laughing, laughing, laughing, laughing.
Like maybe I insulted them, and they actually don't laugh.
They're like, no, I don't.
Okay.
Right?
So it's like you never know.
And also the results, they're posting results in the chat, so that's good.
It's very small.
But I have the people here that are on Rated Y that have been building these,
and others that are getting the same results.
I'll put myself out a little bit.
Well, we're going to talk a little bit more about water, but regarding other things.
But put myself out a little bit.
I had a short conversation with someone today about what the next step is,
because I've been using this system now for about two years.
But I didn't get it for sure aligned until the past six months,
and the past three months decided to speak about it.
Okay.
So anybody playing around with this, getting the water to cross where the magnet is ineffective,
is very important.
If you get it down with a micrometer, like exactly measure the center of your water line
and exactly the center of the magnet, it works even better.
Like if you're slightly off, and you use a micrometer,
or you center the water line exactly over the center of the magnet,
you'll have 30%, 40% even better results.
I mean, it's that fine tuning.
Literally like getting the radio station tuned in, right?
Okay.
That's how well it works.
But the next step, I'm going to put myself out there,
because someone might ask me about this, and I'll say no.
Or I might say yes.
Or I might say I'm not going to talk about it until I know more.
But this is what the next step is, and I had the conversation with today.
This magnet system, I'm determining the proper runner length,
meaning when the water or the liquid goes through the magnet,
how much pipe or tubing should go before the next one goes in, or whatever, runner length.
And then another device that will clear up turbidity.
Turbidity means water that's not clear.
Okay.
Like the water they have in, what is it, Flint, Michigan?
A lot of places, but Flint's a prime example, yeah.
Yeah.
They have a, you know, they show the local news.
They go to someone's house.
They turn on the tap.
The water goes into a clear glass, and the water looks like mud or yellow or rust color or whatever.
So at this point, we're able to progress it to the next point,
which will be producing a device which just looks like a pipe, but a little thicker than a pipe.
Let's say it has a built-on body to it.
And whoever you show it to, they could look right through it.
There's no guts in it.
It's just a straight-through pipe.
And what you do on the influent, you run this turbid water,
and on the affluent where it comes out, it's crystal clear,
and that's going to get people scratching their head.
This kind of technology could probably get you killed, by the way, if in other times.
You know how years ago they used to shoot and kill whistleblowers?
Now they don't so much.
So it's kind of a little bit more.
So that's the next step, and the way that's going to be done is by using a biological vacuum
that metal pipe magnet and things like that can afford.
And I can go on to how to make this.
Basically, you need several metals,
and you need to produce a certain type of water that is encased between the metals, so on and so forth.
But who knows?
In the near future, I might find a simple way to do it and have people build these things, you know.
Could you imagine having turbid water, non-potable turbid, dirty water,
and you run it through this, and it comes out clean and clear?
And someone's going to ask you, where is this stuff going?
You know, the materialist, right?
Where is it going?
Right.
Where is the filter where you're collecting all this crap?
It's got to be somewhere.
Yeah, yeah.
Today I was in the shower talking to the wife about it.
I'm in the shower, she's in the house, and I'm saying, you know, where is this going?
They say, where is it going?
And I say, I'll tell you where I'm going with it, Africa.
Right?
You know what I mean?
You don't want to do it here.
No.
Right?
You'll be stepping on too many toes.
By the way, I have firsthand knowledge of this.
All of your municipalities, city, state, whatever, that buy chemicals and processes for treating water or whatever,
even parts for the power plants and all that,
the ones in the county or the city or the municipality that sign off from these contractors and all that,
they get a kickback.
So let's say you have whatever town you live in buys a quarter of a million worth of chlorine a year.
Okay.
That's all it looks like on paper.
But behind the scenes, that chlorine company that just got the contract for a quarter of a million
kicks back $5,000, $10,000, $20,000, $50,000 to the politicians there, cash or other ways.
So when you go there, they'll act like they're listening to you,
but you have to somehow let them know what kind of a kickback they're going to get,
and it better be bigger than the kickback from the other guys.
Otherwise, you're not going to do business with them.
You know what I mean?
Well, right.
I mean, if you turn around and you give the guy's father a job who doesn't even have to show up for it,
the paycheck better be worth more than what the other guy is offering to pay, you know.
Yeah.
Well, real quick, the way they do it here in America is with cars and houses and boats,
but usually houses.
If it's more cars, when it's less than the tens of thousands, it's cars.
When it's in the hundreds of thousands, it's houses.
Are you familiar how they bribe politicians here?
This is very common.
You can actually see the paperwork, but people don't know about it.
It's kind of like when I tell people the numbers on the dollar bill come from your birth certificate.
You can go to the treasury and put in double e-bonds on the drop-down menu,
put in the birth certificate number that you have, and put in the date,
and it shows you an address.
People think it's irrelevant, but that's the address of the hospital that you were born.
If you're younger than 35, it shows up.
But you see, everything is there.
Okay, should I get into it for about two minutes, how they bribe politicians?
Why not?
Okay, real easy.
Well, let's do it this way.
It used to be with congressmen, they used to go play pool,
and you deliberately lose the pool game, and then you say,
I owe you out in the open, you give them an envelope.
In other countries, it's different things.
It could be livestock in Russia.
It could be in a country, depending, they use livestock.
They pay for someone's wedding.
If they know their daughter, they'll pay for your daughter's wedding.
You know how weddings could be expensive, even Libya or whatever.
The way the Russians exclusively work with bribes is expensive watches.
You buy like a Patek Philippe, or Philippe Patek.
Patek Philippe.
Patek Philippe, yeah.
Philippe, yeah, that's it.
Sorry, I thought that was more Ukrainian, though.
I thought that was more of a Ukrainian thing with the watches.
Am I mixing that up?
Yeah, that whole part of the world, yeah.
It's got to be a watch.
Okay, in America, what they do is, with the judges, attorney generals,
and politicians, the mayor people, whatever, this is what they do.
They have a call.
They have someone call, and they tell them to go buy a house.
They have, quote, unquote, good credit, right?
So they go to the bank, and they buy a house.
They get a loan for the house, whatever, no money down or some money down, whatever,
in a neighborhood where the houses are $200,000 to $250,000, $300,000, right?
So once they buy the house, after closing, they wait two months,
and the next party comes in and buys the house for $400,000, worth $350,000.
So they make $100,000, that's it.
So it shows like they made a profit on the house, right?
Yeah, they just flip a house.
They flip a house, or sometimes they flip a commercial building, same way.
Or a car, or a car, yeah.
And this is very easy to see if you know who your judge is and all that.
Just go look in the county record what houses have been sold and for how much,
and you'll see it's the only house that sold for twice the amount it was worth
in that neighborhood ever, right?
So it's pretty obvious.
But it's all, quote, unquote, legal, and it's just a system.
Cars are also another way.
You have them go buy a car, and then you buy the car from them for, you know,
more than what they paid for, a lot more.
So houses and cars, boats, properties like that are the mayor's, you know,
all these other people that everyone sees on TV, how they do it.
The international figures, like your congressmen and all these, you know,
how are these congresspeople, you know, after serving, whether it's 10 or 20
or 30 years, worth $100 million on a salary that's less than $200,000 a year, right?
That's all done internationally with big deals.
They become partners and stuff, you know.
You know, there was no car insurance requirement until the insurance companies,
you know, said to the congresspeople, you're not going to be in office very long.
Pass this thing where everyone has a mandatory car insurance, and when you get out,
we'll hire you as an insurance consultant or whatever.
So it's all above board legally, right?
But the intention is screwed up, right?
You know what I mean?
Right.
It's all about intent again.
So, yeah, so the moral of the story with water is good, cool, clean water.
And if you can produce that without buying anything, well, yeah,
you do have to buy the setup, but you could bury it in the ground.
You know, there was a water pump found in the Middle East, I think it was in Lebanon,
from a hospital that was – from a building that was 400 years old,
and it was converted to a hospital 150 years ago, and it was renovated 30 years ago.
And they said, well, how does this place have such good water pressure?
It's way up here, and there's no – and they dug down, and there was this water pump
that's been running for 100 years on its own.
It was like a single-piston diesel thing.
No one knew where it was getting fuel or anything, right?
And it was pumping water into this hospital.
And they didn't get more information than that, and they obviously shut it down
and replaced it with one that costs a lot to run, right?
So all this stuff exists out there.
But water, okay.
What I did on private groups, especially right before the pandemic,
in case anyone was concerned, even if you read in the Bible, silver is good for your health, right?
And most people have heard of colloidal silver.
A lot of the normies even – well, the population out there doesn't know.
But if you're enough time around, quote-unquote, alternative stuff,
you'll hear about colloidal silver.
Well, guess what?
Just like the magnet stuff, the colloidal silver stuff is the same.
They are doing it wrong, okay?
Well, you can't – okay, let's go back to the magnets.
If you go to a magnetic water treatment, it's like $150.
They sell you two strong magnets that you put together,
the way they go over the pipe with some zip ties.
And they make some claims that they can't support, right?
Well, why am I saying it's doing it wrong?
Because they're not going to support their claims anyway.
Is that wrong?
Not really.
It's just not doing what this alignment does.
Colloidal silver, they're trying to tell you that the more silver in the water,
the better it is for you.
That's where the FDA stuff comes in.
Is it a disease or your skin turns green or blue from doing too much of the particulate, right?
So, in essence, there's people that measure silver content in water
to judge how good the silver is, the silver solution.
It's toxic.
It's poison there.
I have to lean against the mainstream scientists that tell you it's toxic, right?
Yes, it will denature and kill, quote-unquote, bacteria, yeast,
and fungus, and all this other stuff.
But it's metal.
You shouldn't be intaking metal in metallic form in any size, whether colloidal, particulate, or whatever.
So, in any way, if you're going to take the silver in metallic form,
the body will have to recognize it, right, to get it into the bloodstream
and into the body past the intestines.
It has to be done through induction, right?
So you don't need the actual physical presence of the silver.
You just need enough of the water to have enough of a signal to trigger the signal in the body
to produce the silver in the body, and that would be optimum, right?
It would be most powerful.
So what is the solution?
The solution was neighbor's dog.
Here, hold on a second.
No problem.
Okay, so the solution would be that because we know it works through induction.
So how do we create a system like that?
Well, is it an ion?
Yes.
Is it an ion?
No, right?
So because typically when you try to infuse metal in water, it's called like ionizing the water.
So the quick solution here is always try to get pure silver, silver bezel.
I found out that here in Tucson, Arizona, Star Gems is the company.
It's like one of the few places left in the country,
and I know this from being in L.A. years ago and driving around looking for pure silver.
No one has it.
And if you call them and order on the phone silver bezel, like a foot of it, it's inexpensive.
It would be like $5, $6, maybe $10.
Triple nine or I think it's double nine or triple nine or four nine fine,
depending on what they have in stock, as long as it's 99.99 and better.
So 99 would be double fine, 999 would be triple fine, and so on.
Really inexpensive.
They'll say, oh, yeah, you're another one who found out about this from the Greek.
They send a lot.
People have been going there for years.
But it's the only game in town that I know of.
But if you can get fine silver, people say, oh, I got the silver and I'm ready to do your thing.
Well, I say, well, where did you get the silver?
He says, oh, I just have some silver coins.
No, no, no, because if you look at silver currency, it always weighs more than an ounce.
Why?
Because it's supposed to be an ounce of silver, but still pure silver is impractical in a coin.
If you sit on it, right, you'll bend it, so damage it.
So they have to put copper and tin and zinc and other things in it.
That's why when you weigh a one-ounce coin, guess what?
It weighs more than an ounce because in fair market, you are getting an ounce of silver,
but it has 5%, 10%, 15% more weight of the other metals.
You see, it's not pure silver.
So I wouldn't recommend that because copper does some weird things in the body when you do it this way.
But if you're in a pinch, if you have silver coinage or whatever, not anything silver-plated.
I would stay away from plating because years ago, they gave silverware to couples that got married.
Well, not only does the silver keep disease at bay, so to speak.
Remember, it's not bugs.
It's by induction.
If the couple's household was under economic stress, they could always hawk the silver and maintain the household.
You see why it was done?
It was a financial security, right, also.
Don't use silverware like that.
But if you have coins, since the colonial days, however you want to phrase that time-wise,
when barrels of milk were transported or stored, they didn't have refrigeration.
They kept it out of the light in a dark, cold room.
But they threw a silver coin in the barrel.
And they noticed when they did that, the milk stayed fresher longer.
But it's just a silver coin in the bottom of the barrel or water or whatever.
They threw silver or a pewter pitcher that was silver-plated.
It just lasted longer.
So you're going to have to get the triple-nine or double-nine fine silver bezel or wire.
And what you do is you have, just like the regular colloidal silver,
if you're not familiar with colloidal silver, there's a ton of stuff on the Internet about it and how to do it.
It's all wrong, just like the magnet stuff.
If you look at magnetized water, it's how you do it.
None of that will work if you do it that way.
So the silver stuff, the principle is you have a power source, a battery, a wall wart or something,
some power source, and you have a positive electrode and a negative electrode in the water,
and silver is produced in the water.
Fine, that's the setup.
So the only thing different here is your power source.
They tell you, oh, we do ours with 27 volts, or we do high frequency, high voltage, 1,500 volts,
or we do ours, we cook it.
Oh, my gosh, oh, my gosh.
Okay, so ignore all the voltage.
That's where they all go wrong, and the temperature, too.
You don't have to raise the temperature to get more metal in the water.
All you need is a single cell, which is 1.5 volts.
Okay, cells are called batteries, right, because a battery is more than one, really.
In the military, a battery would be not just one shell, it's many shells, right?
It's a grouping.
A grouping, yeah.
So a single battery or a single cell, it doesn't matter if it's triple A, double A, C or D battery or whatever.
Double D, now we're talking about women's cup size, but okay, just whatever.
They're all 1.5 volts.
The only difference with the double D, let's see in my mind, the D battery and the triple A is the current.
Okay, so a single cell, it doesn't matter if it's a dollar store battery where you get, like,
a pack of eight double As or triple As for $1.25 or whatever, or a Duracell or it doesn't matter.
Right, so you could use just ghetto style Scotch tape or whatever across the wires or the silver.
Put it in the water and for, let's say, a quart of water, five minutes is fine.
A gallon of water, six or seven minutes is fine.
A glass of water, 30 seconds.
What this does, it will give you a silver.
I don't call it colloidal silver because we're not going for a colloid.
So I had to come up with a term.
And so what I did was I used the Latin terms.
Argentum means silver and aqueous means water.
So I call it aqueous argentum, not colloidal silver.
Okay.
It's basically silver water.
So however you want to attach the battery, do not use a nine-volt battery.
Do not use a nine-volt battery.
Now, unless you put in neutral cells.
If you're going to get six pieces of silver and set up what's called a neutral cell, you can do that.
So each electrode only measures one and a half volts between it.
So anyone who's got more than two or three sharpened pencils in their pocket is familiar with electrolysis.
You have these things called neutral cells.
Don't bother with that.
Now, I've experimented with people doing this.
And some of the people that had a scientific background or lived with people with a scientific background said,
that's not going to do anything.
That's not putting any silver in the water.
That's not enough juice.
And I measured the water, and there's no silver in it.
You know, they took it for a perfect.
Okay.
So some of the people that drank this, you know, you have positive intestinal flora and fauna,
which means plants and animals in your belly that help digestion, right?
They're symbiotic with us.
Some of them will agree with the silver.
Some don't.
So when you pass, mostly solids will change radically if you needed, well, if the silver is reacting.
I mean, when I was having conversations with people, especially over 35, I said,
how long did you cook it for?
You know, five minutes.
And I said, did you drink it?
And he says, yeah.
I said, how did you go to the bathroom the next day?
I said, oh, boy.
Right?
Like a laxative.
So I said, cook it, instead of five minutes, do one minute.
And how was it going to the bathroom?
A lot better.
So all you need is 30 seconds, right, the older you are, the less time.
Okay.
Okay, so what does this do?
Okay, if you believe that disease is carried by little pathogens, particles, and viruses and bacteria and stuff,
this will also work for your mentality, even though it doesn't work that way.
You know, for example, the old magnetic tape, whether it was a cassette tape, A-track, VHS,
that was a Mylar tape coated with magnetic particles.
These little bitty brown magnetic black particles, you ran over a tape head,
and it had all this information on it, right?
You had picture, sound, right?
Okay, that's basically how disease is done, very much the same way.
It's carried by information field, but there is material prerequisite for it to a degree.
But it's the material is not the cause.
It's one of the components.
So when you have this water in your body or around your body, that field is messed up,
just like putting a magnet near an old VHS tape or a cassette, or mixing metal powder with your cassette, you know?
It won't work.
It'll be, right?
Okay, so you're interrupting that induction, that spoilage and disease.
Okay, so what else do you do with this?
If you guys remember the handy spray bottles, instead of using dish soap straight up,
people put a little dab on a sponge and all that, it doesn't work very well.
Dilute the dish soap or whatever soap that you're using for washing dishes or general cleaning in a spray bottle, right?
And then spray it on.
And that, by the way, they have household cleaners that work that way, right?
What do you think these household cleaners, Windex, Fantastic, all these other things are?
They're just diluted detergents, right?
So why not get the detergent yourself, dilute it yourself instead of buying the water?
Correct.
And so you have a spray bottle with the sea silver, the aqua sargentum in it that you make.
You could cook it a little bit more if you'd like for use in a spray bottle.
And what do you do with it?
Take a shower.
You have it in the bathroom.
And before you towel down, you have it in the shower niche or somewhere in the tub, somewhere nearby.
So when you turn off the water of your shower and you're just about like, you know, if you shake off like a dog, that's fine, too.
While you're drip drying, reaching for that towel, do me a favor.
Right before you grab the towel, spray your whole body with that, all right?
And now you've got a layer of this on the outside, right?
Also, with the spray bottle, if you don't cook it too long, you can spray it in your mouth and just gently inhale, right?
And that vapor will go into the lung to a degree.
But remember, there's no silver in this.
This is a silver program water, right?
Okay, here's the part that's really cool.
Remember, we're still dealing with the silver in the bottle.
I just use it in a bottle.
I don't drink it.
Now, if I feel I'm coming down with something, I will do a short glass.
Remember, you don't want to drink more than three or four ounces of water at a time.
That's all your body can handle.
Well, under any circumstances, you said that, yeah.
Yeah, because the water triggers the liver reaction.
That's why the blood, you know, there's no such thing as blood sugar.
I mean, there is, but the tests don't work if you're thirsty or dehydrated or overhydrated.
It's just, you know, it's like the blood pressure and whatever.
So anyway, I would do that on occasion.
If you feel a sore throat coming on, right, you do a little shot of that or in the morning
or once in the middle of the day or night, and it's gone the next day.
So here, we go back to the spray bottle.
You could spray it in your mouth.
What happens with these spray droplets, they become sort of naturally,
they pick up an electric charge from the atmosphere.
And they're douly charged, doubly charged and duly charged when it comes out of a fine mist.
As a matter of fact, Chuck, don't think those inhalers and vaporizers and all,
it's a fine mist for people that have, that look for lung treatment, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's always in a mist, not a drop or something.
So the spray bottle, spray on the body in the shower.
By the way, people who've had like itchy parts of their body or breakouts on their body
when they do this right at the shower routine,
after a few days, weeks or a few months, their conditions are gone.
Before I continue with this, by the way, since I mentioned,
when I go out, whenever I see someone, I'm kind of nosy.
No, Greek is nosy? No way.
Well, how do you think you pick up what's going on?
But when I see someone buying like antifungal cream, like jock itch or athlete's foot itch or whatever,
you know, medicine, it's like the same.
I pointed and I said, you know, you put that on your feet, right?
It tells you between your toes and all that.
I said, you know that if you also put it on your ankle,
the condition will go away almost immediately, like a day or two.
But if you just put it the way they direct you,
you'll probably be buying that for the rest of your life.
The same thing for hands.
People that are in the military that go to Asia or whatever,
they get fungus under their nails, believe it or not,
because of the different bugs and things like that that they pick up,
that those under the nails literally will live there, right?
And it's very typical, especially if you go to Korea,
places with radically different diets and things,
and they have these fungus on their hands.
Several military people have run into this too.
And I said, if you just rub that on your hands,
you'll be on that erythromycin or whatever for months and months.
If you rub it on your hands like they tell you,
and put it on your wrist, all around your wrist,
it'll be gone in two or three days.
Do you see the commonality here?
Okay, so why?
Well, because they say it's between the toes and on the fingers.
Why would I put it on my ankle and it works better,
and why would I put it on my wrist if it's on the finger?
Well, because it's not physical.
The energy, the main energy that directs what's going on
at the end of the foot is at the ankle.
The wrist is what directs what's going on with the fingers.
As a matter of fact, the carpal tunnel syndrome and all that,
that also involves the wrist.
People who use their fingers get sore wrists, right?
The energy part.
So anyway, I just wanted to throw that in because
when I mentioned if you take a shower,
or this is a hygienic, you spray yourself with the silver,
these conditions tend to mitigate.
I'm not saying if you have an itchy spot somewhere,
pay particular attention on your wrists and ankles
because remember, you just finished the shower,
and I said do the whole body so you're covered, you see?
But I just wanted to talk about the foot cream
between the toes that people use on the bottom of the foot.
But put it on your ankle, it'll go away right away.
It'll stay away, right?
For the groin area, it's the butt crack and the lower back,
and up to the navel.
You don't have to do your whole abdomen and hip,
but an area the width of your hand from the groin to the navel,
and you could put some in the navel,
and to the top of your gluteus maximus,
to the lower spine, at least to L3.
Okay.
We have the sacrum, the sacroiliac area,
and so you go one, two, three.
L3 is about two or three inches above the butt crack.
If you put some there, if you have any ointment,
and the butt crack doesn't mean all the way around,
and up in the front, a little bit on the navel,
whatever condition.
A lot of women, I noticed, they buy, I call it box cream.
Women have a box, and they have problems with that,
and I'm like, you're only going to be using that for,
it should be like, I don't know, nine years.
I'm like, do it up to your navel and put it up here,
it'll be gone in a week.
And it is.
It's just an energetic thing.
So look, the reason I'm saying this
is because I just finished saying
we're going to spray the whole body
with the Equisargentum in the shower,
so these things are not of concern.
But it harkens back, it kind of,
it's in line with the same thing,
because there are a lot of people using these ointments, you know.
And they use them perennially.
I mean, for a long, long time, and they don't have to.
It either works or it doesn't.
Well, it works if I keep using it.
Well, if you keep using it,
it means you've got to keep buying it, right?
It doesn't mean it really works, then, because you didn't, yeah.
Well, it does work, but yeah,
because if they don't use it, it gets worse,
but they have to keep buying it, so, right?
It's that last bit.
And by the way, the doctors don't know what I just told you,
because everything, you know, remember,
I've been saying for a long time,
if you find an herb that cures or heals something,
you give it to one of these, you know,
modern trained people,
that makes it heal, right?
You have to synthesize it,
not see the whole plant and what else grows near it, right?
Or how it grows and, right?
That's how you would really synthesize it.
How does the plant grow?
Where does it grow?
When does it grow?
And what does it look like through different growth stages,
because it may not be medicinal in certain growth stages, right?
Not interested, right?
Then, if you understand all those things I just mentioned,
then you can properly synthesize it,
not just let's burn and fight with chemicals in it, see?
So, anyway, I went through all of this
because we're talking about the outside of the body,
but going back to the inside of the body
and other things,
using it in a spray bottle
is always going to be better than drinking it,
because I used to give an analogy,
if you're standing on one end
of an Olympic-sized swimming pool, Chuck,
and I'm on the other end,
and you pour a glass of water on your end of the pool
and I take a glass of water out on my end,
is it the same glass of water?
No, no.
Well, we don't know.
Now, somebody funny might say,
well, if he puts blue dye in it
and dumps it in,
you'll see where the water is, right?
Well, that's not how really water works.
You're going to see the dye, not the water.
Right.
There's no way to assure that.
Yeah, right.
You'll see the dye.
That's why people say,
oh, you see the magnetic field
when you put the metal shavings.
No, that's not the magnetic field.
You kind of think about that for a moment.
All right.
So, when you have all these tiny little droplets,
this is the Greek stretching it,
each little droplet could represent
an Olympic-sized swimming pool, right?
Okay.
Think about it.
It's a pretty massive amount of energy in there.
So, the sprayer is really where it's at
for intake also.
But here's the kicker.
You ready?
This is the kicker.
This is where you're going to save money.
People, right,
they say you play at people's fear,
their greed,
and their ego,
and they're always going to buy something, right?
So, if you're selling this,
I'm just telling how to make it,
and I'll recap it.
The way you save money with this is food spoilage.
I did many experiments.
You get wet cheese.
Well, guess what?
I like feta cheese.
Oh, my goodness.
It's a wet pungent cheese,
or any cheese.
Actually, there's a Mexican soft cheese.
Once you open the package,
it goes sour in three days.
It just smells bad,
and in four days,
it actually doesn't look good, right?
So, I did an experiment.
I think it was like a Mexican soft cheese.
Drier cheese has high fat content
like mozzarella and other things like that.
It can last much longer.
But basically, a very strong pungent cheese
that's wet.
It would go bad quickly.
Days.
Not even a week.
Just days.
It would start turning.
Well, what I did was I kept a piece
of this Mexican cheese going for like three months.
What I would do is every three days,
I would open it,
bring it over to the sink,
tilt the container,
and spray some of this aqua sargentum
from the sprayer.
Put the lid on, put it away.
Three or four days later,
it goes away.
If you have some kind of a leftover,
some kind of,
something that,
you don't want to eat spoiled food,
but as time goes on,
it doesn't taste as fresh,
and the flavor changes.
It actually goes sour.
To prevent things from going sour,
if you have tomatoes on a windowsill,
sometimes you'll notice a mold spot.
So, you have vegetables.
Let's say they have this thing
called the crisper section of the fridge.
So, you have the vegetables
in a bag or whatever.
You bring them home,
spray them with this,
spray whatever is going to go,
vegetables going to go into the fridge.
I have a piece of daikon
that I've been doing this with
since what they call last November.
It's still edible.
It's not as fresh as it was in November,
but it's a good piece of daikon still.
I think we might have finished that by now,
but to give you an idea,
three, four months,
or will last much longer,
like several weeks instead of a few days.
Yeah, I was just about to ask you about that,
because one thing I despise is
I get lettuce or I get one of these,
I get a romaine lettuce or something like that,
and within a couple of days,
it gets either slimy
or it starts to smell and taste fruity.
You know what I'm talking about?
Yeah, yeah.
Well, here's the thing.
If you grew romaine lettuce
and cut it and put it in your fridge,
you'd be good for three weeks,
but if you buy it,
it's only good for a few days
because it takes a few weeks to get to you,
a couple of weeks.
I learned this by growing my own veg,
which I do.
Yeah, so the romaine lettuce,
the way you would do it
is you would hold it sideways
and spray right down the middle
and then turn it upside down,
shake it off a little,
and spray it again
because that initial shake
is what you're using this.
If you have a family of two or three people
and you all get involved with this program,
you're going to need about a quart
to a half a gallon a week.
So anything that's going to spoil,
including the outside of your body
or the inside of your body,
this is what you put on it.
If you have animals,
it works really well.
Animals contact certain areas.
You have dogs, they slobber on things.
You use it as a cleaner.
I mop with it.
Or aqueous argentum.
So several questions are going to come up.
So anyway,
I'm praising it
because it deserves praise
because it's not toxic.
Oh, the other thing I haven't said
is it works better
than the silver that has
the high silver metallic content in it.
More effective.
I know people that buy
colloidal silver
ready-made in a bottle,
like 30, 40 bucks for a bottle
or a 16-ounce thing.
And they tell them,
even put it in a sprayer,
your sore throat,
go, no, it's not working.
Well, they tell them to make this,
the next day sore throat's gone.
So this is going to work better
than any of the metallics.
And there's nothing on the internet
about it using one.
Maybe one day there will be.
One and a half volts.
You can get creative.
I have power supplies
that are three and a half volts.
But if you measure it,
it's one and three quarter volts.
That'll work also.
The old NICAD chargers
for anything three and a half volt.
Little hand tools
that were three and a half volt NICAD,
the tools that since it's gone,
if you kept the charger,
it says three and a half volt.
If you have a volt meter,
read it, it'll be under two volts.
That'll work.
If you have just the five volt
and you want to research
how neutral plates work
in a hydrogen cell,
it's the same principle.
I have something called
Silver Made Easy.
And it's three or four pieces of silver
on a piece of cork with epoxy.
And you use a telephone charger.
Or you hook it into your telephone.
And your telephone will make the silver.
Or USB.
Your computer will make the silver.
But it's three plates
in these three spaces.
Three, you see?
Okay.
And that'll work.
So if you had 100 volts,
you need 75 or 80 plates.
But this is getting a little bit beyond.
Here's the other question.
Well, what kind of water do you use?
Because another thing you'll find
on the quote unquote colloidal,
some people call it colloidal silver.
Instead of colloidal, it's colloidal.
You have to use distilled water, right?
Well, yeah, you could.
But you don't have to.
If you're a little bit weary
about processing water at home
with a filtration or the Brita filter
like I've given or the pitcher filter.
If you're into bottled water
like the stuff that they deliver
or you buy, that's fine.
That's good enough.
It doesn't have to be distilled.
In other words, what they sell
as drinking water with minerals is fine
because you're only going to be
quote unquote cooking it for a minute
to five minutes on a quart to a gallon rate.
Right?
So you're not cooking it for a long time.
If you want to use distilled water,
it works just the same.
You can just cook it for a short time also.
Maybe if you want it to be
almost as potent,
you can double the time.
So 10 minutes for the distilled water
for a quart and 15 or 20 minutes
for the distilled gallon, right?
And down from there.
And you could still do a minute for a glass
because there are people
who claim them.
There's a lot of mythology
that if you drink distilled water,
it leaches the body from minerals.
It really doesn't.
But what the distilled water
is negative about
is how they got it distilled.
They tortured the water.
You know what I mean?
Remember Phyllis Diller?
She tried to keep herself young
with a lot of plastic surgery.
But to me,
she looked like someone
that had too much plastic surgery
to look like torture victims to me.
I know maybe it's my perception.
Well, it is my perception.
But yeah, it's tortured water.
So that's why I say the milder processed water.
Any water will work.
But if the water is very salty,
very, very high mineral content
and all that,
yeah, get some bottled water.
Any bottled water will work.
Well, the better bottled water
is a little better
and keep it out of the light
than bottled water
that's deliberately loaded with minerals.
So the water and the voltage
has got to be just one cell.
Now, here's the thing.
You could be using that same cell
for years and years and years.
It will not wear down.
That's the interesting part about it
because it uses very little current.
I shouldn't say never,
but very rarely.
I have one that's been running
for like four years
and it's still running.
Now, here's the other thing
I was going to say.
Oh, this is the other thing
that's very, very important
with the aqueous sergentum,
this method.
Make sure whatever you got,
red tape, nail polish,
I don't know,
whatever you want to use,
you mark,
you dedicate your electrode positive
and you dedicate your electrode negative
forever.
If you have batteries,
they're small.
If you have an adult-sized hand,
you could hold it with two pieces
of tape,
two pieces of silver hanging out of it
over something with water.
Don't drop the battery in the water.
I suggest using wires and things.
You can even buy a colloidal silver kit
that they sell,
whoever does,
if it's really cheap,
just for the setup
with the wiring and all that
and you immerse the electrodes.
Whatever is positive
will always be positive
and whatever is negative
will always be negative.
Do not ever switch them.
If you ever,
let's say,
just do it randomly,
you have two pieces of silver
in the drawer,
you take them out,
hook them up to alligator clips,
whatever,
and you submerse them in the water
and when you switch the electrodes,
it's going to do nothing
but pollute the water
and there's nothing you could do
to really change the silver.
I've had people try to polish the silver out
because one electrode will get dark,
one will turn white
and they'll switch them
and they'll say,
oh, now they're both dark
and it's polluting.
I see stuff coming off in the water.
I say, it'll always do that.
You have to get new silver.
You can't just smooth it out
and clean it that way.
You have to change the memory in the silver
just like you would a tape.
It's really bizarre.
It doesn't hold so much true
with the higher voltage.
With the higher voltage,
you'll pump,
if you switch the electrodes,
it'll get dirty but it'll clean up
but with the lower voltage
it'll always just pollute the water.
The main mistake that people make
is being random with the silver.
Since we're talking about the electrodes now,
I did this two decades ago
when I first got into it.
I would make so much of the silver water
by hammering it with high volt.
I would put three 9-volt batteries in series.
You know how 9-volt batteries,
you keep snapping them together, right?
27 volts and all that.
The electrodes would wear out
and I'd get more silver.
Well, with this 1.5-volt system,
the metal doesn't put any metal in the water
so guess what?
If you had 100 years to go,
100 years from now,
the silver would still be there.
You're going to be producing
aqueous argentum,
not colloidal silver.
There is no measurable silver in the water.
You take it to any lab,
they won't measure any silver in the water.
Maybe a tiny, like parts per billion
if it has a high mineral content.
And anyone will say
that's peddling colloidal silver
or colloidal silver therapy
will laugh at you for doing that
but in the meantime,
this method will work with the body
way better.
And I knew,
I revisited this a few years ago again
because I knew there were benefits to it
but I never got the benefits
using what they did.
You know, the higher voltage
and the hot water
and hammering it,
making sure you get all that gold color
in the water and all that.
I never got the benefits.
So I said we got to go biologically
because the batteries
is an alkaline battery, right?
It's literally a paste
with a cathode and anode,
a carbon, right,
and metal zinc
and it will make electricity
when you connect the two electrodes
but a car, you know,
sulfuric acid with lead, right,
in a car, on and on and on and on.
These are natural or semi-organic
and organic materials
that make electricity.
Just like in the third grade,
you know, that crunchy sound, right?
Or, you know,
if you put enough lemons together
with pieces of copper wire,
a little light bulb
would come on real dim, right?
Oh, yeah.
Lighting a light bulb
with a potato at one point, yeah.
Yeah, that's all three quarter
to one volt, right?
That's enough but it's slow.
If you don't have any electrical power,
you could do a salt battery, right?
Salt water
or vinegar
with two copper wires in it
and then on the other end,
your silver wire will produce one volt.
Chlorine battery or whatever,
you can make, right?
There's a very easy to make
a quote-unquote one volt cell.
Even the Baghdad battery, right?
Remember,
they had the iron and the copper
from 3,000 years ago or 2,000 years ago.
So, yeah, the power has to be low
and what I'm touting about this
is that its efficacy is incredible.
It's very –
and before the –
when the pandemic first hit,
I just kept doing Skype calls
and telling people how to make it.
So, I got a lot of feedback
from the worldwide web community
on Skype calls and whatever, right?
On various things.
The main thing that I wanted
to just talk about,
so we'll talk about water.
It wasn't what you were thinking, right?
No, not at all.
So, the main thing here
is getting the silver,
no silver coins,
no silver spoons, please.
Those could be used
without any ionization,
what they call ionization,
just having the presence in the liquid.
The main thing here
is getting the silver bezel.
I recommend bezel versus wire
because bezel is like flat.
It's like an eighth inch
or a quarter inch wide
in the surface area,
especially when it's round.
So, get creative.
I don't get anything for it,
but Star Gems in Tucson,
you call them up,
they'll send it to you.
It's cheap.
They have very fair prices
on double, triple, nine,
fine silver, not sterling silver.
Sterling means it has copper,
tin, lead, whatever in it
to make it stronger.
It's got to be fine.
The Japanese source,
they have the best metallurgy processes.
In the 80s,
Americans got pissed off
when the Japanese were buying
all the copper.
They're like,
what are you guys buying
all this copper from us for?
You're not using that much.
Yeah, we know,
but you guys leave so much
gold and silver in the copper,
we buy the copper,
re-refine it,
and all the gold and silver we get out of it,
it's like getting the copper for free,
and then we sell the copper again
and we make 100% profit.
And they got pissed,
and they couldn't figure out
how to get more of the gold and silver
out of the copper,
the Americans.
Still, they still can't.
So, anyway,
I hope what I just said made sense
from an economic point of view.
So, that's what I wanted to mention.
Number nine,
to get the bezel silver triple nine
or double nine fine,
one and a half volt,
any water that you would drink
that tastes good is fine.
No more than a couple of minutes
for a quart,
and double that time for a gallon.
Keep it in spray bottles.
I have one in the bathroom,
one in the kitchen,
and another one floating around,
let's say.
It works well on animals.
Use an old fantastic bottle.
No, no, no.
A clean bottle
that never had something in it
that sticks to the floor.
Yeah, dollar stores, Walmart,
you see them everywhere.
The gardening section.
If you got 15 children,
you might want to get
one of those pump sprayers
with the hose.
You have them all lined up,
open your mouth,
and you walk down
and if you're on some kind of
regimen with the aqua sargentum,
it's going to be the most potent
for three days if it's kept
in the dark.
A month later, two weeks later,
it's still fine,
but not as potent as for the
first three or four days.
Here's the other thing.
If you spray it in your mouth,
it's going to have this odd
sweet aftertaste.
Not directly sweet.
It'll just taste like regular water.
Not sweet with no other flavor.
It's like a sickly sweet.
It's not like that.
It's not like if you're ever
changing the coolant in a car
and you touch your mouth
and it's really that sickly sweet.
Not like that.
It's a vague aftertaste,
like you said.
It's way distant aftertaste
and it's very unique to this.
If you tasted the other silvers
that they peddle and tell you
how to make or whatever,
it's not like that.
I have tasted the all-American
colloidal silver.
They put it in...
I've had that before in my mouth.
Droppers.
There's a nasty kind of metallic,
very heavy metallic taste.
It's toxic.
This will work.
There's no silver present.
Once it gets to the body,
the body says,
I know exactly what to do with this.
This is all pure signal.
The body is like,
oh, great.
I know exactly what to do with this.
Thanks.
I got the message.
It works.
Once you have it in a spray bottle,
where do you apply it?
Again, just to recap,
right after a shower.
You don't have to,
but it'll cover you.
Then you towel down.
Your laundry will be a lot fresher.
I use it in the laundry.
Can you tell?
Yeah, of course.
Open your mouth spot,
shoot it in his mouth.
They don't have as much
intestinal flora and fauna
as we do,
but you have to be careful
with older dogs and older people.
It will act as a laxative.
A lot of people get excited with this.
Oh, I've never made anything good
for my health before.
They make a quart,
drink a big tall glass,
that's how you know
the body is reacting majorly to it.
There's no silver content,
but animals, plants,
spoilage for food,
whether it's in the fridge,
any part of the fridge,
or out of the fridge,
feet, underarms,
it works as well as a deodorant.
A woman's box,
a man's butt,
anywhere, groin, feet, mouth,
anywhere.
Anywhere you think
you might want to curb
where things might take hold
and fester,
it will impede that
and abate it.
Probably a good idea
behind the ears too,
because that's another
one of those interesting areas.
Ears, yeah,
I wouldn't try to spray it
in the ear,
I would put it on a swab.
Aphids,
things like that,
yeah, the aphids won't,
but it's not something
like a strong chemical,
it'll be a few days
and then they come back.
I spray it in the laundry.
Yeah, so wherever you want
to curb some kind of
an organic manifestation
and induction
would be the application.
And no one that I've ever
recommended this to
but any nose,
stomach stuff,
skin stuff,
it mitigates that.
And you'll know it's working
if you get excited
when you first make you
drink a glass,
it'll be like a laxative.
That's how you know it works.
What do you mean it's working?
We had it tested,
there's nothing but water,
there's nothing else
but just water and some
antibiotics,
not from a clinical sense,
no, the clinical sense
are irrelevant in the real world.
Generally, yeah,
look, if it works, it works.
That's the thing,
when you hear about
well somebody says
well just put this in this
and do this and it goes
well it doesn't make any sense,
how does that change anything?
Well, you know what,
if it works, it works.
It doesn't have to be
for all American.
All American colloidal silver.
What you're supposed to do
with it is take it
and put it in a vaporizer,
and this is what I did
and it kind of helped a little bit
but it also made me feel weird.
And like I said,
it tasted terrible.
I don't know about you
but I don't put coins in my mouth,
I don't care how dirty they are
or clean they are,
materialist philosophy
is little is good, more is better
and a lot should do the trick, right?
It doesn't work that way.
That's also how drug addicts think too,
but that's okay.
Yeah, if you do over so much
you wonder why it's not working anymore.
So this is my rant
and info supply,
info drop,
whatever for this one.
And yeah,
aqueous argentum,
and spell it how you want.
It's important for other names
because there's no silver cholate in it
and it works like a charm.
Well, makes the most sense to me.