It's amazing that I'm being held on a project so long, it seems to be so worthless.
But anyway, what did I just say?
Anyway, we'll edit that part out.
No, no, no, we won't.
But I don't feel as though it's worthless at all.
I think every time we've touched upon something that is worthwhile, we've answered lots of
questions.
Is there anything in the chat recently that catches your eye, by the way?
Because we do have a little chat in case somebody's listening and doesn't know about it.
Okay.
No problem.
I got a recent message about...
Yeah, yeah, there is.
Oh, okay.
Go ahead.
Yeah, go ahead.
Okay.
I got a recent...
No, looking at the chat.
Okay.
This is miscuing.
Sure.
Go ahead.
Looking at the chat.
You go.
I don't recall anything really to whatever, but addressing at the moment, but go for it.
Okay.
I'll look at it.
Go for the other questions.
Yeah.
No problem.
I got a message about dreams because a long time ago we had talked about dreams and they
mentioned that you had referenced how plants are in a dream state, et cetera, et cetera.
And their question was, what is to stop us from maybe finding out that this world, the
way it is, the fact that we have this odd connection to memory and the way we dream
and all that kind of stuff, that we're not actually in a dream state at this point?
That really real life begins after this visit to this place.
Is that not a possibility?
And that was the question for you.
What was your response on that?
It goes back to...
I think I dropped a serious bomb a while back, maybe a while, like three, four sonics ago,
that I know the meaning of life.
Right.
And you don't, ha, ha, ha.
And it's just that everyone is here to waste everyone's time.
Let me just give you a little example.
So take some common oaf off the street, works in a UAW, which is the Factory Workers for
Auto Workers Union.
United Auto Workers.
25, yeah, 25, 30 years.
He does okay.
He's got all the benefits, whatever.
Then he retires and takes on a train hobby, make sure he gets all his blood pressure and
diabetes medication, whatever, and then he dies.
You mean a model train hobby?
Yeah.
And these cars, by the way, these trains, yeah, these cars that he's building are 130 year
old technology, virtually no improvement over 130 years.
Maybe a little bit that's worth, that's laughable.
Now, if you can't tell me anybody, now replace the factory worker with a doctor, a lawyer,
a priest, a construction worker, whatever, and tell me it's any different for them.
Right.
Now, let's go back to the more personal situation.
Okay.
You have a wife, can't fucking stand her.
She can't stand you, but you have some kind of an agreement that you compensate for each
other.
You quote unquote love each other, even though either one of you don't even know what love
is.
How do I know that?
Just ask somebody what love is.
They don't know.
And now, if that's not a waste of time, children, parents, parents, how do they raise their
children?
Oh, you do what I did.
Now, what are the chances?
I'm going to do with you what was done with me.
What are the chances that parents did not have their, that their lives were not wasted
while they were children by their parents?
And it continues and it continues.
You can give me a cross section of any fucking situation and I will show you how it is just
wasting time.
Matter of fact, over time with parents, the only thing that I can observe is that we do
discover, and I see this generationally and I say this as someone who is a parent, is
that we just find new ways to screw things up.
That's that's right.
But it's not.
I'm going to try to get into parenthood here.
It's any scenario.
So go up to a daffodil rose.
Let's just stick with the plants.
We're at the place.
And what's the meaning of life?
Well, I'm just here.
Right.
OK.
I mean, what could be more than that?
A rose by any other name is still a rose.
Right.
It's no different than that.
So the thing that we like to make up stories to ourselves because we don't even know what
we we think we have an inner voice.
You don't have an inner voice.
That's given to you.
It's planted.
Speaking of which, a little segue, I did the past few days, I'm doing a super deep dive
where I do a deep dive and stuff.
I mean, like I'll have three hours sleep in three days or two days, which is not a lot.
Right.
So in other words, I keep going all day till four thirty in the morning.
I sleep till seven and I'm at it till three in the morning the next day, sleep till six
and I'm at it till the next day.
Right.
Like three hours of sleep tops.
OK.
I've been doing this for a little while now on trust law.
And if anyone wants to get into more of the side that I'm looking at is a guy named Christopher
Houser, H-A-U-S-E-R.
He's on the mark.
He does it again, just like the Brandon Joe Williams guy.
He's leaving out some stuff.
I don't endorse Houser's, but he's the closest that I've seen on operating trust.
So I'll give some examples and you'll see what's going on more with the wasting of
time and how everyone's a millionaire and they don't know it and how people are too
shaky and too stupid to be able to utilize it because of conditioning.
I'll give you another example.
The police are not law enforcement, they're perception enforcement.
So if the TV, the church and says that, you know, you have to do this, the police stop
you because you're not doing it.
They're correct because the general perception, just like 9-11.
It's a fact that if you discuss the 9-11 event, the opening events always start off with whoever
had perceived the event or witnessed the event on television, airplanes being shown going
into the building.
That's fact.
So what is also a fact is that whoever was boots on the ground within visual proximity
of the World Trade Center was happened to be looking in that direction at a time, merely
saw the sides of the buildings explode out.
There was no sound of a plane, no visible confirmation of a plane by anyone.
Fact.
There's another fact that back to the TV, there were people on the ground posing as
bystanders and utility workers saying that the planes went into the towers stacked.
Those people also seen in various shootings across the country.
Same people, Colorado, Florida, Connecticut.
Those people were giving witnesses on various shootings that were supposed to be posed as
local people.
Right.
Fact.
So do you see how?
OK.
So now, Greek, are you saying that one thing didn't have it?
No, no.
I'm giving you the facts to sort it out.
Right.
So the big one is, for example, it's a fact.
Again, back to 9-11.
Anyone who witnessed the event on television saw planes penetrating the towers, which would
normally be impossible.
How do you know it's an impossible?
Anyone that works in aircraft structure, aircraft structures knows that when a plane crashes,
the tail section falls off, doesn't matter how slow or how fast it goes.
That's why in the military or people flying the plane, I was sitting back because first
thing I have is the tail section breaks off.
Right.
It's just a fit.
I can get into it.
Has to do with compound inertia and all that stuff.
And you can't build the structure if you build a structure.
So the tail section doesn't fall off immediately.
It's not cost effective to fly the thing around.
Right.
It's too heavy.
OK.
So because, you know, in airplanes, if it costs less than five hundred dollars to remove a
pound, do it because it's going to cost more than five hundred dollars in fuel to fly the
stupid thing around.
You know, whatever you're adding or taking away for for a high altitude, what they call
space.
It's thirty thousand dollars.
So if you're working on the space shuttle, if it costs thirty thousand dollars or less
to take off pound, take that fucking pound off because it's going to cost you more than
that fuel.
Right.
You see how it works.
OK.
Insurance works the same way when you're in a public building and like there's something
that's going to fall off the building and hit someone in the public.
They look at it and they say, oh, what's our insurance?
Is it cheaper to to let someone get hit and get insurance claim or is it cheaper to fix
it because insurance?
Well, you see, that's how everything is based on this number scheme.
Cost benefit analysis.
Yeah.
So you see the dangers in public and they don't fix it because it's it's more expensive
than the insurance claim would be.
So they don't care.
So there's this analysis thing.
So this is when you ask me about the dream thing, it's about the same thing.
So I've done several protocols on Greek speak where I've gone over food.
I've gone over spiritual stuff, soul stuff, which is medical stuff, by the way.
Now, that's a new one because, first of all, no one knows the definition of soul and spirit
that they're different.
And I say no one with very little exception.
When we speak about the human body and medical stuff, that's soul stuff, metabolite.
Right.
OK.
And body stuff together.
Because when you're if the soul, if the body doesn't have a soul, it doesn't matter.
It's just dense meat.
You end up on the supermarket.
All right.
Wrapped in plastic or whatever.
So we've talked about all these things and those are actually miniature protocols.
Now, the dream aspect of it, when you go back to this is your weight.
OK, there's some kind of a movie set situation where some authority producer would director
finance, whatever, has set up a situation where we have to be on this place called
Earth.
The way society is just to fill something, some purpose, just like extras, right?
Just like extras in the movie.
And then it gets blown up and redone again.
Who cares?
Right.
But it looks real.
But it's not.
It looks real.
Right.
So the other aspect of dreaming, I would I would just go.
If you could find Isak, who is it, Isak, who wrote Swinging the Wild Pendulum, Bentov.
He says him and also a few other people in that study of like paranormal research or
the mind and consciousness, they can't really put their finger on it.
But what they have seen enough evidence of is that we're asleep, we're actually our consciousness
is being used elsewhere.
Now, there's so many excuses and reasons for sleeping.
You know, you can kill someone if they don't.
If you don't sleep for seven days, you'll probably die.
You need that recuperation time.
What's one third of your life?
Right.
So if you live 90 years, you spent 30 years asleep.
And that's a stalking, stalking the wild, stalking the wild pendulum.
Thank you.
So.
So you're being the consciousness has been in Donald Marshall with the cloning makes
total sense.
Of course, the consciousness transfer and all that.
So the dream is something in between.
But you have to have already worked out who you are, meaning physically, mentally, spiritually.
And you've already have to work out the inner voice.
In other words, if you hear an inner voice in your head and it sounds like you and your
voice, that's not you.
Your inner dialogue is without words, sort of how it was before you learned the language.
Think about if you can remember when you were an infant before you knew the language, what
kind of dialogue this is a shortcut, by the way, what kind of dialogue you had internally
before you knew any language at all.
Most people can't recall that much because the physical size of the brain cannot access
that information, because right now you're a different antenna, just like someone setting
up ham radio.
When you set up something for six twenty seven, that antenna, it's not going to work on the
eleven hundred band.
You need another antenna for that.
So you're going to have to go back.
Right.
OK, so.
So right now you're brave.
So, yeah, that's where the shrunken head principle comes in.
Literally, if you can transfer your head, your spirit into a smaller head, literally
a small brain, you will be able to get all your you would even be able to recall being
coming down the birth canal.
Right.
And all that stuff.
So I don't recommend that, but I'm sure it's been experimented with.
Now, we don't get any of this technology very often with certain circles that I've intermingled
with here.
Like I give an example.
I won't mention a company like Raytheon or anything like that.
I was invited to a party and just various sundry people there.
By the way, someone says they're an engineer.
I'm not going to mention the company Raytheon.
Don't be impressed.
The people in the fucking gift shop are engineers.
Right.
There's certain jobs.
Like if someone says, I'm an attorney, you're a fucking officer of the court.
No different than the janitor and the bailiff or whatever.
Right.
So if I'm a doctor, you're a fucking medical technician.
Yep.
You're a medical technician.
Right.
If you don't do these procedures, you know nothing about the human body at all.
Even the brain surgeon, it's procedural.
They're told exactly.
Don't look.
Don't ask questions.
Right.
So all this overestimating and overdoing, right, is where we're stuck.
Asking all these questions is where we're stuck.
So it's basically just a big hole in the wall that we're trying to look through.
But the lights are out on both sides.
Hmm.
Now, is that an answer or not?
No, that is.
That is.
If you can solve the internal.
Yeah.
If you could if you can get rid of that internal voice.
Here's an example of the internal voice, how it works.
OK.
Remember when you were on Normie, if you ever were and then you got some information about
the money system, about the flat earth, about anything that got you out of that normie phase
about like taxes don't pay for anything or the human body is more like or something that
or 9-11 was a conspiracy where everyone really thinks it was 19 Arab hijackers with box cutters
that vaporize those buildings.
Right.
So when you got out of the normie phase where you just blatantly accept anything and you're
just a vegetable, really a walking vegetable and you started getting into, quote unquote,
what's being awake and more searching where you can wear the badge of honor being called
a conspiracy theorist or something.
OK.
For about a week to a month at that point, you had incredible clarity and your inner
voice was very calm and peaceful and almost not there, because at that point, the being
that was providing you your inner voice as a normie had a certain has a certain level
or whatever.
When you start discovering other things about this reality, that being is too dumb to feed
you to keep you in check.
So they have to switch the being.
They have to get another one more advanced that's already been indoctrinated that being
that spiritual entities are indoctrinated in the new group that you're going into.
Right.
The fringe element, the alternative.
OK, whatever.
So until they find one, very rarely is there an immediate replacement.
Very rarely, like within a minute or a day or a week.
Very rarely.
It's usually about a week.
That's why I gave you up to a month.
You'll notice that after about a week or a month of learning these new things and wanting
to go in a new direction, realize that everything you were taught was a lot worse.
Most of the things you were taught was a lie.
You have this incredible clarity and then you start to take on this new feeling of potential
either fear or despair, uncertainty, doubt, and the voice comes back, but it's in a different
dialogue.
And once you transcend that, let's say you go to a higher level.
Oh, again, you get that clarity because that being that was giving you, you know, you're
one of the alternatives will wake people now you're not asleep anymore.
That one's not enough because now you've transcended that that many multitude or subculture within
the main culture.
And they have to send another one when you transcend that one a few more times, a few
more like a rocket booster stages.
When you get to the final stage, there's very little anymore.
There are very few beings, very, very few beings that can, they can replace you with
now and what they do to conserve on their side is they give you a being that makes you
prescient and actually tells you in your own mind what's going to happen anywhere between
the next five seconds to eight minutes in the future.
And those people fall for that and they call themselves psychics.
You're not psychic.
Everyone, in other words, everyone has the same psychic ability as everybody else.
Your ability to access it as an inner dialogue comes from another being for a little while
here at whatever.
For a little while, a few years ago, I was able to tell between five to eight seconds
up to five minutes what's going to happen.
I mean, specifically to the point where I'm going to tell you in the next, the next car
to come down this road is going to be a 1983 Nissan pickup truck, a white color, a boom.
There it is.
How the fuck do you know that?
Because I'm not falling for it.
I know what's going on and UPS is going to knock on the door and the guy's going to say
he's got a package, but he's actually got the wrong address.
Hold on.
Wait five minutes later.
Knock, knock.
Yeah.
That kind of stuff.
All the time.
I said, no, I'm not falling for this shit.
You guys just leave me alone.
Right now.
This is not a vertical level.
This is like when you're in the military and you climb up the ranks.
This is lateral.
You're going outside of the pool, right onto the shore and you're trying to dry yourself
off.
Everybody's been dipped.
The sheep dipping is actually a term, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
For the public.
Yeah.
You look it up.
What it means.
And yeah.
So the dream thing is very, very, very complex.
Now I've gotten into many talks or monologues about Castaneda actually said this too, because
a lot of people say, oh, you got some guys in the red kit, never read Castaneda, but recently
I've gone through most of his stuff on audio books past two years.
If you're in your dream, um, I've said this and I've also, so I haven't heard Castaneda.
Maybe he has or hasn't ever noticed when you're in a dream and there's dialogue, you look
at people and their mouths are not moving.
Yes.
That was a fascinating thing that you brought up to me about, I mean, almost 10 years ago.
And I said, you know, that's something I've always noticed, but nobody, nobody ever says
that.
But it's true.
Yeah.
You never see it.
You just, you make eye contact and you have a transference of an idea.
All of a sudden, you know what's going on.
Nobody's saying anything to you, even if you think they did.
That's right.
So in other words, what you're doing here is you're catching the man behind the curtain.
You're seeing that this is all done as a, as a, as a, as a show for you.
You're not actually another reality, but if you're actually building stuff and doing stuff
with your hands or your feet, and you can actually see your hands and feet moving, you're
no longer in a dream.
You're an alternate reality.
It's kind of like, you can't see the UV spectrum or the infrared.
So if you go into a reality, that's UV and infrared, you, you're blind.
So what I mean by you're going into another reality, when you see tactile motion with
your own appendages and digits, right, you are now, it's not that you're really in a
different reality.
You're taken from here.
What you're doing is you're given UV or x-ray vision now, right?
You see?
Well, about vision, because I pay very close attention to it in the same types of, you know,
scenarios where I, where I know that the mouths don't move.
I can also tell you that my vision is usually in one of two places, either it's within three
feet of me and that's it.
There's nothing past that three feet or it is so far wide that it's beyond any experience
in life.
It's like miles and miles in all directions.
That's the one.
Hold on.
I want to capture some of that.
I don't know if anyone's ever been to a shooting range and if you don't wear goggles, I recommend
you do because bullets can shatter, leaving the muzzle.
Yes, of course.
Yeah.
So I can also get deposit and also deposits of gas.
People think that it's, can also spray back in the eye.
The goggles are absolutely necessary to release some sort of protective glasses, right?
But if you have ones that do not obscure peripheral vision or without goggles, you can actually
see bullets flying from your peripheral vision.
But if you ask someone to look and look directly within that 30 or 60 degree vision cone to
see that, did you see the bullet go by?
No, I didn't see it.
But from your peripheral, you can.
So your peripheral can actually capture in time, much more information in time per unit
of time.
So in other words, within that 30 to 60 to 45, let's just get 30 to 45 degree vision
cone.
That speed of that bullet is not imperceivable.
But through the, beyond that cone, the peripheral, that speed slow seems to slow down.
You could pick up more information at a higher speed.
Well, I can tell you that's true from being shot at, because quite honestly, being shot
at running away, I can see a bullet whiz past me in my peripheral vision.
I don't even have great vision, but I can still see that in my peripheral vision.
If I turn to look at the person firing, I don't see the bullets coming out of the gun.
I don't.
I see a flash or something, or I see, you know, their, their movement when they fire a bullet,
but I don't see the bullet.
Yeah.
Peripherally though, if it whizzes past me and it's in my side, you know, it's perceivable.
Yes.
It's perceivable.
You made the level of detail again.
Okay.
So let's go beyond the peripheral.
What's that?
Now we're out of sight range completely.
Then it's the mind.
Now we're going into star Wars episode four, which is the first one where he's practicing
with the lightsaber and he says, I'm putting blinder on you, right?
Use the force.
Right.
Okay.
So that's the higher level.
And that's where you go in your dream, where you don't need these sensory orgas, which
what I like about what Jason Brashear says, they're filters, these, these, what we have.
So that's why people who are damaged, either brain damage or perceptual damage, they can
hear more, see better because the filter has been changed, right?
Like we have audio filters.
That's why I like when I was really young playing with radios, Oh, some old guy.
So you didn't do it right.
Or whatever.
But I enjoyed not doing it right.
Cause I was starting to hear things that no one, you know, that you're not supposed
to go and listen to.
Cause there's supposedly nothing there.
Right.
Supposedly.
But there's lots of stuff there.
I had more fun not being, uh, not being told how to tune it.
So I was all over the place and saying, well, you know, so anyway, it wasn't tangible, but
it was interesting.
So what I'm, what I'm trying to get to is we don't know because we're, first of all,
if you had the answers for everything, succinct, and by the way, it's not hard to do that, to
get everything in order, how it would be more and more difficult for you to be one
of the members of the surface dwelling earth inhabitants, who's wasting their time.
And the purpose, the main purpose of surface dwelling earth inhabitants is to waste their
time.
That is the main purpose.
And that is, uh, that is, you basically can go up to anyone.
I assure you this, that's fairly reasonable and argue the word argue, by the way, it means
to give reason for it's not what it's like the word nice, the real, the real me or apologetic
means to defend.
Well, it's not about the conflict.
It's about the, to make an argument.
That's why they call it that in legalese because it means to offer a reason for what, what's
going on.
Yeah.
Your reason, your rationale behind something, your rationale, your explanation, almost.
That's right.
It's sort of, it's sort of coupled with apology, Jetix, but they're, they're different apologetics
tend to be more, uh, but your belief system and argument would be more of a situation
or events.
It's more about advocacy than it did.
Just plain story.
Right.
So yeah.
Okay.
Go ahead.
All right.
Where, what will, what were we speaking?
Oh yeah.
So you can actually go to anyone who, uh, and argue this point or knows, provide enough
rationale and say to them, anyone out of the blue, ha ha, I know the meaning of life and
you don't.
Yeah.
You can be a little prick like that and it's cannot be refuted.
In other words, ha ha ha ha, I know the meaning of life and you don't, or yous don't.
And what is it?
Greek or Sally?
What is it?
We're all here to waste each other's time.
What?
At first it's like, well, I never heard it put as such.
Never.
Second of all, it doesn't need a lot of referencing because all you could just give the small
example of the workers, like anybody will see it.
Anyone, everyone will see it.
Obviously, you know, when I say anyone, you know, there's very few people on this planet
anyway.
So what I mean by this is these things are not difficult to figure out, but maybe it's
better that you don't figure it out.
That wouldn't do.