The sonic entity known as Ocelli,
erred in the Greek.
This evening, because the sun's down where I am.
Yeah, it's going down here.
Yeah, well, the thing is that people like the Greek speak,
the Greek perspective,
and, well, not the Greek perspective,
but I'm the only Greek I know, but meaning Greek speak.
So, yeah, we were talking about water, concrete, magnetism.
You said you were dealing with a car mechanic.
I got a lot to say about that, right?
So, you got a car, right?
And you went from one mechanic to another or whatever, yeah?
Had to, because, quite frankly, look,
I'm not great with the mechanics,
so I seek out somebody who is,
and hopefully they help me to maintain the vehicle, you know,
so that it doesn't break down, or when it does break down,
then we got to get it back to running.
And, you know, now I'm stuck,
because I laid out money to a guy
who was really pulling me along there,
due to my ignorance.
And, you know, it's a common problem, I think.
But go ahead, yeah.
You know, here's the thing about that.
Okay, forget about the car.
Let's say it's a horse.
You don't have a horse for transportation for too long
if you don't know enough about horses.
It'll die on you, right?
Of course.
So you need someone who knows about horses
that you cohort with closely,
and is hopefully close to the horse.
And, by the way, when you have a horse,
you know, you can have a car parked for a month, right?
Forget about the title, insurance, all that stuff,
but you can park for a month and just get in and go.
If you have a horse sitting in a stable for a month,
you still have to feed them and water them every day,
even if you're not using them, right?
That's right, yeah.
So cars are a lot cheaper.
But it's all about maintenance.
So what happened was people got very distracted.
I used to go into a car dealership and say,
Hey, this car, I was in here a year or two ago,
and the cars are different now.
Oh, yeah, these are the new models.
He's so happy, right?
These are the new models.
I'm like, what do you mean new models?
I mean, that just means you haven't figured out how to make them yet, right?
I went to the hardware store and I got a hammer,
and I saw an East Wing hammer,
and the one I've been carrying around all my life was made in the 1940s,
and the one I just bought is exactly the same.
East Wing, an East Wing 18 ounce or 16 ounce hammer.
It's exactly the same.
You know why?
Because they figured out how to make hammers.
You don't have to change it.
So they have this vanity thing, right?
People say I got a new car.
I said, well, what's the engine made of?
Is it an aluminum block, aluminum head?
I don't know.
What's the compression ratio on the engine?
You went $50,000 into it?
It's like, what kind of horse is it?
What is a horse like?
Hey, what kind of temperament?
I don't know.
So all this vanity stuff, the new model, the year, all that stuff, the fuel.
On one of the Hiresite chats, it talked about – I'll get to the mechanics here shortly,
and this is the buildup.
You know what?
I don't know if you've ever visited a place where they manufacture cars.
Well, the car comes off the assembly line, and they start it up,
and it doesn't run very long.
And a guy comes over, and he puts like this cushion over the fender
so he doesn't scratch it with his belt buckle,
and he hooks up a laptop or an iPad kind of thing.
Okay.
And they check the computer, and they adjust the computer
so it gets close to the mileage that's on the sticker.
Why?
Some of the cars come off the assembly line.
Let's say it's a Ford pickup truck.
It's supposed to get 18 miles to the gallon average, let's say, right?
Sure.
Okay, it comes off the assembly line, so he tests one,
and it's getting five miles to the gallon.
No good.
It has to be 18 close to it.
So he tunes the computer to give you 18.
All right.
It does that.
It does a couple more similar.
And then another one comes off.
It's getting 75 miles to the gallon.
Oh, we can't have that.
So we tune it down, right, to dump fuel so it gets 18 miles to the gallon.
You see what's going on?
So I do modifications on what they call combustion engines,
and if it doesn't have a computer, I double the time or the mileage.
The reason I say time is a neighbor who was cutting the lawn,
and every 20 minutes, like clockwork, what does he do?
He stops, and what does he do?
He has to put gas.
He has this little can, and he puts gas in it, runs it for another 20 minutes,
runs out of gas.
I said, look, how would you like for that thing to run for 40 minutes instead of 20,
which is double, right?
Right.
An hour and a half later, boom, here you go.
Now it's clockwork 40, 45 minutes before he refills it, right?
It has to do with the spark plug and the carburetor.
But the moment you have a computer controlling stuff,
it's going to introduce sabotage.
All right, so put that together with the vanity that started.
When did the vanity start?
Probably in the 30s with the Model T or before that,
because Model T is the Model A.
Model T stands for tall, right?
Okay, right.
And they started the new car model years.
I think it was really popular in the 50s, right?
And still is, okay?
Total bullshit.
They keep the people completely ignorant of cars,
which is very simple technology, by the way.
But if you're not familiar with it, right, it's complicated, right?
Think about any subject.
Think about, for example, we're doing these Sonics,
and you've been, quote, unquote, involved with radio,
and you know how to push buttons and record something and broadcast, all that stuff, right?
I don't know if you've ever worked in a TV or radio station, a proper one.
I have.
I've been in proper radio stations.
A TV station, I've only ever seen the one side of the camera,
but I've actually been throughout a radio station, yeah.
Yeah, okay.
So basically what you're doing right now is just that, an extraction, an adaptation of the same thing.
Right.
Except there you have to consider the high power and the distribution and all that other stuff.
But here's the thing.
If you have someone who has no experience and you throw them in a radio station
or where you're sitting right now to do what you're doing and say go, they go into a panic.
Right, they have no idea what to do, right.
No, well, they might think they do, but they won't succeed, you know.
Right.
Okay, so this is what they're doing with the car culture, right.
I just buy a new car or whatever, and then when it comes time to the mechanic,
the mechanic is good and ready.
The mechanic culture has adapted to this as becoming predatory.
Right.
Okay, same thing with health.
Oh, I'm not feeling well.
What do you do?
I'm going to go to the doctor, right, because it's like the doctor, right.
Right.
How many times have you heard that?
Somebody's hurt.
You need to go to a doctor or you need to go to the doctor, right.
It's even worse.
Why?
Because they keep you away.
Most people, what they know about the human body is what they got from grandma
or their parents or television.
Think about how pathetic that is, right.
And then they try to look at the alternatives, which tells you take this supplement
and it lowers your blood pressure.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, my.
Or I don't know if I've been on, maybe if you were around,
a couple of alternative medicine people were on a Skype
or I might have been in Revolution Radio Days.
Yeah, we invented this nutrition thing.
You absorb it ten times more.
I said, Absorb it?
Are you sure about that?
And I explained it.
He says, Well, I've been doing this for 35 years.
Right.
It's like, What?
You could be doing it for 3,500 years.
Right.
It's wrong.
Okay.
So, in other words, what's happened is people have gone away from the reality
of their responsibility to that reality.
That reality could be the health, right?
The health is like the car, right?
You don't feel sick?
Go to a doctor.
Go to the hospital, right?
Your car's not working?
Go to a mechanic, right, right away, right?
You need a mechanic.
Right?
What about the ordinary person?
Hey, listen.
I want you to start broadcasting or do some podcasting or whatever.
I don't know, man.
I need a radio set.
I need a pocket.
Why?
Get familiar with it quickly, right?
Don't panic.
So, what's happened is people are being led away from their own responsibility
to their own reality.
Here's the thing.
That's the culture, right?
Well, I don't know.
I'm not a plumber.
I can't fix a broken pipe because I'm not a plumber.
What?
Were there plumbers around?
What came first, the plumber or the pipe?
Right?
You know what I think?
Well, I think what you're trying to say is not really just the responsibility,
but look, if you're going to utilize something and you're going to be in charge of something,
maybe it's a good idea to know how it works unless you're going to sit there
and just toss it away and get a new one every time it doesn't work.
Well, that's part of the ritual that's taught, but this is not on you.
This is not a stain on your side.
The reason I'm saying this is because it's developed this type of culture.
Yeah, can you have honest, diligent, economic-to-use mechanics?
Of course.
The culture could have been built around that, but it hasn't.
The culture's been built around laziness, basically.
Yeah, some of them work hard, but dishonest and shabby.
That's the culture.
That's the standard.
Right?
So I'm not saying this is what you're doing or not doing.
I'm saying the culture's built around that.
The culture's not built around people knowing what they're getting, like compression ratio,
what the materials are, what the tolerance are.
You know, the higher the tolerance is, the longer the engine's going to last, right?
And all this other stuff.
They're not taught that.
They're away from it, so they could focus on who has a newer car,
because they obviously still haven't figured out how to make them.
So this is the culture.
The same thing, the culture, especially in white America.
Someone gets sick for more than a day or two or three,
and people can't fix it with something, what do they say?
Go to the hospital.
Go to the doctor.
Why?
What does he know?
You see, the culture has led people into this.
Because the doctors are predatory.
You know, we never talked about how hospitals work, but they're the banks.
The real bank is the hospital, right?
The banks that you call the banks are not banks.
They're national associations.
If you have a checking number, it says N.A. at the end, right?
And then they have another name, which is Inc., which is the corporate part,
which is different, right?
Where the money is generated is in the hospital.
That's why old people, when they see that they have like a premium insurance plan
from like the Blue Cross Blue Shield.
I know the CEO from there.
It's called Anthem Corporation.
He's got a $36,000 a month pension.
I tell this to people.
I say, what was he making if his pension is $36,000?
What was he making when he was working, right?
Yeah, right.
Yeah.
So anyway, when you have like a premium insurance policy like that,
you go in for like a stubbed toe, they want to remove your lungs
and give you a kidney transplant for a million bucks
because the insurance will be unnecessary completely, right?
You know the majority, 75% to 90% of all diagnoses are completely fictional.
I used to tell people, I don't know, I went to this to diagnose me.
I think I better do it.
I said, all right.
They didn't really diagnose you.
What they did is they said you got to get a lab test, urine, feces, blood, whatever,
and they just show you the lab test and then they make a recommendation.
That's not a diagnosis.
Tell the doctor if he's diagnosing you with this disease or ailment or cancer
to write it down on paper in an affidavit form and sign it.
None of them will do that.
None, not a one.
They're specifically told never to do that, ever.
You'll never get that.
It's all presumption, all of it.
Well, you know what occurs to me while you're talking about this is that,
you know, in recent years I've noticed that they have actually started to develop
like an insurance kind of scheme for cars as well.
Have you seen this?
Yeah, for repairs.
The TV commercial late night, I was watching Star Trek.
$35 for a transmission, get this insurance repair.
And, oh, thanks, it's fixed now, right?
Yeah, actually, I first saw it on Star Trek, too.
Yeah, commercial.
Yeah, the old one with William Shatner, I think is the last one alive.
I think so, yeah.
Techie.
But here's the thing.
Insurance companies don't have any money either.
What insurance companies really are, they are a privilege.
They're access, they're a middleman to the Fed window.
See, if you go to the Fed window, it's not, we're talking about electronic convention now.
But years ago, the Fed had windows in all the 12 major cities, right?
San Francisco, Dallas, New York, Chicago, the other one, St. Louis.
Yeah, these are the main Federal Reserve Bank branches, right.
Yeah, and then they had small sub ones, and you took a document, a contract, a bond,
and you had a signature or two signatures on it, and they gave you an account.
They didn't give you cash anymore.
That was good, a check to deposit in the bank for the value.
So insurance companies, they have access to that window.
That's why the claim forms, they ask you all these questions.
You can't get insurance without a Social Security number,
because that's to show that you're part of the administration of the bankruptcy, right?
So the United States went bankrupt, so you're exempt from it.
All debt belongs to the United States.
You could look this up.
But what happens is you waive it different ways, you know.
Anyway, the insurance company just takes the claim, so the premiums that you're paying,
takes the claim to the Fed window and it monetizes it and gives it whatever.
The reason you have to pay a premium every month is to give you the impression that you're paying into something, right?
It's like tax.
I heard there was a video of someone talking about government funding.
It doesn't know a damn thing.
It's got like 100-something thousand subscribers.
Someone says, oh, this guy's alive right now.
You want to listen to it?
Put him on.
Saying, oh, yeah, the taxes, once the state pulls their federal taxes,
the federal government is going to – there's not – 0% of taxes since 1938 have gone not even for nothing.
You know, not one even stick of chewing gum has been bought from anybody's taxes,
the trillions and trillions.
None of it has nothing to do with – doesn't work that way, right?
The problem that the tax collection agencies have is not that you didn't pay.
It's that you didn't what?
File a report because they're monetizing their report.
People – I think I've run over this many times.
You know, if you're minus $1,000 in the bank and I write you a check for $100, right?
Remember that, right?
Oh, yeah, of course.
Yeah.
But, you know, the government, if the government wants to fund something, the so-called government,
they send everybody a check for $1,000.
You know, it turns into $9,000, right?
They give you the $1,000.
The government gets $3,000.
The bank gets $3,000, right?
And then the other third goes to the other parties.
Yeah, right.
See how it works?
That's why, you know, checks are good for 180 days.
You know, when the last stimulus check program went out, exactly 180 days later, according
to the Paperwork Reduction Act 2002 or 2003, all those documents go to the DTCC, which
is the Deposit Trust Clearing Corporation in Manhattan, and they become re-monetized
after 180 days, right?
You know, after the last stimulus was sent out, exactly 180 days after the inflation
started going up or the prices started going up because it flooded the market with trillions
and trillions of credit, right?
See how it works?
You don't see that anywhere, though.
Nobody tells you that.
I think I'm the last person on Earth.
Years ago, I ran into someone.
Well, recently, someone called me out of the blue I hadn't spoken to in 15 years, and
he came over here from California and all this, and he found out about me because he
went to a seminar with Austin Fitz, whatever her name is.
Catherine Austin Fitz, yeah.
Catherine Austin Fitz, and he went to talk to her after the seminar.
She had a bunch of questions for her, and she said, if you want those answered properly,
you need to find this guy who lives in Tucson, goes by the Greek.
This is back in the day, right?
Right.
And I feel like I'm still the only one around who could do it.
It's kind of sad because everything I'm telling you is accessible if you read it, if you could
gather it all in one place.
It's kind of like the crucifixion.
It's right in front of you, but you can't make it out, you know?
You know what the Christian stuff is, or the human body, right?
Or anything.
Yeah, so in other words, oh, there's another thing.
If you want spiritual help, you've got to go to church, right?
Go to the temple, right?
Yeah, okay.
You see the culture?
You see how the people have become devoid?
It's supposed to be this way.
Sorry, I can't help but laugh at that, but yeah, sorry.
No, all of it is.
I don't like Christianity.
Now I'm a Buddhist, or I converted to Islam, right?
Or whatever.
Oh, my goodness.
You know, that's like, oh, I don't drink Diet Coke anymore.
I'm going to Diet Pepsi, right?
That's better.
Big difference.
It's all the same.
You know, all the religions are Vatican approved.
If you had a non-Vatican, all of them, if you have more than 100,000 people, it's not
Vatican approved, they're going to do a Waco on your ass, right?
And they're going to set it up that you're a terrorist or whatever.
I'm serious.
They all kiss the ring.
Mormons, Jews, every Jewish sect, every Mormon sect, every Buddhist sect.
Trust me.
Yeah, anyway.
Not trust me, but that's a New Yorker in me.
I know.
Yeah, let me be honest with you.
Trust me, those are New Yorker sayings, right?
Let me be honest.
To tell you.
Or trust me.
Or to tell you the truth.
Yeah, to tell you the truth.
You're breaking my balls.
I love that.
You always got to watch the prefix on the statement, right?
Which is what I call it.
Because it's like, with all due respect, hold on to yourself.
Because that's not going to be good.
Right.
Well, you know, you did couch it a little bit.
You knew something was coming.
Right.
Yeah, with all due respect.
Yeah.
How much respect is due by telling someone to go F off, right?
Amazing.
So you see, we went from the car to the this, to the that, to the doctor, to the money, to all.
Yeah, you need money, go to the bank, right?
So what's happened is the people, if there are any left, have been pulled away from their responsibility to each reality.
So you have like the car is a certain reality, right?
The body, the health is a certain reality.
The banking is a certain reality, right?
These are different sections in reality, right, that affect us.
Because they can be addressed.
Well, see, now, I don't think it's a bad thing that I decided to consult somebody that should be familiar with this,
because I don't drive a car, right?
I am not an operator of a vehicle.
But I do depend on it, because I have a partner who drives a car, right?
So, you know, therefore, I've got to find some way to deal with, okay, now I've got a malfunctioning vehicle.
Well, you didn't call me.
I didn't call you, no.
Yeah, so that means you don't know what I know and what other people know.
No, I don't.
That's another story.
Okay.
I fix, most cars I fix over the phone, by the way.
Really?
Or tell you what's wrong with it over the phone.
Yeah, I got witnesses to that.
By the way, if anybody's listening or subbed that has had me fix their car over the phone, email Chuck and tell him.
Yeah, please do.
Yeah, how many people, I do it all the time.
It's that simple.
I wasn't aware of that.
But, okay.
Mechanics don't look, it's, yeah, they're, anyway, anybody's easy to B-rate, right?
B is rated B, but there are no A mechanics anymore.
They're all B-rated.
So the B, the best B-rated mechanic is now your A mechanic, your C mechanic is your B mechanic.
You see what I mean?
I understand.
Because it's not something that people look for.
Look, in America, if you say you're a waiter, that's kind of looked down.
But in France, in Paris, if you're a waiter, that's like, wow, you know, it's like an accountant or an engineer.
You know that?
Not anymore, because they have Pizza Hut there now.
Yeah, well, of course.
I always found that strange, though, is that, you know, the lack of respect for the people that are actually going to hand you food.
You know, I always found that weird.
Here.
Because I would think to myself, yeah, here, exactly.
Yeah, a lot of the northern, that's part of the white culture, but a lot of the southern European culture was very high.
Well, I would think you would have to have some, you know, look, you know how you respect the shark in the water, right?
Because you know that this thing, its place is in the water.
You're in there now, okay?
And you better have some respect for it, because it can do some harm to you if it wants to.
Now it could just swim by you, okay, or it could hang out.
I've had that.
I've had a sand shark tear up my shin just by rubbing against me very quickly.
They're very fast swimmers.
Okay.
And they're just afraid.
Just like rattlesnakes, when I first came here to Tucson walking in the desert, an old Indian man told me, he says,
Listen, the reason you wear the boots, what you do is you don't walk like you walk on hard ground here.
On the desert, you kick and slide your shoes, so you're always kicking gravel in front of you.
Okay.
And this way you let any creatures in front of you know you're coming, you know.
Because they're just afraid.
If a snake bites, it means it's defending itself.
It's afraid, right?
Why would you defend yourself if you're not under, you don't see that, it doesn't see you as prey.
It sees you as a threat.
Yeah, well, it doesn't want to get stepped on, so, you know.
Or attacked, yeah.
Right.
So, yeah, but anyway, sharks and all that.
Yeah, I don't know if we got our shot, but yeah, the culture is the reality is broken up into many little realities,
and then we interject.
So, let's say you're a chef at a restaurant, someone says, I don't know about how to make this,
and you'll, because your reality, because you work in that, you can take responsibility for what you're saying, right?
Because you're a chef, you can tell that person how to make this or that, usually.
Right.
Right?
You take responsibility for what you're saying.
So, most people are, when the car breaks down or the body's not doing well,
they can't take responsibility even if they wanted to.
Just like I gave the analogy starting off about the radio function, functioning.
They can't take, you throw just anybody in a radio station and tell them we're going to be going live in four minutes,
can they take responsibility for what they're going to do?
No.
They're not, because if they're going to, what are they going to say after it's all done?
Well, I didn't know what I was doing, right?
Because that means, okay, so the thing is how much time do you want to devote in learning about whatever facet, right?
Here, I used to try to, this kind of talk I was doing back in the 80s,
and the way I would crack the conversation or the subject matter is being a public laundromat,
and I'd see someone, usually they stand in front of the laundry and watch the dryer,
and I'd go up to them and I'd say, hey, it's better than watching television, isn't it?
Okay.
Just to get them going on reality here, you know, reality talk.
You know, most of the stuff I've been saying, especially the past ten years or so,
I've already said a long, long time ago, a lot of the stuff that we could get into on Rated Y,
it, for most people, might shy away because it gets a little technical sounding,
but it's never more than eighth grade, right?
Okay.
So, but, yeah, responsibility.
That can be very tough if you've never been exposed to first, second, third, fourth, fifth, you know,
I mean, it's a little difficult to jump right into eighth grade, though, isn't it?
Yeah, yeah, I liked some of the comments in the chat, some was about phase modulation,
like it was almost like a semi-quippy chat.
Did you guys notice that the Greek was talking about phase modulation?
You know, nobody said yes or anything, so I went in there and I thought that the Anon who posted that
has at least, he's got some very moist gray matter, if you know what I mean.
Okay.
Which is good to see.
So, yeah, so, yeah, it's just sad because, you know, here's the thing.
People say I want to do something to recreate, right?
Or watch a movie or play a video game, whatever.
It's like, what are you talking about?
We're going to learn how to fix the car.
That's a hell of a lot more interesting and it'll serve you better.
Or go learn how to cook, right?
Or learn how to do this, or learn how to, right?
Okay.
Isn't that, I think that's, they call that infotainment, don't they?
Where you entertain yourself through information.
Yeah, yeah, that's true.
Keros One started that a while back in the 90s.
Chris.
Smart guy, I thought.
Yeah, my roommate was his producer for a while.
I had a short time with a roommate, but was producing Keros One.
So, anyway, when he was at his peak, like, what was it?
The Sound of the Police and all those, remember that?
Made him really popular.
Yeah, like mid-90s, right?
Something like that.
Early 90s, early 90s.
Oh, early, okay.
Like 91 to 90, or 90 to 93.
Anyway, the chat was interesting.
I think I'm going to open it up right now.
Actually, before we go to it, I'm going to sit back down here.
And I did a search earlier.
One thing I mentioned, I put in, let's say I have a, I use Maxton.
I don't know, sometimes I, what do you use on Maxton?
I've never heard of it.
M-A-X-T-H-O-N.
It's a bunch of, it was started by a bunch of programmers who wanted to beat Chinese censorship,
the government censorship in China.
Okay.
Then it kind of became, it adopted the Chrome format.
I really like it.
I've never gotten an ad.
And if I do a playlist of music on YouTube, it never interrupts it.
Are you still listening?
Click here or whatever.
Never get any of that.
It's got the most aggressive ad blocking and the most aggressive anti-cookie
and the most aggressive.
And you still get through, you know, like certain programs like Zoom or whatever don't work.
Okay.
With that kind of aggressive ad blocking.
Right.
But it does.
So it knows when you're, when it's critical and when it's not.
Anyway.
And at Maxton, I'm on Google search here.
I'm going to put in Middle East.
Did this this morning.
Let's see if I get the same.
Just, and then enter.
And then I'm going to go to the top where it says tools, anytime drop down.
I'm going to go past week.
Okay.
And they changed a lot of the, but this morning it was India.
It's going to get into the Middle East to try to get all the countries organized.
Let's see if I can do past day, 24 hours.
Middle East and Europe times.
Now it's escalating tensions again.
But this morning it was very interesting.
It was, it sounded like it was all Kumbaya, everybody holding hands.
It was almost like the twilight zone.
Right.
Cause you know, I've talked about what's coming.
The Middle East union.
Right.
And the search I did this morning, let's just do the past week again.
Middle East history around Middle East, new round of Middle East fighting.
Oh, within eight hours, new round of Middle East fighting again.
Well, it seems interesting to me because it's constantly fluctuating the past few weeks.
Right.
It seems to me, you know.
Yeah.
Is it becoming, all right, here we go.
Is the Middle East becoming peaceful?
India's planned to connect the Middle East.
Cause you do this every eight, nine, ten hours or so,
and you'll see an entirely different result.
But this one, the majority statistically was off the chain.
Here, like Syria rejoins the Arab League.
Okay.
They're building this huge one billion dollar embassy in Lebanon.
They're doing all this stuff.
It's like all under the radar.
All under the radar, you know, in terms of the mainstream collective.
Collective doesn't know all the development that's going on and how they're becoming.
They're getting stuff that, you know how the infrastructure in the West is falling apart
and all the restrictions and austerity.
Okay, well, it's the opposite there.
Everything's booming there.
Right.
But it's not for the collective.
It's not booming like for the people on the street, but it's booming behind the scenes.
Deals are being made, big multinationals, embassies, trade routes, big infrastructure plans.
I thought I saw a lot of stuff on Dubai like last week, right?
Dubai was a big thing.
Yeah, I wouldn't count them in though.
No, okay.
No, that was like never really inhabited area, and they're just a bunch of camel thieves.
Okay.
All those people.
They're very, I think, okay, just to recap, when you go, let's say you're England or the U.S.
or the Dutch 100 years ago, and you go into an area like the Middle East,
which is all these tribal semi-pneumatic culture people,
and you want to unite them so you can have a body of people that you can rule over,
but you don't want them to do it directly.
You want to install a government that's supposedly their own to do it, and that's a puppet government.
Sure.
All puppet governments, you always have to take a group of people that the people generally hate
and put them in power, and the reason why that works is for this,
because they're going to do whatever the suzerain authority says,
because if the suzerain, the colonial power pulls their power and drops these guys back,
the people are going to just tear them to pieces because they hated them anyway, right?
Okay.
But while they're in power, they're going to be less compassionate
because they remember that they were always hated.
You see what I mean?
Okay.
By their own people, you see?
So whenever you see these puppet governments that are indifferent,
like Saddam Hussein was one, he was a CIA puppet.
I think you know that, right?
Oh, yeah, absolutely.
Yeah, yeah.
And Saddam Hussein, I got this from, by the way, I'll just interject something,
because that's what this is about, right?
Why?
I don't know if you, are you familiar with why they punished him so badly?
Well, publicly, as a lesson, you know, in 2003, and then before that, 1990,
what was it, the Desert Storm, and then the other one?
Because he went rogue.
Are you familiar with the story?
I got this from a retired Army colonel.
Well, I'm familiar with a couple of different versions of that story, but, yeah, go ahead and tell me.
Which one would you think was the one that was told amongst the high brass?
I think that there was certain things that he was supposed to do that he refused to do,
and when that happened, they tricked him into making this move, you know, against. . .
Oh, with Kuwait, the first one?
Yeah, the first one.
They tricked him into making that move, and then it was like, okay, now they took him down for it.
The second one?
Right.
And the second one, which had nothing to do with 9-11, anything serious?
What did you get on that?
What intel do you have on that?
Well, what I got on that is that he still did not make the moves that they wanted him to make,
and I think it was a financial thing.
From my understanding, it was a financial thing where there was a lot of money that was brought into there,
and then it was supposed to go certain places.
It didn't, and that's why, you know, people talked about this loosely about the pallets and cash and all that.
That's what I got, but go ahead.
Okay, this is what the inner Pentagon, the brass people had.
Okay, when we say that he was a Muslim country, right,
do you know there are more Muslims in Asia than there are in the Middle East, right?
I think it's like five to one.
There's almost a billion Muslims, right?
There's not even, what, 300 million people in the Middle East, 400 million, not even?
Right.
Okay, so most of them are Pacific Rim, Malaysia, you know, all those, okay.
But Muslim is Muslim nonetheless, right?
Okay, so bear that in mind.
Okay, this is what I got, and I'm going to say it.
It's rated Y, okay?
I was never told not to repeat this or not, so I can say it, but it's not public at all.
You ready?
Sure.
Okay, all right, so he was kind of sore by 2003 or 2002.
So what his plan was, you know, he had already dealings.
He had plenty of American hardware missiles, long range, medium range,
not long range ballistics, but medium range, you know, missiles, right?
You know, could go a few hundred miles, right?
Yeah.
Not just the Scuds, you know.
That's why they just showed these Scud missiles that were crap.
He had missiles that were up-to-date ordnance, Minutemen type stuff, right?
No, he had great stuff all the way up to the year 2000, let's just say, technologically,
and also had access to, you know, the chemical weapons and all that.
They actually did have that stuff.
Yes, yes.
So this is, let me get it.
Okay, so what he was going to do was when the big holiday,
when everybody walks around Mecca, he was going to take an American missile
that just has not been touched and clean it all up,
put a couple of coats of polyglycol wax on it,
and shoot it right where everybody goes around Mecca, the cube,
and drop more than one over there,
and make sure that the fragments are found that it's an American missile,
and kill a lot of people,
and he would go and say the Americans attacked the holiest site on the holiest day
to create a worldwide jihad against the Americans,
and the Americans would have lost, by the way.
If every Muslim in the world decided to fight against America,
what would you call it?
Well, if just the population of Malaysia decided to turn against the U.S.,
we're outnumbered by a lot.
Yeah, by a lot, right.
So what is an honest-to-goodness jihad is what he wanted to do,
and that would be a billion Muslims versus the Americans and their allies,
and most of the allies would cop out too.
But anyway, so that's what he was planning on doing,
and days before, if you go back and look at what I'm talking about,
there was a lot of stuff talking about telling people not to go to Mecca that year in 2003.
I don't know if you remember that.
I do remember that.
Putting all that together.
Now that you're talking about this, I do recall this story,
but I didn't know how serious to take it that there was going to be.
A false flag.
Yeah, a false flag.
That Saddam was going to blame the Americans,
and he was going to pull it off, by the way,
because he had plenty of people around ready to jump.
You have to do it very fast.
Once it happens right away, you call for a jihad,
not like a month or three months later, you know what I mean?
No, you have to have an immediate reaction.
Look, this is the way it went.
We have enough proof that this was an American weapon
because he had actual bona fide American weapons.
Well, no, he had the goods.
No, but that's what I'm saying.
He had bona fide American weapons.
It would look the same as one of the missiles that we would have fired, yeah.
No, it would have been exactly the same missile that we would have fired.
Because it is exactly the same one.
Right, and it would have looked like it, yeah,
and it would have been very convincing.
All you've got to do is throw a live one in a dud one, right?
Because the dud would guarantee that they'd find you, right?
Well, a dud, you can identify it because you can read everything on it.
Yeah, but anyway, all this was put in place.
This was seen as very dangerous, not because he was going to do that,
but because the Americans can handle a scandal like that,
but not a worldwide jihad.
You see, no country can handle a worldwide jihad.
It doesn't matter who it is.
Well, no, because honestly, if the attack was wholly of sites,
okay, that would outrage the entire Muslim world, not just, you know.
That's what I mean.
Yeah.
People think, most Americans think, when you say Muslim world,
they think those little pity countries in the sand in the Middle East.
They don't know that there's, you know, like you said, billion plus in Asia.
Yeah, no, you're not even close to exaggerating when you're talking about
you could easily raise an army of a billion people without a problem that would just say,
okay, they have attacked, you know, God, basically.
Right, and you wouldn't have to pay them a soldier's salary either.
No.
They would go do it completely on their own.
Every man would finance it his own.
Right.
Because, you know, when you go to the army, I'm not getting paid, you know.
Right?
So, no, it would be very, very serious.
When you do something in a jihad where you're not doing it for the money,
by the way, soldiers do it for the money, it will never stop.
It would still be going on right now.
You see what I mean?
So, whether this is true or not, this is what was circulating amongst the high brass.
So, yeah, interesting.
Just file that away.
I think it was notable, right?
Oh, no, definitely.
Look, realistically, again, because this is what I always said about this, by the way,
is that if there was a real, you know, oh, it's a clash of civilizations and, you know,
this idiocy that, oh, well, all the Muslim world wants to kill, you know, all of us Christians,
and I used to laugh at every single one of them because I said, if that were the case,
if the whole Muslim world...
Yeah, they could have done it five times over already, right?
You would not stand a chance.
This wouldn't even be a hiccup.
It would be done quick.
Right, yeah.
Yeah, because, again, when you tell this to most Americans, they're like,
oh, we're just going to blast and turn the desert into glass.
No, most Americans are not aware that the Muslims are not, the majority is not in the Middle East.
No, you're going to level all of Asia?
Because that's what you'd have to do.
Yeah, and they'll come over in bamboo canoes, man, if it was a jihad, yeah.
So, anyway, yeah, I just thought I'd share that.
I don't think I ever brought this up with you, have I?
No, you have not.
That's why I hadn't heard your story about this before.
Well, it's not my story.
I got it from a colonel, retired colonel.
But the story that you're repeating, I hadn't heard it from you, is what I'm saying.
I've heard stuff like this.
Yeah, when you contemplate what I just said, it actually makes sense.
It would have been very easy for him to do logistically.
He already had the goods, right?
And he already has TV stations, right?
You've got to have a TV satellite link, right?
Well, they had all the attention in the world.
Look, and outside of his country, even if you shut down all the electricity in Iraq,
right outside of his country, there was whole huge satellite-connected networks
that could easily carry the action, even if you knocked out his whole power grid, say.
Okay, you EMP all of Iraq, say.
It doesn't matter, because they could cover that, no problem.
So, no, logistically, you've got a serious problem if that was the undertaking.
Yeah, he had everything.
They went over it.
Allegedly, everything was in place, and all redundancies were in place.
So, if he had a failure in one part, he had it pretty tightly done.
So, anyway, there you go.
I don't think that's the reason I was doing this search.
Well, the very important thing to mention here, though, is that whether it was true or not,
whether it was that he had all of his redundancies ready and he was all set,
it doesn't matter if that's what was believed to be true.
Yeah, I think it could have been partially true, partially fabricated.
Like what I got from American State Department people on 9-11,
the higher people got a story that Osama bin Laden put suitcase nukes,
and that's what really brought the building down.
And that doesn't make any sense.
That means they're ignorant, because the flash, you know,
you would have destroyed half of Manhattan, right?
You would see the flash.
That's what Judy Woodlady said.
It can't be nuclear, because you'd see it blinded by the light.
But she's right about atmospheric, but if you do it underground,
which is the way that 99% of all the nuclear testing has been underground,
then there is no flash at all.
It's just a surface reaction.
But they believed the suitcase nukes in the buildings,
so they're not getting the truth, the higher-ups in the quote-unquote governments.
But, by the way, it's really hard to say.
The government, I think what's left, the post office, not the Postal Service,
and the State Department might be one of the last departments that is government.
Like, you know, Treasury, you have Department of the Treasury
and then Treasury Department, right?
One is the IRS, one is the government.
So Department of the Treasury, that's the private credit,
and Treasury Department is closed.
There's nothing there.
If you go to the building, there's just somebody sitting there in the office
and playing Scrabble, right?
They have nothing, because they've been bankrupt since 1933.
But the Department of Treasury is booming, so because of all the credit, right?
I think we went over that earlier.
So there are no, when you hear agency, that is essentially a subcontractor
that is like an NGO but better than an NGO.
It's like they work so closely with the government that they're considered to be government.
You know what I mean?
Right.
It's kind of like when you're raised by someone since a baby,
you call them your mom or your dad, but they're really not.
You know?
So whenever you hear agency and all that, that's a private group.
Like, you know, the FBI is an example of that.
Before the FBI, there was another, a private,
it was more candid that it was a private agency before them, right?
Who was it?
It was not Wells Fargo.
Pinkerton.
The Pinkerton, yeah, right.
Yeah, and then they obviously were doing all the work for the Federal Reserve people
and the industrialists, you know.
I think the attention, they came to them when they killed all those union people
who wanted union eyes.
They went in and shot them up, right?
Right.
And that's when, yeah, then the FBI, the Jewish,
the FBI was started by the Jewish Mafia, by the way, funded and organized, right?
Just like the Bolshevik, you know, the take of the Soviet Union,
the people that took over, as we know, are not the original revolution.
That's the Red Revolution, which came after the White Revolution.
So they sent the White Revolution in to get rid of the czar and what he had in place.
Then they killed those guys and then brought in the Red Revolution.
You see what I mean?
So anyway, it's a long story.
And that's, again, the Jewish Mafia.
If you look at how it started,
it's a bunch of guys from Brooklyn and Wall Street, right,
that did the White Revolution, then the Red Revolution, FBI, same people.
That's why throughout history, FBI busts what?
The Italian Mafia, right?
How many times did they bust the Jewish mob?
Maybe one.
Bust was Siegel.
They mentioned maybe one or two, maybe.
Well, Siegel wasn't really Jewish Mafia, but when you get to Lansky.
Lansky, right.
So yeah, maybe one.
Right.
They went after one, right?
Okay, so yeah, it's very clear how these things work.
These agencies have all, in other words, they're privately funded.
They're privately hatched.
Justice Department is privately hatched.
Do a history, do a search.
I'm not going to do it now, but put in history of the Department of Justice.
Even Wikipedia says it's a historic anomaly.
We don't know where it came from.
Just Grant one morning decided to sign it in as an agency or whatever.
Amazing, right?
So yeah, we'll go back to the chat.
I thought it was like a potluck of stuff we just went through.
Yeah, definitely.
Past half hour.
Yeah.
Somebody asked why – I'm going to open this up, maybe open the chat.
Somebody asked about death, right, and what happens when you die.
That's something that I've been thinking about.
A few people – you know, I brought up –
I think it was two sonics ago about cooking, dry the meat to make it juicy, right?
Right, right.
I even brought that up because when I hear two or three people
or four people bring up the same subject over a period of time,
I've got to say something about it.
So a couple of people have been bringing up death lately,
and I think I – I don't know if I'm hallucinating, but it was in the chat.
It might have been Ed, Heavenly Father and the God's Hymn.
I'm just going to go through it.
I think it was him again.
Well, death is always a fascinating subject anyway because, look,
it's one of those things where quite frankly everybody's got a point of view on it, right?
It's not one of those things where –
Well, here's the thing – well, no, it is, yeah, but not –
I don't think I've ever gotten into it from the Greek-speak point of view.
No, I don't think so.
Yeah.
Well, here's the thing.
You're fully – you're fully liable to death all the time, right?
Because how many times – there was a TV show a while back called Dead Like Me
or something like that about these people going around and they mark people.
They have a list of people that have to be taken out today, right?
They go to work.
It's like the Grim Reaper kind of thing, but they were ordinary people, let's say, looking.
Something like that.
I thought it was a good premise.
You're always liable to it.
I'm going to say, you never know.
The guy looked fine.
He's crossing the street.
Bam, right?
He didn't see it coming, right?
It was at lunch break, right?
So in the Castaneda – by the way, I've been listening to Castaneda audio books lately
in the background here because I have the whole house wired up with speakers and connected
to a computer.
Push a button and you can hear anything on the property inside or outside the house.
You can hear whatever is playing on the computer, right?
Okay.
In high fidelity.
I've been doing the Castaneda books for like 10 hours and I'm in the background.
I'm doing some stuff here, remodeling the house, but heavy.
When I mean remodeling, like foundation work and stuff like that and other things.
I like listening to Castaneda.
Most of the stuff really hits home.
I'm happy about it, but it actually pisses me off because I've been saying similar stuff
and I didn't read Castaneda.
How the hell can I be saying the same stuff Don Juan is saying or similar?
It means we're tapping into the same thing, right?
If you get into something that's true, it doesn't matter what language you say it in,
or what part of the world or who says it or when.
It's true whether they say it or not, right?
Right.
It doesn't matter who says it or how they say it.
I like what he says that you consult death.
Don't be afraid of it.
Consult.
This is my time now.
If you're still alive after you ask the question, well, it's not your time yet, right?
No.
But it's very simple.
You go through it as an organic being, as a baby, all the way through your life as an adult.
They always have old sayings.
When you're a baby, you're crawling on the ground.
On your last days as an old person, you're probably what?
Going to be crawling on the ground.
As a baby, you're pooping and pissing on yourself.
As an old person, I don't have to say it again, guess what happens?
The full circle, yeah, of course.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
Let me ask you this.
Before you were born, let's just know airy-fairy shit.
What do you remember before you were born?
As a matter of fact, you don't really have a lot of memories until you're in your mid-formative years, right?
What do you remember?
Nothing.
Okay, same thing happens with consciousness after you die, okay?
The only thing is, were you able to be manipulated before you were born?
Well, yeah, you can say that.
Like, for example,
I would say I don't know because I don't recall it.
I can't recall it.
Well, from the organic point of view, certainly, like if your mom was an alcoholic while she was pregnant with you,
they have this syndrome, right?
What is it called?
Oh, this fetal alcohol syndrome is the one.
Yeah, there you go.
Mm-hmm.
If you survive, let's say.
Right.
And all that.
So you can affect before you're born biologically very, very much.
A lot of eugenics programs are based on that.
I've never shared this.
This is really private.
I might as well share and rate it why.
Greek was born in a place called Adelphi Hospital, which was 120 beds in Brooklyn,
and it was part of the American Eugenics Society, which also started in Brooklyn.
And I heard that the parents were, let's just say, compensated for me.
In other words, while the mom was pregnant and had me, she was getting compensation.
So what the hell were they doing?
The American Eugenics Society, right?
And every year there's less information about it.
Now Adelphi Hospital has turned into a condo a while back.
But years ago there would be a lot of information
how the Adelphi Hospital was part of the American Eugenics Society.
What they were doing is they were doing, I don't know about genetic manipulation,
but that's been around since the 1930s, big time, and cloning.
But they were trying to breed, hire, whatever.
You can fill in the rest.
So I've never shared this publicly, have I?
Not that I recall.
I think I have.
Oh, and while I'm saying this, the Skype is ringing as if we're not on the call.
Well, we still are.
I guess you can hear me still.
I hear you just fine.
So, all right, where we are on the death map is what you remember from 500 years ago
is what you're going to remember 500 years from now
within the tuning that your consciousness is in right now.
And Chuck, you're still there, I'm guessing, right?
Yeah, I'm still here.
Yeah, while I was getting into the Adelphi Hospital,
if you heard all that, the Skype was ringing as if another call was coming in.
No, I didn't hear anything.
I was just hearing you.
Yeah.
Yeah, interesting.
I like that.
Okay.
Okay, so I don't think I ever went semi-public with that, but at least I might bring it up.
There you go.
That is fascinating.
It's an interesting history, yeah.
Yeah, so the other thing here is, back to death, is when you go into your memory,
by the way, the better your constitution is here,
for example, I don't want to say I implore,
but if I can get people to stop eating what they're eating,
and I'm not a freak, a macrobiotic freak or whatever, anything like that,
but go get yourself some Lundberg brown rice, learn how to cook it,
L-U-N-D-B-E-R-G or U-R-G.
It's an organic, very, very high-quality brown rice,
and get yourself some kale and some beans that you cook not from a can
and eat that for a week, but cook it well.
If you don't cook it well, you'd wish you died, right?
You know what I mean?
Yeah, I think I've gone through that before,
the survivalist packing rice and beans,
and I said, you're going to wish you died if that's what you have to eat
if you don't know how to cook it, right?
True enough.
But if you could eat, and I think I've talked about this before,
when the macrobiotic people came into San Francisco,
and this is not a tangent, by the way,
and they were doing seminars in the 60s and 70s.
Most people from the public came in,
but after like the fourth or fifth week of seminars,
only the hippies were coming in,
and they stopped and they said,
okay, we notice you guys keep coming back,
but no one else is.
Why do you keep coming to our seminars?
And they said, well, because we're doing what you're saying.
We're eating the brown rice and drinking the tea and that,
and we don't have to do drugs anymore, but we feel high all the time.
Right?
It was a lot cheaper than drugs, right?
Sure.
So that's what I'm trying to say,
is when you eat a really whole diet and very clean,
this is a very easy way to prescribe.
You don't have to do what I'm saying,
but you can get it easily.
Lundberg is the only rice that does it.
When you eat, I don't know if you've ever gone to a bakery
where they bake fresh bread.
Okay, well, of course, but listen.
This bakery, the owner of the bakery,
he also has 10 acres of land 10 miles south
where he grows his own wheat and harvests his own wheat
and dries his own wheat, organic.
He doesn't spray it.
And he stone mills it into his own flour,
and then he bakes it and sells you the bread.
Have you ever gone to a place like that?
I don't think I have.
Okay.
We have one here in town in Tucson, the Barrio Bakery.
Now, when you get a roll and you put that in your mouth
and you chew it and swallow it,
you feel like this feeling of love or euphoria.
Do you remember when you first fell infatuated with someone really young?
Sure.
You know that feeling?
It's like giving somebody a hug.
You get this rising feeling through your body.
Oh, yeah.
And it feels like you just got some good news.
Right?
Oh, yeah.
That's what happens when you drink spring water.
Right.
Okay.
So when you eat some of this guy's bread,
it's like, so in other words, if you can get your diet adjusted to,
you start eating food that when you eat it,
it brings you this feeling, this emotional,
wow, I feel the energy in it.
And I'm not talking from an airy, fairy side.
It's tangible.
Just like when you feel infatuated with someone
and you see them, you get that tangible rise,
that warm rise in your body.
Okay, how many people get that when they eat food?
Very few.
As a matter of fact, if you're American, probably never.
Yeah, right.
But if you do the Lundberg rice, the organic short grain,
do the short grain because it's wetter,
and steam some veg, however, organic food,
do that for a week and you'll see what I'm talking about.
If you've ever done any kind of drugs that make you feel good,
that's how you're going to feel.
But you'll have all the energy
and all the cognitive ability and focus, right,
where drugs take away.
I think we've gone into, you know, around musicians,
everybody got high.
We did a recording session.
That was the best session we ever did.
The next day we listened to it, guess what?
It sounded like crap.
Nothing good, yeah.
So what the hell was going on?
You thought it was the best while you were high.
You see, but here, when you get high off of the food
and the water that you drink,
your cognitive ability and your perception,
your awareness and all that,
will be truly in this reality.
You'll be taking responsibility in this reality
and be very focused and alert,
and it will be better.
Okay.
If you can operate in that range
and think about the time before you came to this world,
you will not get any kind of a clear thought,
but you will feel like you've been here before,
not here this earth,
but something is going on that you're not privy to
in a secure way, not an insecure way.
You see, there's two ways to approach an unknown.
One is from fear and insecurity,
and the other one is from a security and comfortable way, right?
The same thing, right?
So if you can get yourself your physical system
or your physical station, your body,
and a high thing,
and there's other ways to do it, by the way.
If you live near a fishing village
and you just ate small fish,
fish that was less than a foot long,
just soak it after the fish has been cleaned,
soak it in salt water for a few hours
and eat that with some veg,
you know, some local food.
Just do some local high energy food for a week
and you will start to see you've been here,
something's going on that you're not made privy to, right?
That's where these questions are,
what happens after death or what happens after life, okay?
That's all I can say about death
is the consciousness that you have in this 3D reality
will cease to exist,
but that doesn't mean your consciousness ceases to exist.
That bumps right away into the subject of reincarnation.
When people ask me,
is there reincarnation in Greek,
right away I say no.
Why?
Because if I say yes,
they're going to think that I'm giving them approval
for all the BS that they've heard about reincarnation before,
and if I hear them talking about reincarnation,
I'm like, where'd you get that?
That's bullshit.
They'll say, well, Greek, you said you believe in reincarnation.
You see?
Right.
Right?
So what I have to do
is when I hear these things that I assess
that where they're getting their information from
is not a good thing to, what do you call it,
give approval to,
I just say no.
Like, are we in a simulation?
No, we're not.
Of course we are.
But I say no.
Right?
Because they're going to, you see?
Because if they say yes,
they're going to attach it to all the,
you know, was 9-11 an inside job?
No.
And here's the thing,
when somebody asks...
If I say yes, they're going to listen to...
Right, right.
No, I get it.
But, you know, when somebody asks about death, though,
they're generally not thinking backwards
to what was before this time
when they are in this conscious state.
They're not thinking about that.
It's the same.
We just started off by saying the circle.
You said the circle.
When you crawl,
you're peeing and pooping and crawling.
Guess what happened in the beginning?
Guess what happens in the end?
So, okay.
You're crawling, peeing, and pooping.
Yeah, no, I just want to make it clear
that what you're saying is
that it is the same as it was before
as it will be after
is what you're getting to.
Yeah, there's no consciousness
within this 3D realm.
Let's call it density.
Okay.
And this is where it gets complicated
with reincarnation.
The reason I say no with reincarnation
is very simple.
It's because the people...
How many times do you hear these idiots
on the internet or whatever write books?
You know, I was Einstein.
This is a current person.
I used to be Einstein.
And before that, I was whatever.
And before that, this linear...
And I was Joan of Arc.
Yeah, and it's linear.
They're going back.
I said, bullshit.
That's not how it works.
Time is not linear.
The people...
By the way, no one's talking about this,
so I'm going to say it.
If you hear this, it's the real deal,
not because I'm saying it.
If you die now,
you can possibly be reincarnated
in ancient Rome.
Well, I agree.
That doesn't make any sense
because ancient Rome already happened.
No, no.
See, now, here's another thing
that's incorrect, too.
I'll tell you that if you don't hear it,
it's also wrong.
You could already be here now.
In other words,
it is possible that you could encounter
your reincarnated self tomorrow.
Yeah, that's possible.
Yeah, exactly.
That's if the loops cross
just like the infinity symbol.
You know how it crosses.
That's what makes it the number eight.
But that's more...
If you want to get into that, we can,
but that's skipping a lot.
Okay, I'm not trying to just skip around.
I'm just saying that
that is another thing, though,
to consider here.
Yeah, they call them doppelgangers.
In other words, it could be...
That gets into the genotypes.
There's only about 30 or 40 genotypes.
You know how the genotype
is also reflected spiritually?
You know what Snoop Dogg looks like, right?
Yeah, sure.
Okay, I know a white guy
looks exactly like Snoop Dogg,
but he's got white person hair and all that,
but he's exactly the same demeanor,
speaks the same way,
looks the same way.
What are you talking about?
One guy's black, one's...
No, no, no.
It's the same genotype set in there.
Right.
Cartoonists know genotypes, right?
Of course.
When a cartoonist draws a fat lady...
Right, they have a style.
It's a style in which it's like
this is sort of the way it is presented
in their particulars.
It's a template, right.
There's only a handful of templates of humans,
and it looks like everybody's different.
We are like snowflakes,
and hopefully not.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, you're right.
In the term that's being used,
but yeah, everybody's a little different,
but you're still part of the template.
Even if you made muffins
or bread out of a template,
no two are still baked alike.
I've been saying that...
No, they're not exact, but...
Exactly, but very similar templates.
Yes, right.
Exactly.
That's what I was trying to get at.
And the other thing is
when people look at these pictures
and they go,
look, okay,
I'll give you a for instance
that people have publicly looked at,
and they take it the wrong way.
Here's Brad Pitt, right?
Okay, so we know what Brad Pitt looks like.
Fine.
Yeah, there's one in the 1800s.
It looks just like him, right?
Exactly.
That's what I was going for.
So you look at that,
and people go,
oh, does this mean that this is the real...
Well...
No, it's a template.
It's a template.
It's a template, right.
There's only just so many...
I call it genotype.
Okay.
So let's get back to the basics on this,
on the time...
Forget about the...
You know, we got screwed up with timelines,
the number line.
Remember in elementary grade school?
Oh, yeah.
We had zero here,
and they went backwards and forwards, right?
Right.
Why?
They screwed us up.
Periodic table is also screwed up,
with all these boxes and stuff like that.
Right, right.
Get the elements out of the boxes, right?
Right.
Anyway, okay,
so what's going on is this.
I said,
we're in this particular density.
By the way,
this is important.
You know how they say space is a vacuum,
and the Earth has an atmosphere?
It's total bullshit,
because if you put a vacuum against an atmosphere,
what's the vacuum going to do?
Pull the atmosphere off the planet, isn't it?
Yeah, the Earth,
the atmosphere is actually in a vacuum,
and the space is the opposite of a vacuum.
It's a very high pressure, ethereally.
Well, we could go back to the car tire thing.
Look,
if you have...
The only reason why
the air is not rushing out of the car tire
is because of the barrier.
So...
Structure, yeah.
The structure itself holds it together.
Yeah,
and when you have two different pressures,
you need a barrier.
So the barrier is ethereal,
but it works on a fourth plane.
You know,
when you look at it,
going back to what they showed us in school,
they screwed us up with a number line,
not timeline,
they do number lines.
Number line, right.
They get on the chalk,
we had a blackboard,
and she made a line and a zero.
Well, here's zero in the middle,
and then when you go this way,
it becomes minus one,
minus two,
and you go that way.
Yeah, why?
It doesn't work that way.
Why, you know, so...
Okay, so...
You have the X, Y, Z axis, right?
So the X is the horizontal,
the Y is the vertical,
and the Z goes through the page.
Right.
All right, so that means, you know,
they're trying to end measurement, right?
So X, Y, what comes after Z?
You have to start all over with A.
And I'm recapping a discussion I had
with someone recently.
That's why I spell ether with an A.
A-E-T-H-E-R,
not just the E-T.
It's the old way of spelling it.
Okay.
That's why I spell ether with an A,
because it comes after Z.
A comes after Z.
Okay.
The A, the ether dimension,
is around each one of the X, Y, Z,
like a bubble,
and those, when you draw something,
there's a bubble around each axis,
and there's a bubble around that,
and a bubble around that,
and that's how you form your vacuums.
Okay, so each bubble is increasing in density
as it gets thinner ethereally,
but decreasing in density materially
as it gets thinner.
You see?
Obviously.
If you said,
hey, why did you thin out that paint so much?
Right?
It's weaker.
It's weak, right?
If I say I thinned out the paint,
it looks like nothing, right?
If it's too thick,
it's much heavier materially.
So it's the opposite.
When you have a heavy ether,
it's a very thin material,
heavy material,
very thin ether.
That's why the crystals get very dense.
They act the way they do.
Okay, so once you get a hang
of these different densities
and how these things interplay,
when you hit a tuning fork,
it's in time.
Once the impact is made,
it's at its highest amplitude,
and as time goes down,
it gets quieter and quieter, right?
Right.
But if you put that tuning fork aside,
even a day later,
I'm telling you,
it's still oscillating.
You can't hear it,
but there are instruments,
if you don't touch it,
that still show you
that it's still being affected
from when you hit it a day ago, right?
Okay.
Okay, so we're in this density right now,
this progressive that we see
or are taught to see linear,
and the Roman times,
2,000 years ago, let's say,
already happened.
It was still on the earth,
but I'm not talking about
if you go look at the Colosseum,
how it's in ruins and all that.
By the way,
if all these things are so important,
why are they left in ruins, right?
But anyway,
if you go back to that time now,
it's going to be a faded memory
that still exists
and is still resonating,
but it's so fine,
there is no material counterpart.
That's what you get reincarnated in,
but when you're in it,
as of that material,
that ultra-fine material,
you don't see that you're in a fine material.
It's just a regular normal world
like it is here,
but you don't see the difference in density
because that's all you know.
Well, if you're in tune with it,
wouldn't it mean that you're...
Everything's normal.
...experiencing it in time.
In other words,
since you're...
I guess I had the right word to begin with.
If you're in tune with it,
then it does appear quite normal
because that's where you're at.
If you're resonating...
because everything is the same.
Okay.
Everything's in the same frequency
or in the same realm
or the same density,
so you don't know any different.
You're not a fish out of water.
You know what I mean?
Well, no.
There's no contrast.
You're not taking your different density
and introducing it into that.
You're introducing it...
You're introduced into it in that same...
Yeah.
The problem is...
The problem is now...
Once you understand...
This goes into time manipulation.
If you ask people,
what do you want?
We want a time machine.
When do you want it?
Irrelevant, right?
So it doesn't matter
when a time machine is invented, does it?
That means that if a time machine
is invented a million years in the future,
can they affect us?
Probability says yes.
Yeah.
So we're all being manipulated.
Now, a time machine has to take in accordance
this very fine resonance of things that passed
that are still resonating,
and if you're going to send, let's say,
you and I in the time machine
to go back into ancient Rome,
we can't go as a solid form.
Our consciousness has to be put into
a very fine resonant body
that resonates with that past residue.
Right.
We would have to be...
In order to even see it,
in order to experience it...
...we would have to be in...
In the ether.
It would be in ethereal...
Ethereal, right.
...in ethereal Rome compared to this one,
but when you're there,
it's just as solid as it is here.
It might even be more solid
from an ethereal point of view
because the ethereal would be more density,
more dense,
just like if you go into the past,
they dig up these cities
and they're three-, four-story buildings, right?
And they're using two-by-fours
as joists and rafters.
You know, if you look at a joist and rafter
in a two- or three-story building,
they're like two-by-eights, two-by-twelves,
you know, pretty big timber, you know,
to put a floor.
Okay.
How the hell were they using two-by-,
you know, very skinny pieces of wood
to make a floor?
Because the gravity was different.
Mm-hmm.
You didn't need...
If you ever look at how fine
these Egyptian Second and Third Dynasty
chairs and chariots...
You see the chariots,
how fine they were built?
You get an eight-year-old
to jump up and down on a chariot
from ancient Egypt,
it'll break it.
And people would say
that that's because of time
and this and, you know,
it wears out over time,
but that's not...
It was made so finely made
because things were very different back then,
so we have that to contend with.
Well, that's why you never notice
there's never a roof
on any of these structures they ever find.
They never find the roof, right?
Because I think the roof is made so light
that it's, you know, it's scattered about
and they don't need...
they can't find it.
You know what I mean?
Mm-hmm.
Roof was very important
even if you read in the New Testament.
When you...
Back in the day,
buildings were put close together for safety
from attack,
from animals,
from whatever,
and it was easier to build.
If you wanted private time,
you went up on the roof
in ancient times.
This was normal.
Just like in ancient times,
if you went to a library,
you read out loud in a booth.
It wasn't like now,
shh, be quiet.
They expected you.
In ancient times,
you went to a library
and took your reading material
and sat in a booth
and you weren't reading out loud
to say something wrong.
Mm-hmm.
Right?
So things were very, very different.
In ancient times,
you wanted privacy,
you wanted...
So all roofs were decks
unless they were thatched
and, you know,
gimballed,
gabled,
which means pitched.
Right.
Okay.
So now,
can you be reincarnated
into the future?
Certainly.
Just like the past,
but it's a phase shift.
Something that has happened
that is in a very fine density
that is different
than something
that hasn't happened yet
that is also in a fine density,
but it's a phase shift.
Once you understand
frequency modulation,
pulse width modulation,
all this other stuff,
how you increase power
and increase,
how would you say,
manifestations
by turning things on and off
or off or on,
this is the technology
that you put into a time machine.
Now, is it possible
that someone
that was living in ancient Rome
that was supposed to
come to this world
a hundred years from now
is incarnated now
and is really out of whack?
I suppose, yeah.
Yeah.
So anyway,
I wanted to give this perspective
of nonlinear time
because all you hear
about reincarnation
is in linear, right?
Linear.
It's always linear.
I was this.
I was that.
And here's the problem.
You could be again
or you could be
going backward, forward.
That's irrelevant
as to whether
it's backward or forward.
It's just a different phase.
Yeah.
If you have
a good enough container body,
like I gave the suggestions
on what to do,
and let's say,
just give us,
this is a scenario for a film
or a TV show
or whatever
to entertain people.
You have a very clear,
confident thing
that something is wrong.
Like you're here.
There's more to them
just being here.
By the way,
that sounds very cliché.
There's got to be more
to this life, right?
But you have enough intuition
which you can't speak in words,
use words to describe things
that are not known,
but you get a glimpse of them.
Imagine then going
and searching an archaeological site
in ancient Rome
and where a garbage dump
is the best.
A landfill, by the way.
That's where you find
the most interesting stuff.
That's how you find out
how a culture lives,
by the way.
If you want to know,
if you go to a landfill
right now
and kept digging down,
on the surface
you would see
the most recent stuff
and go deep enough
and stay long enough
you'll see stuff
from the 1950s, right?
And it'll be very different, right?
Sure, of course.
If you examined all of it
you'd get a very good cultural
slice of what was going on
and how things changed.
So you go back,
you do an archaeological dig
and then you go,
just like the oil wells,
you know how they drill them out
and they're empty
and they come back 30 years later
and they're full again?
Right?
Because of the rock oil?
Anyway.
So you go back to an
revisit an archaeological site
and see if you have written
a letter to yourself
from ancient Rome
that wasn't there
before you knew
about what I just said.
You see the possibilities?
Right.
Because if you,
let's say you live another
5 or 10 or 20 or 30 years,
which most of us are not,
believe it or not,
and you're reincarnated
in ancient Rome,
right?
You could find that letter
at any time,
but it may not show up
within the consciousness
that you have right now
because you're not looking for it.
How many times have people
not seen something
because they're not looking for it?
All the time.
Unless you're specific,
that goes again
back to the reality responsibility.
Are you responsible for the reality
that you're aware of?
Well, look,
if at some point
I went back in time
and placed a letter to myself,
as you said,
and buried it in a box,
you know,
two yards from where I'm sitting
right now outside,
right?
And I did that intentionally.
If I'm not looking for it,
I don't know it's there.
It could be there
and it could be there
a hundred years from now, too.
Yeah, that's right,
because it would probably be in code
and you wouldn't have
the same intent,
which is another thing,
another quick thing
I want to bring up.
Let's get off this subject.
At least we gave an injection
on the subject.
There's a lot more to talk about.
And I think someone brought up
Ibrahim Karim's stuff on bio.
Are you familiar, Chuck,
with the biogeometry symbols?
You know,
they do work, by the way,
most of them.
Are you familiar with them?
I know very little about this.
Okay, that's fine.
You're aware that they exist?
Yes.
Okay.
I had a conversation,
a very short conversation.
I sent him a Skype request
about ten years ago
and he answered it
and I called him.
And I said,
yeah,
and I brought someone else on
as well.
And he does,
I was interested in the health symbols
he did,
and if you're familiar
with the way he does symbols,
he looks at the function
of whatever he wants
to make a symbol for
and then through his intent
does an abstract of the function
through the symbol
and how it's drawn
and all that's very important.
The pen should never be lifted
off the page,
yada yada, right?
That kind of thing, right?
By the way,
you know,
when you're doing,
if you're going to draw a sigil
or do any kind of incantation,
you don't lift the pen
off the page.
Anyway,
that's another thing.
That's why if you ever see
like a real grimoire,
it's one straight,
the whole page is written
with one line.
There's no lifting the pen.
I don't know
if you've ever heard of that.
Right,
no,
you can tell.
It looks very odd.
It's all connected.
that's why a lot of symbols
are that way
so you could lift the pen.
In other words,
the entire thought
has to be complete.
Cursive writing,
curses,
get it,
cursive,
curses,
you know how you don't lift
the pen off of each letter?
Anyway,
I gave him evidence
that the heart
is not a pump at all.
That's why when people,
it's a breaking mechanism, right?
What moves the blood
is the vacuum
in the capillaries.
When the energy
in the body
converts the nutrition
into energy
and then into gas
and then into liquid
and solid, right?
Because in order to
replenish cells in the body,
you need gas,
liquid,
and solid, right?
Liquid and solid
are what most people
think about.
Well, there you go.
And then you need valves
to stop and start
the flow of these things.
The valves are there
to regulate, yeah.
And the heart,
what it does is
when all the,
everything rushes,
the heart is like a dam,
like the Hoover Dam.
Anyway,
he was not aware of this.
He thought it was a pump.
So he made his symbol
like a pump.
And he says
he might change it.
And he hasn't
as far as I looked
a few years ago.
So now I don't know
how that's,
if it's helping
or messing people up
because if you put an intent,
an ethereal intent
that the heart is a pump,
you're going to have
heart problems, you know,
because it's not intended
to be a pump.
It doesn't work like a pump.
No one's ever proven
that it's a pump.
Don't listen to
the medical community.
Don't listen to anyone
that says that
they got an education
more than the 8th grade
that's valid.
So.
Anyway,
what I wanted to just
generally say about
the symbols
and the intent
and all that,
we did a talk
on the corporate logos
and what they're doing
with the corporate logos,
right?
The,
what
Abraham Cream
is doing
is very similar.
So the intent
that we went over
on the corporate logos
and all that
is the same
with the bio signatures
that he calls them.
I just wanted to mention
that as well.
We did a lot,
we did a lot of talks
here tonight.
What do you think?
Yeah, I think,
I think we covered a lot.
Went around
time and,
you know.
Oh yeah,
yes,
it was a grab bag
potluck.
Potpourri,
if you will.
yeah, yeah.
Perfect.
So,
yeah,
okay.
So I think we're good.
There you go.