Rated Y sonic event 91. And here we are once again, Greek, how you doing tonight?
Doing okay. I just want to address a lot of talk in the chat about the new moon. And I think it's
the 13th moon this year. Just by the way it appeared, I would like to have it measure out as
being the first month. But didn't look like a big enough moon to be the first month. So we'll see.
I'll just put that out. What it'll do is it'll shift a lot of the observational days way later
more than in previous years. But that's what a 13th moon can do.
But there's a fast acceleration. If you look at 2024 full moon calendar, and you know,
it's procrastinates, procrastinates, what prognosticates for knowledge of what's coming,
you'll see that we this week, I mean, this week, this week's accelerate, meaning the
moon starts to happen in the middle of the month almost, so it really tightens up really fast.
So instead of it, the full moon kind of corresponding with the end of the month on
the Pope's work schedule starts happening more towards the middle of the month,
almost as if you lose two weeks, it speeds up. It's really interesting to watch.
And that happens after, let's say, the fall, you'll start seeing it accelerate towards a 12
month year. So it's too soon. Well, I wouldn't call it till the next moon, but I'd call it enough
that it's the 13th moon, I would suggest. So I just want to bring that up because it seems to
be a big deal. And one of the Greek speak things lawful timekeeping. And it's not because of any
religious practice. It's just because nothing really works on the Pope's work schedule. Right.
Well, you got to find a way that does. Right. Well, also, you know, what do you talk about
all the time? Why not ground yourself or make give access to yourself the things that are
of the best quality? What is the best quality? Well, to do something that can be reckoned
objectively, you know, because arbitrarily, you know, who's to say that it's actually 1 a.m.,
12 p.m., you know, according to these these markers that they give us on what you used to
say was the plastic windup toy, right? You know, the windup toy or the. Yeah, but they're also
divided. You know, if you study the Greek, well, they call it Julian calendar date. That's what
it still is, really. Yeah. I'll tell you, the day starts at noon and the full moon is is the month
monthly timekeeper in their in astronomical time or astronomy. One on one. So this is have
they spend a little bit of time on timekeeping, just, you know, very little. But they do. They
do it. Yeah. So it's split. Right. Just like you have legal and lawful. Yeah. Yeah. OK. Yeah. Split.
You know what you give the people. You know what the old dictionary is. When you looked up the
word oats, it said what we feed horses in England. But it's the staple of the people in Scotland.
It's kind of like a little dig where you put down or whatever. Yeah. So, yeah, that that's an
interesting dig in the put down. I got a message which is interesting about people. If you just
remove a little bit, they really become space heaters and like pretty much. Yeah. And that
leads me to the without no pun here, the concept of leadership versus management. Right. Oh, yeah.
Because what what happens is it's not the same thing. A manager is there to make sure that
everything's done by the book. There's no inventiveness, really. There's quality control
to a degree. And it's not voluntary where a leader doesn't have a playbook and usually is voluntary.
And half the time a leader is the one going into new territory. Right. So but, you know,
if you go into enough new stuff, you'll find out, you know, it's preexisting anyway. Just
it's called rediscovery. So what happens in this human society is it's being managed by managers
and the people falling for it. They don't know what real leadership is. Right. To to put forward,
you know, OK, look at trends. Trends would be the easiest thing, you know, music, fashion,
whatever, food, diets. That is more of a management scenario, not a leadership scenario.
The same with politics. Those are management scenarios. The political parties are management
scenarios, not leadership. Right. Well, again, it depends on where you come into it, because like
with music, when you come into it and you're hearing what's already being released, approved
monetized, et cetera, it's already passed a whole bunch of points where it's different.
In other words, OK, no, not that not not the actual grind of how it's put out.
Well, what I'm speaking of more is the the metaphor that I used to give years ago was education. If you
had a real education system that taught real stuff, no one would go and no one would understand what
the hell was being said. Right. Because they've it's a it's so radically different than what
they've been used to. Just like, for example, if you look at the education system, you know,
you can look at the history of the current public school, even private school. They follow very much
the same thing. It came out of certain places in history where the industrialists said, you know,
we don't want creativity. We want productivity. Right. So that's all about management. And clearly,
the system. OK, the system of industry is failing because of the new techno feudalism to coin,
to paraphrase a term by Yanis Varoufakis, it's this techno feudalism. Right. That is going in.
And it's what it's doing is it's swallowing its embrace and not embracing. But, yes,
it's encompassing all of industry, but it's putting it into a new system,
which is a feudal system. Right. Right. Where the technology now is the new manager versus
the industry. Still no leadership. There's no leadership. Well, isn't that because technology
allows you to streamline the all of the aspects of managing people, basically? I mean,
you know, technology, you know what? Let's get real. Let's get specific on this, because what
I'm saying is it carries a lot of specific points to it to make it more clear, not just to underscore
it, because if you say techno feudalism, just about anyone who hears that will agree. But the
underscoring of that is this. What makes it different is let's just start off with the
industrial part of the industrial thing people think is factories and whatever. No, it's not
part of the industrial thing is that they've convinced people that you must have money to
get anything you want or whatever you want versus directly getting it right. So now when
scarcities and shortages are created with the monies, you end up with a scarcity and shortage
with everything else, even though there is no scarcity or shortage with anything else. Right.
So that's the pitfall of industry. Most people when you say industrialism, they think
factories and production. Yes, it is. But the crux of this, this has not been said by anyone
before, by the way, is that everyone has been convinced that they need this fiat currency
credit to get things right. Hence, hence the utilities, you know, you pay for utilities
when they're already paid for. Right. So okay, so that's the crux of another crux of techno feudalism
is this. They have a sensor when I mean sensor, meaning with an S, like a sensor that detects
things, something that you write. Yeah. Whether it's artificial intelligence, it speaks to you
like a Siri or whatever, or a query that you type in questions or monitoring data of your searches.
What it does is it sees what you're interested in, which is limited because you're not a product
of leadership. You're a product of management. So it's very easy to put you could be
to determine who you are, what category. Right. And it gathers that data and then it gives
suggestions to you backward back. And then it sees which suggestions you grab.
And then it starts to do algorithms that make its suggestions more efficient, because
if it gives you 10 out of things, 10 suggestions and you go for them, it's pretty efficient. But
if it gives you 10 suggestions and you go for one, it says, oh, we only have 10 percent efficiency.
Let's start looking at him a little closer so we can get our efficiency higher. So this algorithm
now is getting more and more efficient about making suggestions to you and you start using
its suggestions. This is what advertisers wanted to do. And now it watches what you do and it gets
more input from you. So basically, like Yanis Varoufakis says, you train the the the algorithm
and then the algorithm trains you and then you go back and train the algorithm some more.
Then the algorithm comes back and trains you some more. Right. Because it's slowly leaning
you to certain directions that you don't realize very subtly. Right. Of course. Right. So this is
what I mean by techno feudalism. In other words, you are now in a fiefdom where you have no free
thinking, but it's not upfront. It has come through your the premise. Well, like I said,
you're a managed being. You're not you're not a being that works through leadership
because you're managed. The playbook is there. And remember, there's no innovation in management.
Right. So it already knows that about you. You don't know that about you, that you're
pretty much conventional. You know, that's why I say people in the collective, the normies,
they're so convinced they're so predictable, right. Very predictable and undiscerning,
even though that's never you never say that to them. Right. What you do is you tell them they're
all great. They're all individual. They'll have talent. Bullshit. None of them. Very few do. Right.
So so that that's part of the captive system of an industry, not techno feudalism. Techno feudalism
is very different. It's on a very personal level. Right. But it's impersonal because there's a finite
number of things that can offer to you. But that's OK, because you don't know any better. Right.
So when you go to when you go to Amazon or eBay or whatever, Twitter, Facebook or whatever,
I see those things as really limited, like, oh, my gosh, this is what people are doing. But the
people that are part of that system, the majority, they see it as an unlimited amount of options.
Right. So just because there's a billion websites or whatever doesn't mean that it's not like
limited. You know, it's just a lot of quantity. The quality that I'm looking for is just isn't
there. Very rare. The people don't know that. So they're caught still in a managerial system.
And and I'm not trying to say that techno feudalism is leading them at all. No,
it's implementing a mind capture. Right. Because remember, they're already locked
in the industrial system where they don't know that there's no scarcity of anything,
but they do feel the scarcity because when they see their bank account change. Right.
Because they're only in the training and the knowledge that if they want anything,
whether it's a vacation, food, electric power, clothing, whatever they need to get credit,
paper or cards, digital transfer to get it, they don't know that that is absolutely not necessary.
Right. Well, because the interaction, the interaction in and of itself is not just a
matter of control, but it's also a matter of refining that control. So every interaction
gives another piece of data, another piece of information with the techno feudalism.
But the techno feudalism wraps up all the pitfalls and limitations that have been put on people that
they don't see as limitations by from industry, the industrial age and their various industrial
age. And by the way, the information age is one of the shortest ages ever because you're not in
the information age anymore. I think that died in around 2013. What what people that especially
the alternative communities or whatever, the heyday of the Internet ended around 2013. Right.
2012 around there. Right. That's when the censorship started. Yeah. So that's when the
information age ended. You're not in the information age anymore. You're more than
10 years into techno feudalism. Yeah. Speaking of which. Yeah. So this is pretty this is a big drop.
I haven't I've never brought this topic up before. And I'll get more into the development of how I'm
observing it. I like Yanis Varoufakis stuff, but he's a left winger. You know, he's political.
He doesn't know. He doesn't. He's anti banker the way they're doing. So he never talks about
the crux of the banking system. You know what it really is. He can't because he's an ex-politician.
He's easy to reach, by the way. He seems to be a pretty OK guy. So he's he was the former finance
minister of Greece. So let me just say one more thing. How does this affect where we're going in
future? It doesn't because what we're what we're going to be going into in the future is a revival
of some very ancient things that no one that everyone has forgotten about. Right. But this
is just a tag along. This is what your day to day is now. Technical techno feudalism. So, yeah,
just keep in mind that it has not replaced industrialism, which the crux of industrialism
in modern socialism is that you need money to get anything that you want to get. Right. Which
is a fallacy. But wasn't there always through the use of, you know, technology advancement,
whatever, force multipliers one way or another, there was always a an elite control over the
people one way or another, you know, controlling knowledge, feudalism, fiefdoms. Yeah. Like,
for example, if you go back before the year 1700, there were no jobs. Right. There were no jobs.
Nobody looked for you. So a job, even 150 years ago, a job meant someone that worked on something,
it was an order. So if you worked in furniture, and a job would be a custom chair, like this chair
that you're doing as a job, right. So now they replaced all these little projects, the things
that you productions with an overall encompassing thing called Do you have a job? Yeah, I have a
job, I have to mop the floor. And then I don't have a job, right? That's not what it means anymore.
But there was no jobs back in the days, because it was a fiefdom. You did what you did. And that's
what you did. You didn't know any better. You didn't know anything else, right? If you were a
baker, right, you made breads and pastries. The reason you did that is because your father was a
baker, right? You didn't know any different. That's what you did. Right. And you you you
are in society, however, you're in society, even they had bread factories, you know, they even
you could look this up, there are bread factories in Rome that had 2000 people working there making
million loaves a day, right? So back in ancient times, but that was not a job. They didn't know
anything else. It wasn't like I'm going to lose my job. Or, you know, I need a job. You just did
what you knew. Right? It's very different. And this is sort of a little bit of a revival after
the COVID thing about you know, everyone, like don't show up to work, work out or your work at
home. Yeah, right. Yeah. So you can't really hang out by the water cooler anymore. Now you're at
home. So you're only going to be tasked to do what you know, there's no more like punch in
and hang out. You know, if you don't produce what you know, or what you what you're there for,
because of what you know, you're you're going to be fired. So it is a little of a change. But it's
part of the fiefdom. It's all a fiefdom. So it's quite interesting, but it has nothing to do with
the things that I've talked about over the years of what calamities are going to be facing
society. So but it's just a point that I wanted to make, because that's you're in it now for
since the end of the heyday of the internet, I'd say was around 2010 to 2013. By 2014 or 15,
it was pretty clear that the internet was no longer a free place, you know what I mean?
Or free as free as we thought it to be, let's say, right? Well, that's when all of a sudden,
it seemed as though all of a sudden, the Wild West of it was all gone. You know, you had a lot
of freedom at first, it seemed like you could do anything or say anything online, in your own little
corner in your own little way. The only what the only problem was, you had to gain access, right?
And you had to have a couple of pieces of hardware, and you could do whatever you wanted,
it seems or you could go to the library, or whatever, or you don't have to have here's the
thing. It doesn't matter if you have it in your home, you just need you just need to know someone
who has a car, right? You don't need to you don't need money, you just need to know someone who has
money, you don't need food, you just need to know someone who has food, right? Well, yeah, of course,
because look, I'm just talking about access, not really about whether you whether you own it or
not, or you have it in your home. So sure, but the access was very prolific. And right now,
it's in your pocket, right? Stupid rectangle, and I'm using one right now. I don't get into
it like a lot of other people do. I can't see how people could stare at the rectangle all day,
I've seen people do. Because it's not that interesting. Again, I use it as a telephone,
I use it to between Skype and email and whatever. And that's it. I can't see how people could stare
at it. I found out recently I was out. And I saw some people sitting down there staring at it.
And I walked up to the side and they were actually watching a movie. Oh my gosh,
how can you watch a movie on the frickin? Anyway, yeah, no, I've seen that. Yeah,
you know, just really quick on that. It is fascinating to me that as the ease of access
appears to be there, right? It seems like you have the access to go and examine anything,
explore anything. And people stare at these things. Oh, not really. Not anymore. Well,
anymore. And if the 12 2013 I don't think you can explore anything anymore. Well,
I find it very limiting. Okay, fair enough. That's the limiting limited compared to that was
how many times have you done? Well, let's say you do research in any field. And I mean research,
like, you know, look up what's been memorialized completely subject. You go online, you'll see
the a lot of the websites that you might have pulled up before 2010 are gone. And the information
is gone. Google does not show share or show things in searches that get used to look at the
content, the the stuff that's out there is larger, there's more pages, actually, there's more stuff
out there. There's actually a lot more. It doesn't matter. I realized that the actual
quality of the information has been limited. But I'm just saying the actual, you know, the
um, well, of the quantity is actually larger. In reality,
there are more people in whatever town you live in right now. But the amount of people you could
have an interesting conversation with is about the same as it was 30 4050 years ago, right?
Very few. Yeah, no, forget about it. And that's what I was just about to get to is that as that
has gotten easier, and you point out that, you know, everybody's got a phone, right? So they
have access in their pocket. Now, you didn't even have to, you don't have to go sit down at the
library with a big computer and get access even sure. And the reason I'd say yes, everybody's
got a phone is because I have one now when when I didn't have one a few months ago, if you said
that I'd beg to differ, right? Right? Of course, now that I have one every now I'm part of the
everybody was like, Oh, my gosh, it scares me sometimes. Well, I didn't go get one steadily
until I went to go to Dallas again. For years. I didn't have Yeah, yeah, it was about you got
one. What? This past year? Have you had it more than a year? No, no, I got it. Yeah, I got it.
Just before I was going to go to Dallas, which was November, I might have got it in September
or something like that. Or somewhere in there. Because I got it. I remember because I gave you
the number. And you know, the conversation we're having right now about the phones is silly,
because many people listening have had one for more than a decade or so. Oh, yeah, definitely.
Well, they I don't know how long they've had them. I had one earlier and got rid of it. You know,
I didn't want it anymore. Because it just I didn't see the point I threw it across the room when it
was about five years ago. I got an old Motorola and I just threw it across the room. And that was
it. Yeah, I think it was might have been 10 years ago. I said forget it. I can't do this anymore.
Because it was just pointless. There was no reason to have it. But what's weird to me and here's an
honest open question. I have no idea. This is something I don't know. Wouldn't that affect I
know what affects people's brains for sure. To be staring at that thing all the time. But it's
gotta be affecting their eyes too. Because I mean, look, my eyes are very sensitive to stuff.
Well, it's different. It's different than if you grew up a year old enough sat in front of regular
CRT television, you know, the gun tube, right? Yes, don't you know, ruin your eyes, right?
Children get them further away at least six feet. Because of the energy coming off of it.
Well, of course, that was a constant. Anytime I was near a TV, I always tended to
more mechanical that also had well, it was quite well known back then from the
crazy, fringe conspiracy theories. Oh, they're sending stuff through the TV that right,
right. And they did. It was a lot of research that you go into an alpha state very quickly
in a conscious alpha state very quickly watching the old tube, right? Yeah. So the new tubes,
there's no tube now it's a flat screen. It has another aspect to it. Right? I'm not I haven't
researched it or looked into it. I don't know who to trust about it. For me. It's the sensors that
are built into it. Okay, there's the better phones, actually, most of the phones that are
the main, you know, Samsung, iPhone, or they've got dozens of sensors, temperature, heart rate,
movement, voice, sound, not just the microphone, right? Right. To gather data? Well, why would you
gather all that heart rate temperature? I mean, for what reason? There's got to be another reason
for gathering that right to create? What do you call it when you have a target or someone you want
to do something to you get gathered information now you can you know what to use on them? Right?
Kind of thing. Right. So yeah, so I don't Is it nefarious? Yeah, definitely is nefarious. Is it
outwardly harmful? I don't think so. But there are people that came down with quote unquote COVID.
Yeah, I've heard of more than one when they got a new device, a new phone or a tablet or something,
they got sick immediately the same day they got the device. Well, back in the days of the big old
box, that was, you know, the thing that was a tube. And you know, it was about the flicker rate,
you were talking about the alpha and this and that, you know, you had a flicker rate.
Still, there is a flicker rate on these things. Yeah, yeah. But it was more obvious with the
black and white TV, there was a process to the way it was made. And that created a slightly
progressive scan. And yeah, that had a progressive scan, right. And then the other
one actually had a flick, it just actually flashed, it was quick succession of flashes.
And as you well know, just like with strobe lights, you can induce different mental states
with different strobing and stuff like that. Now there's that aspect of it. Yeah, but I think it's
much more nefarious because of all the various sensors, right? Well, yeah, also location and
all that. Well, yeah, there was a point at which that stuff started going the other direction,
like it was going all one way at one point, and just beaming out to people, and it would have
effects on them. And that was the end of it. But now it's the loop is complete, it goes back to
and at that time, there was carry. Yeah, but but they're what I'm trying to say, though.
Okay, when I said people got COVID, I'm not talking about what they say COVID is,
people during that era, that year of 2020 came down with a very severe illness very rapidly,
and they acquired a new phone or tablet. Well, in a lot of cases, that was more cognitive to that.
That's the weird thing. They said it was, you know, why is it that you feel out of it? Why do
you have this brain fog going on? Oh, well, that's because you got this respiratory. Let me just
address this. Yeah. Okay. It's not that I'm talking about a. Okay, let me give an example.
There was a show in one of the convention centers here in Tucson. This is after they announced the
that week. And pretty much majority of the people in there got sick within a few minutes and went
outside of the building. They didn't know what was happening to them. Some of them went to a
medical person and said, Oh, that's radiation. We subject to microwaves, right? And so they
obviously did something, you know, and then they said the people had COVID. You see what I mean?
It's not. But if you do the math on the how much power is in the phone,
there is enough power in there if they have the right frequency and the bandwidth to make you ill
to actually hurt your body. Right. And this has been every Nokia was the one that emphasized it
more than others. When you when you've got a phone, even the old cell phones, it came with a
little instruction manual and it had a big cautionary. Don't put it on your head. Don't
check. Right. All this other stuff. If you're pregnant, if you're right. Yeah, it was it was
funny to me because it's like everybody's holding those things to their head because every you know,
everybody used to put. Yeah. Yeah. But I think it started off on a bad foot. And also years ago,
when the cell phones were new, the frequencies they used for cell phones were banned by the
military because it was damaging the people that were using them. But they freed up those.
They freed those frequencies up for the public. So, yes, is it nefarious? Yes, it is. But what
I'm trying to say is I have heard from several instances, several cases that the phones and
tablets, you know, anything handheld device, whatever those watches also. Right. Yeah.
Can propagate illness. Right. An ill state of being, you know, that could kill you or make
you feel like you have a severe fever, just like any type of infection. And it can induce an
infection. So, you know, that's a very interesting thing. Is that just through the electromagnetic
fields? Because that's an obvious. I believe it's a mixture of electromagnetic and non electromagnetic
magneto electric, which is not electromagnetic. Magneto electric is different. Right. Magneto
electric is would be you set off a pulse. And then when that pulse hits the object,
it produces electricity where electromagnetic is when the electricity from the device hits you.
It produces a magnetic effect. Very different. Right. That's the kind of thing within proximity
you get. You get into an area where there's sort of a cloud of this that's constantly flowing.
That's one thing. And then the the electromagno is a is a particular burst, like just a
something. Magneto, magneto electric is far more dangerous because it will create an electrical
field to impulse in the body where the magnetic field will not be as harmful. Electromagnetic
will not be as harmful as a magneto electric. It's kind of like
we're constantly bathing in all sorts of electromagnetic fields that you can
know. There's the magneto electric ones that'll mess you up. You see, this is kind of like phasing.
I think I brought this up a while back and we had someone with more than three sharpened pencils in
their pocket that put a comment. I'm glad someone did reach out, put a comment, because most people
don't understand this type of phase modulation. If you are at in a room and you're turning the
light on, off, on, off, on, off your little children, right. They discover lights which
are on, off, on, off, on, off, on, off. And I'm in the other room, but I'm not turning it on,
off. I'm going off, on, off, on, off, on. Now, obviously, on and off, on and off, on and off.
And off, on, off, on. Most people say you're doing the same thing. No, it's not. It's very
different. It's phase modulation. So I've ventured during this spot. We may be, I don't know,
somehow without getting it. OK, I don't want to get into what's called technical sonic events,
explain certain technical things I have with the body, I have with water to a certain degree.
But I've not gotten deep. And I think a lot of people would shy away if we turned it in any,
just in general now, sonic that was sounded technical. Notice I said sounded technical
because I would break it down in a very simple way, the way I think of it. Right. So, for example,
if you go to a place where there are rocket scientists or nuclear physicists, before you
approach like, oh, this is really the average person would be. I was very intimidating. You know,
I don't know. But when you go, let's say you were to go and spend a few days with these guys,
you'd be like, oh, they broke everything down into a real simple way of thinking about it. Right.
The same with a neurosurgeon. Like if I say, you know, this guy's a brain surgeon. Right.
Well, I've had many I've had over 20 hours discussion with a neurosurgeon. And until,
you know, most people, again, would be intimidated. Let's go talk to a neurosurgeon for hours. I don't
know. What do I know about it? Right. Because they're intimidated. Right. Well, once you spend
time with them, you'll see that he had to break all that stuff down. It's a very common, easy.
Right. Well, they get intimidated because of the terminology, which is common among people that
are engaged in that. Right. Like what is the biggest problem with understanding the body and
certain things that happen? Well, the problem is you're without using the terminology that
sounds intimidating because it's your right. There's a jargon. There you go. Just like with
you know, why are you so confused about the court papers? Because of the legalese,
the way that they're talking is what's confusing you. What's happening is not that difficult to
understand. Sure. But, you know, when they say, well, yeah, well, I would with the neurosurgeon,
I prove that the what you cannot create pure distilled water. It's a long story. Maybe we'll
get it. But in short, when cranium replacements were like when when a whole you have to remove
a piece of skull from the head to do brain surgery, they put the piece back. Right. And
it only took in America. If you were in South America, it didn't take it took in or in Canada
also. But if it didn't take if you're in South America, like it would infect. So they would just
remove it and put a piece of fiber like a mesh there and you'd have a soft spot on your head.
Right. OK. And I said, well, what kind of irrigation, you know, because you during
surgery, I don't want to get technical and see, I would say it's called irrigation when you flush
something. Right. Right. And just like the irrigation for your garden. But
they have an irrigation machine set up with distilled water and all that. I said that
distilled water is not distilled from the type of water quality that it was distilled in the
Northern Continent. If you switch, let's say you got Deer Park. Well, you know, the regular like
some real Deer Park is like a very common bottled water. They make most bottled water, you know,
make distilled water varieties. Also, you know, the Poland Springs used to be fine.
Right. Poland Spring used to be big. Aquafina is pretty large. Yeah. Coca-Cola or whatever. But
they the ones that are more utilitarian offer distilled water. And they come from actual
springs where in South America, the distilled water is more river water. So even though it's
twice, even if it's deionized, it still has the frequency. So of the creatures that lived
in the river. So when you irrigate and during surgery with water that's scientifically shown
to have nothing in it other than water, that water, the frequency and the energy and the
memory of it from being in a river, once it goes into the person's body, right where it's been
cleaned up. Right. The organisms now the body is warm and it offers all these nutrients.
The water will start producing the organisms you find in a river on your skull. And what's going to
happen is your body is going to see that as something it has to fight off as an infection.
Right. So so you'll end up with an infection. But if you use water that was extracted from
underground, it will start to reproduce those by those things that live underground, which are not
harmful at all. Right. Just like, for example, someone posted, you know, in the chat, you know,
turning plastic into oil. It's like full circle. Right. The rock oil. Right. OK. Yeah. Basically,
the water underground assists in making oils and things like that, petroleum or whatever.
So when you have the spring water garnered from a spring versus river water,
the body will then the water, once it's in the body, which has nutrients and heat and electrical
current, will start producing the organisms that are from underground, which are not harmful and do
not the body does not see as an infection, because, for example, river water. We're not
talking we're talking like river water. Right. That has like old fecal matter. Fish live in it.
There's amoebas, parrots, protozoa. And we'll start producing all that stuff. So you have an
infection. So when they switched to using imported what they couldn't find, they kept asking, like,
why do you want to know where the water comes from? It's distilled. No, no, no. We didn't know
comes from. So they said, oh, it's not good enough. We need to get water that comes from
an underground spring that's been distilled. And once they switch to that, then the cranium,
the mandible or whatever bones were, they would fuse and they would take no infection.
This is becoming I don't know if it's going to take. Anyway, this is a product of my discussions
with someone a few years ago. Anyway, just scratch that part just to say someone else. Right. I never
talk about personal stuff. But so what I what I'm trying to say here is we had a lab where if you're
discussing with someone now we're going to still water it, that distilled water is distilled water.
They don't want to hear anything else. But if you say the source of that water matters and here's
the proof. Well, we have the proof now. You see. So I learned. How do you write a short story? How
I learned about water frequency and water memory from a neurosurgeon. Right. So so this goes back.
So he benefited. And now I benefited because we have a case. Right. We have many examples where.
Right. So I got you. Very interesting. That's something to keep in mind, because
some of these other, you know, alleged what they refer to often is spring water.
Some of it didn't just come from the underground source. Right. There's the above ground source
as well, which is, you know, basically melting snow. Yeah. Yeah. But it just so happens that
practice what you would do. Rock formation. If you were to set up a water, the ground,
ground spring water, that you would have to look at their practices.
In other words, the general practices in other places, which is to get any water or, you know,
clean water sources where if you find that a particular company, what was the ones you
mentioned? Poland Spring or a few of them. Their practices were to get water that was
from an underground aquifer. It was not surface water yet. Right. Right. So you just have to
discover what their practices are, just like, you know, when you like I'm buying plastics now.
Right. And it's very interesting when you look at I want to know where your plastics come from.
It says we do not use recycled products. Right. OK. But another one like on the bombs is 10 percent
recycle. All right. And like, oh, big difference. You know, it doesn't. You know, big deal. It is
a big deal. Right. Because you're going to have contaminants that you can't get out, for example.
Right. Like is another tangent, super tangent time. OK. For example, if you have to get
replacement rotors, you know, disc brakes for your car. Right. OK. You go to the auto parts store and
they offer you various tiers, you know, the cheapest one all the way up to the lifetime
warranty one. Get the cheapest, cheapest, cheapest one. Why? Why? And they'll last longer. Why?
Unless you get the top tier ones. Then there's carbon fiber. Yeah. Why do you get the cheapest,
cheapest, cheapest ones? Like they're eight bucks. I remember the average rotors for the
van that I'm using was like 30 bucks. So they had one for like eleven dollars. And I want that one.
You know, it's junk. I'm like, no, it's not. And I told I explained to the guy why he was amazed.
And this is why. Because the cheapest, cheapest rotors come from the cheapest
manufacturing in, quote unquote, China, where they have very little refining on recycled metals.
They're not going to use virgin iron. They're going to just throw everything, you know, old
guardrails, anything you can imagine that the magnet sticks to and melt it, barely refine it.
So you have this incredible variety of metals and alloy that the craziest metallurgist would never
come up with made in these like dirt floor foundries. You're going to have a brake rotor
that's going to have such an exotic mix of metals in it that it's like nothing natural will wear it
out. You know what I mean? So in some cases, having a dirty mixture or a dirty production
process can benefit you. Right. Because of the diversity. It actually was always the diversity
in an alloy usually makes it stronger. That's right. If you do the right thing. Yeah. But it
just so happens that they are doing the right thing and they should flip them. I said these
brake rotors never wear out. You should sell them as you know, I'd buy them and repackage them as
they'll never wear out for a hundred bucks. Anyway, I just want that was a contrast to the water.
Right. You see, the one has a crappy source and it works better. One has a right. Less crappy,
you know, less crappy and then getting to a source, which is which is not going to produce what you.
Yeah. But let's get into the why of that, though, because here's the why of it.
Water is elemental. It's one of those things that is essential across the board. It's
it's a component of something as opposed to a combination mixture. Right. Without going into
elemental. Hold on. See, they were managing the water. They were managing the water. They said,
well, we are scientifically advanced and we have stringent processes to distill any water to make
it pure water. And I'm telling you, from a leadership perspective, no, you can't do that
because the water, no matter what you do to it, it'll be very angry. By the way, water likes to
absorb things. Even if you have pure water and you left it in a room, you want that to get it
wants to dissolve gases into it. Right. And some of the container, no matter what it is.
So what I'm saying from a set of a management perspective was we have a stringent process.
We could prove it's distilled. And I'm saying, no, no matter how stringent your process is,
you can't fool water. Water will still remember where it came from. So what this was also an
example of leadership, which is let's try this versus management. The management did not work.
They had failures. Now, the leadership came from out of nowhere. No proof. I had no proof of what
I was saying at all. Nothing was tried and it worked. But I knew it would work. Right. Because
I gave the method the reason why, even though it wasn't proven. So that's where leadership comes in.