Hey, Rated Y, Sonic Event 202, Greek, how
are you?
Yeah, it works either way.
I'm doing okay.
We were just trying to figure out, you
know, I'm trying to get the Jitsi to
work on a phone when the screen is
locked.
We have a solution on how to unlock
the screen, but the thing is I would
like to have it in a pocket, because
if you have an unlocked screen in a
purse or a pocket or whatever, it's like
a cat walking across a keyboard.
Yeah.
He was just telling you how to keep
it on so it doesn't black out from
the power thing.
No, yeah.
That's easy.
That's, yeah.
But it's, and I'm not using the Android.
I'm sticking with Apple, because it's just more
unintuitive shit to learn.
People don't know that I've always, when I
was handed a smartphone, I kind of like,
cool.
And then when I found out that all
the phones are going to be like that,
I said, very uncool.
Yes.
Very uncool.
Because it's so large.
You know, it's sort of like when they
started putting the cameras on the phones, I
thought it was great.
It was like, oh, this is cool.
I got a camera now.
And then everybody's phone is a camera.
So it's really a camera.
Well, now you're talking about, you're talking about
the interface.
See, um.
But that's the.
How do you carry it?
How do you carry a smartphone, right?
Yeah.
In your pocket.
And this is deliberate.
Well, yeah, I can't.
I won't.
I'd rather go.
And I do.
I've gone back.
I don't carry it.
But I have gone back.
I do not carry it.
I have gone back to how things were
when I was growing up, when the phone
rang, it was important.
Right.
And or you had a wrong number and
a wrong number was such a bummer.
And the phone was on a cord on
the wall.
Well, if you see where I work or
live or whatever, the phone is on a
cord on the wall.
The iPhone.
Right.
It's another reason they make it so uncomfortable.
First of all, most people are braindead.
If not, if I say all people with
few exception are braindead, it's a better statement.
What they do, they're making them so uncomfortable.
So now when it comes time to put
a chip in you to do it, it'll
be great.
We don't have to carry this big thing
instead of making it ergonomic or something.
Right.
It's very South Park.
What I see going on, which that's why
people like these parodies, you know, they never
tell you the truth.
So whatever they tell you is true is
actually fiction.
But the truth is cloaked in fiction.
If you want the truth, you're going to
have to go towards the fictional venues.
Just like I said, when I first came
here to Tucson, I went to the library
walking around.
I thought it was abandoned.
The librarian pops out and she's like, oh,
everything on this side is nonfiction.
Everything here is fiction.
I told her, hey, baby, everything in here
is fiction.
Because I looked at it, the books on
the shelves and they look like college, they
smell like college books.
Yeah.
But there's textbooks.
But there's a little bit of nonfiction sprinkled
in there.
South Park is great.
I mean, what they're telling.
Yeah.
So this is a ridiculous scenario.
Well, South Park is especially great.
You know what?
I was in the middle of an open
chat last night, you know, on my call
and show.
And it was funny because I went through
this whole thing about, did you see the
recent a with CRISPR technology, we figured out
how to put a pig kidney into a
person now.
A real transplant from a pig.
And I was going, they do this every
couple of years.
They're transplanting from a pig.
I haven't watched a South Park in over
20 years.
You know, I don't need to because I
know what they're doing and I'm glad that
they're doing it.
You know, they killed Kenny as Donald Marshall,
supposedly.
Donald Marshall, really, it's really around the stuff
discussed at cloning centers.
And what I mean by that is, you
know, because Donald Marshall's always killed at the
cloning centers.
You know, this is according to the annals
of Donald Marshall.
And, you know, a lot of people, by
the way, I turn them on to Donald
Marshall and whatever friend of mine, Daniel, does,
does a lot of compilations.
And he's interviewed Time Rider and all that.
People think it's too wild.
And I'm like, are you kidding?
That's mild.
It's really, you know, for example, if you
read the laws or real science, what's going
on, what, you know, all the exclusions that
they take out of experiments, that is way
freakier.
Like the laws and the way the money
system works is way freakier than any story
about underground cloning centers and consciousness transfer.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
And coincidence conspiracy is even more insane than
the most insane.
Because, like, if you look at a guy
like Jolly West, it's perfect example of both
of these things.
You know, Jolly West was right.
I heard of the name that Johnny, I
know Johnny West on Speed Racer or something
like that.
But Jolly West, no.
I think that was maybe Johnny Test.
But Jolly West was an MKUltra doctor.
Right.
And he just happened to get a session
with Jack Ruby right before he went insane.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
But he also, it turns out, Tom O
'Neill dug it up in his own personal
letters and everything.
And there go the dogs for some reason.
That's fine.
But we hardly hear it.
Yeah.
Cool.
But he also was there with Charles Manson
when he was in Haight-Ashbury.
And apparently one of his primary things was
trying to do mind control through LSD.
Also, he happened to get a private session
with Sirhan Sirhan.
You're starting to stack up the interesting coincidence
here with Jolly West and MKUltra.
Yeah.
Funny stuff.
It's kind of like whenever there's a public
incident, you see Wackenhut ascent to security.
Right.
Same thing.
Whenever it's a, what do you call it,
state sponsored, which is you have two states.
So anyway, it's funny.
But it's funny that you brought up the
dogs, because I was thinking about that, you
know, kind of like I try to focus
on when someone else is speaking.
But the thought came up.
I have someone in my contacts.
I think he's a sub and he's Greek.
And he thinks I'm very Greek.
And he always sends me very like stuff
kind of messages that it's like he eats
razor blades for breakfast or something like I
mispronounced a word or I had to look
something up.
It's shameful.
And he says he sent me some philosophical
stuff and I don't get it and all
that.
But he's very cryptic, can't communicate what his
point is.
See, the thing about.
Well, you should know better.
Greeks don't eat that kind of food.
Greek, you know.
What I'm saying, though, is I've had this
in the past.
And I bring it up because he's Greek.
First of all, the only reason I'm Greek
is because I have a really long name.
If you say it fast, you get a
hernia.
The reason I'm not interested.
Nobody can look good.
Because Greece is a Euro trash place, you
know.
And nobody can look good saying a Greek
name, by the way.
It's kind of Euro trashy, really.
I'm not.
It's I really would like to disconnect from.
But it's stuck and it's there.
And it's it allows me some people.
You know, when you meet when I meet
people and I said my nickname is the
Greeks.
Oh, I know Greeks.
I'm like, oh, I'm sorry.
I'm the only Greek I know.
I really I don't have a dislike for
him.
But it's it's I could say they're Euro
trash.
You know, that's fine.
You just don't have that.
You don't have that ancestral attachment.
No, no, they're gone.
No, my ancestors are gone.
I'm some kind of freak.
Well, like you shouldn't even be here.
Like when a guy is great.
Yeah, like the Rocky example.
Sorry.
But with the Rocky example, when people like
call themselves like the Italian style, it's usually
because they're proud of the fact that they're
Italian.
Oh, my God.
They're thinking that you are proud to be
a Greek is what the problem is here.
No, no, not at all.
It's not a problem.
It's a perception.
And the thing is about pronouncing words and
knowing the difference.
You know, I could train a dog to
speak Greek.
As a matter of fact, I had.
So I don't care about any of that.
So anyway, I'm reaching out to whoever I'm
not going to use his name.
You know who you are.
There's a couple of them, actually.
Come on.
We'll invite you on.
Let me know when it's convenient for you.
You probably in that slum known as Athens
or not, wherever you are.
We'll make a time and enlighten us with
your philosophy.
I mean, it's like Greek stuff to read.
And it's like I'm reading.
I'm like, I don't get it.
This is just like airy, fairy crap.
So if you can, here's the thing.
Like I tell people, I try to study
stuff.
If you can't communicate it, guess what?
You don't know it.
And if you're not a good communicator, that
means you have very little.
You have no input.
So either way you the way you know
if someone is.
And this is not about the specific person.
I'm just saying specifically people who can't communicate.
Also, it's a two way street.
Have very little input.
There's exceptions.
You know where people really can't speak or
whatever.
But they're keen.
But it's two way street.
So someone who can take in can also
put out.
Oh, that sounds like a good day there.
It does sound a little lascivious.
Yeah, she put out.
So here's the thing.
When people tell me you're not getting it.
Getting what?
Give it to me in 30 seconds.
Oh, that's too fast.
Man, you're going crazy.
Give it to me.
What's the second half that counts?
You're a little sexually frustrated there, Greek.
Is that what you term?
I would say, well, yeah, I don't do
that anymore.
But I wouldn't say frustration.
It's a new part of my life, you
know.
I'm trying to eliminate other than like quality
food.
Because food is really your fuel.
Like putting the wrong gasoline.
But you're not burning anything.
But I've eliminated all platters like any kind
of celebration.
Go ahead.
I have no interest in that.
People think like, but I'm not a downer.
Hopefully I'm not perceived as a downer.
But if it's a celebration or whatever, I'll
join.
But I'm not interested in any of those
emotional pastimes and all that.
My stuff is just a.
Because I know too much.
I don't know everything.
I don't even know a lot.
But I know too much to participate in
what other people consider to be a well
-structured whatever.
Right.
But the going back to communication and all
this and how to live and all that
is really where it's at.
Because the part that I get frustrated about
is.
And I can objectify this.
It sounds very subjective and opinion based.
But I see people don't know how to
live.
They don't know how to live.
They don't know how to eat.
They don't know how to clean.
I mean, like just general, whether it's hygiene
or their homes.
They don't know how the body works.
They don't know how to keep time.
They cannot coalesce anything that's real.
And keeping time is important.
You know, like, for example, the oleander here
in Tucson always starts blooming on the second
week of the second month.
And on the Pope's work schedule, it could
be three weeks off, two weeks off, right?
Sometimes more.
So but it's always on time.
So what I mean is, you know, someone
said, oh, you should go, you know, someone,
a doctor that I know.
She read a book about another doctor saying
that, yeah, you know, diabetes is this.
I said, he needs to join.
If he if he really wants to learn,
he needs to come on to my sonic
or I'll do a webinar on that.
And she got like she couldn't understand that
because I'm not a doctor.
I don't write books.
How would you know more?
Because she was telling me, would you get
out of that book?
I'm like, this guy's an amateur.
He doesn't know what's going on.
He's beating around the bush for 30 seconds.
But you don't have the piece of paper,
Greek.
So what do you know?
Oh, my gosh, they're all idiots.
Yeah, all of them.
What's a little exception?
Here's the thing with the doctors and lawyers.
They are moronic.
And now they're the exceptions.
I have to repeat this.
The exceptions are the people that are well
intended to go into those fields and they
find out what's going on, really.
Right.
And now they need an exit strategy.
Well, first, typically, when you find out what's
going on, the first even emotional thing is,
can I change it?
Can I do something better?
And if they go down that route, they're
going to find that the superiors right away,
they stick out and they're like, you have.
We don't want anything better.
We want you to do it standard.
And there's a kitty cat.
We want you to do it the regular
way that's accepted.
So so the exceptions are the people that
want to make it better.
They don't last ever.
And then they look for an exit strategy.
Now, an exit strategy could be anywhere between
two weeks and two years, even five years,
I've seen.
So those are the exceptions.
But the ones that stay in there are
happy.
I have to say it that way.
And there's no.
And that's and in that case, there is
no exception.
And unfortunately, like I know a woman from
Chile and she goes, oh, I don't like
American doctors.
I say, well, what does American have to
do with it?
And she goes on to Chile to have
herself examined and all that.
And they do this.
I said, do they today when you walked
in, did they strap a cuff on your
arm, inflate it and tell you had blood
pressure?
Yeah, they did a blood test, right?
Yeah.
They did a blood sugar test.
Yeah, I said they're idiots.
Well, they're speaking the same thing.
Yeah, I don't want to know.
She's I want to show you what.
No, I'm not interested.
They're speaking the same medical language regardless of
the conversation.
That's right.
Same with attorneys.
They're minors.
What they are there.
This is how if you want to get
legal about it or in law, they would
be called as wards or minors in custody.
In other words, they have a custodianship over
them and they're considered minors.
I think I've read several.
Maybe she wants a code, a state code
that said that you'll be even you'll be
considered a minor.
I was about money banking.
You'll be considered.
You can be considered a minor even though
you are of legal age.
Right.
Yeah.
By the way, anyone who deals with the
Social Security Administration is considered a minor.
That's called a minor accounts in the palms
manual.
The primary account is the Treasury account.
So that's why they treat you like a
little baby.
We're only going to give you this much
or whatever.
They're easy to turn inside.
By the way, anyone who wants to get
the quote unquote minor benefits from the Social
Security Administration.
Oh, you have to go to a hearing.
They'll never really because this all this stuff.
Attorneys also.
What's his name?
Brandon Joe Williams put out some stuff lately.
Just randomly bookmark some stuff like just to
see the latest videos.
And he had a pretty good interview, which
is interesting.
30 subscribers or two subscribers, no views.
And it's been a week, which is not
true.
There's over 2000 views.
And they have a funky little channel.
But anyway, he talks about how bar cards.
He's starting to realize that there are a
bunch of retard stuff that I've been saying
for decades.
And they're all about threats and intimidation.
Same with doctors.
Now, all of this is like saying, you
know, an idiot would say, Greek, are you
saying we shouldn't have medicine?
Shouldn't have law?
This is the idiot level, which is they
are.
This is the response that I usually get.
It's like a minor, like a child, a
nine year old reaction.
We're talking about 60 year old attorneys.
And 50 year old doctors react this way.
Greek, you're saying we shouldn't have any medicine.
We shouldn't have any laws.
I can never said that.
We need to have competent medicine and competent
law.
And the reason why it's like this, it's
totally in reverse, is proof.
And it's a testament to the robustness of
the human condition.
You can have a human society set up.
The people think there's government.
And there is no government.
In other words, if you denominate how the
government is set up, you're not in a
government at all.
It's corporate completely, even though the real government's
there.
You have no law.
You have no medicine.
If you think you have any law or
medicine, you are actually pretty normal.
You would have no problem with proper law
or proper medicine.
That's right.
Here's the interesting thing about it.
In law, it's actually harsher because there's no
negotiation.
There's no plea deal in law.
But there's so few laws that you have
to abide by.
And the golden rule, right?
Don't harm.
Cause no harm.
Actually, I'm going to be working with a
case of business that I'm interested in.
And they said, oh, you can't come in
anymore.
We have to do this.
And I said, why?
So somebody slipped and fell outside.
Did you do want him to slip and
fall?
He says, no, we actually helped him, called
an ambulance, and we're being sued.
And we got it.
Oh, you got put an injunction, right?
On you.
Yeah.
How do you know?
I said, unless the guy has a properly
sworn affidavit, you have to have the case.
I said, you have an attorney, right?
Yes, we do.
You probably got him flat $10,000 return.
He says, yeah.
I'm like, you know, get rid of him.
The guy's an idiot.
He's going to, the two attorneys, the one
suing you and the one that you hire
talk all the time about how much they're
going to get out of you and how
much percentage they're going to get out of
the other guy, billable hours.
I bet there's no sworn affidavit that he's
been injured.
He can't do it.
I don't know how to do it, by
the way.
They do affidavits, but they're not sworn properly
according to the code.
And I could give the codes.
Just look up United States codes, unsworn affidavits.
There's two ways to do it.
One is with the United States.
The other one is without the United States.
And you want to do it without the
United States, right?
Because this 14th Amendment citizen is not entitled
to anything when they say with the United
States.
You want to do it as a national,
right?
So they even tell you there's a distinction.
They're just like on the passport application.
So anyway, I said, I'll give you an
hour of my time.
And it's going to be very simple.
A very simple laundry list.
And it'll get you out.
And if they don't listen to you and
they pursue, then you counter sue for disturbing
commerce.
And the penalties of that can be up
to $100 million.
Right?
And you get them off your back.
And then you do an injunction.
And I said, how could they put an
injunction on you?
You see, it's very hard to do an
injunction out of the blue.
But if you have a repeat offense, like,
you know, there's someone else slipped and fell,
then they can do.
There's more right for an injunction.
Right.
But on the first time like that, no,
get the injunction.
Get out, get your business.
And they're like, oh, my gosh.
They're like, are you a lawyer?
So as a matter of fact, it's kind
of a disgrace to say no.
But yes, an attorney.
In fact, not an attorney at law.
Anyone can do that.
For example, a trustee is an attorney.
In fact, you know, anyone who has power
of attorney, you can give me power of
attorney.
Right.
And I can give you power of attorney.
You go sign anything for me.
The only thing is in these fake courts,
you can't go and represent me in a
real court, which is a superior court or
the Supreme Court, which is where you're supposed
to be as a as a national.
And this is all in the Constitution.
You can speak.
You can.
I wouldn't represent you, but I would be
brought in as an amicus, whatever.
It's a friend of the court.
And I would testify.
Yeah.
You give an amicus whatever you give an
amicus.
Yeah.
So it's very simple.
This is law.
But and what's going on is so heinous
and heinous, meaning on criminal level with the
medical and the legal.
And you'll find it everywhere.
There's no.
Let's see.
I remember when I was growing up, when
you had a lung disorder or respiratory, oh,
you got to go to Denver or you
got to go to Tucson, you know, and
you'll recover.
Right.
Know that that you don't hear stuff like
that anymore.
At this point, you know, there's a medical
community.
Say, go here and you live here for
a few weeks and you'll recover.
Never.
So what I'm trying to say here is
even small town doctors.
Yeah.
The only place you see evidence of that
is when they sent Doc Holliday to the
sanitariums in order to recover from or to
try to recover from the tuberculosis.
TB.
Yeah.
This is in the movies, though.
But that's in a movie about recently.
So what I'm trying to say is these
small town doctors are total morons also because
they've been indoctrinated.
If you're considered, quote unquote, professional to work
under that privilege, you have to completely swallow
and vomit out all the indoctrinated bullshit.
And it's getting worse and worse.
In other words, the education.
So what does this mean?
OK, yeah.
People that have been around have heard me
say this over and over and over.
You better learn who you are.
I used to say what you are and
where you are and when you are.
Right.
Which is lawful timekeeping.
You don't think, you know, that's that's like
an optional thing.
But it's kind of good to know, have
a feeling for real time.
You know, that's why, like, you know, the
day ends at solar noon.
That's why you kind of like before lunch,
you want to have lunch and take a
nap, you know.
But anyway, the whole thing is to really
know the way I said all these professions
are so screwed up as a testament to
the robustness of the human or the man
and the woman and the body and biology.
And generally in biology in general is very
robust.
Learn how to take advantage of that.
See people that have been following.
I've done this with several people like medical
protocols and for years and they're getting worse.
Everyone gets worse, by the way.
No one gets better with the medical protocols.
No one.
And if you're on it for many, many
years, they could drag you out and you're
going to just die of cancer.
It's very simple.
And most people that they say die of
cancer don't even have cancer, but they get
the treatments.
Anyway, what I'm trying to say here is,
if you know, well, okay, when I get
them off the protocols, they usually within a
month, they're fine.
And stuff that's gone away completely, you know,
so just do nothing.
What do you do?
First of all, this is the basic thing
to take advantage of the protocols, right?
Not the protocols, but take advantage of the
how robust we really are to make sure
you have a good quality water availability.
And that's not a marketing propaganda thing.
Learn how to prepare water yourself.
One thing that's really easy.
Anyone can do.
They sell these picture filters.
They call them bread of filters like Walmart
has them for less than 10 bucks or
whatever, right?
And prepare your own water instead of buying
it bottled or having it delivered or whatever
like that.
Right.
And but here's the thing.
This is what takes the quality up to
the next level.
That bread of filters considered junk.
Right.
But if you study absorption for, you know,
for filtering, like carbon, mostly carbon and some
ion resin in there, you'll notice that as
the temperature of the water goes down, the
efficiency goes up to 99%.
So if I said someone, I want you
to have good water.
All you need to do is get one
of these picture filters.
Right.
Now, you don't want to just do what
all the morons do is they go to
the sink, fill it up.
And the Greek says is great water.
Is he getting sponsored by these guys?
No, no, no.
If you really want to make it great
water, what you do is instead of being
like a regular moron and going to the
sink and pouring the water in there, get
a similar size volume jug and fill that
with the water from the tap and chill
it overnight or at least eight hours in
the fridge.
Right.
And then run it through the filter.
And you don't I'm not talking about having
it drinking it cold or anything.
You should be cool.
But filtering the water at 39 degrees, which
is basically almost all refrigerators in the world
are set at four degrees Celsius or 39
right now.
Even if you're not a refrigerator buff like
you don't know what's going on.
It's just set by your landlord or the
previous tenant or you bought it and that's
it.
I bet if you put a thermometer in
there, it'll be anywhere between 38 and 41
degrees, which is the average is 39.
And if you're in Europe, it'll be around
for 3.9 to 4.2 Celsius.
I assure you, this is how it works.
So it's almost like we are set up
already for it.
So when you run the water through the
Brita filter, have it be chilled.
And also when you have it slightly open
or vented, you don't have to put a
lid on it on a big jar or
another vase in the fridge.
You want the you want it to outgas
a little bit as it's cooling.
You don't have to put a tight lid
on it while in that initial stage.
Now you have increased the quality of your
water.
Number two, food.
First thing, learn how to eat seasonally.
OK.
If you want to look on a macro
level in the West, not until there was
major interchange and groceries and produce from the
tropics.
Right.
All these refrigerated shipping and all that stuff.
You didn't have the diseases and the ailments
and the liver problems that you do now.
Right.
So, yeah.
So I'm not saying avoid food foods from
the tropics.
You don't live in the tropics, but you
can use tropical food to cool you down
when it's hot outside.
Right.
Now, the exception would be if you live
in a tropical area like Florida.
Right.
Because that is more tropical.
Yeah.
It's less it would be considered more temperate,
I guess.
Or, yeah.
Yeah.
But then but then here's the benefit.
You'd be closer, but you're not quite there
yet.
You know, you'll have your citrus in the
winter because it's citrus winter season.
But I don't think you'll have bananas.
You could have bananas in California.
You won't have coffee in Florida.
No, you know, coffee doesn't.
Yeah.
So so cross latitude is the best.
And usually you'll find the most for.
So let's say you're in Rhode Island.
You're going to have apples, pears, apricots, blueberries,
raspberries, cherries.
Right.
You shouldn't have bananas or whatever fruit, kiwi
or whatever.
You know, even though actually New Zealand would
be almost on your same thing.
But avoid.
Right.
So in the summer you don't eat salmon.
I remember when this in the early 2000s
was a big salmon craze and then they
busted it by saying that it's artificial color.
Remember all that crap 20 years ago, 15
years ago.
I remember going into people's homes in the
summer and they said they couldn't cool down
enough.
They had the thermostat all the way down.
So I walk in.
You know, like a two thousand dollar a
month electric bill.
And I'm like, I'm like, are you eating
salmon?
She goes, yeah, I love it.
I said, stop eating salmon because it's adjusting
your body to the Arctic.
Right.
So that's what I mean by cross latitude
and seasonal.
Now, if you understand this trick, you can
actually manipulate it.
Right.
So let's see the winter seasons coming around
wherever you live, even in Florida, because it
gets cold in Florida for a few weeks.
It gets cold for many years also.
And you're not used to it.
What you do is you go get yourself
a piece of salmon, poach it, cook it.
However, eat salmon for two or three days.
Then you'll say, wow, I'm not feeling cold
anymore.
Right.
But you have to do the reverse so
you can actually engineer your diet.
Now, the other thing about your diet is
this.
No one talks about this.
I'm not talking about protein, carbohydrates or anything
like that.
Right.
You know, at all.
The way that I would talk about diet
would be animal and non-animal.
Right.
And you have to know how to do
combining.
Another thing about diet is this.
People say, well, what do you what would
you like to eat for breakfast?
Have you heard that?
What would you like to eat for lunch?
Well, I don't know.
What would you like to eat for dinner?
Oh, I don't know.
Or I like to eat this for dinner.
OK.
People are thinking of these these meals that
they eat.
You shouldn't really eat more than two meals
a day, by the way.
You know, the three meal a day.
That's the food industry.
Right.
They want you to eat five meals a
day if they would.
The meals work very much like this.
They stack.
Because when you have your lunch, that'll be
in you till tomorrow.
Right.
But you're going to have your dinner in
between.
So you're actually doing food combining.
There's a there's an opening between the mouth
and the anus.
That's the only opening in the body to
the inside of the body, like a tunnel
going through the mountain.
So you got a choo-choo train that's
way down the tunnel and a new a
new choo-choo train is coming in right
now.
You got two trains in the tunnel.
And if they meet and there's and there's,
let's say, from a chemical point of view
or a seasonal point of view or across
latitude point of view, not compatible, you're going
to have problems.
I'll give you an example.
When you have flatulence gas, that's a signal
to your body saying don't eat that again,
please, because that's what that's as far as
we can go with it.
The idiot, the morons, the scientific morons will
tell you, well, you should add stress.
No, what's going on in the body is
when you start masticating and you start chewing,
the digestion begins with your first bite, literally,
and your first bite determined on how much
you bit off is how much chewing you
should do, how much saliva is going to
mix with it.
As you're swallowing, there's more saliva being put
out.
And then there's a gel substance like saliva
and other things that form in the stomach
to continue that process or slight movement.
So what it's doing is it's changing the
food to be compatible to be turned into
energy that the inside of the body can
see, right?
And this happens all through the intestine and
each part of the intestine specializes in a
different extraction or conversion method.
So the way it goes is once the
food is ready, it goes from the solid
or liquid, then it goes to gas and
that gas becomes energetic and then it goes,
this is all happening in the lumen of
the intestine or the lumen of the stomach.
And once it goes from gas, it goes
to energy and then it passes into the
body and then the blood vessels on the
inside of the organs, you know, you'll see
blood vessels around the stomach, blood vessels around
the intestines and so on.
The duodenum, you can get into the anatomy
and figure it out yourself and you could
actually as an engineer would, you could see
the types of the sizes and the amount
of blood vessels in nature and get into
forming a real science on how the body
gets energy from food.
But that's a way other long discussion or
it could be introduced.
I just introduced it.
So when you have flatulence, it's if you
have the body's having a hard time from
the nutrition to go from gas, remember it's
solid, liquid, gas to energy and it just
bounces back and it remains a gas.
That gas quantity should have been converted to
energy.
Now, when I say energy, I don't know
what kind is part of the biological vacuum.
Does it have an electrical component to it?
Yes, it does, but it's not electricity.
It's not electricity as we know it because
as we know, electricity is pressure.
These are chemical source from a battery or
it's pressurized magnetically pressurized.
This is not magnetically pressurized and not a
chemical battery.
It's a different type of electricity that emerges
from a biological vacuum.
And if you want an extreme example, there's
something called a mora ray or stingray and
or a I'm sorry, what is that?
Eel.
That's right.
Yeah.
And that's a very real thing.
There's actually some pretty cool videos about them
in tanks what they can do and measured.
You could say that is also a product
of the biological that they need to be
investigated and then dialed down, just like the
early electrical experiments.
Guess what was investigated first?
Lightning.
Right.
And then it was dialed down right into
what we understand is electricity today.
So basically the gas in the body is
the body is telling you, right, don't do
this.
And that's typically from bad food combining.
An example of bad food combining is if
you just had a glass of milk and
notice it and say yogurt or cheese milk.
And now you take some lemonade or lemon
juice that turns into a poison in the
body.
Don't I'm not going to get into details
of something that completely paralyzes your body's ability
to digest anything else other than this, which
is melon.
Eat it alone or leave it alone.
So if you're going to eat melon, you
should have at least one to two hours
that you haven't eaten or one and two
hours after you eat melon to eat something
else because it requires such a specific process
and chemical structure to digest it properly that
if you include melon, whatever melon.
And by the way, cucumber in some degree
is like melon.
If you ever cut a cantaloupe, look at
the seeds and the smell of the whole
room smells like it or watermelon.
Cucumbers are very similar in that they're almost
like a melon.
I consider them in the melon family, but
cucumbers tend to be a transition point where
they are well combined with other things to
a degree.
They actually slow down digestion enough.
So, yeah, that's another discussion.
So that's why I sell people.
Do you remember the cafe craze with a
garnish?
They put a you get a lunch or
dinner and they have a slice of melon
as a garnish or wrapped with prosciutto.
Oh, my gosh.
Listen, everything that I'm saying now, I've been
saying since the 80s.
This is nothing new.
And this is I've been watching all the
food trends also.
Oh, my gosh.
OK, very quickly.
And people who saw the wisdom in it,
like a lot of people say you want
to learn information.
Yeah.
But if you don't have the wisdom to
sort it out, it doesn't mean anything.
Actually, a lot of these doctors and lawyers
are actually, quote unquote, smart and get a
lot of information, but they don't have the
wisdom to see what they're doing.
Right.
Well, a lot of these.
There's no wisdom in the wisdom is to
be able to, you know, there's a lot
of sayings and cliches about wisdom, but really
wisdom and intuition, authentic intuition, individual intuition allows
you to get a new piece of information.
And then, like, it's not a leap of
faith.
You have this instinctive feeling.
It's an evil, not a feeling that people
say, but it's an emote very deep where,
you know, this has to be handled very
carefully because sometimes the information has direction in
it.
Right.
And people fall.
And that's a misleading thing.
So you need the wisdom to understand these
things when you get the knowledge.
You know, it's all about knowledge and wisdom.
No one ever gets into that, but it's
mostly intuitive and you have to trust it.
But it's a skill.
Just like, for example, when I mentioned whenever
you meet someone new, do a quick snap
judgment, a strong judgment on them, like within
30 seconds or less.
And then as you get to know them,
refer back to your initial judgment and see,
was I correct on that initial judgment after
a week, a month or a year?
And if you weren't correct, start dialing in
your judgment.
I was being, don't say you were being
too judgmental.
I've heard that too many times.
That doesn't mean anything.
Right.
It's like I was walking too fast.
I don't know if I was walking.
You know, what are you talking about?
No.
Okay.
When you, when you, okay, let's say it
was too judgmental.
Okay.
About what specific?
What judgment call did you make along?
What parameters?
See, not because they're trying to get the
obvious things.
Oh, you're too judgmental about what?
No, you have to be too negatively judgmental
if there were anything.
Right.
Or you'd have to be too positively judgmental.
But what specific thing are you judging?
There's a component.
Yeah.
If you don't even give it a direction,
even a vague one, then there's no point
to it.
Judgment about what?
Judgment.
A harsh judgment is appropriate.
Physical appearance and hygiene.
The other one would be the way they
carry themselves, the way they sound.
Okay.
What they're there for, their behavior, their etiquette.
Those are the, that's what you would judge
them on.
Right.
Okay.
So not just being too judgmental.
Right.
See, everything that you hear, all these cliches,
by the way, are all false.
Like, what came first, chicken or the egg?
That's a real dumb question.
Obviously, the chicken because that you could have
been an alligator egg.
Right.
You have all these, these, these things that,
that the paradox no one knows.
I'm like, oh my gosh, you know, you
only use 5% of your brain.
You're probably using less than 1%.
You know, of that, you know, kind of
thing.
If you believe all this stuff that they
tell you, no one is thinking with very
little exception.
Okay.
So the back to the robustness of the
human body, you have the water treatment.
Then you very, very, very basic.
Now, if you don't filter your own water,
just to recap, just put it in the
dark, put it in the dark.
And if you can chill it for overnight,
you don't have to drink it cold.
Bring it down because that's like setting, you
know, cookie dough should be baked.
Right.
And then you have it at room temperature.
Water should, after it's been bottled or processed,
reach that 39 degrees for a little while
and absolutely keep it in the dark.
With my water experimentations now, I've noticed that
the most harmful thing to water is light.
And of course, heat, you know, you put
water on a boiling on fire, you add
something else now.
But exposing it to light degrades it very
quickly.
And I mean, degrades its carrying capacity and
its qualities and all that.
So that's why spring water is better than
drinking lake or river water.
It's not exposed to light and air.
And then there's air that's exposed to air
exposure.
The food, learn about food combining.
And I gave a little bit more than
I usually do on these kinds of talks
on those things.
But when I say food combining, please, the
things that I've always been mentioning.
But when you have lunch, think about what
you had for breakfast or dinner last night.
And does it combine well?
Right.
So if you had a hamburger for dinner,
don't have pizza for lunch the next day.
What does that look like?
Looks that looks like a conveyor belt junk
food.
Doesn't it?
Think about it.
Yeah.
Think about everything you eat as being on
a conveyor belt.
And you're looking down the conveyor belt, which
is what you ate.
And the other way you're looking up the
conveyor belt to what you're going to eat.
And how does that look to you?
Does it look well balanced?
Does it look like too much processed food?
Right.
Doesn't this get a little strange when people
do what they call dessert, though?
Because, you know, I will.
Yeah, that's that's a marketing.
OK, let me just say it.
This is like steak and steak and ice
cream.
They're two pretty common things.
Yeah.
Not good.
If you combine them at the same.
Like, if you think about it, I'm not
going to put a steak and an ice
cream on the same plate and eat them
at the same time.
It's it's almost it's if you have it
where a short order after the steak, it's
almost as bad as doing that.
But here's the other thing.
The temperature.
You ever.
What happens to fat when it's in the
fridge?
Well, right.
It stays.
It's hard.
You know, it's hard and it stays in
its shape and all that.
But you take.
Yeah.
Right.
So how many.
So, you know, if you know those fruit
presses, you put half an orange, the old
school ones, you press the fruit, the citrus
press.
I used to take French fries and stuff
like that, put it in the press and
squeeze it and all that.
You see like a half a teaspoon of
fry oil.
And the person's like, oh, and I'm like,
go ahead, drink it.
Eat it.
You were going to eat those fries, right?
You can still eat them.
They're a little mashed.
But drink the oil here.
Eat it.
I was just I used to talk people
like that.
You know, someone was addicted to doughnuts.
And is how many doughnuts do I could
eat like half a dozen in the morning?
And I'm like, give me three of them.
And I compressed them.
There was like almost a teaspoon of fry
oil.
I said, drink it.
Drink it.
Like, oh, that's gross.
I'm like, yeah.
It really tastes like doughnuts made with lard
anyway.
So you're.
Well, actually, good doughnuts wouldn't be made with
lard unless there were Mexican doughnuts or something.
But really, because they like.
Yeah, I can't eat the real authentic northern
Mexican food because they fry everything in lard.
I don't like the flavor.
It's on.
It's unlawful.
It's unclean.
I never liked the flavor.
What do you do?
How do they do that?
Well, animal fat.
Well, here's beef.
Animal fat has a higher flashpoint.
It doesn't go.
OK, so but let's go back to to
the point which which I kind of lost.
But maybe you could drag me back in.
I was talking about food combining.
And I had mentioned the state ice cream
thing, which is ridiculous.
And yeah, don't put it together again.
OK, now here's the thing that I've seen
when people go to a banquet, a feast,
a holiday.
OK, you could see how vacuous their minds
are.
Oh, if I eat this, I'm going to
be fat.
I'm like, you idiot.
You don't eat like this every day.
It's Thanksgiving or it's your birthday or it's
your anniversary or you're at a restaurant that
you go to once every two years.
Moron.
Go ahead and feast.
Go ahead and have the fatty foods and
the sweet foods because you don't eat like
this every day.
Moron.
Yeah, I've done this.
I've seen this.
Someone has this one.
I don't like going out restaurants.
If I'm going to go to a restaurant,
it's going to have to be the upper
crusty ones.
And I still say I'd like to go
to a high-end restaurant, but I don't
know who I'd bring with me.
But anyway, that's another story.
How many times have you seen people say,
oh, it's a special event.
I'm going to get fat.
No, you're not going to.
You get fat by eating like this consistently
and constantly.
So shut up.
Because what that means is they don't know
how to appreciate and they don't recognize what's
going on at all.
And I've seen this.
I've stopped going out to restaurants.
I hear this all the time.
Oh, no, I don't want to get fat.
I'm like, you dumb, you know, whatever.
You're not going to eat this every day.
Go ahead and live it up.
Live it up.
You're not going to eat like this again
maybe in six months or two months.
It's fine.
See, so there's a mixture that people don't
understand.
When you eat your daily stuff every day,
day in, day out, keep it light, right?
Light is a big thing here.
You know, what's light is relative, based on
culture.
But every culture, you can eat light when
you think about it, right?
So, like, you know, for example, when people
go to Italy and they're eating pasta in
Sicily, they didn't like the food because when
they get a pasta, the gravy looks like
a broth.
It's not this thick ragu sitting on top.
Very rarely.
So you go to the northern climate, right?
In Sicily, it's like I couldn't get a
good bowl of pasta.
Everything was in soup.
I was like, well, yeah, the gravy, the
sauce is very, very light.
It's more like a tomato juice instead of
the thing you used to have.
Yeah, it's at the bottom of your bowl.
You grate a little bit.
You have a little cheese on a bowl.
You put a little cheese on it, you
know, like Americans or white people.
Oh, it's got melted cheese.
It's great.
Anyway.
So the thing is, they eat light.
So learn how to eat light.
Eat slowly.
There's a thing about chewing your liquids and
drinking your solids.
What does that mean?
Don't guzzle.
Anybody who was on the football team, the
coach is yelling, don't guzzle too much water,
right?
Drink it slowly, even when you're really thirsty.
Let it mix with saliva.
Yes, it does require to mix with saliva
to be recognized.
And drink.
That's chewing your liquids and drinking your solids
is you're not thoroughly.
Yeah.
Thoroughly until it's liquefied.
I've seen people on television do taste us.
You know, a guy takes a bite of
a burger.
One, two.
And he's swallowing.
I'm like, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You got to chew that bad boy.
Now, the macroneurotics, I mean, macrobiotics, there's a
true 30 times.
There's no number of how much you're going
to chew.
It's just make, just get it at least
to a liquid, a semi-liquid state.
You know, what would you call a mash?
Like the wet mash potato state, you know?
Like a mush.
A mush.
Definitely a wet mush.
Yeah.
Not a dry.
I've seen people try to, sorry, I can't
be around people.
I mean, when they swallow and eat, they're
like, oh, I need something to wash this
down.
You ever hear that?
You know?
You should have chewed it a little bit
more, idiot.
So, and this is typical.
I mean, oh my gosh, it's so bad.
And it's been, and I'm just, I've been
thinking exactly what I'm saying now since the
80s.
Could you imagine 40 years of this?
I've had enough.
And it's really mostly in the culture, the
Western culture I'm talking about.
And I'm talking about East Coast, you know,
some Midwest, mostly Southwest.
It's all the same.
Actually, I got it.
You know, Canadians are a little more refined.
Why?
Because when you go to a Canadian pizza
parlor, they always give you a fork and
knife.
Pretty much.
Right?
So anyway, that's just a sideways humor.
I don't think it was even funny.
But, you know, when I heard the Canadians
eat their pizza with a fork and knife,
I was like, hmm, that's more refinement.
Yeah.
You know, instead of chomping on it.
How about the Philly cheeseburger?
Yeah.
You know, you're supposed to eat that.
You spread your legs about two feet apart
and lean over a little bit.
Right?
You know, there's a whole stance that a
professional cheese steak eater eats.
Right?
Yeah.
Also, if you go out to the clubbing
in New York and they go get a
pizza at two in the morning, do the
same stance.
You spread about two feet apart, you know,
about two foot distance and you lean over
while you're biting the slice.
Right?
Yep.
You know what I'm talking about, right?
Yeah, so there's all these things you, I
watch, I've been watching all, it's kind of
like, you know, when a dog's going to
take a poop, you know, the stance, right?
Oh, yeah.
Versus pee.
Or you see the leg goes up, you're
like, oh, that's, that's going to be urine.
For humans, I know, this dog is going
to eat the business.
It's like, oh my gosh.
They're very, once you, well, you have to
be sharp on these things.
You have to be really concerned.
Now, I might sound like a real inconsiderate
motherfucker, but actually you haven't gotten any anywhere,
anywhere, anywhere from anyone ever before.
And why?
Well, I think I've answered that in the
beginning of the thing.
So, this is, this kind of shotgun, steamroller
information needs to be given this way.
It's kind of like a coach, you know,
uh, you know, you know, coach has to
be rough to the players that he's supporting
and coaching.
As a matter of fact, he has to
be so rough.
He has to be rougher, should be rougher
than the opposing team would be on this
team.
Right?
Otherwise there's so, so if you have a
coach that's rougher on you than the, than
actual playing the game, if the game will,
what that will not intimidate you.
Will it?
You're going to be, I'd rather be intimidated
by someone trying to teach me something than
the actual act of playing the game.
But then vice versa.
It's like you're not prepared, right?
You're worried about the opponent.
You're worried about failing on the coach.
About your own coach.
Yeah.
And I found that's the best way to
convey information that sticks.
Now, of course, nine out of ten people
won't get it, but it, you know, again,
if you can help one person, that's fine.
So, that's basically the, the idea of if
you, and then there's hygiene, of course, and
which is your whole surroundings.
The idea of a testament to the robust,
robustness of the human body.
There's a, there's a there's food combining.
The medical part, by the way, by the
way, nowhere in the Bible is it plants,
pee, or medicine.
Excuse me, I have a cough there.
I should have a little drink.
No, no, no problem.
Look, why don't you take a moment and
I'll tell you what I'm going to do.
I'm just going to break this in half
because we've done a fairly long one here
and create another.
We'll create another.
The human condition.