We're rated Y, Sonic Event 2, 1, 6.
Anyway, Greek, you know, weird weather over here
kind of knocked me out for a little
while, but I also had a personal fiasco
earlier today, but we're not here to tell
personal stories.
We were just talking about weather, and maybe
we should reiterate it, because it's interesting.
A lot of people here have taken the
webinar, the weather webinar I did.
It was three, three-part.
You know, I kind of like saying that
I did a three-part, nine-hour webinar
a while back, and whoever's new here is
like, oh, I missed that.
Yeah, you did.
But we might do it again.
But there was like 50 people.
Wait a minute.
There was 50 people on it.
How many people do you think actually went
to work on it?
Ten.
I know for sure.
Okay.
Well, that's pretty good.
Which is enough to just mess up all
the weather in the Western Hemisphere, believe it
or not.
And to be honest with you, look, one
out of five, or yeah, one out of
ten even, but one out of five is
pretty good for a rate of turnover on
people actually taking any webinar and doing something
with it.
So I'm just letting you know.
I don't know if you're aware of the
rate of webinars and stuff like that, but
that's a good turnover for something, especially something
that's kind of, let's call it unusual.
Well, it's really unusual, because you're not supposed
to, no one's, like Mark Twain says, everyone's
talking about the weather.
When is someone going to do something about
it?
Because there were people working on it in
San Diego while he was still alive.
That's another thing you could look into.
Weather work was popular in the late 1800s.
I thought it was San Francisco, not San
Diego.
It was San Diego?
There's a statue of a guy who, he
used to do it chemically.
He used to have these little cans.
He'd light up some mixture on fire, make
all these smoke little pockets all over town
and rain would come after he did that.
It was like sulfur and some other things.
There's a memorial somewhere in San Diego attributing
his weather work, believe it or not.
Yeah, cloud seeding kind of stuff he was
doing, right?
Yeah, but it wasn't really high enough to
go up.
It was just like, imagine opening a can
of beans, but instead of a can of
beans, it's like sulfur and a bunch of
other stuff and setting it on fire, on
the ground.
So anyway, what I've been learning is that
the weather, it's really hot.
I noticed that when I do weather work
to cool it down, it made it hotter,
like a lot hotter, like 112, right?
And instead of 100 or 90, like at
the altitude that I'm at at 2,600
feet, 100 degrees is like 85 in New
York, right?
So it's dry.
And if you're under the shade, like even
from a twig or a branch of a
tree, it feels 10 degrees cooler.
So it's not bad.
But this intense heat keeps coming on and
I've been looking at the flows.
Anyone who was around for the webinar heard
me say that it works opposite the physics
that we're taught.
The colder flows move quickly, where in the
physics we're taught, when you chill something down,
it slows it down, right?
And the hot flows move slowly, right?
Colder stuff like that just seems lighter in
its appearance to me.
I mean, again, I got, you know, you
have different forms of density.
The hotter is denser with the ether and
the colder is more rarefied.
That's why the cold rises with the ether
and the heat goes down.
That's what I was saying.
That's what I visually observe, is that cold,
even though they've always told me it's like
heavier and this and that, it's not.
It is actually lighter.
No, no, no.
There are two types of cold and two
types of heat.
There are.
But generally speaking, that's what I observe in
the air.
I'm just saying what I observe.
Look, I may not have observed everything.
Well, even without observing, just the knowledge that
the higher up you go and up to
the colder gets.
But in order to make when you chill
something, it gets denser.
So one is a chemical reaction of cold
and heat where heat rises and cold goes
down.
Then you have the energetic reaction where the
cold rises and the heat goes down.
So when you're using that energy is not
a good term because people think in terms
of when you say energy in terms of
power and work, they think like electricity and
transference.
But that's not.
Yeah, we're talking about the stuff that makes
everything right is still making everything right.
So, you know how the human body has
the 28 elements that you find in soil,
like our bodies are made from your mother
is pregnant.
She doesn't eat what's on the earth.
You know, you're not you don't form.
So we're made from all everything is made
from the same stuff.
And the finer and the less composed it
is, just like when you the early mental
of periodic table, you know, was constantly being
reworked, took him a long time to publish
something.
They just publish it because he was wrestling
with several gases that are lighter than hydrogen,
smaller than atomic number one.
Right.
Because so just screw it.
Just make hydrogen one as well.
It's not one.
It's a grouping.
Walter Russell had known that.
And if you study what's called an imponderable
gas, you'll find a study of imponderable liquids.
What that means, like a ponderable liquid means
when you put a liquid in a container
and it's a well-structured container with a
good seal and a lid, you come back
any given amount of time and it's still
in that container.
Right.
But that's a ponderable liquid because you ponder
it.
You know, you know what it's how it
behaves and imponderable liquid.
You would put it in a well-structured
container with a good seal lid.
You come back the next day or a
week later and it's all over the table
and you study the container and there's no
hole.
There's no breach.
There's no corrosion.
The seal is still perfectly fine.
You're like, how the hell did this thing
get out of the container?
Right.
It went like right through the container without
breaching any of the structure.
Right.
No.
Yeah.
So you can't ponder it.
You know, it's like, my gosh, I can't.
I can't ponder that.
I mean, you can't accept it.
Right.
So there are imponderable liquids.
You can read about them.
There's less and less online, by the way.
But no one's talking ever about imponderable gases.
Now, back in the early 2000s, I mingled
with people that worked in aerospace, military, weapons
design, energy, all kinds of stuff.
And they were really funny.
I'll just give a paraphrase.
When they go up to high altitude into
space, they said, you know, there's a smell
there.
That's why I'm Freeman.
About 10 years ago, I was the first
person ever to say, you know, space smells
like burning flesh.
Not like a steak on a grill, you
know, that smells good.
That sharp fat.
No, no, no, no.
It smells like you threw a cat in
the fire or human burning.
It's very foul, like burning flesh smell.
Right.
That's an ugly smell.
Yeah.
I mean, because I've been near people that
are caught in fires and it's a nasty
smell.
Yeah.
That's what space smells like.
That's why when those ships come down, like
that probe from the Navy, they have to
hose it down and all that because they
think it's the Thorazine, not Thorazine, Thorazine.
The Zine, whatever fuels that are super toxic
uses rocket fuel like a drop of it
can kill 100 people.
That's why they also tell people to stay
away from it because of radiation.
It's B.S. Yeah.
So it's just the smell on it is
so bad they have to wash it down.
Because think about it.
When they're washing it down, it's falling on
the runway.
If it was really that toxic, they have
to contain all that.
But anyway.
Yeah.
No kidding.
Because that's that's that's the real thing.
So they.
So one of the things was when they
go, really, they have planes that go into
space and vice versa, other than the space
shuttle.
And if they were serious about space travel,
they wouldn't be launching them from the ground,
by the way.
They would be launching them from high altitude.
Right.
But anyway, the stuff they show you is
not how it works.
Back in the 80s, I knew people that
I was in contact with that were just
elevated platforms that hovered at 20,000 feet.
But but anyway.
Yeah.
What they did is when they go into
space or what they call space, they have
these containers and they fill them with space
gas.
But every time they brought Earth, they were
empty.
And they were plumbed.
Whoa, you're breaking up.
You're breaking up real bad.
Oh, yeah.
OK.
Yeah.
That's because I'm walking near a weather machine.
Let me get away.
Yeah.
I'm outside.
So yeah, it's amazing.
You know, it's you can measure these.
They're past totally passive devices.
Yet they screw up smartphones.
So because, you know, there's like what, 30
billion transistors in a smartphone.
So there's you know, when you get that
small, it's sensitive.
So anyway, they would try to put space
gas and they just couldn't.
And they saw the container is not thick
enough, you know.
But they did get to the point where
they figured out how to capture.
And I'll let you know how they did
it just to the point, because I just
explained imponderable liquids, the same thing with gases.
They figured out that if they get an
aluminum container like a tank, a gas tank,
aluminum and it has honeycomb structure inside of
it and you put a lid on it.
But like, you know, when you get a
bottle of soda and someone doesn't put the
lid on too tight and it spills out
right now, whatever you do, don't put the
lid on tight.
Just get an aluminum container with honeycomb structure
inside, you know, pretty much filled the inside
of volume of the container.
It's all honeycomb structure.
Fine honeycomb has to be honeycomb and a
loose cap.
You will be able to bring that gas.
It will not escape.
But if you compress it, it just escapes
and disappears.
Yeah.
So weird, weird stuff.
Imponderable gases.
Another way to make them is with what's
called a Joe cell.
HHO, hydrogen, hydrogen, hydrogen, oxygen, HHO.
People try to make HHO gas for their
car.
You need a tremendous amount of electricity to
make you to run your car.
I've done it.
You don't want to use that.
You want to use the gases that are
lighter than hydrogen.
A Joe cell basically works by charging the
water in a certain arrangement.
There's very little online.
I've had over eight hour conversations with him
about stuff.
He doesn't really know how it works, which
is fine.
I mean, I make stuff that I don't
know how it works, but it works.
That way you can you can delve into
the Joe cell.
You can experiment and get to those imponderable
gases.
That's still the imponderable gases are still what
make to go back to the ether and
all that.
It's still part of what makes us makes
up our entire reality, including our bodies.
So with the weather work, make a long
story longer.
I've been discovering that whatever I'm doing here
is slowing down the flow.
So when you slow down the flow, it
warms.
It's a warming trend, right?
When you quicken the flow, it's a cooling
trend.
It's the opposite of what physics is.
You know, the chemical physics.
So, yeah, the only disadvantage of every time
I do work, it destroys Texas because it's
downstream.
And Georgia, Florida, and then it goes to
Europe.
It's because everything goes west to east.
So the solution for me would be to
go about 100 miles west of Tucson and
work there.
So it drops on Tucson.
Or I need to invest time and put
a rain magnets on the ground.
I have to make a map of where
I live and go out to the perimeter.
And a few near the center, like maybe
five or ten devices, very small devices, the
size of a can of soda or can
of beer.
And place them and they have to be
monitored and run every day.
So I'm not doing that stuff.
I was just conveniently trying to cool it
down here and just making it hotter.
I've never seen anything like this before, but
I'm able to diagnose it.
Yesterday, I did have some success of making
a storm, a zero chance of rain and
a storm ensued.
But it came very fast and discharged.
I didn't get any rain, but a lot
of people east of me got rain.
And I made a map of the radar
map shows everything surrounded where I was, coincidentally,
and I was directly in the center, like
a donut with an opening on it.
So, yeah, the weather work is excellent because
it's something that, it's not even discussed, right?
And when you speak to a normie, so
you do weather work, you mean you're monitoring
the weather, right?
You're doing weather monitoring, right?
No, no, actually, they can't, it's unfathomable to
them.
They cannot get it.
You're a meteorologist.
Yeah, they cannot understand that you can actually
manipulate the weather.
There was a guy back in the most
recent, well, one that was someone who cannot
understand it that actually had success, was a
guy that worked out in Corpus Christi, Texas
as a helicopter factory.
Anybody near there would know that when they
make those Apache helicopters and stuff.
He was building a house in Corpus Christi
and they were framing the house with wood
and all this rain kept coming and it's
hard for them to work in the rain.
So I said, look, just do this, this
and that.
That's not where they make the Blackhawks, by
the way?
I think so, yeah.
Sorry, go ahead.
Well, some of the parts.
It would be really, for any military, it
would be dumb to make everything in one
spot.
Well, a lot of them, what they did
is they split the business up and they
started making things in parts.
So you no longer have a factory that
just makes a tank.
And they're assembled in like a warehouse that's
nondescript or underground or whatever.
Oh, right.
So you see a bunch of machine parts
that go all over the country and then
everybody's got to get paid to ship them.
This is how you expand a business, by
the way.
Also, the largest submarine naval research facility is
in the middle of the Nevada desert.
Well, right.
It's true.
You can drive up, yeah.
Submarines sail underneath the desert, underground tunnels.
And in Connecticut, in a body of water
that has no connection to the ocean, is
also another place where they do submarine tests.
So it's just...
Yeah, it's all underground.
Kind of like the James Bond thing.
There was a movie that had an underground
submarine parking lot kind of thing.
And this thing is like, you go under
that small...
Let's just say you have a river, just
theoretically, you have a river and then you
go underneath the river and there's a place
to go under the river.
So that's what happens there.
Yeah, and people think in Hollywood, when you
say under the river, that it's small.
Some of these caverns, you know, when they
get up to 900 feet tall, they have
their own weather system again.
Yeah, city size.
Yeah, literally, like in a large city, not
small.
Yeah, so anyway, he just screwed a piece
of pipe and made a weather gun.
And he was like, I can't believe it.
It's raining everywhere around me, but it's not
raining where they're framing the house.
Yeah, and I said, he called the people.
They wouldn't come out to work because they
didn't believe it.
And they came out and worked, said, hey,
look, this guy could stop the rain.
This was about stopping the rain.
Didn't really want to get into particulars.
He says, look, at this point, if it
works, I'll do it.
And it sounds wacky, but I'll do it.
And he actually did it.
So in other words, brought that up because
there is a...
Wilhelm Reich talked about the why factor, meaning
like you are...
And so does...
The connections in three directions to make the...
Yeah, the person's intent can affect the machinery,
right?
That's why a lot of times when a
technical machine like a phone or a computer
or whatever stops working and the operator gets
nervous, it's really hard for them to fix
it because their energy goes into it.
It's better to call someone else who's not
nervous about the device not working.
But the why factor is what Wilhelm Reich
talked about.
And there's a guy, Pond, his name is.
He works on some devices from Keely.
These pressure devices with platinum stuff in it.
I saw one once.
It's got to be all the input of
the operator because I can't see how this
thing is doing anything.
But with this case, though, the why factor
had nothing to do with it.
The person's intent or knowledge had nothing to
do with it.
He just followed instructions.
As a matter of fact, you know, when
you build a weather gun, it's on a
pivot.
You should be able to move it around.
Think of a telescope.
He screwed everything in place.
I told him where to aim it on
the map.
I sent him a map on email.
And he screwed everything in place, immovable.
Kind of like in France in World War
I or so.
Before World War II, the French gave Hitler
a tour of their wall, of their guns.
What is it?
The marginal line.
And their guns were fixed in the wall.
So Hitler just went around them, right?
So he was fortunate enough that the storms
were coming frequently from the same place.
He just screwed this gun, basically a tube,
in place.
It was not movable.
And it still worked.
It pretty much had the most basic, basic,
basic.
So the thing is, when you bring this
up, because there's a thing that there's the
doubt that does it work or not.
Because no one hears about it.
And then there's the other aspect, which is
Wilhelm Reich or Pond talks about the Y
factor, the intent of the operator or the
energy character of the operator.
And I've seen where with weather devices, it
doesn't matter.
But it does.
In other words, if the person is fine
-tuned and the device is fine-tuned, there's
nothing better, right?
That's basically how it works.
Also, the people that are most successful with
it are the ones that go for low
-hanging fruit.
What I mean by that is, you remember
how growing up, we read literature and things
about how fighter aces from World War I
and World War II were idolized, right?
Young people don't know what the hell is
a fighter ace.
You don't hear about that anymore.
At all.
It's like rotary phone.
So the fighter aces, when one of them
was interviewed, more than one actually, the reason
they were fighter aces is because when a
pack of airplanes showed up, they were able
to intuitively and skillfully pick out the least
experienced and the most novice and the worst
fighter pilot and go after them.
The reason they were ace fighter pilots is
not because they went against good pilots.
It's because they found out who was not
good and shot them down and kept doing
that repeatedly.
The low-hanging fruit critique.
And that's where you can prove the weather
work is the easiest.
The low-hanging fruit.
If you have a storm coming, you could
slice down the middle.
You can do that with these devices.
What's complicated is being in the high desert
and having a heat wave type of year
and drought.
When we have droughts here, they last several
years.
And we're in one right now.
It's come back.
So I'm curious about fighting the drought.
And as I'm saying that, I set up,
I made a change before we got on.
And there's massive clouds forming in less than
the time that we've been on.
It was pretty much blue sky.
Now I'm under cloud cover.
Go figure.
That low-hanging fruit thing makes perfect sense
though, Greg.
Because here's the thing.
It's got multiple benefits.
Because every time you go out in a
squadron, you come back.
And, hey, the new guy didn't come back
with us.
Every single time.
It's sort of like, who's going to want
to be a red shirt on Star Trek?
Nobody.
So you're going to have trouble recruiting people.
You have to adjust for the fact that
you lost people.
And you're going to consistently do it.
And it was acceptable that the new guy
was shot down.
Yeah, it's acceptable.
But after a little while, somebody's going to
say, hey, you know what?
I don't think I want to go up
there as the new guy because they never
come back.
So you demoralize, depopulate, and de-incentivize your
enemy just by picking off the low-hanging
fruit first every single time.
So that consistent strategy makes more sense than
I think people would want to recognize.
Well, actually, too, I would disagree.
I think the champion, like years ago, the
two armies would meet.
Each one would send a champion.
And the champions would fight.
And the winner would be the winning army.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
So I think taking out the champion is
the demoralizer.
It's a multi-layered thing, though.
Oh, it is.
If you can do both, I'm just saying,
if you do both of those things, then
it's excellent.
Because you take away the incentive for the
new ones, you take out their best guy.
And it's just like if you ever saw
the movie Troy, they send out Achilles, right?
Yeah, the champion, yeah.
Well, anyway, Achilles killed everybody until Paris hits
him with the arrow in the Achilles tendon.
It's a secret.
Yeah, his mother held him in Hades and
down the river, held him from the ankles.
Right, and that's how he was not invincible
right there.
Anyway, but I'm just saying, if you do
both, it creates a very interesting dynamic when
these guys have to go home.
Yeah, but imagine, I think there's some people
listening, if you don't know what a fighter
race is, look it up.
They were quite glorified even until the 1970s.
Oh yeah, matter of fact, they would have
never even bothered to try and make those
movies, those Top Gun movies or anything, if
they weren't still trying to populate that and
popularize it as one of the big things,
right?
Because that was nothing but military propaganda.
Yeah, Top Gun would be the most contemporary.
Yeah, and they just made a sequel not
long ago, I don't know if you're aware
of that.
Anyway.
Yeah, I didn't even bother streaming that.
Yeah, well, who would?
You know what the story is.
So, look, I know you're into the weather
thing and all that, but I want to
get to just a couple of quick comments
before you run out of gas, because I
know you're going to probably get disinterested pretty
quick here.
No, no, don't say that.
Let's just do it anyway.
Okay, I'm sorry, maybe I misread it.
Anyways, now look, there was a little bit
of a discussion on a previous Sonic about
somebody not being a cushy or cushy not
liking cannabis or whatever.
So, there was a bit of a discussion
back and forth, and people wanted to know
about your view on that.
Oops, I heard a little introduction.
You're breaking up.
My connection's not that good.
Let me move from where I'm at.
Sorry.
There's something about cannabis.
Go ahead.
Yeah, cannabis.
A discussion broke out about cannabis, and then,
simultaneously, people wanted to know what your view
was on it, because I find it to
be useful.
And just a quick note here, you know,
the Greek is the only guy I ever
heard who is not a pagan, and is
not one of these woo-woo people, and
is not a witch, that attempted to explain,
and you don't see this online anywhere, that,
you know, the five-pointed star has a
meaning, and the six compartments and all that,
and what it actually stands for.
He actually had that correct.
And they used to teach pagan healers, by
the way, that everything was made of 27
elements, but that's because one of them is
duplicated in the 28 that's scientifically laid out.
Anyway, just throwing that in there, that's pieces
of those knowledge that never seem to get
out there.
Anyway, about cannabis.
They basically were going back and forth about
how, you know, certain people disapprove of it,
and they were talking about it for dreaming.
Okay, I'm obviously consolidating this for you, okay,
this discussion.
Dreaming.
The fact is that it does help people
sleep, and it does help them, say, not
dream and all that kind of stuff, because,
you know, it's useless interface, and people screwing
with them, or entities, not necessarily people, but
maybe people, screwing with them and all that.
So they want to know your view on
the use for cannabis to get those entities
to stop screwing with you while you're sleeping.
Well, here's the thing.
Isoch, Bentov, and a couple of other people
have read this, and I've also intuited this
intuitively, that nothing is wasted in nature.
When you're sleeping, your consciousness is being used
somewhere else.
And if you're not dreaming, they're just using
you entirely.
I think dream time would be something to
be looked at.
First of all, I have a feeling that
dream time, you can have a very long
dream, and it's only 30 seconds, right before
you wake up, is what you're getting.
Oh yeah, I've had stuff that I think
is days long, and then I find out
I've only been asleep 10 minutes, you know.
Yeah, exactly.
So it's just a download that you're getting.
Your consciousness, I would suggest, and I would
imply, that is being, when you're asleep, is
being used somewhere else, and you have no
memory of it, let's just say, there is
a, even in the biblical narrative, there is
a consciousness after death, after a certain time,
called the resurrection, whether you're in a body
or not.
So that would then pertain to the question,
is there a consciousness prior of you being
born?
Do you remember, I mean, let's say past
life memories aside, or even included, what do
you remember from before you were born?
So one of the most serious things that
has not been investigated, and it's discussed to
a certain degree technologically under the Donald Marshall
stuff, where your memory is given to you.
So when your consciousness, what I'm trying to
say, one thing that has to be looked
at is, how is it possible to so
thoroughly wipe memory?
So if your consciousness is being used somewhere
else, and you don't remember anything at all,
and you would call that a slept well
without dreaming, what kind of technology is used
to block that?
That's what I'm curious about, because maybe you
don't want to unblock that, right?
Well, a Faraday cage can block lots of
EMF, so why not?
Yeah, Faraday cages and all that, but they
can break through that also, because there's a
tuning.
Here's the thing, there is a tuning to
all shielding devices.
It's not discussed, just like the weather manipulation
is not discussed, but you can break through
any form of shielding if you understand its
tuning.
You can say frequency, but it's beyond frequency,
because there's no frequency at that point, it's
longitudinal, right?
There's no wave function, but it still has
a tuning to it, because there is a
function, let's say a frequency.
Frequency means how much per second, or how
much per given amount of time.
When you eliminate the time factor, that's why
when Tesla first started talking about his power,
it wasn't volts per amp or watts per,
it was volt amps, right?
There's no time.
When you say per, like miles per hour,
right, gallons per hour, volts per amp, you
have this time factor.
In order to break through shielding, and I
believe that this is the thing, to break
through the memory, you have to break through
what's called the time or event factor.
Event is a better, like there's no time
travel, right?
Because time is a made up construct, but
there is event travel, where you go to
past events, future events, this and that.
That's more accurate, and the reason why our
language, almost every word in our language is
an oxymoron, you know that, right?
Once you start researching the way our communication,
everything is an oxymoron, so we have to
start cleaning that up.
Everything is backwards too, like everything is mislabeled,
I mean it's like somebody just randomized the
whole thing and decided to flip it all
upside down.
Well, the key to unlock many things is
to discover how to break through the memory
wipes, is another way, it's called a memory
wipe, lack of memory, a memory wipe, because
you know, for example, if you were conscious
before the now, meaning when you were born,
and even when you were born, many people
are not conscious, the earliest conscious memories are
maybe one, two, three, four years old, so
there's a memory wipe or lack of retention,
that is the thing, that is the major
contention of breakthrough, or breakthrough, let's say, technology
or skill to have, is to break through
memory wipes and memory blocks.
Well, it's not necessarily a problem with the
memory, it's a problem with the access to
it, and the problem with the access to
those earlier memories is that you have, you
know, that certain bit of your neurology is
still incomplete, so you don't have the recall
memory, I think that's fairly solid.
I don't think it's physical, I think it's
tuning, it's a tuning issue.
Have you ever looked at the neurological development
previous to, because if you look at it
from a certain standpoint, that time period matches
perfectly with the time period where still the
blood-brain barrier is incomplete, and you have
this difference in the neurological makeup of the
babies versus, you know, the toddlers even, the
transition.
As your size changes, just like anyone does
AM radio, as the size of the antenna
determines the frequency band, that's still a narrow
spectrum.
Oh, you hear thunder?
No, I do actually.
That's pretty quick, that was a very rapid
storm forming, but it's not going over where
I am at.
It's very subtle, I'm not sure if the
recording picked it up, but yeah, I did
hear a little thunder there.
Yeah, it's about 15 miles to the east.
Shoot, I need it to come over here.
Yeah, okay, last thing I want to interject
in here is just one thing about this,
which was not in the notes or the
discussion.
I hear all the time from a lot
of these woo-woo people that they've had
all kinds of choices previous to the...
Yeah, but hold on, again, that argument is
an open-ended thing until we really, where's
the evidence?
And the evidence would be, you know, because
contracts can be verbal, right?
Right.
So if you're being held to a choice,
it's a contract, so it could be verbal.
Do you remember saying that or emitting such
an agreement, you know, from you mentally or
whatever?
That's the thing, it goes back to memory
wipe and memory block.
So if you can't ever open the box,
that argument never ends.
Well, that's why the MKUltra guys called them
memory caps, right?
Memory cap, yeah, all that stuff.
To me, that's the biggest, what would you
say, block?
Once we can eliminate the memory cap, the
memory block, the memory wipe without time factor,
in other words, you can have access to
all information from all time, that would be
the ultimate answer.
And then you could form your questions properly,
because right now all those questions are valid,
but they cannot be addressed with these memory
blocks.
Imagine having a box with something in it
and the box cannot be opened and is
never opened.
That's all philosophical then.
Yeah, it's academic, you can speculate all day
as to whether that box is empty or
what it contains, it doesn't matter because you
can't get into it to actually prove.
Yeah, academic is actually a really bad word,
by the way, but yeah, I get it.
But that was the point of me using
it, because it means that it's just about
that useless, because if you cannot solve the
thing anyway, because you don't know what X
means, then there you go, you're out.
X doesn't necessarily solve by not knowing it
in that case.
What academia is about is all these different
ways to dumb you down, is what it
is, really.
But yeah, so it's a part of the
dumb.
If you're putting energy on something that you
know cannot be resolved, it's a form of
dumbing down.
And it's a good way to keep people
distracted and wasting their time, which I talk
about all the time, and so do you.
And ultimately you say that's the meaning of
life, so fair enough, I don't argue with
you.
Okay, so here's something about the hierarchy, and
I'm going to just read the whole thing,
which is only a couple sentences, but it
needs to be read because I want you
to take in the whole thing and they
know that their question was asked.
I'm new to learning here, so please excuse.
I thought Yahweh is the God of Israel,
so that is different than biblical Christ?
Satan being God of this world, does that
factor in?
Okay, what they're trying to understand is these
different names, and what are they actually talking
about, and what is the reality of it?
Well, here's the thing.
The Bible is very, very simple, by the
way.
Just look at the story.
We're looking at the story regardless.
Okay, so when you get some information here,
check this out.
I don't know what it is, whatever body
of information.
You have to go through what's in the
information first, and then decide whether it's fact
fiction or whatever.
It's very cohesive.
For example, let's use what Jason Breshears talks
about.
You know, like Yahweh is a desert demon
popped out of a burning bush.
First of all, there's no burning bush.
It's very clear that Moses is speaking to
an angel that's radiating flames, and he's afraid,
and the angel then puts a bush between
himself and Moses, so Moses is more coherent,
but his flames do not burn the bush,
so there's no burning bush.
Yes, that sounds like a large cicada bug
behind you, like a loud bug.
It is.
I'm going to go to the other part
of the house because cicadas that come out
when they're hot.
So the burning bush thing right away, when
you hear someone say that means they don't
know, they haven't read it, or they're going
along with what somebody else wrote, you know,
that person's going along with what somebody else
wrote.
The other thing is when the conversation does
take place about who are you, he says,
I am the God of your forefathers, so
he was known, but prior, he's not newly
introduced in the book of Exodus, like, let's
say, Brashear says, he says, I am the
God of Abraham and your fathers, and Jacob,
and so on and so forth, so he's
not new, so again, it didn't come, wasn't
entered there.
So using that as an example, no stain
on Brashear, he puts out some good stuff,
but he's terrible with the biblical stuff, in
my opinion, and I could back it up,
he would never debate me on this because
there's no debate.
We just go back to the text.
The name shows up.
Now, it doesn't matter if this is written,
it was written 20 years ago or a
thousand years ago or at the time that
it was supposed to be written, let's say,
either way, it doesn't matter.
The text is very cohesive by bringing up
the Yahweh and who the Christ is and
all that other stuff.
The main thing about the Christ stuff is
very simple.
He's the God of Israel and it's not
a geographic Israel, right?
You get it?
But it happens to be because you can
say, if you say the land of the
Italians, it's Italian here or whatever, it's close
enough.
The thing about the Christ, again, it's based
on, I knew someone years ago who, when
religious arguments would come up, he says, yeah,
you believer in Jesus, and they're like, yeah,
what religion was Jesus' religion?
That shuts people up right away, right?
Because it's not Christianity.
So the thing about that is, again, very,
very easy to see that I don't trust
having a discussion with anyone regarding, let's say,
the New Testament or who the Christ was,
because when you bring that figure up, most
people think of a guy nailed to a
cross wearing a diaper, right?
And the three wise men coming, right?
So quick dispelling that, when the Christ was
born, the wise men, we know it was
two or more, not three, it was two
or more, it's probably a caravan of 100,
the Christ was about two and a half
years old when they came to him, right?
That's pretty clear in the text, very clear,
right?
The amount of time it took to The
other thing is, we're talking identity now, and
when he was born, was given by an
astronomical alignment, and that astronomical alignment, if you
take it back, would be the year 3
BC, the month of September, the day of
11.
That's why they had that big birthday party
for him, right?
In September 11th.
So the other thing is, when he was
arrested by the Judaean, notice I didn't say
Jewish, Judaean religious authorities, and brought to the
puppet king, and then brought to the prefect
governor Pontius Pilate, Pontius Pilate says use your
law, right?
And your law to the Judeans, and there
was a retort that says how can we
use our law under Caesar?
So the law, the Judean capital punishment, is
death by stoning, and Deuteronomy 21 says it's
a high crime, you're nailed to a tree,
and he uses the word son.
So you have three men nailed to an
almond tree, because we know there's almond tree
references, not olive tree, almond tree references, and
the same tree, and the people passed stoning,
right?
Passed from third to seventh, on and on
and on, we know that from the book
of numbers, anything hanging from a tree is
a curse and to be burned, that's why
they cast lots for the clothing, because the
people were made aware of the ceremony, right?
So it's kind of like, let's say the
Chinese took over the U.S., and they
do 4th of July here, and the Chinese
military that's occupying the U.S. doesn't know
anything about it, so it's like you have
to explain to them on the fly, what
is the 4th of July about?
Oh, well, they have hot dogs, hamburgers, and
they blow up fireworks.
Oh, okay, right?
Oh, so blow up the fireworks, okay, we
need to have a fire, you know, but
what if there's a fire, you know, whatever.
So anyway, the Romans were made aware of
this, the tree was going to be burned
and all that, and so there's no, I
cannot, all of, in other words, all I
hear online, in books or whatever, it's all
false, because it seems like we're not even
talking about the same text, so I don't
really want to have, when I do biblicals
talk, I almost don't want to hear what
the other people have to say.
I will talk at you, I'll talk at
you, but I won't talk to you, I
won't talk with you, speak with you, unless
you can prove that you know what I
just mentioned, and, which comes from the text.
I have no belief in this, I just
happen to know the text, and that's all
we have.
It's like, I don't bother, you mentioned Italians
before, I don't bother to speak to people
unless they understand that Italy's a construct, actually,
and you're talking about Sardinia, Sicily, and Rome
all being cobbled together.
If you don't know that, we're not talking
about the same thing.
Yeah, well, it's actually a model, it's a
similar thing that's happening here, you know, the
50 states here are all 50 nations, independent,
they each have their state constitution, you have
the powers of the state, and all that.
The only thing was, you know, they put
Mussolini in power, they're like, you know, what
are you going to do for, if we
put you in power, you got to do
us a favor and make the Vatican, it's
a state, you know, it's an independent state,
right?
Yeah.
And that's what he did, so that's why
they put him in power, he was the
only one that was going for it, because
he basically denationalized the group that he was
that he came from by doing that.
But anyway, it's another discussion, I don't know
much about it, but I thought that was
really funny how Mussolini declared the Vatican an
independent city-state, so.
Yeah, it's because it was the central bank
essentially, and it needed to be, yeah, I
know, but that's the They run everything through
there, yeah.
So people don't understand that part of that
history, so it's like, when they start talking
about Italy, I'm like, oh God, you know
nothing.
The Italian language was even...
Well, the Italian, I mean, you can go
from one state in Italy, one country in
Italy, because it's all these little countries put
together, and there's animosity between others.
An example would be Spain and Catalonia.
Catalonia in Spain is an example of what's
happening in Italy, really.
And you have the Swiss, you know, the
Italians near the Swiss border are radically different
than the ones in central about, and then
radically, Sicilians might as well be Greeks, so.
Well, there you go, and that's where my
people come from, and that's what I'm saying.
It's a different situation.
It was a different language, too.
They actually unified the languages through the military.
Anyway, but that's my point.
Yeah, they made some kind of Latin revision
and all that, yes.
Yeah, and they did that by saying, okay,
we're going to put a Sicilian, a Sardinian,
and a Roman together.
Here you go.
You guys each get to speak this new
language, which is Italian, which is part of
each of your three languages, and that's how
they cobbled it together.
I'm just saying.
Yeah.
You got Torino, Bologna, Bolognese.
Yeah, they all have distinct...
Actually, it's proven.
They also have distinct bloodlines, by the way.
Yeah, I know.
They're not even related in terms of DNA
or whatever genetics.
They're a bit more intermingled now, but...
Yeah, after World War I, yeah.
Yeah, after World War I, but starting in
about the 1800s, so it's not this...
Italy's an ancient country.
No, it's not an ancient country.
It didn't exist a long time.
The Roman Empire existed here and there, but
not...
Well, yeah, Libya was a colony of Rome
up until 52, was it?
And Germany.
Germany was owned by Italy, basically, by Rome,
and not only that, but...
Yeah, they had the Hungarian Empire and all
that, yeah.
The entire road structure in what they call
Great Britain, right, in England, the entire road
structure is based on the Roman engineers who
set it up.
Oh, yeah, the Roman miles and the way
the roads are laid out, yeah.
Exactly, exactly.
So, anyway, look, I didn't mean to go
too far...
Well, that came from Greek technology, which was
tied in with Egyptian technology.
Yes, because that's what the Romans did.
They picked up on all the...
But my point is that people that don't
know this history think that it's this other
thing.
Anyway, I understand what you're saying.
Oh, we got off on that, but, again,
memory block is a big deal.
That's the main thing.
That's why I check up on Donald Marshall's
stuff, because he's able to Again, I just
read what's being said about it.
There's quite a body of work that he's
put out where your consciousness can be snatched
using technology, basically, and I believe it.
But one of the keys to understanding the
technology is you cannot factor time in it.
It can't be something per something else.
Like the concept of decibels is independent of
time, right?
An old term is measuring things by decibels,
which was Nieper's.
And if you have any encyclopedias from pre
-1920, dig in and look up pressure, pre
-1920, electrical pressure and all that stuff, you'll
be like, oh, my gosh, what happened to
all this engineering?
If we would have just continued applying the
stuff that was discovered up until the 1920s,
man, we would really be, you know, let's
say, advanced at this point.
Half the stuff we discuss here would not
even be advanced at this point.
It would be normal.
So something happened around the 1920s...