I'll probably listen to this 203 really quickly
before I get the Greek back into the
role he was on before and answer some
questions.
Want to let all you guys know something,
a recent ruling against Apple in an antitrust
court might make it so you guys who
are using Apple to receive the rated Y
through Patreon, you guys were getting charged extra.
Now that had nothing to do with us.
I opted out of it having to do
with us because guess what?
Some creators are getting refund problems right now,
right?
You guys can ask Patreon for a little
bit of a refund, but we didn't pile
on with that because I opted out.
So some of you might be able to
get just about enough money back to get
a free month or more.
Well, what I would suggest is make a
short version of the class, probably class action,
right?
Yeah, just copy the court case and sue
them.
Yeah, it was an antitrust ruling is what
happened, I think, as a result of a
class action.
I'd have to look it up again.
Oh, okay.
But I just have to go to...
Whenever there's a class action, don't join it.
No, no, no, no, no.
Make yourself a summary of the court and
then sue them independently for a lot more
than the people, the $50 or $200 check
they got, you sue them in six figures,
seven figures, right?
So they settled with six figures, right?
If you guys want to go through lawsuits
and everything, great.
If you want to do a short thing,
though, you could just probably request it at
this...
I've been told that you can request and
wind up with a few bucks back that
you were being overcharged for.
That's all.
By the way, another conversation I was having
with someone recently, I was also a sob,
I was saying, I'm looking at corporate acquisition
memorandum and notes from their meetings, and they're
really boring.
I mean, we're looking at...
But if you know what you're looking for,
at one part of the transaction, they said,
we've got received the bills of exchange.
So when one company does a thing with
another, they just send them a bill and
they endorse it back and forth.
There's no money.
When Bill Gates wants to buy a house,
let's say he has a hundred million in
his bank account.
He buys a $50 million house.
What do you think his bank account is
at?
It's still at a hundred million.
Does he have a mortgage?
No.
Because he uses bills of exchange.
And these corporations, it's going to get worse,
people, in other words, because they know there's
a little bit of time left.
I was just going to ask you a
question about that, because in context, Bill Gates
just went on and did a little media
tour about how he's going to give away
the half of his fortune that he still
has, because he got divorced and gave half
to Linda.
Yeah, it's all talk for the...
It's unbelievable how stupid the society is when
it comes to financial stuff.
They're just as stupid as they are about
the medical and the legal.
They don't know anything.
And I'm talking about the people, the professionals
in the field are just as bad.
Okay.
What did we say?
All right, children, what did we say?
If you're going to be, quote unquote, a
famous or important person, right, and you're going
to be dealing with the public, you know
nothing.
You're not allowed to know anything.
Of course.
So do doctors and lawyers and whatever and
professors deal with the public?
Yes.
That means they know nothing.
And if they did know something, and they
spoke to the public who knows nothing...
They wouldn't understand what language they were speaking.
That's why...
That's a guarantee.
Like decades ago.
That's why you can't have education.
People would shut up and say, I don't
know what the hell's going on here.
Well, that's why I find it funny every
once in a while when I'm like, that's
a legitimate piece of information and nobody cares.
They're focusing on everything else, but it's just
hilarious to me because Bill Gates just did
this thing, I just want to tell you,
where he's announcing that he's going to liquidate
his whole fortune to other people before he
dies, basically.
That's what he said.
And I'm like, wow, that's interesting.
Yeah, it's well, because he needs to compensate,
you know, he's not a doctor, but he
was the number one medical advisors from 2020
into 2022, right?
Yeah, well, I mean, half the continent of
Africa...
Who's not a doctor either.
He doesn't even know what an aspirin is.
Well, at least doctors know the drugs, you
know.
Right, half of the continent of Africa got
medicine through the Gates Foundation.
I mean, I'm just saying.
Yeah, they didn't have diabetes or AIDS until
he showed up, right?
That's the other part.
Remember, diabetes and AIDS is caused by the
treatment, right?
It's a fictional diagnosis.
Yeah.
It's pretty sad.
And you'll never, if you get treatment for
any of those, it's just going to get
worse and worse.
So, and we've had some people in the
chat say, oh my gosh, Greek, I fell
for that.
How do I get off of it?
I said, well, I can't, I don't have
direct experience.
I only give information on mostly direct experience,
you know.
So, and I'm not the only one saying
this, that most of the diseases people are
diagnosed with are fictional diagnosis.
And you could tell it's fictional by when
they give you the report.
It doesn't say anything.
Speaking of direct experiences, you and I both
discussed on, I think it was the last
Sonic, these mop-shaped type beings.
Oh yeah, yeah, the attackers.
Yeah, and it caused a couple of comments
to come up.
And I think, you know, they're sort of
right, but they're also sort of wrong.
So the best one, I don't have access
to the Patreon.
I don't do, you know, by the way,
just a little footnote, guys, we meet twice
a week and I just hit say, okay,
hit record.
And that's it.
I don't, I go to the Chitango or
Chilling Creek Chitango because I feel like that's
like a stepchild and a, but I do
go see what activity, but that's it.
I don't know what else is going on.
I don't have a single Sonic downloaded.
I've never heard a single Sonic ever from
this.
I don't even know.
I can't even access them if I wanted
to, I have to get somebody's password or
join myself.
So, but anyway, go ahead.
That's the footnote.
I, I gather all the questions just for,
you know, I gather the questions you're supposed
to do.
Yeah.
And I have Kim administering the, you know,
the, the, the pointless stuff and then I
get the material.
So anyway, Tom wrote this and it's kind
of represents a whole bunch of them.
Okay.
Just letting you know.
The moppings described in dreams are reminiscent of
the ones in Fantasia, according to Tom.
And I'm saying, well, kind of, yeah, but
also no, they're not the same, but the
idea is similar, right?
I mean, I'm checking with you because you
and I both things look like mop things,
but they're as light as dandelions when they
go to seed, right?
It's almost ethereal, ethereal.
It's similar to those things in Fantasia though.
Right.
But it's, it, there's something else different about
them and they are vicious.
I'll tell you that, uh, you know, the,
those, those things on Fantasia, they're dancing, they're
kind of, you know, interesting, hypnotic, but these
are not hypnotically dancing.
These are some vicious creatures, whatever they are.
Yeah.
Like a Star Trek, you know, were you
touched by that thing?
You know?
Oh yeah.
It's that bad.
You don't want it touching you.
I had one land on my arm and
then I had to wake up.
Right.
So, uh, yeah, but, okay, uh, let's do
another question and then we'll jump back to
the robustness of the human condition.
Well, fair enough.
This has to do with the human condition.
Uh, let's see.
I would like to hear some thoughts on
receding gums.
What is the best treatment and what's really
the cause behind it?
Many people seem to have this condition.
Young.
Okay.
Well, the gums are supposed to be soft
and expansive, right?
Because when they're expensive, they'd go to the
base, the gingival edge and all that.
So when you, and you have flexible, as
well, because right.
Well, that's more of the PDL, the periodontal
ligament, but, uh, receding gums is that a
young, uh, contraction for, you know, yin and
yang, you know, the universal principle, it's contracting,
they're contracting, receding, um, and the pulling away.
So you want those to expand.
And, um, one of the ways, uh, I've
done it for a little while with, with
some success and some people really have good
testimonials with what's called oil pulling in the
morning.
You just gargle with don't swallow gargle with
some sesame oil or, um, olive oil or
something like that.
Yeah.
I was very acidic.
Um, look up oil pulling techniques.
The other thing that I know works well
when I was having problems, let's say 10
years ago with that and, uh, citrus, uh,
not juices, uh, industrial, you know, uh, citrus,
if it's a citrus, um, you know, just
cut a slice of orange, put it in
your mouth, chew it and swallow it.
Right.
Uh, citrus is very helpful.
The other thing is like cornbread, cornbread, tortillas,
good cornbread, uh, did I say cornbread?
You did.
Yeah.
The good stuff.
Um, not the GMO.
Um, that's very good for the gums as
well.
And actually when you think of corn, if
you just had a little section of corn,
it looks like teeth, doesn't it?
Going across.
Doesn't it?
It does.
Very interesting.
Yeah.
And the citrus is not the vitamin C
by the way.
No one knows what's in, you know how
they say it's vitamin C then Greek, because
I know nine, nine or 10 people are
going to say that no one knows what's
in an orange dude.
No one knows.
And you're like, that sounds ridiculous on its
face, right?
If you have the indoctrination, how do they
tell you there's these minerals or these acids
or these things are in food?
Do you know what they do?
They take the fruit and they smash it
and then they burn it, heat it into
a powder and then combine other chemicals with
it.
Right.
It sounds like a blood glucose test, right?
Anyway.
Yeah.
And so it's no longer the same thing.
It's no longer, we don't know what's in
an orange, right?
So this is where like someone asked a
question about the nine star key.
It's actually almost 4,000 years of, of
gathering data and compiling it and saying, well,
statistically people who have a left mole on
their left cheek between the side of their
nose and their mouth are not good managers.
They can't manage people.
So it sounds ridiculous, right?
But that's scientifically information gathered, right?
Or the people born around this time, you
know, these things, you know, this is all
information that we've gathered.
We're not, you know, divining anything.
We're dividing.
There's a difference between dividing and divining.
So that would be the receding gum thing.
The other thing is avoid animal and avoid
salts, but salts, there are salts that are
healing and salts that are not, and are
damaging.
The commercial salts are damaging typically.
The healing salts are the natural salts.
And I wouldn't do, there's a big thing
about Himalayan salt that comes from land.
Sea salt is much more beneficial than that
pink.
There's a big craze about the pink.
Red and pink.
Right, right.
Yeah, that I find to be harsh and
I don't find it to have healing properties.
It might have healing properties if it's combined
with something to turn it around because it's
very powerful.
But the quality sea salt would help.
And by the way, years ago, even now,
if you have a tooth pulled or whatever,
the dentist gives you, it says rinse with
warm salt water, right?
Yeah, I've always done that.
Yeah, yeah.
And that would actually help.
But ingesting it in your food will contract
the gums.
And it's also, being in the gums, the
upper part of the body, that's where all
the yin, the expansive things rush to.
So if you're having a contractive stuff happening
on the upper body, it's usually an irritation.
So it's good to find in your diet
what's irritating you, right?
In other words, if you know you're sensitive
to something, remove that from your diet and
that would probably help.
But fewer animal products also help, I've noticed.
But the oil pulling, just look up online
what oil pulling is for dental health, let's
say dental fitness, right?
And citrus also helps, and corn also helps,
eating corn.
Not necessarily, it could be corn flour, however
you take it, cornbread.
Just do a little regimen of that and
you should have a stabilization.
Very rarely do they grow back, but you'll
slow it down.
Right.
I had a neurosurgeon talk to me about
the use of hot and cold for different
effects for this as well.
Sure.
So what are your thoughts on that?
Well, avoid hot and cold.
You want to have moderate temperature in the
mouth.
There's a reason why, oh, that's too cold
on my teeth, or that's too hot in
my mouth.
There's a reason for that.
Well, doing healing, you definitely want me to
be moderate about it, but sometimes if there
was an issue, like if you end up
with a dry socket or whatever, right?
Oh, dry, oh, that's horrible, yeah.
Most people do if they don't, yeah.
So the use of hot and cold, I
forget how it went, because I was always
careful not to get the damn dry socket,
because I didn't want to go through that.
Yeah, dry socket also comes if they don't
clean out the PDL, or the best way
to lose a tooth is a tooth that's
just rotten and has high mobility and comes
out easily because the PDL's been dissolved by
the body, but yeah, it's the PDL mostly.
Most dentists don't even clean the socket.
They just pull the tooth and send you
on your way.
There are some that do, some that do,
but yeah.
I advise people, I say, my so-and
-so's going to the dentist, what should I
say?
They say, well, what are they going for?
Make sure, and then when they bring this
up, like what I mentioned, they should advise
the dentist is usually very surprised and pretty
happy about it, usually, that you know this
stuff, and you say, yeah, I'll do my
best, right?
So you've got to watch these guys.
When you're dealing with people in law, oh,
that's the worst, or medical stuff, you better
know exactly what you want, I mean, down
to the T, and then have the reason
you're going to them is because you can't
do it yourself for some reason, right?
Just like when you get a haircut, right?
Don't you tell them exactly what you want,
typically?
Oh, yeah.
You know?
Yeah, I mean, so it's very much, think
of it, you know, the typical thing, take
a little off the top, more off the
sides, whatever, you know, it's the same thing
when you go to a legal or, heaven
forbid, oh, my gosh, I almost, my legs
got shaky, if you ever, don't, ugh, if
you ever have to go to an attorney
for anything, I mean, oh, my gosh, that's
like, ugh, that's like really gross, but anyway,
I understand the doctor part, right?
Because you may not be able to pull
something out of your butt on your own,
but, you know, whatever, and don't look, because
there's a lot of people that go for
that kind of stuff, like polyps and all
that, you don't even need, that's dietary change,
you can, those things disappear within days if
you change your diet properly, or you know
how to balance it out, those things usually
get worse.
You wouldn't believe, I know at least three
people whose mom was, you know, 60s, 70s,
and she had a small growth on her
foot, and then they removed the growth, it
got worse, and they had to remove her
foot, and then they had to remove it
to the knee, and then they had to
remove it to her thigh, then they had
to remove her lung, and then she died.
Right.
So some things need to be done internally,
they do too much use of surgery and
chemistry, because I know three people, over the
past three decades, that have given me a
story like that.
Right.
You know, I'm talking about a little tiny
growth or whatever, and you know, they end
up dying within a year, and anyway, and
I think I mentioned I had a doctor
client, and he parked his three-car garage,
all cars were always outside, not in the
garage, and one day, he invites me into
the house, and he couldn't park the cars
in the garage, because there were banker's boxes
full of documents, mostly lawsuits, filling the space
that three cars would fill.
So, just wanted to let you know.
No problem.
Listen, about water quality, somebody asked something, now,
they're kind of behind, because they could have
gotten in on the aqueous argentum thing earlier,
but anyway, I was listening to an older
podcast where Greek talks about what he calls
aqueous argentum.
Right, because it's not colloidal silver, right?
Yes.
How easy is it to learn how to
make it for someone who knows nothing about
it?
I would like to dive into it.
Well, it depends on your sensibilities.
The simplest way to explain it is everything
that's online about making colloidal silver is BS.
Don't do it.
It's toxic.
I have to side with the FDA on
that.
Regardless of the testimonials, it's toxic.
As a matter of fact, a lot of
the pharmaceuticals are known to be toxic, sometimes
do work, right?
So, the aqueous argentum is, you want to
use a biological form of electricity which would
be less than one and a half volts
across the two electrodes.
If you can't do that, you put a
neutral electrode, use three electrodes, the center electrode
is not attached to anything, it's spaced very
nicely, or very well, and just the outer
two electrodes are.
I personally make a unit that plugs into
a USB, I've posted the circuit on the
Chitango, I've posted what it looks like, and
all that.
I can't make them now.
I can, but I won't.
I think it was $200 for one, and
if you gave me $400, I wouldn't make
one.
It's just that much time.
But at least you got to see what
a well-crafted unit should look like.
We actually did a giveaway of one.
I don't know what I was thinking, but
yeah, we are benevolent.
We did a giveaway of one of these
units, by the way.
Right, and we had a lot of reports,
you wouldn't mind me using his name, Joe,
I don't know if he's around anymore, but
he was sharing it with his family in
his neighborhood, and they had a lot of
positive results.
But basically the idea is, go study how
to make colloidal silver, but don't use any
of the voltages that they suggest, it should
be less than one and a half volts.
Now a typical battery cell, single cell, whether
it's A, triple A, double A, C, D,
sounds like bra sizes, right?
Anyway, make sure when you're out of the
package, they're 1.7 volts.
Just use it a little bit until the
voltage gets down to 1.5 or 1
.3 is even better.
Closer to one is even better if you
have a high mineral content in your water,
and that's it, and just a few minutes,
if not less than a minute.
Joe was grateful enough that he told me,
and nobody has asked a question like this
in a long time, but he told me
a while ago, if this person who asked
the question wants to get in touch with
me, let me know on the chat on
the Patreon, and I will put you in
touch with Joe, because Joe was willing to
make some, and even explain stuff to somebody.
So we could pass this along, and he
said that he was grateful that he would
be willing to pass it along to somebody
else if they asked.
So this is the first time somebody asked,
there you go.
Let me know, and I will put you
in touch with Joe.
That's fine.
Joe has the unit that I built, so...
And also, he's mechanically inclined enough that I
bet you they could reproduce one if they
wanted to.
Well, the circuit is potted, so you need
the diagram for the circuit, which I've posted.
And if anyone sends me an email regarding
this, actually I shouldn't put my time out
like that, but I will, UncommonSenseRadio1 at gmail
.com.
If you want to, just send it to
me once, and I'll keep it.
Yeah, I'll send you the images and the
circuit, because the circuit is an interesting...
I call it proprietary, because I'm making a
very simple junction, also incorporating the LED.
The LED and the circuit lets you know
if it's working, because if it's not in
the water, the LED is off, and when
you put it in the water and you
have proper power, the LED comes on as
an indicator.
It's kind of a neat thing.
So what you do is just pass it
to me as your administrator, I'll know it.
I'll do that tonight.
I'll drop the blueprint for that.
There we go.
So I will have the blueprint.
If you are inclined enough to create it,
no problem.
Then you can.
Yeah.
All right.
Yeah, let's go back to the robustness of
the human before I run out of steam.
Well, just one last piece, then, and then
we'll be all cleared up, as far as
I'm concerned, I think.
Yes, I'd like to agree to comment, if
we can cast him out...
Oh, this is back to the mop creature
thing.
Okay, just let me...
Oh, okay.
If we can cast him out for good,
probably not for good, but does he do
any daily cleansing of entities to declutter?
This is a big part of shamanic culture
to psychopomp, psychopomp, I guess, yeah, that's the
word.
No, not daily.
Yeah, good.
No, it's constantly.
You have to train yourself to do it
constantly.
An example would be, people spend a lot
of time on a computer, you walk up
and look at the screen, you see they
have a lot of bookmarks, things open, tabs
open?
Yeah.
And they're always like that.
Okay, you open a tab on keeping these
things and being conscious of them, and it's
constantly on, just like when they talk about
prayer, you know, the Christian thing, you get
down and you're always in the constant state
of that.
It's a way to relate.
It's kind of like, imagine you've got to
change water pump in a car and watch
a National Geographic video on Alaska at the
same time.
Can you do that?
Can you put two videos on at the
same time and take in information from both?
So it's not easy, but it's simple, right?
I'm not talking about playing two songs at
the same time that kind of don't work.
I'm talking about two separate things.
So what happens in the beginning, you have
your normal you, usual self, but in the
background, you're constantly running this awareness scheme around
you.
And sometimes you highlight it, like if you're
going to do something important in a room,
this is a Walter Russell thing, you go
in the room, tell them to get out
and then slam the door, make a gesture,
or with your hand, make a gesture out,
you know, you know that sweeping hand where
your hand goes above your shoulders and you
sweep down towards the floor out, right?
Make these gestures and they will follow.
Remember, in most cases, they're envious of us
being in a three in this physical body,
even though they know we are limited.
It's kind of like people watching someone that's
sitting in a Formula One race car, you
know how limited you are sitting in a
Formula One race car, but people are envious
of it, right?
You see?
So you're in this incredible situation, condition, you're
so limited in comparison, and anyone who's in
this physical world who just wants to be,
I wish I was a spirit or whatever
is really missing out.
There's a difference, you know, the physical experience.
Now, a lot of times I say I've
had enough and I've had enough, just like
if I walk into someone takes me to
a movie, I'm famous for this, by the
way, because I worked in film and I
know what a good film is, within the
first minute or two minutes, if I see
this is going to be a piece of
shit movie, I say, I'll be back.
Enjoy the movie.
I walk out and usually movie theaters are
not in the middle of nowhere, right?
You can walk around the mall, you can
walk around for two hours or hour and
a half, right?
I do that.
So I'm like, if I go to a
party or I got to go, you know,
and I'll tell them why the food is
not as is not what I expected, you
know, and nothing to the host or whatever.
This is a way of saying things.
Everyone has their own way, you know, just
to excuse yourself.
It's fine to excuse yourself.
And it's okay to excuse yourself from this
reality, right?
But to want to be just a spirit,
I think you're missing out, missing the point
of being in a physical body.
But anyway, no, there's no way to, there's
no daily thing.
It's a constant thing.
That's the aorist tense is, is a tense
and aorist in, in literature and it means
it's a constant thing.
So that would be that.
Okay.
Fair enough.
So I guess we should just get back
to the robustness and close out with that.
Definitely.
Because, oh yeah.
I think, yeah, this is just like a
coaching session because, you know, people, you know,
we're so, I include myself up until later
in life, well actually until the eighties, when
you needed a subject matter, always any subject
matter that had a quote unquote professional field
attached to it was where you should go.
If it was legal, you get a lawyer,
a doctor, you get this, right, whatever, right?
Spiritually go to a priest and you tell
him whatever you have marital problems, he says,
oh, just get her together and bake cookies.
Right.
Well, you know, stupid shit.
These people don't, you know, they're, they're lost.
Both people are lost.
Remember when you have these professionals, whatever professional
you want to pick, did they come from
Jupiter or Mars or a series or some
other planet or are they humans came from
here?
Yeah.
From here.
So it can't be good if you're paying
attention, you know, so it doesn't mean they're
bad, but they're definitely not good.
That's one thing that I always bring up,
you know, does it, does it make these
people at Catholics?
Are they bad people?
Well, no.
Here's the thing about being Catholic.
You're either totally ignorant of the Bible in
history, which makes you ignorant, or you know
what's going on.
You're just an evil son of a bitch
pushing the thing.
Right.
So does that mean they're bad people?
No, but they ain't good.
That's for sure.
So you, you can not be good and
not be bad.
It's just this gray mat.
It's called gray, gray water.
It's like this lesser lesser of two evils
concept.
They always throw at you.
It's a lesser of two evils, but it's
still an evil, right?
It's a lesser, but there are bad doctors
and there are bad attorneys that are, there
are some pretty good, you know, there are
attorneys that scour whatever to steal from people's
public records.
That's their thing.
You know, they won't admit it, but it's
pretty common.
And there are scumbags, but yeah, every, every
death camp in throughout history in the 20th
century was headed by a doctor, a doctor.
Yeah.
It's a fact.
Every death camp, you know, when you go
to a Walmart and they got a picture
of the manager on the wall, right?
Or the state department, they got a picture
of the president on the wall.
Every death camp had a picture.
I'm just saying the metaphor of the doctor
who runs the thing, right?
So anyway, we're so brainwashed to go to
these things, right?
You have to treat them.
If you're going to go to these things,
these professionals, the way they act and what
they purvey in society is almost as if
they are a predatory species and they are
predatory without them even knowing it most of
the time is the way you would go
to a hair cutter.
You tell them like they ask you, so
how would you, what would you like the
same as the last time, you know, or
how do you, or the first time going
to a hair cutter, this is how I'd
like you bring a picture, right?
You bring a picture of a magazine, right,
or whatever.
So if you're going to go to a
doctor lawyer, you bring the code, you got
to know the laws with the lawyer.
He won't know any of that, by the
way, I assure you.
And the doctor, he'll be shocked because I
haven't seen anything like that since college, even
though I've been practicing for 25 years, you
know, because they do give some things, you
know, some procedures in college and all that.
So you're going to have to do more
studying.
So that means no Netflix.
Well, you know, Oh no, no.
Greek says no Netflix.
No.
Well, less Netflix, less cop shows, less sitcoms,
but I don't do any of that.
Well, less of what you're doing.
That is not what I just mentioned that
you might need to know less of whatever
you have plenty of time.
You know, typically if you're going to have
a medical procedure done, it's not like tomorrow.
It's not, you know, if you're ambulatory or
whatever, it's usually a month or so.
So start researching it.
Don't trust these mother effers, right at all.
Trust no man is a, is a maximum,
isn't it?
Right.
So going back to the robustness to break
away and you, you're going to have to
be a DIY or in everything here, because
you know, you know how I give advice,
don't go live out off the grid.
We should be living in a city, a
harmonious city.
And most people that have lived off the
grid came back and said, yeah, man.
But the problem is you have to create
a harmonious.
So the city is a jungle in a
way, because the way it's set up, we
have predators at the top of the elite
social ladder.
We're predated on, we're basically treated like cattle,
you know, head count comes from cattle, only
cattle have had, and they do that in
schools, prisons, whatever.
So you're being treated as cattle.
And once you know that you're going to
have to be a little more of a
DIY or sort of like in between suburban
urban and living out in the country, like
grizzly Adams, I don't know if people are
old enough.
You don't even know grizzly.
Adam is looking up.
Right.
I remember those from the 70s, I think.
Yeah.
So you're going to have to you can't
be convenient, right?
No, nothing is convenient.
And you're going to find joy in it.
If you have hobbies, I feel sorry for
you.
That means you've fallen down the trap.
There's not enough time in the day, the
week, the month or the year to learn
what you should have learned when you were
a child.
So scrap your hobbies.
You know, whatever that might be.
Your hobby is a waste of time.
Everything is a waste of time.
But you're going to need to focus on
all the things that are necessary in life
for yourself, your family and the people around
you, which is learning law, learning medical stuff.
I'm sorry.
And such as both are such a distraction,
learning about how things really work and learning
how to do things, fix things, make things
right.
Your hobbies are a waste of time.
Does that mean that?
Well, like if you play golf, forget it.
You're an idiot.
It's such a waste of time.
That's a purely.
Yes.
If you play golf or whatever, because it's
in certain circles, that's where the meetings are
done.
Right.
And you get to know people for business
there.
Yeah.
But practicing that is stupid and it is
a very stupid thing, especially now the way
things are.
You should be more supportive of the people
around you.
And how are you going to support them
if you know nothing?
And if you think you have an education
on anything, you know nothing.
You're all a bunch of memes and what
do you call it, cliches and all this
stuff.
And trusting to these professional morons that there
is not enough time in the day, the
week, the month or the year to learn
what you should have learned by the age
of nine or ten, which is how the
body works, how the law of things work,
both natural and man's law.
Your spirituality has nothing to do with these
religions at all.
Spirituality is your mindset, having a clean, sharp
mind that you can apply wisdom, knowing what's
wrong or right.
There are wrongs and rights.
There's maxims of law you need to study.
So when I have run into people, I've
had years ago, have meetings like Skype and
call and say, oh, I'm playing golf tomorrow,
but, you know, practicing, you're an idiot.
Golf.
Are you kidding?
There's not enough time in the day, the
month, the year or the week to learn
about anything.
These hobbies need to go away.
Now it's different than if you're doing it
because you appreciate a certain level of fitness
like running or cycling or swimming.
I'm not saying don't do that, but don't
go to a freaking swimming camp with some
idiots over the whole weekend to go do
whatever.
It's a waste of time.
Right.
Now, does it sound like I have a
sense of urgency in my voice?
Yeah, because that's how things really are when
you wake up.
Now, even when you sleep, don't you want
to sleep comfortably?
And I'm telling you, most of the stuff
that people waste their time with will bring
you into very inconvenient situations because you'll be
more trusting of these people that know nothing.
No, they don't know more than you do.
They have the appearance of knowing a doctor
and a lawyer have the appearance of knowing
more than you do, but they don't.
And because they all operate in the same
thing, ask them whatever and they answer the
same.
They have to tell you what's on CNN.
That's all they're taught.
Now, the robustness of the human body.
Also, this is a segue that was more
like the mental part.
The more of a segue I'm going to
get into hygiene.
Hygiene means actually, yeah, you know, it actually
means health and well-being.
The means well-being generally.
And I notice there's a big problem with
that with people because of the chemical age,
your cleaners and the way you live in
your abode and all that stuff.
There's something called outgassing.
And I'm going to bounce around here.
You ever walk down a supermarket aisle?
And even if you were blindfolded, you know
what aisle you're on by the smell.
You ever walk down the cleaner aisle?
It burns your eyes, right?
Aren't all those bottles sealed in the supermarket?
Well, they are.
They're just about as sealed there as they're
going to be when you bring them home.
And they're actually going to be less sealed
once you bring them home and start using
them and close them up again.
Right, right.
That's what's happening in your house.
You're being like homeopathically poisoned by these poisons,
petrochemical stuff.
Right.
So what I suggest to people, besides the
point, if you live in one of these
what I call ticky tacky stick and mud
houses that are built here in America since
the 80s, all that material that they're sheathing
the house with, you know, sticks and mud,
they put up these sticks, two by fours,
and they put plywood, the particle board on
the outside.
Then they put the, you know, the licum
stick and bricks.
Right, right.
You know, peel and stick bricks or whatever
they're doing.
OK, that's 20 percent formaldehyde.
What's formaldehyde?
I'm not going to get into that.
Go look at the particle board.
It's 20 percent, 15 percent formaldehyde.
You're living in an embalming chamber.
So if you live in a modern house
less than 40 years old, you must have
windows open no matter how cold, not all
the way open, just slightly open.
Now, as a matter of fact, anyone who
lives in one of these ticky tacky houses,
subdivisions or whatever, will know that if you
have more than one story on the top
floor, this looks like a bathroom vent fan
that's always running to create a negative pressure.
So these chemicals go out and people don't
start dropping dead because some people are more
like a canary in the coal mine.
Right.
So, yeah, anybody who who hears this and
has that will be like, oh, shit, what
do I do?
Move.
Anyway, you're going to need to ventilate those
spaces.
That's part of hygiene.
The other thing is washing.
A lot of the soaps were much worse
in the 70s and things like that.
Soaps are getting a little milder with the
chemicals that are in them.
Minimal soap.
Your focus on hygiene is your face, your
armpits, your groin and your feet.
Now, in terms of hygiene for your personal
body, I'm going to jump back to your
living space for your maybe I'll jump back
to living space right now.
So I remember when I was dictating these
things back in the 80s, I walk into
someone's kitchen.
I could smell the chemical stuff.
What you do is you put all the
chemical cleaners you have, laundry detergents under the
sink.
Usually they go bathroom sink under the bathroom,
under the kitchen sink or in a side
closet.
Put them all together in a box.
If you have chlorine and ammonia, separate them
because together they become mustard gas, by the
way.
They go into what I call the chemical
closet chemical box.
Keep it on the freaking fire escape if
you have to keep it out of your
environment.
Find a space if you live in an
apartment in someone else's apartment, right?
Uh huh.
So in the basement or a little storage
room, keep all that shit out from where
you live, not in the same living space
or near a window, but a window that
you're not relying on fresh air, a window
that was more like sending the air out
like a vented area.
Yeah.
So if you have a real like leaky
house where it's kind of like, you know,
you have, you know, you don't have gaskets
in the window, keep these things near a
place where they could be vented away from
your living space.
It's very important.
And the hygiene also, what do you use
for cleaning plain water?
Basic soaps like Borax, the natural dishwashing liquid.
Make sure you have hydrogen peroxide in a
spray bottle.
It has to be.
You just use the same bottle that comes
in.
Hydrogen peroxide exposed to light is worthless within
three days.
It's as a lower pH.
It's a very strong oxidizer.
You know that oxy clean stuff.
All it is is citric acid or on
hydrogen peroxide and some reaction.
Right.
So hydrogen peroxide is an overall cleaner.
If you have pets, things like that, you
know, whatever pet pee, baby vomit, whatever oxidizes,
cleans, make sure you use a plastic bag
and paper towels to pick it up.
Don't put your hands in it.
You know, wrap the plastic bag around your
hand.
Right.
And keep those things.
So basically, your cleaning supplies should be minimized.
And heaven forbid you're buying like Johnson and
Johnson or Procter & Gamble cleaning products.
Heaven forbid.
Right.
Make your own rubbing alcohol in a spray
bottle is an amazing degreaser and cleaner.
Amazing.
It's actually an industry.
Alcohol is a necessity as a degreaser for
parts and things like that.
So learn how to use that.
I don't know if I've done a sonic.
That's your basic hygiene, ventilating your space, keeping
yourself clean.
Now, going back to keeping yourself clean is
the main thing about hygiene is face, armpits,
groin.
Now, this is like I don't know if
anyone here is listening from a country where
it's not popular to take showers.
I live with these two French twins.
She looked like Catherine Beta, Beta Jones.
And when I saw Catherine Beta Jones in
the early days in the 80s, I saw
her on TV.
I said, oh, they finally made it to
Hollywood.
And I was Catherine Beta Jones.
Well, I knew these twins look just like
her.
Actually, they were fraternal.
One was shorter than the other.
And what's interesting is one time we're having
dinner and one of them's like, it's Saturday,
let's say.
And she goes, I'm going to take a
shower on Tuesday.
Like it's big news.
Right.
And I'm like, that's weird because I take
a shower in the morning and I take
a shower at night every day.
Right.
And they thought I was weird.
So anyway.
There are places where people don't wash and
but when they do wash, they're concerned about
the areas that I mentioned, face, armpits, groin
and then feet.
Even in the Bible, washed his feet because
they had sandals.
They had boots also, but they're not mentioned.
So those are the main concerns.
So when you want to save water, you
have minimal water.
You live on a submarine or whatever.
You got a 30 second shower.
That's how you target yourself.
Right.
Face, you know, hands, of course, hands first,
then face, then armpits, groin, feet.
Now, one little thing here, because I've run
into people that were in the military and
various.
So when you change environment, right.
Like, for example, there was someone who was
a colonel in the army and he stayed
in Korea.
When he came back, he had like a
fungal infection on his fingernails between his fingers.
And they blamed it on Americans coming back,
you know, from Korea had that as like
the fungus that's measured, by the way, is
created by your own body.
Right.
Yeah, that's that's amazing because I think you
have to catch everything from something else.
When they pull blood from someone and they
got TB in the blood, that TB did
not come from someone else and entered your
bloodstream.
Your body created that just like the replicator
on Star Trek creates whatever, you know, chocolate
pudding.
Yeah.
So anyway, this is beyond that.
But they found like erythromycin and various things
like that to be effective on it.
And he would put it on his hands
and he says, I think I need to
change the prescription to something stronger.
And I said, well, are you putting it
on your wrists also?
I said, but it's not on my wrists.
And I said, yes, I know that this
is all about energy.
When you treat your hands, rub a little
bit on your wrist, which is one of
the strongest energy points in the body, by
the way, go around the entire wrist like
a bracelet.
Right.
Guess what?
A week later, as I've been doing this
for six months and now I did a
thing on the wrist and a week it's
gone.
But I'm going to keep going because I
don't want to come back.
So fine.
But you notice when you do it on
your OK, now people that have itchy feet,
do they put medication on their feet for
whatever they put it on their toe, on
the nail or the heel, whatever is specific.
Right.
But it says it put topically on the
area affected.
Right.
You should put it around your ankle as
well, even though the ankle is not affected.
The ankle is a very powerful energetic area.
Remember, once you understand these things are emergence,
they're created by your body, even though they're
measurable as being foreign and someone else doesn't
have.
Yes, they're on your body because your body
made them.
Just like an example.
You know, the microscopic view of people's skin,
these little mites that look like sci fi
monsters.
Right.
And some people freak out and keep taking
showers to get rid of them.
Actually, the heat and water makes them grow
even more.
They come from your body, produces them.
They're not jumping off something like the idiot
medical people.
You know, they'll say, well, it must have
come from this or that.
They cannot fathom in their mind that your
body nature is so incredible.
Right.
So again, the ankles and the wrists are
very strong, energetic points, transfer of energy because
they're always bent.
Right.
What I mean by that is in the
human flow, the flow of the human body,
when you lock out your arm and your
fingers straight ahead, your energy slows down.
It's not like plumbing.
You know, you have a straight pipe.
It runs through faster.
No.
When you bend your joints, the energy moves
through much more freely, I should say, and
more energy moves through.
And that's why, like in the Matrix, when
Neil puts his hands up and his palm
backwards, oh, that's how you cut the energy
off to your hand.
Right.
The way you bring energy to your hand
is by limp wrist position forward fingers slightly.
All the joints are slightly bent.
That's you can even do that exercise.
The wrists and the ankles are typically bent,
constantly moving.
And they're always in a non locked out
position.
That's why people with back problems, when you
stand, let's say if you're standing, you know,
cooking, washing dishes or at work, I bet
your knees are locked out.
I never thought of that.
Unlock your knees.
They're like, oh, no, now it feels like
I have to support my weight with your
muscles.
Right.
Yeah.
It's kind of tiring.
Yeah, exactly.
Learn how to do that.
And then when you do lock out your
knees, it'll be in a more beneficial position.
It could take up to a month to
train yourself to stand with your knees not
locked out.
Right.
It's amazing with the healing powers of just
doing something like that, because, again, it's a
it's an area where energy will flow better.
So now I sound like one of these
energy airy fairy types.
No, these these things that I'm telling you
are experienced facts that work in almost all
or most cases, most or all cases.
So with hygiene, when you're treating the hands
and treating the feet, you have to do
the ankles and the wrists.
Why?
Because the Greeks said so.
Right.
So do an experiment with that.
When you wash your hands, wash your wrists.
You know, surgeons, you know, they scrub to
the elbow.
Right.
As a matter of fact, they're so afraid
of bugs that the the valves are controlled
below the waist.
Right.
You know, a hospital sink.
So a surgeon in surgery.
So these things are integrated within the concept
of why you're doing things.
So let's say you run into someone who
is putting topical ointment on their feet.
Suggest that they also wrap it around, put
it on their ankles all the way around
like a bracelet, right where on the ankle,
you know, where the joint is.
I mean, you want to get anatomically just
around where the leg meets the foot, where
the hand meets the the forearm for the
wrist.
And you'll notice a massive improvement.
That is also part of hygiene or well
-being.
Right.
And by the way, no one is discussing
this.
And I've never heard it discussed.
And it works so well.
So the other thing with hygiene, of course,
will ultimately is your food intake.
And I don't know if I'm going to
be doing a food seminar.
I would like to.
And if I don't, we'll just start hammering
it here for the subs.
Yeah, it'll be stuff that you've never heard
of before.
And it'd be easy.
Again, the food intake is very important.
The food seminar seminars when you're in person,
it would be a webinar.
Or a sonic, it would be actually I
would reduce it to a sonic.
Excuse me, because it wouldn't be that hardcore.
People that were around for the financial stuff
for the weather work webinar, they did notice
I was pretty hardcore on that.
It was three, three hour sessions just to
get into the subject, just to get into
the subject, a working knowledge, a basic working
knowledge.
I would have to do three nine hour
sessions to get to the point.
All right.
We'll see 27 hours at least to become
familiar.
We're in the we're not talking Q&A
now in the three hour thing.
Very little Q&A.
But this is what it takes to learn.
You know, like everything they teach in school,
even university, you could learn in two or
three years, but they spread it out for
12.
Why?
Because they have to waste your time.
Right.
They know it.
So and you know it, too, and you
don't mind it.
Right.
Because how do I know?
Because you stayed there.
Right.
No one ran away and said, I can't
take it anymore.
I'm sure there are.
Hopefully there are some people here that left
after the eighth grade or before the eighth
grade.
Oh, my gosh, that's great.
You know, you get a medal for that,
right?
Screw the GED.
I saw people, by the way, you know,
they can't get out of school till 14
or whatever, and then they give them a
hard time.
Take the GED at 11.
I can teach an 11 or 12 year
old how to pass the GED with flying
colors very quickly.
As a matter of fact, they actually give
you last year's test.
This year's test is slightly modified.
You're guaranteed an 85 by just doing the
previous tests.
Right.
So if you're paying attention, you've seen that
was last year's test.
Well, what do you think this year's test
is going to be like?
Right.
Yeah.
So slightly modified version.
So you just play around.
So the intellectual side is also part of
the robustness.
Right.
Can you take a hint like one thing
now?
It's always been the same way, but it's
coming at you faster as propaganda.
How do you know you're being propaganda?
You see all the media outlets repeating the
same thing constantly.
And it does it with no they tell
you it's science.
They tell you it's facts, but there are
it's completely devoid of science and facts.
And usually it sounds like it's breaking the,
quote unquote, laws of nature or physical laws.
It sounds like an impossibility.
And you see this propaganda all over and
over.
And right now, you know what the propaganda
is financial.
We're going to have a financial crash.
Things are going to go bad.
Well, no, they're not.
It's going to be quite the opposite.
You're going to have a blip in the
fall because that's when all financial hiccups happen.
Right.
But yeah, so I just brought that up
as an example.
So that's the robustness of the human condition.
Imagine the amount of propaganda that's been put
on people to make them do things.
And they actually come through it.
Right.
And they look back at it, whether it's
the world, what they call the World War
conflicts or whatever.
And the 9-11, COVID, whatever.
Same, same stuff, same programming.
By the way, what you saw, the propaganda
that you saw for COVID and 9-11
of the terror terrorism is exactly the same
propaganda that they did for World War Two
and World War One.
Exactly the same, the same script.
Well, different subject matter, obviously.
But the reason people don't see it is
because most of it's been washed away.
Like, for example, if you try to research
and do a documentary on the propaganda that
was put out for COVID, you're going to
have a hard time.
Most of it's been washed away and not
not stored.
I mean, I'm sure like the CNN tapes
are there somewhere, but you won't get access
to them anymore.
Right.
All this, the propaganda and the BS they
did for 9-11.
You're going to have a hard time if
you did a documentary on just the propaganda
aspect.
Right.
What was put forward?
You're going to have a hard time.
They don't preserve it very well.
Fortunately, I was able to actually hold in
my hand newspapers, live newspapers from the period
of World War Two.
And I was like, what a bunch of
bullshit.
I was exposed to this in the 80s.
And when I started seeing the propaganda, I
was like, oh, this is like the stuff
they did in World War Two.
And people look at me like I was
crazy.
What are you talking about?
World War Two?
That was the greatest generation.
No, shut up.
Right.
I'm like, oh, my gosh, you don't know
the protests and all this stuff.
That's all that's hidden.
You don't get that.
Right.
But the 9-11 and the COVID was
so shameful that they're not going to say
that's the greatest generation we came through because
of the vaccine.
Right.
And by the way, I'll leave it off
with this.
According to stuff that's been studies have been
done actually in the 20s and 30s about
vaccines, and they were null and void.
Right.
But then they picked it up again in
the 30s, 40s and 50s with the polio,
which was the DDT spray, the bug spray.
Right.
People don't know that most mainstream towns in
America, for some reason it happens and it
comes in cycles.
People would be out on Main Street shopping.
And suddenly the sky gets dark with houseflies
sweeping down on people, biting them.
And the people start saying, why is this
happening?
We need some help.
So the government had the smart idea or
the municipalities, not the government.
These tanks of DDT and various other mixtures
like that and fumigating, they're called it the
public.
Right.
And they didn't care.
People and then suddenly young children, even old
people couldn't walk.
And they said it was a polio virus.
Right.
Soon.
And there's actually a woman that wrote a
book about this.
It's called Spring Something.
Right.
About the DDT spraying.
There was no less than 10 or 15
doctors that testified in Congress about banning DDT
because it's paralyzing people.
And then the other side of the medical
things, we have a vaccine for this thing
called polio.
So polio.
Right.
And this thing came up also recently in
Brazil about 10 years ago.
The Zika or something.
Babies that couldn't walk because they had a
mosquito problem.
They were spraying DDT.
There's no Zika virus.
They were spraying.
They were fumigating DDT at night and the
children couldn't walk.
And they said it was a Zika virus.
Oh, my gosh.
The same stupidity.
This is like if you lived in a
real world, the people pushing this would be
hung and celebrated that they were hung, right?
Or shot, you know, whatever.
And it's it's called the what's it called?
The one bullet thing.
You know, they tell you deliberately miss.
You know, you go and get shoot at
the firing squad.
It's a one bullet.
No reload.
It's called a no reload.
Yeah.
Everybody's you have a deniability.
You know, that person suffers.
Yeah.
You shoot him in the leg, the arm.
So he's got to be tied to the
stake for eight hours where he bleeds out.
I mean, this is the stuff that we're
done to get back at people like this.
We you know, we don't have that kind
of stuff anymore, but I'm sure it is
in private.
I mean, they did suffocate that Scalia judge
with a pillow when he was at that
sex ranch in Texas about a decade ago.
But anyway, keep your thoughts, keep your opinions
to yourself, Greek.
Right.
Yeah.
So the vaccine thing I've been studying that
and the idea with that is no confusion
in order for it to be legitimate.
You need a blood type to be considered
your weight to be considered your gender, your
race to be considered and your age.
Mm hmm.
Or you can go the rock and roll
style.
I said, did you get the rock and
roll shot?
And they're like, what do you mean by
rock and roll shot?
I said, you know, when you go to
a rock and roll concert and they sell
shirts outside, one size fits all.
Remember?
Yeah.
That's why I call it the rock and
roll shot.
OK, so I think they'll wrap it up
for.