Rated Y, Sonic Event 196, how you doing,
Greek?
How I'm doing, let's do it.
You got some questions?
Yeah, let's do it.
Okay, so I got things from the chat.
I got stuff from the Patreon, so we'll
hit it all as quick and as best
as we can.
So, Greek, when you mentioned the inner voice
change-up, can screw up, is being double,
does the confusion go beyond God to life
partner?
Okay, you know what they're asking you?
I didn't get that one.
Yeah, they're kind of asking, okay, they're trying
to confuse you, but are they trying to
influence the things around you, like your partner,
other people in your life?
Yeah, I'll stop right there without getting into
more stuff that I've gotten into.
So I posted two videos in the, it's
Ocelli and the Greek Chitango, right?
Yeah, it's Ocelli and the Greek Rated Y.
OcelliandtheGreekChitango.com.
Yeah.
Dot Chitango dot com.
Website, I mean, a YouTube channel, everybody should
check out.
It's simple, it's called Lookout for Charlie, and
it's Lookout F.A., and then Charlie.
And he's been recording, he's an audio guy.
Okay.
And he's been looking at, you know, ambient
noise, you know, when you record it.
And he gets in there and he filters
out the common denominator, and there's voices.
There's always voices in the background, and he
has a spin on it and all that.
And what the thing that makes it so
profound, what he's doing, is that they react
to you.
So in other words, if you're hammering or
there's a dog barking, those voices get slightly
larger.
They adjust, and they're aimed at individuals.
And they're not, quote unquote, like the typical
used word, nice.
They're usually very negative.
And these things exist, and he's been finding
them in old movies.
It's not a new thing, like with harp
and all that, even though he does bring
that up.
Right.
It's part of the artificial intelligence, the A
.I. that runs everything here doing that.
So the voices in your head, okay, that
I talk about are different, but are they
really?
How many times have you heard me say,
you don't see with your eyes, you see
with your brain.
You don't hear with your ears, you hear
You don't taste with your tongue, you taste
with your brain.
So everything, these are sensors, and sensors are,
what good are sensors without a controller?
So in essence, we're talking about the same
thing.
He believes that they're 100% man-made,
which I believe they are too, because if
you heard me say, the gods are men,
which is the, and the more, okay, the
more, let's just say radical whistleblowers tell you
that they meet these beings that call themselves
gods, and they're just people with tech.
Right.
How many times have I been saying that
for?
I've been saying that for decades.
Yeah, and I actually heard that a long
time ago from some very strange old man
that seemed oddly legit, even though they kind
of sounded crazy, even back then.
Oh, that's a good person to listen to.
That's usually the guy, you should listen, because
one way or another, even if they are
crazy, you're going to learn something.
Well, they're crazy based on what?
Well, but that's the thing.
Right now, I'm at the point where I
see pretty much everyone around me as being
crazy.
Well, right, but that's my point, is that
throw that away, and try and learn from
what you're observing, is all I'm saying.
It's kind of like, you know, what is
it, walk silently and carry a big stick?
I walk silently now and carry a yardstick.
I just measure everything around me, and nothing,
everything's falling short.
So what you do is you lower your
expectations.
There was a thing on, was it Mad
TV?
Lower expectations.
And then you realize that, hey, fuck it,
you know, can I use that medical term?
Sure, I've used it a lot.
Yeah, and you just got to say, hey,
when is this all going to end, you
know?
Usually, if I walk into a movie, and
it's not a good movie, I walk out
and just walk around the neighborhood or whatever,
till, you know, whoever I went with finishes
watching that piece of shit, and a movie
or whatever, crap.
But you can't really walk out of this
movie too easy, can you?
Well, I mean, see, now there's a thing.
You could, because psychologically you can kind of
tune out and go into another direction.
Oh, yeah, what do they call it?
Catatonia.
I've tried that.
20 years ago, 30 years ago, I think
I sat in a room still for about
8 hours, and that was about it.
I don't need to do that again.
Okay, fair enough.
But I mean, there are ways where you
can sort of adjust and go into, you
know, some people say that there's tech stuff
when they go into virtual reality or they're
playing games or whatever.
That's their escape, right?
Yeah, that's people watching these piece of shit
movies.
Yeah.
Okay.
I can't do that.
So anyway, I don't want to get into
subjectiveness.
You know what I say about that, right?
You've got to talk about things that help
others in a general sense or generally specific.
Like, for example, we'll get off the voices
because I didn't get any comments on Lookout
for Charlie.
I almost thought he's got a little bit
of a Jersey twinge to his voice, but
it turns out he's not Jersey.
He's not too far.
Baltimore, I think.
I'm going to say Baltimore.
Baltimore, I mean, you know, is a half
-hour drive depending on where you go.
To Baltimore?
From where?
Yeah, from Jersey.
No, no, that's not a half-hour.
That's Maryland.
Oh, no, I'm sorry.
That's a ways away.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
What I was thinking, no, it's an hour
and a half if you're hitting the gas.
You're thinking of Delaware from the tip of
Jersey.
Yeah, that's right.
Don't worry about it.
Look.
No, okay.
My geography is messed up today.
I've been building sunshades all day outside.
Well, let me just, let me tail on
to this voice thing real fast, though, because
I have a question for you because I
used to hear things and I used to
record a lot.
I just made many, many tapes of many,
many things.
I used to record interviews.
I recorded sound outside.
I used to just enjoy hearing sound and
splitting things up and actually kind of like
analyzing it in my own brain, right?
And I used to do this with the
magnetic cassettes and later on.
Oh, but hold on.
What he's getting into is none of it
is subject, all of it is controlled, and
it's aimed at the listener.
It's very interesting.
Now, it's very hard to find a quiet
spot.
Also, you'll find these voices everywhere.
And what I'm saying, though, they're not just
in your head, like I've been saying.
He's saying is that they're in the ambient
field and it's okay.
Well, that's what I was getting at here.
That's what I was trying to get at
is that they're actually in a lot of
different fields because I discovered extra things in
broadcast and people said, oh, no, that's just
channels bleeding over.
And I'm like, no, that's not possible because
when you go from one frequency to the
other and the voice remains the same, that
to me indicates it's all along that type
of frequency.
In this case, if you can get semantics
out of the voice, you can actually hear
what they're saying and it's relevant to the
subject matter that the observers, let's say, or
whoever's in the environment is pertaining to them.
It's very kind of spooky, but it's not
a surprise.
If you've been listening to what we've been
talking about, especially since the old ONG, you
shouldn't be surprised.
But I see what he did is he's
able to record what the artificial intelligence that
runs this place is doing.
And I think it's fascinating.
And I think the more you know about
it, the more you can, if you're intelligent
enough, is to, how would you say, defend
yourself, right?
Okay, but what I used to pick up,
though, personally, was gibberish.
And I know that people have found other
bits of gibberish where they pick out a
phrase.
Like, you know how people find stuff in
the backgrounds of Disney movies and they go,
did you hear that?
Well, that's more effective.
That's why TV commercials turned into gibberish, because
they found that if they played gibberish, it's
more memorable subconsciously.
Well, there's no subconscious, but it's the part
that it gets past the filter, which is
your senses, right?
You know, this is an entire sonic, if
you want to delve on how the senses
work.
Fooling the senses is the opposite of what
people think.
Like, if you've got to fool the eye,
you've got to be really fast.
No, you don't, because you're not fooling the
eye.
You're fooling the brain, right?
So the brain has to follow a logic
train.
I'm saying that, and I'm biting my tongue,
because if you didn't met anyone recently who
could follow any kind of train of logic.
Anyway.
Well, no, not logic, but the brain looks
for patterns.
Forget about logic.
Yeah, exactly.
It just looks for patterns.
Well, it's going back into the previous files,
right?
Right.
So, like, if you tell someone, you know
what a house is, and right away they're
going to think of the stick drawings they
did when they were in kindergarten of a
house all the way to the house they
live in.
Pretty much, yeah.
And if you think, you know, and they're
stuck in that.
And the brain likes to conserve energy, so
it reduces it to the simplest thing of
a house, a car, or a voice, even
when you say a voice.
Right?
There's a psychology to it.
Years ago, in the 90s up until the
early 2000s, they found that if they, in
public spaces, made an announcement, they had someone
with, in America, with a British accent, because
Americans were always enthralled with someone with a
British accent.
They would always stop and listen.
Oh, you and I talked about this many
times.
I told you, PBS was loaded with it
because it was meant to be the go
-to for you to educate yourself, and an
educated voice had a British accent.
Yeah, sound more refined.
Right, exactly.
And, yeah, so the whole thing is you
reduce the mind.
You find out, and this is what you
call, what are they called?
Trends.
It changes.
It changes, right?
Like, years ago, for example, you know, I
met an old person, I'll show you how
trends work, and because we lose certain trends,
we lose certain trains of thought.
When I was growing up, maybe I was
in grade school, and the Kennedy assassination came
up.
We're talking about 1974.
And there was an old guy around.
He says, yeah, they killed Kennedy because he
was the first president not to wear a
hat.
Right?
Because whenever you left your house and you
were a man or a male, you wore
a hat.
You didn't leave without your head covered, right?
And to see someone on the podium without
a hat in public, you put the haberdashers
out of business.
By the way, if you don't know what
a haberdasher is, someone who works with hats.
And they got together and they paid the
mob to kill him.
And this is what I was told when
I was, like, eight years old, 10 years
old or something like that.
And that stuck in the back of my
head when I hear everybody talking about the
Kennedy assassination.
They say, yeah, they killed him because he
was the first president not to wear hats.
Everyone looks at me like, what the hell
does that have to do with anything?
And I don't sit there and explain it
like I just did, right?
So if you lose the idea of what
these trends were like, you could make a
statement that sounds utterly ridiculous like that, right?
If I didn't explain it, it would probably
sound utterly ridiculous today.
Even to older people, you have to give
an explanation.
So what happens is we tend to fall
into things that are pieces of information that
are missing that sound ridiculous.
Like, how many times have you been told
the America's the richest country in the world?
And you go to someone and say, you
know, the U.S. has been bankrupt.
They're like, I get out of here.
We're the richest country in the world.
What are you talking about?
Right, right.
Yeah.
So it's all backwards.
So not only are they confused with misinformation,
they're taking partial under-informed, misinformed stuff and
forming it as their basis.
And then you have trends thrown in.
Okay, so what I'm trying to say is
they have nothing to lean on, the average
human, unless you go to an old culture,
right?
I mean, like a place in the Pacific
Rim Islands where they haven't been affected in
500 years, right?
Maybe 300 years or whatever, right?
Places like that, those people have a much
more firmer grip on reality, believe it or
not, right?
Like people, they're calling them Bush people, believe
it or not.
They have a much firmer grip on reality.
Yeah, so anyway, I would be curious to
see with – because I did a whole
bunch of mental outlines.
If you do check out Lookout for Charlie,
that's Lookout, F.A., and then Charlie on
YouTube, I would like to ask him to
go in a primitive – why would we
call them primitive?
Oh my gosh, I got to slap myself
for that.
A basic society that hasn't been affected by
Westernism, that hasn't changed in old Bush people,
and see what they're being told.
Because I think it's subjective based on your
culture.
But anyway, and also it's based on the
individual.
Like one of the questions – go ahead.
Well, I was going to bridge this with
something really odd that somebody sent me and
wanted to ask you a question about it,
because they found this article, Evidence of Ancient
Ritual – this is the headline from the
article – Evidence of an Ancient Ritual to,
quote, kill, end quote, the dead and destroy
their tombs in a final feast 4,000
years ago found in Crete.
Now, the question – Well, if we know
anything more than 200 years of suspect, right,
how accurate it is, what's the source of
that term?
Do they find that inscribed on something in
linear A or linear B, because that's the
language they used, or what?
Well, they did a whole thing on the
island of Crete, an excavation, and they found
a graveyard where they did weird things with
tombs and this and that.
And therefore, the person wants to know, you
know, what is the lawful burial ritual anyway?
Because it's a little confusing based on what
they see in the text.
And they were reading this article saying, you
know, look, the Greeks had all kinds of
odd things going on at different time periods,
and pointing to this article as part of
the evidence.
Of course, this is archaeologists and anthropologists interpreting
what they found when they dig things up.
Yeah, and they're not going to tell us
– you know, there's over 1,000 archaeological
digs all over the world going on, and
they're voracious.
I mean, they're really going after it.
But they don't report anything, because everything they're
finding always leads to some kind of human
sacrifice, some really grim, macabre shit.
So why would they keep putting that, right,
in there, right?
Well, this is a weird thing about destroying
the tombs afterwards.
Like, you leave the tombs of people there
for a little while.
But they were wondering if there is a
lawful practice that's simple about this.
It's lawful as to do with your deity.
So if you're an atheist, you go by
the laws of the state, right?
Of course.
So, you know, like red meat's bad for
you this decade, next decade.
Sugar's bad for you the next decade.
So right now, here's your three options.
Cremate, bury, or now they have composting, and
you have to do that with the body
as the people that are left behind.
You've got to, you know, finish up their
business, so to speak, with that.
Well, also, it's in every culture.
Every culture, hidden, is a powerful person is
usually – they eat some of his flesh
to get his power, right, because the flesh
carries the spirit and all that.
This isn't found in every culture.
I mean, but, you know, it's not publicly
known.
But, no, look, I think burial would be
the way to go because people say, what
about cremation?
Well, you burn garbage, I said, right?
What do you think of cremation, great guy?
You burn garbage, right?
So, I mean, then you could take that
several ways.
You know, is cremation dishonoring or whatever?
I think it matters to a certain degree.
I think the transition – I've gone into
it not too much.
Maybe I should in the future.
What happens when you die without – how
can you talk about something that you haven't
experienced, right?
It's all supposition, right?
Right.
Hypothesis.
But you can imagine, you know, it's a
form of drowning, but you're drowning in gas,
you know, air, instead of drowning – like,
suddenly, imagine a fish is drowning in water
where he was just fine the rest of
his life.
So, it's no different than suffocating, right, without
the pressure.
You know, that's why you always wish a
painless death on whoever.
What do they usually say in the film?
He didn't feel any pain.
He went peacefully.
Yeah, he went peacefully, yeah.
Because typically people are kicking and screaming when
it hurts, right?
Typically.
Not always.
So, yeah, I don't know, man.
It's a tricky thing.
But, yeah, very rarely do I get something
I'd recommend, other than a rated Y, is
look out for Charlie.
Did I bring him up?
Yeah.
Look out for F.A. Charlie.
Check out his work, because he's one of
these evidentially based guys.
You know, so he'll go over an audio
and say, well, if you think this is
just whatever, check this out, right?
If you think it's just a fluke or
whatever, it's too consistent.
It's in the background.
He leans a little too heavily on it
being current man-made technology, but he's finding
the stuff from 50 years ago, 30 years
ago in recordings.
Not all recordings.
It seems to be wiped out when they
do digital stuff.
You have to have a good analog recording
or something that's not online.
It's filtered out.
But anyway, you got any other questions?
Yeah, let's see.
You seem to hint that you'd be accountable
in the afterlife, but you also say that
you were left on this planet as a
shipping error.
Yeah, absolutely.
So why would you be held accountable for
not assisting space heaters, in quotes?
Those of us among the space heaters, if
he's being here, was a mistake anyway, or
was it all just a story slash joke?
I did not understand.
Thanks.
It goes any way you want to take
it.
Okay.
You know how the mobsters, okay, when they
sit around and they're drinking, they start insulting
each other.
They say, no, no, I was just joking.
I was just joking.
And they try to take it to a
limit.
Right.
Where then the guy says, okay, now you're
not joking.
You say, all right, now I'm going to
kick your ass.
And with all due respect.
Yeah.
I was just joking.
That's too many jokes, man, in a row.
Now you're starting to say what you really
mean, right?
So I don't know.
I don't know.
Okay, here's the thing.
Someone calls me up, and he says he
has a model car or whatever, and it's
making this noise, and this is what happens
when I drive.
And I can tell him what's wrong with
it over the phone.
And about 75 to 90% of the
time, I'm correct, right?
This is what you need.
A mechanic says, no, no, no, it's a
$20 part.
It's not $900.
Right.
You could probably do it yourself in 15
minutes.
I always like to be – I tell
people that are afraid of working on cars,
if you can change a light bulb, you
could pretty much do most of the stuff
you need to do to fix a car.
And I can attest to that because, actually,
I'm somebody who doesn't do much at all,
and you got me to replace the starter.
You know, in a car.
If you can change a light bulb, you
can work on your car.
Right.
And it was pretty simple, and it did
not take you that long.
It did not take me that long.
But, you know, other things happened that made
it irretrievable.
So what I'm saying, the same thing applies
here.
What I'm doing is I'm not there.
I mean, I wasn't there when they made
the decree or whatever.
Maybe, you know, I doubt it's completely random.
But, you know, even random machines are not
random.
But, you know, randomness is one of the
hardest things for them to figure out because
the more they look at it, the more
they see a sense of order.
So scrap that word.
But for whatever reason, for me, analyzing the
situation over the phone, what I'm doing here,
what I've done and what I could be
doing and all these other possibilities is what
I've come up with.
I'm not supposed to be here.
Right, because there's a lot of people that
come here, are sent here to either have
a good time, be wealthy, which doesn't necessarily
mean you have a good time, or to
suffer pain and agony and distress.
I just simply don't care.
I just see it all as being so
worthless.
And then, of course, you take in these
things of natural beauty, right?
Because, you know, you look at a bed
of flowers that came up naturally.
Wildflowers are so beautiful, a sunset, whatever, whatever.
Whatever you enjoy in nature.
It's only a short time that you can
enjoy that because you say, OK, screw this
city life.
I'm going to go live in nature.
Whoever I've recommended to, I said don't because
you're going to find out everything in nature
wants to kill you, no matter what part
of nature you go.
Jungle, desert, temperate, everything there wants to kill
you.
So what I'm trying to say is a
temporary overbrush and then take in the beautiful
wonder of nature.
Yeah, just temporary because once you get into
it, you're going to see it's actually against
you also.
So everything seems to be that way with
a sense of worthlessness attached to it.
So then there's just taking up time.
It's like, OK, all right, what's next?
And, oh, yeah, that's so predictable or that
is so whatever.
So you just take each breath, each step,
each whatever.
But what I see going on, just like
when someone calls me and they want to
know what's wrong with their car, I've done
it with myself.
You know, remote, try to be as remote
as possible.
And I'm like, oh, I must have been
sent here on a shipping error because none
of this shit is.
And just put it this way.
I have such a unique perspective on just
pretty much everything that it doesn't jive with,
like we said, anything here.
And I won't say it unless I could
dig it up and say, hey, check this
out, man.
You know, look at it.
You figure you've been sent to the wrong
neighborhood.
I think I've been sent to the wrong
time.
address, but in the right neighborhood.
So that's why I'm half miserable half the
time.
Anyways.
Oh, OK.
All right.
Well, it's the second half that counts usually.
Usually.
All right.
Anyways, here's one.
They were asking.
Basically, it's a long thing.
But, you know, like you have a day
where all of the electronics seem to be
working against you.
They're either breaking or malfunctioning or giving you
trouble and all this kind of thing.
And everybody mentions to this guy Mercury retrograde.
And he goes, oh, come on.
So he wonders, you know, is it spiritual,
electrical, a matrix glitch?
And, oh, by the way, what are your
thoughts on what some call Western astrology?
I know it's all airy-fairy, but is
it just a version of something that might
have been valid information in its original form?
Yeah, but if they make it believe.
What's that thing when enough people believe it
and manifests?
Egregores or what do they call them?
Yeah, I think it's an egregore.
If enough people, like the stick man.
I don't know if it's a fictional character
and people start seeing it, right?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
What do you call it?
Slenderman.
Slenderman, yeah.
So enough people believe it, it works.
But, look, I've seen, I've witnessed this where
they blame it on Mercury, and then when
Mercury's out, they blame it on Pluto.
So which one is it?
Just say it's all the planets affecting everything
all the time.
And shut up, right, is what I tell
the astrologers.
But they have been quite accurate.
I've had a reading by Santos Bonacci, believe
it or not, a long time ago, with
a minimum amount of information.
He wanted the birth date, full name, and
all that.
And it was really accurate.
I mean, in terms of, like, conditions, things
that attend to, whatever, without telling him.
So, yeah, whatever.
Santos has some interesting insights, but I'll tell
you something.
Once he started getting into the urine drinking
thing, I was out of there.
Drinking, yeah.
Well, he's a little too excited.
You know when people are excited about getting
new information?
Right.
It's good, but don't be.
If you're too excited, it's going to show,
and you're going to overstep.
Right.
You're going to overcompensate for it.
Because when you find out it's not what
you were so excited about, how do you
remedy that now, right?
Oh, I'm not into that anymore.
No.
But Santos Bonacci was one of the few.
He was on American Freedom Radio.
You know the history of American Freedom Radio.
And I used to call in, and he
had me as a guest, and people were
like, oh, I've never heard this stuff before.
So that was why I got vocal.
But anyway.
I was part of that history, too, and
Santos, I had a little thing with him,
too.
You were on another thing.
You were doing something else, I think, and
then you came back in when Vinny Eastwood
went, I don't know.
And Danny was a good proponent.
He said you and I would make a
good match, which is kind of true for
all this.
It's long-lasting.
It has worked out sonically.
Sonically, yeah.
Right.
But to go back to the rest of
the question, there was a second part.
The other part was more interesting, other than
the astrology.
What was it?
Oh, about all the electronics kind of turning
against you all at once.
It seems like a thing that happens every
now and then.
So what do you think that is?
Because everybody tells them Mercury retrograde, which led
to this.
Take it as what Archaic Brashear talks about
as a pattern break.
And welcome it.
For example, when I was building my first
prototypes, when I say prototype, like a thing
you can go and present and demonstrate, you
know, a loudspeaker.
Every day something was breaking that's totally abnormal.
Like I did laundry one day, and I
take the laundry out of the washing machine.
There's a puddle of water under the washing
machine.
Oh, my gosh.
You can't just say, I'll fix that later,
right?
Things would break.
Life fixture would break.
I mean, it's been there for 20 years.
It finally decides to break the next day.
The car doesn't start.
I'm at a parking lot.
The car doesn't start, right?
I just decided, you know, and then I
get out and I hit the starter.
It wasn't the starter at all.
I had a little bit of an oil
leak, and the oil leak went on the
starter solenoid and prevented a contact.
So I cleaned that, took care of the
oil leak.
And every day, just about every day, it
was something unusual.
Something else, yeah.
Okay.
It's like imagine as unusual as this.
You just bought a brand-new pair of
shoes, and a week later they're totally worn
out.
You're like, how could that be possible?
Right.
These things last for years, you know?
So, you know, good shoes.
And things like that, very, very strange stuff.
So, yeah, I'd lift my arm, shake my
fist at the sky and at the ground,
and yell out a bunch of medical terms,
and then go back to what I was
doing.
But when I went back to what I
was doing, I was refreshed, and I was
actually making even more improvements that I had
not thought of before.
So this is the, all right, what did
I just say?
You could have been replaced when you got
lemons.
You're right.
Got you.
Yeah, you killed the bastard who sent you
all the lemons.
No, I mean, you make lemons.
Yeah, right.
I got you.
Yeah.
So take it as a positive break.
I got you.
By the way, someone asked me also about
Assyria.
This is very interesting.
Let's go back to archaics.
There's a lot of palindromes, like Abraham was
born in 1947 BC, and Israel was founded
in 1947 AD, right?
So these palindromes between BC and AD.
The other day I put in what happened
in the year 2025 BC, and guess what
came up?
Assyria reformed.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
So I've been saying for a long time
that Assyria will start to form, if not
be formed, by 2025 or around 2025.
So I just found that to be like
a punch in the eye, maybe?
Better than a punch in the nuts.
A punch in the nuts is the worst
thing for a guy.
Vagina, you could punch a vagina.
I could take it.
But for a woman, it would be a
punch in the breast or a punch in
the nuts for a guy.
It wasn't that bad.
Listen, a punch in the nuts can ruin
your day, okay?
A punch in the eye, you can get
over it.
It'll ruin their day.
Yeah.
But yeah, because you don't want them attached
to your body when they're feeling that way,
right?
Exactly.
Remember the song, Detachable Penis?
Do you remember that?
King Missile, yes.
Yeah, yeah.
I was walking down Avenue A, I was
missing, and I saw it on the sidewalk.
Because you have to know East Village at
the time.
There's a guy shoving it on a blanket,
and I talked him down.
Yeah, I used to buy lipos.
I mean, because I need some lipos.
My favorite part is you talked him down
like $3 in the discussion.
Yeah.
This is what?
It was like 1980s you're talking about?
Something like that, yeah.
Oh, okay.
My gosh, that was 40 years ago.
All right.
But the Subway bulbs, that's from the Subway.
Don't buy it, because they're left-hand threaded.
They used to steal them from the Subway.
When you take lipos out of the Subway,
they're left-hand threaded.
They won't thread onto your fixtures, which are
right-hand threaded.
So I was like, oh, the bulbs don't
fit.
I said, let me check it out.
I know I've been working with mechanics my
whole life, and I look at the thread.
He doesn't hold it up in front of
you.
It's pointing to the left.
It's a left-hand thread.
Right.
And that's left-hand thread, because they're stolen
from the Subway.
And you won't be able to buy a
left-hand socket.
Anyway, that's from detachable penis.
But anyway, back to the Assyria, 2025 BC.
Right.
It was like a punch in the eye.
I was like, ooh.
See, the more information you get, like by
listening to archaics and Jason Brashear's getting a
different perspective and all this.
And even like Santos Bonacci, he's big into
astrology.
It can be accurate for you, but it
seems to work more accurately for individuals than
for a collective, like the electronics going bad
for Mercury.
So there are certain things that you have
to learn to apply that works for you.
And I hate to say it that way,
because I like to talk about things that
work across the board as well for people.
Like, for example, the most exciting thing that's
happened to me in the past six months
other than the audio and stuff with the
water, is finding out that getting rid of
BO in your laundry, fresh clean laundry, it
still has BO when you put it in
the dryer, is by changing your soap.
Right.
That works.
I just found a bunch of clothes that
I always put away, you know, washed and
all that.
And they had like a BO on them,
and I washed them in a new soap
that I got, and the BO went away.
I just gave that advice to somebody last
week, because we talked about this about a
week and a half ago or something.
Yeah.
And I gave that advice, and yeah, it
worked.
Yeah, it does.
Because I found that.
Now, if you go with regular science, they
tell you it's bacteria and all that causes
that smell.
Okay, it's fine.
But where does the bacteria come from?
Oh, it comes from, you know, whatever fecal
matter on the dirt.
No.
What I'm trying to say is the bacteria
that they see that supposedly gets blamed for
it is because they blame bacteria and viruses
for everything.
Well, the whole theme to this is the
breaking patterns.
It's an emergent.
Just like, you know, you want to freak
people out.
Don't do this with someone who likes tripping
on acid.
Show them microscopic scans of the skin, and
you see the mites, and this looks like
something out of sci-fi monsters living on
your skin, right?
Or even just the things on your eyebrows.
It's even worse.
Yeah.
And you know, the more you wash, the
more they grow back, right?
Right.
And they're not in the air.
They're not in the ground.
They're only found on human skin.
Only.
So how can they say it comes from
somewhere else?
That's what they're...
They do not...
These idiots, these academic idiots...
By the way, if I said they're all
idiots with little exception, like the medical, the
legal, the academics, it's true with little exception.
And this is...
And I've brought this up many times because
some people just stop and think academics, doctors,
and lawyers are idiots.
Yes, they are.
All of them, with the exception of...
I've always gone over the exception.
The exception is very important.
You have someone that wants to be an
academic, heaven forbid.
It means you're not paying attention.
A lawyer, a doctor.
And they get all the studies.
They get all the qualifications and criteria.
They go into the field and they realize,
what the F is this?
This has nothing to do with...
And now they're stuck.
Now they're stuck.
They're like, oh my gosh, I dedicated 10
years to this.
I found out...
What do I do now?
I got no skills.
What do I do?
Those people usually transition out of it within
two weeks to six months, sometimes two years.
I knew...
I've heard of someone that took them two
years to transition out of that kind of
field, right?
Okay.
Those are the exceptions.
But the ones that stay in there, eh,
idiots.
And then there are the ones that stay
in there and they're very low key.
And they're not happy.
They're not happy at all.
And they go both ways.
They're serving two masters, right?
So it's a very...
Humans are in a very, very, very, very
bad spot when it comes to looking up...
Who are you going to look up to?
Who are you going to go to?
It's exhausting serving two masters anyway.
Look, I got two more things to get
to.
Yeah, go ahead.
So I want to get to them.
And you want to go with the timekeeping
question?
Yeah, sure.
Is that the one in the Chitango?
Yeah, because...
I could skip that.
That's just like how to do two sacrifices
in one day.
That has to be looked at carefully because
one of them might be at noon and
the other one is at twilight, which would
be dawn and sundown, and that would make
it the same day.
So that's done.
I have to go look at it again
in the language of preservation.
We don't want to say Hebrew.
We don't want to even think of Jewish
now, do we?
Oh, my gosh.
99% of the people that hear my
songs think I'm Jewish, by the way.
Well, because you mention the Old Testament a
lot in there.
Yeah, yeah.
So, I mean, this shows you how much
they know.
But anyway.
Anyway, so last thing then.
Your view on Bitcoin.
Do you have a view on this?
What do you think of it?
Is it a pyramid scheme, a CIA creation,
pump and dump?
It's all 1,000% because it's anything
that makes it.
What is it?
A kilo of cocaine is less than $3
,000, $4,000, and it sells for $10
,000, $20,000, whatever.
Right.
Anything that has that kind of markup is
an intelligence operation.
Is it lawful money?
No.
If it's not gold and silver, it's not
lawful money.
Lawful money is something that's based on lawful
substance, and there's no substance to it.
Right.
I think it's a joke.
Now, when someone said buy this stuff called
Bitcoin, it's $2.50. It was in 2008,
2009 when it first came out.
If I bought it, would I be happy
I did?
Yeah, sure.
So, like I said.
If you held it to today.
Look, I got offered it at $80, and
I'll tell you something.
I feel foolish sometimes, but then I say
to myself, I would have sold it by
now.
I mean, definitely.
Yeah, that's the idea.
You hold it for years.
You say, I'm going to hold it five
years and sell it or whatever.
But, yeah, the whole thing is you want
to get caught up with these morons.
You know what I like, by the way,
the luxury?
I'm researching the luxury industry for the Scalarator,
and with all the tariff nonsense, the Chinese
videos coming out.
You know those $38,000 handbags we make
them here?
If you want to buy it from us,
it's $1,400, the same one, right?
Right.
So, at least that came out because I
think it went viral for a little while.
And then what's funny is I watch YouTube
on the big screen TV while I'm eating
because I'll put on food stuff.
Nothing better to put on food stuff while
you're eating, let's say, right?
Okay.
And there'll be an ad for Hermes.
So, now Hermes and Gucci are doing ads
to counter it.
That's like if you told an eight-year
-old to go become CEO of these companies,
that's what they would do, right?
So, anyway.
Of course.
All right.
What else?
Yeah, is that all?
Yeah, that's pretty much it.
I mean, I just got one basic question.
I mean, you seem really energetic today.
Has it been a good day, a pattern
break day?
What has your day been like?
I got what I needed to get done,
to get out of the way so I
can do other things tomorrow.
So, I feel good.
I feel like the day was fairly complete.
It's sundown here, what they call Saturday, some,
what is it, the 22nd, 3rd, 4th, something
like that.
20, what, 25th maybe?
Yeah, it's the second week of the second
month.
Yeah, 26th, 26th technically, yeah.
Okay, yeah.
All right.
It's fine.