Rated Y, Sonic Event 229.
Excuse me for the sound of my voice,
it might sound strange, but here we are,
it's shifting a bit.
Anyway, Greek, how is the evening going where
you are?
It's all right.
Busy, man.
Just doing consulting with engineering projects and same
old, same old.
You know what I say?
Humans are, right?
So, yeah, I hear that.
Anyway, you know, a weird thing happened today.
Weird thing happened today when I was gathering
up the questions and comments, a guy wrote
to me and was asking what happened.
Why is it like, in other words, I
think they're still signed up for the old
Greek speak thing.
And or maybe with Sam.
Yeah.
So I think with Sam.
Well, that's an administrative thing that should have
been worked out.
I try to stay out of that.
Yeah.
No.
Well, I thought we had established and done
everything, but it was weird because, you know,
we did that about a year ago and
it was like, yeah, yeah, there's I've gotten
responses when I was doing this stuff with
the paranormies.
He was signed up to both and he
was wondering the same thing.
So yeah, I stay away from it really.
I mean, privately, I just sit back and
watch for people that work with me and
do stuff.
I just sit back and I'm like, why
bother?
But, you know, just keeping someone's benefiting from
all this, I hope I know pretty much
not a super fact, but most people that
are subs and listen to me before did
not know how the money system works, how
the human body works, that what they think
was in the Bible was never in the
Bible or what's in the Bible they never
heard of all these things.
So I'm going to be continuously putting out
that stuff and just doing it on like
a platform like the Internet or whatever is
more efficient.
I've been doing this since the early 2000s
on what was called conference calls.
You call like a one meet up by
something I meet up some members one eight
hundred number you get up to ninety nine
people.
Yeah.
Well, and I was doing it there.
I think talks you right before talk show
before just regular conference in the late 90s
conference calls.
You call this number and a whole bunch
of people meet on a conference call.
And then after that, when I moved to
Tucson, it was pretty much like little law
groups, retirement people like, you know, the one
of those Knights of Pythias kind of thing.
They're looking for people to come and speak,
you know, OK, like Ralph Epperson.
Right.
Ralph Epperson ran a publishing company and he
asked me to go and speak all.
And I've been saying the same stuff now
for three decades.
So, you know, whatever.
I want to bring something up since the
last time we left off, it was like
politicians, children and drug use and debauchery and
all that stuff.
Yeah.
It's funny when you know about it secondhand.
I wasn't there.
So I can't say firsthand from people that
actually were there firsthand.
And then you see what they put out
on the media about it.
You're like, yeah, that's that's it.
But it's actually a lot worse than what
they're putting out in the media.
And it's also very convoluted.
I think when I was bringing up the
former vice president's son debauchery, I was working,
I said, with a Korean businesswoman.
She went to his house home somewhere in
Florida.
Yeah.
And he's basically just a little more.
She basically told her, yeah, I'll talk about
the business context, what we could do for
everybody.
Take your clothes off and get high first.
This is like a business meeting.
Right.
She's like, I'm married and I'm really not
into getting high.
So I'm going to go outside for a
little bit.
You know, she took off.
Right.
This is with the Hunter Biden guy.
And so this was back in 2015.
I think you and I were in touch
or somehow I think I brought that up
to you.
I remember speaking to you about it.
Yep.
And and then when you see the thing
about the light, you mentioned a laptop.
I don't even know what the laptop meant
or anything like that, because what they do
is they put a curve on it.
Like, for example, now with the Epstein stuff,
Epstein was just a broker.
One guy that is a fall guy for
a broker.
I'll give you another thing that I found
out a while back.
All of the attorney general's offices do what
Epstein did.
Right.
What does that mean?
What they do is they they have people
that are predators and they go out to
places like Disneyland, Coney Island, public beaches.
So you're going to have all up and
down the East Coast, West Coast, inland.
It would be places that have water parks,
Chicago, stuff like that.
And they take photographs of children that might
their their clients might be interested in.
And also they follow the children to their
family and they get a picture of the
license plate.
Sometimes they even follow home and get the
address where the children live.
And they have like a photo album.
And when their clients are interested in the
child, now they circle back and they have
the license plate and the address and they
go to the attorney general's office to get
the rest of the details.
Just like that.
Right.
See.
So this is like, well, you know, I
mean, so when you hear on the news,
attorney general, they caught these criminals and put
them behind bars.
It's so convoluted.
The world is so dirty.
I'm always going to go back to say
what I always said was you can go
online and look at the weirdest, craziest conspiracy
theories.
I'm telling you, if you sum up what's
really going on, it's even worse than all
the stuff you hear online.
So, yeah, well, yeah, pretty much.
That's what you'll if you dig around.
And I don't know why I've been made
aware of all these things.
Like sometimes someone would start speaking on something.
You know, the attorney general is really dirty
because I'm like, why are you bringing that
up?
I really don't care.
I know they're great, but they give me
all the details and I'm like, holy shit.
OK, well, what am I going to do
with that information?
Right.
Well, here we go.
I can convey it to 10 other people
that are listening or whatever.
The other thing that was very open that
some people remember that guy, Jared of Subway
Sandwiches, I think they did lock him up
for pedophilia or something.
Right.
Yeah.
Well, kiddie board.
Well, that's the small part of it.
The big part of it was whenever he
would be involved in like marketing meetings, they
would go and sit down and like the
board table.
And before the meeting ever started, this happened
more than once.
He would stand up or ask people around
him, do you want a place where I
could find some young boys or young children
to have sex with around here?
And that would be like, whoa, you know,
what the hell?
You know, so, so many he asked that
to so many people that they couldn't just
like tell him to shut up and slap
on the wrist.
They just nailed him right for whatever.
So and I knew that information before he
was locked up for all that.
That's why when I mentioned this to someone,
they said, oh, yeah, he's locked up for
child porn.
I was like, really?
I didn't even know that.
You know, most people find out about what
the media put forward first, you know, where
by the way, if you were going around
10 years ago saying the Hunter Biden guy
to go to him for influential business meetings
and tell you to take your clothes off
and get high with him, you're crazy, right?
So you don't really openly speak on these
things, you know, too much.
Oh, I know.
I got in trouble for the drug thing
because I tried to explain to people when
you see those big drug busts, those are
intentional.
They let them catch that.
And how do I know that?
Of course, from DEA agents who say, yeah,
that's the one they let us catch.
You know, there's 100 of them, but they
let us have that one.
So we look like we're doing our job.
You know, that's that's what it is.
I was just going to pull a name
thing.
I'm not going to mention his name.
He's a witness protection program official for the
DEA.
I won't pull his name, but I'll give
a little background.
He was a State Department of Mexico sniper,
like their best guy.
And he started going around to State Department
parties and hitting on the other dignitaries wives
when he was younger.
And they didn't like that.
So let's get rid of this guy.
All we got to do is tell the
Americans we got the best sniper in this
side of the hemisphere and they should have
him.
And they told the American DEA that and
and State Department actually.
And they came and kidnapped him from Mexico.
The way they did that, he was very
close with his sister.
They sent a bunch of guys in to
his sister's house like she was going to
get accosted or molested.
She got on the phone screaming, you know,
I need your help.
And he ran out, ran over there into
a trap.
They handcuffed him in a blindfold and put
a bag over his head and helicopter flew
him somewhere in Texas.
That is funny because he was an all
tile room.
It was just like the Matrix.
And he says, I need to speak to
an attorney.
And he says, you see a phone in
here, asshole.
That's what they told him.
So when I saw the Matrix, I was
like, oh, this is kind of like a
connection to the Matrix.
But make a long story shorter.
He's like, hey, I know you know about
money or whatever.
You know, they have a pallet, a few
billion dollars for me.
Of cash in Brazil in a warehouse.
The only and it's got my name on
it.
But the only caveat, the only conditions are
that I can't leave.
It can't leave the building.
So what do we do?
And I was like, well, if it's cash,
it has to leave the building.
That's the purpose of cash.
Cash is no good when it's in a
pallet or under your bed or whatever.
Right, right.
And I said, how would that why would
they give you, you know, a million dollars
and hundred dollar bills is like the size
of back in the days when you got
business cards, remember the business cards when you
ordered the thousand pack?
Right.
Not the 500.
That's what a million dollars in cash feels
like in hundreds.
And how do I know?
Okay.
So I said, God damn it.
You know, how do you get so much?
Are you kidding?
The DEA is the biggest drug dealer in
the world.
This is from a DEA person, right?
Yeah.
And I can keep on going.
I've on private Skype groups.
I gave stories in his name and all
that.
I mean, it's just not stories.
These accounts.
Yeah.
It's not too far from stuff you see
in the movies, actually.
But the movies actually are mild.
Yeah.
It's actually quite mild.
Sounds very much like a guy I met
in the 90s named Carlos, but we'll leave
it at that.
Tell me.
Yeah.
But here's the thing.
When you but here's the thing.
When you do a movie, it has to
make sense to the audience.
Stuff I've experienced didn't make any sense at
all.
You see.
So it has to make.
That's why these movies sometimes you.
I don't know.
Would you.
Who would you say is makes movies that
are kind of eclectic?
Who's the guy that did Snatch and Lock,
Stock and Two Smoking Barrels?
British guy.
You know what I'm talking about, right?
Geez, I should just look it up.
Who is it?
Who is Snatch and Lock, Stock, Smoking Barrels?
Oh, Brad Pitt.
No, no, no.
The direct.
The guy who did the film.
Guy Ritchie.
There you go.
It's more like a Guy Ritchie film or
Quentin Tarantino.
But even there, they let you tie things
together.
But, yeah, it's bizarre.
And yeah.
Anyway, let's let's get off of that.
I just wanted to let people know these
are the reason I'm saying this stuff is
because when you do your whatever, whatever media
collection and entertainment or whatever, keep in the
back of your mind that things are.
Yeah, it is like that.
And much worse and much more elaborate.
Right.
So.
OK, so there was a response from the
last Sonic where you were asked about German
medicine, new German medicine.
And he said it's good for analyzing potential
emotional root causes for manifested physical conditions.
It doesn't seem like a good catch, although
is how he put it.
Easy.
That's that.
We already have that.
If you there's something called the Mase John
Mase method where your mind, your mind associates
all memories traumatic or not with images.
Right.
So imagine you had a photo album.
That's all.
There's no audio.
There's no you have to recall the image
before you recall the audio and the feeling
and the smells.
You know, we talked about how smells can
bring you back and all that.
So the image is the first thing that
has to be recollected.
So you basically and you don't have to
do any association with these psychiatrists, psychologists or
who is it?
Samuel Goldin of Goldenmeier Films.
Twenty said anyone who wants to see a
psychologist or a psychologist should have their head
examined.
But yeah, so it's all imagery.
So that image, if you have a trauma,
you never share it with anyone.
What you do is you expand that image.
You can't do this alone.
That's a weird thing.
You have to be coached through it.
But you never tell the person what the
trauma is, who's coaching you, walking you through
it.
It's interesting how it's like a bilateral thing.
You expand the image so it can't get
any bigger.
And then you shrink it till it can't
get any smaller.
And it disappears.
And it's a cure all for for anything,
even if someone's too happy.
So the physical attachment comes in where if
you have very trauma, especially if you're going
to one of these demons known as psychologists
or psychiatrists, they're there to adjust you.
So you fit into the system, by the
way, just like doctors are there to suppress
the symptoms.
They even tell you this will reduce your
symptoms.
Right.
It doesn't treat the cause.
So your symptoms are that you're you're not
adjusting to a system that's really fucked up.
Right.
So they try to find out why you're
not adjusting to a fucked up system.
But what happens is when you do have
the trauma in your mind, your body, your
mind starts to change its identity to become
relevant to that hidden trauma, to that thing
that you're carrying around.
Your identity will change the way you relate
to other people, the way you relate to
every aspect of your life, including what you
consider to be personal.
Time will change after that.
So when you your identity starts to change,
your emotions start to change, your physical actions
start to change.
You're going to definitely manifest ailments.
Well, the emotional side to ailment is also
very external because we're subject to induction.
For example, when you go into a hot
tub, bathtub to take a bath, even a
shower or in a pool, you know, say
no peeing in the pool.
Well, you cover all of your skin with
water.
There is enough induction to create new water
inside your body and then displace that older
water at the at the bladder.
Now, the water doesn't run to the bladder.
It's energized and energized, materialized in the bladder.
Remember, when I say induction, it's like the
food replicator in Star Trek.
One thing moves to anything can move from
any side of the body to out of
the body by just replicating itself in the
particular location.
You start replicating things in the body or
whatever by induction, which is it could be
fields around you, other people.
This is how diseases are caused.
You know, you don't it's it's almost impossible
to contract disease by breathing airborne.
It has to be through induction.
There have been many enough tests that have
been publicized.
Good luck finding them now where they would
people with advanced tuberculosis or whatever classic diseases,
smallpox were injected.
Blood was drawn and then injected into healthy
subjects and they never came down with it.
So it's not a physical thing, disease or
nutrition or.
So the disease is really not physical.
So saying there is a way to figure
it out through the emotion is spot on.
But do they know what they're talking about?
Now, I'm going to venture to say they
don't.
They don't know.
I bet most of those people in that
unless they prove otherwise believe in, quote, unquote,
what is it?
Microbiology theories like virus theory, transmutation of transmittal
of disease by microorganisms and absorption of nutrition
in the body.
I don't think they understand the human body.
If they did, their research would go through
the roof.
I mean, they would be a thousand years
ahead of the current state.
So I don't know.
Interesting.
I hope they don't.
Interesting thought, though, is that, you know, you're
saying you can't breathe in the disease, quote,
unquote.
But if you breathe in particles, they could
then through induction create something in the body.
If they're in there, in there or no,
if you can induce it.
Yeah, exactly.
Well, it's just like radiation.
You could be subjected to a lot of
radiation and you'll get a sunburn or whatever.
But if you if you inhale like 9
-11, people around 9-11 or the or
several places through the like, the other one
was Oklahoma City.
A lot of people die from radiological diseases
or the burn.
If you breathe in the dust, the burn
pit syndrome in the Middle East, when they
the soldiers came back with the exotic.
Yeah, that also.
Right.
OK.
Yeah.
If you breathe in these particles and they're
constantly ionizing like tiny little x-ray machines
in your lungs, that will cause disease.
Yeah.
So if you have, let's say, if you
inhale something that's airborne and it gets into
your body, that's not enough.
It has to create induction in the body.
Right.
Because the lungs are completely sealed, by the
way.
Nothing ever goes through the lungs.
As a matter of fact, they collapse.
If that happens, if the tissue gets so
thin that it can't support the lungs will
collapse.
But anyway, there is no by the way,
in the lungs, there is no you breathe
in oxygen and give off CO2.
That is the dumbest thing you can ever
say.
Once you understand the lungs are completely sealed
or nitrogen breathers.
I know I've gone into this before, not
oxygen breathers, but we do require a certain
content of oxygen.
Right.
So, yeah, it's kind of like saltwater fish
or salt swimmers.
No, they're water swimmers.
They just happen to be in saltwater.
We're nitrogen breathers and we just so happen
to need oxygen in that nitrogen.
You see, this is not how it works.
And by the way, whenever you see these
old people or even younger people on pure
oxygen, you're walking around with that tank.
I usually tell them you're going to die
of pneumonia in six months if you keep
that up.
And they always do if they keep it
up.
Right.
So too much oxygen.
Yeah.
What else?
OK, well, it creates oxygen is gravity moves
downward and hydrogen is heavenly.
It goes upward.
Anything that is affected by oxygen goes to
the earth.
What do you what if I said this
guy's going to the earth pretty soon?
Do I have to keep explaining what that
means?
Right.
If you're going to the earth, most culture
would take anything.
Yeah, you take that as being dead.
Yeah.
So the oxygen is earthbound gravity.
So take a piece of shiny iron, oxygenate
it.
What happens to the rust flakes?
They fall down.
Anything you oxygenate, you notice develops an oxygenation
reaction, goes down, falls to the ground.
Hydrogen, on the other hand, goes upward.
Right.
That's that's how I was explaining an agricultural
meeting recently.
When you go pick an orange off of
a fruit tree, you notice all that water
and juice.
These these morons believe that the water is
drawn up through the roots, through the trunk
of the tree, down the branch into the
orange.
That's not what's happening at all.
Anyone.
And I like to keep keep it practical.
I tell people you ever cut a tree
down, you ever cut some fresh wood.
Does it ever look like any water can
travel through that with any efficacy at all
to fill that orange?
Never.
It's that orange produces its own water.
It's all energetic and the roots are hydrophobic.
If you remove those live roots off the
tree and rinse them off real good, let
them dry a little bit and then spray
them with a water bottle.
Mr. You'll notice the water beads up.
Yeah.
On the roots, just like a freshly polished
car hood with wax.
That's hydrophobic.
Yeah.
So if they did any absorption, it would
be more like akin to holding up a
dry piece of cotton and misting it with
water.
What happens?
It soaks right in.
Right.
So or microfiber, there is absolutely no absorption
in the roots.
It's serology.
You could look it up and they show
you the cells.
They are so tightly packed and hydrophobic.
I had a medical person email me about
investigating intestine, stomach and GI tract.
This is Greek.
There's no way that could be absorbed.
As a matter of fact, it is hydrophobic.
Like you said, I was like, well, thank
you.
Thanks for checking, checking it out.
So anyway.
Anyway.
So slightly different subject.
Would love to know more about how to
stop income tax being withheld.
Also, is there a process to recoup taxes
already paid?
Yes.
They don't like to do that because, OK,
I can give the codes.
Actually, see if I could go find them.
I'll go to the laptop.
I might even switch over audio if we're
going to be on longer because the echo
is really severe.
Like I'm hearing you speak twice.
So I have to filter it out.
Sorry about that.
The purpose of taxation as it's an oxymoron,
just like you're always going to be a
taxpayer because they set up the all caps
name, not you.
They could because they created your legal status,
your legal position, which you can't get out
of.
The only way to get out of it
is stop using it.
They could call it whatever.
So you're a taxpayer.
That's just a name.
It's like calling you.
I don't know, a red ball player or
whatever.
It doesn't matter.
But the overall purpose of taxation where people
have to participate, by the way, it is
voluntary.
Every time they give a C-SPAN is
good for looking this up, believe it or
not, on YouTube.
Every time a new IRS commissioner is commissioned
within the first minute of his new commission
acceptance speech, he says, we have a voluntary
system.
Otherwise it won't work.
But most people get in trouble.
So they don't know how they get in
trouble and how everyone says it's mandatory.
The purpose of taxation all around is very
simple.
It's to take your time away because they
know you're working for it.
If you work for seashells, they would take
seashells.
If you work for frog skins, they would
take that.
Right.
They take the reason they're taking your labor
and your time is because this thing called
education with a capital C education, because all
of it is about reading and comprehending what
you're reading and actually committing yourself to read.
If you educated yourself on how the system
works, the level of voluntary participation, which most
people think is involuntary, would be very, very
low.
It would be so low that would be
your you would have much more free energy
and all that meaning of your own time.
That's the first reason they do it.
The second reason, the second thing about recouping
that then you have to be like expert
level on all this.
So a basic novice, that's just, you know,
if you might succeed, you will succeed if
you keep it simple.
Having withholdings.
It's very simple.
You will succeed with all that.
But recovering that you would have to be
much more advanced at that because it requires
then shifting things around.
There's something called the palms manual, P.O
.M.S., the public whatever, whatever it's the
P.O.M.S. It's online, but the
one that's online is very heavily abridged.
That is the manual that the Social Security
Administration uses to give out so-called benefits.
Right in there, they tell you the right
way to get benefits is to put the
all caps name, the beneficiary into a trust.
And then that trust has is managed and
administered.
And all of the fees of administrating the
trust and property is sent to the IRS.
So then so let's say if you were
to get a professional trust manager, they charge
like 250 an hour, 250 an hour, usually
between four, between, let's say, 250 and 450
an hour.
Yes.
OK.
And so let's say you're doing that 10
hours a week.
That's forty five hundred a week times 50
weeks.
You get into a quarter of a million.
So that's how you recover it.
But to recover it directly is is refi.
You have to do what's called an amended
return.
Right now.
Now it's a full time job.
And heart boat heart like the heart and
then boat B.O.A.T. on YouTube.
A little convoluted, but you'll hear some testimonials.
And it's a full time job to do
this.
But let's see.
I'll go into the office here and I'll
bring up the code for a very simple
statement.
And there's two ways.
There's several ways to deal with withholding.
The easiest one is the David Merrill go
to savings to suitors forum and look around
there.
That's where you do a conditional endorsement on
all your financial instruments.
And if taxes taken out, it's refunded plus
five percent.
That's where you make a demand for lawful
money.
Twelve USC for 11.
That's all you have to do on the
back of all your written instruments.
And you have to have a written check.
I believe that if they do direct deposit,
just go do a screenshot of it.
Make a print print copy of it and
write that on the screenshot and predate it.
So if you do is let's say it's
April 1st transfer.
You go ahead and do a screenshot, hit
print on your printer and then put March
31st on it that you made the demand.
Right.
OK, let's see if I can find that
channel for testimonials again, though, because you broke
up a little bit during it was a
hard boat or something like that.
Yeah.
Heartboat was the YouTube channel.
Heartboat.
OK.
Yeah.
It's recoupers.
Recoupers is the group.
They're on Telegram.
Talk about a convoluted mess.
People keep saying get on Telegram.
You have to do it on your phone
first and then they send you an email
and then you can go to some site
and then go to their site on the
computer.
I was like, you know what?
I'm not making time for that.
Sorry.
I have plenty.
Everyone people say I don't have enough time.
All you have is time.
That's all you have.
You have time in a naked body.
And that you hopefully are clothed occasionally.
And that's all you have.
Some people say I don't have time.
We're not paying attention.
But things do you want to invest your
time into that?
Right.
The answer for me would be no.
So let's see if I can find.
Besides, if you really want to social media
outlet, there's a lot easier things to sign
up for that take no time.
So, you know.
Yeah.
So the easiest thing, by the way, also
put in on YouTube 1913 Federal Reserve remedy.
David Merrill, you'll get a 30 minute video
that was done 15 years ago.
He goes over it like on a 20th
grade level.
20th grade level is like fifth year in
college.
Right.
Sixth year in college.
But it's normal.
It would be normally, you know, what people
how people used to converse, let's say, 100
years ago.
He uses big words.
Right.
So, yeah, that would be another place to
start.
Any time we see if I think I
bookmarked, I think it's on another laptop.
But let's say I'll bring it up in
the car.
What anything else in the meantime?
I have a very long comment that I
thought was very solid.
And I wanted to run it by you,
but I don't know if you can put
up with my echo.
Oh, yeah.
The echo is pretty.
OK.
So all medical theories, whether conventional or, quote,
alternative and quote past or current are based
on the concept that disease are, quote, malfunctions
and quote of the organism.
Dr. Hamer's H.A.M.E.R. discovery
show, however, that nothing in nature is, quote,
diseased and quote, but always biologically meaningful.
According to the five biological laws, diseases are
not malignancies, as claimed by conventional medicine, but
are instead age old biological special programs of
nature.
Biological special programs of nature is, in quotes,
created for our survival.
The five biological laws are in perfect harmony
with spiritual laws.
Because of this truth, the Spanish call the
new medicine La Messina Sagrada.
Yeah, La Messina Sagrada, the sacred medicine.
OK, I thought that was a good comment.
That's pretty good, right?
Yeah, yeah.
The whole idea.
Let's go back to the.
Everybody knows enough about cars.
You're driving down the road, reciprocating engine water
cooled.
Your water pump stops working.
Now your engine doesn't cool down.
The engine burns up and seizes.
The pistons get so hot that they actually
bind themselves to the engine block.
Right.
So someone, the current disease theory would be
like, oh, the problem is we is the
piston getting stuck to the engine block or
the metal melted.
Right.
No.
Well, it all started because a water pump
wasn't working.
Right.
So the water pump led to the engine
seizing.
You've heard that before.
It's very common.
It used to be common.
I've heard a lot.
And that's just because you didn't have cooling.
It led all the way to these other
disasters.
So the body is very much like that,
but it's also too much energy, not enough
energy.
But, you know, you know, I'll just reiterate
something during covid.
People have I walked into a place called
Sprouts and this was like two months into
the mask mania.
And I'm going to go in without a
mask.
And I just march in like, you know,
and I'm halfway into the store.
And a guy comes up, says, you have
to have a mask on.
I said, well, I don't have an immune
system.
Is that a big issue?
Is that like a vegan?
Is that like a vegan focused grocery store?
Sprouts or not?
You know, it's like a dish.
It's like a discount version of Whole Foods.
Oh, OK.
It used to be called it used to
be called Sunflower Market.
And yeah, it was it's weird.
This did some weird stuff to the guy
who originally owned it.
But it's California, Colorado and Arizona.
OK, it's like imagine Whole Foods been to
a Whole Foods, but discounted.
Right.
Pretty thankful.
Yeah, that's pretty good.
So so I told him anyway, I don't
have an immune system.
And he took that as I don't need
a mask now.
And I would have taken a hundred lie
to test detector tests and put my hand
on a stack of Bibles.
And it would show that I'm not lying.
Right.
Because I don't have an immune system.
As a matter of fact, no one does.
There's no such thing.
But anyway, what was cool about it?
Everyone's all masked up and I'm walking through
and he's walking me down the aisles, tell
people ahead of me to move away.
And he's asking, what are you here to
get today?
I want this.
So he would walk me right to the
office.
He's like assistant manager.
Right.
He knows everything.
Help me do my shopping.
He he stopped the line for the cash
register.
No more people go to the other register.
And he had me give it was like,
oh, my gosh, I got first class treatment,
got out of it.
Thank you for coming in.
Right now, most people can't say that confident.
OK, so if you have an immune system,
what's the organ for the immune system?
Huh?
What?
Yeah, I thought so.
There isn't.
So explain what the immune system does.
Well, you see, Greek, it has antibodies and
it captures things that are nasty toxins, viruses,
stuff, and then eliminates them from the body.
Ah, sounds like.
So it's basically the elimination system.
So elimination system.
We've got kidneys, bladder, liver, large intestine.
Yeah.
So we do have organs for the elimination
system, don't we?
We do.
Ah.
So now.
So now immune system equals elimination system.
How is your elimination system working?
Like Linda works with people, you know, by
appointment and stuff.
And, you know, they have a lot of
chat to chat times.
And she says a lot of people she
talks to when you get health stuff.
Yes.
How often do you pass a bowel movement?
Some of them are like once a week,
twice a week.
Can you imagine all that stuff in there
was you hear like John Wayne and Elvis
Presley?
He had like 30 pounds of undigested meat
in his intestines.
Remember that?
That was I don't know why they put
it out there.
Yeah.
So we're reading about that or hearing it.
Because the the but the opioids that they
give them arrest the digestion.
So neurotoxins and food will do that.
So if you're not eliminating, isn't it the
same as not taking the garbage out to
the curb for a long time?
Right.
What's the difference?
You're going to a really gross house.
Let's get all the garbage out of here
first.
Right.
OK.
So you're rotting.
And then, of course, combine that with poor
nutrition coming in in great quantities, really using
the wrong type of gas in the engine
and filling up the tank with the wrong
type of fuel.
Right.
Imagine.
Yes.
So this is where this is the rot
and ignorance and destruction of your society is.
Yeah.
And the people that are the medical people,
most of them don't know it because they're
they're not bad people, but they're not good
people either.
That's for sure.
For sure.
I can't tell you for sure all the
people in the medical industry are bad, but
I can tell you for sure, for sure,
for sure.
They're not good people.
And so somewhere else, the people that are
running them even don't know the stuff we
discuss here.
It's the people above them and the people
above them.
And then ultimately you go to the people
that are running it are not really human
at all.
All right.
Like, again, I've mentioned there's no species in
the universe.
Let's say in the in the realm, even
on Earth, that will create a long term
demise for its own species.
Can you think of one?
You might hear about like a spider eating.
It's that's what the black widow eats her
mate.
Right.
Or whatever.
And you have certain animals that eat their
young and whatever.
Or eat the mom or other ones.
I think when there's some spiders.
Yeah.
There's a couple of them.
They eat the mother.
There's a couple of them that, you know,
do a territorial.
Yeah.
They do a territorial thing, though, where it's
like there's too many males.
So they fight with each other and kill
each other a bit to thin out the
herd.
You can have a species wide.
But what's going on?
In other words, with the delusion.
Right.
So at least with those guys, the animals,
you know, there's no delusion.
It's well known that they do that.
Right.
Yeah.
But the humans are so delusional that they're
going to these, quote unquote, professionals for help.
I had a legal discussion today with someone
that didn't want to identify themselves as an
attorney and talk about every time I have
a discussion with a medical person or an
attorney, it just.
Do you remember when you were young and
you knew a sidewalk was poured and you
go put your name on it?
Right.
Yeah.
Or scratch into it or whatever.
You know, it hardens that.
It's like every time when I speak about
how horrible the legal financial medical stuff is,
whenever I speak to one of these people
that work in it, it helps harden that
concrete.
It makes the stuff that I'm saying seem
even harder, more true, not more true, but
harder and harder.
Like like sometimes like maybe I mean too
harsh on these guys.
And I get a refresher every so often
that this is definitely how it is.
And they're just helping me.
What would you call solidify the fact, you
know?
So it's sort of that whole, you know,
when people show you who they are the
first time, you know, pay attention because it
doesn't get any better.
You know, it's that concept.
It's, you know, if you're right the first
time, you're going to be right the last
time, too.
Anyway.
Well, yeah, that's that's where the thing says
you don't have to say you're sorry.
Like very often with people know me for
a long time.
I've never said anything to anyone that I
would take back and say, I'm sorry.
I might maybe now modify the way I
said it.
Right.
The way I delivered it, maybe.
But what I said, no, that still stands.
You have to be very careful about what
you say.
And then, of course, there's stuff like when
you find a historical thing that you might
have espoused as it was incorrect.
And it shouldn't be a surprise, by the
way.
Then you go back and change and say,
I was wrong about that.
Right.
But it's still it's not taking it back
or saying, you know, what do we say?
Say you're sorry.
You know, no.
Everything I've ever said, even when I've called
people idiots or dumb or whatever.
Yes.
It took a lot to get me to
that point.
And, you know, it was well, it was
may not have been well taken, but it
was well-deserved.
Right.
Anyway, what else?
All I've ever had to do is modify
a position on a historical thing.
You know, I discuss that kind of stuff
all the time.
And it's like, well, because of this new
information.
Yes.
There's more proof of this and that.
And, OK, I have to adjust a bit,
but it's never like I don't make sweet.
And it was objective anyway.
You couldn't you know, you did the best
you could at the time.
So always do the best you can.
And here's the other kicker is that I've
been saying the same stuff about the medical
stuff since the 80s.
In the 80s, 40 years ago, I said,
all they do want to do is cut.
They're going to give you a diagnosis, then
which is presumption.
And then they're either going to cut on
you, burn on you or poison you.
So take your pick.
You know, what's funny is there were TV
characters in the 80s that pretty much were
echoing what you were saying, but they were
usually portrayed as the, you know, belligerent nut
job who just didn't want to fight with,
you know, the good medicine.
And but they were saying the same exact
thing.
It's just that they were then characterized as
that's the resistant idiot who's going to get
himself killed because he's not listening to us.
And I take note of that.
There was a representative character now and then
it was usually an older guy, you know,
and most times they would just, you know,
act like, oh, well, he was just old
and ill informed, you know.
But it turns out he was right.
Anyways, well, the 80s was a good was
40 years ago.
I wouldn't go back there, but I'm glad
I was there.
Exactly.
So here's something else about the body.
If our bodies are electrical, what is the
effect of rhythmic breathing?
Question mark.
Would that be something like electrically recharging the
body, increasing the voltage?
Mark.
OK, no, it would it would increase the
processes.
Right.
Because when you breathe faster, other things follow
through.
Right.
A whole bunch of other things from that
metabolic.
That's why you have aerobic exercise and anaerobic
where you can't get enough air.
Right.
The electrical part is a substrate.
Don't really be concerned too much about that.
That takes care of itself.
It's kind of like your car needs work,
but you're always just looking at the battery
fluid and the battery is charged enough.
That's OK.
That's fine.
And then go to the next thing.
It's all these other things that are putting
a drain on the battery or not allowing
it to recharge.
Right.
And electricity is a very, very, very touchy
subject because it is not any electricity like
you'd find in a battery cell of any
type or coming out of a wall or
whatever it is.
All electricity is it's an expression of the
ether and how it's being pressurized.
You know, most electricity, except for the chemical
electricity from a battery, is magnetically pressurized.
And believe it or not, the one even
that is batteries are designed for tend to
be magnetically pressurized also, but not like, you
know, a rotating stator like you see on
a generator.
So the more chemical cells, batteries are more
realistic to live, you know, what a body
is, but not really again.
Right.
So it's a complex subject that if I
I'm going to be going that that road.
Actually, I had a conversation with someone today.
There's an energy device that's being used on
large groups of people for good, by the
way.
There's a company that is making like if
you're going to have a big venue, a
rave or whatever.
Right.
They set up these devices.
At least I didn't say scale or neither
did they.
So good because scalar is an oxymoron when
it's used to with waves and stuff.
And he says that it gives you a
feel good feeling.
And they want me to look at the
circuit and transducers.
And I said, I'll be glad to look
at that shit.
Who doesn't want to feel good by just
plugging something into a wall?
Right.
Other than you know what?
So I hear you.
OK.
Also, this is a follow up from another
sub subscriber, that is.
And also on the body, electric can Greek
comment on the effect of the emo on
our organs.
And if there is any electrical charge that
happens between people in conflict that can harm
us.
That's a good question.
The emo is created by the the organs,
by the way, that they would be part
of the generator.
Because remember, when you set up your body
to do the emo, you can just think
a thought.
It has to trigger that feeling also like
the giving feeling.
I say gesture a hug.
And when you feel that feeling that you
do when you're giving a hug, now you're
ready to give the giving.
Right.
And all that.
So you have to get the body into
that feeling.
And that's generated by the organs.
And I know that when people are missing
organs, you still have a phantom effect from
it.
You know, but yeah, that's a good question.
The organs, if you look at them, you
know, they're very discernible.
The kidney cells are very different from any
other organ.
And liver cells are different from so on
and so forth.
It's almost as if a group of aliens
got together to cooperate, to work inside of
you.
That's how strange they are.
Right.
So but the charging and all that, the
Tai Chi, Qigong fighting method, which is there
is no way of doing it.
There is no it's not like practice this
like a Kido or Tai or karate.
The Qigong is to borrow as much energy
as you need to focus where you need
it.
So, for example, if you're in a conflict,
an armed conflict, a physical conflict with someone
and there's people watching, you draw the energy
from all the people watching around you to
yourself and then focus it out towards what
you want to focus on doing.
Right.
We're not on YouTube, so I could say.
So if you want to knock the guy
down, you're going to have to go after
his legs.
It's a lot easier to knock someone down
by attacking below the knees than hitting him
on the shoulder.
Hitting someone on the shoulder is not going
to knock him down.
Hitting them below the knees will.
So you start portioning off where you're going
to send that energy.
Now, let's say you're alone with someone and
you want to you're on the defensive or
the offensive and there's no people around to
take energy from.
You take it from the tree.
Right.
You can take and say there's no trees
and there's parked cars.
You take it from the car engine, the
residual field of energy that was around the
car engine.
And when you're training for Qi Gong and
Tai Chi, you train yourself to draw energy
off of your surroundings and then focus it.
Isn't there an X-Men that does that?
No.
X-Men seem to be autonomously powered, aren't
they?
Well, no, there is.
There is an X-Men.
Magneto?
He draws from his environment?
He draws.
He can manipulate metal.
So metal is something that he can just
choose to move and pressurize.
But there are others.
There's a big, wide range of them.
So there are others that actually draw in
all of the stuff.
There's ones that draw from the ether.
There's ones that draw from other X-Men.
There's ones that draw, you know, like the
one guy can draw from everybody's mind.
It depends.
They all have different sources, actually.
They're conduits of all sorts.
So this ties in with the emo, ties
in with the...
everything is tied in.
That's the whole thing about Qi Gong, Qi
Gong Tai Chi.
I think Bruce Lee in his final days
was talking about it, but he couldn't really
put much forward because there's nothing to put
forward.
Everyone does it differently when you get into
Qi Gong.
Now in the secret schools, which you will
be...
If you've learned what they teach in the
secret schools and you start teaching it without
permission, you will be taken out.
They will send an assassin after you.
They could probably even do it remotely.
Actually, some of the things they do teach
in the secret schools is to do it
remotely.
I've been accused of teaching stuff in the
secret schools, and I never was in the
secret schools, so I guess I'm okay.
Yeah, it's funny you bring up Bruce Lee
because toward the end of his life, one
of the things he was talking about is
how energy is extended beyond your hand.
It's not necessarily your fist making contact and
stuff like...
He was trying to explain that to people,
that there is...
It's rivers of energy.
You want to tap into a river of
it, yeah.
And then there's...
to get more...
I dare say I'm going to do a
webinar on Qi Gong and how to...
I haven't...
I have so many things to talk about.
But I think we do well here on
the Sonics.
But that's a whole discussion because it's so
subtle.
And when you realize...
well, it's like the weather stuff.
How are you going to...
the weather stuff is a Qi Gong thing.
You have this hollow pipe that's grounded.
How does it affect thousands of square miles
of atmosphere, right?
It behooves anyone to think about, but you
know it works.
It's scientifically proven, you know, on your own.
You can't go to these scientists, you know.
The real scientists are the ones...
The real scientists that are employed are the
ones with sledgehammers to go around and destroy
what doesn't conform to their bullshit, right?
Right.
But the Tai Chi Qi Gong, that's a
very, very personal thing.
All you could teach is the concept.
There's no method to teach.
The best thing about the way how you
advance Qi Gong is by getting the people
to understand what it is, giving them some
hints on what you know, and then seeing
what they come up with, and then add
that to your toolbox.
So if you were doing Tai Chi or
Qi Gong practice with 10 people, and you
did it properly, you would have 10 different
ways of doing something very soon, where initially
you only had one, right?
Yeah.
And how are you going to teach this
to a society that is designed to be
enslaved in a school system that teaches you
that you're worth nothing, and everything goes by
the bell, and you're always looking for approval,
and you're being degraded by being graded, right?
Right.
Remember we used to talk about that a
lot?
Absolutely.
You know, it's very much that Eastern concept
of being a teacher and a student simultaneously,
which people misunderstand because of poor translation, number
one.
But number two, they can't wrap their minds
around that.
If you're there to teach, you're there to
teach.
If you're there to learn, you're there to
learn.
There's actually a process where that doesn't necessarily
stand, that that's all you do.
Well, here's the thing.
I got into education for a little while,
and it's such an oxymoron because it's a
severe oxymoron, because children, like it or not,
let's say children in an open environment, right?
You just go to a place, you drop
children by themselves, nothing else.
They are ready to soak up everything.
They are learning machines.
They are learning machines from 3, 4, even
2 years old and on.
I've seen 2-, 3-year-olds hang out
with the 4-, 5-year-olds, 6-, 7
-year-olds, and they're all into what you're
doing, right?
So they are learning machines more than anything
else, right?
And yet there's a problem on how to
teach them?
Come on, guys.
The problem is how do you get them
to all uniformly conform to a system that
objectifies them into nothing, right, and has them
always looking for approval?
Well, if you think carefully about the stacking
questions that are constantly brought up, right, the
2-year-old that keeps asking why, how,
they're asking a profound thing, and they're connecting
things together, and you're literally teaching, but what
happens is the adult gets exhausted from answering.
Because that's what they do.
They're like kittens and puppies.
They're learning machines.
They want to get into everything.
That's why with the animals here, whenever I
bring something new, like I open a jar
of something I haven't opened in a while,
they're all like, what are you doing?
And it's like they're afraid to come over.
Is it dangerous?
So what I do is I calmly show
them very slowly and let them sniff it
and look at it, and then they turn
away.
They're like, oh, thanks for showing that.
I never saw that before.
Thanks a lot, like I tell Linda all
the time.
These cats, they like to learn.
So educate them, always educating them.
Something new, whatever, you'll show them very calmly
because if you don't present it to them,
you notice how they take a cautionary stance
when they're trying to figure out what it
is.
It's like, yeah, let's just teach them.
Just bring it right over and say, hey,
this is what this is, and they're like,
oh, cool, walk right away, just like children.
Pretty much.
Children are learning machines.
All they want to do is learn constantly,
and it's such an oxymoron.
Education is how do we teach children?
What do you mean?
You don't have to do anything.
You just have to accommodate their physical size.
If you're working on something that's tall, you
have to pick them up to see it.
If something's too big and too heavy, don't
let them carry it.
Just accommodate them in the slightest ways.
It's incredible to me how they can say
we have a problem in education with beings
that all they want to do is be
educated.
That's all they do.
Yeah, and Tonya, it couldn't get any sicker
than that.
You know what I mean?
Exactly.
It's like how do we give water to
thirsty people?
All these people are so thirsty.
How are we going to get them to
drink water?
You don't have to do anything.
Just present them with the water.
Everything's already in place.
God damn it.
They're really bad.
Fair enough.
Really bad shape.
Some episodes ago, O and G mentioned doing
a home ec show.
Excuse me.
The wife and I are eager to act
on that info.
We're up on universal principles for diet and
lawful behavior and timekeeping.
Broaching finances now, I guess, in more home
ecs next.
Thanks for the efforts.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah, I'll bring up something on the home
ec.
I've noticed this because I've been moving stuff
around, doing preparations and things.
If you live in a tight space or
not, I've found this with people who have
property or an outdoor space, if you have
these commercial cleaning chemicals or chemicals in the
house, put them outside.
If you have any substances, chemicals, cleaning, or
otherwise that that company is being traded on
the stock market, just put it that way.
It shouldn't be in your house.
What I've been doing is you do, like,
for example, here I have what I call
the chemical.
Where's the polish for this?
It's in the chemical cabinet.
That's outside.
And I could go out there and it'll
be like car wax, detergents, laundry soap, all
outside.
The importance of that is this.
You ever walk down a supermarket aisle where
the soaps are?
If I blindfolded you and asked you to
guess what aisle, where are you, you'd be
able to guess right on, right?
Oh, yeah.
Because you smell bleach.
It's degassing.
Yeah, you smell bleach and you smell all
that stuff.
Well, it's an all mixed together flavor montage.
You know it's chemical.
So you're breathing this indoors.
And what I used to do when I
lived in Manhattan and New York, I had
a milk crate with a cover on it
and I would put it on the fire
escape.
And sometimes you'd come back and the whole
thing would be gone.
That's when it was more of a rough
neighborhood.
But usually they respected stuff on the fire
escape.
It was like an unwritten rule.
You leave people's shit alone when it's on
the fire escape.
Or the landlord says you have to move
that because the fire department is going to
give me a fine.
Or you put it, if you have a
walk up, you go all the way to
the top where the exit is, you put
it in a box up there.
The other thing you could do is box
it up and have a hose that vents
it out near a window.
But you don't want to vent it out
in the window.
That's also going to suck the fresh air
in.
But putting chemicals and things outside, like I
have a cabinet with various glues, like what
they call crazy glue and other things like
that.
And now I put it in a mason
jar, which has a seal on it.
And when I open it to get the
crazy glue out, there is the strongest fumes
of crazy glue.
And that would have been leaking into your
apartment or house.
It probably makes a noise from the pressure
release because it's been building up those fumes
in there, right?
Not that much.
No, it's just a very strong fume.
It equalizes pressure.
The noise would be, you'd have to make
it really hot or really cold difference where
the vacuum would build up on either side.
But what I'm saying is most of the
problems, especially when they're building these ticky-tacky
houses, these subdivisions, houses that were built after
the 1960s or 70s, yes, it's that much
of a problem.
You must leave a window slightly open, even
if you're in a cold place.
As a matter of fact, these new homes,
they make these special bathroom fans, these little
fancy-using bathrooms that go up on the
top floor, and they're designed to run 24
-7.
And the reason they do that is so
the inhabitants in these homes don't die because
the homes are made of 20% formaldehyde,
meaning all the particle board and composite boards
are up to 20% formaldehyde.
So embalming materials, very toxic ureas and things
like that.
So most of the elements you see in
suburbia are because the houses are not ventilated.
Also, when the houses are shut down too
tight, these super-insulated houses, you get these
weird strains of mold that only grow in
those conditions that you would find, like, growing
in a cavern or something combined with the...
So what I'm trying to say is fresh
air exchange and things that are outgassing should
be away from your living space.
And I've been experimenting with that lately, like
putting certain things with VOCs, volatile organic compounds,
in mason jars and then opening them not
much later, and you could see the fumes
that come out of there.
So you're actually toxifying yourself.
Now, fortunately, not enough people are dropping dead
for them to do anything about it, but
I think enough people are getting ill or
toxified from it.
But the home economic thing basically is to
be clean in your home, and it doesn't
mean using chemicals.
Most white Americans think being clean is going
and buying these chemicals with companies traded on
the stock market, you know, that toxic stuff,
synthetic.
No, it's water, use of water.
Just most of the time, like, give you
an example.
When I mop here, I have all tile
floor, all resilient floor, and stained concrete in
the back bedrooms.
No carpeting.
We have area rugs, but no carpeting.
When I mop the floor, I use something
called ship shape.
It's like a yellow powder, or I use
a little bit of a dishwashing liquid.
You could even use, like, a hair shampoo,
by the way.
You just need a little surfactant.
And when I mop, I do the soap
once.
The next time I mop, I just use
plain water to get any residue that was
up there.
So every time I mop the floor, I
only use a soap every other time.
How many times have you heard, especially in
commercial floors, oh, we got to come in
and strip these floors and repolish them, right,
because they get soap buildup and wax buildup,
right?
I've noticed that most people, when they're clean,
they use soap every time.
Try to use it every other time.
Believe it or not, if you have a
clean enough diet, all you need is water
to clean your clothes, unless you have grease
and grime that the soap needs to release.
And I used to tell people, when you
do your laundry, go ahead and do your
laundry without any soap, and then open the
wash and look inside and see how sudsy
it is, even without the soap, right?
So I only got two more pieces left
here.
Let's see.
Is the weight loss jab phenomenon happening now,
part of the setup for the, quote, perfect
society, unquote, before the glitches, question mark?
I see it as a poison being presented
as a good thing, so a prank for
sure.
What was the first part?
That goes really intense.
Go ahead.
What was the first part of the question?
Sorry.
Is the weight loss jab phenomenon happening now,
part of the setup?
I'm not aware of it.
The weight loss phenomenon being recently, or since
we first came out back in the 70s?
No, no, no.
This is new stuff where there's these injections
like Ozempic and stuff like that.
Oh, my gosh.
Well, thankfully, we'll put it this way.
Thankfully, I don't think any humans are taking
that next question.
Okay.
In other words, you have to be so
removed from your humanity to fall for something
like that.
I never want to even address it.
Okay.
Fair enough.
But it is rather commonplace among the masses,
so to speak, just so you know.
It's a good, but not to discount the
effort of the question.
It's great.
Thank you for asking, because I didn't know.
I mean, if you, yes, other people, look,
there's even people that, men that want to
be women and women that want to be
men.
I mean, you know how deranged that is?
Yeah, but that's.
You know, we're two different species.
But no matter what.
That's like saying I want to be a
dog.
Yeah, but no matter what.
No matter how they try to amplify that,
that's still a small number in the in,
you know, among the masses.
This is epic.
Thing is large.
There are people even like creating compounding facilities
to try and make the stuff cheaper and
everything else, which the drug companies.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, it's it's a very large.
Most.
Yeah.
Unless.
Okay.
There's two types of weight gain.
One is because you're malnourished and the body's
like we need to store up somehow because
we're not getting any nourishment.
We're actually in a famine condition.
So we need to store up.
Okay.
Right.
Because the food that's coming in has so
little nutrition.
And the other one is that you're eating
food that is so rich in nutrition that
you're getting fat.
Right.
How do you discern the two?
Very simple.
Just ask them what they eat.
You're right.
You know, I have pepperoni pizza and Diet
Coke.
Why am I gaining weight?
Right.
So, yeah, that's well.
So years ago, gaining weight was a sign
of wealth.
Right.
You know that.
Oh, yeah.
So everybody was skinny at a point.
And they actually had, you know, look, she's
a nice thick girl.
Right.
Or a thick boy.
They're very well taken care of.
Yeah.
So they're well fed.
They obviously have money.
It's bizarre.
Yeah.
No, definitely.
But I'm just saying it's much like much
like that trend you were thinking of with
the diet pills and all that and the
diet systems.
Yeah.
This thing is new in that it's just
an injection like there's nothing else.
It's just inject yourself with this.
I get it.
I get the injection part.
Fine.
But let me just say it like this.
Thankfully, there aren't any humans that have gotten
it yet.
There you go.
All right.
So last one.
Last one.
And this is quite a doozy.
Greetings, Chuck.
In Greek.
Can you please elaborate on how Christianity is
satanic?
Hmm.
Adversarial to the scriptures.
Yes.
Satan means adversary.
Right.
So satanic would be your.
See, Satan is very simple.
It's when it should be black.
It tells you make it white.
When it's to go up, it tells you
make it down.
It's not this Hollywood thing.
Right.
It's just adversarial.
So like, you know, you should be going
to the right.
He tells you to go to the left.
Absolutely.
Satanic.
And from that respect.
Now, you can take that on a broad
term where you have a character that brings
other specific things like disease and whatever else
like that.
You know, you could say that goes on
there, too, because if you look at the
Christians, they're tied in with the medical industry.
Right.
Very much.
Absolutely.
And the political.
Every time you go to church, they tell
you, pay your taxes and go see the
doctor.
So they're satanic for disease.
Yeah, it's pretty satanic.
All right.
And but the only thing is, I don't
know.
I would say that it has to do
with that's what happens when you don't study
and read.
There's there's an emphasis on gaining knowledge in
all the ancient writs.
Right.
And one of the things, if you go
to the biblical narrative, how many times does
it say to gain knowledge and to study?
I mean, I don't have a number on
it, but it's dozens of times, if not
100 times at least.
Right.
And what do the Christians do?
They just told to believe.
So it's definitely satanic adversarial to what you're
supposed to be doing.
For sure.
It's just a control mechanism.
It's very cheap because anytime you want to
control people, you want to before you set
out on doing that, you want to figure
out how much you have to invest into
a control apparatus, don't you?
Of course.
So if you have something like Christianity, that's
a marvelous control apparatus.
And guess what?
How much do you have to invest in
that?
You tell the followers to pay for it
to donate 10 percent or whatever.
So you couldn't end it with a more
perfect system.
Yeah.
It's kind of like I was discussing some
finance.
You know, anyone who has a checking account,
anyone who has a checking account, a regular
one, is paying 100 percent bank fees, 100
percent.
So when you write a check to someone
for one hundred dollars, when that person, that
someone gets the check and they endorse it
and there are two signatures on that instrument
and there's a date and the number, the
amount is written out in words, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, of giving you 100
percent fees on my checks, let's make it
10 percent according to like what state the
state law suggests.
So in other words, you would write a
check for one hundred dollars to someone and
you go back to your account and they
took out ten dollars instead of one hundred.
How about that?
It doesn't take a genius to figure that
out.
Just go read about what negotiable instruments are.
blah, blah, blah, UCC, you know, 3-104,
all these little simple acts, Federal Reserve Acts,
right?
Right.
And go to your bank.
Yeah.
Your bank statement doesn't say we get 100
percent fees, 100 percent checking fees.
No.
They just say you're giving us all security
and just giving us all of it, bitch.
Right.
So how about write a letter to them
amending the terms of service?
How about you guys?
Let's start off.
Take 10 percent on my checking.
All right.
So I write a check for a thousand
bucks.
You take out 100.
Or if I write a check for 900
bucks, you take out 90.
How's that?
Isn't that more reasonable, people?
Because when you send someone an instrument that
says pay to the order of electronic also.
Right.
And the funds are created.
The accounting credit on account is credited when
the person on the other end endorses it.
Also, is there anything that I said that
an eighth grader couldn't be explained?
Was it?
Where is it?
Remember?
And it was at the eighth grade.
They showed you how to write a check,
how to write numbers with words.
Remember that on the blackboard?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
That was earlier than that.
I think it was seventh or eighth grade.
Yeah.
Well, you one day you'll get a check.
You have to write a check.
Now, write this out, please.
Right.
Yeah.
On the blackboard or whatever.
Why don't they tell you that?
By the way, they're going to be doing
100 percent fees on your checking.
Well, they don't say that part.
Yeah.
But the thing that I remember this.
No one does.
But by the way, I'm the only person
that I've ever heard on the Internet or
not that just said all checking accounts are
basically 100 percent banking fees.
I'm going to I'm putting together a much
simpler way to discuss the financial stuff because
it's time.
Yeah.
It's like Molotov cocktails.
Instead of driving in with a tank, you
just have these, you know, you just want
to you got to put your stuff together,
you know, and make it real easy.
When you start explaining the negotiable instruments and
all that to people, they glaze over when
you say 100 percent checking, 100 percent bank
fees on your checking account.
What does that mean?
They get you get their attention a little
more clearly.
Right.
So and during one of these discussions back
and forth about, you know, finance and money
and stuff, the somebody posted the Emergency Banking
Relief Act, the Emergency Banking Act of 1933,
1933.
Yeah.
There is a Wikipedia page and they just
said hint.
So I think I think that's that that
goes back to your discussion about the receivership
and all that.
Yeah.
But it's over.
There is.
It's all leveled out now.
It's no it's all accepted.
In other words, you're never going to go
back to substance money.
They say so.
Right.
Because as long as they have the full
force and might of the U.S. military,
they're going to also have the full faith
and credit of the U.S. government and
also the Federal Reserve Act that states that
Federal Reserve notes represent a first lien mortgage
on all property in the United States, persons
and property.
You might even say persons.
I'm not sure.
I read it both ways.
So, yeah.
So, you know, they have a lien on
everything.
So basically, let's say there's 300 million people
in the U.S. You're a one in
300 million shareholder of everything.
Right.
But there's no cap and there's no conditions.
Yeah.
So basically what I just said will collapse
the labor market, by the way.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
I mean, is that is that a cat
acting like a dog, by the way?
Or is that a dog?
No, that's a dog, not a cat.
Yeah.
The neighbor got it's a beautiful, good looking
pit bull mix.
And it doesn't know how to act.
It's quite far away, actually.
But it projects because we're in the desert.
You know, dry air.
I think it was a dryer.
Humid air projects more.
I think dry air.
I think dry air is a damping effect.
Yeah.
But yeah.
So, yeah, I'm going to be giving some
more just down factual to the point financial
stuff, because I think it's been time for
a long time.
You're not going to destroy the labor market.
Most people are just too moronic.
I mean, they're really dead people.
I mean, again, going back to Christianity being
satanic.
I mean, let's just say this.
Fortunately, there are no humans in that Christian
religion.
You know what I mean?
I mean, what are they?
They're cattle.
Yeah.
And here's the thing.
Are they bad people?
I'll say it again.
No, they're not bad people.
But are they good people?
No, they're definitely not good people.
It can't be good because if you even
if you do good acts as a Christian
or whatever, you're going to get suckered into
some evil shit real fast, thinking you're doing
good.
So does that still keep you good?
In other words, even if you haven't done
anything like they at the potential of being
led into that so automatically.
Right.
You cannot be classified as being.