A sonic event 102, rated Y, Ocelli and the Greek. So, let's just get it started where
it needs to start. I would ask Greek how he's doing. Not gonna ask, I'll find out in a moment.
I'm gonna ask him this instead. How's that celebrity chef thing doing? You know, apparently
as people got bombed, you like to bring up celebrity chefs, Greek. No, actually, I don't.
I bring up a lot of cooking and what I do say about celebrities and, well, chefs as well,
is that no one, in remark to the popularity of cooking shows, is no one will ever learn
how to cook properly or good food by watching all that, right? Oh, right, but you bring
that up every time. Like, lately, we've done a bunch of things where you've given people
instructions. Yeah, I keep saying, because people gravitate. Just like you're not gonna
be a good filmmaker from watching good film, right? No, no, and even if you watch the documentaries,
The Making Of, some people like to do that, right? You're not gonna, yeah, exactly, so.
But that's the level, I think before we started recording, you brought it up, I said, did
I spell that chef's name right? Yeah. Right, because it's bad news, right? So, you see,
it's all BS. And what did I say? Do you know in the past four hours, over a thousand people
were killed by doctors knowing that they were gonna, you know, their patients were gonna
die. And maybe 3,000 or 5,000 in the U.S. alone since this morning. How many people
are listing that in the television program called The News? None. So, you know what I
say about those celebrity people? Fuck them, and their help. And here's the ultimate, here's
the ultimate statement, right? Which, you know, here we go. I'm gonna challenge the Greek
and tell them to tell me that I'm not telling the truth entirely when I say this. I love
doing this. No, it's not a matter about the truth, it's a matter of what you're, if what
you're conveying has any value. But go ahead. Okay, well, let's see if this has any value.
How about this? I have stated before, and will continue to state, that the medical industrial
complex has literally killed more people in the time that we're looking at, you know,
modern times, and all the combined wars. You combine all those casualties all together.
I do mean World War II, World War I, all of the stuff since the United States existed.
In that time period, the medical industrial complex has absolutely killed way more people
than all the wars combined. Right or wrong? Right, and you don't even have to factor in
aborted babies. You don't even have to factor in, you know, other stuff, too. So, car accidents
or anything, I mean, it's just the medical, yeah. Yeah, I agree. Okay, well, here's the
thing. I'm not anti-medical, I'm just anti-stupid. But here's the other thing. I recently, um...
There's a t-shirt. Yeah, I had a conversation with a doctor recently. They're actually gonna
be installing some water devices, for plural. And I've known them for a while, a decade
and a half or so. And by the way, you know, when you hear me speaking... Curiosity, doctor's
home or office for the water devices? Home, yeah. Okay, just checking, go ahead. Yeah,
the offices, they're an academic doctor, so... Oh, so they don't care what happens in the
office. Go ahead, yeah. There is not much of, yeah, the office is just a landing. But anyway,
when I speak about the attorneys and the doctors and the priests, it's not because I have some
opinion from reading an article or just see... It's because I know these bastards, right?
By observation is what you're doing. Yeah, and you know, it's funny, through the years,
among the older sonics here and there about various sundry places where I did sonics,
I would challenge people, if you know any one family member who's an attorney, you ask them
this and this is their answer. And if you know a doctor and you ask them this, this is how they're
going to answer. And, you know, I gave a specific answer in a specific question and people would
message me back and say, you know, my dad's an attorney and I asked him this and he answered
exactly what you said. How is that possible? How are we not noticing what kind of a... Yeah,
they're not... So anyway, regarding this medical person, they know what's going on, by the way.
They know, but they fully agree... Actually, let me just say this. Let's just be biased. I've
known them for a decade and a half, so I gave them the entire full Greek speak over the time
that we spent together regarding AIDS, virology, disease and all that. Okay, maybe I'll be a little
self-aggrandizing and say that they learned it from me. Most of it, yeah, in order to put it,
you know, what calories don't matter, there's no blood pressure. They know all this and they're
still continuing in the field because it's a matter of, you know, how else are they going
to make a living? Now, I do know, this is from seeing, when attorneys do quit, they become
car salesmen, not used car salesmen necessarily, but they always end up... Okay, when I say always,
most of the time when an attorney decides, okay, enough with the bar, the bar is a
Isn't that funny? Now, doctors, when they quit, they end up getting into some kind of retail
business, either a shop or whatever, or sports, you know, kind of thing. You're right. Retired
doctors, I used to work in the convenience store business, right? So I saw a lot of different angles
on this. And quite honestly, a lot of these like older guys who are coming in, not somebody who
worked their way up and decided to buy a store, but like an older guy who shows up with a check,
basically, and buys a business that's already existing, usually, and takes it over, and,
you know, sets it up so that like his kids can work there, this kind of thing, right?
That's usually a doctor. They end up working, I'm saying even from any perspective, but those
are the industries. But here's the thing, it's so, so predictable. But I want to be neutral,
like the Swiss on this, right? Which if you go even deeper, I'm not, because the Swiss are a
pretty evil bunch, meaning the, you know, the collective, the collective organization. But on
the other hand, you do have to give them some, the Swiss regarding, they were the last sovereign,
not sovereign, the last free nation, they were not, up until 2002, they were not part of the UN,
right, which is a club for all the corporations. And they couldn't join the UN because each man
and woman was considered to have their own rights and their own standing in politics.
So they couldn't send anyone to represent them, but they became a corporation,
they sent out some paperwork, had people sign them, they announced to them what they were doing.
And they joined the UN on, I think, September 12, 2002, because after 9-11, they gave them
an ultimatum, I don't know what it was. But I know that, like, for example, in World War I,
Turkey was given, the remnants of the Ottoman Empire was given an ultimatum that all their men
take on family names and surnames, and they switch their language from, you know, into
Roman characters, and also adopt the Pope's work schedule, right? So these things are done,
and they're quite major changes, and no one talks about them just like major changes.
Like, this is kind of a source, but I know someone that I was kind of fond of for a while,
regarding the medical, and, you know, about a month ago, someone told me that, oh, yeah,
they're not answering your calls, they're okay, they're just getting this medical treatment,
they have to be there every day. I said, oh, they're going to kill them. Two weeks later,
such and such died. I said, told you, pretty obvious, and he looked just fine. Anyway,
so I call that, by the way, medical Darwinism. You know, the whole evolution of species and all
that is not, because even Darwin himself, you know, said these were all theories that he borrowed
from his grandfather, by the way, who was more popular at the time. Darwin did not become popular
until the late 20th century. Well, and much like the Bible and everything else, the people that
pound on it and quote it and source it and everything else usually haven't read it. They
don't even know what they're talking about. No, but this is different. Darwin himself stated that
the majority of the, his evolution is a theory, but what he does know is that major changes come
from calamities and catastrophes, right? So it's really a catastrophist, which is basically the
creationist or catastrophist, too. Archaics is really good, has put forward a real good
synopsis and presentations on that. So what I'm saying here is medical Darwinism in the sense
that if you are stupid enough to proceed with what is going on in the medical community,
you pretty much deserve not to have your gene pool, or genetics main, you know, hang around,
right? You know, that's the Darwinism idea after that done. I like the donald bird got wiped out
because it was dumb, right? Well, whatever. Right. So let's just say, right. Okay. So yeah,
you're actually a dodo. Actually, we start coining that people that believe what the medical
establishment you call it, what is the medical complex? What did you call it? Yeah. Yeah,
the medical industrial complex. Yeah, there you go. Yeah, you're a dodo. They don't have patients,
they have dodos. So yeah, so it's really harsh. You know, it's kind of harsh. It's kind of like
I was listening to someone. I knew quite a bunch of people, especially when I lived in New York,
in the 80s that were in Europe during World War Two. And they knew a bombing raid was coming
because of espionage. And their city was quiet. This is in Hungary, and near Budapest. And
they they said, let's leave the apartment. Let's leave the apartment, just grab whatever you can.
And we'll come back in a few days and get the rest of the stuff. Well, they left, but they came
back in a few days. And guess what? It wasn't there, but it was hit, right? So and another
story was that they had, this was in Berlin, someone that I knew, an older person, they
early on in the war when the major actually towards the middle end, you know, 42, 43, 44,
bombing of Berlin. They had bombing shelters, and they would be in the bombing shelters. And
it was kind of like, you know, you knew something was going on on the surface.
And they would, and after the bombing stopped, they still kept the people underground for quite
a few hours, and he'd come up, it would be daylight morning. And you'd see elephants,
and lions and giraffes in the streets, right? Because the right the zoo got hit, right? And
the animals got out. Stories like that, right stuff that you don't see on the history channel,
right? You'll see. So what you see on the history channel, all this other stuff,
is the same stuff that the medical industry is doing, right? It's just the same stuff over and
over and people go for it. Now, what's going on that makes it so bizarre is the same thing that
if you start researching ancient cultures, and we do some research, I used to have like a pretty
like these encyclopedias of weird stuff. Do you remember those? Not not Ripley's, believe it or
not, but there was others like that. Yeah, no, there was a couple of different books. And they
were usually in the bookstore right next to the Guinness Book of World Records. Yeah,
novelty kind of stuff, you know, old information that's brought out newly. So look up if you can,
even on the stupid rectangle of bizarre traditions of ancient cultures, right? That no longer
practice. That's what you're living in right now, right? You know, that calories have something to
do with food. You have all these. All right. Okay. Anyway, going back to being neutral.
I want to thank people, by the way, who are trying out the suggestions and recommendations
that I'm making regarding the things to prepare food food wise. And I think they do find it to
be even though it might sound if you listen to the cabbage pot roast and broccoli steak,
right? Sounds kind of like this guy's insane. You know, who wants to eat that? Well, whoever tried
it. I've gotten some feedback from a couple of people. And there's one in the chat was like,
dude, this is pretty amazing. I mean, I know, I know. It's pretty amazing. All right. You know,
I got to try the cabbage thing, because I'll tell you, truthfully, generally, the way cabbage has
been presented to me in the past, and I usually don't work with it. But I've eaten, you know,
coleslaw, and I've eaten, you know, the cabbage that's inside of the egg rolls or whatever else
from a Chinese hold on, you're missing the point. You missed the whole point. I'm not saying eating
cabbage at all. You can eat cabbage 500 different ways. If you have to make it, it's very specific.
Oh, go back and listen to that sonic. I understand. That's what I'm getting to is that,
you know, I've eaten it before, though, and don't think of it as something that could be turned
into something that is substantial. Cabbage pot. Yeah. And it's wonderful on its own.
Yeah. It's a very substantial and it's very healthful. By the way, there's no such thing
as health. This is a repeat. This is very important. And I don't know how to drive it
home enough because you have to think about this every day to make use of it.
It's almost as crazy as people go, you know, the lettuce diet. And it's like,
OK, well, let me just say something. It's almost like I almost feel like every time I do a sonic
simply by just speaking to people in my own personal life. And now it seems like
every it's like there's no what is it? The goldfish has memory. 15 seconds or five. You know,
that's an analogy. Right. Just like I hope they spelled their name right. Yeah. OK.
There is no such thing as health. Right. Good health means that you have the fitness to do
what you require of yourself to do. So if you require of yourself to go climb a mountain tomorrow
and you have not achieved or don't contain or have the ability to do so because of your
fitness level, you are in poor health. Right. So you see what I mean? There is no such thing
as good health. So that's another medical fraud. They have this baseline of what blood pressure,
blood sugar. By the way, there's no blood measurable blood, blood sugar or sugar in
the blood that's done by analog. It's another fraud. Well, I've been meaning to ask you about
this, actually, about this good health thing, because isn't there a minimal baseline that you
could say is good health? For instance, you know, people that have trouble staying awake.
But people have trouble staying awake right now. Right. No, no. So stop. Stop there,
because it's so unusual. And I've given this analogy. I just I've been studying the medical
stuff since the 1980s in the big public library on 42nd Street, Fifth Avenue, the ones with lions
outside. Right. Yeah. No, I don't know. Nineteen or two. I've been to that. One of them was in
a movie a couple of years ago. It was like really cool. And I'm like, I don't think that place is
even there anymore. But good. Would people would go. I've maxed my time there. So I knew the hours
and I knew. So whenever I had free time, I would go there and because it was just beautiful
architecturally and all that. And just, you know, it was there was a film where it was a film. Maybe
it's imagining it. There was a film where some children are like they pull a book off the shelf
and they open the book and they go to the setting in the book. Right. That's how it is for me.
And I watched between like nineteen eighty three and nineteen ninety five, the salvage or removal
of areas of the library I put to the from public view. So I knew what what we have now was coming
just by when they remove these sections in these books, what are we what are they going to give us?
You know what? Well, anyway. So while I'm looking at all everything in the from the 1980s, let's say,
I realized that how easy information was to get and no one was looking at it at all.
But there was another point actually escaped my mind before you said that about health.
OK, I wanted to continue with which is your fitness level and the baselines that are created do not
exist. Like give an example. OK, this is the example I wanted to get. Recently, I spoke with
someone who works with a stationary bike company. I'm not going to mention the company. You probably
know they're the largest in the world and every it's all the rage. You know, it's got all the
tech and all that. And this person I brought up, the most famous cyclist, and they didn't know who
it was. It's like almost someone speaking with. And this is a point. This is not a smirch or
stain on them at all, because they're just a part of the culture. Right. It's it's is it
is it bad? No. But is it good? No, it's definitely not good. But here's the thing.
It's like someone who a young person, let's say someone in 30s is just getting into rock and roll
and doesn't know who Elvis is. Right. They want to do pop music, though. Right. Not. Right. OK.
So and they don't. Right. So that's right there. There's a problem. Right. Or you don't know who
the Beatles never heard of Elvis or the Beatles. I was going to say, yeah, that would be like,
oh, wow. OK, so are they bad for not knowing that? No, no. But is it good? No, it's not a good thing
either. Right. So you try to be neutral. Remember, so you said earlier. OK, so what I mentioned to
them in short is this stationary bike movement in terms of let's use the sex analogy is like
creating a whole culture that's based on masturbation, where the other the original
culture of the bike movement, where you go out and cycle would be like having sex
with a partner. Big difference now from an anatomical point of view. And this is a very
good analogy, because from an anatomical point of view, while, you know, you're stationary bike,
you're still turning the cranks with your feet, you're still getting cardio, whatever.
But you know what? No matter what you those people that focus on that stationary bike will
don't understand that 90 percent of the finesse of riding a bike and energy goes into balancing the
bike. Right. Taking your line steering right now, maneuvering and navigating the terrain.
These people on stationary bikes don't have that. Just like, for example, navigating the terrain
and all that and steering is in sex. Right. With a partner versus masturbation. Right. Right. So
and so and they're focusing it all on physical condition, which there is no such baseline.
And they also brought up their baselines. Those baselines don't work.
What I did learn from going back to the library, this is the point I want to bring up.
There was a study because back in the day, medical institutions that did research would
actually publish their findings in books. Right. It would be like the latest, you know,
usually five years after the study is done, you get just like now when you look at economic figures,
they're from twenty nineteen usually. Right. Yeah. You know. OK. So this was a study done
where they went to various medical institutions, went to study centurions, which are people that
live over a hundred places like the Hunza region, places like near Crete, Okinawa, so on and so
forth. And when they arrived, they asked where these people were and they were like, well,
they're not here. Well, you're sure they are. Where are they? Oh, you mean? Oh, yeah. Where
they are. Oh, yeah. They're out in the field working. So these people are one hundred,
one hundred and five, one hundred and ten. And they're working just like everyone else,
normal behavior. And they took their blood pressure and their blood pressure would be
like two eighty over two twenty. Right. Which means they need a quadruple bypass.
Their blood sugar would be four eighty or five hundred count, which means that you're going to
die. Right. Right. Normals, whatever. A third of that or a quarter of that. And so these people
would be on insulin and kidney dialysis and have quadruple bypasses. If you use the baseline,
right, that's being used in the society here right now. And it's not that they're that different.
Right. Like I sometimes joke around medical people with them. I said, what do you do with
someone that has two hearts? And they're like, oh, no, it is. Oh, yeah. They show up and the
hearts are underneath their armpits. It's not in the middle of the chest. And I start giving all the
anatomy of how if someone had if you had two hearts, where they would be and how they would
work and the doctors, they start. I use medical terms, of course. Right. And because you have to
know the language. Right. And they start freaking out. You know, I saw I did this once with someone
a few years ago and they ran out. They ran away from it. You know, of course. Right. So
it's not that strange. It's not that off. I mean, that's the two hearts. That's a fictional account.
But what they're doing is is almost as if they're applying that to you because there is no baseline.
And I can go on and on and on and on with when these baselines are very, very dangerous because
it's narrowing the field. It's not like when you're playing darts or shooting arrows,
there's a baseline there, because if you're playing darts or shooting arrows, well, not
shooting arrows, archery more than playing darts. You don't have to wonder what they're aiming for.
What does everybody know? What's the baseline? The bullseye. Right. Generally, generally. Yeah.
That's what everybody. OK, so, you know, it's not like that. It's not like there's a bullseye
on everyone. There's definitely a target on everyone. Well, you can be targeted.
Right. Then then it gets really rough for you. It doesn't mean that they'll succeed,
but it just gets really rough for you. But they see these baselines. It's just
like painting a target on someone and they have to. Right. So. But they do it in a way where
they shoot you in the kneecaps first. Right. Then they do the center mass. Right. So anyway,
that's the situation with that. Now, the thing about the I want to maybe continue a little bit
with the container is people that have been listening for a while know that I always talked
about wrapping it tight because of the biological vacuum in the body. Now, one situation came up
and I've done this naturally. Most people do. When you have a natural expulsion in the body
where something needs to be discharged through the skin, like let's say you have an itchy, OK,
on a limb, most likely it'll be on the left side, by the way. If it's a slow expulsion,
if and if it's a fast something that's going to last a very short time, it's going to be on the
right side. OK, what will happen? Let's say on your leg or your arm, you'll have an itchy spot.
And as it keeps getting issue, then it gets sore and then it breaks out and the skin breaks away
and you have a manifestation assist or pass or something, something might grow or whatever.
OK, that means that the body needs to let it out. So you want to encourage that by by massaging,
you know, and not wrapping it tight. Wrapping it tight at that point would be like putting a
potato in the exhaust pipe. I know some actually saying, you know, people may not know what that
means in the 70s. If you didn't like someone, you put it but you stuffed a potato in their gas pipe
in their car. Right. Right. Right. It wouldn't start. OK, so they need to encourage the flow.
But the flow just now just leaving it alone, let's say, or massaging doesn't mean you have to
consider why it manifested what's there. By the way, I've gotten several messages from people.
They'd go to the doctor. Right. And they said, well, there's some kind of streptococci or
these bacteria growing on it. It could be dangerous. Well, your body creates that,
by the way. That's part of like the garbage eaters. Right. And they do go out of control.
If you're out of balance, they can go out of balance very easily just because
there's back to the test. So the slideshow is
foggy. These these type of bacteria that eat flesh. Right. Let's say it doesn't mean it's a
bad thing. It's just that you're already in balance. If these things go in and out of balance
again, that will be hard to get rid of. And that kind of makes them go more for those other
treatments. So the entire thing here is when something like this happens to you and you have
something that wants to come out from the inside of the body to the outside and it's readily doing
so. Right now, I think I've mentioned someone that's among us here in this one of the subs.
Right. I had a breast tumor and I kept saying, try this, try that. And it got to the point where,
you know how the Catholics say, God bless her heart.
Lived by California, went into the cold beach in the winter, in the morning,
got numb completely, went home, put a mirror on the floor, drank a half a bottle of something,
put a mirror on the floor and cut the breast open. So the tumor come out. I mean, not you know,
I mean, so a lot of people who could do that. That's like Rambo type stuff. Right. There's a
little lady did this. Right. Little, little. Yeah, it takes a little lady to this. It's not
old. But you know what I mean? You know, it's up there at age, but not like, you know, like,
I'm at our age. Right. But that's that's something else. Right. That's that came and went. I mean,
that's like, well, that's Rambo type shit. Right. Yeah. So that's rare. OK, so this is not what I'm
talking about where there's stuff is under the skin, where it's at the skin. The best thing to
do at that point is what that cause that manifestation, whether you know exactly or
not, is what you've been doing. It could be let's just take it from an outside route. It could be
the route that you take to work every day. It could be where your bed is, the location of your
bed in the house or the apartment where you sleep and that location on the earth. It could be your
diet. Could be your thinking. Could be some circumstances that have come up. Usually it
takes four seasons a year for something like that build up for something like that happens
because every time there's a seasonal change, your body tries to mitigate. And if it carries
over from one season to the next, to the next, that means it's going on for more than a year.
Right. And so changing the route you take from work to work every day instead of taking the same
route, which you shouldn't do, by the way, anyway, changing where you sleep, the location of the bed
or because the bed is the location of the bed in the house. Your apartment also has to be a specific
location on the earth. There's something going on there and your diet. And once you've accomplished
making enough changes, that manifestation will change as well. Now, the easiest way to do that
in terms of diet is make a list of all the things you like to eat and all of the and how many and
then check next to those things. Which one do you do frequently? A secondary list within that list
and then make another list of all the things that you don't like to eat and then make a check next
to each one of those which you think would be beneficial if you started eating them because
of the known properties and vitality. And then you switch those two lists. Eat the things that you
normally don't eat right and don't eat the things you normally eat. So changing all this. So what I'm
trying to say is people's financial situation, mental situation, health situation. I'm using
the word health in quotes. It is because of your behavior and what you've been doing. If you want
to change any of those things, you have to change what you do and give it a try. It doesn't mean
that it will necessarily change immediately or the way you like it, but it will not continue the way
it has been for sure. For sure. You see? So that is the main thing. So when health comes up,
it's not. By the way, the antithesis with the medical industrial complex, right? They say,
okay, it's true, because what they're doing is always the same thing. Anything comes up,
what do they say? Go to the doctor. I made it right. Go to the doctor. Same thing. Same thing.
And you're going to have the same results. Now, for some people who are infrequent by going to
quote unquote, the doctor, the doctor, right? Or my doctor, where do I get one of those, right?
Um, uh, is a break in, in a pattern or a break in what they normally do.
And it's that break or change that leads to the change. In particular, you cannot logically,
rationally, emotionally, or psychologically. It's all psychological placebo, by the way,
if it does work, if whatever they're ordering you to take by prescription, pharmaceutical,
all of it is toxic, all of it. There's no way that's going to help anyone.
Right there. And their procedures are very evasive, which can help sometimes, right?
If you're at a terminal end, like, for example, when a house is on fire,
and the fire crew comes with an ax to break down the door to put out the fire, that's pretty
fucking evasive breaking away, breaking the door. Yeah, but the Yeah, if you don't break down the
door, right, you see, it might be right, right? Yeah. So yeah, now you have a burned house
with a broken door where the house would be more burned without a broken door, which one you say,
yeah, you're better off breaking the door. Yeah, yeah. So they're better, you're better in some
way. But that is the something that you're gonna have to decide. But there is no health. So whenever
you hear of health care for what, you know, the thing called health care, health care for
mountain climbers, health care for deep sea muff divers, I mean, scuba divers. Yeah.
Uh, right, because we're talking about the bike analogy. Yes, yes.
Health care for construction workers, health care for office workers for who?
Don't give me that baseline bullshit. Right? Because I gave this centurion
analogy, by the way, if anyone could find that study, most of them are under NIH, which
or an England, nobody NHS, they're the ones and then there's the Red Cross, but they don't do
that stuff anymore because they're, by the way, the Red Cross do not donate there. That's just a
money laundering thing now. Worse, whenever they show up, children go missing. Okay. You know,
I think you've heard there's some stories on the outliers, you know, out fringe on the internet.
Well, yeah, I've never, I've never been able to verify any of that stuff. But yeah, I've heard.
Yeah, yeah. But that's obvious, you know, and also drug running.
Well, that yes, that that drug running human trafficking arms,
the triggers trigger devices for nukes, right? Sure. Don't I've noticed I've been looking at
the landscape and they've really calmed down. So since 2020, they really calmed down on the use of
nukes on the population, by the way. In other words, these car bombs, by the way, that leave
30 foot craters in the ground. They're not carbon. I mean, they're car bombs. All right. Anyway,
so I think there'll be a big resurgent resurgence in that again, you know,
like a little Nissan Sentra walks in and it completely demolishes a 20 story building.
And you know, you do the math on it. And you needed 35 tons of TNT to do that.
Do you think we're going to go back to those days where the Yeah, I think so. I think it's coming.
So yeah, a little Nissan Sentra, the explosion goes off as a bright flash. And yeah,
totally pulverizes, you know, a 40 foot diameter hole and everything around it turns to dust. Yeah.
Reason why the Pinto was so cheap, you know, just yeah. You know, by the way,
when you say I got a one ton pickup truck, that's a pretty big truck, right?
So I don't think you could put like 25 or 30 tons in a Nissan Sentra. Yeah. Anyway,
generally, no, I would say yeah, the ignorance of the public is astounding. Yeah, it's it's the
ignorance is so astounding. That's one thing when Newtonian physics doesn't, you know, it works out
well, you know, it does it fits and you can't discount it. So when you see the amount of force
that it takes to do these things that say we're done by a car, really? No way. There's no way.
Yeah, but the people are ignorant about this stuff. And the people in the mills, I don't know
how they've, well, they have been through the years. Well, JFK, how do they have all these
people in Department of Energy and in the military stay quiet? Right? Are they that ignorant? Also,
I don't know. I mean, there's got to be something. I think it's, it's got to be character
too. Because I know you if you you end up you end up dead if you do speak like recently, the Boeing
engineer who spoke out that Boeing's been negligent on their maintenance and stuff
suicided and they paraded it around quite well. And no one does anything. No one cares. You know,
by the way, when you have a someone like who a whistleblower who's a benevolent, you know,
benefactor really that says, Hey, this company everyone trusts is doing this and that,
and they end up dead. No one cares. There's who should be like, protests and marches in the
street, right? Something ought to happen. Yeah, they don't care. So that's what I'm saying. Just
why bother just leave it alone. This is Darwin. This is Darwinism, social Darwinism,
or medical Darwinism, social Darwinism, whatever. Yeah. And I've been saying for a long time,
this society does not deserve to continue. So yeah, doesn't want it anyway. Right? Yeah.