Rated Y, Sonic Event, 83.
I had to think about that for a second because I was looking at the reverse number, I was
looking at what we did on 38 and that was interesting.
Anyways, Greek, how are you doing tonight?
Doing all right, yeah, it sounds like we both got up from a nap, which we did.
I did, you know, I didn't ask if you got up from a nap, I actually needed one real quick and yeah,
you can tell when I wake up from a nap, I'm like, hello, how are you?
It's the CO2 or whatever, yeah, the heaviness.
Well, we've talked a lot about yin and yang, so think about it, you know,
the balance when you're one way, you express the antagonistic side, right?
Well, there's no effort being extended during your sleep time, you're kind of,
your body's relaxing, so when you do stand back up, you're kind of stiff or you're kind of young,
right, because you're sort of, you've been recharged a little bit, yeah?
Yeah, well, the deeper voice, right, is a longer frequency, longer sound waves are more young than
shorter sound waves, that's the direct approach and it works every time, but what happens is the
behavior of lower frequencies are more yin, they spread out, they're more omnidirectional,
the behavior of the yin short frequencies are more directional, actually, no, I'm sorry,
yeah, they are more directional, so you know, higher frequencies, you know, you make beams,
lower frequencies spread out like dropping a stone in a pond, then it flips again, right?
So, yeah, the antagonism, but I just want to quickly bring up, there's some activity in the
chat, a lot of it's redundant, but important, meaning going over something, even not,
well, let's just say, how many times is irrelevant if there's room for improvement,
right? So, that would be at the Chatango, I guess, Rated Y or Greek Speak Chatango,
I'm not in front of it right now, what's it, anyone can go there and post, there's been
some activity about the Aqua Sargentum stuff recently and I believe that it's quite important.
Right, it's actually, it's actually ocelliandthegreek.chatango.com,
that's where you can go directly to it, yeah.
Okay, good, all right, good, I'll commit that to memory then, okay,
yeah, redundant stuff that's been gone over, but apparently needs to be gone over again,
so, yeah, what do you want to mention? Well, let me ask you this, what about confirmation?
Because confirmation seems to be an important thing, right? Even though you've had a thought,
you've studied something, you've been over it, you've observed it, a lot of times you seek
confirmation, you know, in scientific terms, a lot of times, okay, I hate to use it,
I know it's a dirty word, but scientific terms, what do they do? Can you replicate the experiment?
Can you confirm that this is what happens when this happens, right? Because...
Yeah, well, the confirmation is still a perception and it has, all perceptions have biases built in
and they're all subjective, but when you say scientific, yeah, it really is a bad word,
it has been for a long, long time, until people stop accepting it and let it just die out in the
form that it's in, and then let it be reborn in the proper form that it should be, in any proper
form of anything, whether it's the legal cult, the medical cult, the scientific cult, all they
have to do is follow what they're supposed to be doing, and no one's following or doing what
they're supposed to be doing, and in other words, what do you mean, Greek, what are they supposed
to be doing? Well, if they memorialize it, they have a set of codes and rules and things and ethics
or procedures, and they've memorialized it, meaning written down, whether it's black ink on white paper
or even digital format, if it's something someone can access, if you go contrary to that and go far
away from that to the point where you no longer resemble what you're supposed to be doing from
that point of view, you need to be done away with, and the way to do away with them, by the way,
whenever you hear of like revolution, overthrow, civil war, that's all this, that's all rooted in
secret societies, by the way, the order out of chaos meme, right? Right. Real rational people
don't do that, right? What I mean by real rational people don't get involved in civil wars or
revolutions or overthrows, why? Give me an example. So you really, well, you're having lunch with
people and you walk into a diner cafe, and you really don't like tuna fish sandwiches or tuna
fish on the menu, they've got other things, and you really don't like ham and cheese. The moment
you see those things that you don't like on the menu, do you gather up a whole bunch of people,
go back and let's grab all that stuff and throw it in the dumpster and beat the chef up for
putting it on the menu? No, what do you do? You just don't order it, right? So whenever you hear
about all that stuff, it's just people are suckers, you know, and they fall for all that stuff. So,
okay, so hearken back real quick, is the American Revolution a fraud? 100%. Name another country,
by the way, and if you don't know this, you can look it up. Name another country that teaches
that the Americans had a revolution against the British in their history classes, whether it's,
you know, grade school, elementary or college. You can't, you can't, this is the only country
that does it. It's totally it was a total hoax, just like everything else, right? So, you know,
they'll mention other things, but never the revolutionary, because all these things that
people get caught up in are pre-directed, prescribed, even Roosevelt said anything
that happens has been pre-planned, right? So, you know, you can keep going down the line and
see this stuff. So until the mental attitude is checked by the individual, right, each individual
and the process that they use, which is important, and it's negated, and the process that they use
is usually a proper process, something that's very rational, and benefits everyone is inaction.
Not doing anything is the best thing one can do. You know, it's not dropping out, because let's
say you want to get rid of the scientific system or just academia in general, right,
which has no purpose anymore. You don't go to sign up for college ever or and reject their
things, make fun of them. Now, okay, you notice the part that was don't go to college, don't sign up,
that's the inaction. But to make fun of it, you have to put action and energy into that.
And it's not about dropping out of the system or that subject, you actually have to invest a lot
of time in promoting the necessity of avoiding it and, you know, not using that system. So
when I say not using a system, and so it goes away, you starve it, right? By popularity,
it takes a lot of work to do that you have to actually create, you know, helps propaganda,
what they call propaganda, you know, propaganda just means advertising and awareness of why you
should not use that and avoid it, right? So it's not when I say inaction, on one side inaction
directly relative to the thing, because you're no longer feeding it, but it takes a lot of action
on the other side to show other people why they should not participate.
I'll give you a fun example to work with that, you know, I know you've heard of over the years,
I don't think they do this anymore. But it used to be every couple of years, there would be some
sort of rumor that would circulate that no one is going to buy gas on a particular day.
Yeah, right. That's very effective, by the way. And no one does it.
Well, here's the thing, everybody starts talking about it. And they would go to and I used to work
at gas stations, as I've told you many times, and I worked at Exxon Mobil specifically, mostly,
but I worked at other gas stations. And people would come in and tell me, you know what,
tomorrow, you're gonna be bored, you know, a couple of people would get into it to the point
where they thought no one was going to show up and buy gas, because that was going to be their
big protest against what they thought was a high gas price, which, by the way, was hilarious,
because we're talking about around $1 on a gallon of gas in the time period, I'm talking about where
this happened several times. And it was $1, including the taxes, the state taxes, which
anywhere, you know, I get it. But you know what, it doesn't matter. It's the relative, you know,
like right now, the dollar is about point seven, eight cents. Yeah, people when people say 70. No,
no, that's it. It's three quarters of a penny is the buying power right now, right? Yeah, it's
and it's all relative. But you actually actually things are cheaper right now, because you use
lawful money, like a silver piece is $1. And a silver piece is around $25. You know, dollars
right now to buy, right. So that means that if gasoline was $1, when silver was $1, that means a
gallon of gasoline should be $25. And it's not it's where I'm at, it's $3 or less, California
at $6 or more. So it's still pretty cheap. Actually, a minimum wage. Well, in law and biblical, it's a
silver dollar per day as a minimum wage. But now even if you're on minimum wage, you could buy at
least two and a half after, you know, if you're not in redeeming lawful money, two and a half of
those. So things are way cheaper. And an easy way to I postulate that is by watching the price
that price is right from the 1970s, which is a factor of 12 to one right now. Right. So when
you look at like a thing of wishbone salad dressing, that was 79 cents in 1972. And today's
money that you know, 12 ounce wishbone salad dressing would be over $13. And it's not no,
it's like it's not three bucks. Yeah, two, three bucks. So yeah, so things are much cheaper. It's
relative from that point of view. But because it's an elastic currency, you know,
the situation is taken advantage. And also, I've done a bunch of research on this and had
quote, unquote, confirmation. And a lot of these border state cities regarding gas stations,
I'm talking about the gas stations that take up a good amount of acreage and have all the bright
lights and they look polished, and they're well maintained, right? They're owned by ex cops and
ex military, their money laundering operations, because I think I've gone over this before,
if you're a cop long enough, or in the military long enough, you're going to find that your
superiors are putting while you're in your career, I'm asking you to do some strange things. And
after a while, you find out like, hey, shouldn't we be arresting these guys, instead of protecting
them. And you find out that the police and the military actually controlled by the cartels,
right. So when you get out of the business, you still have all those content contacts,
you have a little black book, maybe not the top guys, but all the guys, you know, the runners and
whatever the captains, the guys doing all the, you know, boots on the ground, and you still have a
long list of all these guys, and you're like, they need to turn cash. So average gas station
can make several million dollars a month gross on a bank account running through the bank,
they make a tiny amount of profit barely to keep the lights on. So what they do is they ask their
friends, hey, we know we run several million dollars a cashier a month, you give me a half a
million a week or whatever, I could run it through and it won't flag anything. If some people don't
understand, like if you have like $5,000 in your bank account, and you have a friend who is a drug
runner, and he gives you $200,000 in cash to put in your bank account, that's going to flag you big
time because they have averages really say, this guy's usually between five and 10 grand suddenly
jumps up to a quarter of a million, let's check them out, right, get in trouble. So the IRS is
the largest money laundering, the taxing franchises are the largest money laundering,
like right before war, billions per day get run through the IRS. And no one, you know, any
international monitor, if I look at it, say, well, it's the IRS, of course, billions,
right, and they just redistribute it. And this is how the world works, by the way, and most people
kind of sit back. And again, they don't think there's anything they can do about it. There's a
lot they could do. Right. And for you to have massive cash in an account with a gas station is
not a big deal at this point. Because every truck that shows up is like a $25,000 payment that needs
to be made upon receipt. So before you sell it, so literally what they what you need to have
actually is a couple of those deliveries in the bank at a bare minimum to take Oh, yeah. Now
you attach Yeah, they move a lot. In other words, their activity is so high. It's not that they're
making profits or what they call just the general activity, you know, like the two brothers selling
watermelon out of the truck joke, maybe I should rehash that one. But But yeah, it's just the
activity so high that you don't get flagged if he goes up, you know, shipping companies, you know,
telephone bills, if you ever want to run a telephone scam, run it through a big corporation
that's got 100 $200,000 a month phone bill, they'll never see a $1200 phone call, right?
It's hidden in there, right? That's how the system works on their end, you know, and yeah,
and by the way, you know, the these cops and military that run these gas stations retired or
whatever, they still enjoy the benefits of their contacts in the police force and the military
also, by the way, right. So they're a formidable group. And actually, I should know shouldn't really
disclose exactly how I know this exactly, exactly, because it'll be too obvious. But it's for sure.
I've seen it. So I happen to know you're right.
Yeah, it's and I mean, I was like, wait a second. Okay, this is too obvious, right?
Yeah. Notice, I didn't say I think you're right. Or that sounds right. I said, I know you're right.
Um, yeah, so this is a dirt. Now. Is it dirty? I don't know. You know, it's up to you to decide.
Is it because after all, look, you set up a business and you basically regulate it so that
you're supposed to make you know, what, what is the best gas station make 10 or 12 cents on a gallon
of gasoline at best that can't keep the lights in the maintenance, you know,
I'm talking about the nicer gasoline stations, right? Well, right. When you see a place that
has all those lights on you not much that costs to keep that lit when you pay that bill straight
to the power company, you got to be kidding me. Once you take that 1213 cents a gallon, you say,
oh, you're making a good profit. How? Because think about the electrical cost per day when
you break that, forget it. It's gone. There's no way to make those work. I mean, yeah, the work
they'll be self sustained. But again, there's still not making a tremendous amount of money.
It's actually the ex cops and ex military set these by these gas stations and run them as a
service to their, to their contacts, really, they're even the guys, you know, and also they
do make a pretty good bank from they get a cut, right? The growing rates anywhere between one or
2% 5% sometimes. Yeah, but they're not going to get it. It's a service is the way things are done.
I mean, you know, by the way, the real money with the high profit, like for example, this is the
going rate for intelligence agencies option in black market is 1000%. So whenever you see things
that are 1000 2000 5000% profit, it's an intelligence agency up like Bitcoin, all the all the
the major cryptocurrencies are 1000% intelligence agency operation. And people fall for it. They
think they're bucking the system, right by getting it, but they're going into the dirtiest aspect
and supporting the dirtiest aspect of like, for instance, years ago, I used to ask all the time
an open question. Nobody quite understood why I was asking it. But how does the search engine
make a billion dollars? You see, it doesn't. Okay, well, no, he I think there's a zero point
that happened about five years ago, where right now you should if you have an internet hookup,
or a smartphone, you should be getting paid to use it. Because they're actually making more
money by selling your activity. It's, you know, 10ths of a penny, every time you do something
right now. So I think it's been three years or five years or something that they crossed a zero
point. It was it was a very small article was written in a financial paper, but it was written
in a way that you really had to know this was going on for it to matter. If you didn't know
this was going on, and you read that you wouldn't know what they were talking about. For right now,
if you in other words, because there is what brought this up is in the door, there's a new
fiber optic companies, 50 bucks a month, you get 500 megabytes. I'm like, Are you joking? I pick
you have to pay me, because you're monetizing every so everyone right now anyone if you have
any kind of internet subscription or smartphone or whatever, a few years ago got to the point where
they are making more money off of you, right, then it costs to provide you the surface now.
Right, right. So in other words, anyone who has a smartphone or internet hookup should be getting
a check every month, a tiny amount or a small amount, all the albeit, you know, percentage.
And no, is that happening? No, they're asking you to keep paying for it, because you're used to it,
right. So that's how the scientific system works. Also, it's just like people that continue to
complain that, you know, they put people in prison, and then my tax dollars pay for that. Whoa,
hang on. What is what? Yeah, that's the programming. See, the aspect of programming is you get people
into the programming. So when people say when you say people are programmed, right, or brainwashed,
they think it's because Oh, yeah, you just give them false information. They believe No,
it has nothing to do with the information, you create a stance in the mind. In other words,
the mind thinks first, and then you give it the false information because any rational human,
if you give him basic information that's false, enough times with enough of these humans,
even though they're not smart, they'll figure it out pretty quickly. But if you instill a
programming and operating system in first, like, you know, you have to be patriotic,
the authorities arrive without telling them anything first about taxpayer dollars or any or
whatever, whatever history that or how their body works, they'll believe anything. So you have to
give them the setup first, right? Right. And that's, that's what people no one talks about,
they'll bring up a bit of bad information, and say, that's part of brainwashing. No, it's not.
The brainwashing has to happen before any information is disseminated. Otherwise, it'll
be rejected. Well, and that's the thing is that look, and I started with that stance, and you
stopped me a tax dollars, but we can keep going. The idea that it caught will cost money to house
people in it. Well, yeah, okay. But here's that. Well, here's the thing. In short, they fund it
themselves if they right. Okay. In other words, when you go to places, and they say, Oh, do you
want to donate the change to this charity? I'm like, why are their hands broken? And they're
like, what, excuse me? I said, the other hands broken mean there's no money. And it's all
generated from the signature. Why don't these charities just go to the Federal Reserve window?
Have everyone in there sign a piece, you know, sign a document with how much they need in the
Federal Reserve should honor that. Oh, I mean, that's how the money system works. You don't need
the very fact that charities exist is a fraud. Because the money is generated from their
signature. I mean, isn't all right, let's say it's an orphanage with children. Isn't there anyone?
Is there a principal at the off or someone at the orphanage? Anyone? Executive power there that is
older than 18? Of course, there is someone Why don't they just sign whatever, you know,
a bill, whatever, and go to the Fed window and get the money you need to run the charity? Why are you
asking me for? What do I look like a bank? Right? So that's how the money system works. And they
keep going whenever, by the way, whenever you hear of charities, do not give do not donate to any
charity ever. By the way, you know, the scam on that too, right? So I used to do that. But you
know, I, there's a lot of things I used to do before I understood. But even still, you know,
these people that are in even at the mid level of the system, they're monetized, it pays for itself,
it's for profit. You're telling well, it's not it's about control. There's no payment.
There's settling in that we might have to get into how this works. Because the language
the way it's just like the aqueous Argentum and the scalarator and the talks that I do on certain
technologies. Okay. You know, I'll talk about it. And I'll watch what people do. And then I have to
back and talk about it from, you know, point one, again, maybe a little more detail, right?
Start all over from the beginning again, you know, on many things, by the way, yeah, we did a
there's a Skype group with the about the scalerator, basically, I call it mark one.
And I just want to, I'm going to be doing one again very soon, probably tomorrow or tonight,
and record it. But I'll throw in some cool stuff there. And the reason why I'm saying cool stuff,
is because since this came into development around April of 2023. As the moons go by the
moons literally every month or so there is a new development or a revelation on what this
thing is doing and what can be done more to make it more effective. And each improvement,
each change modification that moves it forward and making it more effective
comes on a monthly basis. I've noticed this by just looking at my notes. So every month,
there is another improvement or some revelation regarding what's going on that comes about.
So is that a slow process where you get one new thing about it every month? I think it's pretty
slow. It's but then again, whoever sits down and bring something new into this reality,
and you get it all at once, right? Never, you know, if you look at how let's say automobiles
were developed from the mid 1800s till now, I mean, they didn't pop, you know, modern looking
car right away, did they? Right? No, not at all. You started out there. They started out with
bicycle tires, from my understanding. And then yeah, you know, slow development. Yeah. So but
I've been getting these improvements every on a monthly basis has been over, you know, it's been
910 of them right now. So and one, okay, why am I saying this? Because one just came up a few hours
ago. I knew it's hot, not still still hot. And we'll talk about it. And it makes sense anyway,
because look, if you need to take it and then actually do it, and then observe the result,
then turn around and disseminate it. I mean, realistically, that's about a month's worth of
time. Yep. Well, yeah, and it's developing to the point and it's so radical, the scalarator must say
so that eventually, well, if we had enough time, and you went into the future, there'd be this
would be a new thing that would be taught at university. It would be a look, there's a new
thing here. It should be taught, but it won't be, you know, when computers and all that were
up, you know, like becoming a desirable item, by the way, in the late 70s, people don't know this,
but the PC movement started in the late 70s, right? Early 80s. Yeah, there was no college
courses on computers about PCs. No, not at all. Not at all. Matter of fact, to go to popular
culture, when you saw that kid screwing around with the, you know, computer on in the movie
war games, that was literally the front, you know, the vanguard, if you will, of the PC movement,
because it was people getting these things and working with them on their own and sorting it out.
What to do? No college courses, university, nothing like that. Well, let's use the phone
lines, because that's an existing transmission that we can use. And therefore, we can transfer
data that way. We know we can already do that because of stuff like the telex and
what was effectively a fax machine. Yes, those existed long before we ever did.
Oh, yeah, those existed in the 1800s. By the way, they found out with the telegraph,
you could send images with the telegraph, right? It wasn't very popular. But yeah,
detailed images also, you know, yes, it took a very long time, but you could get done. Yeah,
I was gonna say it was a very long process. I mean, and then then later on, we had the printers that,
you know, you know, and that technology, by the way, the current technology is was around back
then also just wasn't available to the public, as per usual, just like the internet itself was
available in the 1970s. When you're talking about the vanguard of the PC movement, well,
that was the public PC movement, the military was already using these things and keyboards and all
that. You know, like when they showed you in 83, and they go to the massive, you know, war room
with the big screens and all that. Okay, that's not the way it really looks. But at some point,
it might have because they already had those keyboards. That's the antiquated technology
they were showing you in 83 that you thought was on the cutting edge, because we were just
getting these things at Radio Shack, you know, so therefore, it made sense to the public. Yep. And
well, yeah, that's, that's a funny term, because as we go through time right now,
less and less will make sense. So yeah, and exactly the opposite happens. I mean, at this
point in time, we can instantaneously communicate with individuals anywhere on planet Earth, right,
according to the technology that we're allowed to have. Right. And guess what, you notice people
are communicating less and less, even with the facilities to communicate more and more easily.
Lean and young. Yeah, yeah, their minds are becoming mushy and soft. And yeah,
the human animal is something I mean, it's not they're not animals, but the human creature,
right, you know, I still go around, by the way, oh, I just want to mention what I do
did this past week, what I've been doing for a while is there's meetups groups on the internet
for your local city, town, whatever, right, just type in meetup, wherever place you are,
and you'll see there's a website, it's like a social thing. And people post, you know,
like a book club or authors meeting or whatever, whatever subject in your neighborhood, right,
you sign in, sit up and show up. It's usually at a cafe or someplace, a lot of them are online.
Right. But I go to these, by the way, I've been going to them for a couple of months now. And,
and usually the ones for authors, author meetups and book grab meetups, people want to write books
and you know, all this other stuff. And because why? Well, because who writes books? Pretty much
anyone, right? Is it possible that doctors and psychiatrists, psychologists,
lawyers, engineers, military housewives, right, everybody can write a book. And I very often when
I start knocking these academics, by the way, it's not because I sit around and I imagine it,
it's because I don't know how to say it. Yeah, I actually go and meet them and listen to them talk
and speak. And because what you know, when you're in the in person, you can actually speak to them
in person. And I run the Greek speak by them not not the Greek speak that I do meaning the emanations
of the Greek speak. But I asked questions, like you would hear in Greek speak wanting to ask and
you should see them all flat every time every one of them. And they're just wonder what you know,
maybe this guy is not from here. Maybe he's really not from here like he said he was, you know. And
yes, I run into pretty much across the gamut. Because remember, they want to write a book,
they think they can communicate, they think they know something, right. And it's funny. It's funny
to I've been I've been observing this. And it's I'm actually happy. I'm grateful that that this
exists. Because, you know, very often, you'll hear me like, you know, talk about how dumb these people
are, you know, the academics are professionals, is because I probably just got back fresh from a
meeting from an author's club or something. I just wanted to throw that out there in case people were
curious. Look, and we all do some form of this, right? What do you do when you meet somebody and
you don't know much about them? And you can't really glean that much from looking at them.
They're kind of just, you know, general sort of generic looking. People often will ask questions,
right? They'll see what their interests are, they'll see what it is that catches their attention
in general, to see if there's some common ground commonality, maybe. So if you do this with
Greek speak stuff, you know,
in mind, yeah, like, like, you know, I say the engineers don't know anything about engineering,
the physicists don't know anything about physics, psychologists don't know anything about psychology,
on and on and on and on. I'm saying it from a firsthand point of view, meaning firsthand,
you know, experience with them show up with the doctor and you say, Doctor, what is your thought
on digesting food? You know, regarding this, this, what do you think about eating these kind of foods
and digesting them? Now, if they don't correct you and say, well, you know, all these things are
done by induction. You know, you've got somebody who is not on the side of understanding this,
this end of the pool. Yeah. But if he lets his peers know that he knows that he'll quickly find
himself sleeping on a park bench, right? Because now he'll be the crazy guy. Oh, he just doesn't
adhere to any of the stuff that we know is true in academia. Therefore, and I am polite, like,
you wouldn't believe how many engineers I met. They said, I'm an engineer retired from Raytheon.
I'm like, should I tell him like everyone at Raytheon, even the one in the gift shop is
an engineer? I shouldn't say that. That would make him feel kind of right. Because you go out
in the public and you say, I'm an engineer at Raytheon. Oh, wow. He's an engineer at Raytheon.
But the public doesn't know that the janitor is also an engineer. And so is the person working
behind the clerk at the cashier at the desk at the gift shop. I mean, there's no gift shop,
but you know what? It's not it doesn't mean anything. And the security guards are taking
night classes to become an engineer. Yeah. No, I mean, but, you know, when someone tells you I'm
an engineer or whatever, I'm like, yeah, the guard dog. I mean, it means absolutely nothing. But
outside. Right. And he knows they know that means nothing. They walk around in the public and they
say something like that. Oh, he's an engineer. Oh, boy. You know. Yeah, it happens all the way
around. You hear people say, oh, well, this guy, you know, he went to college for a lot. You know,
what's really funny is that some people don't even inquire about what the degree is. Right.
He's just got a college degree. Oh, yeah. It's it's the doctor who the psychic papers. I don't
know if anyone's familiar with Doctor Who. Whenever he goes about his annals and adventures,
he has a wallet, just a blank piece of paper. And whoever he shows it to it, they see like what is
the highest authority from their world. Right. Right. And they let him go. It's just a blank
piece of paper. It's called the psychic papers. You just show them psychic papers. Oh, yeah. Wow.
Look at that. I love the puns and jokes on society that are done in Doctor Who that way.
Oh, yeah. And I still appreciate I know you're not I don't think you're the biggest fan of Star
Trek, but I appreciate it. I was taking a look at something earlier today. Just listen.
No, but Star Trek, by the way, is real Marxism. You know, no one. By the way,
no one has ever done real Marxism. They just show you like the bad stuff, you know,
that could be interpreted poorly. The Marxist. Yeah. Even it's a good example of Mark, but still
not because in Marxism, once people organize a certain way to benefit themselves, the state is
eliminated. There is no top authority. So it is a form of anarchy. And oh, boy, does he say anarchy?
Yeah. Anarchy just means you rule yourself. Castle doctrine. But anyway, Star Trek. Yes.
Just without without the leader. That's all that is. But anyway, no leadership required.
But what's funny about Star Trek is I was listening to something and what I caught in the midst of it
was, you know, are you naive enough to believe that there is a difference between physics
and biology? There is physics through biology and vice and vice versa and vice versa. Like they are
interconnected. It's not a separate. But see, if you talk to an academic,
they would tell you, well, there's either physics or biology. Right. Yeah. You shouldn't be talking.
Well, what they do is like you can have someone studying geology, but they don't know anything
about biology and vice versa. But the two intermix. You have some of these things called
fossils, right, which are biological forms that are now mineralized and become logical. Yeah.
Yeah. But they don't crisscross. They don't. Yeah. Yeah. This is a very simple ploy to show
that this is how you control people and stop doing. I wanted to do you know how that bumper
stickers. My child is an honor student at whatever. Oh, yeah. I want to do bumper sticker.
So if I had a child, the only time I would consider sending them to university is if I
knew they were a total idiot. Right. Anyway, I did see a bumper sticker sort of like that
one time that said something like, I send my child to your school because I hate them
or something like that. Oh, yeah, that's pretty much. I thought that was kind of funny. And I
thought of you, actually, that this was a couple of years ago. You just reminded me of it. The
bumper sticker. I said, my child do your school because I hate them. I just I don't know why
I thought it was funny. Anyway, a lot of a lot of comedy. And that's another thing, too, is,
I say we should laugh at a lot of things, especially when we see that they're so absurd.
And I always appreciated that form of theater, theater of the absurd. What are your thoughts
on that, though, like entertainment and how it educates people or mis-educates them or
de-educates them? Entertainment is it is. Well, just like the education system is there to take
your time. Yeah. But you like to be entertained sometimes yourself. I mean, you intentionally
waste your time and find value in it. No, actually, I don't think of it that way.
When I engage in what they call entertainment faculties, it's because I have a curiosity in
the subject also. Yeah. OK, so that makes sense. I was just curious about that because I'm saying
to myself, you know what? It's a form of emo also the way you feel. Right. Well, but that's the
thing, is that to me, if it if it allows you to expand to casually engage in certain emotions
and explore that, isn't that a purpose in and of itself? So, you know, people feel like laughter
is the best medicine. I do think that it is a positive thing to enjoy the comedy of something,
whether it's because it's ludicrous or whatever the point of it is. You know, you know how it's
like a lot of people say in that work in comedy, they'll tell you something like, I don't know how
to explain to you how something is funny. It just is or it isn't. It's one of those things where if
the experience works, it works. And laughing and enjoying something for its comedic aspects,
whether you're mocking the ridiculousness of this idea of authority and where it comes from and
exactly how poorly educated the authorities are, or if you're looking at somebody getting, you know,
smacked in the sack, it doesn't matter. It can all have a movement in your emotional core reaction
that I think also has some value. So even though a lot of times you, me, a lot of people might mock
what comes out of the entertainment business and you might not want to engage in a lot of it.
Entertainment has its place, you know? Oh, yeah. But but here's the important part is years ago,
I say, why would I go to college? I have a television because they they have to be in
accordance with each other. Right. They can't. Right. So, you know, whether it's smart fact or
fiction, usually fact and entertainment, you know, like History Channel, whatever,
they have to teach the same stuff in school. Right. So you don't need. Well, why are you going
to go to school and they're going to give you the same B.S. that you're getting on TV? You know, so
you do one or the other. You're just as educated, you know, even now and pretty much on any subject.
You have enough documentaries that feed you enough bullshit that if you study what they tell
you in documentaries and go to university, it's the same bullshit. So why? Right. The only thing
is you don't get a degree. How about a degree in watching television? You know, I think everyone
pretty much has that anyway. Look, and that's true. And there are degrees in that, oddly enough.
But back to it, even even your discussions about going to YouTube University, which,
again, 40 years ago, not something you could do. You did have to go somewhere to find out,
figure out, or you had to figure it out for yourself how to say, you know, install a pipe or
make something, you know, repair your lamp or whatever it was you were trying to do,
you know, put your drywall up properly, this and that. You had to go get a book, you know,
the Time Life Series, something you had to go do something. But nowadays, at the tips of your
fingers, a lot of things that used to be specialized knowledge are no longer specialized.
And it makes the the the idea of university, the idea of a lot of trade schools,
although I don't object to trade schools, it makes the idea of a lot of this training,
these certificates, this nonsense, completely irrelevant, because it's still relevant.
It hasn't there isn't a complete takeover of the media, you know, YouTube or
digital media. There's no complete takeover yet. I don't think it'll ever happen because
people intuitively know that it's temporary. It's going to go down, right? It's going to go away.
But it all seems like but if you were to maintain that, if that was carefully done,
it seems to me like indeed, anybody could be anything, you could be your own plumber,
you can be your own electrician, you can be your own mechanic all the time.
Sure, it's an advantage, because there are people that became their own whatever without
the digital help, right? The digital help makes it a lot faster. I mean,
give me an example, again, with the scalerator bending heavy schedule 80 PVC pipe,
I figure I need to heat it from the inside and the outside at the same time, how about pouring
hot sand in it, and experimenting, you know, what the right temperature is and plugging it and I'll
make it soft like taffy and also heat it from the outside. And I did that. And then I said,
I said, Wait a second, why don't I go on YouTube and research or the internet how to bend PVC pipe
and guess what they were doing? They're filling it with hot sand and bending it around. But you
know, so makes perfect sense. Because you know what, when you I don't know if you know this,
but you know, plastic glasses, right? You know, your glasses frames, that's exactly how they used
to bend them. Sure, sure, sure. But to me, it was intuitive. But at the same time, if I didn't have
that intuition, and I just went ahead and went and straight to the stupid rectangle and, you know,
searched it, I would have found it right away. So what I'm saying is, someone who's intuitive,
and someone who isn't intuitive are more on equal footing now because of YouTube University.
Yeah, well, but that's, but that's my point is now it makes it even more relevant that I went
to school to learn how to bend pipe, you know? Right? Yeah. Well, by the way, I just want to
footnote here, I've told people go to YouTube University, and they've gotten back and I couldn't
find it. I'm like, What do you mean you couldn't find, you know, changing the water pump on your
whatever, like, No, I couldn't find this thing called YouTube University. Oh, no, no, no,
I just call it that. I just call it that, you know, so I just want to footnote, there's no such thing
that I know of is just go to YouTube and search what you want to do. And someone's probably
done a video where you can at least see it is almost as good as firsthand knowledge.
Yeah, there's almost always a how to whether it's, you know, trying to whatever the warning
thing is on your computer, or it's to, you know, restart your phone properly. If you press these
buttons in this order, or if it's to again, put in, you know, the starter on the car,
there's likely a video, but here's one thing that demands there's a lot of stuff that I discuss,
that demands it being done on a YouTube or instruct. Well, there's a lot of stuff that
I discussed there is instructional. Okay. And this is one thing that I'll assure you for sure,
you will not be you will not learn how to cook or be good at it by watching any YouTube video
at all. They do not discuss technique. Very rarely give me an example. Recently,
I made sushi, I went out and got a real nice piece of yellowtail and tuna,
sushi grade, and I make really good at making the rice and seasoning it. And so
go out and having some sushi. And it's like, my gosh, I get the bill. And I'm like 50 bucks for
that. That was like bait. You know, if you're fishing, you throw it in the water, you wouldn't
want to eat anyway. So while I'm doing that, I put on some YouTube videos on how to make certain
things. And, and I already know, and I'm watching the guy given instructional, like you watch this
video, you can make sushi at home. And I'm laughing like, No, you do. He's not. He's skipping so many
things. And he's telling you to do this. And that doesn't work. Right? Give an example over and over.
But there are, for example, a really good instructional is, let's say on a 2003,
Chrysler Town and Country minivan guy, you know, changing the water pumps in the title.
And he says, this was this is going to be a video on changing the water pump on this,
on this minivan engine. And we're going to get started right now. But I'm not going to change
it. My girlfriend's going to change it. And you're like, Whoa, cool. You know, she comes out, right?
And she gets in there with the wrench shows you how simple it is. Right? So that was cool. Right?
So you expect a car mechanic video to be the guy and says, yeah, my girlfriend's going to do it.
Not like, you know, a little double whammy there. Right? Yeah. Because of the stereotypes, right?
But he's better off. It's not just because of the stereotype. He's better off because if he takes
somebody who doesn't know how to do it, that's likely who's looking at that video carefully.
Sure. Sure. Well, it's less intimidating. It's less intimidating. But also, you know what? Okay.
Somebody who's constantly working with cars is going to skip over stuff because look, I already
know I should have this clean. I should have this ready. I should have these tools out, etc. Now,
new fresh person who has no clue what they're doing does not know that. You know, do I need
a screwdriver? Do I need a wrench? What do I need? You know what I'm saying? Well, let me give an
example. Let's go back to the sushi video that I was watching. Okay, sure. And I'll give a small
example and show the fine point. So this way, when you're watching stuff, you know, once you understand
this fine point, you won't be able to unsee it anymore. But cool. So there he makes a roll,
which is a maki. You know, it's a sea vegetable roll with rice and the fish in the middle.
And it comes time to cut it. And he says, well, when you're cutting the roll,
make sure your knife is kept wet. And he's cutting and cutting and cutting. I said, no,
that's keeping the knife wet will only be good for the first cut. You won't be it'll stick on
the second cut. And you'll make a big mess. Everything will stick to the knife and the
roll will break. What you really have to do, which he didn't say was you keep the knife wet. But as
you're making your cut, you have one hand on the knife, obviously, and the other hand on the piece
that you're cutting. And as you're cutting it, you're gently pulling the piece away very gently.
And you repeat when you go to the second piece, you hold the second piece and you gently pull
it away from where it's being cut. So you're right to release the friction. That would be a more
proper way. And if you write these little subtle things, you know, that they're not being expressed.
That's why I've done actually cooking shows on Skype years ago with certain people. And I didn't
need the camera. They were like, put the camera on, put the camera on, put the camera on. I'm like,
no, not necessary. And I would just walk through what I was making. And there'd be no recipes.
It would just be the approach, you know, the very subtle things that no one talks about on how to
make whatever we were making. And right. It was much more successful that way.
Yes. Yeah. But again, those things might have been skipped. And, you know, here's the bad part,
too, is that that chef who might be skilled might be doing what you're saying, but he's
not going to bother expressing it. He's not he doesn't know how to communicate well enough.
There's the point like he was actually doing again, cutting the sushi. He says, keep your
knife wet in order to cut it. And he is actually doing what I said. Each time he would cut a piece,
he gently pulls it away from the main part. He didn't express any of that at all.
No, he didn't tell you. Yeah. Even though he was doing it. But it's such a subtle motion that you
won't pick up that he's doing it. It's just like a tiny amount of effort you have to do. You can't
tell it's being done. Right. So. Yeah. So it goes down to how well can can the let's say the
instructor. Right. Or the host or whatever. How well can they communicate? And they can't
communicate that well at all. Right. And that seems to be a very common theme is no matter
what you do, people, even if they're fully aware.