Sonic Event 96 rated Y and interesting, interesting times we live in, maybe, or maybe you're bored
to death.
Who knows?
It is the, what, the Ides of March, right?
Beware the Ides of March.
Julius Caesar, isn't this when the conspiracy- It's arbitrary, though, when you use the number
in the day, right?
Like, it was supposedly Friday, and today's the next day, but what I did want to bring
up is that it's measurable, 12 hours, well, on the, oh, gosh, wonder ground weather.
I've been looking at about two weeks ago, and it was 11 hours, you know how many minutes
per day.
Today, I guessed it, and I looked it up, it was correct, it was 12 hours, zero minutes.
So today is the equal day, equal night break.
It's on the Pope's work schedule, let's say, American Southwest, it's the 16th on a Saturday
night, so we had to, and what's interesting, this week, I was following the sun coming
in, the building I live in, the house I live in, is really north-south cardinal, so the
front door and the back door walls are west and east, and one end of the other end of
the house is north, the other end of the house is south, and I mean dead on.
So in the morning, when I get up, the back door, let's say, kitchen area, when the sun
is due east, it just comes in, centered on the door, and makes a perfect square on the
opposite living room wall, and that happened today, yeah.
So you can actually, you know, basically, it's a form of sundial, right?
Well, I guess, is your house is oriented, you mean to say exactly so that, you know?
Exactly north-south-east, yeah, in other words, the rectangle, that is the floor plan
of the house, is aligned, all the walls are aligned with the cardinal directions, not
magnetic north, but true north, you know, as the poles and the solar movements go.
Yeah, so I want to bring that up, also we're getting into a change of season, which is
my favorite time of year, and it should be yours as well, because it's, whatever you
experience during that season, here's a time for it to change, right, and what I mean by
it should be yours as well, is, okay, you have the day-night-day, the atmosphere expands,
pulls everything apart, at night the atmosphere contracts, compresses everything, so the yin
and yang again, right?
You cannot fight that, so if you have a condition, or you want to do something when the atmosphere
is being pulled apart in the day, that will overwhelm you, right?
Where, if you want, when the atmosphere is compressing at night, right, you want to stay
uncompressed, no matter what drugs or exercises you do, it might counter that a little, but
the overwhelming force of it being nighttime will overwhelm you, right?
So the actual seasons overwhelm you as well, and now we're in a transition.
Well you know, because almost everything is personalized, though, I got a question here,
and I got to drop a little information, and then ask the question, so I give you context
for it, but here's the deal.
I always think to myself, and this is the right time of year for me, because about a
month from now, I guess, a little less than a month from now, is what they call my birthday.
Now you and I have gone over this about the cultural idea, and the weirdness, and the
sweet cake, and all that about birthdays, and maybe we'll do that one more time in the
near future, but put that aside.
Yeah, very hard to find information on that, but go ahead.
Yeah, no, it is difficult to find information on it, but it is the reality in front of you,
it's obvious, but here's the question for me, because of what it is I experience.
Around this time of year, around the time of year that I was born, and indeed around
the time of night that I was born, it is dark when I was born, you know, it was dark on
that day.
Well if you were born in the spring, it's the same as being born in the fall, in terms
of the overall pressure, but the direction is going in a different direction.
Right, but the thing is this, I feel as though things can be easier renewed around the time
I was born.
I feel as though I get a little bit of a recharge, and I'm wondering if that's a psychological
thing, because so many elements of your life, whether you realize it or not, and whether
you're one of these hardline schedule people or not, it always ends up revolving around
the marking of the day, you know, because some people might say, why do you bother?
What I'm talking about is exercising perception, like most people, when you have a change of
season, they call, oh, we're going into the holiday season, or it's going to be Easter,
or it's springtime, or it's fall, let's go fly a kite, this is before video games, when
fall came, we went out and bought these kites, Gala was the brand, right, I don't even think
people do that anymore.
You got treated to the Charlie Brown would try to fly a kite, and you never could get
the kite to fly, and yeah, of course.
Yeah, but you know, that's the kind of child that I had.
So the only thing that resembled a video game was a pinball machine, let's say, right, or
those soccer fooball things, you know, with the men on the rods that you twist.
Oh, foosball!
Air hockey, foosball, yeah.
So what I'm trying to say, it's an exercise in perception, when everyone else is saying
this season is coming, and they're acknowledging it, you're acknowledging it differently.
In other words, with an energetic concept, because here, I'm going to say something that
I've never said before, and I do this in private conversations with people that are studying
finer energies, I keep hearing recently, this is a little bit of a tangent, the emo, what's
the purpose of emotions, I have speakers throughout when I'm working.
And sometimes when I clear the computer, the YouTube music or whatever, it's on continuous
play, and it'll play a video.
And I'm like, Oh, no, why isn't it music?
What happened?
Right?
So I go to change it.
But last week, three times, various podcasts came up.
And the thing that was in common with all of them was, what is the purpose of having
emotions?
Or why do we have emotions?
Or what's the reason for emotions?
I was like, Okay, I got to bring it up.
What what the emotions are, it is a clear state of consciousness.
Now, what?
Well, wait a second, because people seem to be reasonable, and they do unreasonable things
when they're emotional, right?
It seems like clarity would be the last thing you'd think of if you're getting emotional.
But yeah, good.
What it is, is it's a contrast.
Right now, we're mortal beings in a physical container that's mortal.
And in a very mortal, violent world, the world is very violent.
You know, when you talk about, will there ever always be war?
Yes, there will always be war.
And in other words, to stop the war, you're going to need overcoming it with even something
more powerful.
And whoever has that is the one who decides.
Well, emotion, if you're connected to emotion directly, and you're very clear on what your
emotions are, in all honesty, they teach you that that means that you're unclear in your
thinking.
But the truth is, you've eliminated a whole lot of the confusion, nonsense and programming,
if you're directly in touch with these things that are, you know, not just reactive, but
proactive, your emotions, right?
That's the mix that I'm bringing up here.
So in other words, all the negativity, the necessity for animals to kill other animals
to live and the way the ills of society and the ills that you die after a certain age,
even if it's 1000, let's say, okay, that is a stark reality that you're in a mortal situation
usually ends up not very good because you die.
What the emote and you have your reasonable thoughts based on your education, your culture,
what the emotions are, is the source form of reasoning and thinking how your consciousness
would be when you are in an immortal state from the immortal realm.
There is an immortal realm, it changes, but it changes in line with how change is known
on the emotional level, where right now, if you are on the physical mortal level, when
you talk about change, whether it's, you know, whatever type of physics, pick your flavor
or philosophy, you're going to always lean on change being material or the ebb and flow
of energies, right?
That is still mortal.
There is a side of us that is sourced from an immortal realm, where death is not known
and degradation is not known.
And in that realm, when you exist in that realm, your form of reasoning and thinking
is all emotion.
So the emotion we have here is a trickle over a spillover, a carryover from that realm.
And I'm going to end it right there, because that could be developed.
This has never been said before, by the way, as far as I know, because all I can see is
that it is a direct line.
It seems to me to be more of the natural state, actually, if you react with emotion, and thought
is something that is, what, done in the after action.
You have two types of thought.
You see, in the immortal realm, it's all emo.
In the physical realm, it's the type of reasoning we have.
That's why, for example, I'll give a little more.
That's why when people are, let's say, a mild mannered guy, nine to five, family, white
picket fence, new car, right?
One day he comes home and kills his whole family and kills himself.
We never saw that coming.
What kind of an emotional state?
You can also be the opposite.
You could be something with a tremendous amount of elation, right?
Someone deciding, I'm going to just give everything I have to the poor and live in an RV or something.
What I mean by that is that whether it's really drastic and negative or elation, when you
bring that immortal realm into here, they too don't mix entirely.
When you have too much emotion happening, and you, let's say, kill your whole family and
then yourself, that is something that doesn't take place in the other realm.
But because you're mixing the two and you have too much of that energy coming here, it
ended up really negative here, you see.
I'm still working on this.
I'm looking for tidbits that have been around.
It's very hard to find, but there's always ... You know how there's been talk in all
of the ancient scripts, and even modern, whatever.
There is another realm, right?
Plato is the one that made it academically the most, the platonic heavenly realm, right?
What is perfect white?
We have all these whites.
We say the color white, for example.
Polar bear is white.
Snow is white.
The wall is white.
But they're all different.
Somewhere in a platonic realm, there is a perfect representation.
That's what I'm discussing.
Even in that realm, there are several shades of white, but it is an immortal realm.
In other words, that is the source realm.
The emotions that we have, and by the way, animals have emotions too, and so do plants.
How much is there to the immortal realm, considering that we know that only the chief deity is
the only living thing, living existence, that doesn't know death, as far as I know?
It's complicated, because it becomes a paradox, and any paradox can be solved outside of the
thinking that led it to become a paradox.
This is too formative, I don't know, but there's something to be ... In other words, when you
look at pure material reasoning, let's say a high culture with high science that's in
harmony with its environment, that could still be dubbed reason and thinking, but it could
also be separated from an emotional counterpart.
I'm saying that in its entirety, there is another realm, and in its entirety, all of
its thought is emo, and that spillover is what we experience.
Anyway, enough of that.
I want to get back into the change of season and why it's important, because people that
are living upside down, they're going into a cold season, right?
So you have transition, we've discussed diet, and of course, there's, what would you say,
utensils, implements, now you prepare your living space to either be cooled down instead
of heated, or vice versa, depending on the season that you're going into, right?
So when you perceive these things in a fine way, very simple, up here we're going into
an expansion time, right?
And down, where people are living upside down, they're going into a contraction time.
So the sooner you prepare for that, right, like for example, you know how I talk about
food is seasonal, right?
Don't eat salmon in the summertime, right, because it's an Arctic fish, it'll make your
blood thicker, you won't be able to cool down, right?
So let's say winter's coming, don't eat tropical fruit, but don't, so if you heard something
like this from Greek-speaking, you're in the middle of the season, you could still make
a change, but actually starting to change it before the season kicks in makes it really,
really simple, and you adapt really, really well to it, right?
So for example, I've been getting into walking barefoot a lot, so when fall was, I made sure
that I started walking barefoot more and more as fall season started going into winter,
so now I could be more transitioned and used to being barefoot even in the winter, right?
But if I decided to go barefoot and it was middle of winter, boy, would that be uncomfortable,
right?
So, you know, and Diogenes made a couple of talks about that, but a couple little snippets,
but either way, now is the time to consider what's coming and prepare for it energetically,
right?
Because the way society and culture has been taught to prepare for things is basically
within whatever culture they're living in, and it's really dumb, right?
There's not much talk about it, so, but yeah, the other thing I wanted to bring up, and this
is a segue, total segue, people are familiar that frequent Greek-speak, that I've been
working on water devices, particularly one called the Scalarator, basically-
Before, hang on just a sec, before you segue into that, I really do want to ask this question
because I think it might be relevant, alongside of the change of seasons, and you should recognize
this, this does change many of the things that you need to, you know, go along and go
along with the flow-
You get the most benefit if you start thinking and adapting now.
Right, a little bit ahead of it, but the thing is, is there a personal element to this, though,
where like I said with the birthday thing, so I'm born in the spring time, for where
I live now and where I was born-
Hold on, let me just interject something, I'm going to lean on the nine star key, you're
older than 18, right?
Yes.
It doesn't have any relevance anymore.
It's no longer relevant.
Up until you're 18, I would say, child was born at night, consider that, but you're way
over that and it has no relevance anymore.
Go ahead.
No, but it's funny-
I'm not trying to dismiss what you're saying, but I'm saying that when you're older than
18 as an adult, using tendencies that were from when you were infantile or your early
state doesn't work anymore.
Well, true, but certain conditions do persist throughout your life regardless of your age,
for instance, you're always going to require food and water.
What I'm saying is that I'm just curious and you're telling me that once you get past the
developmental time-
18 or 20.
Somewhere in that time where society says you're about an adult in there is when that's
no longer relevant.
Yeah, 20 is the best because it carries late bloomers as well, right?
There's no personalized end to this where it's like if you're saying-
There is.
Okay, well that's-
There is personalized.
When you get older, you switch to a different character.
Look at the Nine Star Key.
I brought up Nine Star Key.
Remember, this is not like horoscopes.
This is based on statistics.
In the earlier imperial oriental empires, they would have statisticians over 4,000 years
now collecting information on people from birthmarks on their body, what businesses they did, how
their lives went, and they collected all this information when they were born and all this.
It has to do more with the seasonal calendar because the year starts around February, more
like what they call the Asian New Year.
That would apply.
Here, give me an example.
I've turned several years ago, especially, several people onto Nine Star Key who were
big into the horoscope stuff.
They put the horoscope stuff aside and said, wow, this is super accurate, but they had to
go back to it because you're not going to create a business out of Nine Star Key in
a Western society, right?
It's probably not as-
It's far more accurate.
Yeah.
It's not as interesting to look at, though.
It doesn't have all the fun stuff like your animal and all these other things, right?
Actually, yeah, but it has energies and it shows you how people relate, but yeah, I found
it to be a pretty good statistical measurement.
Now, you know there's things that break statistics all the time, right?
Well, look, a statistic, nothing is absolute and therefore there will always be exceptions
even to the strongest rules.
Of course, but it's one of the better structures that we have that are cosmologically based,
let's say.
Cosmologically meaning it's time and season and not necessarily, there's no astronomical
stuff in it, very little.
Right, and there's no one size fits all no matter what you do.
I was talking about before, it'll always prevail that you'll require food and water,
but some people might be able to survive a lot longer without food than others because
of various things.
Yeah, that's conditioning.
I think that's all conditioning because when you notice, especially going into the seasonal
change into various seasons, you'll notice, okay, for example, when it's really hot out,
you don't eat much.
Even in the military, when they prepare MREs, they make sure that they have, quote unquote,
more calories in the winter, MREs.
In the military, they have summer food and winter food, but what they do is differentiate,
quote unquote, thermal calories, which we've been over that.
We might want to recap the container.
Yeah, there's a little bit coming out right now that calories have nothing to do with health
and finally, it's like 25 years or so of discussing this.
Well, I think soon we should do an absolute dedicated recap to the container because I
think that would be helpful.
I think it should be once every so often as a, what do you call it, a refresher.
Yeah, definitely.
Yeah, because memory, even my own, very often people ask me about certain things and after
I leave, I'm like, you know what?
I didn't tell them about this, that, or the other.
Right.
Before we move on to the Scalarator though, but you're saying the nine star key thing
is the way to take a look at it and try to personalize this as far as ...
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, definitely, definitely.
You'll notice that when you ... This is when the nine star key works really well to see
how accurate, for its accuracy and how ... Is when you do it on yourself, you're like, okay,
I'm kind of like that, but when you start doing it on other people that you know, you have
to know when they were born pretty much and then it gets into male, female and all that
other stuff.
Then you'll start saying, oh my gosh, because when you do it on someone else that you know
or spend a lot of time with, for example, it's easier to see them overall because you're
outside of them, right?
It's kind of hard to see outside of yourself, but when you start seeing how accurate it
is with others, then you go back and reflect more on yourself and you're like, oh wow,
I could see how accurate it really is.
We did a couple of talks on this about a month or two ago.
Yeah, and the other thing is, look, if you're judging someone from the outside, you have
enough of a disconnect where you're not going to sit there, let's be honest here, a lot
of people will fudge their numbers a bit, you know what I mean?
You can easier judge somebody, maybe that person eats too much, maybe, but you don't
see that you eat too much or, you know, go ahead.
The reason why you judge them outside is because you're not hearing their internal dialogue.
Right.
See, when you have the internal voices, right, that hopefully, from listening to enough Greek
speak, you shut them down by anticipating them, you know, there's an old saying, are the
voices in my head bothering you, right?
So anyway, yeah, so let's go to the Scalarator real quick.
Yeah, let's move on.
What I want to bring up is, everything that I've presented so far, people that have gone
to the chat have seen it, right?
Right now we've established for sure we're on Gen 2, no longer producing Gen 1.
What does Gen 2 look like?
Like Gen 1 with a double spool.
So when you see a pipe going around a central disc that's copper or gold, you'll see two,
a double wrap now.
And why was that done is because when the device was hooked up, it gave certain results.
And the basic reasoning is, what if I put two in series, it should be better, right?
So and it didn't have any change at all, like less than 5%, more like 2 to 5%.
It was like, wow, you tripled it.
Still no change.
So in other words, if you put one or two or three in a chain, it doesn't matter, it still
does the same.
So that doesn't really add up, literally, right?
You know, that math ain't mathing, right?
So what's going on?
Well, it turns out that it's not necessarily how many devices you have in series, it's
what the relationship between the spool, the wraparound to the orbit around the magnetic
reactor, right?
So if you look at, for example, Saturn, the images of Saturn, you'll see the rings are
flat, pretty much go across the equatorial part of the planet, and they have different
colors and some bands are narrow, some bands are wide.
Vandy posted in the chat, different octaves in a circle.
So when you have a still body of water and you drop a pebble, you'll see how the ripples
go out.
Those are different, also represent, you might say, octaves to a degree, but the frequency
changes as it goes out, right?
Same thing with color and a rainbow.
More amplitude in the middle and less amplitude as it hits the shore, to a degree.
Same thing with color and a rainbow, right?
As you go out, the frequency of the color changes and it creates the different colors.
Yeah, there's a spectral element.
Spectral element, there you go.
Okay.
Element, yeah.
So we have noticed this, and the difference between going around once and having them
in series and the difference between going around twice and having just one unit is tremendous.
It is double.
In other words, the Gen 2, looping twice around, is what you would expect if you put two in
series.
So this is working on some other level, which we understand, we see it, because we're not
looking at this purely materialistically, we're looking energetically and we're looking
at it in a scalar form, you know, in terms of the elements as described.
Have you experimented with changing the nature of the orbit?
In other words, instead of a circular, you know, a proper circle, how about an ovoid
shape?
Would that change it?
Well, we want, yes and no.
Early on they were sort of ovoid, and because right now they're made with high precision,
we want to center the water flow over what's called the block wall, the inertial domain
where there is no magnetic field.
The part of the magnet is equidistant from the center, so it's going to have to be parallel
to the magnet.
And by the way, if you have a square magnet, it's still a circular magnetic field, right?
Regardless, you can do this, you know how with children they put the magnet under a paper
plate with metal shavings?
Oh, right.
And then you move the shavings.
And you see the donut shape?
Yeah, they have a game.
It doesn't matter what shape the magnet is, it'll always be a donut shape from the center
out, right?
Right.
And the edges will pull it in a little bit if it's a triangle or whatever, but not much.
Well, the reason why I was asking this is because, see, if you took, you know, two perfectly
equal ovoid shapes and you displace them in equal distant ways, that would create a particular...
Yeah, it's a variation, but it actually, based on what we're chasing, which is the block
wall, it's a flat plane, that would be, having an elliptoid would be a distortion.
So we want to keep it as even as possible.
So around that, because it's the block wall that's doing it, and the block wall is equidistant,
so circular or concentric would be the way.
This is what I wanted to bring up.
People, whoever has interest, you know, I put out, these retail for 5k a piece.
And right now I have several of them that are first generation in hard cases, and they're
very precision made.
And what I'd like to do is auction them off.
In essence, it's Gen 1, and I'm going to auction them off.
So if you're interested in one, this is an opportunity to get a precision made by the
Greek Gen 1 Scalarator, without the hard case, I will not send it with the hard case, it'll
be packed, double boxed, in a nice package, but not with the hard case.
And it will be an opportunity for someone who is curious about getting one on an open bid.
So if you're interested, send me an email at uncommonsenseradio1 at gmail.com, that's
the numeric one, and tell me how, give me an offer, and if, what I'll do is very much
like a, because it's a bid, it's not a donation, after a certain amount of time with several
people, if they make offers, I will keep their names anonymous, I might use a first initial
or whatever, just so I can delineate a number, and email everyone who's put in a bid, these
are the bids.
So before I give it to the highest bidder, everyone has a chance to counterbid, at least
one time.
At least once.
Yeah.
This is not someone I spent, you're going to create a bidding war, no, not at all, because
I haven't, through the Greek-speak rated Y, I haven't gotten much request, a lot of interest,
but not request to acquire one.
So at this point, there's no starting cost, so whoever would like to get one, and of course,
the shipping, I always do priority shipping, because it's a flat rate, but if you're in
New Zealand or Australia, I don't know what it would be, so we could always work that
out as well, but no matter where you are, where you hear me, here's a chance to get
into a Gen 1, they're all one-inch diameter, 25.4 millimeter, and there's more to it.
These are specifically made for wells, or a one-inch pipe, okay?
So here's your chance, just put in a bid, whatever you think you'd like to send to acquire
one, I have several of these, and instead of what I was going to do, was take them apart
and salvage them, or rework them and add a piece with a connecting fitting to make them
a Gen 2.
It's just best to keep them Gen 1, and just get them out to whoever would like to acquire
one.
I know there are a couple of people that have been speaking on acquiring one, they just
don't have the funds at this time, they said, without making a ridiculous offer.
So no offer will be denied, any ridiculous offer is an offer, because I'm saying, this
is an open bid, right?
So this is a great chance to get, these are all the, by the way, these are not scratch
and dent and rejects, these are all the high-precision tested ones.
So I just wanted to put that out, so just email me, put in a bid, and I'll give it a
week or two, I'll collect them and I'll send you anonymously what all the bids are, because
obviously it goes to the highest bidder, right, so everyone has a second chance, or whatever.
I was thinking, I asked Sam, have you ever worked with eBay, I was putting them on eBay
and anyone who wants one can go there, and I'm like, why, let's just keep it, I think
we'll see what happens here first, right?
So I just wanted to put that out as like a public disservice announcement, right?
So if someone wanted to get one, here's a chance, right?
Because there's no pricing or anything here, there's no minimum or whatever, just put in
a bid by the email, which is UncommonSenseRadio1 at gmail.com, numeric one, and that's it for
me, yeah.
All right, so that's all you want to talk about, about the Scalarator then?
Yeah, that's it, yeah.
I think it's a fair offering, there can't be any more fair than that, yeah.
I'll tell you, I think I would really, really love to get a full recap on the container soon,
like a refresher though, I think that would be a good idea.