Sonic Event 128? I believe it's 128. Anyway, here we are, Ocelli in the Greek Rated Y,
and let's just roll the ball as fast as we can, kind of like bowling for ideas. Interesting
thing, a follow-up question came in after some other questions we didn't get to last
time, and it was like this. I'll shorten the whole thing. You know, a lot of people like
you, Greek, a guy like you who has original ideas, who's outside of the box, etc., etc.,
is often recruited into think tanks, is often recruited into industrial stuff where they
want to develop certain things, but they want to protect their intellectual ideas, so they
get somebody with bigger brains than themselves, which is not too difficult, and there are not
that many sheep available, so they go after a guy who actually has the ability to speak
English and other languages like you, who might give them new and profitable ideas.
They pay them a good amount of money, and they put them on the shelf to what? Generate
ideas and concepts. Have you been approached by? Why are you not working with think tanks
or developmental-type agencies like this is one of the big questions, because you've said
stuff about water, you've said stuff about energy, you've talked about weather work,
which makes sense according to them as far as, oh, anti-grav technology and stuff like that.
Now, I don't know why that makes sense, but all of that rolled into a nutshell. How come you're
not working for the secret department with ExxonMobil, or you're not one of Elon Musk's
people, or etc., etc.? Boy, there's several ways to answer that, but I'm not at the moment.
I was back in 2008 or so I was approached, but no, for whatever reason, I can give you the main
reason why. It's not recognizable that already exists. Everything that anyone would be hired
to come up with already exists. It's just not known. Here's the point. Let's make a fictional
example, wink, wink. You go to a planet, and everyone on the planet is a fucking moron or an
idiot, with little exception. You organize the planet to have professional classes that are
trained in universities from the same people, and you have lawyers and doctors and scientists
and engineers and all. From the same people, a planet is full of fucking morons, with little
exception. Okay, so the people that know better than the morons turn around and say, you know what
we need? Some king morons. Let's make some morons that'll run things. The people that organize
these idiots already knew everything, right? So it's all a show. In other words, you know,
it's like the biggest joke on this planet is university doctors, lawyers, what people says,
I had a really good teacher, where they born on this planet, are they human? And they're like,
Yeah, of course, they're I'm like, really? No, far as you're not gonna know. And if they do know
what's going on, they won't want anything to do with any of it, right? They just want to pass their
time, waste their time, whatever. Well, they could waste their time anyway. Yeah, well, they could
choose to waste their time doing something like that. Because it might be amusing to train other
morons. You know, there's people that enjoy training animals, directing animals to run off
the cliffs. I mean, just yeah, but those are animals that humans are not really trainable
after a certain point. Everyone, you know, I assure you, this with little exception has stopped
developing like nine or 10 or 12 years old, max, everyone. In other words, they're just seem to
have a more of an adult appearance or whatever behavior, but they're still stuck. And yeah,
it's very, very difficult to find people that are constantly growing and maturing. And then
those people will want nothing to do with what's going on. You see, which which brings me and we
finished off with someone was asking, you know, but tell us about the brand. What would you not
do with Brandon Joe Williams is the serial repeat. I keep bringing him up on everything because I'm
doing what he's doing. Right. You keep saying there's great stuff there. He's got some great
things to also organized. Yeah, but he goes the wrong direction at a certain point. No,
the wrong direction. He's going. There's a I don't know if it was jackass the movie.
Yeah, there were those stunts that they perform. Sure. That's that's what he's doing. Does it mean
that he won't perform this time? But it's really fucking dangerous and stupid. No way, right?
OK, so because in one word, he's admitting what it is and then he goes to the set. OK,
so by the way, before I get started, it's summertime here, really hot.
And that means that you eat less. By the way, whatever you eat less in the summer.
How hot is it where you are, by the way? I mean, is it getting up? Well, there's two.
There's two where I'm at. There's two places where I'm at. Sure. Where I'm at in the southwest
is the heat wave. But where I'm at within a mile or two mile radius, it's 10 degrees cooler than
everywhere else. So it's not bad at all because I'm doing weather operatives, which is ruining,
creating some really bad weather downwind. But, you know, if they don't want the bad weather,
they can move right now or do weather themselves or they can move the weather. Yeah,
they can move. They can move. They can keep bouncing it over until he hits the French.
And the French, if they get screwed, they need to learn to do weatherwork to keep bouncing it
around the potato. Right. When you do weatherwork, it's hot potato. Everyone downwind or downstream
of you is going to get the brunt. Right. So, you know, what the fuck do I care? I'm cooling it down
10 degrees here. I send a couple of screenshots where the high was one hundred and seven
forecast for the day. The day before was one hundred and eleven two o'clock in the afternoon.
It should have reached one hundred and seven. Right. But it was eighty six. You know,
I can show you the screenshot. And I kept taking, you know, high tomorrow. One eleven.
Take a screenshot. Eighty nine. The hottest time of day. How is that possible? But but but if you
go ten miles east, west, north or south, it is one hundred and eleven. How's that?
So nobody's mentioning this anomaly, this pocket of coolness. OK, these idiots. No,
I just thought they might try and explain it away, even if they give the wrong explanation,
they might say, you know, big things they do. When I took out Hurricane Lee last year,
they they were bringing up like, look, the hurricane stopped. It's not moving. We've
never seen that before. Has it moved in eight hours? Well, it moved like a mile in eight hours.
Right. So we never say, oh, look, it disappeared or it's gone to nothing. And now it came back
again. You know, yeah, yeah, yeah. So the weather's good. Fortunately, I'm trying to get
more people on board to do it just for whatever reason, you know. But look, it's one of these
things that you're brought up in life that you shouldn't be do that that can't be changed.
And obviously it can't. So what can't right? We're starting to change something that we're
raised to believe cannot be changed or dealt with. And we're doing it on a very small.
It's even less than grassroots level. It's just someone, you know, knowing what,
you know, what some of the techniques are. But anyway, you eat less in the summer
and like a meal in a glass. I just want to share something. I've been talking about food for a
while. What I do for like a nutrition blast is I go to Wal-Mart and get all the organic stuff
at Wal-Mart. It's much cheaper than the local health food store. That's twice as much for
everything. So I get organic peanut butter, organic soy milk, organic bananas. By the way,
when you get fruit, always get the organic. Why bother if you buy bananas? Right. Why?
They don't taste like anything. Right. Get the organic. They're 10 cents more pound or whatever.
Yeah. Well, bananas are not a big deal. But I mean, there are some things that it's like,
you know, I know it's not right, but the organic is so much more expensive.
A non-organic apple has no flavor whatsoever. But the worst part about that is,
comparatively speaking, they might also be lying to me as well because they do that,
you know, just because it's organic. It has to be 40 percent or so. Right.
Sixty percent organic. And then it could classify. Well, you know, back in the 80s,
when there was a when it started by the 90s, it became popular. I said, ah,
it's not going to be good because anything that the mainstream catches on fucks up. Right. So
that's why. Right. So that's why I can't discuss so much in so many places now.
A meal and a meal and a glass. What I do is this is when you don't want to cook or where I've been
cooking some really good food lately, but basically Greek salads. There's no lettuce in a Greek salad,
by the way. It's garden vegetables. Right. It was a thick slab of feta cheese, olive oil and
vinegar and bread. But what I've been doing was a popular drink. I had a whole bunch of apricots.
I did this way, but we're out of apricots. There's a place, a lady that grows apricots,
got hundreds of them. Those are done. But what you do is you get your soy milk, put it in the blender
and you throw in a capsule of mineral supplements, you know, like, you know,
the capsule, the gel capsules, right. Like a one a day vitamin kind of thing.
No, no. It's a gel capsule. It's called mineral supplement.
The generic mineral supplement. OK, just minerals. You look on the back and it's got all the various
magnesium minerals and all that selenium, all that stuff. Right. But I get the vegetable gel.
If it says gelatin, it's pork. So you want to get the veg cap. Right. So I keep that. I buy one of
those bottles every three years. It's worth 30 bucks. And, you know, it's got 500 tablets. It
lasts a long time. I just use them for smoothies. And you always want to have gone over this in
private Skype groups when you make a smoothie. You always want to buffer it. What is that? What
is buffer? It means if something's acidic, you make it less acidic. Right. If something's alkaline,
you make it less alkaline with buffering it. Right. So when something's acidic,
you add a little alkaline. So when you're going to make a smoothie with peanut butter, bananas
and soy milk, it's not acidic like citrus, but it is acidic. You know, anyone that starts studying
nutrition, food and nature, when you start breaking things down and processing them,
the first thing they do is become acidic. That's why, you know, you need salts and things to
preserve them. And soy milk doesn't neutralize like cow's milk. No. So it's acidic. Right.
It's as cow's milk is acidic. Also, once it's processed, it's something called that people
are lactose intolerant. Guess what lactose is? It's lactic acid. Right. So and that's only a
problem when you refine cow's milk. But we're talking vegan now. We're talking no animal
whatsoever because your gel caps, your gel, your your your mineral supplements are vegetable
gel caps. I don't like the five hundred milligram, the big ones. Right. The horse,
you know, it doesn't have to be anything special. I get some generic brand.
And and also when you have a big bottle of pills, vitamins or supplements, don't open that bottle
every time you want to get one divvy, divvy like a week or two weeks or a month's worth in a smaller
bottle and put the bigger bottle away. So every time you open it and close it,
you put more air in it that, you know, you'd start degrading it. Right. Yeah. Shaking it around.
It's always divvy somehow, you know, into a small container, you know, 20 or 30, whatever you think
you're going to use in a month and then a refill instead of chugging the big container around.
It's much better for the storage principle. So anyway, you get your blender, a good blender,
and you put your soy milk in there and you turn it on low. You throw in your your mineral cap first.
Let the mineral start breaking down as the soy milk spinning. Then you add your peanut butter,
teaspoon, tablespoon, organic peanut butter, and then you add your banana. Now, here's the secret
with bananas. Anyone can do this experiment and it works every time. OK, that's if you're not
dead from the neck up. When you peel a banana, don't do it the way they show on TV, which is
they grab it from the stem end and they pull it and peel it. Now, you always want to peel
it from the blossom end, meaning the opposite where the stem is. That's where the blossom forms
the flower. Right. And it tastes different. If you peel a banana from the stem and break off a
piece and taste it, you could take the peel away, throw it away, do an A, B and X comparison.
You know, A, B and then X is you don't know which is which. And you'll always taste the difference.
If you peel a banana from the stem and first down and put it on a plate, take another banana and
peel it from the blossom and first put it on a plate, they taste completely different.
Doesn't it go doesn't it like turn brown faster, too, if you peel it? No, no. We're just talking
about, OK, all things being equal. OK, OK. All things being equal, whether it's how
the way you peel is kind of hard to believe. I see you're you're even having a hard time.
Well, yeah, I'm reaching. It has nothing to do with the banana. You take two bananas that are
on the same bunch, right? Take two off or take four off or whatever. Take two banana,
take one banana, peel it from the stem and first put it on a plate.
They take the other banana that's just like it, peel it from the blossom and put it on a plate.
They taste completely different. It seems based on how it's peeled away, changes the flavor,
just like the cut we've talked on vegetables, changes the way the vegetable tastes.
Well, see, I can understand with a cut, but this one makes less. I mean, I'm not saying
it's wrong, but it's less intuitive. Yeah, the banana will be sweeter, have a much more mellow
flavor where when you peel it from the stem and down, it doesn't have that sweetness,
doesn't have that rich banana flavor. Do you know why? Do you know why that is or
does it matter about the weather work? This is just a technique. See, most techniques.
Yeah, it's we can we should be able to give the why. But if you learn the technique and you
employ it and you reap the benefits of it, even if you don't know how it works, right,
is the advantage of learning the technique. Right. Of course. I just wanted to stick in
people's minds. Well, yeah. Why it works is obviously it's ethereal movement. Motion matters.
Right. In other words, the way things are done can change the outcome. Yeah. And this is the
energetic consideration. Yeah, exactly. Close to more validation of that. Now, we can't be measured
with their equipment because they don't have equipment fine enough. But you have the best
equipment, just like you can take a fine wine. If you can taste the difference, you have a
measuring. That's right. You know, that's right. Just like any any of the scientists who can't
measure whatever. OK, well, you can analyze chemically any wine that's preferable to a lot
of people that like like a 19, let's say a twenty eighteen Bordeaux heavy wine. You know, the heavier
wines are easier to make and then go to a lab and have them copy that with their chemicals.
They were it doesn't even taste like wine. It's like that weird wine. Yeah. Like that
weird wine in a box, like the individual box stuff that they can't even copy that.
They can't even do that in the lab. Yeah, they can't even. So it's all energetic.
But you should put wine in a box, by the way. Shame on you. But it's the shape that matters,
too. So. So here we go. So the soy milk, the mineral goes in, peanut butter goes in next and
blend it. Don't be like a white people where they throw everything. They have these slurpy smoothie
shops and malls and they have the thing, all the whatever mix they're going to put in their preset
and they put it in. Never do that. OK, so making a smoothie or slurpy, everything has an order
which way what goes in first and for how long. Right. So quick recap here. Sorry, but just just
help me out because I got lost and I distracted myself. So what I do is I first put in the mineral
channel, the liquid first, the liquid first. So first the soy and started on low. And as it's
in, well, you drop your tablet and then I put my tablet and I just put the whole thing in.
Then I put a whole banana in. No, no. See, that's I'm mixed up. So please,
peanut butter. Well, you had your peanut butter and you mix the peanut butter,
the soy milk and the mineral already. So the reason why is because peanut butter,
this is not well known by white people, Westerners, but peanut butter is a thickener,
just like we use cornstarch and things and flour to thicken soups and whatever. Yeah.
In Thailand, it's used as a thickener or something called peanut peanut sauce.
It's a thickener. So anyone, I mean, I've seen people use that as like a dip. But anyway,
so you put these minerals in the peanut butter. If you ever cook peanut butter,
you'll put a tablespoon of peanut butter and half a cup of water straight around through
water as soon as it comes to a simmer, goes completely solid. And you're like,
what the hell happened here? It's a thickener. So. So what you're doing now is, again,
we approach the blender, put a given amount of soy milk and you always put less soy milk than you
think you're going to need, because the banana is 75 percent liquid, by the way.
You add your mineral, spin it on low. It could be on low and then add your peanut butter. And
after you add your peanut butter, give it at least 30 seconds of just with the peanut butter alone.
It's smooth peanut butter. But if you have crunchy, it'll break it up.
Not as good. All these things are organic, by the way. Right. And then you add your your banana.
Now, when you add the banana, you peel it from the blossom end up and you break off as you're
peeling, you break off a piece of banana and use your thumb, forefinger and middle finger,
index finger, let's say, to squeeze the banana. So it crushes slightly,
then drop it into the blender. Don't slice it with a knife and don't put a whole banana
in because the little pieces are very slippery. No pun intended. Bananas are slippery and they
will never catch the blade. So you want to start it off by bruising or breaking the banana fiber
so as you break off a piece of banana, squeeze it between your three fingers.
So it kind of breaks up a little bit, cutting it on a cutting board. Won't do it.
Putting a whole banana won't do it. By the way, again, just to comment,
they have these smoothie shops years ago on Skype. Some people started doing smoothies the way I
recommended because they used to bring their family to these smoothie places. You know,
they charge an arm and a leg and it's disgusting. I would never drink that stuff. What they do,
it's like, oh, that's like if you're feeding it to animals, you know,
finesse in what these smoothie shops do. You know, there was a point at which they
had these places called Orange Julius in the Northeast. That's different.
Which that's what's processed. That's heavily processed. Yeah. And but there but there was
a competitor to them that existed for a very short amount of time. It sounded like Orange Julius.
Yeah. It was almost the same color and something. Yeah. Something like that. Julian. It was like,
maybe, you know, like orange or Julian or something like real close. And the guy used
to break up stuff like you're talking about by hand as opposed to cutting it.
All kinds of stuff he did. And I just recalled this because of the banana. So what you're saying
is you break a piece of the banana off kind of like monkeys do when they're breaking pieces of
banana. Right. As as as it's spinning. Remember, it's been spinning for 30 seconds with the peanut
butter, mineral and soil ready. So if you put it. Yeah. In other words, if you don't fight,
if you put all the ingredients together at once and hit the on high, it's not going to be the
same at all. You could even don't trust me on that. If you want to experiment, waste a portion,
do one the way I'm saying and do another one where you throw everything bulk in there,
hit the button. You'll see they won't want to taste anything alike. So it sounds to me like
it won't blend right if you do that because. Well, it won't. Yeah. That that also. But it's
beyond physical. So. OK. So basically, it's just those three ingredients and you want to blend it.
And then what you do is another 30 seconds or so, vary your speeds and then turn it off
until everything settles. Count to five and then start from low to high again,
just ascending. And that's good. Reason you do that is if you missed a spot,
if you have a holiday banana that decides to go on holiday and not get mixed, what will happen?
It'll drop to the bottom. It'll be right next to the blade. So when you start it again,
it'll get caught. That's how you finesse a smoothie. And this is like a meal in a glass.
So you want to let that five, 10 seconds go so that if there's any chunks that are
air, they'll come back to the top, right on top of the blade. So when you restart it,
yep, you'll get them again. This is how you finesse. This is how you make a five star
smoothie. Nice Michelin, Michelin three star. I like it. Yeah, it's like so. Anyway, this is how
you do it to finesse it and impress people. Now, if you do this for white people, forget I love you.
They'll never because they'll never, they can't do it themselves. They lack finesse when it comes
to food. Definitely call you a gourmet. Yeah, they'll never. Yeah. You don't press the ladies.
If you're a guy and if you're a gal, don't press the guys. So anyway, this is finesse. This could
be a second or third date kind of move when they come to your house to watch Netflix or whatever.
Right. I mean, sure. Sure. In Spanish they call it Baja Panty. There we go. But anyway, anyway,
so. So it'll spent people in the Spanish would get a kick out of that, hopefully.
So, yeah, that's a Baja Panty move. So what what I'm saying is the important part to note here
is use whatever soy milk you think you're going to start out with. Use half of that
because the mixture is going to more than double, almost triple by the time you're done.
Now, what are you looking at? Jack would put half the soy milk in there and the thing would explode.
And by the way, for for like six ounces or seven, six ounces or seven ounces of soy milk,
I use two bananas and end up with two eight ounce glasses really thick. You know what it's done?
It's like cake mix. You know how delicious cake mix is, right? You know, especially a runny one,
you know, like me. Yeah, it's like a cake mix meal in a glass. Really, really good. Now,
on the old days, kids used to love to lick the beaters because that's right. Yeah,
that's right. And yeah, so I'm not going to touch that one. I know. But anyway,
so because, yeah, so the next one is if you're doing a smoothie, what I also do,
I call it a fruit bag. I go to get a mixed fruit, which is blackberries, strawberries,
blueberries in a bag frozen. OK, so you want one of those berry. They actually have plenty of these
things. Yeah, they have them at Walmart. Again, organic, non-organic. Now, a lot of these,
it's going to be hard to get organic. But anyway, get that. And I get some OJ and some banana and I
mix it in with some ginger slices. And again, I'm not going to give instructions on this,
but guess when you put your OJ, what's the first thing to go in after the OJ? Your mineral,
because you're going to buffer. It's very acidic. You know, one thing I remember when people get
these to family, go out and get the smoothies. So I spent fifty dollars on three or four smoothies
and the children in my belly hurts because they drink it. It's cold. It's full of acid. It's not
filtered. So when you add your mineral, you always add mineral to a smoothie. That's why
first I started. I would go ahead and get one of those big generic mineral supplements.
I don't know which one I use. I don't know. I could go and look if you want. Maybe that'll
help some people. You don't have to be like me. You could just. But don't get the powder. Don't
get the compacted tablet. It has to be a capsule. There's a difference, right? You know what I mean?
You know what a tablet is like an aspirin tablet. You don't want that. It has to be a capsule to
break down. You don't want a solid thing. Right. I got you. This one is. No, this is no. Let me
hear it is mega mineral. Yeah, it's a big extra. It's called Mega Minerals. Nature's Life.
OK, right. Some food has 13 essential minerals, 250 vegetarian capsules. Thank you very much.
Then it goes down the line. Price wise, they're not that dozen or so. Yeah. Price wise,
they're not that bad at Walmart. They got a big old cardboard pull out everywhere in the country
and you can find them in that section. Whatever. Yeah, I think now I think that was one in 10
or 15. But that's a year we've been running that now for a year and a half. Well, if you're
going to make it's for 250 smoothies. Right. So right. So how many smoothies are you going to
you're going to have one every single day, even if you had one every single day, you got
more. Yeah. And you probably won't because you want to break from it. So when you do the mixed
food and all that stuff, you should strain it. So what you do is you pour it out and you put it
through a colander, a strainer, a fine strainer, like a 30 mesh, even a 20 mesh is fine. You know,
it looks like a window screen. Right. I was just going to say it goes into another container.
Yeah. And then you put it back in the blender a little more. Now, your your mineral goes in
first and then your ginger slices and then your fruit slowly and you put a banana in last and you
make this delicious. It's almost like a passion fruit. And that, again, is a meal in a glass.
That's for summertime when I say meal in a glass. I mean, you'll have that. It'll hold you most of
the day. And then when you get hungry, you don't have to have a full meal. You can just have a
snack and you're good. And just eyeball the amount of mixed berries you want in there.
Just kind of OK. Yeah. In the beginning, whatever amount some people I prefer them so sick that
they're like a meal in a glass. You almost need a spoon. I like this stuff, really. But that's
harder. That's more on the pro smoothie maker level. The center smoothies are more for beginners.
They just practice on getting them thicker and thicker. You should always have a spatula,
those silicone spatulas to get it out and also for screening it. But you should always strain
your smoothies if you have berries. Always. Oh, my gosh. You're charging like twelve dollars for
a smoothie is more than 10 years ago. And they didn't even strain us with it. It's like it was
like people paying twelve bucks for a smoothie with berries and with all the seeds and everything.
They don't even know. And it's like, my gosh, you throw that in a trough.
Too many damn seeds. Yeah, of course. Yeah. It's like who would want to drink
that? And no buffer as you buffer. What? What? It's full of acids anyway. So that's this.
That's pretty much a summer regimen diet. You do need the mineral because of the heat.
See, because this summer, the heat is very young. It's going to make you yin and produce
yin in the environment. You just get your energy from the environment. Right. So you're in the
winter. The cold is very yin. And that's going to make you very young. Right. That's why when
something is soft, when you put cold, which is very yin, what does it become? It becomes hard.
It freezes. Right. So it's young. You see the yin and yang cold when something is
heat is very young. When you put a lot of heat on something, what happens? It melts.
Right. So I'm also just curious. It might be a dumb question, but at no point do you
add any water to this, huh? No water. You don't have to unless you end up wanting to thin it out
for any reason. Sometimes if it gets too thick, it won't spin at the top. Stop the blender
because it will burn out the bushing. The bushing on the blade requires for it to be in water or
wet. OK, so you might want to add you could add water if it depends on taste again or if you want
to minimize on the orange juice. OK, let's say it doesn't have to be orange juice. I've used other
juices, whatever. If you if you have fruit like you, you can make an apricot puree using water.
If you have really good tasting water, you can puree the apricots, make like a baby food out of
them using just water. So it's a lot of apricot. But things like apricot, you don't have to peel.
The peel dissolves very readily. Well, somebody somebody who's listening to you about food before
them might say, well, look, a lot of this you're not talking about eating locally here, you know?
Oh, yes and no. The bananas are kind of odd because they're they harvested in the winter
sometimes or they grow all year round. But that's a tropical fruit. Right. It will. OK,
so what does a tropical fruit do? Does it adjust? It's grown. What? Tropical means it's warm and
hot. Right. Right. So if you eat tropical fruit, it will adjust your body chemistry to what? A
warm and hot climate. OK, so that will be easier to get along with. Right. OK, now it's easier to
do that for the summer to adopt because, believe it or not, most of the fruit that people partake
in and that's popular tend to be of the tropical type, even sugar is tropical. So it's easier to
go and sink in the summer than the winter. Now, the thing that'll really mess you up in the summer
is something like polar fish, like halibut, salmon. Remember when there was a big popularity
in salmon 20 years ago? That was the thing that people were dying, even with the ACs. I mean,
they were felt uncomfortable no matter how cold the room was, because, you know, the polar,
you know, the cold weather fish. Right. So and meats also, certain meats, cured meats in the
summer you want to avoid. But you do need the mineral and the salt because your body needs that
to process and stay active, you know, because your body produces all the minerals it needs from
sodium basically and magnesium. Right. Anyway, we've we've kind of gone into that before,
but let's jump off of the food thing. But that's how you make a pro smoothie. I want to go back to
the Brandon Joe Williams stuff. Right. OK, what's happening is he's going into a jackass scenario.
Now, if you watch the movie Jackass, not every stunt they did was successful, but not everyone
failed. It was kind of like some some people did succeed in all the stunts. Right. Yeah. Well,
that was part of the you know, that look, that was part of the entertainment value. Like you try this
and now we get to see whether it succeeds or not. Yeah, that's right. So that's what's going to that's
what he's going through. So it's fun. It's good that he has pokes fun at everything because he
should. Now, what I suggest that he's the last time on last Sonic that he is not doing well
is that he's doing blanket and blank endorsements or a nonconditional endorsement he's putting
without recourse. But without recourse does not mean that you do not not have a tax liability,
could arise a tax liability. The only way to get out of that using the system they set up
is titled 12 USC for 11, where you just every country, by the way, has their own thing where
they cannot stop you from putting a restrictive endorsement by law, they can refuse to give you
service, but they can't stop you see, there's a trick there. But so I know in Europe, if you put
lawful money only, right, that helps, right, you could do that here too, but citing the code.
So he might get nailed on that. The other thing is regarding signature, there's a lot of stuff
about people with traffic stuff, the cop wants you to sign and they don't want to sign because they
think if they sign, by the way, you autograph as a human being. But when they ask you for a
signature, that's usually like an authorized signature for someone else's signatory.
A signatory is someone that represents someone who are you representing the all caps name,
right? Because that's a public corporation that was started after you were born. If you look at a
birth or long form birth certificate, it has the date and the time when you were born. And then
it shows another date and time when they created the all caps public corporation, what they call
straw man, right? And then the way you identify that is, is when it says when it made it to a
public official's office or hands or whatever, right? So it's usually a week or a few days later,
usually some states have codes, it has to be done within 72 hours. So if they really wanted you to
make your mark, they'd say I need your autograph. When you go to people, they don't ask for your
signature. If you're famous, they ask for what your autograph, right? But corporate and legal
and law, they ask for signature because you're a signatory for someone else. So what I've done
in the past, and this created quite a ruckus, and I've been telling people this, you know,
this is one way to escape, you know, the binding. You get a traffic ticket once you sign Sure,
no problem. Boom, what do you sign void? You sign void and it looks you ever see how doctors sign?
Yeah, right. You're right vo ID with a dot but it looks like and they say what's that? You know?
Well, that's how I sign and then you send the ticket back and you write a letter
that this is no good. I signed it void. Why is it no good? Oh, come on, come on completely
illegal what they're doing, right? You can depending on your own way, or I'm returning
it back to you. By the way, it's signed void. I've done that. And then it's an attorney for
the city came back. He can't sign his own ticket void. Like it's my ticket. Now. You see how they
play around? You know, it's not my ticket at all. That's your property did the hot potato.
But you sign everything void. I mean, people are like, Oh, you sign that? Of course,
we're going to sign your stuff, too. I don't care. And but the thing is, if you don't tell them it's
void, they think it's a signature and they keep moving along. If you want to act on it. You do
this and you send back say, Hey, look, there's your document back. And by the way, it's signed
void because it's void. Why is it void? You get some examples. So unilateral contract, meaning
the only one signing. So obviously, you're here to defraud. Number two, it's unconscionable
because this thing you're bringing up law, legal stuff. And you're asking me to waive
all these things. You know, you can go on and on and on and on, however you want to do it.
You know, basically, the in order to do this right, you need to do A, B, C and D or whatever.
Or I signed it void because I was under a complete panic and I didn't want to do anything legally
binding. That's the best one. I was I felt like like my life was threatened and I didn't
want anything to do anything, anything legally binding. Oh, you should see that freak out.
One of them was like, Oh, we sent your stuff to the Department of Justice. So I'm like, Oh, great.
That's great. Thank you. Yeah, that's great. Educate them. Okay, here's the thing about
education. And Brandon's mentioned this also, and I've been saying this for 20 years.
Do you think people working in any government office, any government office, the IRS or the bank
know any of this? No. Do you think you're going to make 20 or 30 bucks an hour sitting in the bank?
And the reality of it is you just need to write your name and write out the amount and go to the
Federal Reserve and have that given to you in notes or on an account. Do you think you're going to be
doing what you're doing like a cop or a lawyer or an accountant or working at the IRS or working
at the DMV or working at the State Department? Do you think if you know the reality of the
Bill of Exchange Act and the March the 9th Emergency, 1933 Emergency Banking Act, do you
think that if you knew any of the UCC, these people would be sitting there working, trying to
quote unquote pay bills? No, nobody knows this. Nobody because let's hearken back. How many times
have you heard me talk about stuff in the Bible that sounds fucking outrageous, and you go and
look it up and it's right there and it's contrary to what everyone thinks? Yeah, all the time,
right? All the time. This is the same stuff. So basically, endorsement, endorsement, endorsement.
In other words, you are free. Okay. America is the free one of the freest countries in the world.
That's why it got so bad. What happens is when you have a free society and open society,
a bunch of people over here are going to say, hey, it's real easy to steal from them over there.
We just go over there. How are we going to steal from them? Well, the best thing is you don't have
to rob a bank if you own it. The best way to rob a bank is to own a bank, right? Yeah, of course.
So that's how they got in. So basically, this is the same ancient group of people.
And well, the old saying, right, you can rob a bank with a gun, but with a bank, you can rob the
world, right? So yeah, on and on and on. Yeah. And they're not even banks. They're national associations.
And we've got all that on older Sonics. So what's going on is no one knows what's going on. And I
think anyone who's been into Greek food for a long time is can validate that for sure.
When I say no one, I mean, with very little exception, you're not going to be happy. But
the thing is, would you rather know what's going on and not be happy or not know what's going on
and not be happy? Because believe me, all these people that think they're happy or not happy,
they did these, you know, there's something called the misery index. Yes, right. Yeah. And
they found like, what is it, 78 or 87, one of those percentages of people are unhappy.
And 100% of those people are 99.99999% don't know what's going on. They're still unhappy.
Right? So you're here to waste your time, folks. You know, and one of the most important things
other than that, is this is a planet surface dwelling Earth inhabitants are fucking morons,
right? That's fucking with a cup capital K. Oh, they're idiots. And it ain't gonna change.
Because the children now can change. But the children are being raised by idiots. And it
continues and continues and continues. The only way to stop it is to pull when the children are
born to take them away from the parents, by the way, and have them raised in a situation a new
society. Somehow. Right? It would look like a big orphanage. Right? Because you will be like one
adult for 10 children, no pedophiles. You know, I didn't say pedophile because pedo is feet.
Yeah, right. So yeah, and you've raised that way. And then you have to wait for the adults to die
off. Because you can't throw them back into society, you have to wait a good 7080 years.
Or you can accelerate the process of dying off the the adults with a big war or a real pandemic.
Right? And I'm all for that stuff, but not the bullshit to a real one. You're gonna have a real
war, do a real fucking war where you wipe out everybody. That's the opposing side, right?
But only after you separate a group of children that can that's right.
That's right. This is all bullshit. So so this is proof that there are higher powers that don't
allow this because all this thing has to chug along what has to chug along the era of everybody
wasting each other's time, which has been over 5000 years, 6000 plus years, sorry, that everyone
is wasting everyone's time. And that's just cosmic. It has to go that way. And fortunately,
you don't live that long. And what I mean, like 70, even if you live 70 8090, you're more fortunate
if you die when you're 30. But either way, you don't have to put up with it that long, right?
And your memory isn't that good. And you're emotionally limited, meaning most humans,
so they're not going to be that their spirit isn't going to be that negatively affected by
being an idiot for the whole life, their whole lives, right? Because you're most they don't know
what emotions are for. So they're not going to be right, their spirits can have minimal effect,
they got video games, they got porn, they got sports, they got church, they got each other,
right? outward appearances, to me is that the most idiotic people seem to be quite pleased,
you know, with everything. Yeah, but they're still unhappy. But whether it's 78%, or 87%
of the people are none of those people know anything about anything at all. Right? So that's
just the thing, because they know something's not right. And they, here's the thing, if anyone ever
tells you you're anti government or anti, you know, you're actually the United the laws of
the United States, even the corporation, those beautiful laws ever, just right, if everyone
followed the law, think about it, you need to feed your children. How much do you need $42,896.40
you write that out, you write it out in words, right, you put the number just like a check,
you go to Federal Reserve, you write down the demand, right, Federal Reserve window, and they
have is I put this in my account. And then you say, Okay, 15 minutes, you go to your account,
you run your card through and guess what's there? 42,890. Right, go feed your children.
That means a gallon of milk will be like 1800 bucks, but that's fine. It doesn't matter. Just
numbers. Especially if you can just go back and write another piece of paper out. Well, you know,
in the Matrix, when they had Neo tied down, it says we created a world for you where it was a
paradise. But it didn't couldn't last, right? Right. That's like, did you remember there was
they rejected it was the problem is raised to perfect, right? This was done a starting in the
1800s. So the 1930s, the entire world, if you study all the banking laws and all that stuff,
that all a we're in a perfect world, but they can't tell the people that certain people who
know how it runs, it would be perfect. In other words, there's no need for money. So at all,
because you just, you know, eventually, let's say, once it gets to the point where it's $10,000 for
a gallon of milk, people say, Wait a second, stop. Why do we even need this ridiculous stuff, right?
And then you move on to the next level. And that's exactly where we are right now. That's
why branding and talks about infinite money is 100% correct. Just like I've been saying for
two decades now, on Greek speak, you know, when I go to a checkout, and they said,
you want to give the change to charity? And I said, Why? No, no. Why are their fingers broken?
They look at me like, what? What do you mean? They just sign their name, right? Go to frozen,
they'll give them whatever, just write your name comes drawn off your signature.
been saying this ever since anyone's been listening to Greek speak, and I can give you the details.
It's exactly how it's done. So and where and who and what. But no one knows this for a reason. It's
part of the cosmic censorship. But it doesn't mean that the time isn't right at any time.
When someone jumps forward, it makes a big deal about it. Now, to answer sets a semi answer of the
email I got about what's the negative of Brandon Joe, Joe Williams. The other thing is, if there's
if you put in his name on YouTube, most recent their YouTube search where there's some people
that are having successes, and they show you what they write on a gas bill, basically,
you got a gas bill, electric bill, credit card bill, whatever, you know, the voucher that says,
cut this off and send it, it says it's a voucher, a coupon says, yeah, no one knows how to fill
those out. So what they do is they stack them. And you know, if you have unsigned checks are
called non performing instruments, and those are still cashable, as long as they have a number on
them, but you get like one or 2%. So the companies keep these, and they still monetize them. But what
you're supposed to do is cross out a few things on there. In other words, adjust the address,
you write your name, and who it's for, meaning you write your name twice, and you write out the
amount with words, just like you know, to check how they have you write it out with words, right?
If it's right, yeah, if it's 1000, you write o n e t h o u. That's right. Yeah, that's right.
Because in the UCC, the priority is when something is typewritten. It's it has authority. But when
something is handwritten, it has an even higher authority than anything printed, right? So that's
why they make you write it out, it has nothing to do with it, you know, so what you do, then,
is a few more items is a few people that show you could state a couple of codes,
and you send it in with a letter with instructions, right? They in other words,
their computers are connected with the utility company. So they're part of a network. And that
network eventually ends up at the Federal Reserve discount window, you tell them what to do with it,
I'm not gonna, this will have to be, we could spend an hour going step by step, just like we
did the smoothie, maybe we should have done this instead of the smoothie, right? How to write a bill
of exchange, right? Let's get it next time. Yeah, yeah, yeah. So and you send it in and it works,
it does zero out. It's really funny, though, because I remember doing this a long time ago,
call started zeroing everything out. After a while, they sent you a bill, but not never for
the amount that was zeroed out, just starting new again. And you call around and they're like,
well, if we do it for you, basically, the long story, make sure if we do it for you,
we have to do it for everyone. You get it, duh. That's how everyone should be doing it.
It will collapse the system, it will collapse the system, but the system was set to fail this way.
You How many times have you heard that the money collapsed in the country failed the society
collapsed, right? In the past 150 years, this happens very often, right? So that this if you
have a society like this one, that's based on Christian values, and the money system and the
medical system, it deserves to collapse. And it's amazing that it's held on for over 150 years this
way. And in earnest over 90 years this way with the fake medical and the fake law and the fake
money, it needs to collapse and it's going to be horrible. But then again, if you have a good
pandemic and a war, a real war, you know, and a real pandemic, a real war with real generals,
where you take out huge amounts of huge civilian populations and take out the military, everything.
That's what I'm about a real war. And a real pandemic where people go to work in the morning,
and then they die on their way to work, right, but coming back home, a real pandemic,
the collapse, what will be less people will come together when they're have a real war and a real
pandemic, and the money will not be so important. So that's how you buffer out the society solely
collapsing, because the money systems falling apart. So fun days, man, fun days. You know,
that's that's what that's the absolute necessity. And if you happen to be here, it's going to be
rough. But you know, hey, sorry, you know, you ask your parents to be born here, or you dropped
here from a higher power. So the only solution to total mayhem from us money, everybody finding out
the money system when the legal system is a complete fraud, and all that and the medical
system is a complete fraud is to have the war and a real pandemic. So the chances of all three
happening are slim than none, you'll get another fake war another fake pandemic. And will the
people find out how the money system works? No, so it's not going to happen. But I just gave you
the solution. Yeah.