The sonic entity known as Ocelli in the Greek.
This is fun, because, well, we wind up talking about certain literary characters and books.
And we start talking about, well, what is the biblical text, what is the Bible, you know, common parlance.
All right, well, the character of, and we've seen some questions in the chat.
I'll leave it to you to begin to just explain that, because we're all familiar with the greatest story ever told, you know.
I'm pulling out these metrics on purpose, but go ahead.
It's like running a stop sign, right? Let's just put it this way.
Image training, the whole society, I think it was Confucius that said it's not laws or words, it's symbols that control people.
So, you've got a stop sign, it's basically an octagon with a red field with some letters written in it.
Now, most of the people here are English speaking and used to seeing stop.
But if you go to somewhere like Qatar or Saudi Arabia, and you go to an intersection, and you see a red octagon, and it's got some Arabic script on it, guess what?
That's probably a stop sign, isn't it?
Right.
You see what I mean?
So, someone pulls a badge on you, right?
This is my authority.
It's just a piece of metal.
Someone raises a flag.
It's just a piece of cloth.
Right.
What are they trying to communicate?
You know, there's an old story.
Let's see if I could really redact, make it small, short.
Arizona farmer government agencies in the 30s started being introduced to the people.
Gets a knock on the door.
I'm from the federal government.
Here's my badge.
That means I could go anywhere on your farm.
He says, fine.
So, about an hour later, he doesn't see the guy, but he hears somebody, the same guy screaming.
He's climbed up the top of a tree, and there's this huge Brahma bull ramming the tree.
And the Fed is asking him for help.
He says, come help me.
Come help me.
And the farmer tells him, why don't you just show them your badge?
Right?
You see?
There you go.
So, this is all image training.
So, when you have an image that people rely on, let me just say that again.
People are relying on images.
Should we just end it right here?
We could just end the sonic right here and do sonic 16 and make sonic 15 the world's shortest Greek-speak sonic.
You see what I mean?
You're relying on images.
Yeah.
Okay.
What did they do?
Well, this is the thing.
I love the stop sign, by the way, because I've seen that, and I've also seen that people translate it in their mind.
They'll tell me they saw an exit sign in a piece of film.
Now, they did not see an exit sign where the letters E-X-I-T were actually printed on an illuminated sign,
something that we've gotten accustomed to seeing in the United States, right?
But they did see that sign.
They translated it in their own minds, even though the language on it is not English.
Right, but in this case, the language is irrelevant.
It's irrelevant, but that's the point.
The symbol, the badge, the stop sign is the most universal.
Well, that hanging rectangular light near a door, somebody goes, that's an exit sign.
That's what they know it as.
Oh, no.
That star, that piece of metal.
I got you.
That star, that piece of metal, it's just a pointy piece of metal with some spikes coming off of it
and in some places it's a six-pointed star, in some places it's an eight-pointed star, right?
Well, yeah.
Well, I've worked in TV and radio, I mean radio and TV,
and when you're walking down the hall towards the studios,
they have a lit box sign that says recording or on air,
and it looks a lot like illuminated metal frame sign with writing on it.
It's not an exit sign, but it means something important.
But it's also positioning of the thing.
See, that thing is usually either above a particular door and or, you know,
a lot of those on air signs were lower, right?
They were lower to the ground.
The one that hangs from the ceiling is the exit.
The one that might be over the door on the wall, now that's more of an on air sign.
You see what I'm saying?
There are cues to the placement and use of these things as well, aren't there?
Yeah, but in the case of the subject we're going to bring up,
it's more like the badge of authority.
Well, yeah, but that same shape.
That's why I said running a stop sign.
Well, yes, yes, but that same shape, understand, on the tag of a dog,
you don't think that's a police dog, do you?
No, no.
You don't assume that's a badge.
No, but the thing is, yeah.
You see what I'm saying?
Context, right?
Context for placement, no?
It has to have authority behind it, though.
In other words, we've talked, beginner Greek speakers, people are motivated by penalties.
So if you don't believe in that sign or don't have the issue that you've been told it's been issued,
then you're in trouble, right?
Like in this case, as we get further subject, you're going to burn in hell, right?
So that's the real interesting part.
All right, continuing on with 15.
Greek, again, authority.
The authority behind the thing.
All right, go ahead.
It's not just the authority.
There's an engineering aspect to it.
Because as we go further on this, we're going to notice that it's false.
Most of the symbols don't really represent the way that they're handled, how they should be.
How are they represented?
Like most people want to stop at a stop sign,
not because they're going to be T-boned or hit by another car.
It's because they don't want a penalty by being caught that they ran one right.
Again, people are motivated by penalty.
And there's an engineering aspect to this.
Let's say social engineering, right?
I think I gave a couple of examples, you and I, before we started.
Diamonds.
Diamonds were not considered valuable until recently, past 150 years.
It was a marketing campaign that De Beers did to people that were engaged to be married.
Just like no one ate bacon and eggs until the pork belly market went up,
and petroleum was never known as a fossil fuel.
It was oil from rock, rock mineral oil.
Actually, you can still buy it, and it's called mineral oil, right?
Baby oil, right?
So all these things are the way that they – so things are what they are.
They change, and new things come in with symbolism.
Now, that's the engineering aspect of it.
Like, for example, the bacon and eggs, the diamonds being precious,
and the fossil fuel, those are social engineering examples.
Combine that with the symbols being very important.
Combine that with how people accept it and what they do with it.
Once they get up and running with it, it doesn't change,
and because it becomes generational, right?
So let's give the engineering point of view.
Sure.
It's not that simple.
People are always speaking on social engineering in this,
but I'm going to give an engineering point of view because it's very important
and how you see a little bit.
It's the same whether you're doing a building or social engineering or whatever
or an airplane or a bridge or anything.
Engineering concepts are the same.
It's about how do you handle the qualities and the quantities, right?
Okay.
Here's a simple example.
Let's get started.
You have a 10-story building, okay?
It's a steel building, okay?
Whatever facade, let's say glass facade, very simple idea.
I want to build a 100-story building that looks just like that.
Okay, so I'm going to need 10 times the material.
That's the simple linear approach, right?
It's still linear, right?
That's fair.
Well, yes, but from an engineering point of view,
you see most people would read the Bible or whatever,
and it's a very linear approach if you ask them how much more material do you need
for a 100-story building versus a 10-story building.
They're all going to say 10 times more.
That's not really how it works.
Well, here's the question, right?
Doesn't the condition change because of the fact that you're adding the height?
I'm not an engineer of any kind, by the way.
I have zero engineering ideas.
Go ahead.
Yeah, we're told that if we don't know engineering,
we have to get an engineer, so I'm going through this.
So basically what I'm going to give you here is basically equivalent
to a four-year education, what you'll get after a four-year education,
because basically in engineering,
a really good engineer can draw anything on a napkin,
and you'll go into reference manuals to design it,
and you won't be more than 5% or 10% off.
So that's basically what anybody could do.
It was all engineers look at computers and reference manuals.
Okay.
But the whole scope of engineering is how it's linear even when it's not linear.
So you have one linear aspect.
If you, let's say, go to the public, well,
100 stories requires 10 times more material than a 10-story building.
Yes, okay, very good, but that won't – no, that doesn't really work at all
because you have to go floor by floor.
So the load on the building on the first floor will take the nine stories above it.
So the first floor has to support nine stories above it.
The second floor has to support eight stories above it, right?
The third floor has to support seven stories above it
in terms of how strong it needs to be, right?
So from a stress diagram, it ends up looking like a pyramid.
It gets narrower and narrower, the amount of material that you need.
Okay, so when we go to a 100-story building,
the bottom floor has to support 99 stories.
That's just the second floor.
First floor, right?
If you go to the second floor of the 100-story building,
it's 98 stories above it and so on and so forth.
You see it's like a backward – okay, now, on the 10-story building,
if you look at how much material you need to support those nine floors,
and if you look at now the 100-story building,
that's the same looking building except it's 100 stories tall,
has to support 99 floors.
It's 11 times as much, isn't it?
You see?
Absolutely.
So that means that the beam structure and the structure of the first floor –
you know, the same building, one's 10 stories, the other one's 100 stories.
That basement and that first floor has to support 11 times more,
just the vertical.
We're not even going wind loads or complex shock loads and things moving.
What if – you know, this is true.
Some captains on medium-sized boats, if everyone goes to –
if it's a ferry or something and everyone goes to one side of the boat,
you know that boat could flip, right?
Right, right.
The same thing with buildings, by the way.
Okay.
So as we go up, it's going to get less and less.
So now here's the thing.
When you get up to the 90th floor of the 100-story building, okay,
that will have very similar supports as the first floor of the 10-story building
because they each have only nine – or 91st floor.
Go to the 91st floor of the 100-story building.
That could be built just like the first floor of the 10-story building, you see,
because they each – because it's just nine stories above, right?
I understand what you're saying.
The one thing that I'm wondering that's missing from this, though,
just because I worked construction and just basically did what I was told, right?
I had nothing to do with design or anything.
But move this, break this, do that, right?
Here's the thing.
The foundation, that's the only thing I haven't heard you say anything about,
is you have to build it on something.
Right.
Well, just talking about what people perceive down on the top
because it gets a little – the foundation is what you're building on.
If you're bedrock or how is the load going to be distributed, very important.
There's a building in California right now or San Fran or somewhere that's tilting.
It's a recently built thing too.
There's one in Manhattan too like that, and it's moving.
Leaning Tower of Pisa type stuff, right?
Right.
Okay.
So we're going to get into the subject of who the Christ is and how –
this is really start here Greek-speak, but I always say the same thing
because I'm presuming that if people are interested,
they'll be able to go to the text and see it, right?
Okay.
But it's an okay – it's actually – that's a – I keep presumptions in a certain way
because they're safe and they treat people properly.
In other words, when I say what I say about anything, you have a choice there.
Like I gave you the punchline to the joke or I gave you the most important part first.
It's up to you if you want to go back and confirm it, find it, or use it,
or just say, okay, the Greek says there's no crucifixion.
That's good enough for me.
Someone else might say, oh, that's total bullshit.
I don't buy it, but let's go look where he said I should look to see that,
and it's totally obvious.
And other people will go and look to where I say to look to see it,
and they won't see it even though it's right in front of them, right?
Right, right.
You see?
So the presumption that I have saves everyone a whole lot of time, right?
And that's why I like to just get to the point.
That's a problem that researchers have.
I know you do research or whatever, but researchers go into the philosophical side,
which is once you – let's say you're researching what happened in a certain event
like 9-11 or JFK or whatever.
Once it's discovered what really happened, your career as a researcher is over.
So it's not in your interest to find it, you see.
It's not in their interest to find solutions to problems.
So when I look at stuff and I discuss it, if I can't see a clear shot,
just like designing this building, how it can be explained, I leave it alone,
and I give the reason why it's like that, where I see the reason it's like that,
and compare it to other things that are similar.
For example, with JFK research, how many public figure, high dignitary figures
have been assassinated in the past 150 years,
and how many of their assassins were actually the real assassins that we were told?
Probably none.
Very few.
I mean, there's a handful of circumstances I can think of off the top of my head
where, yeah, I think that's exactly what happened.
But otherwise, no.
One out of 10, 10%?
At best.
Yeah, at best.
Okay.
So now we're going into a field, when we do that,
that we know that at best we just said what it is at best, right?
I don't like to do that.
That's fine.
But I'll state it, at best is.
But the reason why at one out of 10 at best is because of this other reason now, right?
It's a cover-up.
Why is there a cover-up?
Again, psychological operation.
By the way, I know someone whose professor teaches medicine, right?
It's a doctor that teaches doctors, right?
Oh, boy, yeah.
And they're given an award.
Anyway, I don't want to get into too many details.
Recently they're going to be getting an award for what they're doing or whatever.
And I'm like, you know what you're doing?
I basically say it's psychological chaos is what the university is.
And they look at me.
You know, here's an interesting thing, even with this particular individual.
They got all the Greek speak on the medicine and more, a lot more.
And they agree.
They have never confronted me as challenged or anything.
They're like, yeah, yeah, it's pretty much it.
They either say I can't acknowledge it or they don't acknowledge it, meaning they,
whoever they is, you know, they in the big quotes, right?
They, yeah.
So, but when I say the things I do, there's this presumption that you can do
whatever you want with the information.
So there's an engineering, there's symbols, there's all this stuff.
But when you go back to what this is all spurring from what's in the chat,
and I answered recently, I'll address that on the next sonic.
Because going over it again, which is part of basic Greek speak,
what's any biblical stuff or any whatever stuff is all really basic Greek speak.
I don't need to get into it, but I want to get into the engineering aspect of it
and how to look around, just like the 10-story building.
It's still linear, by the way.
The 10-story building versus the 100-story building, it's still very linear.
You know, yeah, you do need 10 times the material on the outside,
but what's supporting it, you're going to need a hell of a lot more
on the inside, you see, right?
And the engineering is so simple, I just laid it out.
Basically, an undergraduate degree in engineering, I just laid out.
I could do one in aerospace also, if anyone's interested, and chemical engineering.
I could lay out a basic bachelor's to a four-year degree in about five minutes,
basically the premise of it, okay?
So it's very simple.
It's not easy.
There's a lot of homework you have to do, right?
But here's the thing.
Who is the Christ?
This is very important in the Western culture, by the way.
It's more important than most people give it importance to
because if you study history, there have been major wars for cause of religion, right?
But also, a lot of these quote-unquote religious wars,
each side was carrying the same cross, right?
So you have fights.
Okay, so there's a lot of aspects to this that may or may not really strike people well,
and I do say this in a humorous, sarcastic way when I bring up the subject of the Christ.
You know, the Christian era is dubbed the Christian era because of the academics,
and they're self-professed atheists, by the way, the academics, right?
How do I know?
Go to any university and do a survey with all the faculty there.
You'll find that about 75% to 90% of them profess atheism, right?
Right.
And they call it the Christian era, so it has nothing to do with religion.
By the way, this is something for the atheists, you guys out there.
You're full of crap.
You are victims of some major league bullshit.
Why?
I'm not saying this from a religious side.
I'm saying it from a legal, lawful side.
Why are the atheists full of bullshit?
Why?
I'll tell you why.
Very simple.
Everyone has easy access to the courts if you can pay the fees, right?
Everyone has a certain amount of access to certain medias that they can start a movement,
let's say, put information out.
You can do a blog.
You can even buy time on TV and radio or make a point, right?
Okay.
Okay, so you atheists are full of crap.
Why?
Because they say that there is no God whatever.
They're not necessarily anti-God, but you could almost hinge it as if they were, right?
G-O-D, which I don't believe in a God anyway as just one God.
No, there are many.
It's a pantheon.
It's like saying army and thinking there's one soldier.
It's ridiculous.
It's a plurality.
But this is why the atheists are full of shit, and I'm dragging this up because I'm waiting
for people in their own minds to see how obvious it is that the atheists are full of crap.
And I'm not going to say why.
We'll say that on another Sonic.
No, I'm just joking.
Why are the atheists full of crap?
Okay, very simple.
Take out a dollar bill.
What does it say on it?
In God we trust.
Okay.
How easy with all the things that I mentioned that there are plenty of people self-professing
being atheists.
Well, by the way, 300 years ago, if you did that, it was very unpopular.
All right, so they wear it like a badge, right?
First of all, it's out in the open, and it's quite popular, right?
Second, I just mentioned that you have very easy access to the court system, and you have
easy access to media, in other words, getting your idea out to a plurality of groups, right?
Okay.
So why are they full of shit?
How many atheists have actually filed a suit in district court to take, in God we trust,
off the money, what they use as money?
How many?
I have seen like one case where somebody tried to assert that.
There was like one odd case.
Really?
I've never heard of it.
Yeah, no, it did happen, and it was in New York.
It was very strange.
It was part of a case with a bunch of facets to it, and they just, you know what they did,
is just dismissed it.
No, I never heard of it.
I actually looked it up.
I couldn't find anything a while back because I was making this as a point.
I'm not saying that it didn't happen.
Oh, yeah, I read about this in New York.
It was a certain New York.
Well, why isn't it pursued?
Well, yeah, there you go.
Is there a movement behind it?
Where is the support and the underpinning of their ideology when they have it in their pocket?
The opposite is true.
Those that do believe are not creating any kind of a support.
But both things, look, here's something that I've always said, and I wonder if you disagree.
To me, when somebody says atheist, that just means that they have selected an atypical God structure.
Well, still, if you're an atheist, then you just find out where they get their laws from.
Well, you believe in the laws of the state.
Yes, I do.
Well, then the state is your God, and April 1st is your holiday.
Bottom line.
I said that before I ever met you.
That's where you get your law.
Because that's what it is.
You get your law from your God.
That's the structure.
Yeah.
So if you just look, the laws of man, that's it.
Okay, well, then guess who your God is?
Well, the guy who's running the men, which is the state, in this case, not the government.
So here's the part that I'm always sarcastic when I bring up Greek speak,
and I preface that I've spun off on the atheist things.
What do they show you?
Even the atheist academics dubbed it the Christian era.
Well, it doesn't have to be, but they did.
And I can get into why they did also, because of the Gregorian calendar.
But I always make a reference to that figure that they show you, a guy nailed to a cross wearing a diaper.
And I say that in a way that it's not respectful.
No, it's not.
And it's not meant to be.
But that's what I see when I first saw that.
Objectively, it's the image.
It is the image presented.
I mean, that's it.
There was a guy wearing a loincloth.
Yeah, a loincloth.
It's practically false.
Actually, we'll get into this a little bit.
Sure.
If you understand what really happened, he was naked.
Should have been.
Yeah.
Yeah, he was naked.
Okay, so one thing about this is you'll never hear me really reading out of books and stuff like that,
because plenty of people do that.
They'll sit there and read where their reference point is.
And for some reason, I found out, like the word nice, when I tell people, you know what the word nice means?
I can tell them.
But I say, go look it up on your own, because after a while of trying to define things for people,
I found that if they look it up themselves, it has like 70% more punch than if you just tell them.
It really does.
And off air, you said to me I was a nice guy the other day.
I want to see if you're awake.
Yeah, I got you.
I told you.
You know that.
I said something rude back to you, but we laughed about it.
It's okay.
But this point got me in trouble, actually, when I was about five years old.
So I want to just throw this in real fast, because you just brought up something very interesting.
I think it's very basic and is in any translation, any representation of the biblical text.
And it's there, and I wonder if you would concur with this, because I've always seen this,
and at five years of age, I knew this.
Here's the thing.
They describe the crucifixion, right?
And at a certain point, he's stripped.
Now, it says it there in English.
It does.
I don't know how it's stated right off the top of my head this very moment,
but you bring it back to my mind.
At five years old, I had recently read it.
And I said in one of those religious-based institutional schools,
first of all, he's got all these powers.
How does he not get himself off of the cross?
But this is me at five.
Sorry, Greek.
Well, he didn't really have – here's the thing.
We'll get into that, too.
Bring that up.
No, that's fine.
Okay, but the other powers thing, because that's very interesting,
because the powers that he exercised were always collective.
He needed two or more people.
Not needed, but he was done that way.
We can get into that maybe in the future.
But here's the point I want to bring up.
Well, but the other thing, really fast, is that he was stripped.
And it says he's stripped.
He is bare.
So why is he like that?
And it was explained to me.
Oh, no.
No, no, no.
But I'm looking at –
I agree what you're saying.
I'm not disagreeing.
Let's just chalk it up as we're in agreement on that.
But it's too fine of a detail for those that are not really aware
of how we come across how the hundred-story building really is put together.
Well, I'm just pointing out that it's just one of those flaws that they look at you
and then they explain away.
But that doesn't show you what I've just told you.
And I'm five years old doing this.
So, again, this is not a seriously sophisticated point of view.
It's just you brought it to my memory.
Subjecting young children, even at five or so –
five is when you're considered alive, by the way, in law,
because many things go wrong up until five years old.
Five years old is also the age where most breastfeeding was done to.
So when a child died between being born and five years old, it was more typical.
And it wasn't until the child was five that it could be counted.
This is kind of like – this is in law also.
But, okay, I see what you're saying.
But there's many – there's thousands of fine points like that that work.
But this is the – I want to come up with a way to explain the engineering aspect of this,
which is very simple, just like the ten-story building analogy to a hundred-story building.
It's very, very simple.
Now, there's another thing I wanted to mention that I'm going to throw in.
They call it the Mandela effect.
Now, I don't – I'm not going to read tonight or now any verses or any –
I'll give the books where you can go.
And you can find it.
The computer search engines are still very good.
They haven't gone totally woke yet.
By the way, if you ask ChatGBT for Jesus jokes, it's full of it.
But if you ask for a Muhammad joke, they say they don't want to disrespect anyone's religion.
Right?
So ChatGBT has gone woke.
Thanks, Megzy, for that.
Okay.
Here's the concept.
I almost – which – well, boy, I want to say so many things at once.
It's really difficult to – everything is going to all come out in one shot almost.
I want to say five things at the same time, right?
I'm sorry.
Generally speaking, I try and slow you down just so you have enough time to choose your direction.
That's usually what I do when I disrupt you.
Sorry.
It would actually be easier to do what I said, which is what most people do,
is they'll tell you where they got it, the page and the verse and all that,
regardless if it's biblical or not.
I don't do that.
There's this thing called the Mandela Effect.
And everyone remembers – and I'm saying this, everyone air quotes –
that the lion will lay down with the lamb.
There's actually lion and lamb ministries where they have lions and lambs
and postcards and Christmas cards.
Right.
But it's not.
It's the wolf and the lamb now.
Right?
And planets were never mentioned in the versions.
Now they are.
So we live in this fluid kind of reality.
Am I a Mandela Effect?
In other words, if people start watching all these videos on the Mandela Effect,
do I subscribe to it?
No, just like I don't for the flat earth.
But is the earth flat?
Depends on what you're doing.
Well, see, that's the interesting thing.
You have an explanation in Greek-speak already of the Mandela Effect.
Whether you know it or not, you've already been given it.
Just so you know.
It depends on what you're focused on.
But there is a change in this reality that we're living in because –
Well, certainly.
But here's a simple explanation.
Well, maybe you don't want me to give it.
No, go ahead.
Give it.
I've given so many.
But which one are you referring to?
The technical one or the general aspect of this?
No, this is general.
General, relatable.
You can see how this works.
Very simple.
When you talked about getting the message from yourself in the future.
Well, assumption.
Very simple one.
I'm assuming that I'm not special.
So if I can do that, you can do that.
The little voice in your head is you remembering, recounting the event.
Right.
So what's happening is that displacement of time, being constantly in motion,
means that the past can be affected.
Right.
It could not be changed, but it's affected.
And it's also – you notice it's not malevolent.
The effects just seem to be fairly innocuous.
No, no.
I didn't describe any negativity to it.
I just simply said the past can be affected.
That's all I'm saying.
Yeah, it can be affected.
Oh, yeah, from that point of view.
But I recommend – the only reason I'm going to recommend what I'm saying
is because it's very well written.
If you could put up with it, the Carlos Castaneda books.
Okay.
Of Don Juan.
I don't know how many there are.
They started – maybe there's half a dozen of them or so.
But I was told to get into that in the early 80s, just like in the 80s
where I was going around and asking people, do they know about the flat earth?
Okay, so when I saw it coming back.
But anyway, the reason why I'm recommending the Castaneda books is because
they're well written and you can follow the story, even though it's very, very slow.
But, yeah, the point – I find myself coming around to those points of view.
In other words, there is a general point of view where he talks about being indifferent, right?
That's the only way – being objective, right?
So this is the aspect of it because if you're going to invest in belief,
some people get to the point where they're in eternal salvation.
You've heard them say that.
On something that you know nothing about or care nothing about or don't see it,
you're going to have problems, right?
Either that or you're a victim of some social engineering, right?
Yeah.
Like bacon and eggs and diamonds are forever kind of thing and fossil fuel.
All right, so again, I'm not going to be reading anything,
but I'm going to be referencing where people are interested to do their own research.
Good.
Okay, so the essence of the story is very simple.
And here's the thing.
Like with the JFK research, especially 9-11, 9-11 was a wake-up call, an alarm to wake up.
So people hit the snooze button, and the snooze alarm went off in 2020 with the pandemic,
and they're still not waking up.
So the next one is going to be kind of – you get the point?
The 9-11 was supposed to wake you up.
It didn't.
Snooze button, 2020, hit the snooze, right?
Snooze alarm, usually this is 15 minutes or so, so 19 years later, still asleep, right?
So this is – I'm not addressing those people.
But here's the thing.
What happened on 9-11 is still a secret.
That's why you have all these people still trying to discuss it and putting –
but it has been exposed for what it is on many, many levels.
If you look, the only person that I know that has a good handle on it is Dmitry Kaluzov, okay?
The only thing that he doesn't mention that he agrees, and he almost said that he forgot, is the smells, right?
Because it was ionization, and you only get that smell from ionization, okay?
Now here's the point with the scripture.
Everything you know about the Bible that you've gotten from religion, movies,
or even reading the versions is not so, pretty much.
I haven't still – I've tried to meditate on that comment that I've mentioned.
Is there anything in Christianity that is accurate?
Nothing, zero, right?
So it's kind of like when you go on a construction site, sometimes you have people that literally can't read.
There was someone I remember.
He was much older than I was.
I was in my 20s.
Every week he'd come to me with the paycheck, and he'd ask me to read it, what was the amount on it.
I thought it was cute.
Then after a while, I figured out he didn't know how to read, and he was like in his late 40s.
So there are people like that don't know how to read or can't read.
There's also people on a construction site, when you ask them how wide is that board,
and they'll say it's 49 inches and three lines.
Three lines?
Is that three-sixteenths or three-quarters or what?
They didn't know how to read a tape measure, which is – I can understand that to a certain point.
But the ones that didn't want to learn were going to have problems,
but the ones that admitted that they didn't know and wanted to learn, I think were able to proceed in advance, let's say.
So this is very similar to that.
But here's the thing.
Anything and everything that's contained information-wise, and knowledge and information are not the same thing, by the way,
which is another thing.
If you have knowledge of what's trying to be communicated, people that only have, for example, information on the Bible,
if they go to court, they tell them to swear on it, and they think the version of King James is a holy relic.
People that are knowledgeable of the Bible, if they go to court and they say –
well, actually, you don't have to swear, you affirm, but put your hand on the Bible.
No, no, I don't have to put my hand on the Bible.
I have it here on this smartphone.
I have it all downloaded.
Can I put my hand on that?
No.
Or I have it here on a CD.
I have the whole Bible downloaded on a CD or DVD.
Can I put my hand on that?
No.
Why?
Because not – you see, so people that know the scriptures know it as a form of communication.
It's not this pagan thing, the amulet.
I remember when, before I did work here, the office door wouldn't stay open,
so I just put a stack of Bibles as a doorstop to keep it from opening, because at the time I was collecting them, right?
You get it?
All right, so what we're going to be giving and speaking on in this long-winded prefix is knowledge of the scripture.
The information is up to you.
So everything is secret.
So in short, in short, let's just jump to the meaty part about there's no crucifixion.
In short, I've always mentioned that when you have something that's chronological, right,
and it's a saga, meaning it starts off with certain situations,
and then someone appears or a situation appears where it climaxes, you know, there's a peak to the story, right?
And then it continues after that, whether it ends well or ends poorly.
That is a cumulative book.
In other words, if you pick it up in the end and you don't know anything that came before that,
it's not going to make any sense.
Well, you might—you're trying to make sense of what you're reading, but you don't know what came before it.
So it's cumulative, you see?
Turn to the last chapter of just a pedestrian sort of novel,
and they tell you the ship sank and the little girl cried on the last page,
and you go, okay, well, I don't know what happened.
But reference manuals, like here, I've got some 1920s Britannicas here,
and I could take the last one, which is the letter Z.
No problem.
I could open that and just study it just fine.
It's just an—you see?
The biblical text is not encyclopedic.
It's actually—it's a chronology.
So one of the things that you know is in the conspiratorial world, you're called a nutcase if you bring up any—
if you ask for any information, right?
Because the society—part of what we're doing is called rated—what's rated Y,
and the motto of it is the unculting of humanity.
So one of the aspects of being—how do you know you're in a cult is you cannot question the leadership.
That's a very basic one, right?
And also, you know, in order to keep people controlled in a cult, you give them poor food quality because the poor food, right?
They lose their stamina, mental stamina.
So in a conspiratorial world, when you ask for more information or question what the mainstream or the politicians say,
you're called a nutcase, a wingnut, conspiracy theorist, denigrated, whatever.
So if you approach a Christian about the Old Testament, what do they say?
Oh, that's been a done away with.
Are you Jewish?
Right?
Same exact cult phenomenon.
So going on.
All right.
So if you just get into the meat of the story, it has to happen from the beginning all the way through.
So now you've eliminated everything before.
Of course, you're going to be manipulated.
And the more manipulation there is, I'll give you an example.
I think when Trump was still in, he went and visited and paid homage and venerated the Shanksville Memorial,
and they even put a bunch of airplane parts, even though when the plane supposedly went down,
there were no airplane parts found whatsoever.
But the Shanksville Memorial now in Pennsylvania has airplane parts in it.
And he even went there and said, oh, these are all right.
The same thing you see now with all the Christian religions, all of them together, they venerate all this other stuff.
So they make stuff where it never was that way.
It never was that way to begin with.
Yeah.
Now the simple beginner Greek speak is like this.
By the time you get to the New Testament, the Old Testament progresses, let's say, from grammar school to high school.
When you get to the New Testament, that would be graduate degree stuff.
Like the Book of Matthew would be your entire undergraduate, and the rest of it is graduate-level stuff.
So you have people that profess themselves to be quote-unquote Christian and believe in whatever that have not changed
or are pretty much the same mindset as they were when they were five, six, seven, eight, or nine,
when they were first introduced to these concepts.
Their concepts now, they think they're more evolved because they just keep reading that part that they're told to read and not the rest.
But actually they're very immature.
The example that I give is let's say you're graduate-level physics, and you go to lecture a bunch of five-year-olds for an hour.
There's a room full of them, let's say.
After an hour, you say, any questions?
And they all raise their hands.
All right.
What's the question?
Do you have any candy?
All right.
Now, if you isolated – no questions about what you were talking about at all.
Now, if you isolated those five-year-olds amongst that subject, right,
and 30, 40 years later or 20 years later you went and lectured them again and asked them any questions,
it won't be like, do you have any candy?
It will be like, Mark, can I use the bathroom or something like that, right?
Nothing.
So that's the difference, but it's still the same context.
They know nothing about what's going on.
With that said, from the engineering point of view, from the 10-story building to the 100-story building,
how much has to be supported, you go back to what they are referring to,
and they tell you to read that New Testament thing, right?
Okay.
That's graduate-level.
When you take, let's say, graduate-level mathematics in university is your first day in class,
okay, what's one plus one?
Very good.
Three times three, you know your times tables, right?
No, it's cumulative.
So at this point, when you have the individual that's mentioned in there,
there is no detail on the specifics because, first of all,
all the information in there is addressed to a certain group of people,
and they're not Christians, by the way, right?
And you know what?
They weren't even Jewish, as we know Judaism today, okay?
They were just pursuing a certain way of life.
They were part of a community.
Now, I want to go back to basic Greek-speak.
This is real, real basic stuff, and I'll give it this way,
and then I'll give some references and just reiterate.
So the Christ, even if you just watch the movies and you'll see the sleight of hand,
he is arrested by the Judean religious authorities.
They actually indicted him.
The Pharisees and some Sadducees got together and had an indictment against him,
a grand jury type situation in private where they were saying such and such and such,
we have to get him.
And there was some retort, you know, why don't we just lick a demon so allegedly?
Why don't we let him go?
Look how many other messiahs tried to do this, and they ran to the hills never to come back.
But the head priest Caiaphas says, no, we have to arrest him.
We have to get him to save the nation.
Okay, so it's a double entendre.
You see this all the time where something is said and it means multiple things.
Okay, so now here's the thing.
Before I continue, there's so many biblical naysayers.
You know, oh, it's not true.
It was forged.
It was copied and all this stuff.
But the only time I look at what they say, you know, a lot of people say the Bible is written there.
It was copied off of that.
No, it wasn't really copied.
I haven't seen no evidence of that.
And the evidence that they give is very weak and very narrow.
And the reason I don't give any biblical commentary, even the ones that are academic, especially academic, any credence,
and I have to rely on doing my own work, is because no one comes out with what we're going to be saying today,
which is so obvious and in your face once you hear it, right?
Now, once you hear this, if you don't see it, that's fine.
But if you see it after you hear me explain it or anyone that explains something similar, it does two things.
One, well, now you have a revelation on something that you thought you knew that was in front of you the whole time,
but you didn't know it, right?
And it also realizes you how censored you are.
You're lifting off a piece of censorship.
And the censorship is invisible.
It's not tangible even physically.
It's just like rearranging yourself again.
We're building a hundred-story building that looks like a ten-story building.
What does it take?
I'm not an engineer.
But sure, you just have to approach it logically, right?
It looks the same.
It's ten times the material.
But you have to realize how much weight each floor holds, and that makes it very, very different.
So you can loosely apply that to what we're speaking on, on the biblical,
because if you're going to read the New Testament, you have to be standing on what came before.
And that was actually one of the comments there.
So let's go back to he was arrested by the religious authorities,
which they do have their own military police-type order-keeping force,
just like the Vatican has the Swiss Guard, right?
Well, actually, that's for the building.
They have the Jesuits, right?
Right, right.
So, yeah, and whatever.
By the way, if you're an ordained Catholic priest, do it anymore.
They say, you go up to whatever they call the higher-ups, and they say,
okay, well, here, go see this person.
And they give you a name and a phone number and an address.
And the person goes and shows up, and it's the CIA office in their nearest city.
It's like you're an honorary CIA agent.
Isn't that some crazy stuff?
This is from someone that it's happened to, and their sister gave me the lowdown on that.
You go to the building where they tell you to go, and you go to the floor,
and it's the CIA office.
Can you imagine?
But anyway, the protection that they have, and the police and the army or whatever,
the force, paramilitary, was set out to go arrest the Christ.
Now, I'm going to throw something in there.
One of his abilities, when I speak about abilities, by the way,
I think you and I, Chuck, brought something up.
When you hear of someone with special abilities, if one person can do it, everyone can do it.
It's just that person happens to be able to see how to do it.
It's just like Tiger Woods really good at golf.
You know what?
Everybody, anybody can play golf, and everybody, as a matter of fact,
even if you're in a wheelchair, they'll make the ADA, whatever,
compliance will make sure that you get something going.
But you're not going to play it as well.
One of the things that was very well known that you won't find in the New Testament,
nothing that I'm saying is emphasized in the New Testament, right?
Just like when you go to graduate-level mathematics,
do they emphasize your times tables and your addition and subtraction tables?
Do they emphasize that? No.
No, the assumption is you've already covered it.
And you're expert in it, and you're expert.
Yeah, the assumption of the New Testament is you are expert,
not just read it, you are expert in comprehension of everything that came before it.
As it's said, by the way, later on,
not into it, paraphrasing-wise.
All right, so where were we?
So the Christ, one of his abilities was he had the ability of invisibility,
which is not like the invisible man where you see him only when he's wrapped up with bandages,
not like that.
But he would make himself disappear from your perception.
So a crowd of people want to molest him or throw him off or whatever.
Amongst the crowd, he escapes by just turning around and walking right through them, right?
And it's not only with a crowd.
If he came to your door, knocked on the door and says,
Would you make me some coffee? I need some help or whatever.
Sure.
And he sat down with you for three hours and spoke.
And if I asked you the next day, what did he look like?
You wouldn't be able to describe him.
How strange is that?
Now, that was borrowed in Men in Black.
Remember when he says, When you put on this uniform, people you meet, you will just be a whatever, right?
You become a vague memory, the stuff of rumors, et cetera.
Yeah, you just become a vague memory.
Okay, no need to give personal examples.
No problem.
Do you understand what it is?
Because I've had certain things where I've practiced that, and it works.
Maybe on the emo discussion.
Yeah, spoiler, just so you know, though, everybody who is listening to this right now,
anyone who is listening and comprehends what's being said, you are capable of this.
Of course.
Go ahead.
But not like, in other words, you could hit a golf ball with a club,
but you may not have the ranking and the score, the number sheet as Tiger Woods.
No, no, no, I'm not saying that you can do it with…
Yeah, and so many holes.
Remember, in golf, it's the fewer, the lower the number, the better.
Look, I can build a table right now, okay?
I can build one practically, no problem.
But, you know, the blind guy swinging a hammer and cutting stuff
might not quite do as well as somebody who's done it a hundred times, et cetera,
and someone who has practiced at it.
Just saying.
I bet I could do it.
This is not to denigrate.
I'm just saying that all these things have found,
all the things that you hear about Christ doing have a very strong foundation
and basis in all of our natural systems.
But if you don't understand how natural things really work,
you can easily think that it's something else.
Let's just say, I'm not going to say miracle, because miracles do happen,
but they're not as we're told.
It's just compression of time.
So the Christ is arrested,
and the priests knew that the people that they're going to send,
no matter how well they described him,
because even they could not see him, right?
They would have to acknowledge him by how he spoke,
and he knew this was coming.
So when they give him a description, you know,
like when the police are looking for someone, if they got you in the database,
they'll take the photo you have for the driver's license
and blow it up to an eight-and-a-half by 11, right?
So even if they did something like that,
they know that they still would not be able to be recognized.
So they needed a very direct, first-hand, tactile identification.
In other words, someone that knew him really well,
that knew that his followers were not subject to this invisibility.
So they got Judas.
Let's just say those stories.
It has nothing to do with what you believe in or not.
To kiss him.
The New Testament doesn't tell you that the only way the Christ could be identified
is with a kiss because he had the power of invisibility.
It doesn't say that, does it?
No.
At all in the New Testament.
But we know that he has the power of being vague.
What I mean by invisible is, you know,
if you're in a room with ten people, they're only going to count nine.
And then, like, isn't there someone else here?
Oh, yeah, wait a second.
Yeah, there's a tenth guy here.
You see, like that.
So in other words, just nonchalant.
You could be your vague memory or vague perception.
So how come people don't ask why he had to be kissed directly, right?
Because, well, we've given examples prior to that, you see.
Okay.
He's arrested by the Judean authorities, sort of.
You could read the parts.
It's harmonized in the books of Matthew, Mark, Luke, and John.
Some of the books don't harmonize.
Some do.
I mean, usually in pairs.
Matthew, Mark, Luke, and John.
All these things were prophesied specifically in the book of Isaiah
and in the Psalms, by the way.
So this is the compounding and accumulation of all the works that you have to have
in order to see what I'm saying, how obvious it is.
Once you hear it, he's brought in a sort of,
I'm not going to get into how the trial allegedly transpired.
Then after he's considered guilty as accused,
which actually the accusations kind of changed, but they stayed pretty much guilty.
Then he was brought through the judicial system.
You have procedure, right?
When you go to certain things, they call it, like in jail, they call it intake.
You've got to go to intake and then holding.
The police arrest you.
They identify who you are.
Then they bring you up for charges.
Then those charges are billed out.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, so you have all these procedures, and they run you through.
You see what it is.
Then he's brought to the Judean political or ministerial authority,
which is Herod Jr., let's say.
He kind of heard about him.
There's this interchange, and he gives him a robe, right,
which is very high value, let's say.
Then he's carded off.
This is over days now of interaction in this setting,
because the setting is very important.
Whenever you read something, what is the setting?
Like what time of day is it?
The geography.
How many people are there?
Is he alone?
You see?
Try to pick up on all of that.
As if you're making a film.
They call it storyboarding.
You put in the details what the scene is going to look like, right?
Well, you have to do that.
That's why a lot of people say,
go ahead and just read the red letters in the Bible.
I mean, sometimes I'll put a video on, and someone will bring up the word.
My wife and I are listening, and we're laughing our ass off.
I said, just the only part that's important is read the red letter part.
I said, yeah, but you don't know the setting and what that's being said in.
Right, because that's what the JES.
It's out of context.
Yeah, the JESUS character said this.
Okay, that's great.
But what's the context of it, right?
See, everyone has always got him as love, love, love.
But the only time he said anything about love and compassion is when he was with his private group
in a private setting in a closed house.
Everyone else, he was pretty much like, just ignore them.
Or, you know, you're better off Sodom and Gomorrah.
You would have been better off if you were in Sodom and Gomorrah.
What's going to happen to you?
He was the most hateful character in the entire biblical narration, hands down, by far,
in terms of the public and in terms of the collective.
Completely abhorred.
Just hate.
Hate is a mild term.
And anyone who reads this, I've had people message me,
reads what's called the New Testament in context as I'm saying it,
says, God, I can't believe I've been reading this for like 25 years,
and the first time I see it, yeah, he's extremely hateful.
And, you know, all right.
So all that love stuff is only to the people that were closest to him in private, right?
So I'm not saying that you need to do it.
I'm just giving the information so you have a certain amount of information.
I'm giving the knowledge of it.
You find whatever you think is information that applies to you.
Well, this is a report, okay?
This is what happened.
You're not judging it or trying to spin it.
This is just what is, okay?
That's what's there.
The report on this is I'm trying to be linear
but showing you how fat the ground floor has to be
because you have to support 99 stories, not just nine.
You notice how I'm not just recapping like I usually give in the standard
start here, first Greek-speak stuff,
because the 100-story building, the first floor is really, really robust
because it has to hold all this other stuff.
So when you find out who the character of this venerated individual in the Bible is,
you'll see right away 180 opposing view
to what the religions that supposedly have captured this character,
not even a name, by the way, are portraying.
And when I say that, by the way, J-E-S-U-S is a metric, okay?
It is a metric that is used.
You want to call them Illuminati, Freemasons, the elite.
They rename things deliberately and put words out there to see how people will use it,
and that is an easy gauge for them.
When I say gauge literally, I mean it literally,
just like if you're, let's say, you're using what they call a car,
you have a gasoline gauge and you rely on it, right?
So if the needle goes down to empty and you're on a long trip, do you heed to it?
Of course.
Oh, let's just ignore that, you know?
No.
Okay, so literally it is a gauge.
So the J-E, there are many words that are metric words,
and the main ones are ownership words like my, this is my thing or whatever.
I've gone into that in the previous Sonic.
So this is very important.
It's not to condemn anyone, but when you see people using the J-E-S-U-S word,
that's been put out there to see how many people know,
and the more people that use it, that means the more people don't know what's going on, right?
It's very simple.
There are many metric words like that.
If someone is really savvy and is a wordsmith,
I would one day appreciate some help to put together a collection of metric words,
words that are used as metrics.
I have not used, you notice on this Rated Y, a lot of the previous Greek-speak terms,
you know, like dummy load and space heaters.
On the old ONG, I had a collection.
I think every time we did an episode, I came up with another Greek-speak type term,
you know, or every other one, you know.
Someone once put a collection together, about 26 of them or 24 of them that are unique.
I haven't been using those, and I haven't really been coming up with too many more.
Well, anyway, I just wanted to throw that in there.
No problem.
But the J-E-S-U-S is a metric term there, and what I'm saying is use it if you need to,
but it's not necessary because it's Joshua, or Joshua if you have to use the J, it's totally fine.
And there is a book of Joshua.
It's totally fine.
You know, that's a very simple way to break the metric.
So that's the report so far, and now we're going to jump.
Well, yeah, because you were still on the story here, okay?
Yeah.
You talked about, you know, where they had taken them, and they're in the process now.
The next part is very well known.
Do you want to get into that?
Yeah, yeah.
Well, the next part, well, and the story so far, yeah, but we're not done so far.
He's brought to Pontius Pilate, right?
Why?
Because he is the Prefect Governor of Judea.
Now, the story behind anyone that was assigned.
Now, the Romans just, well, I can't imagine any society that wouldn't be.
The Romans were excellent bookkeepers.
They liked education.
They had a certain law that was actually quite free and open and very, very civil.
As a matter of fact, a lot of patriots complain about Roman civil law.
So before they send someone to, just like today, to rule over a group of people, be a Prefect Governor,
in other words, Judea was as far east as they could go because they couldn't go further over the Jordan
because the Parthian Empire was there, and it didn't last very well.
In other words, any time the Romans tried to make progress to the east, they got their butts whipped,
I mean, really, really bad.
So the Romans were powerful as they were, but they couldn't do anything about moving eastward,
and that's another story.
But anyone could study the Seleucids and the Parthians, how they were really badass,
and at any point in history, other than natural calamities preventing,
the Parthians could have taken over everything the Romans had.
No big deal, no problem.
So there was a truce at that point.
Yeah, but the basic point is that this territory is controlled by a representative of the one who conquered it,
which would be the Roman Empire at the time.
This is Pontius Pilate.
Pontius Pilate being that represented that he was at the most eastward part, furthest away,
in terms of east-west, and also it represented that he was in a very rich cultural part,
central-type area, and before he was sent there,
he had to know all of the laws and rituals and customs just like today.
Which, by the way, you can read the Roman history on this if you want to,
which is separate, and they were good bookkeepers when it came to this kind of stuff,
and did have a decent collection of histories,
where you can see that literally there was a purpose behind the control,
and it was seen as the frontier of that particular expansion in that direction.
Or the termination. They couldn't go beyond it.
This is not very popular because it shows like a stain on Roman history.
So he was also a friend of Tiberius Claudius Caesar, who was a historian,
and they wrote letters back and forth quite often, as terms of the history that we have.
So he's brought to Pontius Pilate, and there's several things that happen there.
There's an interaction. I won't get into that.
You could read that, the interaction between Yahshua, the Christ, and him,
and it's very civil.
There's an interjection of comments from his wife.
We've heard of politicians and notary people of power,
where their wives were involved in influencing them.
For example, Woodrow Wilson's wife pretty much ran the country for the last year he was in office.
He was too sick to come out into public, so she would say,
just give me the paperwork. No one ever saw him.
She'd go in and she would give the paperwork back.
Any type of imperial structure you can find, kings and queens and stuff like that,
where the king's office is what's important, but the queen has a great deal of influence,
despite the fact that they're not technically part of the influence according to the government,
but they influence the king.
For instance, you had the queen mother there that was in office for a very long time,
and everybody talks about the queen,
but really what it was is that she had control of the king's office, and so on.
So, yeah, yeah, go ahead.
All right, so in this case, this is mentioned in the story that she said,
leave this man be, I've had dreams about this, right?
Now, you have to realize that dream interpretation in pagan culture,
in any culture, is very, very important, right?
They take it as a fact that if a dream is interpreted, the results of that interpretation are fact.
So she discouraged him, and he also, from his own reasoning,
if you study Roman law, anyone could plead to go to Caesar, right?
So if there was a plea to see Caesar, he would have to be held in a carcer,
which is a citadel, or it's where you get the word incarceration from,
and he could be shipped off to Rome, or they had places, you didn't have to go to Rome,
but other places in the empire that were considered, just like you have a district court, right?
They're not all in Washington, D.C., anyway, it gets technical.
So he didn't want any of that mess.
Also, there's evidence, historic evidence, writings, and whether it's true or not,
that he had pretty much gotten familiar with him in the past.
Pontius Pilate got familiar with Yahshua,
and his comments, as preserved today, are that he didn't see him to be speaking out against Rome or anything like that.
He kind of liked him.
He didn't know if he struck him to be like a philosopher or someone, right?
So he had previous interaction.
Now, the interesting part here, this is where the switch happens,
but there is no switch, because if you read in the book of, I think it's Mark and Luke,
it gives the interaction, those two books give the interaction in different ways.
I don't see it as being, I don't know how they switched, it's just complete ignorance of what's in the text.
Pontius Pilate states to the Judean authorities that, you know,
I'll discipline him, scorch him, whatever the words they use in the versions,
and I'm going to return him back to you to use your law.
And in one of the books, there's a retort where he says, how can we do it under Caesar?
You know, the Judean authorities says, well, we're under Roman Empire, how could we use our law?
And he says, I'm making this exception.
So he's handed over to the Judeans indirectly to the point where you have Judean jurisprudence being applied,
not Roman jurisprudence.
So in this case, this is where it gets complicated for people, right?
This is where it gets complicated, because through the rest of the quote-unquote sentencing and execution,
there are Romans involved.
Like, for example, there's a Roman that puts a spear through his side and all that, right?
Right.
Okay, so why?
Well, why were the Romans involved?
We just went through kind of a slow iteration that Rome was ruling over Israel, right?
Now, what does that mean?
They were the occupying force and the occupying authority.
And let's give this as a very basic analogy.
Let's say you're in the United States of America and you're listening, right, or whatever country you're in.
And your country was invaded 100 years prior, let's say the U.S. by, I don't know,
do you want to call it the Germans or the Chinese or whatever?
Let's just use the Chinese for now.
So the highest authority in the land is the CCP, okay?
They're sitting in Washington, D.C.
They have their own buildings, and each state has their own CCP governor,
and your local officials also are CCP, alongside your existing president or maybe not,
or your existing whatever, Congress.
It's totally possible, right?
Okay.
Okay, so let's say you have something, a public event.
It's the Super Bowl or the Fourth of July.
When these events are held, like in the Super Bowl, you'll have police helicopters, military snipers.
You know, they're prepared for trouble, right, and security that the government puts up, right?
Sure.
But in this case, you could still have the Super Bowl by permission,
but it's going to be all CCP, army, police, whatever.
Let's say you want to do the Fourth of July.
You still do your fireworks show, but guess who lights the fireworks?
Someone from the CCP.
Right, okay.
Right?
So let's go to a prison where they still have capital punishment.
When they're going to put the guy in the chair or the lethal injection or hanging or firing squad,
guess who's running that part of the prison and who's going to pull the switch?
CCP.
You see?
Anything that's going to put authority or, like, for example, all these things that I mentioned are military or paramilitary.
The helicopters offering security at the Super Bowl are military.
So if you're already occupied by the CCP, everything in your military and high-level paramilitary is going to be CCP,
even though your own people are there.
Very simple.
So we switched over to Judean jurisprudence, and we know that it was the Law of Moses.
And to say it's the Law of Moses and its capital punishment, it's lapidation, which is the technical term for stoning.
And then we can get into the rest in great detail or stop right here.
What do you think?
I think that should do it, really.
I just have a quick question, though, because, look, what you're saying is, just to complete the full ring on this analogy,
the CCP, you go to them, you say, okay, you're the occupying force, tell us what to do.
This guy has disrupted stuff, basically.
That was the general complaint that Pilate heard, from what I understand.
And he said, look, I can deal with him about disruption, but the rest of this has nothing to do with me.
It could. It could.
But you decide to use the prevailing culture and the prevailing laws before you occupy.
That's done often also.
Why don't you deal with him?
Because, again, like you said, first of all, it's a big pain in the neck.
And to put him into that system, maybe he thought it wasn't a very good case against what was laid out as the Roman law.
So that's that, right?
And this could be the CCP says, well, look, he's not saying anything against the state.
He disrupted the Super Bowl, right?
Going back to the other part of the analogy.
But, you know, really, a little disruption, all right, we'll give him tickets for that.
We'll punish him a little.
But, you know, maybe you guys should deal with him your way about this, since this is your case.
And that's exactly what happened.
And it doesn't have to be a long-winded, long-running conversation or detail or footnote,
because this is an account from those that were there or nearby, let's say.
Let's continue real quick.
So what happens?
What happens with this is if we look at the book of Deuteronomy, a disobedient son is you're nailed to a tree.
And also consider in the book of Joshua anything that's considered accursed.
Being nailed to a tree is the worst way.
It's a method of being stoned, because typically stoning was you would be beaten up so you don't run during the arrest, right?
Well, actually, when you're arrested, you're kicked in.
You're pretty much beaten up the whole time.
So the Christ being beaten as he was was not unusual.
As a matter of fact, growing up in the 70s and 80s, it was very typical.
If you were of color and arrested in New York, you were beaten up.
It was almost like a guarantee.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
Yep.
So in this case, the beating and all of that punishment I didn't see as being unusual.
Anyone that understands jurisprudence or police, it's very common.
The interesting part, though, is that what people miss out on this is when it's a stoning,
there's no talk about it other than in some cartoonish way.
Or maybe when there was more stuff going on in the Middle East, let's say between 2003 and 2010,
the kind of alternative media threw some things in there.
You know, oh, they're stoning people in Afghanistan or Iraq or something like that.
But people are not aware of it at all.
Let's say you go somewhere in the future, and let's say society continues like it is,
which it's not, but let's just say it does.
And you bring up an electric chair, let's say, a thousand years from now.
People will just think it's just a piece of furniture.
Like, oh, I never heard of that furniture, right?
It's an electric chair.
Get it?
If we have an electric blanket, what's an electric chair?
They're not really familiar with its purpose or its methodology or how it was done.
Hey, mom, I heard about an electric chair.
Can we get one?
You know, kind of like that.
It has no bearing and no significance.
Or even now today, or actually, again, growing up in the 70s,
it was very common to say, what happened to this guy?
Oh, they gave him the chair.
Right?
Remember that?
Yeah.
You don't hear that anymore.
No, you don't.
But to be given a chair, now if somebody looks at that a thousand years from now,
well, okay, somebody gave him a gift.
You don't know what, yeah.
Right.
Very far removed.
So here's the thing.
This was a public spectacle.
Now, there's a lot of things.
We're just going from what's in the text.
There's a lot of twists and turns and dual meanings in this.
When you are stoned in a public fashion, you have to be with a lot of people.
The higher up you are, just like if you're doing a rock concert,
you don't do it at ground level.
You need what's called a stage, staging.
So he and two others, I'm bypassing a lot of things here in between,
because there's no reason to belabor the point.
Well, and it gives a good basic outline anyway that's relatable.
Anybody can follow this, even given what they've been given in information,
like you said, in films, stories, books, all together.
Yes, because we're not giving information.
If you want all the information, you go and read it however you want.
Here's the interesting thing.
You can go to someone who really believes in the crucifixion and the J-E-S-U-S,
and they could read.
Actually, I think I mentioned someone on his YouTube channel.
He said they've read the Bible 50 times and have the notes to prove it,
and they don't know what I'm talking about.
This would be new to them also, and they've read it 50 times.
So if you go to a quote-unquote Christian,
he could read the Bible every day of his life for the rest of his life,
however long it is, long or short, and he won't see what I'm saying.
It's just amazing.
They won't be able to put it together.
But we know, let's just say from a knowledge point of view,
it's an almond tree, okay?
So start looking up references on that almond tree, almond branch, not olive, right?
And we know that he was front and center,
and also the people were passing by from the third to the ninth hour
or the sixth to the ninth hour was six hours,
so third to the ninth hour doing what?
Passing by doing what?
Waving, playing dice, what?
Right?
And he's high up on a tree, and he's front and center, one tree,
and one man on his left, one man on his right.
And if you read in the Psalms, all the flesh was torn off of his body
because if you know that part of the world,
the rocks are like decomposed granite and various types of shale, very sharp.
Yep.
You ever toss a playing card across the room, how it floats?
And if that were to hit you really hard, right?
Imagine that being made of stone, like pieces of broken tile almost.
So he was front and center, and he passed first,
and the man on his left got hit only on the right side,
and the man on his right on the same tree only got hit on his left side.
So their legs were severed to die because you don't die when you're nailed.
And the nailing part, he carried a stake.
Many people, again, don't have the comprehension,
and they think it was a stake like you put a fence post in the ground.
The body is very frail.
You can literally pull people apart with not a lot of force, right,
once the ligaments are torn and the skin breaks.
So in order to be in such a position where you don't move,
what would happen was you would be nailed to something
that looked like a railroad tie on the ground,
and then a rope is put around that railroad tie
and pulled up, thrown over a branch like a lynching,
and the individual is pulled up to the height
that the crowd would have access to on their volley of rocks.
And once it gets to a certain height that they think is the crowd,
you know, it's high enough for the crowd,
they tie the rope off and they put a nail through your feet
to keep you in position, right?
And that's basically what you see.
Now, the stake that he carried was, they do that out of shame
because it was a shaming also.
It's a public execution.
And the same thing is done in modern times.
I remember, again, in the 1970s when people were being executed
in a gas chamber or electric chair,
they made sure that it was in the news prominently
for at least two or three days or even a week before the event.
Do you remember that, Chuck?
Yeah, when they reinstated the death penalty in, what, 78?
It was Gary Gilmore.
That was the big one.
It was in the news every day.
Oh, they're going to execute him in three days.
Oh, they're going to execute him in two days.
It was constantly.
Right, and what they showed you was the crowd outside,
you know, people that were anxiously awaiting his death
versus people that were protesting, all that.
Right, but what they do in public executions,
it's very, very, very common that it's announced days before.
There's the shaming aspect that's part of human culture to do that.
It sort of justifies the ends.
It's a means to the end, you know, so shame you to the point
where you're completely, when you lose all integrity,
there's no integrity left, right?
Well, the other thing that is always assured with any sort of execution
is that there are official witnesses that are selected
and placed in a position so that they can view this directly
to be able to relate to the rest of the world that this happened,
this person died.
Well, that's the purpose of a public execution.
It'd be a deterrent.
Right.
You know, whenever there's a crime problem and it's the same crime,
I just say you need a public execution, not meaning a public execution,
but an execution without the follow-up and the shaming has no effect on society.
It actually does on a higher level, like I said earlier on other sonics
that I've been saying for three decades now.
By the way, I've been speaking like this since the early 2000s.
2010 is one decade, 2010s to the 20s is two decades,
so 2020 and beyond is three decades, right?
So this is three decades of Greek speak now.
It's kind of crazy.
But the shaming aspect is when there's a certain crime repeatedly,
what you need is a public execution.
That doesn't mean kill someone for stealing.
If there's a lot of bike theft, you just find a bike thief and make a mockery of him
to the point where the mockery and the shaming is the deterrent, right?
But from a lawful standpoint, the reason why you don't have prison in a lawful,
you have jails, jails to protect people.
You don't have prisons in a lawful society because the payments are meted out.
In other words, if you steal, you have to give back double what you stole
or is it three times?
I think it's double.
And if you're totally broke, well, that's okay.
You work as a servant.
You work it off, right?
There is no jail.
If you murder deliberately, you're put to death.
If it was an accident, what they call second-degree or third-degree murder,
you can no longer live in that town.
There's a city of refuge, on and on and on and on.
There is no prison in a lawful society.
When you have prisons, the earth spirit, let's just say, the aspect of the earth,
is saying, why are you keeping this?
Why are you putting them in prison?
It doesn't help.
You have to have them mitigate the crime or put them to death, you see?
So the very fact that there are prisons and people being held for life
or all this stuff is going to bring problems on the earth,
meaning you're going to have poisonous crops, droughts, earthquakes,
all this other stuff.
The earth will react, right?
I've discussed this loosely in the past,
because the earth and the sun are addressed directly as sentient beings.
Our well-being is running alongside how the earth and the sun
and all that perceives what we do from a lawful perspective.
So these little points, we could keep going, by the way.
Just the robe that was given to the Christ,
they cast lots for it before the event happened, right?
Why couldn't they just take it and leave?
Well, you know, they wanted to make it fair, cast lots,
but why was that point made?
Because when you are hanging from a tree, it's an accursed thing, right?
I'm giving hints here.
You could look up these verses in the Bible.
And anything that's an accursed thing is to be burned in several places.
The Book of Joshua is one.
I think there might be another one in the Book of Numbers.
So at the end of this execution,
the three men that were nailed to the almond tree,
that tree would be set on fire,
and they would be effectively cremated with all of their belongings as well.
You see?
That's why you have in the story Joseph of Arimathea,
the wealthy man who had premade himself a grave out of stone,
ran over the palisade from the Mount of Olives
over to Pontius Pilate, who was on Fort Anatolia,
which they call the Dome of the Rock now,
to ask permission for the body.
He had to do it very fast, right?
And the body was taken down.
So when someone—here's more fraud and on and on and on.
When they say this is the piece of wood from the cross,
first of all, there's no cross, right?
A crucifix.
And second of all, everything was burned, right?
There's something called the menorah or the seven-branch lampstand,
which was ordered to be made during the tabernacle days,
and it also was something that proceeded along all the way until the temple days,
was to be made out of a piece of gold and have the likeness of an almond tree.
And what does the menorah or the lampstand do?
You have fire, right?
Right.
And it had seven arms, right?
So you have three men, two arms each in the air,
plus the center one, the nerikadim, the center one.
Okay?
So actually when you look at a menorah—by the way,
one that is biblical as it's directed to be built,
prescribed in the Book of Exodus, for example,
or throughout how to make this,
one that doesn't exist.
You won't find a true aspect of that.
All you have to do is find out the directions of how to build the lampstand
and what it should look like with an eight-year-old that could sketch
and have him sketch out as you're reading it,
and it will be pretty accurate because it's very simple,
and you'll see that there isn't one in existence today that looks like that
or functions like that.
So, quote, unquote, all of the Jewish people,
when they put their things up and they light them the way they do,
it kind of loosely resembles, but I'll tell you for sure,
there is no menorah, quote, unquote,
as it is prescribed to be built in the Bible in existence on the Internet.
The same goes for the Ark of the Covenant, by the way.
I know what I'm saying sounds ridiculous, doesn't it?
But it's true.
All you have to do is go to, like, some fourth graders
that are good at sketching and drawing,
and while you're reading the text on prescribing how to make these things,
have them draw it out, or a professional artist.
They'll probably charge you much,
but you don't need more than a 10-year-old to draw it out,
and you'll see that it won't look anything like what's on the Internet,
all these relics and objects, right?
It's kind of bizarre, isn't it?
Well, it is, and there's also this other relic that supposedly,
you know, it's a cross between two things.
The sacred spear aspect, right,
which some people say is the spear, literally the spearhead of destiny,
which was, you know, the spear that actually poked him.
And then other people say it's made actually from the nail.
Now, the nail could have survived.
Now we're going to get into what, I'm not saying you,
but what shoe size Santa Claus has, or who's wrong and who's right.
Yeah, well, that was what I was leading to, but yeah.
But the spear of destiny, the one that's ridiculous is the Holy Grail,
the cup that he drank from.
Because, first of all, it wasn't the Last Supper.
I think I mentioned him in the last one.
I'm not going to mention his name again.
Actually, this time I won't.
But he did a video on how the Last Supper painting by da Vinci, I think it was,
is really the Zodiac.
And he just insisted on telling me about this for about an hour and a half,
and I stopped and said, you know, there is no Last Supper in the Bible.
It was the Passover.
And as a matter of fact, one of the ordinances in the Passover,
you eat lamb and flatbread, matzah, right, no yeast, and bitter herbs.
Guess what?
You're standing up.
You're supposed to do it standing up.
So the Last Supper, it shows a bunch of guys sitting down.
Sitting down, yeah.
So that is really the Last Supper, but it's 0% biblical,
negative 1, negative 100% biblical, right?
The interesting part in that is when the Christ said during the Passover,
the Passover, this is my body and this is, right, it was very confusing.
Take this as my body and this as my blood.
Why?
Because if he's known as, quote, unquote, the Lamb of God,
in the ordinance of the Passover, part of the ordinance is what?
None is to remain till morning, meaning the end of the day.
And if anything is remaining, you're supposed to burn it, throw it in the fire.
So he's telling them, he's giving them these metaphors that he is sort of like a Lamb of God, right?
Indirectly, he doesn't say that.
But he's considered that, and they're saying if you're going to die,
you're going to be burned up in their minds because they know the ordinance.
They know the law, they know.
And he's telling them, no, no, look, I'm bread, not the Lamb.
Right?
You get it?
This is kind of advanced, but it's so simple.
Right?
Because he was not burned in the New Testament.
The Christ was not burned.
No, he's taken to the tomb.
Resurrected.
Right.
He's taken to the tomb.
Resurrected.
And he's telling them this.
He's telling this to them, he's hinting, he's giving hints during the Passover.
This bread is my body because the ordinance of the Passover is no Lamb is to remain till morning.
If there is, it is to be put into what?
The fire.
So they're like, oh my gosh, he's going to be killed and then burned.
He's like, no, no, I'm the bread.
Right?
Anyway, what I just said is very advanced.
I've never heard anyone describe it this way.
Right?
Give you another example of how simple this is all.
It's very advanced because of being maybe the only one saying it.
But anyone could see this, and I'm not reading into it, I'm reading out of it.
Okay.
Here's another thing.
One of the Ten Commandments, the ones that were written on stone, is that you are to ransom a donkey, a male donkey, with a lamb.
And if you don't, you break its neck.
So before the Passover, when he entered Jerusalem, he was to enter on a donkey.
Right.
And it was a young one.
He even said, this one has never been ridden before.
So did that donkey have, was that donkey ransomed with a lamb?
Yes, it was.
You see?
So you have these dualities in there that satisfy one thing and satisfy the other.
Because if the Christ was burned, he would satisfy the ordinance of the Passover.
But it wouldn't satisfy the resurrection directly as it was done.
You see?
So I don't know.
These things, I mean, here's the thing.
I have an affinity, in other words, I like reading the biblical text and the scripture.
And I like to project the knowledge of the scripture instead of just the information.
Because again, information, here, I'll give you an example.
They did the Warren Commission for JFK and they did the 9-11 report or whatever for 9-11.
That is packed full of information, isn't it?
Aren't they full of information?
Sure.
Yeah.
And what kind of knowledge of the event do you have when you read that?
Nothing.
Next to nothing.
Next to nothing that's usable.
Pure example, you know, a study of Jack Ruby's mother's teeth in the Warren Commission volumes.
That's there, by the way.
Lots of information.
Lots of information there, though.
I mean, look, if you're a dentist and you want to understand this guy's mother's teeth, I mean, great information.
So the point of view that I brought up is unique to Greek-speak.
It's knowledge that one gets from reading the scripture.
By the way, there's no deflection here.
You notice I haven't said you have to go back to the original language at this point on anything, did I?
You could read the piss-poor versions that the Illuminati put out for you, and you will get 100 percent everything that I've said.
No, it's still there.
It's still all there.
It's almost like a hologram.
When you tear up a hologram, a little piece still resembles the entire – you can still project the entire image through it.
So I haven't really got into anything.
I don't think we will on this episode about the – forget about the versions.
Very little value, but the story does come through.
Knowledge comes through, but the information that you're getting from the versions doesn't.
If you want more direct information, you're going to have to go to the Aramaic, not the Greek.
Well, you have to know all of it.
You have to know all of it, actually, right?
But if you know where the mistakes are, it makes it even – that's the reason why you go back to the original language,
is to know where the mistakes are and what is incorrect, because we're English speakers, let's say, or whatever,
whatever language the version is in.
But once you start studying what was in the Aramaic,
you're going to see even more of a different picture on information that's given around this subject that we're discussing right now.
So in essence, most people say, what about the three holes in Golgotha or whatever?
Well, the first thing, the Knights Templars made those three holes there to sell tickets, right, back during the days of the Crusades.
Second of all, executions were to be done according to the biblical ordinance outside of the city.
Those three holes that they have drilled in the stone to tell you where the three crosses were, guess where they are?
They're in old Jerusalem proper.
So again, it doesn't hold.
This sounds a lot like probably what you do with the JFK research or other people have done with the 9-11 stuff,
which 9-11 stuff is too much of a whatever.
It's really bad out there talking about what they talk about.
But part of doing this kind of study or discussion, I don't like mentioning what's incorrect.
Oh, by the way, on the last episode, I kept saying and I meditated on this.
Why do I keep saying, do not correct your enemy when they're making mistakes?
I believe it's, do not disturb your enemy when they're making mistakes, is the original quote on that.
That sounds actually better.
Yeah, that's actually what it is from memory.
I don't know.
Someone will probably look it up and probably find that more true to the original comment.
Do not disturb your enemy because you know what?
You're not going to correct them.
But I just kept saying in a debate.
So I don't like bringing up what's incorrect.
You notice even when I go on a long dissertation on 9-11, I never start making fun of all the other people at all.
There's no reason to or making fun of attorneys or doctors, what they're actually saying.
Not at all.
You just go right to the point because when you start going and trying to counter what doctors tell people
or attorneys tell people or priests or whatever or 9-11, when you start saying what they're saying is wrong,
that's just more information to counter information.
The thing is, where's the knowledge?
You see?
There's no knowledge in that.
So the knowledge is understanding the methodology.
Again, to go back, if you're going to build a 100-story building, is it 10 times more than a 10-story building?
Yes, it is, generally speaking.
Right?
But not really.
Because each floor, the first floor of the 100-story building is going to hold 99 times more, not just 10 times.
See, the overall building is 10 times.
Right.
But the first floor has to hold 11 times.
You see?
So that's where the knowledge comes in.
So one thing out of this, and I got kind of excited, is let's just hit this on the chat
and talk about what's on the chat about the Christ again.
Because if anyone's ever listened to Greek speak where I have more than an hour, I'm going to bring this up.
Not more in the early days, but more recently, always.
You know, what's this guy knelt to a cross wearing a diaper?
You notice what they're doing.
And one of the metrics with that also, just like using the word J-E-S-U-S, is that symbol.
If you believe in that symbol or whatever, that's part of the metric.
They got you.
They're like, this person is totally ignorant.
They're going to buy into all the rest of this stuff.
And I bet you every time we do something, they're just going to hit the snooze button.
Get it?
Right.
Yep.
So every 10 years or every five, we're going to hit them with something, and they're going to just buy into it.
So either way, metrics or not, information or not, this was basically an exercise in what the difference between knowledge and information might be.