I don't know if that's got anything to
do with anything, but uh maybe it does,
maybe it doesn't.
Greek you talked about some glitches recently um
first off though, how you doing?
Uh glitching.
You're glitching, like right now.
Glitchy.
The jitsy.
Well, not really, no.
When you put stuff in people's minds, you
know, it gets more whatever.
For me, the existence here is always glitchy
and incorrect ever since as far back as
I can remember.
So I'm not really the best person to
ask, but I am very good at objectifying
stuff, so maybe I am.
I don't know.
Well, I was thinking about something objectively, and
we got a question recently regarding induction.
And you talked about this early on.
They went way back in the Sonics and
started listening to you when you talked about
the Transporter and Star Trek and all that.
And I pulled that into two different pieces
myself, and so did this listener.
And they said, you know, it seems to
me as though the key to being able
to do anything in this entire universe or
matrix or what did they also call it?
Let me look real fast.
Simulation.
Construct is another good word.
They didn't use that, but they said simulation,
whatever it is you want to call it.
The Transporter would be a great everything, not
just a weapon or a way to cure
things.
I mean, look, if you wanted to factor
something out of the body completely or if
you wanted to change the age of somebody,
all you would need is the patterns, right?
And, like, I'm thinking about it because I'm
familiar with the Star Trek canon, and I'm
saying to myself, yeah, induction in that way,
but that's also transportation.
But I guess induction is transportation, too, just
over a short – you know, like if
we think about food going in, right, and
then it creates induction.
It creates a reaction which creates something else
in the blood, whatever, but that's the body
creating it because it had this other material
to work with.
By the way, in terms of creation, the
echo just stopped.
Whatever you just did, did you lean forward
or touch something?
I did touch something, yes.
I will leave it that way if it'll
stop.
Okay, whatever that was, that's the echo.
Yeah, that was the echo.
Now it's gone.
Excellent.
Okay.
Okay, that's cool.
So I get it.
Well, here's the – this is the primer
on induction.
We have monsoon season here in Tucson.
If you have a rainy season right now,
this is what you do.
When you see rain – okay, when you
understand how water is formed in the atmosphere,
specifically rainwater, you'll get a handle on, let's
just say, witnessing induction firsthand.
Now, that sounds kind of stupid.
It really is because you're witnessing induction firsthand,
first principle inside your body constantly, but you
can't perceive it because it's a first principle
thing.
If you could perceive all the functions in
your body, even some of them, you'd go
mad, right?
So I used to like – when I
was a child, I used to cover –
press my hands over my ears real hard
and you could hear your heartbeat if you've
ever tried that, right?
So there's a lot going on, but okay.
Take a sip of that coffee.
Let's get started.
Rain, if you understand – also rain has
a strong spiritual implication in many ancient rites,
right?
So they're trying to tell you why does
rain always show up in ancient rites, but
okay.
So this is what you do.
Well, okay.
Let's just say what you do.
All right, so you go outside and you
find a cloud that's – typically they're very
thick, cumulus clouds, white fluffy.
They might turn gray and they get a
very flat bottom, like a very flat bottom.
You could actually – if you're not aware
of cloud formations, just be aware that thunderstorms
typically – not always.
When it's fully charged, it will get a
very flat bottom as if it's being pressed
up against something, right?
Now go get yourself some binoculars, telescope or
whatever if you've got good vision.
Focus on the edge of the cloud or
the bottom of the cloud and then watch
the rain appear.
It'll start falling or when it falls.
And watch the entire rainfall.
Stand underneath a soffit or an overhang or
something.
So you're not in the rain, an umbrella
even or whatever.
Don't get hit by lightning.
And just watch the rainfall.
Now you don't have to do this for
hours.
Sometimes the rain goes on for hours, but
just watch pre-formation and you'll get a
feeling.
Your mind – and understand that the rainwater
itself, the droplets that are falling to the
Earth, are formed underneath that flat layer of
the cloud.
Now not always because sometimes if you go
out in a storm and you look up
at the clouds, you kind of see them,
but then there's like this fog under the
clouds.
They're very undefined and you can't really see
much.
Your best, let's say, visual experience would be
when the cloud forms that flat bottom.
Now what they tell you – OK, so
you're going to witness induction.
You say, well, Greg, I don't see anything.
It's just typical rain.
I see the flat bottom and I see
the cloud and then I hear some thunder
maybe or I hear the rain.
I see the rain, but what?
OK, well, you just witnessed it.
Whether you saw it or not or noticed
it or not, whatever.
I remember when I was really young riding
the public transit, the bus sometimes, and I
see all the people run to one side
of the bus and look out the window
because there was a car accident.
I didn't see the car accident.
All I saw was the people running to
the side of the bus to look at
the car accident.
So it might be like that for you
even though you were there.
You see the result, but not the process.
Yeah, they saw enough of it to know
that they want to go see more, and
I saw them looking at something and then
I went to go see what they were
looking at.
So either way.
OK, so this is what the idiots, the
morons, the academics, the scientists tell you happens.
You have humidity in the air and it
clings on to dust particles, forms droplets and
falls.
OK, that's so stupid.
OK, now you could use their own science
to disprove that because their own science uses
conservation of mass.
So if you have a given humidity, let's
say 35 percent, because that's typically required, which
is 15 grams of water per cubic meter.
And when you have 35 percent humidity and
the humidity is now clinging to the dust
particle to form water, a form of condensate,
you should have some kind of a humidity
meter.
There's several varieties of them.
And you will see that the humidity in
the air is decreasing now because it's leaving
the air and condensating like a dehumidifier almost
on the dust to form a water droplet.
That's not how it happens at all.
Right before the rainfall, we see the humidity
climb.
So where is that water coming from?
Where is that humidity coming from?
So their conservation of matter falls apart.
To give you bullshit like conservation of energy
and conservation of matter, that's only true in
a closed system to a degree.
But all closed systems are in open systems.
Like a closed system would be, let's say,
your automobile car.
It's a closed system because you have a
gas tank, you have the engine, the cabin
and all that stuff.
But at one point it has to dump
out into an open system, the exhaust, and
at one point it has to suck in
air from the outside.
So it's not really a closed system.
It's semi-closed.
So there's no such thing as a closed
system.
No, there's just cooperative subsystems that combine to
create an effect or not.
That's all there is.
Right.
Yeah.
Yeah, so their thing about humidity clinging to
dust particles is total bullshit.
And if you want to be paid to
be lied to, go to university, go to
eighth grade and beyond or whatever, and you'll
be lied to really well.
And that's what this reality is about.
One of the best ones is go get
yourself a degree in psychiatry.
That one's beautiful.
I've been looking at that lately.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, gosh, they are so screwed up.
I'll tell you a story about it.
We'll stop right here.
OK.
I dated someone who was trying to get
their – or they were getting their doctorate.
Like they tell you you got it but
you don't have it.
It was like a curing period, you know,
after the peer review and your recitation or
dissertation or whatever, bullshit, and your paper and
your thesis.
Yeah, you write your thesis, which basically ends
up being a book that you wrote during
your time, and it's supposed to encompass everything
that you're supposed to have known.
So it's this big book-length manuscript that
they call whatever, and that has to be
reviewed.
Yeah, so anyway, so let's go back to
the thing I was talking about psychiatrists.
And back in the early 2000s in Jerusalem,
there was a lab that was experimenting.
They didn't buy – these were academics and
scientists, but they were on the fringe.
They didn't buy the dust particles forming on
water – humidity forming on dust particles, accumulating
to form raindrops, and that will never happen.
It doesn't work that way.
So they fired these lasers as a form
of inforometry where they could measure the quantity
of water based on spectrum analysis and all
that.
OK.
And they found that every time they did
that with a successive rainstorm, that it took
a few nanoseconds from no rain, no water
present, to lots of water present.
Nanoseconds, billionths of a second, right?
So you're trying to tell me, idiot, moron
scientist, that in billionth of a second, all
that humidity forms on a dust particle?
In a billionth of a second?
That would be so much momentum, it would
be almost like a sub-nuclear detonation.
It would be like a capacitive discharge.
It would look a thousand times brighter than
any Fourth of July fireworks show up there,
if that were true, what they're saying, again,
with the humidity forming.
So it's actually forming out of thin air,
literally out of the ether.
The ether collapses through the programming, no different
than Photoshop, or no different than, well, what
are computer programs where you generate things, right?
There's an outline, right?
It gives you an outline, then you have
different fills, different shapes, right?
There's some control network somewhere that is pumping
us what we need.
Like, for example, Charles Fort, Fortian stuff in
Book of the Damned, and the other book,
Lowe, I think.
I was reading Fort in the 80s, and
by the way, when I was at the
New York Public Library, one of the librarians
came to me and says, you know, this
is where Nikola Tesla sat, and I'm just
going to tell you that, because you're reading
some of the same books that he did,
you know, reportedly.
So the books that Tesla was reading, I
was reading, and sitting where he was, unknowingly.
And also Charles Fort.
Okay, so Charles Fort talks about how things
were unusual appearances, where people thought about certain
things.
Like, for example, all the insects went missing
in England in the 1800s, and they were
reporting on it.
Hey, you notice there's no flies or beetles
or butterflies or dragons?
Yeah, I was like, what happened?
And then suddenly one day, thousands of, you
know, tons of insects started falling from the
sky, live and dead.
Yeah, enough that the people could shovel off
the street, because the constructor or the programmer
kind of like, what's that, Hunger Games?
Hunger Games where they're running around, or they
could program your reality, right?
These controllers, you remember that?
I don't remember if there was a Hunger
Games.
Hunger Games was more like a competition, because,
you know, the rich people wanted the poor
people to compete so they could feed their
sick.
Sure, but during the competition, they had a
control center where they could make it rain
where you were or give you a weapon.
Oh, well, climate control.
And it would just appear.
Yeah, climate control stuff and things like manifestation
have been in a lot of...
See, that's why I wanted to go back
to the Star Trek thing real quick, because
the thing that the subscriber gets to here
is that, look, you're talking about all sorts
of natural observations of induction.
And indeed, we need to know about it,
we need to know how it works, but
what he's saying is, or she, I'm not
sure, is saying, is that if you had
control of that, if you actually knew how
to direct that...
Yeah, that's a good point.
Okay, look, let's just say it's involuntary, but
when we do, for example, when we do
the weather work, we do have a certain
amount of control.
And when you say control, you're implying there's
some form of planning or engineering in the
background, right?
So, like, for example, a simplest form would
be the room is dark, you know there's
a light switch, and you say, I'm going
to go in and turn on the light.
There's a sense of planning, there's a sense
of engineering that's in place already, and you're
confident that you can apply that planning and
engineering because everything's in place, and you have
control that way, right?
On and off, right?
So we can do that with weather, pretty
much, at a rate of anywhere between 50
% to 90% success, which is very
high.
In terms of baseball statistics, there's no one
who's ever had a record like that on
basic weather stuff that we do.
So the control aspect of it, yeah, you
may not fully understand it, but you know
enough about it to control it.
That's fine, and we do.
That's why I speak on, in terms of
the human body, universal principles.
I speak to people often, and they say
that they have a sore on their leg,
and they say, well, what do you eat?
I say, oh, the sore's on the front
of your left leg.
They say, well, how did you know that?
How could you know that?
Well, I just asked you a few questions,
and the things that you intake into your
body and the way you age and all
that stuff, it would have to go on
the front of the body and on the
left-hand side, right?
They're like, how did you know that?
99% of the time, people explain they
want to speak to me about a condition.
Don't tell me anything about it.
After I do an interview, I tell them
exactly where it is and how long it's
been there.
They're like, how did you know that?
And I ask them, don't tell me specifically.
I just want to ask you some questions
first, because I'm piecing together what they're telling
me, right?
Now, do I know any more than that?
No, I don't.
But it's simply being able to ask people
questions about their lifestyle and what they eat
and mentioning against them is pretty amazing.
Do I understand all of it?
Sorry, something just disrupted you during that last
sentence and a half.
You must have passed by.
Oh, okay.
Sorry, go ahead.
No, no, I'm not moving.
I'm not moving at all.
What I'm saying is simply asking just a
query about certain conditions and lifestyle of someone
and then telling them where the sore is
or the tumor or they're having the affliction.
They're amazed by it, right?
Because I've pieced together enough controls and enough
of the engineering of how the body works,
that it can be applied.
So you could say directly you can reverse.
You know how many times I've said the
current establishment has done tons of grunt work
just because they're morons, don't throw it all
away, right?
So like in other words, ditches have to
be dug, right?
If you had most of people digging ditches,
that's all they did, and they didn't know
why they were digging them.
It doesn't mean just go fill them up
again.
They're useful.
You could throw things in there, right, or
whatever, build a foundation.
For instance, anatomical maps in the medical industry
are useful because they show you things that
are under the skin.
This is where this is.
This is where that is.
I'll tell you what though.
They are useful if you're dealing with dead
people.
They're not very useful when you're dealing with
living.
Remember, when you die, the body changes very
radically within minutes.
Do you remember we were talking about thyroid
and all that, and they show anatomy of
a thyroid?
That's not really what the thyroid looks like.
That's what the thyroid looks like when you're
dead, right?
What the thyroid looks like when you're alive
is very different but similar.
Like a live fish in an aquarium will
look very similar to a dead fish at
the fish market, the same fish, let's say
whatever trout, let's say, or whatever, right?
Very similar, but they're actually very different.
They appear very different because they're alive.
They're in motion.
If it's still, it's still in motion.
Yeah, even the color changes.
Like I've actually seen an open head wound
and it's still a living brain.
It does not look like the anatomical examples
that are photographed after autopsies.
It is a totally different looking thing.
It looks like purple and brown, and then
you see a very light spot where the
brain would be, almost white.
Yes, when it's alive.
When it's alive, yeah.
It's not gray matter.
It's gray matter when it's dead, yeah.
Right, that's what I was going to say.
Think of dry flowers and live flowers.
Anything living and anything dead is not a
direct comparison.
It's just one thing's alive, one thing's dead.
But what I'm trying to say here, these
morons, the medics, the medical people, the academics,
the scientists and all that, now they are
morons because there's an exception.
When I say they're idiots or morons, the
exceptions are those who figure out that it's
all bullshit and politics.
They're still there, but they're like, how do
I get out of here?
I need to do something else.
Those are the exceptions.
The ones that stay in there are morons,
for sure.
There's no doubt about that.
So take what they give and try to
use it and apply it with universal principles,
living versus dead, up versus down.
Here's the thing.
Everything has an electrical – it's not fair
to say electrical because you think of battery
cells and the power in your wall and
all that.
If all living things were not electrical in
some capacity, no pun intended for you electrical
heads, you couldn't kill something alive with electricity,
right?
Because it has to be a parity.
So if you can kill something that's alive
with electricity, it's because it has electricity keeping
it alive.
You get it?
So where is the study in that?
Now there used to be – you used
to interview – I remember a long time
ago this doctor that came around and talked
about Iraq where they did have weapons of
mass destruction or whatever, and he was a
gastrointestinologist or something like that, working medical stuff.
And I asked him a question.
I don't know if it was – yeah,
I don't know if it was on air
or off air.
How would you explain the impulses or what
keeps the digestive system going?
He says, it's electrical.
And I'm like, where's your electric medicine then?
Why are you putting chemicals in there?
And drugs, right?
So yeah, OK.
Take what they – it's a very broad,
broad field, but you have to learn it
on your own.
And unfortunately, the universal principle stuff, I don't
know where you're going to learn it now.
We would have been better off without a
computer in the 1970s or 1980s and tell
people just go run to some good libraries
or good old bookstores, and you'd have a
much better chance when things like macrobiotics and
Taoism and Qigong and things like that were
taught openly, right?
You could always find a place.
OK, now you think with the advent of
the Internet, you'd have access to that information.
Yeah, you do, and it's so watered down
it's almost not worth even looking at, right?
So anyway, the induction thing, yeah, you do
have control.
You do have control.
You have to understand the universal principles.
We do this all the time.
We speak about that all the time here.
Right, absolutely.
Well, OK, so another one is another input
from a subscriber is this guy always asks
about stuff that has to do with what's
coming next, that kind of thing.
Anyway, do you think things will get better
as a type of deception?
OK, I know what he's asking here.
In other words, are we going to have
sort of a false nice time here where
everything's going to get really, really good before?
Absolutely.
Yeah.
Yeah, I wonder, that's one of the things
I spoke about in Sonics.
It'll appear real and you'll benefit from it
because it's real.
Like, for example, with the finance, again, you
go to buy a house or a car
with a loan from the bank.
Oh, thank you, God, for getting me a
loan.
Actually, they didn't lend you anything.
They took your note.
They have permission to run your note and
get money from the Federal Reserve.
You don't know what's going on, but if
you really needed that loan to make a
business move or buy something that you couldn't
have without the loan, is that a benefit
to you?
Yes, it is.
But what you think it is, it really
isn't, right?
So you're going to get a very conservative
state.
Archaics talks about this also, but I spoke
about this 20 years ago or 15 years
ago with you, or 10 years ago, that
you're going to get into a very classic
Old Testament type, what do you call it?
Culture, mindset, lawful kind of conservative.
That would be conservative for sure, right?
Well, conservative kind of outlook.
Yes.
Yes, definitely by today's standards, conservative, yeah.
Yeah, and everything that comes along with it.
And by the way, when there was that
very conservative mindset where, like, the white people
ruled, if you were not white, you didn't
count.
By the way, by law, you still don't.
If you read the slaughterhouse cases, only white
men can function in law and all that
other stuff.
It hasn't been repealed.
I'm not saying that I'm for that, because
actually the white men is actually...
Anyway, I've talked about it.
You know what I say?
Think about white people.
So not the white people, the color of
your skin, because you could be any color
and act like a white.
It's the culture.
It's so watered down and lost, and I
don't know what happened.
But actually I do, but it's another discussion.
You need some European flavor.
Yes, I'm borrowing that for a public presentation
I'm planning on doing, by the way.
So just to let you know, there's going
to be a serious influence where I'm basically
going to explain to a room full of
white people that they're stupid.
Well, it's not stupid.
Something happened to their culture.
Give me an example.
You go to any multi-ethnic, multicultural, hip
cultural place like New York City, San Francisco,
whatever, you're going to get Thai food, Chinese
food, Greek food, Italian food, Spanish food, Peruvian
food, on and on and on, Ethiopian food,
right?
You're not going to see English food from
England or Dutch food from Holland.
Never, never, ever, ever, ever.
As a matter of fact, the British...
Yeah, and the fish and chips are terrible
there too.
They supposedly are the king of fish and
chips and they cook it in beef tallow.
It's soaked in oil.
It's lousy.
You want good fish and chips, go to
the east coast of the U.S., the
seafaring states like Massachusetts and Maine or whatever,
even New York.
They got better fish and chips at Wendy's
when they had it than anywhere in England.
So something happened to that culture.
Any boardwalk will give you better fish and
chips.
Any boardwalk venue will give you...
Yeah, will give you better fish and chips
than anything you'll get in England or the
U.K. or whatever.
So something happened to the culture and the
people have been walking around with their head
up their ass for a long time and
they don't have to.
Yeah, I talk about white people food all
the time.
Oh, yeah.
My whole presentation is going to be about
how these people have this perception of what
life, you know, the mafia is.
And you know zero is what the problem
is.
Oh, the mafia again.
Well, here's the thing.
I spoke to an engineer.
He designed most of the...
He's kind of damned for it.
You know, everything has to go through Atlanta,
right?
With I-10 and the highways and all
that.
They made it some kind of hub.
He didn't agree to that, but he worked
on it, designed it.
He's a melanated or black guy who studied
in the 1940s engineering, got a doctorate in
engineering, civil engineering and all that.
And when all these civil rights...
No, when the affirmative action came out, he
was in on the writing of it or
the consulting of it before it was even
made public.
Right?
Like in other words, when they do...
They have these...
What do they call these groups that work
with the government?
They're NGOs like RAND.
They consult...
What are they called?
Like think tanks?
You can call them think tanks.
There are think tanks.
There's also the NGOs like you were talking
about which may be a think tank or
not.
Sometimes they have a think tank as part
of it.
They call them an institute, etc.
But they're really just these organizations that operate
within and around governments that are not governments.
That's all they are.
Yeah, so by the end of the 50s,
he found out they were doing this affirmative
action program and it had nothing to do
with a lot of people the way they
get it politically and through the media.
It's all you're giving people that, you know,
without merit, a position where they should...
Not meritoriously positioned, you know.
It's just because of their ethnicity or skin
color and a lot of people griping about
that, right?
But the real reason it was done, he
explained to me, was because by the late
50s, the industry of America realized it was
all populated almost exclusively by middle-aged white
men.
And the creativity, the design factors, the engineering,
all that was getting really stale and inbred.
They couldn't come up with new ideas.
Stuff they were building was...
There was no progress.
It was not very good.
And they figured, like, why are we falling
so far behind?
And we can't see how we can get
anything better.
And then the idea came out, because it
has nothing to do with your education.
It has to do with you need cultural
influence.
You need other ethnic culture.
You need geographic culture.
You need ethnic culture, different culture culture to
come in and that acts like...
It cross-pollinates indirectly flavor.
Adds flavor, let's say, right?
And that's why they did it, is because
the middle-aged white, which was all exclusive,
all the above middle-level management up was
all white, middle-aged, whatever, and exclusively, no
women, right?
So they said, you have to integrate.
You have to bring in other cultures, ethnicities,
all that.
Even though they may not be specialists in
the field, they will bring something that will
allow the...
It's like fertilizer, in a way, in a
good way.
It'll enrich.
It's like bringing in new nutrients, right?
And that was the reason why they did
it, but they never went public with that.
They just said, okay, we got this thing,
affirmative action, because a lot of people are
disenfranchised, and if you get federal money, you
have to comply.
That's all they said.
They didn't really give you the history of
it.
When I heard that, I was like, oh,
that makes total sense.
And actually, not only does it make total
sense, it makes too much sense, because I've
been talking about shit like that for years.
Thank you for telling me.
Right?
And actually, no one's ever heard of what
I just told you, because it was very
private at the time.
That would be an insult and a slap
in the face to white America if they
came out and said the reason why we're
doing this is because you guys are inbred,
and now conscious or mentally inbred, professionally inbred.
You need some external genes, right?
Let's say, right?
And to your industry, they couldn't tell the
people that.
And when I heard that, I was like,
wow.
Thank you for sharing that.
You know what's funny about that is that
very recently, a couple of, like, very, let's
call them Afrocentric bloggers or very, like, you
know, black sort of bloggers have actually started
talking about this.
And I thought it was the wildest thing,
because I've heard about it from you a
few years ago already.
But these guys started going, you know what
the real problem is?
Is, you know, because they're arguing about DEI
and all this, right?
Diversity, whatever.
The point is, is that diversity.
Well, they're calling diversity now is something different.
They want men to dress like women.
But anyway, go ahead.
But no, but that's not the whole thing.
The whole thing was meant to bring everybody
in.
So it got perverted, and now we're going
to bring in the whole, you know, transgender
and all that nonsense.
But the truth is.
Yeah, that's what the new stuff is.
But to bring everybody in is not the
point.
The point was to cross-pollinate and bring
in, instead of having this monoculture that is
dying, right?
Like brother and sister having babies over generation
after generation.
They needed to, what do you call it
when you, it's incestuous almost.
Intellectual incestuous kind of degrading thing.
Yeah, they needed to bring in.
Yeah, intellectual incest.
Perfect.
But that's the thing.
You have to diversify things a bit in
order to strengthen the product.
It's that simple.
And as time goes on, yeah, it's going
to get stale.
And this is how these guys are starting
to talk about it.
And I was like, are these guys listening
to the Greek?
Because it's almost exactly the same thing, except,
you know, they kind of go, you know.
Well, the thing is, well, ask them for
their source on the info.
Did they intuit it?
Is it intuitive?
That would be good.
You're picking it up from the field, right?
Yeah, I have written to a couple.
It could be intuitive, but I could give
you my source.
I just gave you my source.
No, I know.
So it was an engineer, yeah.
I didn't mention him by name.
No, no, no problem.
But I wrote to them and asked them,
and I didn't get many responses.
But I did get one response, and the
guy said it is just what makes sense
and is obvious.
And I said, okay.
Oh, so they intuited.
Good, very good.
So they're picking up from the intuition.
Yeah, absolutely.
This guy Ken Yeta out there, if anybody
runs across him on, like, Substack or I
think he might even have a YouTube channel.
But he talks about this kind of stuff
and goes, look, this is the truth about,
you know, a bunch of different things.
But it just so happened, and he said
almost exactly what you said, about how diversity
is not what it is.
But his source essentially was a thought experiment
or intuition.
Yeah.
See, I wouldn't have picked this up.
Well, maybe I would have, but I'm telling
you, I had a conversation more than a
decade ago with someone who was directly involved
with this.
You can look up who designed the –
it's called the Atlanta Interchange or all the
highways that go through Atlanta, whatever, all the
engineers.
And his name is there.
He's given credit.
They put his name on a bronze plaque
or whatever.
But anyway, I thought that was really cool.
And, like I said, they couldn't come out
with that kind of deep, let's say, intel
back in the late 50s publicly.
Not even now they're doing it.
They're not even talking about it now.
Anyway, and by the way, a lot of
wealthy, melanated or black people were very upset
about the Civil Rights Movement because they knew
where it was going to lead to.
They knew that they were going to give
this false sense of, quote-unquote, civil rights,
which are not constitutional rights.
They're not lawful, by the way.
It's all statutory and has to do with
economics.
If you receive federal money, you have to
do this, right?
What I heard from them, this is from
one of the inventors, his dad, the super
soaker, he's worth like $150 million.
I forgot his name.
Somebody that was working with him, and I
was in that group, but indirectly I never
crossed over and had direct conversations with him.
But a lot of people that were prominent,
they were like, this is bad because the
Civil Rights Movement is just a bait.
They're doing that so they could beef up
their police force, and then they're going to
bring the police in and start predating on
people, which is what happened.
There's more to the story, but the idea
of a, quote-unquote, black neighborhood is a
ghetto was not prevalent until after the Civil
Rights Movement, right?
The ghetto concept, right?
And so, yeah, what it did was the
opposite.
It actually brought slavery back.
If you brought the concept of, let's say,
black slavery and how that was administered, it's
very much administered, black, quote-unquote, neighborhoods are
administered the same way today.
So anyway, they saw it as a very
negative thing.
No one ever speaks about all of the
affluent black neighborhoods in the country.
When you say black neighborhood, they go, boom,
ghetto.
Where did these rappers or basketball players come
from, right?
So it's still going on.
I mean, it's just sick.
I mean, you're being deceived about everything.
Well, go figure.
So anyway, any more questions?
No, those are the only two I have.
Yeah, and also it was like what's coming.
Yeah, it's going to be false, but you're
going to benefit from it, just like most
people feel like they benefit from whatever, going
to medical or going to attorneys or going
to doctors.
It doesn't work that way.
It's a short term.
It doesn't last long.
Anyway, what I want to bring up was
someone we've been in contact for a long
time, and regarding healing modalities, we tried certain
things.
This was a skin condition, and he emailed
me.
He says, guess what?
You know, I tried eggs, and eggs really
worked out well for me, even though we
were talking about no meat, no oils, and
things like that, no animal.
I don't like to say meat.
I just say animal, right?
That covers it a little better.
And then there's, by the way, with animal,
you have typically when I say animal means
where you have the flesh of a dead
animal.
But you can have animal products where the
animal stays alive, like eggs and milk, for
example, except fish eggs.
Fish eggs, they usually kill the fish.
They have to get it out of the
corpse of the fish.
But typically, eggs from fowl and milk from
milk goats, milk sheep, cows, the animal retains
its life, right?
And it's putting out that product anyway.
So that is a different class when I
say animal.
But I include those in there typically because
that's more conservative.
But he found that eggs were very regenerative
and helpful.
Now, if you know anyone from Asia, and
you know how Americans eat two eggs and
bacon and all that for breakfast, right?
In Asia, if you eat an egg, they're
like, oh, wow, you're eating an egg.
And you're like, yeah, I usually have two.
They're like, wow.
It's a big deal to eat an egg
in Asian culture because they understand that if
you ask them why this is such a
big deal, they can't tell you directly.
But in their culture, which uses a lot
more, they're more considerate about the energy of
things.
When you eat an egg, right?
Remember, when a chick hatches, the shell is
left behind.
You're not eating the shell.
You're eating everything that makes that chick, right?
So essentially, when you're eating an egg, whether
you eat chicken or not, let's say you
eat chicken.
I had chicken for lunch or dinner or
whatever, right?
You had the muscle.
You probably didn't eat gizzard or liver or
the feet, whatever, right?
Actually, fried gizzards and stuff are delicious, and
the feet are delicious too.
Most people can't handle it.
It's very sweet, almost like white corn in
sweetness.
So you probably just ate the muscle tissue,
dark or white meat, right?
But when you eat an egg, remember, when
the chick is born, it leaves the shell
behind.
So we're not talking about the shell, just
the inside.
It's the same thing as eating a chicken,
all of the internals, the beak, all the
feathers, the claws, the feet, everything.
You get it?
Because everything that, all the energy, all the
substance that it took to form that chicken,
the entire chicken, feathers and all, let's say
when you say feathers and all, it means
the whole chicken, is in that egg that
you're eating.
Remember, the shell is left behind either way,
right?
So it's pretty powerful.
Now, typically, I think chickens, they just get
fertilized once, right?
And they make fertile eggs.
They just get inseminated once by a rooster,
and all the eggs continue being fertile, I
believe.
Or is it every year or two they
have to do it?
I'm not sure.
Yeah, I think it's something like that.
It's more than I'm getting.
But anyway, so the idea here is this.
This is one thing I didn't clarify with
him, and I said, I'll talk about eggs.
So you're eating the entire chicken, but you're
only eating the entire chicken if the egg
is a fertilized egg.
Most eggs that you buy, even if you
go to a farmer's market, if they were
ever refrigerated and you took them home and
put them under an incubator, they would never
form and hatch because they're not fertile.
Fertile eggs, right?
You get it?
So most of the eggs that we eat
are not fertile eggs, for several reasons, obviously.
So that will remain as this basic albumin,
yolk-type protein, almost like stem cells, right?
Stem cells, remember, you've heard of all the
– what was it, 10, 15 years ago?
Oh, stem cell therapy.
Remember, it went away now, right?
But in that vein of thought, it's like
a pre-cell, so whatever you need, those
stem cells actually latch on and grow and
help the body develop what it needs, let's
say, right?
The idea is that further down, you have
cells that are sort of blanks, that can
become something else.
They don't have a nucleus or mitochondria, let's
say.
So therefore, the egg is sort of like
that because this doesn't necessarily have to become
a chicken, but it could.
Only if it's a non-fertile egg.
A fertile egg has everything necessary energetically to
form that chicken.
When you eat a fertile egg, you're essentially
eating the chicken feathers, beak, and all.
So when it's a non-fertile egg, it's
essentially the same kind of folklore that you
have in a stem cell.
Now, I'm not saying that eating non-fertile
eggs, which is a typical egg that you
buy, is like having stem cells.
No, but I'm giving the comparison.
It's not the same.
And actually, under any testing, it would be
very strenuous testing to see if it was
a fertile egg or not.
They have to actually do what everybody else
does, wait and see, or get the history
of the hen.
So that's an interesting point.
And I brought this up.
It's interesting because the eggs came up again
because I did a short talk with someone
about this about a year ago.
And I mentioned in the email, I'll speak
about it on a sonic, and I want
to because I thought about this, that having
not so much the eggs, it's that the
eggs are not fertile or fertilized, or the
hen hasn't been fertilized.
I'm not up to my chicken lingo, guys.
Sorry, I'm not being precise enough.
Maybe I should look up some zoology or
the fauna of the fowl and see how
they operate.
Now, I wouldn't be surprised if different breeds
or species of fowl had different characteristics as
well.
Well, they do make slightly different eggs, different
types of chickens.
They have different breeds and whatnot.
Oh, there's a hundred varieties of chickens.
You know, like what came first, the chicken
or the egg?
I used to tell people, the chicken farmer.
The chicken farmer came first because the chicken,
as you know it today, did not exist
more than 300 years ago.
As a matter of fact, if you go
look at— No, I was just going to
ask because another strange thing that happened with
the eggs that I noticed changed over the
past few years because I don't eat that
many of them.
But, you know, they used to—sometimes I would
crack one open and there would be this
little chunk in there.
Yeah, a red dot.
Well, sometimes a red dot, but sometimes it
was a white thing that was just kind
of there, and it almost seemed like, well,
gee, that kind of egg has tried to
form into a chicken.
It's the end of the albumin.
Yeah, well, typically—well, a chicken egg, by the
way, a fertile one, is a good example
to show how the blood is pumped without
a heart because when the capillaries form around
the yolk, you flash a light and you
can look closely and the capillaries are pulsating.
And there's just capillaries forming around the yolk.
There's no evidence of any animal at all,
and forget about even looking for a heart
because there's just capillaries wrapping.
Like the capillaries, it almost appears like the
capillaries on the white of your eye around
a yolk.
That's all there is, and they're pulsing.
This is an experiment, a very crude experiment,
and they don't discuss this.
That's why they literally used to pay people
to hold the eggs.
They used to literally pay people to hold
the eggs up to light to be able
to see that.
If they saw that, the egg was rejected
for consumption.
Sure, there's many old egg tricks about spinning
them on a table, all kinds of stuff.
But I just want to say that the
chicken that is popular today was not a
popular bird to eat.
Back in the day, more than 200 or
300 years ago, there were other fowl that
were more popular because it wasn't worth killing
a chicken because it didn't have enough meat.
They were used for eggs, but they were
not good for meat.
So what they did was they started breeding
them for meat.
Just like, for example, if you buy...
Go look at some sketches.
They're around 1,600, 1,500.
They're surviving sketches where you look for the
oldest sketch or drawing of a chicken, and
you look at it, and you're like, wow,
that's a really skinny bird.
That chicken doesn't even look like a chicken.
It's so skinny, it's unbelievable.
You wouldn't recognize it as a chicken.
It almost looks like a dove or even
skinnier than a dove.
That's why, for example, if you're in the
market for goats, they ask you, do you
want a meat goat or a milk goat?
Different breed.
I mean, they breed them for...
One is bred for having a sizable udder
for milk, and the other one is bred
for a sizable mass of muscle, right, for
meat.
So this has been...
We've been messing around with this stuff for
hundreds of years now, and when we think
we bring up animals, it's not really in
the...
It's only recent culture.
But, yeah, so anyway, the moral of the
egg story is rationalizing that if the egg
is not fertile, it will be more of
a distemper.