Sonic 88 rated Y, here we are.
Anyway, how are you doing tonight, Greg?
I'm doing well, yeah.
Long days, and we usually record at 8pm on a Tuesday and a Saturday, right?
What's called a Tuesday or Saturday, so it's a Tuesday.
And yeah, I feel like I need a nap, again.
You know, I bring up the expansive, contractive nature of things, and going back to scriptural,
you know, people always talk about higher and lower, it's the way we've been trained
in this iteration of our age.
But if you go back to scripture, it's inner and outer.
It's the inner circle and the outer circle.
I've been bringing up much of the yin and yang lately, which is, again, inner and outer.
Expansive, right?
Well, when you say higher and lower, just really quickly, when you say higher and lower
and you're correcting that, I mean, there's a lot of ways to look at that.
You do mean the above and below kind of thing?
Yeah, which there's three levels to that.
Well, of course.
You could look at higher and lower as volume, right?
You know, higher volume, lower volume.
You could look at higher and lower as quality.
No, no, it's more advantage point here, more advantage point.
Basically, the essence of the control system is higher and lower.
You know, the rich guy lives up in the tower.
The government's up in the tower.
Powerful people up and you're down low, right?
The pyramid, right?
Top of the pyramid, bottom of the pyramid, right?
All that stuff.
That is not pertinent to a sustainable thinking and a sustainable society.
That is only pertinent to a society that needs to be controlled and manipulated.
People do want to be manipulated.
They don't have to say it.
Absolutely, and high ground is useful in short-term strategies.
You know what I mean?
That's where the higher and lower is good.
It's in the short term.
But when it comes to what's more expansive, what is more inclusive, like what includes everything,
it's funny because we were looking back.
We do this thing looking back at the palindrome of the numbers, right?
We went and looked at eight because of 88, and I was thinking back to when I was early on the Internet
and 88 was some kind of, I forget what the reason for it was,
but it was some sort of symbol that had to do with Hitler, allegedly, right?
It was sort of like the thing you said in the chat room to let people know that you were a white supremacist.
And 88 is an interesting thing.
Well, it's good luck.
Yeah, it's good luck.
In the Asian culture, yeah.
You have the two infinity symbols kind of standing up, you know, that you can look at it that way.
What about the concept of infinity?
Is there such a thing?
Is it merely beyond our comprehension because everything to us is finite?
But there is no infinity if it's always—well, the concept of infinity has to be there
when you have a beginning and an end, right?
But most people, when you say infinity, it means no end,
but they never think that there was no beginning either, right?
Okay, I want to go back to what I was saying.
Yeah, sure.
What makes the Greek speak sustainable is understanding where you want to be in this reality, right?
I'll take a pause there for a second because that's a heavy statement.
Yeah, again, about vantage point too, right?
And the real vantage point, the only real thing for people that are free is to understand that it's inner and outer,
contractive and expansive.
That's it.
There is no higher or lower, this, that, or the other.
The more contractive you become, the more expansive you can become, right?
So more contractive would be extreme accuracy of knowledge and information,
extreme finite accuracy, precision and abundance.
That allows you to be very expansive, right?
So anyway, these are just concepts, but it's not higher or lower.
You know how to say higher knowledge and all that?
There is no higher and lower.
And when you get down to the brass tacks, like they say, it's inner knowledge, right?
The inner circle right there, right?
The secret, right?
They have it in the inner circles, right?
See, so it's never higher.
And look, the secret societies don't come out and say we have higher knowledge.
They have occult inner knowledge, right?
Inner knowledge, right.
Yeah, it's inner and outer.
So the more intense the inner, the more capable you could be on the outer.
If you so choose, if you so choose.
If you want to, I've been once called to be an ascetic.
Ascetic is someone like, you know, shuns opulence and wealth and all that.
I don't.
I just don't care about it because this is not the right place for that.
This is the right place and the right time for everything, right?
Right.
So merely people that are wealthy and show that they're wealthy are just wearing the
uniform of the wealthy.
And what I mean by that is, I don't know if you remember, there was a whole slew of articles.
This is an analogy.
Maybe about five, four, five, six years ago.
About how all these billionaire rappers or, you know, hundreds, actually all that stuff
is rented, their jewelry, their cars, their houses.
They really don't have any money at all, really.
Oh, yeah.
Remember that?
It was a whole bunch, especially like 50 cent.
Yeah, that's been like a revelation a couple of times, right, where they showed that toward
the end of the 90s and then they showed it again, like you said, about 10 years ago,
I think now, where it was like, hey, remember those guys that, you know, had all their stuff
in their videos?
All that stuff was rented.
Nobody owns the yacht.
Nobody owns the limo.
Nobody owns the helicopter, etc.
Yeah.
So, OK, so let's say what if I had chosen.
OK, if you're going to be wealthy in this world, you would have to have a military,
your own military apparatus, which, by the way, it does exist.
There are certain wealthy people that if something goes on on their property around
them, they don't call the popo.
They don't call the police.
They have their own security.
They're not going to deal with you appropriately.
And they're allowed to do that.
But, yeah, you would have to build up in order to be wealthy.
OK, you must have a castle doctrine to look it up, whatever that is.
The king of your castle.
Right.
You know, like simple ways you have a moat, you know, and all that.
But, you know, it could be a digital one these days.
Sure.
So, yeah.
So I'm not for that.
But I do understand and have comprehension of the way things work enough that.
So I care to use them.
I know, you know how to do it.
So when you have.
The ability to go extremely young with information means you get anything and everything that
could be known about it with precision.
Then you can expand it, be extremely lean.
So the amount of expansion depends on the amount of contraction.
Right.
Like inhalation, exhalation.
Someone who's really good could do a really good inhale.
Could also, I bet, do a really good exhale.
Right.
Or a shallow breather will probably do neither.
So.
The masses have run down a program for a long time.
And you could see these programs, they bud every couple of hundred years, especially
now every decade.
Right.
But they're still running this big program, which leads me to.
I want to just, in a very contractive way, bring up what's been in the chat about how
to determine the moons.
It doesn't matter which moon it is, but, you know, which one of the, you know, is there
a 13 moon year?
There's there's many ways to go about it.
But the layman's approach, the one that I've been using that I settled on a long time ago
is the one that I find works best.
All right.
It's very simple.
And I've gone through this maybe a dozen times.
Actually, close your ears.
I'll tell you, Chuck, I've gone over at least 100 times.
OK.
The easiest way is the first moon, number one, and the seventh moon, number seven, four,
five, six, seven are the largest moons in appearance when they are full.
And they are more on the cardinal than any of the others.
Both the first and the seventh, meaning they rise in the east and settle dead west.
Don't look at the sun at this point.
Sun will bounce around just the moons.
So let's say we come up right now.
We're in the 12th month.
We're coming up on the first month.
So when I look at the first month and it's also in retrospect.
So when I look at what I think is the next moon, which could either be the 13th or the
first, I look at how large it is when it's full, meaning the first time that it's full,
usually yellow near the horizon, and also look at how due east it is.
And when I go to site it, you know, the moon after the 12th, and it's not, it's more towards
the north, let's say.
It's not that big.
It's probably next month is the first.
It's really strange that way.
When I paid more attention to the intercalation, I was able to predict it a couple of three
months in advance.
But right now, I'm just going moon by moon.
The smallest moons, by the way, just for contrast, are the 9th, 10th months.
They're really tiny and they're, you know, far north, let's say.
And in the summer months, they don't get smaller because the atmosphere is thicker.
But by the way, the more atmosphere you have, the bigger the moon will look, right?
Because the atmosphere has a lensing effect.
That's why when you, when any object near the horizon looks much larger, not as crisp
and bright, but much larger.
So I remember flying in one of these, one of the last of the big airplanes, and it had
an upper deck, a little spiral staircase, and it had a moonroof in an airplane.
It was like a sunroof, moonroof type thing.
I remember seeing the moon and it was tiny.
I've never seen the moon so tiny ever.
And it was around the full moon period.
And I'm at 30,000, 35,000 feet.
So, you know, you think it should be bigger, right?
I would think so, yeah.
Yeah.
No, because there's less atmosphere.
So the higher you go, the smaller the moon looks.
The lower you go and the thicker the atmosphere, the larger the moon looks.
My favorite shots of the moon are like near the equator when it's full in the east and
the moon looks like it's huge.
And it really is perceptibly.
So I just brought that up just to consider what we're looking at is it's all perception.
But the easiest way to do it is when it rises due east and it's the largest size.
And by the way, let's say it's the 12th moon and the next moon we go to visualize.
You notice when I said the moon looked a little too far north, not due east.
So it'll probably be a 13th month.
Use that.
I lean on that more than the size of the moon, by the way.
A beginner will always think the full moon is usually the day after.
But it's not fully round either.
Yeah.
So I enjoy, I don't, I'm anti-cult.
As a matter of fact, this is called the unculting of humanity.
Do you know how simple and easy it would be to start a website dictating?
I'm saying dictating with a capital C.
All these things that I've been talking, Greek speak, making points and you better follow them.
Right.
You know what I mean?
You know how easy it would be to start a cult, you know, and push this.
And also when you look at, when you push any information, meaning you're forthright about it,
where do you get your authority from?
Right.
Other than the people.
I'm looking at, you know, is there, where do you get your badge?
Right.
So most of these things that I discuss should come from a quote unquote priestly class.
And I'm not a priest.
I've never been, I'm not from any lineage and I've never been adjudicated to be that.
I'm just some whatever that says these things because they feel like they have to.
And the reason I just said what I said is because you notice, like in the chat,
in other chats from previous through the decade, it's not more than a decade.
People are always, you know, comes around a moon, you know, deciding the moon.
I'd never chime in.
I never chime in and say, yeah, this is what it is.
You know, I don't know if you'd notice.
I never do that because, and I'm not looking for someone else to take the lead
because there's no leadership in this.
If you go back to castle doctrine, it's anarchism.
Meaning that word's been turned into something that it, you know,
like ground zero means it's an area where a nuke or an atomic device has been detonated.
There's nothing to do with what you think is the center of a place.
So in a sense, when you bring up, oh, any subject at all,
I don't feel like I need to go forward on it.
And I'd like to see everyone else because that is the castle doctrine in anarchism.
Meaning in anarchy, anarchy means without a leader,
like archon or archos means leader or old, right?
Ana means without, not against, like a would be anti.
Ana means without.
So that means that everybody knows the law.
Everybody knows what to do.
Everybody does the right thing.
Everyone's educated, right?
This is a concept that is not for this age of people that have been bred.
They've been stock bred, corn fed, whatever, into this way of thinking at a young age.
I believe that it's possible that in the future, if not was so in the past at one point,
that just like animals, humans would have a pre-downloaded operating system.
Can you imagine where you would be born intelligent?
I have a hard time imagining that because of what I witnessed.
But no, it's fascinating to me because I have this conversation every so often
and it's a repetitious conversation about, well, you know,
if you believe in all that and you think that that's the way it should be,
you know, if we tried that right now, it wouldn't work.
And I go, of course it wouldn't.
The people are not prepared for this.
I think it's a lack of maturity.
Yeah, it's lack of preparation, right, because they don't know what to, right?
If tomorrow all the governments, all the organizations just evaporated,
all went away off the planet all at once, nobody would know what to do.
Well, actually they have.
There's three levels to everything, and right now it's been sliced up into three.
It's diluted three times.
Everything is diluted three times, whether it's religion.
That's why I like the statement, you know,
I like atheists because they're always non-profit, right?
So everything's been sliced up.
So when people say government, I can prove to you there is no more government as defined.
Now there are corporate entities that are bankrupt and in receivership to private trusts.
Oh, my gosh.
That's the threefold, right?
Three slices, right?
So then you look at religions, right?
Well, they're not based on the books that they're supposed to subscribe to
or they profess to subscribe to.
Are they based on also revived other ancient religions
that they're supposedly not supposed to be congruous with?
Yes.
Then there's a third other point.
Is it a form of control mechanism and separation?
Yes.
So everything has these three truths to it.
So try to imagine going with that.
By the way, I like the two strikes you're out, not the three strikes you're out.
Three strikes you're out, it's like too much wiggle room, right?
So if you do me wrong once, you get one more chance, not three, not two more chances, right?
So in other words, not just me.
I mean, this is just a philosophy, right?
In some cases, you can't do wrong at all,
and that would be more of an anarchistic society, right?
In other words, where you would have a high sense of discipline and a high sense of order.
So, yeah.
Yeah, but again, that would almost have to come, like you said,
factory installed, right, as part of the operating system already intact to begin with.
And I have a hard time even beginning to envision that with people because, again—
No, but hold on.
Just because you don't—
Okay, I have a hard time with it too, but notice I didn't say that.
It is possible.
If you remove anything that is impossible, then only the possible is most probable.
Only the possible is probable, right?
You see?
So is it impossible? No.
I didn't say whether you have a hard time with it or not, right?
Or anyone would have a hard time with it, even if they can't even grasp what we're talking about.
I suggest that it's possible and more than probable.
I believe there have been a time period, and there will be a time period,
where, you know, the analogy where a puppy newborn is adopted by a family of gorillas.
After it reaches adult doghood, you can adopt that puppy or dog now,
and you wouldn't know it was raised by gorillas.
It would, you know, chase a squirrel and bark and chase a stick
and pee just like a regular dog that wasn't raised by gorillas.
But if you had a human raised by gorillas, and as an adult you brought them home,
the first thing you do is jump up on your kitchen table and throw poop.
Right?
So, I'm not joking, that's what they do for, anyway, for domination.
So, this is, yeah.
So that's the, you see, the download.
The dog has the download and humans don't.
I believe that it's a necessity.
In other words, to escape the pitfalls of what you see in history
and what we see outside your door or in your family or wherever you see it.
It's a necessity.
And because it's a necessity, it will come.
You know, the universe always brings all necessities, always.
You know, meaning the construct that we're in, you know.
So, again, speaking of the construct, the dreaming thing has been coming up,
and I wanted to do more in depth.
We're not going to go in depth now.
Maybe I'll just make some quick statements.
I'd also refer to the Michio Kushi video that I posted in the chat.
The name of the video, I think I mentioned, is Spiritual Nature.
Actually, I should try to bring it up again.
But it's basically, the reason I brought it up is because he's a master teacher.
When he starts off the video, he shows how we're inside out plants,
how plants and humans are in common.
And I've always talked about how we're upside-down plants, right?
The root ball being the brain, the limbs are the limbs,
and the fruit or the flower is the sexual organ, right?
So we're basically in an upside-down stance.
If you take it further, because we also have the analog of a plant,
animals do as well, but they're at 90 degrees versus us, right?
They're horizontal. We're vertical.
They also have the analog or the archetype.
We also dream because of the plant nature in us.
And I'll give you an example.
You know how you can go up to a plant and cut a twig off and prune it?
I garden, so I'd break off various greens if I don't want to deroot,
pull the whole plant out, right?
The plant actually thrives in many cases when you prune it, right?
Well, some people cut the flowers off, you know, different things.
Sure, why not?
Sure, and pruning is a necessity in a lot of the more domesticated agriculture.
You know, anyway.
Well, imagine you're in a dream and, you know,
someone comes up and cuts your arm off.
You're like, oh, why'd you cut my arm off?
Well, it's just a dream, see?
So we borrow that dream archetype from plants also,
and I'm being kind of affirmative about it.
Then when we move forward, okay,
skip a big juncture that we might get into in the future.
Now we dream when we talk about dreams and what are they and all that, right?
Well, we're anchored in that plant architecture
because, see, a plant is always in a dreamscape.
By the way, most of you are hallucinogenics,
and, you know, actually all of them were derived from what?
Plants, right?
Duh, right?
Of course, because you see the energy transfer through that dream world, right?
So we dream, and I believe that I'm affirmative on this,
that it goes back to the nature of plants,
that we are upside-down plants,
and we are contemplative beings,
and also the difference of a plant's intensity
to be a dreamer and a human's intensity is much more
because a plant can't move when there's danger, can it?
Not that easily.
Right?
Well, we can.
We don't need to suffer certain things,
and we literally biolocate, you know, move our biology somewhere else, right?
But we still have these dreams,
and these dreams now, because we have the ability to dream and do dreams,
some people don't, by the way, which I commend you,
and I don't, I've only been dreaming recently
because I've been going into other worlds
and trying to go back into this world with things that I'm doing,
this world meaning the collective,
entertaining it, I should say.
Parts of me are entertaining it.
But because, see, the plant is in a much more intense situation,
again, because it can't move, but we can move.
So we have to balance out our ability to not want to suffer certain things
by moving our location, you know,
whether it means getting up from your chair and walking three steps
or running or going to the other side of the world.
We have to blend that with the ability to dream also, you see?
So this is a big concept which I'm still investigating,
but the dream that we're in right now, what we call reality,
is still a dream. Why?
Because we still depend on plants.
So at one point, will we no longer depend on plants?
The dream question will be answered.
Dogs and cats appear to dream as well.
I mean, you know, I'm not inside of their heads,
so I don't know exactly,
but it appears to be that when they're sleeping,
they're having experiences, they're reactive, right,
to things that are seemingly incongruous with what's going on around them,
which I interpret as them dreaming.
Sure, sure, they do. Well, they depend on plants as well.
Everything here depends on plants.
If eating another animal, right?
As a matter of fact, we go back, you know,
you know the term pushing up daisies, right?
Right, right.
Yeah, so, yeah, it's all plant-dependent.
And when we do not,
the only way we will be able to really figure out dreams
in a succinct, objective way
is when we no longer are in an environment
that requires any dependency on plants.
It's just an interesting idea, and I'm working on more on it,
and I think it'll be a pretty good presentation.
Well, another thing to work into that when you do it
is the cycle, right?
Because eventually the decayed or the remains of the animals
go back into the earth and do what?
Create plants also.
Not necessarily, though.
If you are in the desert, by the way,
if there are no plants present,
you know, if you buried someone in the Sahara Desert 400 years ago,
you dig them out, they look like they were only dead for two months, right?
They would not decay at all.
Very little, because of the dry.
But if there are plants in the area,
they will decay and go back to the earth.
Well, this goes back to where the body belongs to the earth,
but the plants are sort of like the archetype also,
you know, the secondary.
Once you were conceived,
if your mom did not intake earth elements,
you would not be formed.
And then once you're done here,
you go back to earth elements.
So the physical body, this is a very...
I'm trying to abandon the notion
that we solely depend on the, you know,
this body solely depends on the earth,
which it really does,
and just go into the dream side.
But when you hit that,
the dependency on plants prevents to go any further,
you see, until we do.
Yeah, that's why I was going to ask.
The next thing is, what about the fungus,
the spores, the mushrooms, right?
Those are not plants.
The fungus is not an animal, it's not a plant.
They don't know what it is.
Yeah, that's why I was going to ask you where that fits,
because it seems to me as though, again,
it's part of both things, right?
I was thinking about the decay in the desert.
Sometimes you find a lot of fungus
and things like that which will grow,
and it does end up decaying.
Well, a yeast, a proper yeast, a high-grade yeast,
will go into crystalline form for thousands of years
and then come back out of that crystalline form, right?
So crystal is the most stable structure.
No, right, but I'm just saying energetically, though,
at some point in the cycle, again,
fungus, spores, these kinds of things also have to be in there,
and they are separate from the plant or the animal,
and yet they're ingested by both,
and they are produced by both, it seems like to me.
Oh, right, your body produces fungus.
Your body produces everything,
even uranium in the cells, yeah.
Right, well, through induction.
Yeah, exactly.
Again, induction, again, we're not free enough.
We have not freed ourselves enough.
By the way, Greek-speak is what it is.
It's a chisel and a hammer, right,
to break away all this stuff that we're not free from.
I'm not saying it's revolutionary,
because, by the way,
revolution is always done by the same people.
Whenever you hear revolution, you go dig deep enough,
and you see it's this new boss, same as the old boss.
The real revolution, the real change is to not participate,
but not drop out.
Just don't endorse what you see going on around you, right?
You could still use it, but use it conditionally, right?
So the whole thing with Greek-speak
is to let's just get to not necessarily the bottom of it,
but get to what it can be in good form,
in its best form.
How can it be explained?
Well, it seems to me that people that claim to seek revolution
really are in search of evolution.
They do seek to become better
and to increase their quality themselves, right,
the quality of their life, the quality of the things around them.
So it seems to me as though they wish to evolve
is more of an accurate description as opposed to...
Yeah, evolve more than...
Yeah, revolve, revolution is to go around the circle.
You know, there's a famous political circle.
Yeah, there's your hit, revolve.
What do you do when you revolve?
You never want to partake in any revolution at all,
because it's a scam.
All the revolutions have been scams.
The only way to really create change
is stop using the things that harm you.
Oh, what a simple concept, right?
Yeah.
And only use the things that benefit you and others.
Very simple.
So, getting to the nuts and bolts of it.
Yeah.
I could just rehash a conversation I had about the pandemic
with some people, professional people,
and their mouths were hanging open
on how simple it is to debunk something.
And I think I've gone through that before,
so it's not necessary.
But again, it seems like they were in a dream state
and still are, as we all are.
And the common expression, right,
is, you know, are you awake?
Are you aware?
You know, it is a lot about dreaming,
and it's funny because...
Hold on.
When you awake from one dream,
you're waking into another dream now.
That's because we're still tied into it, you see.
I find that to be one of the most annoying experiences,
by the way,
is you think you woke up when you're in a dream state
and you haven't come back to, you know,
what I understand as conscious, right?
And you almost get tricked for a moment.
Did I wake up or did I not?
Sometimes it's difficult to tell.