Rated Y, Sonic Advent 2.2.3, and
that's the way this is.
Okay.
Anyway, Greek, how you doing today?
All right.
Kind of, yeah.
You said we have a lot of questions.
Let's get to it.
Yeah, we do have a ton of questions,
and just quickly, to make sure that people
understand this.
I'm not skipping anybody's question, but some things
are personal.
Why do I say that?
Because right at the top of the question
list, somebody asks about understanding their daughter, and
I'm not even going to bother to read
the rest of it, because it seems to
me like it's something where you would have
to talk to the Greek specifically, directly, because
it's something that would involve diagnosis, and I'm
sorry.
I don't want to do that on here,
because ...
Right, right, if it's too specific.
Some specifics are actually general.
We'll go to that.
And some specifics are too specific.
Got it.
Right, and I'm just covering that, because people
might wonder how it is I filter this
stuff.
I try to bring every single thing you
guys ask, but you've noted I've combined questions
for you guys, and there is a ton
of them this time, which we may break
into two Sonics.
There's so many.
Okay?
So I'm just letting you guys know that
at the top.
All right, anyway, next question.
What is the best way to deal with
an upset stomach?
See, that's general.
Upset to the point where you drink a
little water and feel like you're going to
throw up.
What they call stomach flu, in quotes.
This thing can last for days.
If there's a trick to recover quickly from
it, do you know of one, Greek?
Yeah, well, let me just preface by saying
there's more and more people in recent times
that are getting that, including myself to some
point.
Well, maybe it's because I'm being subjected to
a lot of heat, Arizona, in August is
every day over 105, 110, but no, that's
a common thing.
The stomach is a very interesting, it's like
a sensor.
You have sensor area in your mouth, in
your nose, and if it bypasses that, your
stomach will act like a sensor, right?
True, and anything in a container, including the
container of the human body, is subject to
its environment.
We must admit that, despite the fact that
the media lies to us all the time,
reports like this is the hottest day we've
ever recorded on the planet may be true.
Well, yeah, we know anything they report to
the public is already predetermined, right?
Oh, yeah, but I'm saying that they don't
lie 100% of the time.
And they may be reporting the high temperature,
because you dummies are going to notice it's
hot.
Well, yeah, the global warming is always in
the summer.
Yeah, right.
No, okay, so my point here with the
stomach is, let's take it from this point,
it's kind of like being a mechanic now.
You know, a good mechanic will hear a
car going down the street and say, oh,
that guy's power steering pump is bad, right,
versus it's making that noise, right?
Or they hear somebody turn a corner and
they go, you know what that is, brakes
and power steering fluid.
Or your axle if you're clicking somebody, okay,
so here that you have the sensors, which
are there, we have very poor senses, by
the way, you know, they we only see
a very tiny percentage of visible light only
hear a very small percentage of sound, small
percentage of and that goes also for taste
and smell.
Right.
And, right.
So like dogs can smell through concrete, pretty
much.
So right.
The way we sense what's coming into the
body is most likely through the nose, because
it'll usually pass the nose before it goes
into the mouth.
It's like a, it's like a hood, you
know, like a kitchen hood over your oven,
right?
You notice that the nose protrudes over the
mouth.
So you'll get the olfactory nostrils right over
what's right before it goes into the mouth.
If it passes the olfactory, it goes into
the mouth, then the mouth, you have taste
buds all over the place, their taste buds
in the back of the throat, right?
Some all years, we'll tell you that.
And then if it passes that, it gets
to the stomach.
And the stomach has a very interesting setup,
where there's something called a gag reflex, or
whatever, you know, or beyond the gag reflex,
what is it?
Is it a reflex when people see something
that actually makes them throw up?
What is that called?
Anyway, there's a term for it regurgitation, you
will anyway, so when it gets to the
stomach, if it passed the nose and the
taste, the stomach will eject it, right?
If it doesn't pass the stomach, right?
For you know, emotion, you know, years ago,
people saw a really something really gross, they
would throw up, right?
Just from visual.
So that's the stomach, because by visually throwing
up, you're not getting an olfactory and an
oral sensory pass.
I wonder...
Well, quickly, any one of the senses could
trigger that, because some people hear a sickening
noise, they tell you, it made me sick
to my stomach to hear that noise.
Yeah, it could be that as well.
Yeah.
So but the stomach will react to, yeah,
like, like, like you said, it will depend
on everything else and make its own decision,
let's say.
So let's keep that in mind, because we
don't consider the stomach to be, let's say
to have that kind of function, right?
It does.
So when it's when it's just the stomach,
and it's going to eject something, it's out
of tune.
In other words, if it passed the olfactory
and the oral taste, and it got into
the stomach, there's something probably that's odorless, but
the stomach senses it chemically, energetically and all
that, right?
The other thing that you could have is
a is a what they call an amoeba,
a bug, a parasite in the stomach, it
doesn't go past the stomach because it won't
survive.
By the way, if you go past the
duodenum or the duodenum, small intestine, large intestine
called those parts that I just mentioned in
the GI tract, the gastrointestinal tract don't have
that function that I just mentioned.
So be careful with your stomach.
In other words, be careful, because if you
can tune into it, it will actually save
you a lot of it actually, the feedback
from the stomach can be used to tune
the olfactory and the oral, right?
So things you normally wouldn't smell or taste
before, because you're tuned into how sensitive the
stomach can be for anyone, you can retune
your olfactory and your oral.
Now, give you an example, when I traveled
at one point, I drank some water from
a spring that wasn't really a good spring.
And I felt like someone kicked me in
the stomach for like two months in a
row.
And I told someone where I was, oh,
you got an amoeba, you know, it was
pond water, you know, and basically sat in
stomach, what I did was I took charcoal
pills for that, right?
And it was gone in two days.
And so I would say that having a
stomach issue can be actually two things.
One is it's rejecting because it's just out
of whack, like they say, or you have
an amoeba or something sitting in there that
is making anything that goes in there irritating
to the stomach.
Or it could be a toxification or something
that landed there and is coating the stomach
or whatever.
Typically, if it's a short, whenever you have
a short onset of something, doing nothing is
the best thing and doing what's known to
be good for you.
Typically, if you have a cure-all or
whatever, like typically teas, right?
Don't dehydrate or starve yourself, what will be
your favorite tea?
Stay away from teas.
When I say teas, by the way, tannin,
teas with tannin, you know, that look dark
are not medicinal.
They can be very rarely, that's a whole
other subject, where when do tannin, tannic acids
become medicinal.
But an herbal tea, a light tannin like
a chamomile or ginger or whatever, usually to
soothe that and see how that results for
you.
Because typically, most stomach issues are a sensory
problem.
It takes a lot to really mess up
your stomach.
So yeah, and do whatever, see, there's so
many things, like for example, I was speaking
to someone the other day about discomfort, is
they always give a chemical or physical reason.
But ultimately, because nothing goes in and out
of our body, it's all by induction, it
gets teleported to the inside and teleported to
the outside as waste product.
It's induction, it's about tuning the field.
It's like a radio device that's out of
whack, again, you have to tune it.
So typically, when you're not feeling well, or
you have an infirm condition coming on, you
will have, for most people, the craving could
be so short that you don't notice it.
You can crave something unusual that you tend
to like anyway, for half a second.
And that's what's going to fix you very
much like the bladder produces the anti-venom
when you have a venom, the body subject
to a venom.
Like if you're bit by a poisonous snake,
typically, I'm doing what Grey's Anatomy does, typically
most likely, presumptive language here.
The antidote of the venom is produced in
the bladder, but you only got 30 seconds
to a minute to apply it, a little
bit in your orally and then on the
area.
The bladder produces it.
So typically, when the body is infirm, it
will give you a signal, a mental signal,
eat this dummy.
That's where I did the, what I had
the circus flu, long story, it's in a
previous sonic, it's been brought up many times
over a year ago, a piece of a
really fine chocolate or finer chocolate and some
wine.
And I went to bed and three hours
later, I woke up and I was fine
as if nothing happened.
I was wrestling this thing for like five
days.
So it could be something odd.
Like if you're craving a pickle, a cucumber
pickle, a sour pickle, you're not feeling just
take a bite of that and it'll retune
the body.
This is, again, where when you have a
research, real research being done on the induction
side of the body, we can figure out
things where you can actually in the future
take a pill.
Right.
But the pill has a little dial on
it.
You tune it.
Right.
I mean, you can imagine what can be
done.
Right.
So.
Yeah.
But anyway, that's that's what I have to
say about stomach stuff.
Well, and a universal basic apothecary could be
developed, like you mentioned charcoal, which is another
funny thing.
Call back to an earlier sonic.
We don't usually put charcoal.
But if you eat some charcoal in there,
you might have an allergy.
Calories have no effect unless you're pooping charcoal
because it has to be reduced to charcoal
to have any caloric measurement.
That's.
Yeah, that's the joke.
So anyways.
Yeah.
So I think that's that's excellent.
Thank you for that.
OK.
If the gods created the reality we live
in, how did these dark entities take over
the whole thing?
All right.
I'm going to.
Well, who says they're dark?
That's how they're labeled.
Right.
Well, they appear to be malevolent to most
people.
And a lot of people have this idea
that the gods aren't.
Which.
Yeah.
Well, here's the thing.
Like, for example, give me an example.
I recently was out and I started talking
about the financial stuff and some people got
really pissed off.
Oh, yeah.
Deb, it pisses them off when you break
their paradigms.
Really, really.
Yeah.
Sorry.
Really quick consolidation to this question, though, is
they want to know if this is some
sort of game here.
Like if we're actually just game pieces on
a board and that's all there is to
this.
So go ahead.
Well, a game.
What is a game?
Most of the games are a reflection of
activities, opportunities or conditions that you have every
day.
Social, cultural, whatever.
Like, for example, the Monopoly game board.
What was that was based during the Depression,
you know, acquiring property seemed useless and hopeless
at the time.
So they made a game board to so
you can experience, you know, the passion was
no longer a serious thing.
Yeah.
I put Atlantic City in the mix.
I mean, those are literally the streets there
and everything else.
We have the risk.
You have all these game boards.
What are they?
They always represent.
Battleship is another one.
Oh, right.
Right.
Chess, checkers, bridge, all these things represent a
lot of people speak on, you know, international
politics is a chess game.
It's not.
It's actually a bridge game because chess, you
have one versus the other.
And always when you have international conflict or,
let's say, incidents, it's always a partnership.
Allies are involved.
So well, there's more like bridge.
Well, there's a guarantee of a triangulation.
And then there's partnerships where you have teams,
which would be bridge more than chess.
You hear a lot of people say, oh,
yeah, they're playing 3D chess.
No, it's not.
Very rarely do you see chess in the
open political scene.
It's always a game of bridge.
But so.
So, again, I'm giving the game analogy.
Yes.
Only if you take the game analogy the
way we just mentioned, because if you say
it's a game, it sounds like children's whatever.
Right.
It's not.
It's games are.
What would you say?
Would they be a reflection, a representation of
real things or scenarios or events or incidents
or whatever?
So, yes, in that context, it's a game.
Yeah.
There's simplified methodologies for representation of real world
things.
Right.
I mean, that would be.
But what I'm trying to like overshadow and
get away from is when you say game,
are you playing games?
It means like it's frivolous and whatever.
No, games are not frivolous or whatever.
But that's how the language is used.
Right.
Just like the word nice is used to
connote something and it means something else.
I would suggest here the meaning of a
game is to represent larger, bigger events and
things that are very serious.
So it's a serious game.
And then they got things like you play
stupid games, you win stupid prizes, you know,
saying things like that, cliche stuff.
So, yeah, it would be a game in
that context.
But who's malevolent?
You know, when a bank is robbed, the
robbers are considered malevolent.
But when the robbers get busted by the
cops, the cops are malevolent to them.
Right.
You can see how religions battle it out.
One one venerated God on one side is
the enemy of the other.
And yeah, that's really difficult.
Well, you know, here's the thing.
In the large scheme of things, there's no
good and bad openly.
It's about things making balance.
Give another example.
In Star Wars, people think it's the dark
side of the force versus the light versus
the light kind of force.
No, it's not.
If you even study the lore that the
writ of Star Wars, not just the film
or listen carefully.
It's not about light versus dark in Star
Wars.
It's the it's out of what out of
balance.
Right.
The light, the Jedi, the good Jedi never
wanted to get rid of the Sith or
all these other.
It's about putting it in balance.
It's when the dark side started overcoming.
I was out of balance.
So when you say malevolent or good or
bad, it's it's not good when it goes
out of balance.
Let's just put it that way.
It's a balancing act.
So what's good or bad is what you
pick.
Like, you know, if you go to the
Bible Belt or the buckle of the Bible
Belt, Muslims are bad.
Oh, yeah.
Right.
So and if you read so.
But if you go to a country that
is Islamic, by the way, Persia is not
Islamic.
And I've been watching what they're doing there.
And it would be quite good to eliminate
Islam out of Persia or Iran because it's
not an Islamic country.
Never was.
Never will be.
The people there, they just whatever.
So, you know, get your your sights on
how things are viewed internally and from the
inside out and from the outside in.
And you'll see there is no malevolent, really.
It's just a matter of is there a
balance.
Right.
So is death malevolent or benevolent?
Well, it's neither.
In my mind, it's it would be viewed
very much as malevolent.
She didn't even accept accepted as a fact
of life.
Yes.
If you want to understand these things, you
need to remove sentimentality from it.
Very simply, like if you stand facing another
person, ask them to hold up their left
hand.
Now, when they do that, that is on
the right hand side of the image you
are viewing.
The person you are.
Yeah.
I get it.
Right.
If one side's right is another appears to
be someone's left.
Yes.
That's just as simple as you can make
it, I think.
Yeah.
But let's let's say even from the biblical
thing, let's just go in.
In Job, Satan is walking around in a
heavenly court or a heavenly council.
Yeah.
And he's like, what are you doing?
Hey, I'll go down and mess with this.
This character is brought up and he's OK.
Go mess with him.
Well, if he's so malevolent, so bad, what's
he doing in the heavenly council?
Satan with.
Right.
You see what I mean?
Of course.
So it's not this.
The public has been over cheap dip, let's
say, or indoctrinated in the concept of it's
either good guys, bad guys, black and white.
You know, the winner loser.
There's this.
Right.
Cowboys who wear black hats, cowboys who wear
white hats.
You know what?
They're both cowboys.
Period.
There you go.
And black hats.
So that's a meme in the alternative media
and all that.
But yeah, when you get over that, then
you tend to accept the not.
Here's the thing.
I was going to say fear.
You know, a lot of people say don't
fear.
That's bullshit.
Everyone will always sense fear in certain conditions.
The real thing.
You know, you hear that.
Don't fear.
Right.
That's that's like having someone sit in one
place, like in a meditational lotus position position
and having them quiet their mind.
It's impossible because when the body is still,
the mind is racing.
Right.
So when someone says, well, when there's a
meme, no fear, that's total bullshit and that's
very disabling and it makes people crazy.
The real thing is, even with fear, can
you still function?
Right.
Because most people, what does fear do?
It disables you.
Right.
So can you remain able and as able
as you were, if you're not, you're under
fear.
That's the point.
So can you stay on the path and
the covenants and the things that you agree
to do, want to do, aspire to do,
live to do in the face of adversity,
which would be considered malevolent?
That's the point.
Can you function with how much malevolence?
For example, I see in the public, everything
is malevolent, coat sugar coated.
Right.
Does that mean that?
So what does that mean?
Well, I am so, let's say, planted and
firm.
I'm standing on what I know these things
are.
And you just go about, however, don't let
them affect you.
Right.
OK.
So from a previous Sonic on menopause for
women, it is good to increase quality yin.
Quality is young, but I read it depletes
yin long term.
Do you recommend saying that again?
What is your coffee?
OK, let me, let me begin again in
case I'm OK, in case I much mouthed
it a little bit.
Sorry.
OK.
Previous Sonic menopause for women.
It is good to increase quality yin period.
Coffee is young, but I read it depletes
yin long term.
Do you recommend to eliminate coffee in this
case?
Like in somebody who's menopausal, I guess.
Very personal.
Are you an upper or a downer person?
In other words, do you when you take
a downer like wine or any other chemical
downer, does it satisfy you more than an
upper or it doesn't matter either way?
That is, in other words, are you a
stimulant or a relaxant?
Right.
What would the opposite of a sedative?
It would be stimulant and sedative.
Right.
Well, yeah, that would be the there's another
term for it.
But yeah, it's a yes, sedative, sedative.
That's how they put it.
All right.
Sedative, sedative.
Yeah.
Which one are you?
Upper or downer?
Right.
So that's the first thing in your character.
And then the second thing would be the
quality of the coffee.
Give you an example.
I cannot drink inorganic coffee.
If I do, I have like this chemical
rush and I'm jittery and whatever.
For some reason, it's what they're spraying on
the coffee.
Maybe it's overharvesting.
When coffee is overharvested, it produces a lower
quality caffeine, kind of like the growers that
grow the cannabis.
They pick on the plant because it irritates
the plant.
When the plant is irritated, it makes a
higher supposedly THC content.
Right.
When coffee is overharvested, it does something similar.
So there's so many factors here.
Like, for example, if I were just to
drink non-organic coffee, I would probably not.
I would cut back on coffee to the
point where it was an irrelevant thought.
Right.
And so it all these things matters.
That's the fine point.
I wouldn't think coffee is such a big
issue unless you're like me that drinks like
ten cups of coffee a day, right?
So if you're a serious coffee drinker and
you consume a lot of it, switch to
a higher quality coffee and then throttle back,
see how you feel.
But things like menopause, a quality yin.
But remember, that part of the body, as
you go lower, that's more of the yin
part of the body.
As you go lower, where the feet are
the most yin.
So in order to attract an energy to
that part of the body, it has to
be yang, right?
So meat products and salts and minerals go
downward, right?
And the yin stuff, which goes upward towards
the yang part of the body, which is
the top of the head.
So it depends on what you want to
do.
Do you want to nourish that part of
the body and meaning the reproductive organs, right?
Then you would need something balanced, vegetable, grain,
whole grains, beans, fish, things like that.
So it depends on what you want to
do at the quote-unquote menopause stage.
Is it you're looking for nourishment?
Are you looking to counteract a condition?
We can get more personal on this, like
lubricity for women is an issue at that
point, right?
And sensitivity because of that, right?
So do you want to, you know, there's
so many factors, boy, oh boy.
And you know what?
If I was doing a consult with 10
different women, it would be almost five or
I assure you five to seven different remedies
and approaches.
So this is, but at least we brought
this up and give you a little more
of a concept of how to think about
it.
Yeah, no, fair enough.
And it's a big point.
Like, like, okay.
So when I took painkillers, they used to
give me energy.
I've seen other people turn into zombies.
Exactly.
Like, yeah, it's, it's like we said earlier,
if it's your character, right, right.
The first thing we mentioned is, are you
upper or a downer, you know, person, you
know, which, which, which suits you better, right?
Right.
So you've seen the depressed person drinking versus
the, you know, guys running around screaming and
yelling.
He's all energetic.
If they're drunk, even in a drunken state,
you have different types of people, you know
what I mean?
And yeah, alcohol is pretty universal.
Anyways.
All right.
In a, let's see, can we, oh, can
we get a sonic or segment of the
sonic dedicated to better understanding the cosmic ether?
Also would like to know the Greeks take
on the Trinity the Christians are always talking
about.
You could skip that one.
But yeah, the Trinity is something that's better.
Let's go backwards, because it is backwards.
There's no Trinity in the Bible.
It was injected later in one of the
New Testament books.
The Trinity, there's nothing wrong with that.
But if you study, let's say, let's say
the biblical Trinity, it's not father, son, Holy
Spirit, because the spirit is, is not, it's
not tangible.
It's the mind of the Godhead, right?
Spirit is mind.
So the real Trinity, believe it or not,
if you were to make it tangible and
have a real Trinity from a religious perspective,
theological perspective, let's say, by the way, religion
and theology are not the same.
And right.
So think about that for a minute.
You could pause and think about that and
in three hours, hit play again.
But anyway, yeah, religion and theology are not
the same.
The real Trinity is, you're ready, father, son
and man.
That's the real Trinity.
Right in the middle.
So yeah.
Anyway.
So OK, let's put that one aside.
What was the first part of the question?
Oh, yeah.
Back on the first part of the question
was they'd like to get a sonic dedicated
to better understanding the ether.
Oh, my gosh.
OK, what I would like to say on
that is, can you use something when you
don't really fully understand it?
Answer is yes.
Forget about all the mumbo jumbo and academic
bullshit.
Ask any physicist or electrical engineer or electrician,
electrical engineer, electronics engineer, what electricity is.
And you're going to get if you ask
100 people, you're going to get 100 variations
of something.
And you're going to say basically the the
most technical term to describe what all these
people that I asked what electricity was, was
bullshit.
None of them know.
But do we still use it?
Because we don't fully understand it, does it
mean we can't use it?
No.
And we do use it.
So and by the way, I mentioned electricity
is because you cannot understand electricity without comprehending
the ether.
And the electricity that we use is pressurized,
magnetically pressurized ether, static electricity.
And what makes the static electricity is the
ether.
The ether is not purely electric as there's
the five ethers you could look it up.
What are the five ethers?
You know, there's the life ether, chemical ether,
the heat ether, the light ether.
Right.
I think I left one out.
Yes, you did.
Yeah, they have different colors associated.
This was like a very much a Rudolf
Steiner.
Rudolf Steiner had a secretary and he wrote
the book after Steiner died, because Steiner was
such an asshole.
Oops, did I just say that?
He was afraid of over over criticism, you
know, Steiner would step on him so hard.
But anyway, I don't remember the name of
the book.
It's Man or Matter is something similar to
that.
Man or Matter, M A T T E
R.
You can get into ethereal experiments.
There's ethereal experiments that were done that were
supposedly debunked and whatever.
But they they redid them.
And there is an ether shift.
So that's all I'm saying.
All this stuff, it's like who who knows
what it is.
And I've mentioned before, we may never know
in this state that we're in because it's
really like a primary thing.
Like if you are a video game or
a video character, it's really hard to discuss
the pixels.
We cannot objectify it, but we can use
it.
And anyone who's been around for the weather
work webinar that I did can attest to
the fact that it is accessible.
Right.
I don't know.
Cosmic ether.
When you say cosmic, typically meaning all the
stuff out there.
When we say cosmos is a Greek word,
just means world.
But cosmic from the if you grew up
in the 70s, wherever billions and billions and
billions of.
Right.
So that was the Carl Sagan joke out
there.
I'll tell you what, though.
Tesla, the writings, which are very few of
his writings are on the Internet.
But I remember reading a bunch of Tesla
from Joe Blankenship's notes, whom he met Tesla
when he was a young man and then
people that were around Tesla and Tesla pretty
much figured out in his mind, he had
a very good mind that as you go
further up, like vertically in elevation and out
of atmosphere and so on and so forth,
the ether is more dense and more dense
and more dense to the point where, for
example, let's say you were able to go
to the moon.
It would be like walking through mud or
eventually it would be so dense to you
that it would be try to burrow through
a piece of steel.
You couldn't move.
And but you can see right through it.
See, that's also what makes gravity.
The ether is dense out there.
The earth is in a vacuum and it's
rushing in, pushing everything down.
So, oh, my gosh, I just had like
a whatever explosion.
What is the ether?
I can go on for four hours.
Stop it.
Where's the pause button on me?
OK, let's pause that because you did bring
up weather work and somebody did ask something
about they wanted to get their eight year
old involved in weather work.
And I thought that was kind of an
interesting thought.
But how would you start an eight year
old off on weather work?
The concept.
Well, eight year olds love seeing moving pictures.
So go go to YouTube or whatever and
type in Trevor James Constable weather engineering or
you don't have you've put in weather engineering.
Scroll down.
There's a couple of forty five minute one
hour videos.
Sit and watch that.
And Trevor is a very explanatory.
And he brings up the ether.
And that would be a good place to
start.
OK, but about weather work, though, for me.
Yeah, that's weather work.
OK, OK.
I just want to make sure I understood
in a recent lookout for Charlie.
He says that the Shuman and I'm thinking
he means shaman.
But anyway, residence residence has been hijacked.
So any psychic readings these days are not
trustworthy.
Do you agree?
No.
Let's just say early German, let's say post
World War one, the Nazis, right?
The Germans.
They did a lot of stuff, even with
experimentation, let's say, of all sorts, natural frequencies,
electrical stuff, microwave stuff, time machines, on and
on and on.
And they found there's nothing to be found
in their writings of any significance of the
Shuman frequency.
And I agree.
The Shuman frequency is not is not relevant
that much.
And psychic, I believe, is when you're being
the ethereal beings or non-physical entities don't
know what to do with you anymore, what
kind of mind to give you.
So they send someone to you that makes
you opens up the psychic part of you.
And so then you could see what's going
on before.
Yeah, but it's possible everyone is the same
psychic ability, by the way.
Yeah, I think we talked about our previous
sonics, right?
When they can't anticipate you anymore, they send
someone that helps you become psychic.
So it's external, again, being psychic.
So I wouldn't it would be a no
and no on both of those aspects of
that question.
OK, fair enough.
Look, here's probably one of the last things
we're going to get to maybe today.
But the predominant force in the environment in
cold weather when organizing your eating through the
dark and this and that.
OK, hold on.
The reason I'm going to condense this to
touch, because there's basically saying, look, when it's
cold outside, you know, but it's warm inside.
That's two different environments that you're dealing with.
Which one really counts or do they both
count?
OK, good answer.
He answered the same thing, which.
OK, let's just take this really slow, because
this is the kind of reasoning we need
to apply.
And it's so basic.
Remember, we're mid-level, mid-range thinkers.
We don't comprehend the simple or the complex.
Either end of the spectrum eludes us.
What's bigger in mass and size the inside
of your space or the outside?
That's obvious.
OK, so what's going on outside?
What's going on inside is the immediate comfort
point, like scratching your nose.
Oh, that feels better.
So when it's wintertime, that is the predominant
environmental condition.
And you go inside of your dwelling for
some comfort, right?
Right.
And that's that's really minimal compared to the
overbearing environmental condition.
And a good example is getting acclimated for
submariners.
Submariners think of the conditions.
Yeah, well, they're fine in the boat.
They call it a boat.
It's called the boat and they're fine in
there.
But their bodies change very much according to
where they are in the depths of the
of the water and how they're trying to
how fast it's traveling.
A lot of health issues, by the way,
with submariners because of that.
And it's never really been addressed.
Well, they address the symptoms, right?
Remember, all the pharmaceuticals address symptoms, not causes.
Yeah, so well, that's always the purpose to
mask the symptom as opposed to addressing the
issue, which, by the way, somebody asked about
parasites and look what kind of parasite.
You got to be more specific.
And also, if you don't understand the parasite,
how are you going to understand how to
kick it out?
It was too tight.
There's one that you that goes in through
the GI tract, which is the mouth to
the anus.
Right.
It goes in.
It actually could go, but either way, it's
external.
And it's just like a choo-choo train
going through the tunnel.
Just like that.
Right.
And there's the other type of parasite that
the body creates internally, just like in Star
Trek.
Right.
They push the button, get on the what
do they call the thing where they beam
you the transporter pad?
Yep.
And they transport it.
Actually, your body actually creates some of them.
Yeah, that's a really bad signal.
You know, just like in Star Trek, the
transporter, whatever is on one side can be
if it's broken down.
Right.
And then the signal is sent to the
other side and it's reassembled.
Right.
And it's an emergent.
There's a lot of stuff, by the way.
I've been speaking to some people in the
media about emergence.
Like they don't know how, for example, a
very high quality stainless steel water bottle.
You know, the you know, the big water
bottle fad.
People carry water bottles around.
They protect it more than maybe, you know,
years ago.
That was more popular, maybe.
Right.
And all the stainless steel ones developed a
real nasty fungus and mold and bacteria in
them.
And you're like, you know, why the glass
doesn't do that.
Right.
It's because it's an emergent.
In other words, it actually forms in the
water because of the stainless steel.
This is commonly known.
And that's the only steel bottles develop that.
Where does it come from?
It's the same water that we put in
plastic and glass.
It doesn't form in those same condition because
it's an emergent.
You have emergence, things that just appear like
biogenesis would be an idea.
This is way this sounds so freaky, you
know, to people.
But it's you can experiment with it and
see how it happens.