Rated Y, Sonic Event 129, Greek, little noise this time, how are you doing?
I'm fine, I just got in, I'm testing a new amp, and it's funny how these things you have to burn them in, all the circuits and all that,
that I have to do my upgrades, because believe it or not, these guys don't really understand electricity any more than I do,
but I think I'm a little better with it, so basically I use something called doping, doping is like when you coat something with something else,
right, to change its qualities, so I have a special doping formula I put on the circuitry, and it really, really improves it.
Nice, so do you make sure it's well shielded, because I hate it, I had many experiences with amplifiers as a musician.
Yes and no, yes and no, there's a balanced and unbalanced, shielding should only be where you need it,
because if you shield too much, you get inductance and it kills the sound.
I just like to block it so it's not picking up radio transmissions, you know what I'm saying, that kind of crap.
Well yeah, it also depends on the topography of the circuit, something like an old Krell KSA 150 is so massive,
or if you're using, anyway, look up Krell amplifiers from back in the day, Dan D'Agostino, he's a really good guy too,
but then you have the valve amps, which are tube amps, and those are so massive,
and the only place you'll get noise with those is what they do with the big amps still, is they pot them,
the toroid, the transformer is filled with asphalt bitumen, right, to damp it out.
But anyway, yeah, I'm an audio guy, and pretty soon I'll be doing a seminar on how to make counter space acoustic modules,
they work in rooms, they work in speakers, they work in cars, recently sent a pair out to someone,
it's a little flat, you know what those cheese cutting boards look like, you know, the small cheese cutting boards?
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, okay, they look like that, and you put it behind the speaker in your car, you take the speaker out,
and it's like the reports I've been getting back, it's amazing how clear the music sounds,
and I could be driving at 70 miles an hour, and the noise doesn't bother, and you can hear it right through it,
just more clarity, and how to do it inside of a loudspeaker, how to put it on a headphone,
that's a little more technical, because to put it on a headphone, it's a little earbuds, it has to be small,
the device has to be smaller than a grain of rice, and most people are not used to working on that scale.
Yeah, I hate that kind of thing anyway, even as I sit here with you, you know, I wear the old style,
you know, headphones like that we would get in the 70s, sort of, you know what I mean?
That's fine, those would be the size of a nickel, earbuds would be the size of a grain of rice,
for a home loudspeaker, the only problem with this in a home loudspeaker, is this creates a pseudo volume,
so now the box is too big, so you have to build a baffle, so let's say you have a cubic foot,
a cubic foot, 12x12x12 speaker, you put a module in there, the box is way too big now,
you just need a half of that, so you know what that would do for manufacturing, right?
You use half the material, right, and you have better sound also,
it's kind of like the scalerators to the water industry, this is what it would be for the audio industry,
but that's another discussion, I'm not that naive to think that these things that I've designed
and others have done that are going to help anyone, it's on a mass level.
Well, you never know, musicians might appreciate that though, like for instance,
I was just thinking, does it require four of these things if you have a cabinet with four speakers in it?
No, one.
You just need one.
It does a given volume, so if you have a three-way speaker with, let's say, a tweeter, a squawker,
you know, mid-range and a woofer, you need one for each one of those,
or if you have a cabinet with four, five, six, ten, twelve woofers, you just need one.
You just need one for every enclosure.
Now, some loudspeakers have four woofers and the enclosure has four separate sub-enclosures inside,
in that case, you would.
Oh, yeah, well, if you have a PA speaker that has more than one type of projection,
then you would need several, but if you have a singular type.
Sure, yeah, these are acoustic modules.
It also works on anything that vibrates that makes sound.
What it does is it creates a coherent counter-space.
It's kind of like, imagine architects design bathtubs with no drains, right?
This is what acoustic engineers are doing, and it's not a physical drain like a vent.
It has to do with counter-space.
Everything in nature recognizes where it has to be and what it has to do in space,
and it always creates or looks for a counter-space, just like when you're doing circuitry.
The ground, you know, the positive and the negative, the ground on a DC circuit,
or even AC circuit, is your counter-space, right?
So, anyway, just to take off from where we finished last, a quick segue is about how to turn a—
I'm going to be going over some notes and something else here.
I hope I can pull it up.
No problem.
Well, you did the smoothie recipe last time, too.
Yeah, about how to turn a bill into a check.
Now, the notes I'm going to be going over, just so anybody can do it, is someone asked that to ChatGPT.
A bill of exchange is a check, and I'm going to read what ChatGPT said, because ChatGPT gives you the whole thing.
So the question is, just real quick, now, I don't—first of all, going into this, just like I'm going to say now,
is like someone thinking they can cook because they heard one or two Greeks speak, and they don't have sharp knives,
they don't know proper kitchen hygiene and all the fine stuff and food combination.
You're not going to be able to cook, right?
Of course not.
You're going to need to prepare first.
You're going to need to have your tools, you know, and your space.
Yeah, so in order to do this, you really have to know about the bankruptcy.
You really have to know about March the 9th, 1933.
Google, if you put in March the 9th, 1933 right now, Google will set up a big paragraph for you in bold of what it was.
Would you do that?
Put in March the 9th, 1933, just as a date in a Google browser, and it will—you know how it gives you websites, time and date?
It won't give you any of that.
It'll give you a big paragraph about the banking holiday.
It's called Federal Reserve Discount and Banking Ordinances or something like that.
It says the Emergency Banking Act was a federal law passed in 1933, signed into law by President Franklin D. Roosevelt on March 9, 1933.
That's right.
But do they give you, like, an excerpt from it in bold?
I did not get an excerpt right away, no.
Oh, okay, just a link.
Is it a link, or they actually make a Google statement?
They give a Google statement.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
See, see, see how important that is?
Yeah, and then you have Ballotpedia.
You can go to Emergency Banking Act on Ballotpedia.
That's the first thing that comes up.
And Federal Reserve History is next, and that's at the—let's see.
Notice that's not a .gov address, by the way, the Federal Reserve, just saying.
No, it's not.
It's not.
Any government entity does not have to use postage.
So if you get a letter from the IRS, it's postage prepaid because it's not government.
Also, the IRS and Federal Reserve, in the telephone book, there's a government section.
They're not in the government section.
Yeah, it's what they call the franking privilege, right?
The ability to not—
Yeah, well, it's really simple.
This is for every country by the 1950s lost their—and put up their citizens in the other land.
They lost the country.
Every country's government lost the country in a card game with the central bankers by the 50s.
Canada was lost before the U.S. was lost, by the way.
They experimented there.
Just like, you know, they're experimenting on North Korea, you know, for 60 years.
They're just waiting.
There's no reason to end the experiment, right, because we're still experimenting.
So, you know, it's funny.
Americans are no different than North Koreans.
There was someone that went there in 2019, a French journalist, attorney,
and he asked one of the professors there, one of the colleges in North Korea or high school teachers,
said, if the government allowed you to travel, what countries would you like to visit?
This is in 2019.
And the North Korean teacher said, I would like to visit East Germany and the Soviet Union.
So he didn't know that those don't exist anymore.
This is how Americans are with this.
Americans do have no idea.
But let's go back to it.
How to turn any bill into a check.
This was asked to ChatGPT.
This is the question.
What is the proper way to endorse the back of a bill to legally convert it into a check?
Now ChatGPT answers back.
Endorsing the back of a bill, parentheses, such as a utility bill or invoice, close parentheses,
to convert it into a check involves specific steps to ensure it meets the requirements of negotiable instruments
under the Uniform Commercial Code, UCC.
Here's a detailed guide.
Steps to endorse a bill as a check.
Write the payee information, one, which is to the order of, on the back of the bill,
and write, in quotes, pay to the order of, name of the payee, usually the person or entity you want to pay.
Then it has number two, endorse the bill, your signature.
By the way, when you ever hear signature, it means you're signing your signatory.
It means it's not you.
When someone wants you, they ask for an autograph.
So all the governments, all the corporations, all the banks ask for a signature because you're signing for the all-caps name,
which is not a straw man.
It's a public corporation that was started.
You can find when it was started on the long-form birth certificate.
The long-form birth certificate application has all the information, when you were born, time and date.
And then it has a date when it was received by a public official.
That's when you went, that's when the all-caps public corporation was started.
Isn't the paper thing, it's the date it was reported because it's usually reported by the mother?
No, it was the date it was received by a public official on the form.
And then that's when the all-caps name started, that corporation.
So you can actually, if you have that information, you could say all-caps, you could say the public corporation that was started on,
and it's usually three days to two weeks after you were born.
Don't call it the straw man because it's not a straw man.
It's actually a public corporation.
That's why when you understand the back of a social security card has another set of numbers,
you can get a routing number from the treasury.
Just call them and get a routing number and then put those numbers in.
You could pretty much go to a car and buy a car, buy anything you want with it.
It works sometimes.
And later on when they audit it, a couple of years later, some attorney general will say,
that was fraudulent. You were using public funds for that.
You have to go to jail now.
Get it? Public funds.
And people agree, they don't know.
The attorney general doesn't know any law at all.
If he did, he wouldn't be there.
Anyway, so I just wanted to bring up, so your signature, that was okay too.
Endorse the bill.
Your signature below the pay-to-the-order-of quote line, sign your name.
This signature endorses the bill and makes it payable to the named payee.
Remember, this is all chat GPT now, right?
This is taking, what I'm saying, attorney bill.
A gas bill, a phone bill, a mortgage payment, whatever.
They send you those vouchers, coupons.
Detach this and send this in with your payment.
In the negotiable, okay, there's a dunning law.
You know, when you send someone a bill, it's called your dunn.
You dunn them, D-U-N-N-E-D.
It's a dunning.
There used to be something called dunning report,
which is like bills that were sent to the government.
Anyway, this is older language.
They stopped using the language in the 70s.
You know, when I say that, I remember those days.
That's fucking 50 years ago, right?
Yeah.
So, 74 is 50 years ago.
Wow, I remember.
Anyway, yeah, so when you get dunned,
one of the things in the laws was written that if you, in a credit-based economy,
and you send someone a bill, you also have to give them the voucher
or the check to pay for it.
And payment consists of them agreeing, receiving, and signing it,
and then you receiving it back, right?
So anyway, okay, so to endorse the bill,
the next step from CHAT-GPT is restrictive endorsement, optional.
For additional security, you can add a restrictive endorsement,
such as for deposit only to the account.
Use the account number on the bill, quote.
This restricts the checks that could only be deposited for that specific account,
which is actually very important because they'll take it and use it.
They'll go to Vegas and use it or whatever, and they'll tell you they never got it.
And it won't show on the books that they ever got it
because they didn't apply it to your billing, right?
Number three, include.
Remember, this is all CHAT-GPT now, right?
Number three, include important information, which is the date, right?
The date of the endorsement, right?
So you write that next to the endorsement, right?
Amount.
If not already clear on the face of the bill, indicate the amount being endorsed.
Now, you have to write the amount also in words, just like you do on a regular check.
A lot of people that – if you don't have success –
I've seen people who have not had success, they did not write it out just like you write a check.
So 500 would be F-I-V-E-H-U-N-D-R-E-D, right?
And no cents or whatever cents, right?
All right, okay.
Example endorsement.
This is still CHAT-GPT.
Suppose you are converting utility bill to a check to pay John Doe.
Let's see.
Where am I?
I lost my place here.
Okay.
What happened?
It disappeared.
Suppose you are converting a utility bill to a check to pay John Doe.
Pay to the order of John Doe, your signature, date, and then amount
if you want to add a restrictive endorsement.
Okay.
It ends there.
We can keep going.
Did you get that last part?
So, okay.
Suppose you are converting utility bill to a check to pay John Doe.
That means that – let's say I get a utility bill for $127.46.
The voucher on the bottom.
I could write all those things on it and write pay to the order of Chuck O'Chelley on it.
You could go and cash that.
My utility bill.
Now that – you really want to flip a normie's head out?
That's a mind-bender.
Right.
It's not actually if you understand the negotiable instruments acts.
So in other words, Chuck, you could get all your bills, tear off the vouchers on the bottom,
endorse them a certain way, give them to me, and I could go cash them.
Cash them so I could go buy cigarettes and coffee.
Right.
With your bills.
Yeah.
Okay.
I get what you're saying.
It's just it's a mind-bender though because that's –
Yeah.
It is because you've never heard of it before, but this is what's being done all the time.
That's why you don't get – if you have a checking account, you don't get them back in the mail like you used to.
And they said it was the Paperwork Reduction Act of 2003 or 2002 after 9-11.
No, they're taking all of those and they're bundling them up into funds and they're called NPIs.
NPI stands for non-performing instrument and they still have a value.
So all those vouchers that people are sending in unendorsed from their gas bills, phone bills or whatever, they're unendorsed.
So they're NPIs, non-performing instruments.
They stack them up until they get 100 million of them.
Now, the number sounds impressive.
I got 100 million of NPIs.
How much can we put them on the market for?
I could put them on the market for 1.5 million.
Okay.
One and a half percent.
Do you see where I'm going?
Do you see?
Yeah.
It's like the old days when they told you that coupons had like a two-cent value.
Oh, yeah.
Well, look.
I remember in the 80s I had some coupons and something – it was an old coupon.
Because some coupons can go six months, usually no more than three months.
And something had gone on sale.
It was a coupon for $5 off.
It went on sale for $4.79.
I gave them the coupon.
They gave me 29 cents, 31 cents change.
Because it's – right?
It's actually – right.
Also what I suggest if you're going to get more into this, what you put on the bill, if you're going to endorse it, use it as a check.
I had a few more phraseology.
I'll just throw some of it in right now.
One thing you should put on there is void war prohibited by law.
Write that on there too.
Right?
That makes sense, right?
So let's say some scumbag attorney wants to come after you for it and he says it's the law.
Well, it's void if you say it's against the law because it says it right there and without recourse.
And also Title 12.
You write 12 U.S.C. 411, demand for lawful money.
That takes you out of there too.
Now, remember, the attorneys do not know this.
You know how I say attorneys do not know it.
OK.
Segway.
Utility bills.
Everyone's utility bills have gone up anywhere between 30% and 80% if you're talking about insurance, fire insurance and all that other stuff, right?
Why?
Because all these companies have now put their billings – they've sold them to financial companies under what's called a CTO.
I've talked about this before.
A CTO is a rule from the SEC that CTO stands for a confidential treatment order.
That means if you have, like, money coming in, you can make a secret deal with someone that they get all the money coming in and they kick you a certain percentage up front.
And that's what all the utility companies – not all, but most utility companies are doing with private investment firms.
And if you go to them, they will – no matter what you do, they will not disclose that they're doing it because it's under CTO protection.
So the only way to fix that is by getting about 20%, 30%, 40%, 50% of the people to boycott paying their bills and give a reason why.
So now the people that they sold the future billings to will say, hey, wait a second.
How come no one's paying their bill?
We don't want this anymore.
They kick it back to the utility companies and all the prices come down to how they were being even cheaper because right now with automation and efficiencies and new equipment, your utility bills should be coming down.
Right.
Because they're using – right?
They're using things automated where a power plant that needed a staff of 30 people now just needs one or two because it's automated.
And also they have more efficient equipment.
So the bills should be coming down, but they're going up because of this reason.
So the reason I mention this is there is absolutely no hope in any of this getting better because of the reasons I'm mentioning out here.
There was a bunch of well-dressed guys walking around the neighborhood the other day and I saw them pass by the bay window and the picture window in the living room.
I said, oh, I'll get that before you get knocked on the door.
And he wanted to just basically talk to me about billing.
Now, they're doing a survey like how people feel about billing and if your billing is too high, maybe we can do assistance.
I said, wait a second.
Wait a second.
I said, do you know about – I gave him the CTO thing.
I said lawyers don't know the law.
He pulls out this thing.
He's a lawyer.
He used to be a lawyer.
Not anymore.
A young guy who worked as a lawyer for ten years.
And I gave him the Greek-speak law and he was just like laughing in his office.
Exactly.
So this is the first time I've met someone who's an ex-lawyer that's not selling cars.
I just wanted to bring this up.
That's right because you said they're always the ones that are selling cars.
They're always selling cars, yeah.
And that doesn't mean used car salesmen.
New or used.
This is the first time I've ever met a lawyer, ex-lawyer that is now doing surveys, but it's still financial stuff.
He worked for judges.
I said judges, all judges are failed attorneys and he's laughing and he's like, oh my gosh, exactly right.
And all that he just confirmed – most lawyers, especially ones that I know that are no longer in the field, it's a sore spot.
If I bring it up with them around, they'll say, oh, that's an evil organization.
I don't want to talk about it.
This guy was fresh out and he – anyway.
I just wanted to bring that up.
It was fun.
OK.
I do the same with doctors, by the way.
They all flip out.
If a doctor or a lawyer wants to debate me, you're going to have to get all the lawyers and all the doctors, not just you,
and all their friends and they're still going to lose.
That's how bad it is.
Right.
As a matter of fact, I've had a professor that wanted to debate me once and my friend was there with his daughter who was in the eighth grade.
He said, I'm not going to debate you.
She's going to debate you.
I'm going to coach her for 10 minutes on the subject and she'll still win.
Oh my gosh, the guy was so infuriated.
It was true.
The guy was a no-wade and didn't know anything about anything.
So now everything we just mentioned now, let's go back to the negotiable instruments, how to turn a bill.
Now when I say a bill, it's the voucher.
Yeah.
When they send a bill, it's a thing.
It's a cutaway.
Sometimes it has a dotted line.
It even has a little picture of a scissor.
Detach this and send it in with your payment.
That is the payment.
Well, it's not the payment until you make it a payment.
OK, that's what we're talking about.
Now when this is received at the envelope openers that open this, whether it's machine or human, they don't know anything.
And their supervisor doesn't know anything.
And their supervisor, I assure you, if you have 1,000 or 2,000 people working in that company, maybe on a good day, one or two people might be available that know what's going on.
That's how bad it is.
Like if you go down to the court building, there's maybe one or two people out of all the hundreds of employees that know what's going on.
Then we've talked about this, especially since 9-11.
They've been really stomping on making people that deal with the public to not know anything about things work.
So if you're going to have success, you can't call up or go down, let's say, to places where you can pay in person and talk to that person about anything, anything.
They are no different than what someone ate for dinner last night.
In other words, if they're working in a government office or you chop them up and serve them for dinner, there's no – they're not much smarter than what someone ate for dinner last night.
That's the level of mentality they have, right?
OK.
So you cannot – it's like going and arguing with a hamburger.
They don't know anything.
There's nothing there.
There's absolutely nothing there.
OK.
Because look, do you think they're going to be working for $18 to $20 an hour or even $30 an hour to pay whatever they're doing if they knew this?
No.
No way, right?
That's your giveaway, right?
Yeah.
OK.
That's what Brandon Joe Williams, again, the serial mention, he keeps bringing this up too.
That's why he's on the right track.
But they're going to show him his hat and they're going to show him his ass soon enough.
Not soon enough.
They usually give you about a year or two because they want to see who's going to follow.
So he needs to get his following going.
So go ahead and support him however you can by subscribing.
All his stuff is for free, by the way.
He gives everything away for free.
So go ahead and whatever.
Use his stuff.
I absolutely – I don't endorse it because he's leaving out some pretty like soft white underbelly stuff, right?
But I think that if you do what he does and the stuff that I've said about signing things void, void were prohibited by law.
You've all heard that void were prohibited by law.
They even put it in ads, right?
Yeah.
You put that on an instrument also without recourse.
So they try to come back with you and they say, well, that doesn't matter that you wrote that.
Of course it does.
Remember, attorneys are there to make people's lives miserable.
That's all they're there for.
They don't know – they're like worms and fleas and parasites.
They do exist.
Cockroaches or – cockroaches are not that bad.
They clean up.
But there are things in mosquitoes.
There are things here to pester humanity.
An attorney, that's all they do.
That's all they do.
You should see – you can have fun if you have competence in the law and legal, which is not hard to do.
You could study for five minutes a day and be more competent than all the attorneys in the country because let's say you're a lawyer.
You study law for five minutes a day for a month.
You'll know a certain amount of law, which is more than all the attorneys in the country put together.
So let's say you have a country with three million attorneys.
What's three million times zero?
It's still zero.
So they don't know anything.
It doesn't matter how many attorneys there are or which one.
They don't know anything.
By the way, I tell even this attorney.
I said ten years ago I started saying I'll give any attorney $1,000 for each law that they could cite.
It's context and define all the terms in that particular law.
I'll give them $1,000 for each law they can cite.
I still have the $1,000.
I've told this to every attorney I've ever met.
They try to cite laws and they won't even take the challenge because they know.
So if anyone says they're studying law, I said, oh, in Costco, right?
So this is how bad it is.
Now are people going to clean it up?
No.
But am I going to go down in history hopefully as one who said it should be cleaned up and this is exactly how and why?
Yes.
That would be nice, right?
And I mean it in the foolish, stupid, and senseless way.
Now the medical people are just as bad because talking to someone, neurosurgeon, young guy, quick.
And the whole thing was they always have these older doctors in there to kind of guide the younger guys before they go into residency and further training.
And they constantly remind them you're becoming a doctor to ease the suffering and pain of people.
Not to heal them or fix or give them help, right?
You see what I mean?
Do you see the difference?
Yeah.
Okay.
So it's very, very important.
They're just as bad.
Now the other thing about the doctors, I've never had one argue with me when I bring up induction and there's no absorption and the heart is not a pump.
No arguments there at all.
They just sit there like a three – like a four-year-old listening.
So that's not so bad.
But it is bad.
You don't want to – and also, by the way, another thing that doctors do when they're trying to learn, they ask their patients various questions.
Let's say you're an osteopath or whatever and you do all these surgeries on the body and you ask – you do your own personal surveys on what the people's lifestyle is like.
And you think you're amassing a group, a body of information that you could use.
And I'm saying you can't because the species of human that goes to a doctor and relies on is completely different species than those that don't.
So if a doctor keeps asking his patients broad general questions to develop a body of knowledge, that is not going to be a good body of knowledge because the first thing is these people that go to these guys for their health are not complete humans.
In other words, you're not going to get anything.
You need to go to those that do not go to doctors and survey them, right?
Do you see the point?
The same with attorneys.
Surveying people, why they go to – it's too late.
I mean those are not – the people that go and use attorneys or doctors are a completely different species.
Their opinions and how they live has nothing to do with reality.
They are a subdued, almost second or third class type human.
I do everything I can to absolutely avoid doctors and attorneys or lawyers in any way, shape or form.
Yeah.
The false – so the level of falsehood you're going to get – so you're already dealing with an inferior mindset is what I'm saying.
Right.
So forget – there used to be a commercial.
It's four out of – three out of five doctors surveyed recommend dentine.
I see it on TV or something like that.
Trident.
Trident maybe, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh my gosh.
So that kind of bullshit is still going on.
Yeah.
Anyway, there was something else I wanted to continue from last week that was kind of critical and if it was that critical, why did I not remember?
It had to do with what we brought up.
The bill of exchange thing, guys – by the way, it's on the same subject.
The bill of exchange thing, you really got to know, especially we have an international crowd.
Find out when the central banks started monetizing – collateralizing – the government started collateralizing the birth certificate.
When did the social security numbers start to be issued to people?
Because they issued them in the US in the early 20s and they didn't become collateralized officially by 1935.
By the way, you can go look at old tattoo shops from the 20s and 30s.
They have little signs on menus, what kind of tattoos they do, how much.
They do say in these old tattoo shops, we'll tattoo the social security number on your arm.
So when you hear about people having numbers tattooed on their arms, certain type of people, that was a fashion call.
Oh, I met someone who was in a concentration camp.
They even had the tattoo on their arm.
Well, people did that all over the place because they needed that number to get stuff, right?
Anyway, so you could look this up.
You could look up old tattoo shops and you'll see – try it if you could zoom in on the background.
It says we even tattoo social security numbers on your arm.
This is in New York, a New York tattoo shop.
We're not talking Germany, Hitler's Germany, right?
It's amazing what you learn when you look.
No, it's actually amazing what you learn even when you're not looking.
New York outlawed tattoos too.
That was another thing.
Even though there were tattoo shops that still existed, they were outlawed.
Yeah, that's why if you had a tattoo up until the 1970s, you were considered a biker, an outlaw, or a sailor.
Yeah, so – yeah.
Anyway, I just wanted to bring that up.
The tattoo on the arm thing was vogue.
It wasn't a prison war camp that the Nazis did.
You know what they called them, the Nazis.
So –
It couldn't have been both though?
It couldn't have been both things true or –
Yeah, yeah.
But anyway, find out when the social number, whatever they call it, social welfare number, social benefits number became official.
And that's when they finally bankrupted the country you're in.
So – and then they have a set of laws.
But the Bill of Exchange Act of 1882, which was, I believe, done in England or – let me look it up.
It wasn't England.
It was another international – that applied to the whole world.
Bill of Exchange, Bill of Exchange –
At some point in England, they were calling that stuff gold checks or whatever, and then they started –
Certificates, yeah.
Yeah, and that was like your welfare check pretty much in England.
And then they started calling it council –
In the UK, yeah.
Council payments, right?
Because they were handled all by the local councils, they said.
So that was the idea, but that was like your public assistance, your public support was from that.
And they changed those terms a few times.
But in the 70s, there was weird terminology for that in the UK.
Well, the thing is – OK, there's two things happening.
Just like I mentioned, the French journalist in North Korea asked one of the professors in North Korea in 2019 if he got permission to leave the country where he would go.
He said, I'd go to East Germany and the Soviet Union.
East Germany, which doesn't exist anymore, yeah.
Yeah, I think it was like 1992, 1993, right?
Yeah, so it's gone by then.
And he doesn't know.
Well, for him, it would have been 29 years, and he still didn't know.
So this is exactly what's going on with people asking.
But there's something that's – OK, the cosmic censorship.
These guys are doing some serious voodoo.
Asking people to discuss money, their competency of it or their interest in it is like asking them about their wildest sexual proclivity or sexual fantasy in public.
They will not say.
They just don't want to talk about it.
And this is because of the voodoo, the magic that's been done on them, right?
Come to think of it, I think people are more likely to talk to you about their sexual proclivities than they are about money.
I think they're more likely to do that.
Yeah, because there's more magic being done on the money subject than on the sexual subject.
Yeah, I agree.
Yeah, OK.
So, yeah, go ahead.
It's really bad.
It is.
That's how you really want to know if someone is censored.
Ask them if they know how the money system works, like bills of exchange.
And if they don't, if they want to learn about it, they want to know about it.
If you get one of these really dull, like, no, I don't care about that or whatever, you see the cosmic censorship because it's very important.
You know, it's just we live in a society that relies on money, unfortunately.
You know, so and it would be fine because if we had real money, you could work at the post office and have, you know, buy a house, pay a mortgage off or, you know, satisfy a mortgage in less than 10 years, have a family of five and support them.
Right?
Right.
If you're on.
That's why, you know, they warned every country not to let paper money come in.
And it's going to get worse and worse.
It's not going to get better.
What's happening is the understanding of anything, the human body, money, religion, all that is going down less and less.
The more TV there is, of course, and the more media there is and the the negative aspects of those things that I mentioned, you know, the human body, medical money and religion is going to get worse and worse.
Like what people don't know, for example, is segwaying through religion.
You know, like you have the access of evil.
What is it?
Iran and North Korea right now.
I think Syria is part of it.
Yeah.
And probably.
Iran, Syria, North Korea.
There's one more, though, right?
Washington, D.C.
Anyway.
Hey, look, you got to count the real access of evil.
Let's go with the Vatican City.
Let's go.
Yeah, it would be the real city of London.
Most of the underground.
Yeah.
That's on the surface.
All the things that people consider holy.
Even the Bible says that all the stuff you consider holy is like vomit.
You know.
So anyway, most people think that the vision that they've got, it's kind of like if you were in the Soviet Russia in the 1970s, anyone off the street to describe Americans, they would say, oh, they wear cowboy hats.
Right.
And if you asked any American in the 70s to describe someone who lived in the Soviet Russia, they'd say, oh, they drink vodka all the time.
Yeah.
Right.
So now if you ask anyone, describe people in the Middle East that they're radical Muslims, that they're Muslim, and actually they don't want to be Muslim.
That was put on them by a series of acts.
And you know the movie Lawrence of Arabia, you know, all that stuff, right?
Which was true.
There was a Lawrence of – Lawrence Thompson, I think his name was.
And he was a guy that united all these tribes.
They needed to unite the people and then they took the worst people and put them up, you know, as puppet governments.
And I give them reasons why you always want to pick the worst people, right?
Like a puppet government, right?
Because they'll do whatever you tell them to the people and they'll make sure they maintain power because if they lose the power, people will tear them to pieces.
So they always have in these Muslim countries the worst camel thieves, the worst, most atrocious families were put in power by the British, the Americans, whoever was responsible for whatever zone.
That's why they all have – all the countries in the Middle East have a red, yellow and green flag, right?
They're actually going to give them numbers and all that.
And they did have numbers of which one came in.
But what they did was they wanted to really put on this caliphate kind of concept that everyone has to be Muslim.
Now, if you live in Iran or know people from Iran, and even recently this has been going on more and more, they're burning – the Iranian people are burning the mosques themselves because they don't want that.
Each country doesn't want Islam, the flavor of Islam especially that's being put on them by the Vatican, City of London, Washington, D.C., CIA.
They don't want that at all.
All those mullahs and all these guys that you see wherever, they're not – they're the worst of the worst.
And the West thinks that the people want them there.
They don't.
So what you're going to see is the burning and destruction of Muslim-type mosques and symbols by the people in the Middle East.
They don't want that.
That was put on them by the foreign powers.
So this is something – I'm saying this to dispel a myth.
Just like I mentioned what Americans thought of Soviets and vice versa in the 70s.
This is still going on in America.
They think that the Iranians are radically Muslim.
They're not.
They hate it.
They absolutely hate it.
Their national religion is Zoroastrianism.
So it's not Islam at all.
And now out of fear, most people, just like Americans, they'll say anything to sound patriotic or de jour, like what's the flavor of the day.
They won't speak out against it.
But they hate it, right?
So just like if you speak to people in Israel, they hate that orthodox Judaism.
And everyone has a reason why they hate it.
It's like there's no bus lines running on Saturdays, right?
They hate that.
So that doesn't make any sense, right?
So you could have a bus line running on a Saturday even during the Sabbath as long as it doesn't leave town and no one's driving it.
And that sounds crazy, but, yeah, there's a reason for automated machines, self-driving buses.
Why not a self-driving bus, right?
I mean nobody's doing the work.
You're just riding on a vehicle.
You're not doing anything.
And you're not leaving town.
So, yeah, buses usually don't leave town.
Ninety percent of all bus riders don't – they're not riding the dog.
They're not going across country.
It's very local, right?
Just to save walking for half an hour.
You take a five- or ten-minute bus ride.
Exactly.
It's to avoid walking an hour to get from one side of the town to the other.
You just take a bus for five minutes.
But everyone has their own reason for whatever.
They don't like Judaism, what's put on them.
And the Catholics have the jokes about being raised Catholic and all this stuff.
So there's going to be a big turnaround against this stuff, which is going to help out with the collapse of this horrible society.
And one thing I commented on –
Is that why we have the big push to make America the Christian nation now, like so that we have –
Oh, yeah.
Jason talked about that.
I talked about it, but not in the detail that he has years ago.
You're going to see a very radical right adopting religion, religiosity.
Jason of Archaics calls it the Christian Reich.
And when you have people killing other people in the name of God, meaning that they say they have God on their side, they'll do the most heinous shit in the world, right?
I tried to make that point recently, like in an open discussion with a bunch of people.
Boy, did I get attacked from every side.
Yeah, because it has nothing to do with the rationale.
No, it doesn't.
We're taking advantage of the times.
My point is that if you create a system where you point to people and you say they are literally on the side of everything that is evil, the absolute adversary, and you've decided to target those people, you can expect that somebody might take you seriously.
Sure.
And here's the other thing.
Anyone who knows any scripture at all will know that the true God of the heaven and the one that's in power has no showing here whatsoever right now.
It's the God of this world that does all the religions and the churches and the moralities and all this other stuff, right?
The adversary.
But anyway, Archaics talks about that.
He's been leaning on it very heavily.
I haven't listened to him in a while because his narrative – I've given the value of his narrative.
And everybody's narrative sort of peters out after a while.
If you say the same – research the same stuff or say the same stuff over and over, I got it.
But one thing you'll find with Greek-speak, it's extremely wide.
We can talk about many subjects and we can go very deep and give you sense – add sense to it.
Sense means that you can use it.
That's where you get senses from, let's say.
So these things are going to be coming around.
I would avoid all of it.
The problem with understanding what I'm saying here, as in the Greek-speak, what we do, is you have no one to talk to about it, right?
Very rare.
I'm talking about even where you live or where you work, anywhere.
This is tough, yeah.
Because you won't be here if you're cosmically censored, right?
So if you want to know more about cosmic censorship, ask yourself why you're listening to Greek-speak and how much you've integrated it and whatever.
Recently, I was speaking to someone and he wanted me to recommend some people regarding a certain topic.
And he also asked me to recommend someone who knows Greek-speak because it's very hard.
If you want to take someone who knows Greek-speak and start working with someone who knows nothing about these things we've gone over over the years, it's very hard because they're living in a complete fantasy, right?
About everything, any topic.
Imagine working with someone and they say, I've got to go to the doctor right now and get some blood pressure medication.
Oh my gosh, where do you start?
Where do you start?
Do I have diabetes?
There's a guy online, I'm not going to mention his name, Jerry Marzinski, who is like this alternative psychology guy.
I've spoken to him and he says, oh, I can't eat that.
I have type 2 diabetes.
I'm like, oh my gosh.
Oh my gosh.
I'm not even going to start with this old dummy.
There's no way I'm going to start.
No way.
But it doesn't discount stuff that he talks about.
But imagine being around someone like that on a working – you can't.
It's very difficult because if you bought it – once you buy into this stuff, right, and you start suffering the consequences because if you're – give an example of the diabetes.
Most people are perfectly fine and they get a thing that says you have diabetes.
I feel good.
Actually, maybe you should start treatment soon before it gets worse.
Well, guess what?
When you start treatment, you get worse.
You get worse and worse.
It's a scam, right?
So where do you – so it depends.
If you ask someone how long you've been getting treatment for diabetes, yes.
How long?
Five years.
That's really – that's already done enough damage.
Your kidneys are going to fail, right, and then you're going to get all the bad circulation.
That's the standard protocol.
They're the drugs that destroy it.
I'll tell you a terrible truth.
My second wife, I met her and she was telling me that she had thought for years that she was a diabetic but she wasn't doing anything with it.
Not at all.
Oh, my gosh.
And I said, OK, well – and I didn't know all this stuff back then at all.
Not at all.
But I knew that most of what she was talking about made no sense.
She weighed 95 pounds soaking wet.
Yeah, they don't have – by the way, they do have demographics.
They like to go to certain neighborhoods.
But it doesn't mean if you go to a very wealthy neighborhood, you have to – people are not on – they are.
I know the Golden Ghetto up here where the houses are four or five million and above and all of them are on diabetes medication.
But then you go down to the ghetto or whatever, they're all on diabetes medication if they can get it.
So there's no – there's a certain demographic but is there?
But she was 48 years old and within 18 months of starting to get this treatment, she was gone.
Yeah, exactly.
That's the idea.
That's what they're supposed to do.
That was the horror of it.
Yeah, it sucks.
Ignorance.
My people will be destroyed through that lack of knowledge.
Yeah.
So, yeah.