The sonic entity known as S.H.O.N.I.K.E. ends this week.
Rated Y and it is Sonic Event 81. So here we go.
Greig, how are you doing?
Hey, I'm doing okay. Yeah, fully recovered, I would like to say, but I'm not.
Let me just give a little bit of history. If you guys are in front of a search engine,
type in Wendy Blades, and what you'll see in images is a very voracious, vivacious looking redhead,
about just under 30 years old, very physically fit, like Miss Fitness,
and she's a sword swallower and acrobat at the Paranormal Circus.
And what does that have to do with anything?
The Paranormal Circus.
Yeah, Paranormal Circus. It's out of Italy, actually.
Nice.
Well, that's my niece.
And I'll give a little bit more of a, I live a very solitude lifestyle, even though I am married or whatever.
I'm what you might say, celibate, platonic. I don't touch people at all.
Even, you know, I live with someone, I don't make any physical contact with them.
And when she came by and gave me a hug, it was a shock.
If you don't touch anyone for about a year or nine months or so, right?
Imagine being in solitary confinement, but not physical solitary confinement.
You just haven't had any human contact in nine months at all whatsoever.
Not a handshake, nothing.
And I felt like this electric shock and I got nauseous, right?
And that kind of gave me this, it's all frequency.
See, that doesn't feel natural to me.
It doesn't, you know, to completely abstain from physical contact.
I don't know if it's a cultural thing.
No, it is a culture. I'm going to get into that.
It's actually, the benefits are incredible, though.
Really?
You can do it. Do it. Absolutely.
I thought it was a negative.
Well, maybe you didn't think it was a negative thing when they started encouraging this, you know, six feet apart social distancing deal.
Did you think that was a negative?
Anything for the collective is for the wrong reason, even though it might seem right.
It's crap. The collective is garbage and they're never going to get it together.
And anyone who's listened to Greek speak and found it to be shocking or whatever,
and you listen to it long enough, you'll be like, he's right.
Because a lot of the stuff that I say you could and have said,
you could paraphrase it as being said 2,000 years ago, 3,000 years ago.
And it's just the human condition, right?
Well, sure. But that's why I find this a little bit, you know, against the grain.
It almost seems like it would be part of the natural human condition to sort of be connected with others.
No, there isn't. Here, I'll give you an idea.
Like an example, like more than two decades ago,
I went on a blind date with this white girl and we ordered a dinner platter to share.
Immediately, she wants to take half the platter on her plate.
And that's not the European way or Asian where everybody just picks on the platter a little bit.
Right. You just take a little portion.
But if you're around white people and you bring a platter right away,
they want to take their half right away off to the side,
as if like there's some kind of battle ensuing or some kind of fight.
Or you've seen like little rascals in an orphanage where if you don't, you know,
when the food comes out, if you don't get what you get right away, it's all gone.
You know, just like with dogs, with puppies.
If you put the food down, you know, it's like it's all gone, like piranhas, right?
Right. And that's a cultural thing where if you go to if you go to something like an Asian community,
there'll be 10 people sitting around a table and they all eat from one plate.
No one tries to take their portion completely on their plate and start munching on it. Right.
Well, like in Sicily. It's a culture.
Like in Sicily, we had these little tiny plates in front of us,
but they were just meant to catch things we were dropping that we were eating really stuff.
Yeah, it's a different culture. And that's why I want to get into.
I got a message from someone who is an architect also and said,
Oh, I've only discussed Feng Shui. I call it Feng Shui, Feng Shui.
I've heard it called Feng Shui also.
Texas accent, I guess. Feng Shui.
I did hear that somewhere. Yeah. Yeah.
All kinds of things like Fox painting. Right. F-A-U-X. Right.
What's this Fox painting? Let me look at that.
You mean, oh, faux painting, huh?
Yeah. So what I would suggest is it's the culture that you're from. Right.
So if let me just tie it. I want to talk about architecture.
I want to talk about nine star key and a couple other things.
And we're going to bounce around like a banana in a monkey grove.
OK, instead of monkey grove and monkeys in a banana grove.
So backwards twice. So. OK, so you have you know, I always harp on white people.
It has nothing to do with the color of your skin.
It just so happens that most of them do have white skin also.
It's a shit culture to me, to me, to them.
They don't know what they're doing. Right. It's a very depression baby.
It came across post-World War II, post-World War I in Europe and post-Depression in the U.S.
This internal competition amongst family members and neighbors.
You've heard you've got to do better than the Joneses. Right.
That's the white people. You don't hear that in other cultures at all.
It's this culture of it's all engineered, by the way, and they fall for it.
They don't know what's going on at all. They're not conscious of it.
And I believe that it's it was brought over by a spiritual element.
That is time for it to come into the earth and it manifested.
That's why people that are like that are not fixable.
You know, they they can be if they're totally immersed into another culture,
totally immersed and they have to stay there because the minute you take them out, they go right back to it.
So I've seen this. I've been watching it for decades.
It was very unusual to me in the beginning. Here, I'll give you an example.
I grew up in a very Greek family. Parents came over on an airplane, not on a boat.
And I have two siblings. We're about six, nine and ten.
Parents put us to the side and says, listen, we're Greek. We're not Americans.
They're animals. Well, what? I'm like, what? I have friends that are American.
They're not animals. I was in the third grade, fourth grade, whatever. Fine.
No, you don't understand. You go to their house, knock on the door.
They'll have you standing at the door for four hours talking.
They won't even offer you a glass of water. Right.
And that shocked me. And two blocks over, I was associating with the Bono family.
I'll give names. Cologero, Biagio and Giuseppe. Charles, Blaze and Joseph.
It's Sicilian family boys. Cologero was Charles, Biagio, Blaze and Giuseppe.
Right. Anyway, and we spoke and the mother was, you know, very traditional, very traditional, very traditional.
Sounds northern Italian, too, because to go with the Colosio and all that, that's got to be.
Yeah, but there was Sicilian Palermo. So anyway, and the other city there next to Palermo.
Anyway, make a long story short.
I told him how shocked I was that my parents said Americans are animals because, you know, it's fine.
I have friends in school are Americans.
They looked at me and they said, oh, our parents said the same thing.
I was like, what? You know, well, that's the thing.
I was thinking to myself, Mediterranean culture.
And we started out with this whole thing about physical contact.
And I'm thinking to myself, you know, Greeks generally, as I remember them,
they definitely were of the Mediterranean mindset, which included physical contact.
This is more of an energetic stuff that I've been doing.
And it's really I understand. I would recommend it to anyone.
Like, give me an example. Walking barefoot.
For example, I have a problem with balancing yin and yang energy.
I'm very young. Right. Give me an example.
About 10 years ago or eight years ago, I did a Skype call maybe six years ago.
And I invited someone who was from Skype calls from 15 years ago.
And he showed up. His name is Abel, a Middle Eastern guy.
And he's an arms dealer, by the way.
I shouldn't say that, but, yeah, it's true.
Yeah. And yeah, a real arms dealer.
And he was on sitting in the background listening. He says, Greek, I haven't heard.
I haven't heard from you. I talked to you in years.
You really mellowed out. And people on the call were like, oh, my gosh.
Oh, my gosh. The Greek is mellowed out.
What the hell was he like five years ago? Oh, my gosh. Right.
So, yeah, I've mellowed out a lot.
Well, I hate to tell you this, but you mellowed out in the time I've been talking to you.
Yeah, but it's still a regular quote unquote white people being super hard.
Oh, they can't. Oh, my gosh. They got to run, run, run.
Of course.
Okay. So walking barefoot. So I have a problem.
I'm very young, but I'll get cold feet that are wet and clammy in shoes in the winter.
But if I take the shoes and socks off, it doesn't matter how cold it is.
I walk barefoot. My feet are warm and fine.
Right. Because now I've made the connection. Right.
The bottom is the most lean. The top of the earth is the most young.
Boom. They make connection just like, you know, putting batteries in the right way in the flashlight.
Right. Alternate them. Right. Right.
A lot of people talk about this. They call it grounding themselves, which I think is a fair description of it.
But I'm telling you exactly why it works exactly like the batteries in the flashlight.
You can't line up all the batteries unless the terminals are set up to be that way.
You notice how they go positive, negative, positive, negative, positive, negative to keep the energy flowing.
So for some reason, if I have an insulator, socks even, or slippery, my feet get cold and wet.
So it works really well. But how it all came about is not relevant.
But what happens, though, if you avoid human contact for a long time, more than six months, nine months, a year,
what happens is you are so sensitive to the way your body picks up energies.
Because the moment you touch another human body, that is the most powerful thing you can touch.
Great. That doesn't sound true because I could touch up a live wire and it would kill me electrically.
No, no. It's not what I'm talking about because it's the same.
Because another human body is more similar to you than anything else you can touch, even a hot stove.
Right. In the way that it's made, doesn't matter if it's, you know, boy, girl, child, adult, grandma.
It doesn't matter. Any human is going to be closer to your frequency than an object that you can touch that will energize you.
Right. Once once you are depraved of that, deprived of that long enough,
your own body becomes overly sensitized to the fields that it recognizes because it's no longer getting,
quote unquote, grounded by any other humans. So you have an incredible feeling like when you go to pick something up,
like a sim in the kitchen counter right now, I see a scissor before I touch the scissor.
I have the imprint of the scissor, all the energy in the scissor. Right.
Before I touch it, I feel it. Right. It makes you extremely sensitive on more than any physical level you can ever.
Right. And the moment you touch a human, it feels very odd, very odd, very strange.
And when you're frequently touching people, meaning like shaking hands. Right.
Let's say in business or at work, people shake your hands when they introduce and meet. Right.
Right. Or spouses, lovers, friends, hug, hold, sex, whatever, whatever. Right.
Yeah. They're not used to they touch each other so often.
Let's say you you shake your someone's hand at work a couple of times.
It's put the social stuff aside and then you go home and you kiss your wife and then you have sex or whatever.
It's the same. The feeling. But you don't notice the changes. Right.
Because it's all physical. One is more elevated than the other. Right.
So if you have zero human contact at all, at all, when you touch another human, you get a serious download.
I mean, energetic. It's it's not like a download of information or anything.
You get their energy completely. Right. And it's it's not good.
It's not good unless the person is very clean, very well on your level, let's say. Right.
So it's very interesting. So actually, when you're in prison and solitary confinement,
I think it's a predisposed mental psych out to people to say that because anybody in solitary confinement in prison will say, oh, that was the worst thing.
I just need somebody to talk to. Bullshit. That is total bullshit.
That is because you're preconditioned.
You were told many times when you got into prison that the worst thing is solitary confinement.
Mentally, it breaks you. OK, I'll remember that.
Then when you go into it, you apply that programming to yourself.
And it is terrible when I'm telling you it's not the best thing could ever happen to anyone.
Right. You see how you can turn things into giving an example how this is true.
America is the richest country in the world. Legally, it's the poorest country in the world legally.
Well, how do I know? Because which country in the world legally has the most deficit?
The U.S. So legally, the U.S. is the poorest country in the world, right?
Because I owe twelve dollars. My neighbor owes forty thousand and my other neighbor owns six million.
He owes. Who's the poorest? About three of us. The guy who owns six million.
He'll never get out of it. Right. So what do they tell you?
U.S. is the richest country in the world, but it's actually the poorest. Oh, my gosh.
OK. What does that mean? The reason why people call it the richest country in the world is because there's no scarcity.
One thing that people visit here from other countries, the U.S., you got everything everywhere.
Go to a supermarket. Get more things here. Right.
But except for Germany and places like that, let's say. Right. Everything's available.
So what what's where's the scarcity? The scarcity is in the money, in the credit.
Material energy is very cheap. Like if you lived in England, you have a heater in each room.
And when you go from room to room in the winter, you make sure you turn off the heater that you're not in the room.
That's how expensive it is to write. Electricity is in England. Right.
Right. Excuse me. In the U.S., they still have 50, 60 year old burners that are only 10 percent efficient,
meaning 90 percent of the money you spend on fuel goes out the chimney, not to eat the house.
Right. So it's a crime. They still have houses remodeled down the street.
They're putting that unit in there. The same one. I'm like, oh, my gosh.
Right. Because, OK, the reason why people came to the two of the Americas across the Atlantic was, first of all, to escape justice,
because justice that revived goddess religion was destroying them after Napoleon.
Napoleon was their last hope. But that was a game also. Napoleon was like the Trump of the time, by the way.
Right. You know, is a bullshit. You know, anyway. Anyway, they came over here because the system was destroying them.
But also they came here because of free energy or cheap energy.
If it was cold in the winter in Europe and you needed wood for your little hovel to heat up, you couldn't find it.
You were fighting for sticks. If you can find them where you come to the U.S., even in a city,
you just walk off to the outskirts of the city like Boston was surrounded by forest. Right.
New York was surrounded by forest. Right. You all the logs and sticks you want to burn.
You could accumulate in three days enough wood for the entire winter, you see, and coal and oil.
And so the reason why people came here is because cheap energy. Gasoline.
Oh, you know, euro in a dollar is almost the same. Right. So let's say it's three dollars for a gallon of gas in the U.S.
Well, in Europe, it's like 275 euro, which is almost the same, but for a liter. Right.
Less than a quarter. Right. So it's really twelve dollars a gallon. You see, it's still going on.
So this was set up. It's all programming. It's all programming.
Again, let's go back to solitary confinement, because anybody you hear stories in prison,
the worst thing that ever happened in solitary confinement, even 30 days. Right.
You hear that all the time. That's psychic probes. That's there's psyched up.
You could psych someone up. That if you walk into a pink room and you're locked in there for three hours, you will die.
I bet if you did that to 100 people, 10 of them would die only because they were told that.
Well, you know, I was locked up as a juvenile and I don't remember being pre-programmed about that at all.
And when you went into solitary, it was a punishment that was clearly a punishment for acting out of line,
you know, getting locked up. And if you didn't behave like the rest of the prisoners were supposed to, you could get thrown in there.
But outside, I did not find it to be something that was pre-programmed. I found it to be an awful experience.
It was not good. Well, yeah. Well, because it's different.
I'm giving that as an extreme because you're you're you're, quote unquote, your privileges and freedoms and things you have access to are more limited.
Right. Gone. Yeah. But if they gave you anything you ever wanted, it wouldn't be.
I probably would not have bothered me. No, I probably would have been happy.
Again, it is it is a psych. It is a psych thing. Yeah. Yeah. But this is again.
OK, I want to jump over to the one of the requests now with the nine star key and everything I just said ties in the culture.
Right. The reason I brought up the nine star key and I think it needs to just be brought up now and let's let it sit there for people that are interested
to do more research into it and get more familiar with the methodology. Why?
It's not like horoscopes, even though it does show days of when you were born.
You notice it doesn't get into planetary alignments and all that other stuff, right? No.
OK. What it is that I'm going to say this again, because it helps to repeat myself.
There were imagine an agency and a government agency, a monarchy have an agency and they assign people,
scholarly people to monitor all the towns, villages and cities based on, you know, may keep records.
And when people were born, what their lives were like, you know,
they keep records and keep those records going for 4000 years.
And you could cross reference details about the people.
So you did you went all the way to even moles on people's faces, where the mole was, you know,
on their right cheek, on their left cheek, on their chin, on their forehead. Right.
OK. You know, you actually interviewed the people and you made detailed assessment, you know,
and description of each one. And then you found out you went back, you know,
do you know how they do the census every 10 years? It was very similar to that. Right.
And they would review everyone as many as they can for 4000 years.
And I started noticing similarities, like, for example, like people who usually had a mole on their right cheek.
If they ever try to have employees or get a management or administrative position, they failed.
No one would listen to them. Right. So they said, OK, all the people that failed administratively didn't make good managers.
What else do they have in common other than days they were born, months they were born?
And you notice they all had on their paperwork a mole on their right cheek.
Should we ignore those details or should we just make a category that if you have born around this time
of this earth element and you have a mole on your right cheek, you're probably not going to make a good business manager.
Should we ignore that or should we? Was it a valid category? Statistically, it's a very valid category.
Statistically, it continues to emerge as a pattern. I mean, what exactly?
It's very strict. It's very, very strict. In other words, the exceptions were very few that were outside of that domain.
Let's say character is characteristic. That's what makes it so fascinating.
And that's why it's not popular. That's why it's not popular.
The airy fairy stuff is popular because the people you shoot, you must.
The mushroom people, you must keep them in the dark and feed them bullshit.
All right. Because now, OK, just like I mentioned about white people, you cannot fix it.
You either put up with it or you leave it. Well, you cannot fix it.
You know what I see consistently here is there's flexibility, right?
Is you can take and adapt these facts or adapt these alleged facts or these alleged things.
And what can you say at the end is you can find a way to make yourself special somehow.
And that makes people feel good. That's what I think happens with a lot of these religions.
You're special because you're part of this. You believe this. So that makes you special.
Right. I think that happens with organized religion. I think that happens with this organized airy fairy stuff.
You're special as long as you are the opposite. Yeah. Yeah. You know, and that's how they control.
That's the flattery. Right. Yeah. Flattery. There you go. That's the best singular word for it.
But that's how it goes. Right. If they can make you feel special, you'll keep coming back. Right.
Yeah. That's which leads us into the architecture. Someone messaged me about architecture.
I have a lot to say about it. Fortunately, well, here's my background.
I actually studied architecture 40 years ago and I had some pretty good design professors.
And I worked for an architect who knew the system was bullshit.
And he started a small minute. It was called Men at Work.
And he did architectural projects, remodels. We actually physically worked and designed stuff.
And he still has a studio in Manhattan. Looked him up about a few years ago.
Wasn't that company that like a small crew could show up and pretty much do anything?
Wasn't that the idea with the Men at Work group? Yeah, pretty much.
But it was most of our clients were people in the entertainment industry like the Segovia brothers,
Molly Davis, who was one of the early videographers could go on and on and on people in the theater business.
And but not the struggling artists, the ones that would go and buy a loft on Broadway.
Like, remember Tower Records in Manhattan, where it's fourth and Broadway?
Yeah, yeah. Well, that building, that building on the third floor,
they buy the loft for two million and they spend two million to remodel. Right.
Right. The elevator opens in your in your loft like that.
Those kinds of projects, fun stuff. And we did some very interesting stuff.
And he was a Yale. He went to Yale. And after a few years studying Yale architecture school, he stopped.
He said he wanted his work in the field and go back and finish the degree.
His dad, if I get is a famous, very famous artist. And his godfather was Marcel Duchamp.
Most people don't know who he is. He started the Dada movement and the Impressionist movement.
But, you know, you could look up Marcel Duchamp.
He was also a famous chess master. The chess master community knew him as a chess master that painted.
And the artist community knew him as a painter that played chess.
He had two lives. Anyway, I had his ladder for a little while.
But anyway, yeah, I rubbed I was around those those high end artists.
Dori Ashton was my landlady. I'll just name drop to 17 East 11th Street.
I lived on the ground floor. I'd go up. I should invite me for tea.
And I'd be sitting there with like Matisse's in the living room.
All kinds of artwork. All those artists from the 60s, 70s and 80s.
Like if you didn't know her, you couldn't be famous. Andy Warhol stuff.
I mean, so basically I'm sitting there having tea. And if I if she left the room and I opened the front door,
I could grab 50 million dollars worth of paintings out of her living room and run.
Right. But I didn't care because the stuff was as ugly as modern art masterpiece.
You expect to be right. So closest I ever got to something like that was Peel.
I knew a Peel there that lived in the East Village when I lived on 9th Street.
You know, so you remember him. Oh, I had a client.
The Scalamandres. And oh, my gosh, they're like the De Beers of Dimino, the Scalamandres or the Silk Empire.
Right. They're not as prominent as they were. I'll use names. So what?
And she was cheap and she had a duplex on Park Avenue on 56 and Park, a two story apartment.
Right. With a big grand staircase. You know, she's like selling.
So I got I hired one of the handymen to paint the ceiling.
There were water stains and I think he got some paint drops in some of my heirloom paintings.
So I walk into the room and I see this painting. It's like, you know, a foot and a half by foot and a half oil.
You could tell it's old. It was at least 500 years old, you know, because the oil, the shellac is really dark.
Right. You know, you see really old paintings. Right. So I wrap it up in paper, take it on the subway to Jennifer.
This girl, she's a conservator, conservator like she would.
They would give her World War, Civil War photos and very wealthy people photo albums that were 100 years old.
And she would restore the pictures. You see like a really jacked up black and white picture, all distorted water stain.
And she would make it look like it was brand new. Right. She could reverse all the processes and stuff.
So anyway, I bring this painting and you could see there were some paint spots like someone's painting the ceiling.
They didn't use enough drop cloths kind of thing. OK. And I opened the painting and she froze.
She turned white and she's like, I can't touch this painting. Where did you get it? A museum or something?
This is a such and such. You know what? I remember the artist. There was some.
I looked them up, some famous Renaissance painter, not so famous, but there was slews of them.
Right. Like, you know, four or five million dollar painting because I can't touch it.
And I'm like, look, look, this lady, she hired a handyman to paint the ceiling and he got painted.
Do you think she fucking cares? Right. Just get the damn paint off.
And she's like, I can't, I can't, I can't. Maybe I know someone who. And she she's like, you need an armored car to move this.
You took it on the subway. You know, I'm like, yeah, nobody knew I had it.
You know, it's like, what the hell's wrong with you people? You know, I'm just trying to help out this lady. Right.
So, yeah, I can go on and on and on with art stories with the art community like that.
Oh, my gosh. For hours and architectural stories, too. But this is what I want to say about the architecture.
What's going on with architecture is some of the education. All right.
Before I continue, I'm going to stop. I know this is a triple segway, triple tangent.
OK, if academics were in control of what is created and designed in the world, we would not have electric motors.
We would not have the light bulb. We would not have the propeller driven airplane or jet airplane.
We would not have any of that. We would not have the computer at all.
We would be shoveling horseshit, literally, literally.
And we'd be doing well, not whale oil, but probably petroleum oil candlelight.
If academics and I mean this, I mean this. If this is the last thing I'm going to say ever, my last words, this is it.
If academics ruled really the you know, the way society was going to go, we wouldn't have any of those things.
That's how bad they are. They cannot create anything. They're not creative at all, at all.
They cannot do anything. The people that have designed and built all the things that we have and we use,
the car, the airplane, the electric motor, the bay, I'm giving the bay even water treatment.
We're people practical working in the industry with intuition.
Why? If you are an academic, it doesn't matter any of the sciences or psychiatries or medicine,
that system is designed to take all the creativity out of you so much that you will not be granted a degree by the trustees.
If you ever read the diploma, you're not getting shit out of a diploma, right?
It says the trustees recommend you have enough credits to get this, right? It's bullshit.
Anyway, these people, they have all the creativity so pushed out of them,
out of what academia has been doing for the past 200 years, yes, 200 years,
that not only are they become totally blasé and incapable, that they also defend the system now, like the Matrix, right?
Not only are they hopelessly enslaved by it, but they will defend it.
So I have to say this, why? Because since I did the water, I've reached out to,
several have reached out to me, people in the academic field, various sciences, engineers,
and they have not contributed anything at all, zero, to how this works, intuition, nothing at all.
And I've seen this in common, I've been watching them for four decades, academics,
and I wanted to wait till now to say it, because it's reached the point where I could say it with confidence,
and it applies throughout, and it's a very damning statement, a very damning statement.
What I've always noticed is the only innovation that ever emerges in anything, practically,
is from people that have their hands on whatever it is they're working on,
and they decide to make progress one way or another, you know what I mean?
It's like if somebody's already doing something, they go, you know what, I've come up with a better way,
because they just reason it out, they come up with some intuition, they say, let's do this different,
let's do this better, and they do it, and they make it work.
It's not the people that are sitting there with the degrees, and it doesn't matter if it's in literature,
if it's in practical engineering, any of this stuff, it's always somebody who is,
who is the guy who brought you this?
It's some guy that was sitting in his garage, said, you know what, I want to make this better,
I want to do something better, I want to do something faster.
Well, also they promote all this artificial geeky technology.
For example, the water group just started, it's called Inertial, let me go back inside,
Inertial Domain, and I put it in the chat, you just click on it and join.
I wanted to bring this up because I was going to do a PowerPoint and all this other stuff,
but I found out that if I do a PowerPoint and put it on Skype,
if you show up with a stupid rectangle, a tablet or phone, it may or may not work, forget it.
What I'm going to do is number the pictures and give descriptions in a regular plain Skype format.
So, like anybody's device will work on a plain Skype format.
There's a tablet, an Apple tablet, iPad that stopped working and it still can do Skype.
So, you know, there's no excuse.
But anyway, I want to get back to, this is the third tangent I've done.
Yeah, I want to bring this up, 3D printing.
3D printing to me is the most vulgar, most ugly, unintuitive, should I keep going,
technology that I have ever seen.
Now, it has its place, but when people gravitate to that,
that is like telling me Greek, I can cook, I have frozen dinners.
Oh, my gosh.
I think I'm one of the causes.
People that say that they cook, they really can't.
They just reheat food.
There's a big difference, right?
I ran into so many white people that said I could cook, and no, they don't know how to cook.
They just know how to reheat things.
There's a big difference, right?
That's why they have all these meals in a bag you buy now,
there's fresh groceries delivered to you,
has a recipe instructions on how to heat everything up a certain way,
and they're making great meals.
No, they don't know how to cook.
It even tells you you don't have to know how to cook.
The 3D printing industry to me is garbage with a capital B.
If anyone approaches me with that, I'm not going to say it again.
I have said it to several people.
That's garbage to me.
If I see something 3D printed that costs more than 39 cents,
it's not worth it.
You're being ripped off.
Yes, I know that there's a lot of technology,
especially the AI-assisted, and they're able to do additive metal forming,
little tiny particles of metal that are centered together
to make almost biological-looking skeletons inside of machines
that couldn't be made before.
I get it.
But for things that can be well-crafted by hand,
and you prefer 3D printing, gag me.
It's like, please, barf bag time.
So academics promote that.
They gush over that.
They gush over it.
So anyway, yes.
Are they a necessary evil?
Okay, academics are a necessary evil, footnote.
Why?
We are in the unwinding of society, unwinding devolution.
We started off with no parentage, very high technology,
and all the series of catastrophes are to keep us in a certain place,
to not go back to that high state, right?
We are unwinding right now.
The spiral can wind inwards and tighten up,
or it could unwind and loosen up.
And how do we say it's unwinding?
Everything is being spread out, right, everywhere.
You can go anywhere in the world.
It's unwinding.
It's not contracting or some contraction.
So all society is unwinding like a cheap sweater.
So does academia fit in to a society that's devolving and unwinding
and decomposing?
Of course.
It's a perfect additive, right?
It's a perfect additive.
Is 3D printing being preferred instead of, you know,
some hand skills and beautiful art, right?
Of course, right?
The woke political agenda, is that unwinding or, right?
Yeah, you see?
So, yeah, it fits.
In other words, does it need to go the other way?
For the sake of humanity, yes.
But in terms of understanding the era and the time that we're in, no.
It has to go that way.
So just beware.
So in terms of architecture, I gave all these tangents to build up,
and I said I was very much involved in that community.
And I could keep mentioning names and people and things
and actually give some stories.
But architecture is the same way.
I had some really good design people around me,
and I got a really good sense of what it means.
And one of the things, because of my architectural training,
is why I say food, clothing, shelter.
Those are the three priority things, right?
You're going to live least without food and then clothing
and then shelter, right?
You can live without shelter longer than you can without clothing,
and you can longer without food.
And when I say food, it means food and water, right?
So food, clothing, shelter in that order are the priorities.
Now, what happens with architecture is very simple.
I hearken back to Jack Fresco.
If you look at modern cities, postcards, total disaster.
You see people buying tourist postcards in New York City.
They stand there, right?
Total ignoramuses.
And they look at the postcards.
Oh, how beautiful.
They're talking about the skyline of New York City.
What the hell are you talking about?
It's beautiful.
That's a fucking disaster.
It's the ugliest thing I've ever seen.
All the city skylines, all of them, maybe mosques,
maybe a few of them that I've adhered to certain, right?
Okay, what happens is you could have –
like I had a very good foundation in design,
and in private Skype calls I had spent hours
going over design principles that I was taught.
Not necessarily to do it with O and G or rated Y.
Okay, but what happens then is when a big difference
between the basic fundamental training of design principles –
and it's not complete.
It's not very thorough as it used to be.
When they go off into foreign partnerships and solos,
now it becomes all about the ego of the architect
to make something look different and expensive
because when the architect puts a portfolio together,
if everything is modest, he's not as famous
as the guy who makes like the $100 million loft, right?
So the architects, when you hire an architect,
it's going to be all ego, and he's going to want your project
to be as expensive as possible.
He doesn't want to cut cost
because the more expensive the project is,
the more impressive it looks on his portfolio.
Of course.
This is how sad it is right now.
Yeah, I find it strange that you bring up Fresco though
because at a certain point he was advocating
for the use of 3D printers to create habitats for people.
Exactly.
Yeah, I agree.
I agree there's actually 3D printing a building,
but we could build them faster by forming Lego-type blocks.
But no, the academic engineering style,
they apply 3D printing as a cure-all for everything.
They want everything to be 3D printed, right?
Even the Mona Lisa or the Statue of David
should be 3D printed, right?
No more sculpture, no more hand skills,
no more manipulation of material by hand.
Fresco had the idea that if you created the baseline stuff
with 3D printing and it was all virtually the same
and everybody had access to all the same things,
that you could indeed 3D print the tools
and then people would have the time.
Yeah, exactly.
But what you'll find with modern engineers and academics,
that's all they know.
The ones that, if they ruled the world,
we still wouldn't have electric motors, light bulbs,
or airplanes, right?
It's serious.
And if you don't believe that statement, I'm rehashing it.
Go read the criticism when people came up with airplanes,
light bulbs, and electric motors.
Who was on the front line to hound these people to death?
The academics.
The resistance was the academics, yeah, of course.
Yeah, yeah.
But this is a necessary evil.
It's like a cancer that you live with, right?
Are these people bad, the academics?
No.
But are they good?
Definitely not.
Definitely they're not good people either.
But are they bad?
In other words, are they there to be malevolent and hurt shit?
No.
But is stuff going to go better with them?
No, not at all.
They have nothing to contribute.
It's all circular, back and forth, back and forth.
And I've seen this.
I've been watching this for 40 years.
And I've kept my mouth shut until this, the water thing,
because I've been dealing with maybe half a dozen of them now,
from all parts of the world, ages and parts of the world.
And they're all the same crap.
Nothing.
They have zero to contribute.
It sounds like they have a lot to contribute.
But what they're contributing does not show why the device works so well,
why it's different than everything else.
Nothing at all.
Zero.
Right?
And then they want to 3D print everything.
My gosh.
3D print me a rope so I can hang myself.
That's what I'm waiting for.
Yeah.
Or, yeah, some furniture known as electric chair.
Yeah, so the architects now, what happens is they become ego and portfolio.
Now, I used to work as a liaison between builders and architects here in Tucson
on the expensive homes.
And when I'd get a plan right away,
I would shave $100,000 to $200,000 off the build price.
And the architects were pissed.
Because now it's no longer a $2 million house.
It's a $1.4 million or $1.6 million house.
And they wanted a $2 million house in their portfolio.
Who cares if we're squandering?
We're building these buildings.
We have a rec room with $50,000 built-in shelving.
I'm like, $50,000 built-in shelving?
What if you wanted to repurpose the room?
You're going to hire a bunch of whatever handymen with hammers
and bust the shit up and take it.
They're going to charge you $800 and take it away.
No, you don't build $50,000 buildings.
That's stupid.
And the architect would be, who are you?
Where are you from?
And the owner is like, oh, we love you.
We love you.
The architects hated me.
I can't use our architect as a reference in town.
Are you kidding?
The Greek?
He's the worst.
He'll ruin your business.
That's what they say.
Instead of having a portfolio of $2 million, $3 million homes,
now they have a portfolio of $1 million homes.
Aw.
At everyone else's expense.
Okay.
It's ego.
Yeah, it's really sad.
And I know plenty of architects.
But, okay, now here's the way you fix it.
First of all, when you build, it depends on what the purpose is, right?
Industrial, recreational, what they call residential is also commercial, by the way.
Residential, you're a resident in a place that you don't belong.
That's not yours.
So to say that your house is a residence, well, where do you live?
It shows you how, again, this completely unwinding society,
but where people dwell in their dwellings.
I'll give you a simple example.
I live on a middle class, middle of Tucson sort of.
And the houses are cookie-cutter houses, slightly different,
you know, about 10, 20 houses on each side of the street, 20 houses each side of the street.
And they're all laid out next to each other, the same floor plan.
Okay, not mirror image.
Whoa, what does that mean?
This is a sonic event, so I'm not getting a picture, right?
Okay, so you face the house.
So you've got the garage on the carport on the right and the bedrooms on the left,
entrance in the middle, right?
You get a garage on the right, bedroom on the left.
Okay, and go to the next house, same thing, garage on the right,
bedroom on the left, entrance and living room in the middle.
Next house, garage on the right, entrance, living room in the middle,
bedroom on the left.
Okay, you get the picture, right?
Why is that bad?
Because remember I said the garage is on the right.
Now if you follow the house down to the right, the next house,
what's next to the garage of that house?
The bedroom.
So the guy just bought one of these straight pipe Harleys or a straight cherry bomb pipe.
He likes to restore 1960s pickup trucks.
He has a straight muffler on there, right?
So now his garage is next to your bedroom,
and he likes to get up at 4.30 in the morning and fire up his Harley,
go to work at the airport.
You see what I mean?
And all the houses are like that.
Why should they be mirror image?
Mirror image, so you'd have one house, the garage on the right,
living room in the middle, bedroom on the left.
Now the house, let's say, to the right of it where the garage is,
instead of putting the bedroom on that house, put the garage there also.
So it's garage to garage, bedroom to bedroom.
Garage to garage, bedroom to bedroom.
Not garage, bedroom, garage, bedroom, garage, bedroom.
Yeah, I saw a retirement community set up like this in New Jersey where it was like that,
where you had the garages were next to each other.
That's exactly how it was done.
Yeah, a mirror image, mirror image, not just cookie cutter, the same floor plan,
build it here, build it there.
You just flip it around.
When you have two houses next to each other, they're not identical layout.
You make one a mirror image of the other.
So the garage to garage, bedrooms to bedrooms.
Now if he's a screamer or he's a screamer and the windows are open in the summertime,
it's better to hear that bedroom to bedroom than to hear a straight tailpipe, let's say.
Some people would rather hear the straight tailpipe.
I don't know, but you see what I mean.
I'd take the screamer over the tailpipe.
So what I'm saying is the architects didn't even have enough sense to know that.
It's not basic.
There are some neighborhoods that were designed like, for example,
the Sam Hughes neighborhood here.
When you go into that neighborhood, none of the roads are straight.
They're all windy and curvy.
And the reason they did that is because when the architects laid out that street,
they did mirror image.
And also when you stood at your front door to get the paper or open your front door
to see what the weather was like outside, you wouldn't see the other person's front door.
So your house is on a very windy road.
So all the houses are facing a slight different elevation.
So no front door could see the front door of another house.
All right, I get it.
It makes you feel more private.
You can't see through another person's house.
So these are very, very, very, very basic things.
Now, if I were an architect, what I would do,
instead of making the nightmarish architectural stuff that the ego,
it's all ego, look what I built and how expensive it was.
If I were going to a city, town, whatever, and build something,
let's say a new mall or a new building, it doesn't matter what it is.
I'm going to see what's in the surrounding area I already built,
and I'm going to copy that.
And what I'm building is going to have a very similar facade, right?
Almost exact, almost make it the same looking,
as if I've just copied that building that was there 50 years ago.
But I won't just copy it.
I'm going to fix all the mistakes and improve it.
So when I build my structure, and my structure is built,
it doesn't look like anything was built, right?
New, no eyesore, no ego, no, right?
It'll look like it was always there.
Like, for instance, if you've got a lot of things in the neighborhood
that are brick-faced, right, you're going to make sure it's got a brick face.
This kind of thing.
Sort of.
You might want it.
It depends.
If you have too many brick faces,
and the lines of the bricks line up too much,
you're going to feel like you're in a prison wall.
So you might want to break it, right?
To give you an example,
when I sit in the living room and eat,
I put a TV on with YouTube,
and I usually put in what we're eating or topic or whatever on YouTube
and watch that as a background.
And the architecture came up.
Frank Lloyd Wright.
What?
Some ugly shit.
Ugly garbage.
Oh, he's working with nature.
Are you joking?
If you look at the, you know, I mean, yes, I understand, you know,
he believed in designing the furniture and all that.
That stuff is ugly.
Tear it down.
It's got terrible roof lines and leaks.
The stuff that they're telling you as classics is junk.
Just look at it.
How does it make you feel, right?
Like when you first were young and you saw what they called modern art,
what was the feeling you got?
Repulsed, right?
But later on you didn't mind it because you didn't want to sound weird.
So you had to say it was, you know, okay, just like everybody else.
You see what I mean about how the psychic gets psyched out into it?
So the architecture, you know, the architecture is very much like this.
It's not, okay, I'll use this as a metaphor.
You know, in cliche, you know,
first of all everything they tell the collective is untrue.
You know, like they give you a cliche that the collective uses.
It's the oldest profession, right?
And what do they say?
That's prostitution, right?
Prostitution is the oldest profession, yeah, right.
Yeah, that's what they say, but it's not true.
The oldest profession is mining.
But use your head anyway.
How is that going to be the oldest profession?
Somebody had to have something to trade for that.
It can't be the oldest profession.
Yeah, exactly.
So in other words, you can't even do agriculture without mining
because in order to cut wood you need metal.
If you were just limited to wood to cut wood, you're not going to get –
you're just limited to a bunch of organic shapes
and the people that show up first are going to get the best shapes
and you've got to wait 30 years for something else to maybe grow in that shape.
You need to find surface metal material and hard substances,
obsidian, stone, glass, natural forms of glass, metals,
and start making tools.
The oldest profession is tool making for humans, right?
And then it goes on from there.
Then it's agriculture and then maybe what they say.
But the collective is fine with that.
Like what came first, the chicken or the egg?
Again, stupid.
The chicken came first, dummy.
Of course.
Oh, here's an egg.
I don't know what it's going to be.
Bullshit.
Everything reproduces after its own kind.
So all these things they put out.
Okay, so I can keep going with those analogies.
Architecture is an analogy of the collective.
It's supposed to be design, beauty, and all that, and it's ugly chaos.
Ego and money.
And things that I talked about tonight, you could find a lot of videos.
There's over 5 million videos at least or websites or whatever we're talking about
or pages on how modern architecture is ugly as sin.
There's more of that than there is that it's not.
There's a massive social outrage against architecture for the past 30 years,
massive outrage.
And then no one's listening.
Now, nothing's being done because it's the decline of a society.
It's an unwinding society.