Ah, Sonic Event 133, this one is anyway, Greek, you know, interesting conversation we were
having before we started recording, as always, by the way, yeah, you're trying to say what
we say about the conversation on the recording is not interesting.
No, not at all.
Not at all.
I just look, I actually have a couple of things that we recorded before we started talking
a few times that I put together, and I might release those soon.
But anyway, as is today, what is on your mind?
I looked in the chat, by the way.
And I noticed that somebody was talking about, you know, some of the stuff that you had discussed
regarding the monetary system, and yeah, we're gonna get into more tonight real quick and
give a confirmation.
Oh, excellent.
Okay.
I also had a question from somebody about murder, by the way, um, in a contact, it was
a Facebook contact, weird Facebook contact.
Somebody who never had a Facebook account until like this month.
And I know the person.
Well, I hear you.
I know someone who's never going to have a Facebook account.
Yeah, you.
Anyway.
Yeah.
But anyway, those things first came out, by the way, just like YouTube, PayPal, or whatever.
I will never do that.
I will never, ever, ever, ever, ever do that.
And guess what?
It's been what, a decade or so?
I'm still holding my word.
Well, it's more than a day.
Look, PayPal.
I got a PayPal account when they were giving you five bucks to sign up, and I did that
in 97.
Oh, how did they give you five bucks to sign up?
Listen to the past few, uh, uh, we're talking.
Yeah.
You know, the U.S. was bankrupted again in 2003.
That's where the Paperwork Reduction Act comes from.
Right.
But anyway, that's where everything's done digitally.
Absolutely.
Just like when they bankrupted in 33, now everything was a check.
Well, that's why.
Not a certificate.
That's why.
I know when they bankrupted it before, you know, hold on.
When they bankrupted it 70 years before that, in 1863, what did they do then?
They put the entire country under, essentially, not martial law, but military rule, General
Rule 100.
Anyway, so these are just simple, basic things that are not being communicated.
What about murder, though?
Yeah, no.
Lincoln's suspension of the Constitution happened right around then, didn't it?
Yeah.
And Congress went into, uh, more quo or something, like they can meet, but it's not official.
Right.
In other words, they could meet, but it's not official.
And when they meet, they could still keep the congressional record going and all this,
but it's not official.
That's why there's an official congressional record paper that's printed every single day,
which tells you the minutes of what happened.
And okay.
Anyway, about murder.
Murder.
Murder, right.
So the reason why they asked about it is because we had done a sonic years ago on hell.
And we talked about it and we were kind of making jokes about it.
That's all misinterpretation.
And the hell that the Christians talk about is Dante's Inferno type.
Yes.
And that's the weird thing, because Dante is not making a commentary on Christianity.
No, no, no.
But his whole thing is just like the Necrocomicon.
There's some truth in it.
Yes.
Right.
There's a lot of truth in it.
You know, the the.
All right.
You know, when you do a flyby on a planet and the surface is totally there means it's
an advanced civilization, just like when you do a drone fly over a subdivision, you don't
see like beds and couches on people's roofs.
Right.
And right where we're in the chairs and tables on the roof.
Where is everything inside?
Right.
You might see some patio furniture or whatever.
Yeah.
But but the earth is in the perspective that humans have is strictly from the surface mentality.
And any advanced society will not be on the surface in any world, let's just say, whether
you believe there's such a thing as space or not.
The concept is, is there to dictate something that, you know, that I just illustrated.
But go ahead.
So, yeah.
Hell.
Concept of hell.
Yeah.
The concept of hell.
OK.
So here's the thing about murder and all this, because during that same time period, we also
did a discussion on sexuality and perversion and, you know, people having sex with animals,
which you're the only guy I've ever heard talk about how, you know, there really were
these hybrids, et cetera.
And you know, the whole thing about man laying down by the way, animal to death.
Yeah.
So I think it's human and jellyfish are the two known species that could pretty much intermix
with anything.
That is weird.
That is outside of the other aberration.
What is it?
There's more than rats.
More.
Yeah.
You've seen on the cloning where they grow a human ear on a rat.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
But you can't grow a rat ear on a human.
No.
But anyway.
Yeah.
OK.
So let's let's go.
And then.
OK.
Well, see, and that's the thing.
So what is special here?
And the question is, what is the deterrent?
Right.
I mean, you talked about with sexuality and with mixing with animals and with men mixing
with men, et cetera.
But then what about murder?
Because we never discussed, is there really a justifiable or a righteous killing, et cetera,
this kind of thing?
According to, you know, biblical law.
And my response was, look, to my mind, biblical law is by agreement.
It's by agreement.
OK.
Social.
What's the difference between adultery and being polyamorous?
Right.
What's the difference?
It's the same action.
What's the difference between rape and and regular consensual sex is the the consent.
So with murder of someone, murder is as prescribed, killing another person.
But when it's socially accepted, like in other words.
The law we live in is if you an eye for an eye, if you take a life, your life is taken
and they have an open court and everybody agrees and they cap, you know, they hang the
guy or whatever, shoot him.
Is that murder?
Capital punishment.
Right.
Is it?
No.
It's all about consent.
And that's why it's so important since I've been speaking.
Pick a law form and that's your law form.
And I'm going to get into something here that goes back to 2013, 2014, maybe.
But does that satisfy the question?
It's all based on what law form you live under.
Well, I think it does.
But there you go.
Right.
So the executioner is not subject to being a murderer, even though he doesn't know the
subject.
He's actually serving a purpose in a societal agreement.
Right.
Well, OK.
Let's leave the murder out of it.
Replace it with adultery and being polyamorous, meaning having more than one partner.
Right.
Not polygamous.
Or even violence or even violence versus BDSM.
Right.
Which, you know, is pretty simple.
OK.
I've got stories about all that stuff.
Well, OK.
I didn't want to go there, but.
Yeah.
But that's fine.
That story's accounts that these accounts.
So whenever you give an account, it's you have to give it in the form of a story where
you preface and form and discuss, but, you know, the discussion is just you and I right
now.
Right.
And I think what we speak on over time has brought up discussions in other places, which
will.
Yeah.
So, you know, it's all about the culture.
That's why it's so important to know your law law form and where you get your law form
from.
And, you know, so that's all about murder has to do with law.
If you go back to the Bible, murder, no murder.
But it's OK to go if you're ordered to destroy everything and everyone, even the children
of a certain, you know, under certain conditions.
It's all conditional.
Right.
All conditional.
So in that case, the concept of where the soldiers don't go to hell, that's that sort
of thing, which is a very Italian.
And I think they're glorified.
Actually, right.
They're glorified.
Yeah.
I had 50 kills.
I killed 50 Nazis.
Right.
So you got you got a Greek concept, which was then picked up by the Romans, which has been
carried on throughout society ever after, I think.
Right.
It's before the Greeks and it's up until now, it's it's yeah, it's always been this way.
In other words, the social order has been always about law and culture, what's accepted
and what's not and what what's consented to and what's not.
So if it's consented, anything goes.
Right.
This kind of ties in.
I wanted to give an account also.
Are we good?
Yeah.
I think so.
Sure.
Good.
Now, another thing that you'll find is back in the early days of 2010, I used to call
in American Freedom Radio, Revolution Radio, and then with Seth Michael late at night,
I would do three, four or five hours with him on a weekend in 2010, 2011, 2012.
And then I think we started we didn't get, quote unquote, a show till much later.
But I would call it and be a fixture on American Freedom Radio, Revolution Radio and by demand.
People say, hey, Greek, we want you to come on.
I'm like, yeah, not tonight or tonight.
I could do it.
So one of the things that I was putting on blast back then was, you know, people go to
court asking for justice.
Do you know what you're asking for?
Yeah, I want, you know, right ruling to the right thing.
High moral code.
I said, no, no.
Do you know what you're really asking for?
So I was I put that on blast and I think I might be the only person who's ever done that.
You're actually asking for the intervention of the goddess justice.
And yeah, that it's a pagan goddess.
And I'm the only one that I've actually framed it that way on blast, meaning when I would
come on and give a dose of Greek speak.
That's what you got.
You got time.
You got the human body.
All right.
Well, I was researching Christopher Houser on trust law.
I want to get into a little bit of that's very important.
And he did a video on Lady Justice.
And he says around 2013, 2014, a buddy of his came out to me, says, you know what that
justice thing is?
And he says, yeah, you know, it gives the dictionary definition made a long story short
because I'm going to give the remedy here because I used to give.
Why do you say that?
Right.
Because these are not courts.
It's like there's no Congress and all that.
Right.
Because people say, how do I get out of this court case?
Well, you don't really want to get out of there if you belong there.
If you don't belong there, you don't have to think about getting out of there.
Just give them a surefire reason why you don't belong there.
Right.
Never.
You know what I mean?
People say, how do I get out of this?
I said, why do you want you should never want to get out of something.
Is it something?
Is it your responsibility to deal with it or you shouldn't be there in the first place
is the question.
And you should have good reasons for both.
Right.
So people say, how do I get out of this court case?
And then and they tell me they just want to get out.
I'm not going to.
Yeah, I got a solution.
You got it's your responsibility.
But if someone does answer, how do I get out of this?
Well, because you don't want to handle a responsibility or you just don't belong there in the first
place.
If it's I don't belong there in the first place, then this is what you do.
Right.
And I do give advice on that legal advice and lawful advice.
But not at law, you know, in law, in fact.
So interesting thing here is anyway, Hauser looks at his friend, tell us what just is.
Listen, I'm going to call you.
This is 2013, 2014.
He says, why don't you look it up and we'll talk about it in a couple of weeks.
Well, Hauser looks into it.
Christopher Hauser keeps finding these definitions, but finally finds one that it's a Roman pagan
goddess borrowed from the Greek D.I.K.E.
D.K.
Dyke goddess who was on the Isle of Lesbos.
Right.
Can't make that up.
And so he said to and he says to pay us.
So what he did was he went into court.
Yeah.
Now, Howard Stern didn't invent that.
By the way.
Yeah.
Right.
And.
And yeah, so he goes into court.
This is the first time I felt like a man.
I had a man up and reason I had to go to court is because he was being tracked or tailed
because he was dealing in copious amounts of marijuana.
OK, so at a pound or half a pound of marijuana in the car.
And when they turn the lights on, the cops behind him, he tossed it out the window.
They got out, picked it up, took him in, you know, all that.
Right.
So I had to go to court for that.
And so that's where to go court for. So he shows up early, and he judged everybody that comes in,
and he says, I'd like to ask a question. The judge says, go ahead. He says,
are you here to serve justice? And the judge kind of giggles. He says, yes, I try to do my best.
You know, then he looks at the prosecutor. Are you here to serve justice? I guess so.
Looks at the clerk. Are you here to serve justice? Yeah, I guess so. He says,
how dare you bring me into a pagan house of worship? Right? You're serving, right? You
serve God, right? Serve justice, right? It's a temple, pagan temple. And they all got befuddled,
and they told him, case dismissed. Now, this is not the first one, but this is on YouTube.
Now, I wanted to reach out to Chris Houser and say, by the way, did your friend happen to hear
about this from a guy called the Greek back then? Anyway, I had interviews, various copious
interviews, because I'm the only one as far as, like, in other words, I'm not, I don't want to be
belligerent about it or take credit for it, but if suddenly you see a YouTube video about saying,
I spoke to a friend about keeping time, that the full moon is the first day of the month,
and the day starts at noon. The chances that they got it from listening to some Greek speak,
or someone who knew someone who knew someone that listened to Greek speak is about 99.999999%,
right? So that's why I'm bringing this up, because it's so unusual, and it's so simple.
Now, I want to bring up a few things about Chris Houser. I remember I was studying trust law.
Now, most of the stuff that he puts out, again, this is like Brandon Joe Williams.
I don't endorse him, because a lot of the stuff he says about 1099A, ignore, because that gets
people in trouble, and I'll explain what that is. The US has been, this is the story that people
don't know. The US was bankrupt in 1933, and public law 73-10 or HCR 192 states that, and it's also in
the codes, in the UCC codes, that all debts are owed to the United States, right? Because they
didn't put it out for vote, should we be, you're right, go bankrupt, right? So because they did
that, and remember, this whole system is set up by demonic people, you know, the bankers, right?
If you don't know that the bankers are Satanists, not that I have anything against it directly,
because all the religions basically follow a similar path, but you have to understand what
Satanism is. If someone says, I'm Catholic, devout Catholic, you don't have to ask him what he does,
just go look up what devout Catholics do, right? So if someone says, be basically inclined to
Satanism, you don't have to ask them what do you do, just go look up what they do, right? It's
general. So this is the banking system. But the US went bankrupt in 1933. And they put out all
these public laws and all the debts belong to the US, United States, the corporation that's
somewhere in the District of Columbia. Now, what they did also, they did it under trust law. Now,
I can't find this, I think it's 1990-1992. James Traficant was on the floor of Congress. And he
says, here we are, congressmen in front of the largest chapter 11 and the largest trust in human
history in basically the United States, right? In receivership, and I can't, I was trying to find
the speech on Google, right? I did another browser still couldn't find the speech, where years ago,
it was easy to find the speech that he spelled this out in the 90s, right? Traficant, the guy
with the pompadour style toupee, you know? Right. You know, what's interesting about that is if you
go to C-SPAN, you might find it in the C-SPAN archives. Oh, okay, maybe, you know, we've got
some people that do due diligence. James Traficant's speech on the United States is the
largest trust, and it's a chapter 11 bankruptcy receivership. So anyway, what he gets into is
anyone, all the people, regardless if you're a citizen, resident, and all the stuff that
Brandon talks about, are a beneficiary of this trust. Now, if you understand trust law,
the trust is set up with a grantor, a beneficiary, who is supposed to benefit,
and everybody else working in the trust is for that person's benefit. So here's a simple
example to make it easy. You are a beneficiary, especially if you sign all this paperwork,
and you give a social, any place they ask for a social security number or social insurance number,
and you have to sign, and you sign with a B-N-E, B-E-N-E dot, short for beneficiary,
after your name. You now assume the title that any actions of anyone that has to do anything
with that form has to benefit you. Now, I used to tell this to people a long time ago, but I
never saw it so clear like Hauser talks about it. Like, give me an example. There's somebody here
in Tucson. They had a pirate radio. They got busted by the FCC. They'll find you, by the way,
if you broadcast more than a watt and a half. They'll find you. They'll knock on your door.
You're like, how the hell did they find me? Even if you're in a moving van, they'll plot,
they'll plot your, they'll map you out and try to predict where you're next going to go.
Well, there was a minor change to the AM stipulations, and you can use a 10-watt
tower from your backyard now. Legally, no license, nothing necessary.
Yeah, go ahead.
Yeah, but we're talking, this is a decade and a half ago. We've got some other stuff going on.
Skipped out on this bench warrant, whatever. So anyway, he goes in there, and they go through
all these counts. And the judge says, how do you plead all this? And he says, I can't,
I'm not here to argue the facts. I'm not going to plea anything. I can't see how any of this
would benefit me. The judge looks down, puts his, Judge Green, not going to mention any names,
in Tucson. This guy, this judge made so much money for them that they actually built him his
own building. Anyway, he pulls his, he had these half-style reading glasses. You know which ones
I'm talking about?
Oh, yeah.
The half-style, yeah. Puts them on his nose, looks at him for about 10 seconds. He goes,
okay, case dismissed. Get out of here.
The bifocals without the top focal.
That's right, yeah. So anyway, when you are a beneficiary, let's say you go to a court or
anything, a cop, cop pulls you over, gives you a ticket. You sign it beneficiary.
And anything the cop, okay, the cop is going to attach social security number. The bank is
going to attach social security. Anybody that's got a social security, social insurance number
has to act for your benefit, right? You see what I mean? So it's all a trust action.
And if you say it's not for your benefit, it's trust violation, trust fraud, trust
impairment. You can go on and on and on. And they can't say no. Now, one way you can entrap
them is if you go like people for social security benefits or a traffic ticket or a court or session
or whatever. Everybody talks about the all caps name as a straw man, I guess, defined to convey
property. It is a straw man, but it's different. It's the name of the trust. Now, what you can do
is, and I've seen this, you go to a court, it doesn't matter what it's for, traffic ticket,
anything, or DMV, anything, anything at all. It could be your telephone company.
If you have the B, A, E, N, E on your signature card, your beneficiary, you just ask them what I
signed here, whatever it is, corporation, government. Did you take my social security
number? You could say my social security number on the record. Yes, we did. What is the social
security? It's a trust. And I signed a beneficiary. So anything you do that is not to my benefit
is a trust fraud, trust misdemeanor, trust impairment. You can go under several, yeah,
it depends on what they do and how far they take it. Very, very powerful. Social security benefits.
I know a lady, she's not getting basically a thousand dollars a month to live on. And she's
broken neck and all that stuff. The thing for her to do is to go there and basically say,
I can't live on this. And just ask them the same thing. You have my social security number.
Let them say what it is. What is the social security? It's a trust. It's a SESTICA trust.
SESTICA means it has a definite beneficiary. SESTICA trusts came about back in the sailing
days when a port was in Dock and Harbor and it left, disembarked, and it left some rope behind
or a piece of cargo or a tool. The harbor master had to put it aside with that ship's name on it,
right? Because it's not his. And he can't use it for his benefit.
So that's where it came from back in one of the places. This is on the Tontine and all that.
So this is the crux of what Hauser talks about. Now, what he was doing. So if you go to buy a car,
what basically he was teaching people to do is you just go to the car salesman or whatever,
a new car or used car, new car, because it doesn't matter what the cost is. Remember,
I've been saying for years, you just take a piece of paper, write any number on it,
write it out in words and sign it. It's good for that. It could be a trillion. It doesn't matter.
Right. But if everyone, okay, I want to make one more point before we go. But anyway, he was
telling the car people, well, you know, my credit sucks, but run it anyway. Boom. Soon as they run
your credit report, don't they have the social security number on them? Yes. Absolutely. Didn't
you sign it with a beneficiary signature? Yes. Now they're holding the bag preventing you from
getting something that you need. You give them a 1099 a and you put the treasury on the form as
what the debtor because remember, the law says the United States owes everything is owed. Right,
right. All debts are. Yeah. Yeah. So running this, some people got the cars in there. But what he
doesn't talk about people is if you read the full instructions for these forms, you can't use it for
this kind of stuff. It's really basically between financial institutions or investments, cashing out
investments and all that. But a lot of people did get cars. But a lot when he since he got on
YouTube, I know someone who did get a new Harley Davidson pickup truck and was working getting a
house and he got all that stuff. But two years later, the Attorney General came after him for
using public funds. Right. And a federal court. And I remember in the in the federal court,
this is a deck more than a decade ago. He brought up laws like the laws we just brought up in the
justice. You can't use law here because it's not it's not a court. It's an administrative hearing.
Right. Yeah. People don't know. How do you prove. OK, that's enough for that. I just want to give
the spirit. How do you know it's not. You have three branches of government. Right. And they're
supposed to balance each other out. Right. We don't have to mention here, but we'll mention
him anyway. Legislative, judicial. Right. Executive. Right. Now, the way the courts are
since the Civil War or the War of the States or the War of Northern Aggression is this. Yes. You
can see this right now. This what happens is the executor appoints a judge and it has to be
confirmed by the legislator legislature. And once the judge is in this, this is on all levels,
federal, state, local, whatever. They do election ballots. They still have to be confirmed by.
Now, who runs the courts? Who's the top poncho? The attorney general. And he's what? Is he
judicial? No, he's part of the executive branch. Right. And the legislature confirms it. Where's
the judicial branch in this? There is no judicial branch. It's all a mockery. It's all because you
can't have. How many times have you heard me say on sonic events? OK, Greek, so what? It doesn't
matter. It doesn't matter if we don't have money. We use anything and we get what we want. Yes,
it does matter, because when you lose your money, what's defined as money, not finances,
but money has to have some kind of value. You lose law. You're no longer under law.
Everything's commercial. That's the problem. Right. So now here, just to fast forward,
what I want to say that actually for a couple of weeks now, I haven't put it so succinctly.
If everything OK, there are rules written down, whether you like them or believe them or not.
Can you go and find, let's say, for the financial system how it's supposed to work? Yes,
there is a UCC. There's each country. Each state has its rules and laws. Right. If everyone I'm
talking about, the person who gets the electric bill or the rise in bill and wants to buy
something with a credit card, those people with the big financial companies or whatever,
it doesn't matter or with what's called taxation. If everyone followed those rules,
it would destroy the system. Right. Right. Because you should be able to go into a car dealer,
a Ferrari dealer and say, I want two Ferraris. Right. And you write it on a piece of paper,
sign it, and he'll give you the two Ferraris. Why will it destroy the system? Because by the end of
the week, it'll be eighteen hundred dollars for a gallon of milk. All right. And people who work
only with cash, you're going to need more than a wheelbarrow. You need a pallet that's shrink
wrapped with forklift to go buy a refrigerator. Right. OK, so you're going to need trillions and
trillions of quadrillions in cash. It's going to become impractical again. It's going to be worse,
less impractical than having to bring gold or silver coins in. Right. So right. Imagine a
thousand silver. It's a thousand silver coins. Right. No, I carry it. You know,
I tried carrying a hundred silver coins to pain in the ass. I mean, that's only a hundred dollars.
Prima facie. Right. OK, so so anyway, and they really are a hundred dollars. So so if everyone
followed the rules and the financial, the financial system would completely collapse.
Let's go to another system. Religion. That's easy. If what is Christianity supposedly based on,
say, the Bible, if they did what was in the Bible, Christianity would not exist.
Same with Islam. Same with all those religions. So if people followed the rules of religion or
finance, both of those systems would completely collapse. Same with the medical. If people
follow the rules with the medical, everyone knew, in other words, the patients, the doctor,
everyone knew everything that was memorialized or enough of it that it was accurate.
They wouldn't say you're a slab of meat with calories. And, you know, basically,
if you listen to Greek speak, you know, I define what they tell you is that you're a
pressurized filter bag. Right. Right. Right. By the way, you know, I see the heart is not a pump.
A lot of people say that. OK, but you got to do research when you say that, because you know what
a pacemaker is when they do experimental work on people with pacemakers. Some of them say it's OK
to experiment on me, whatever. Right. While they're still alive, they have a button on the
pacemaker and they notice that when they make the heart pulse faster, the blood moves slower.
And when they push a stream of blood through the heart and a living person
really fast, the heart slows down. What kind of fucking pump is that?
If you're making the pump, the heart pulse twice as fast and the blood goes half as fast,
slower and slower, the faster you go, what kind of pump is that? What kind of pump works that way?
And that would be more accurately described as a regulator, wouldn't it?
Sounds like a regulator or brakes. The more you use the brakes, the slower the car goes. Right.
Yes, a regulator. OK, so I just want to throw that in because I think every medical journal
in the world has published something about what I just said. Right. They may not leave it up,
but anyway, it'd be interesting to see what's left. So, you know, the faster the blood goes
through the heart, the slower the heart goes. And then when the heart is artificially sped up,
the blood goes through slower. That's a that's a wonderful pump design. Yeah, right. OK,
so if they looked at the tissue, like I've gotten so many people saying, you know,
the tissue in the body is hydrophobic. You know, in other words, no moisture
goes through it at all. There's no absorption. This, that and the other.
They wouldn't say that you're just a pressurized filter bag. Let's say you're a walking miracle.
You're a walking, magical, mysterious miracle. And we wouldn't need it. It wouldn't it would
be a joke to do what they're doing right now. And we would all go back more to studying
the, you know, like the ether. Right. How that works. What is it? Right. And we wouldn't have
a disease. First of all, half of the diseases that people think they have would go away instantly
because, you know, there's no blood sugar. There's no right. All these diseases that do.
So what will happen is the medical system will completely fall apart if people found out really
what was memorialized. You see how it works. And this is how everything on Earth is. And
right now, every subject, any subject, even engineering,
you know, you know, they they practice exclusions when they do physics experiments and they see
anomalies. They don't want to include those things in there. When the early transistors
were invented by Schlotzky and these guys in the 1920s to get away from vacuum tubes,
they were wet. They weren't there. They were solid, but they were wet putties.
They would shut down the lab at night and come back the next day and the things would be on
by themselves. Right. They had to get rid of that. Right. We don't want somebody to buy a radio,
plug it in for a few hours, unplug it. And then the thing starts playing again. Right.
So anything, every subject under the sun, anything that has any social structure will
completely fall apart if the people just knew what was written about these things.
And that's pretty much the reality you're living in. So you can't tell me this is a real world.