The Sonic Fenton T-Mobile has been saved and retrieved.
Sonic Event rated Y 62.
Okay, now, a note for the listener on the Pope's work schedule, it is what they call Halloween.
Yeah, Salon.
Day of the Dead.
Interesting, interesting thing there because I asked you about, you know, some other customs
out there where people get dressed up and whatnot but it is it is one of these
things that's happened throughout different cultures but this is one of
those things that prevails now I wonder you know how is it that you interpret
what you see regarding this you know saw one day of the dead transitional time
period I mean it is in the fall after all but yeah I'm gonna go back to the
the archaics Jason Brashear's he's brought up something interesting that I
might have seen in passing but he nailed it a little bit more that was one
you know in Genesis everything was created in the second verse everything
is dark and void and destroyed right that happened around this time it's also
in many cultures it would be around what we call the ninth month or this time
where the fall after the ingathering in most cultures the fall was the
ingathering that's when you knew how well I was gonna say how rich you were
but yeah in the fall as you is when you did all the accounting for all of your
assets just like in a lot of in the corporate world it's September is when
their financial year ends or you know they pushed it out to the regular
calendar and they do quarters but it used to be that you knew what you were
worth by the end of the fall and when they did that in ancient culture they
were all completely destroyed by the way in that culture if you harken back to
Jeremiah and all that wait it doesn't mention that tohu wohu again total
destruction it was very advanced culture much more advanced than we are right now
you know so in other words you'd have like remember back to the future of the
hoverboard right that's how they got around you know hoverboards and baby
strollers were hovering and stuff like that it was all they didn't have an
infrastructure like this and ever since then I think I've gotten into a little
bit how the atom that we talked about mostly that was the dumbed-down version
of humanity you know eighth David eighth day man right pathetic creature right it
was a right where the man on sixth day was not at all he actually got a
blessing and so yeah it goes back into that I believe that if you look
cross-culturally around this time that would be fairly accurate to what we could
bring forward not accurate like we know but accurate in terms of what could be
forward by consensus of ancient collections Ritz even according to the
people it's pretty strange nowadays because I remember some years ago there
was this discussion about levitation being a more common thing that could be
achieved by earlier societies which totally explained you know how is it
that they got the giant stones to be moved here or there and these different
places etc etc and the weird thing is even the woo-woo among us right you know
the ones who come up with all kinds of fanciful explanations of everything they
never talk about that anymore they don't even mention that there might have
been levitation actually and yet no no they don't even talk about what happened
two weeks ago no but by the way since you're mentioning levitation I just want
to bring this in is a I had a personal talk today for two and a half hours with
Kurt Hallberg who's who's he water world watch Rico realize he's been working on
Victor Shaw burger stuff since 1996 he's an engineer he's in his late 60s or mid
60s and he's in Sweden and Sam got us together because I brought up Malmo
Sweden it was pretty big let's say 10-15 years ago people in Sweden and Olaf
Alexanderson people are familiar with Victor Shaw burger right you could look
him up and since you brought up levitation I'll just want to insert this
will be interesting for those I believe that but by the way I've been having
some private Skype calls with some some of our subs and they're really a good
bunch of people by the way you know I'm very happy so that's why I'm
suggesting that most people would well presuming know who Victor Shaw burger
would be and we think of Victor Shaw burger now you get like kind of a neo
Nazi thing that he made flying saucers and all that right yeah that's that's a
common reference right yeah right but the thing that he had written was about
how one of the devices broke free from a table it was bolted down with six
quarter-inch bolts which takes you know several more than several tons to break
that free and levitate so we got into a conversation about water he's a seasoned
individual in the field and knows a lot he spends time at the Victor Shaw burger
mansion the PKS Institute in Austria so we got into the secret part the part
about Shaw burger that you won't find in books the part about Shaw burger that
you won't find on the internet and I think some of the people listening here
might have enough interest and if you've never heard of Victor Shaw burger this
would actually fill in what I just said stuff you will not find anywhere because
you brought up levitation my mind I wanted to bring him up anyway for two
things one about the emo and one of what I'm about to say now regarding the
secrets of Shaw burger right and one thing he asked me says have you heard of
Shaw burger cement as in cement right and and I was like no what is it so
basically it's three materials a quartz silica very fine colloidal very fine
aluminum powder and what's called water glass which is like a silica again gel
they use it water glass is like a very it's clear as water it's real thick
syrup back from the 1930s to the 1970s if you had a hole in your car radiator
you pour this stuff in and when it leaked out it dried and made a seal right but it
is water-soluble yeah that's another thing that has actually kind of
disappeared from a bunch of industrial things I know that was in use for a
bunch of reasons this sort of weird stuff that would kind of go into a gap
fill it it was like yeah I almost thought that's what they were
introducing when they put out that new sealant stuff in a can that they've been
making you know big way they're doing it but with plastics because the bad thing
about the water glass is if you wet the radiator from the outside like drove
through a you know the rain or hosed it down it would break and you have to do
it again because it is water-soluble but it's slightly water-resistant but
anyway what they what they did with this material Shawberger did he made like a
cement of it and like a putty it would almost look like modeling clay and when
he built his devices he would coat them with this cement right so it would almost
look like one of those mud brick ovens right okay and that's how he got some of
the effects and the reason I'm bringing this up is it's a very clandestine group
the Shawberger group they speak only German they are you know it's a they they
spend their time in the basement of the place you know where Shawberger you know
the things they don't bring out into the public at all this is not in any of the
books or any of the internet so I just thought I'd bring that out the other
thing I want to bring out about speaking with Kurt Halberg is he mentioned some
dowsing but no dowsing that you know is unusual you call it the emotional dowsing
I was like oh you know I'm being quiet here you know because it's emo work
right and I said what do you mean by that he said well you're out in a field
and you lose your wallet you want to find your wallet so what you do is you
go to the edge of the field and you start thinking about your wallet you
know how it feels how it looks how it smells every how it you know touch
everything about it and you bring up the emotions that you experience when you
think of the wallet how it looks how it feels and all that and you do that for a
few minutes and then you take out some dowsing rods and immediately the
dowsing rods will point exactly to your what where your wallet is and I was
like funny you should mention that because I've been doing he's more
telling people that the emo work can be turned into affecting your physical real
world and become practical instead of hearing about a mild-mannered guy who
shot five people because he went into an emotional tizzy right and how we're
never told what the purpose of emotions are but we're always right considering
them and no it's almost like you don't know what that thing is you know you
imagine going into a place where these objects someone works with every day and
you well this thanks for bringing me to where you work what's this and he says I
don't know is it we've been working here 40 years you don't know what that is
Wow you know you see what I mean right that's how the emotions are for people
if you ask them what they are well you know they'll say well their emotions you
know you know emotions and it's a buzz far as they go so I thought those two
points were very interesting I wanted to bring them up and what prompted just the
the initial the rapid insert is that you brought up levitation so no no problem
look it makes perfect sense too because I mean I've known people that have
lived in neighborhoods for years where there's a distinct smell that like kind
of hangs over the area they have no idea what it is where it comes from
nothing they just know it's there they know it doesn't yeah it doesn't take
well we spoke on one of the Sonics about interest you should be interested in
everything what what you invest your time in you know ergo your career or
whatever is different but you hear people say you know I've covered this
many times you know well I'm not into math I'm not good at math you know so
and they leave it as such for the rest of their life right like like it will never
affect them of course it's gonna affect them well I'm not good at this I
don't know anything about electronics right but you're using it all the time
but what's that in your hand right what's that at home what right yeah so
yeah this is where the the service communities take advantage you know the
mechanics right and the reply I remember I got really upset with someone I was
living with we we bought a VCR back in the late 80s for about 70 bucks and it
stopped working and without telling me person took the VCR the next day to a
repair shop and so where's the VCR so what's not working so I took a repair
shop so I'll go get a repair shop but he wants $95 because he examined it and he
says it's really it's gonna be 250 to fix and I'm like I paid 75 bucks for it
I'm not gonna spend another 300 and he demanded his $95 you know and I'm like
oh my gosh I just got ripped off right right you see you know same with cars
I've had a neighbor who spent $700 on a tune-up but look at the car was it was
disgustingly dirty there's no way they tuned that up right this has been good
you know calling doctors right I just lawyers I just had a conversation
yesterday with somebody he says oh yeah I had to go get an oil change I spent
$90 I said what I said what are you spending $90 on an oil change for 90
bucks but here here Chuck really know the realistically realistically that
should be the price of an oil change to do a quality job well by the way so when
you hear about the cheap oil changes or when you do yourself I understand but
you know it's 100 bucks an hour you know for somebody to do service now yeah but
it does a it doesn't take that long be it's look you buy it yourself you can do
it yourself it's not that big a deal no but for many it is like for example give
me an example right now I'm in a situation where I could fix anything
right and I'm not bragging in a situation where if I had a chain if you
told me go change the oil in the car that you're using must be changed
tomorrow I won't do it I'll take it somewhere because I don't have the time I
just don't have the time right right I'm just involved with so many things and
what you know the water project so yeah one thing I also wanted to bring up that
I was thinking about I was having a conversation with individual about the
difference between intent and will okay think about that there is a difference
there yeah okay so difference in the simplest way from Greek in Greek speak
fashion is very simple okay intent is something that is exercised when you're
conscious awake thinking but will is always being exercised even when you're
asleep and unconscious it's still there hmm think about that for a moment we
don't need to get into that subject but I just might be sure I repeat it no I
like it because it look it's it sounds awfully oversimplified but it really
isn't it is it is very oversimplified but if you learn that you will sense the
difference between your intent and your will right and you will be able to
manage it a little bit better remember we say if you can't measure you can't
manage it if you don't know what the thing is how are you gonna manage it
right you should have the ability to wield both of them to some degree right
I mean it's not as though one of them is out of your control either is it well
the conditions are different if you go let's go that's repeated intent is
something that you exercise right when you're conscious awake during your
waking hours day but will is something that is constantly being exercised even
when you're asleep it's still active right where your intent is not but your
intent would influence your will would it not and actually the other way around
it's the other way around okay so I will is a very sure a will is something that
the body's mind takes part of I think we got got into a little bit about some
let's say take a typical suicidal case right a person is disenchanted with life
wants to die yeah while they're killing themselves they're there they just put up
with it and go for but the body's like don't kill me you know the body it's
conscious itself the part of the body that runs the heart the lungs the
metabolism does all the epithelial cell apoptosis all the natural functions the
body has its own mind you know every five times a second this all the cells
all the brain we're okay and every five times a second their brain asks the
cells are you okay you know like the like the switch I turn the switch on off
on off but you turn the switch off on off on right these complex things right
that's the mind the body of the mind so while this person is killing themselves
yes the body's like don't kill me don't kill me through this and we went through
this in both directions actually because the body also you see people that just
shut down after a while that's it the body just gives up well that's it well
just that's see one is the intent to kill oneself but the will of the body is
still there right so but but the can will be diminished well in the suicide
of course yes but in the suicide I'm just using the suicide case as an example
please don't know doesn't apply no no it can go in the other direction as well
where somebody has the intent to continue living but the will goes the
other way they die in their sleep I mean sure sure sure sure well that's
that's when you know people that's when they say they died happy mm-hmm right
they were ready you're ready to go but aside from death let's just say in a
functional situation right because that by the way death can be very functional
but it's quickly becomes dysfunctional non-functional I should say in a sense
intent is where you focus it's like the fine-tuning of a radio station and
dialing in the radio station but will is what volume you play that does that
help okay yeah right so you could play the say so your intent is you're moving
around all the bands you I want to listen to you k-rock or whatever right
or 101.7 where oh no I know I don't like that let's go to the next one let's go
to 95.7 let's try that one okay that was good that was good okay that's all your
intent moving around the dial but once you land on on that with intent now it's
like how loud are we gonna play it are we gonna make it really low background
are we gonna turn it up and jam yeah that's your will in my mind those things
are absolutely reversed normally that's their reverse they're exactly the
inverse of each other so okay I just I have to switch it around because the
will you don't have to do anything I'm just bringing this up because these are
things that no one talks about oh no I got you I'm just the way that I think of
it though is I would consider the will exactly the intent in the intent
exactly the will the way you're describing it but I don't know why that
well that's like that well that gets into the conundrum of the soul and the spirit
you look up spirit it says it's a soul and you look up soul it says it's the
spirit right there it's a con game right so anyway I'm not saying it's a con
game that if you believe the opposite but I'm just bringing this up because
it's thought for food yeah well no it's not like a belief like I have this
belief it's just that I thought that that's the way it was you know well this
is an outline to bring up so you can measure it because remember if you can't
measure it you can't manage it can you manage your intent can you manage your
will of course mm-hmm right well like I said one one works with the other it does
in a certain way because it can it can it doesn't have to it doesn't have to by
the way doesn't the will is almost autopilot yeah think about you've got
your car on cruise control that would be the will right versus versus you know
cruise control now you if you don't push that pedal the car slows down if
you push it too much it speeds up right and you also use the brake right so yeah
intent is the finer aspects of direction and will is the general overview of the
drive and the amplitude and here's the thing the important part that people
might say that I didn't go into is why is the wheel operating when you're
unconscious and asleep well that's just a really big question also and I'm
looking into that and now let me just suggest this or take it for what it's
worth and you're doing the JFK risk research you will probably understand
what I'm trying to say all the intelligence agencies throughout the
past 75 years really 50 years by you know when I say 50 years that's 1973 right
this makes me feel old 60 years since the event now just about yeah yeah but
I'm saying it's for 50 since best let's say 40 years they've been all the
intelligence agencies and somehow been publishing papers on consciousness you
know the woo-woo and right like the X-Files type stuff right and more and
more actually let's just be a little more accurate for people in the past
three years it's been more and more right three to five years so what they
all agreed on would take it however you want to take it you know is they said
that they from studying people our consciousness it they have evidence it
believes they believe more than presuming that when we're asleep our
consciousness is being used somewhere else and the will maintains that all
right the will is still there with us when we're somewhere else I'll leave it
at that because now the rest of it I'm gonna have to confabulate I really
haven't put together anything that I can really talk about regarding that well
you'd have a landscape of all the different influences because here you
are you're subject to external we talked about this before you're subject to
external input at this point you're always yeah but hold on this is also
external output because if you're being used somewhere else when you're asleep
you've just outputted yourself to where somewhere else like okay this is not a
play on words let's do a play on words since I said somewhere else you ready
okay okay let's say you and I are in the studio in the same room right sure and
I'm gonna say Chuck I'm gonna prove to you that I'm not here use and you're
gonna say okay that's funny how are you gonna do that are you standing right in
front of me right I can see I can hear you I can reach out over here and touch
you so I using using just legally I can prove to you that I'm not here using
words right okay so we're in front of each other right now and Chuck I'm gonna
prove to you that I'm not here you say okay go ahead so am I in Philadelphia
well no let's say we're where were you are right now we're in the union where
you're you're in my office you're making Georgia we're together yeah there you go
I'm in making George so am I in Philadelphia no okay so I must be
somewhere else okay so am I in Chicago no all right my in New York no all right
so if I'm not in Philadelphia I'm not in Chicago I'm not in New York I must be
somewhere else so if I'm somewhere else how can I be here well I would say that
somewhere else could be here it's just not described because somewhere else is
under is not right with the description but you see how it goes both ways if I'm
telling you I'm somewhere else just audibly even then I can't be here well
somewhere else yeah okay so you defined yourself as being somewhere else well
it's this let's go back to the consciousness thing if someone is
sleeping they're still here aren't they yes right but they're not here not
entirely no all right so what is the person the consciousness or is it just
the bag of meat and flesh the meat popsicle which one is it well on so it's
both yeah yeah okay so so in this case it's both so yes they're here but
they're also not here just like I've the what the joke that I just did with
you I'm both there but I'm but my words just show you through reasoning that I'm
not there just by you admitting that I'm somewhere else so it's very similar yeah
well silly question even awake right normal time of the day not sleeping and
you're awake how about this your mind wanders they say your mind you got your
mind somewhere else you got your mind on something else your mind is not
necessarily always with you either is okay stop stop right there that's your
intent but your will is still the same so give you an example let's just break it
down let's say you use basic slave talk I want to buy a new car I can't afford I'm
gonna get a second job so I'm gonna get a second job so when I come home from I
do my nine to five I go home for half an hour then I work from five to ten okay
another five hours every day right this has been done by actually remember back
in the days people did this they wanted to buy a new Z a new Camaro right is I
might get a second job and in a year I'll you know I'm like okay you're gonna
you know you know work like that you know 16 17 hours a day you can do that
by the way instead of going home and watching TV and recreating just
constantly be working right might as well so I'm gonna get a second job so
now I met this job from my you know nine to five and now I'm at this other job
from five to ten every day during the week right okay and after like a week of
doing this I'm getting kind of tired of it and when instead of while I'm doing
what I'm supposed to be doing my mind is going somewhere else right but I'm still
at the job right right okay my intent my one when we say my mind is somewhere
else because obviously I didn't expect it would be so boring or you know
whatever you know it's easy to drift away because it's a second job is it
taking the best of you let's say but so you know you're not performing exactly
what you should be doing or maybe you are but you physically being at the job
as part of the will that you established you're doing this why because you want
to make enough money to buy that new Z by the way that's a Camaro z28 and for
people you know that's the old thing but yeah I got yeah but this is what I'm
this is actually almost like a true story this is like talking about 1980s
early 80s man I sound old some people and people are born in the 80s you know
I know it's so weird I'm thinking to myself I was doing something like this
somewhere in the 90s so I could buy the girlfriend a car and I was working a
security job extra aside from my regular work and that was you know four
or five hours at a clip and quite honestly the security job was me mostly
just doing nothing actually just being present right so you so the will was
doing the job to do to get money by the girlfriend a car but the while you were
there your intent was floating around oh yeah I was reading books there's another
example of what we're talking about okay okay does that make sense see there's
many ways and here's the thing I haven't prepared I've been thinking about this
for a little while now and I'm like I have to present this point because you've
gone through the emo this ties into the emo because the emo will not override
your will once the will is established and the other thing it can if you
understand how to use the emo because then you're talking about a higher level
of emotional demand and projection anyway you know I wasn't planning on
talking but here's the thing and I got to be honest like a lot of people say I
don't want to go on anymore about this because I really don't want to
confabulate I don't I have to really think about this and do some research on
the way I do research on these things you know you always should go back to
what the professionals are saying which as as I get older I'm realizing like
let's say years ago you want to know something about like whatever we're
talking about the mind so let's go see what the psychiatrists and psychologists
have written about it you might get something right now when I go back let's
say oh it's all junk all of it it's crazy no it's all crap and you know what
the best the best of anything is something that's nothing original you
know very much metaphorically Hollywood is the same thing well it doesn't have to
be original no but it's if they're all if they're all saying the same thing and
it's true and it works it's fine right but they're not even doing that but
that's great but what I'm saying is when you're talking about expanding the pool
of knowledge and trying to reach for something new you know going to strange
new worlds like they would in Star Trek they don't it's well if you want
something really new you got to go back to get it's got to be very old if it's
going to be very new because everything that there's nothing really new under
the Sun so you know how you always say if you want a new idea read an old book
yeah but that's what but even from that point they're failing miserably it's just
trash so with this what I mean when I say I'm gonna do research it's actually I'm
gonna just be looking at several things on what's been put out about this and by
the way it's minimal like the emo work I said let me let me just see what
convention has because I had a conversation one of our subs it was he
posts and on the chat and all that and he's wonderful person that was so glad
we've had some skypes and he brought up someone that I've never heard before and
this person other people have heard of them I brought him up in another
conversation recently Gilbert Ling and he had written he had proposed Gilbert
Ling he's passed away now he I hope I got his name right he proposed that the
way cells interact and move and grow and expel things is by induction and not by
the direct chemical exposure expulsion method that we've been told you know
absorption through the entire you know he believed in he proposed theories that
everything in the body works by it's a closed system and it works by induction
go figure I'd never heard of them before when they actually have shown
this stuff I don't see you know now that I have thought about that deeply and I
think back to the things I've witnessed already you know I talked to you before
about how they are able to photograph things that are being seen through a
microscope right and I'm thinking about how stuff was done microscopically it
isn't like a direct feed there isn't something coming from one place to
another where you can like see it being sent by a tube from one cell to another
no but it does happen let me just and this is the converse part of the
conversation this might enlighten people because there's always the duality side
this is this ends the duality and shows the firmness of the induction let me
just get into this there's videos of like you said microscopic where a cell
is ready to expel something from the protoplasm right right so what it does is
inside the cell it forms a material that's just like the membrane and then
that bubble of stuff goes to the edge of the membrane and the membrane opens to it
and it's like a cul-de-sac and it spits the stuff out right right and then it
closes again and that's true that will happen but what I use this analogy
that's not always happening it's mostly by induction is this do you know how
they always say that blood cells are created in the bone marrow it's true
they did a study but under normal conditions they're not right in other
words the study that they did to determine that blood cells are created in
the bone marrow all the people had to be fasting and immobilized now let me
ask you this the normal everyday life are you immobilized and fasting that's
not normal just like blood pressure measurement is not normal you don't you
don't walk around with pressure you know unless your pants are too tight right
you don't put a tight cuff right it's an it's art of completely artificial the
when they determined they had that little microscopic video of the cell let me ask
you this what is that a normal condition for a cell no cell under
stress unusual stress absolutely well yes because it's usually not in wherever
the cell belongs naturally it's never there it's sitting on a slide or it's
sitting in a in a you know think about you like they take you from what you
normally do and put you in a room with bright lights and glass floor and all
that right that's what look the slide is glass right and they put bright lights
and bullies cameras on you is that normal exactly I'm gonna act like you
normally do no no cuz I'm no longer in my natural place see that's the thing
yeah well you got kidnapped you got you've been a bastard you've been
abducted you're not gonna act normally in an abduction so they abducted this
cell right and stressed it right just like the people where they determine the
but the blood comes out of the bone marrow they're immobilized they can't
move and for days and days and they're fasting oh my gosh of course you know of
course the body's gonna act differently so that's the other thing I've always
found interesting where they're like well we have this here and that you know
this cell came from here or wherever and I'm like you took that cell from a dead
body and you're telling me about what the living body does how do you do that if
you're not witnessing it in the living environment I've always had that doesn't
work how does that work and well yeah that's where I went on I said like no
one you know eat oranges got vitamin C no one knows what's in an orange is it
what do you mean no yes they do so well how do they know there's vitamin C in an
orange they take the orange and they crush it completely crush and then they
centerfuge it and then they burn it to get an assay oh really you know all
those processes will change the orange into something completely different so
you really don't know what's in a living orange you really don't but you know
its effects and all that's like the car the conversation with the bear right no
one knows what a bear is what we say we do well even though they say that our
bodies burn calories and burn food here's the fire where's the burn yeah
there's no burn at all that's well because we live in a society that was
developed with fire that's why I use as an analogy imagine a society that was
developed through magnetism instead of fire hmm right you make heat with
magnets you right but not even using the the magnets north-south like right like
most people would imagine by the way right now also we're going through again
another study with the water device on the third component there's a third
fourth fifth and sixth component of a magnet that is not being acknowledged
the fourth component component a third component slightly is it's called the
block wall but there are many others so we can get into that in the future and
I am working on things in the future more like things that I've done in the
past by the way you're always you know when you think about the past or the
future you're still in the past right you can only be in the now for and you
cannot perceive it because it's right when you try to grab it your times
already passed right now for that split second that's that it's gone it's all in
the past so being in the now is the hardest thing forget about the future but
what I brought like for example the aqueous Argentum device I get a message
I wouldn't say every day but just about every day about the excelling the
virtues of it and usually ones that people have made themselves and we're
gonna that has to do with induction by the way because it's not putting any
silver in the water at all right as a matter of fact if you do or if you're
able to measure silver in the water stop using it because it's not right and
it's much more potent and powerful than what they call colloid of silver which I
think is a toxin and it doesn't work well by the way more on that idea
induction simple methods and things so I've been working on that not as much as
I'd like to but I am still working on things like that so just like we brought
forward a few years ago the idea of the aqueous Argentum using a very very low
voltage low current silver electrode to produce you know the essence of silver
and water with no silver in the water at all working on other things for other
biological reasons and things so that's going to be very interesting right and
tell you the truth the one guy that we both know got exactly one from you you
know tells me about it all the time how the winner the winner yes our winner
Joe it has done you know keeps telling me all the time all different things that
this is doing well you didn't even ask for it he didn't ask for it but it's
it's really wild because honestly if you were to show this to somebody who does
make the colloidal silver stuff or believes in that which by the way I know
you see it as a toxin and all that but it has had some positive effects for so
yeah so the thing is though compared to that though like that stuff's crap
compared to what he's getting and meanwhile if you showed it to somebody
who you know is on board with that whole colloidal silver deal they tell you this
isn't doing anything that's right and and here's the thing let's go back to
what you said the coil silver does work but let's use it for an example the the
various ways that Joe is presented that it's been successful regular colloidal
silver would not have been that successful first of all the second
thing when you're using the material silver it's just like drugs what happens
like you take a drug let's say certain antibiotics or painkillers what happens
when you keep using them the body develops a resistance or it stops
working right we'll get just something else right exactly because because it's
a material based thing but if you're using the material silver does the same
thing by the way with the body this doesn't because there's no material
there right that's pure energy it's what the body needs directly versus when you
take the material it's a two-stage process the body sees the material and
what does the body have to do by induction turn it back into energy but if
you're just presenting straight energy right there's no reason to develop a
resistance so there's no no developing tolerance to energy is what what you're
saying sounds like to me no that's right hmm that's interesting because any
other physical thing you know whatever it is food or whatever I mean you're
guys why that's why what do you think about they're not so concerned about
putting fluoride in the water to kill you now if they want to well what are
they to use they're using what kind of weapons right think about energy weapons
energy weapons a lot more efficient because you won't develop a tolerance to
it