Sonic Event 57 rated Y. Anyway, interesting stuff in the chat. We'll address it real quick
at the top. But first, how you doing, Greg? I am doing all right. You know, we're in the
about the middle of the week for the first week of the eighth month. So which which actually
starting to line up. I think we talked, you know, oct right
means a octopus. Right? I mean, whatever octagon octagon. Yeah,
of course. Yeah.
Dr. octopus. Yeah, octopus octagon. So, hey, yeah, couple
things in the chat. Kudos to the guy working on the magnetic
device. My advice is when you're working with that stuff in your
beginner, don't let your work go down the drain, so to speak, make
sure you think it through and have clamps and, and things to
hold things together. So if they don't seem like they're going to
hold together, they do. So you don't waste your time. Or you
could privately message me on common sense radio one at gmail
dot com. It's number one, I think you have. The thing I want
to get into is I was mentioning. Well, for one thing,
there was a couple of things in the chat. Let me just dispense
with that thing, too. Yeah, if you don't mind.
Well, please do. Yeah, on the record. Yeah, just let's put it
on the record. You know, there was a bunch of stuff about
timekeeping. So I'm glad you addressed that right away. I see
people working on it. There's an app an interesting app. I don't
know what your thoughts were on that. But anything that'll help
you reckon? No, I did not see the app. Okay, well, they showed a
picture of an app where it lets you see when the you know, with
the the moon when it when it first is emerging over the
horizon, this and that gives you an idea. I mean, look, oh, yeah,
there's plenty of I thought you said a lawful timekeeping app.
And I'm like, Oh, finally, thank you. No, no, I didn't see a
lawful time. Oh, no, no, no. Yeah. Because there's tons of
apps. But go ahead. Well, no, it's just look, these can be
tools to get you to a helpful conclusion. Let's just say it's
cloudy. Well, you got to know what to do it again. It's like,
you know, if you're five years old. By the way, this is true. I
had a relative who was a naval engineer, naval architect.
What's that they design ships, not boats, you know, the
difference in a boat and a ship, right? Oh, well, you could put a
boat on a ship, or you can't put a ship on a boat.
Yeah, absolutely. True. But they design a lot more than that. I
mean, they design the mechanisms, the winches, the
things that actually, you know, move boats up and down.
Yeah, they're consulted for harbors and things like that.
So also, so so here's the interesting part. I would love
it five years. It was like 1969 1970. And going through books
and looking at all these equations and technical
drawings. I was fascinated. Did I learn anything? Did I know
what to do with that? No. You see what I mean? You can have all
the apps in the world. But if you don't know when to place the
marker, you know, when does the day start? Right? And why? It
doesn't matter. By the way, all that stuff has been staring me
in the face, you know, when I was really young, and I remember
depositing a check in the, in the bank in the 70s. And it was
counted as the next day because it was our one o'clock. Oh,
yeah, that kind of stuff stuck in my head. It was like, why are
you gonna remember that? Remember that? Because it's
bizarre. It's like everybody sticks to this calendar, except
at the bank, because I'm there at two in the afternoon. It's the
next day. Why? Yeah, I know. It's weird. Um, look, there was
all that stuff going on. Yes. And I remember as a kid, that
there were plenty of again, a lot of let's just go ethnic for a
moment, a lot of Italian and Irish guys around big surprise
in New Jersey, right. And a lot of them, you know, they could
build a house or almost anything with what they carried
around on what they used to call a tool belt. That's all they
really needed. As far as tools went hand tools, even they could
build entire structures. No problem. Nowadays, geez, these
guys show up with truckloads of crap. I mean, you know what I
mean? Oh, yeah. Well, it's pretty fabricated. And there's
not much to it. Yeah. Yeah. Well, here's the thing. Okay,
let's just jump to it. Book of Revelation. Someone asked, he's
a very good participant in Greek speak for a long time.
Right? He's been around since the beginning of you and me
talking. Absolutely. Yeah, he's a veteran. Yeah, you're right.
So yes, the answer is, get into the book of Revelation. Not now,
not next week, maybe in a few months. I'm rehashing
everything, especially thanks to who sent me the Aramaic version
of the New Testament in hardcover. Very gracious. A
present that was sent to me a while back. I'm looking into
that as well. Again, does the Vatican sort of approve the
Bible? And the answer is yes. So you got to be wary, right? So it
has to be looked at from a way that they don't want you to see
it. And I've been doing that more and more. And we'll get
into it more and more as the timelines that I've brought up
are approaching. Well, and it is accurate to say many, many
things are hidden in plain sight. And we'll leave it at that for
now until and I'm anxiously awaiting you getting back into
that. Because, you know, that that has been a fascination of
mine pretty much since I learned to read the book of
Revelations. And it was much more popular among people to kind
of examine it on their own. But really, again, it was, you know,
monkeys working with machine guns. Well, it's banned. It's
indirectly banned by the Eastern Orthodox Church and other
things like that. And you cannot approach anything in the Bible
with religious, you know, approach, right? In other words,
if your faith depends on what you understand in the Bible,
you're going to be, you know, it's going to be very difficult.
In other words, you won't have much faith until you figure it
out, right? You get it. So most people's faith is based on
feeling and things like that, which we I'd like to get more
into that in the future. But before we do, I wanted to say,
hey, I said, Chuck, let's I want to get into how to cook a five
star meal really simply, right?
And I love this practical knowledge is the best after all
look, we can discuss the the different things that are not
quite practical in the moment. But I mean, a five star meal is
useful at any time.
Yeah, it'll be an example. It'll be a quick run through. And, and
it's interesting. Okay, what it is, it's basically meat and
potatoes, right? I love it, right? I love it. Okay, so
really, what you do is you'd say, I'm going to give the you'll
get the shopping list, as I say, which makes basically a slab is
slab of meat, beef with potato salad. Okay. Now let's get into
you want to get into this, the meat first or the potato salad
first, which one?
Well, I like the meat first, because that's often, you know,
problematic. I mean, which kind of cut, you know, blah, blah,
everything. What would you have?
The wife says she likes the meat first, too. Yeah. So let's do
this.
Then why is she with you?
That's right.
I couldn't resist.
Alright, so this is what we do is you get a good slab of meat.
This particular is a fairly lean cut of sirloin. It's about an
inch and a half thick, a little bit more than several of them.
But let's say two inches would be good. Right? But on bump,
right? So, because that's definitely what you said.
All right, I'm done. Sorry. Yeah, right. But you got to
multiply. So here's the thing, your choice of meat, there might
vary. But I would suggest that it's a rare thing to no pun
intended with the meat to pursue. To want to get a piece
of meat. For some people that is of the highest quality. Most
people say I want a steak, they'll go to a steak house or
they'll go buy a piece of steak, and they don't think about the
quality too much. Right. So when I say I cooked a piece of meat,
it's a it's a it's almost like literally like you went on a
hunt. Like, you know, the amount of energy right back in the days,
right? Because, you know, so in other words, it's a it's a good
quality piece, right? What makes it a good quality piece? Well,
you figure that out, right? Okay, so. Alright, so what we did
here is I sectioned off enough for two people about a little
bit over a pound and a half, and started drying the meat. So
it's out of the fridge, everything I'm saying is out of
the fridge. I when I got the meat, it was cold. And that was
the last time it saw the cold was when I purchased it, it never
went into the fridge after that, from all this time that I'm
going to mention what's going on. You want to dry the meat.
Now, if you're doing poultry, fish, any kind of meat, that
you're going to subject to a flame, a pan, a broil, you get
the idea, not a stew, not a soup, but something that's
going to be cooked on, you know, in a pan with some fat or oil,
you know, butter or whatever, or in the on the grill, or a
griddle or flame, okay, in other words, you're going to
subject that piece of meat to above the boiling, the boiling
point of water. If you're going to cook a piece of meat above
the boiling point of water, which is actually what it is, when you
when you're going to fry something in a pan, that pan, if
you hit it with a thermometer, one of those laser thermometer
deals, it's going to be like 350 375 minimum before you start
anything, right? Yeah, before really. Okay. So so why am I
stressing this? What is he? What's his point? You want the
meats, whether it's fish, fowl, or beef or whatever, anything to
be as dry as possible. Why? Because when the the higher than
boiling point temperature hits the flesh, you want it to
develop a sear, you want it to develop a caramelization, you
want it to develop a browning, right? Okay, if it hits the
moisture, it will never it will not start to do that until all
the water is boiled off. Right, right. Because in order to get
that that coating that browning, you need to be above 350. If
there's moisture on it, guess what, it will not go above the
boiling point of water till that water is gone. So now what
you're doing is you're actually poaching and boiling the meats,
whatever it is, fish, fowl, beef. Okay, so how do you dry
the meat? Well, initially, I would wrap it in paper towels,
you know, you don't want to spend $20 a month on paper
towels. Remember the commercial? Oh, yeah. Wow,
whatever. Okay. So you don't want to do that. So what I do is
sometimes I do that I buy a cheap cheap restaurant napkins
is a big box room for 40 bucks. They last like 10 years, you
know, or you dry it out, literally, you have a rack and
you put the meat or whatever after you've batted it down. You
know, like the brown paper bags you get from shopping, right?
Oh, that's a, you know, not not the small bags that you put
something but the you know, the ones with the handles. Oh, yeah.
Hard to get nowadays. But yeah, you can get them in from you
can get them. Yeah. And when you open them up, they have a nice
flat bottom, right? You have to stand up on their own, right?
That's right. Pour some salt on that and put a piece of paper
over the salt. And then a small rack like you know, the toaster
oven racks, right? Something like that. If you don't have a
toaster oven rack, you can use bamboo skewers, some wood
chopsticks, whatever, right. And then you have the the the
meat, fish, fowl, whatever over that bed of salt, not touching
it. And then you just fold the top of the bag staple it put a
clothespin or something. And you can leave it in there overnight
eight hours at all, you know, whatever. And that will allow
for the drying of the meat. So there you go. So we drive the
meat overnight. Now, should that be stored in the fridge or out?
No, not necessarily. No. Remember, we're talking about
good quality meat. Let me give you an example. I remember once
I was grilling some fowl and there was some dogs person that
came over. This is a long time ago. I gave him I broke off some
chicken wings and gave the dogs that we had here some chicken
reasons. No, no, give the dog raw chicken. It might have
salmonella. I'm like, Are you kidding? You think like cooking
is going to get rid of that? I don't want to buy if I know the
chicken or any animal is diseased. You're not you. I
don't eat it, whether it's cooked raw or anything. Right?
You see what I mean? This is a you have to cook it for food
borne illness. So okay, so that's the thing about the
fridge. No, no fridging here. Because, you know, if you're
going to do something where you want to be extra safe, the fridge
is fine. Right. But it's more than fine. I'll tell you why,
even though I'm not a proponent for it, because it doesn't allow
the muscle, the flesh to relax, right. And the fat to slightly
melt and tenderize. The fridge is fine for drying, because guess
what fridges do? They dry things out. Right? Yeah, so that's
fine. But I'm not a proponent for it. Because there's a
tenderization. What I also did was I put some baking soda and
water with some spices and I dunk the steak in there. Right? The
slab of meat for 10 minutes, and then I rinse it off. That gets
you know, I think I talked about why you should never have raw
hamburger, right? Because raw or rare, rare typically, because
the E. coli develops on the outside of the flesh. So when
the animal dies, it actually starts to develop very quickly
depending on where you live and other conditions, right? And
then when you grind it all up, it's all it goes inside, right?
Where if you have it on the outside of a steak or something,
it burns off on the outside, right? If you have E. coli
parasite, okay, which is an emergent, but also it could be
transferred. So I just wanted to mention that. Yes. Alright, so
at this point, we've got the meat dried out. And what I do
now is I set up an oven. This happens to be a small electric
oven like the large size toaster oven. I set it at 145
155 degrees, it bounces around between there. It's like, wow,
what's outside a warmer. And the meat goes in there in a small
pan. And for one hour at 150 degrees, you're like, Oh, what's
he doing? Very, very low temperature for cooking. But
high temp higher than the room temperature. Right? So it's
basically warming the steak. Now this is just under two
inches. So an hour was enough to get it to about a little bit
over 110 inside. Yeah, it's only double it's only double the
room temperature really probably so it's warming the meat. So
basically you got a warm slab of meat now for an hour. What I've
prepared outside is a mesquite fire. And I take the slab of
meat and throw it on the grill, close the top very little
oxygen for two minutes per side. Then it comes off of the grill.
In other words, it gets grill marks browning char the fat and
all that right gets charred goes back into the the the small
oven for 145 155 degrees for about a half hour. Then you turn
it off and you prop it up on an angle somehow with skewers,
forks, whatever, and let all the juices drain out. It's called
a Jew, Jew, right? Okay. Right until the meat comes down to
just above room temperature, like what's a high fever
temperature like 105 or so. Okay, it's also rested. Okay,
so that's how you prepare the steak this way. Now this has
nothing to do with you know, people go out and they grill
they take the meat, they put it directly on the thing. Is it
done yet? How do you want it rare or whatever? So you know,
so rare before a few minutes on each side, you know, and then
from then on, you know, right? No, we're not. This is nothing
like that. We're not on cooking yet. We're still on prep here.
Yeah, no, this is the cooking that was done. The meat is done
now. Done. Oh, yeah. Okay, it is done. Yeah, it's very okay.
Years ago, there was a fad of poaching meat when you had a
high quality piece of meat. You put it in a Ziploc bag, and you
seal it and you drop that Ziploc bag in boiling water, right? You
know, holding it up, you know, like they even have rice things
like prefabricated food is like that, you know, there was a
bunch of the old buck Uncle Ben's rice, you know, you put
the pouch in the water. Remember? Yeah, there was a
bunch of different foods you could put in a pouch in the
water, and then you pop open the pouch done. Yeah, I'm
Maurice are like that they have the heating element, you know,
the meal, right? Military has these little heat packs, too.
That's right. Okay, so what they did was they did that. And they
did that for about 10 minutes, 15 minutes of the meat came up
to temperature, then they would grill it in a very hot pan with
butter or flame again, just to finish it on the outside,
right? Sure. So it's it's very antithesis to, you know, is it
cooked through as a heated through? Because here we're
heating, you know, they say, basically, you know, when you
look at the packages, it's got to be 135 degrees 128, right? So
now you're bringing it up to that temperature before you do
the cooking. And then the cooking is just for show and for
flavor. How much char do you want? How much brown do you want?
Right? By the way, I'm going to photograph all this and put it
on the chitango. Okay, what the finished meal looks like. So we
end up with a very rare steak, but it's not bloody rare. It's
not black and blue, where the meat's kind of raw. And there's
no juices that are dripping because it's completely rested.
You know what it's like? Back in the days, remember, you go to
an old school deli and they have a heat lamp with a turkey and a
big slab of roast beef. And if you order, you know, they slice
it right off right there.
Guy comes over with a big knife and cuts off your piece right in
front of you. Yes.
Yeah, yeah. Right. It sounded like he cuts off your piece
right in front of you. But anyway, yeah, yeah, exactly.
Yeah. Okay. So that's exactly what it's like. It's a very
dry, very tender. So what happens when the meat gets to
relax at room temperature, there's a micro amount of fat
that tends to melt off and get between the other muscle fibers.
By the way, when I say most, you know, if you go to a hardcore
Chinese restaurant, that's really for Chinese people with
all Chinese menus, and they have some menus with English
translation. When you look at beef, it says muscle, it doesn't
say beef, it'll say cow muscle. And if you're right, because
that's what it is. It's not organs. It's not liver. It's not
kidney. It's not tongue. It's not brains. It's not testicles,
right? It's muscle.
It is muscle and people can eat those other parts if they want,
but when you're eating steak or beef, you're eating the muscle,
muscle, exactly. And when you tell most people, it's muscle,
they're like, what do you mean? It's steak, it's hammer, it's
it's you're eating muscle. By the way, it's toxic to many
animals, you know, in the in the wild, the large predators, they
eat all the organ meat first, right? You're aware of that.
Yeah, a lot of the animals are getting sick in zoos, because
they just fed them leftover, you know, supermarket steaks, they
need liver, they need kidney, they need brains, they need
right? The tigers and lions. And that's why a lot of those
guys have tried keeping those big cats in the in the 70s and
80s. They kept having to run them into places to save their
lives because they were throwing them steaks and they were not
not well, it creates toxicity for them if they just eat
muscle. Yeah. All right. So that's basically the steak and
what basically it's finished, you know, once the final warming
and resting is done, what you'll end up with is with an
incredible beef flavor, because you know how heat and fire adds,
you know, you know, caramelization, browning, golden
brown adds flavor, but also takes away flavor, right? It
burns away very subtle things, right? Like, you know, like
bread, if you toast bread perfectly, it's delicious. But
if you overtoast it, you just taste the carbon, you don't
taste anything. Oh, yeah, you get that nasty bitterness on the
outside. Yeah. And that's what that's how most people when
they're grilling or subjecting things to fire, you know, so so
what this does is it allows you to get the full spectrum beef
flavor, with the full spectrum cook, appearance and taste both
together. Because remember, it only hit the fire for less than
two minutes on each side. And the rest of it was at 150 degrees
100, you know, you see, so it allows this incredible flavor of
beef to come through almost like imagine a really good beef stew
with a really good steak and a really good hamburger, all put
together. It's really very different, right? And the meat
is exceptionally tender, because you've let it rest and dry
before you've done all this. I personally let them go for about
24 hours, you know, outside of the fridge, but it's covered,
you know, you know, you've got to be smart. And as you
described it, closing up that bag. I mean, it is covered.
It's not gonna right. I mean, if you have dogs and cats, you
know, yeah, I have a place outside usually or inside, you
want some air movement also, because it could get humid in
there and stuffy, right? So that basically, you do the same for
fish, you do the same for poultry, for example, poultry, I
hang the bird outside for a few hours, right? And you always have
to Brian poultry, which is a saltwater Brian, you know, based
on weight, a turkey can go six, eight hours, a chicken an hour
and a half, two hours is fine. If you Brian it over Brian, it
tastes like fake food. They don't it tastes like if you're
Brian, any foul, it tastes just like the deli meat you get.
Right? Like, yeah, it tastes like deli meat, you know, like
turkey slices, or whatever, it ends up taking on that flavor.
And it's like, why bother? It's vaguely like the meat that
you're looking to taste. And it's more like the process than
it tastes like a processed food, right? Very much so. So you got
to be careful, but always hang the bird and dry. And I've had
several people say, Look, I, I don't dry the meat and all that
because I like it moist. I'm like, Oh, my gosh, where do you
start? Right? You know, unless you're going to make a super
stew, even then, if you're going to make even a super stew, the
meat will be more tender if you add it to the broth or whatever
you're doing. Prior that in a dry state again, because it will
not right rely on the water in in it to change temperature. So
that's pretty much the steak. Now you let it rest and you
slice it really thin. And one thing I'll get into solo sonics
other things hopefully one day soon, is how to set up your
kitchen will probably be a multiple part series. And I
won't talk about how to cook or make anything, it'll be just
basic kitchen setup and what to look for. And one of the things
that I'm going to be stressing is how to go one of the reasons
I haven't done it yet, because I haven't found any information
out there. So I'm gonna have to somehow say on my own how to
maintain your cutlery, your knives, right? Because if you
don't have a sharp knife, you ain't you're not good. It's you
cannot put one of the hallmarks. If you go to a
really high end restaurant, right? When there's time for the
chef to go home, he wraps up his knives and puts them in a bag
and leaves with his knives. And when he shows up to work the
next day, guess what he's got? He's brought his knives. Right?
Why? Because it's right. You see what I mean?
Those are his tools. I mean, and that's his Yeah, of course.
And it's not just I mean, chef knives on the average are
several hundred dollars each utility, utilitarian ones, if
you want to get fancy, they get into the 1000s. But here's the
thing. It's what you've invested to get the edge as
sharp and just right for your use in the sharp as possible.
The last thing you want is someone who has a different
attitude with knives to use it to cut something or a technique
to cut and then you have to start honing and creating a new
edge, right? I've actually invented a tool to put a the
edge that I like, which is a very shallow edge on a knife,
you have to have good steel. So
side issue, I actually wanted to get into cutlery. And you know,
what, what your thoughts and process were about that in a
future? Yeah. And it's also your cutting boards, your, your oven
setup, your accessibility to what you have. Yeah, I'll get
into and hygiene and how to real hygiene is when you're preparing
food and why. Let's get to the potato salad.
Oh, yeah, sure. Let's get to the potatoes or potato salad. But I
think it's very important to remember that if you don't have
an effective set of tools, I mean, the quality of your work is
going to be limited if you have limited tools. So
well, so yeah, if you don't have a good knife set or a good knife,
there are certain things you just can't do. Like when I give
the rice number eight, you know, when you cut the carrot burdock
on a bias real thin, and then and then match stick it again, you
can't do that with a dull knife, you'll cut yourself, it'll flip
all over the place, it'll take you an hour to cut half a
carrot. Yeah, that's the other thing. So cutting carrots, you
know, I mean, what are you doing? You know, it's going to
take a long time. And yeah, you could indeed hurt yourself. So I
would make pesto and sauces years ago, the we had a food
processor here. And so we split it, I took half the ingredients
you with the food processor me with the knife and the cutting
board, let's see who's done faster. Obviously, by the time
they push the button and got all the ingredients in the food
processor to make the pesto, they were done before me. But I
said, ah, you got to clean that thing now. And by the time they
cleaned and put it away, I was done before they were, you know
what I mean? Because you know, the food process, you got to
take the thing apart. It's got the canister, the blade, the
spindle, right? Right. Try not to cut yourself while you're
watching this stupid, crazy blade shapes, too. That's
another way. Yeah. So what I'm doing is I was faster. In other
words, they by the time they got I was done. And how long did
it take for me to clean the cutting board and the knife?
Well, you know, a couple of swipes, dry towel, done. Right.
And no, and I was just and also the energy and then put that
electric motor energy in there. So let's get to the potatoes.
Yeah, what I what I did was I got what's called like a yellow
gold potato, but the creamy ones are slightly larger, the
smaller yellow gold or denser waxier, these are non waxy,
they're called yellow potato creamy. Okay. Okay. So I started
with a bunch of those, let's say I have at least like three
potatoes, four potatoes, five potatoes, whatever, right. And
guess what, if you guys have not been around for a while, I do
this thing called stove top baked, where the potato, by the
way, when you get a potato, and it looks dirt, that's not dirt on
the outside, that's humate. So those are humides. It's not soil.
It's not like, oh, it's dirt, you know, it's not. So you could
scrub them, clean them off, right. But that's a humus, a
humus or humus. It's a humate. It's a it's a humate that grows
as the potato grows, it actually transmutes some of the soil to
humate around it, right? That's what it is, right? Think of it
like dead skin cells or something, you know, it's, it's,
it's not dirt, you know, like soil, you know, so anyway, so
your movement, just really quickly, your movement is
disrupting your signal a little bit, just a little bit. Oh, I'm
not moving. Oh, maybe I just went outside maybe earlier.
Maybe that's what's a struggle. Okay, I'm gonna move. I'm gonna
move around a little bit. Hopefully, it won't disrupt it.
Now, the last recording we did, I lost you for about a minute. I
didn't say anything, we kept going. I figured I was on a
thought there. And so I tend not to bring it up as much because I
know we have problems, but it ends up being sometimes it ends
up being fine on the recording, usually. Oh, I know.
But that was you literally like breaking up like,
okay, like,
real time. Okay, so I got these yellow potatoes, put them in a
pot with just to cover with water and salt. And basically 20
minutes is fine. After they come to a boil, you bring them down
to a low and I do the ghetto pressure cooker, which is a
weight, a weighted mug and a lead weight on the lid, right?
Very low. 20 minutes, check it to see if it's tender, dump the
water out, or you know, take the potatoes out, dump the water,
put the potatoes back in, turn the flame on low for a few
minutes. And with no water in there, got to be careful, you
got to have a thick bottom pot. If you don't have a thick bottom
pot, get yourself what's called a heat diffuser that will save
you from burning stuff. And it also creates more even heat. Five
minutes with the lid on. Five minutes rest, take the lid off,
let all the steam and repeat that once or twice again, and you end
up and rotate the potatoes. So now you end up with a baked
potato flavor and texture. I mean, when you do that stovetop
bake that I just mentioned, it tastes like you know, that baked
potato flavor, right? You know, it's much better than a boiled
potato flavor, right? Yeah, but you end up getting it, you know,
what the tiny I mean, think about someone the average kitchen
burner, how small how little fuel that uses compared to
firing up an oven. Don't say microwave. Because that's like
the big hit in the 80s. Everyone got a microwave because it made
perfect baked potatoes. I disagree. I always thought that
was crap. The only thing the microwave is good for is
popcorn to me. But yeah, maybe Yeah, I don't. Yeah, I had
gotten one. I remember in 1988. The family brought me in my
house living in Manhattan. They brought me a microwave. After
they left, I put it out on the curb. You know, Merry Christmas,
right? So anyway, snatch that up about five minutes. Yeah, not
even Yeah, I didn't even actually I went in. So I'm going
to wait five minutes now that it's gone. Guess what? It was
gone. This is 11th Street between second and third Avenue
in Manhattan 1988. Yes, definitely gone. Good. Yeah.
Yeah. So
alright, so we got the stove top baked potato. Basically, what
we do let them cool down. And you peel them by you just you
don't use a peeler, the skin just comes off. And I was
thinking when I was peeling these potatoes, you know, people
say onion skin is real thin. Oh my gosh, if you think onion skin
is thin, you got to try potato skin that's much thinner than
onion skin. But anyway,
not barely you pinch it, you can just take it off with your
fingers. Yeah, you take it off with your finger. You could use
a utensil just to start you know, pulling I use a popsicle sticks
to whatever you know, the back edge of a small blade, a fork,
whatever. Alright, set them aside. Okay, now what I have on
the other side is prior to doing that, while the potatoes were
cooking, I quartered an onion, I took a quarter of the onion. And
I cut it in half again. So it's about you know, it's a wedge,
but it's about one inch on one end, turn on the burner, and I
put the onion right on the burner. And I'm burning the
onion basically char charring it on one side and the other. And
just like you're making as if you're making far you know, the
Vietnamese soup, you char the onion and and I have a carrot
that's charring also don't rinse it, you know, once the the
onion and the carrot cool, I chop up the onion in a chop. So
I chopped this quarter inch by quarter inch, put it in a bowl
and you add some sugar, you got to do this in this order. First
you put you salt the onion, a good amount of salt, what you
more than what you would salt to taste. And then you cover it
with vinegar, your vinegar of your choice, always use a good
quality vinegar, stir it around. And I also cut the carrot very,
very thin on a biased and match sticks very thin match sticks,
right? And excited with the onions.
Particular vinegar, like a red wine vinegar, any quality red
wine vinegar, I have an organic one. You can also use a rice
wine vinegar if you like that. Okay, fair enough. Right. Yeah.
And this what you're making there is a pressed salad pickle
with the onion and carrot. What I do is I've had a small bowl, I
put some cling wrap over it and a weight, you know, lid or another
mug or something to press it down, just enough vinegar to
cover even less and stir it up. And salt, you would you know, if
I said put salt on something, you know, you salted to taste,
this is not salting to taste, this is literally adding a
couple of pinches of salt, right? And the vinegar, what
that does is the vinegar and the salt and the sulfur in the onion,
what does it mean sulfur in the onion, you know, that strong,
raw onion taste, that's an organic sulfur. Those three
combinations, the acidic acid, the salt and the they form a new
flavor, they all cancel each other out. And if you've never
done this before, if you really heavily salt the chopped onion,
add the vinegar, stir it up, and just put your finger and taste
it, it doesn't taste like onion, it doesn't taste like vinegar,
it doesn't taste like salt, you've just created this new
flavor. And most people have never had that. And it's it's
like a relish. Almost, you know how a relish doesn't taste like
pickle, it doesn't taste like relish, right?
You know, I've had something like this. And it's kind of
sweet, right?
It can be it can be even though it's very salted. Okay, so you
put this aside, it's a pickle. Now, we have some raisins also
maybe two tablespoons of raisins, and I've softened them and put
them on the cutting board, just do a liberal chopping of the
raisins, right? Okay. Okay, so now you have your potatoes
cooling. And hopefully they're cool enough. They're peeled. What
I do is I cut them in thirds one way, lay them down, cut them
in thirds again, and then they end up looking like cubes about
half inch by three quarter, less than a cube. It's there. They
look like a quarter of a potato, but it's thinner than it is wide
and long, right? You don't want a cube. You want it slightly like
a thick slice, but they're small pieces. Right. So what I have now
is a bowl with some baby kale and baby spinach greens. All
right, I've rinsed that out in the bowl. And what I do is a
pressed salad. What you do is once it's rinsed out, you put it
in the bowl, put some olive oil over it, and just grab it with
your hand and mush it and just keep moving it around until you
just crush once or twice the vegetables and they'll get that
dark green broken leaf color almost wilted but not wilted.
It's a broken leaf, right? You don't want the because a fresh
leaf whether it's lettuce or spinach, whatever, it's very
springy. You know, I mean spring like a spring that moves, right?
And it's hard to get a hold of when you make a pressed salad
when you press it down, it looks wilted, but it's wilted
mechanically and broken. The leaves don't have that perfect
shape. They're all wrinkled up and they turn a dark green,
right? This is this is makes a much better chew. It's easier to
pick up. It changes the flavor as well. Okay, so now we're
going to go to how do you prepare the salad, you start
cutting your potatoes on the cutting board, the way we said
you lay them out with a little bit of olive oil, you want to
use a little bit of olive oil on the potatoes and the knife
because the starch makes it very sticky. So always have some
olive oil ready to go. Before you even start cutting the
potato, pour a little olive oil over the potato. So as you're
slicing it, the excess lubricant, right, as opposed to
getting that very thick, starchy stickiness, which will
also contribute to the breaking of the pieces.
Quick thought, isn't it good to have olive oil in a spray bottle
sort of so you can spray it out?
You could do that. For some reason that changes the taste
that I don't like it.
Okay,
so get handy, you know, there's a little pour top thing or
whatever you could use or Yeah.
That's the ones I have with a little pour top with a little
should be fine. It's usually the pour top that hides under the
cap is too big. Usually it pours out too much. So you make your
own or whatever you can use the ones that use in the bar use that
pour top, you know, the in the bar, they have the the hard
liquor pour tops, right, right. The pointy ones use those. You
could buy three pack of those real cheap. Yeah, that's and
they're 28 millimeter or 32 millimeter bottles is usually
standard. Okay, so now you lay out your potatoes and as the
potatoes are laid out on the cutting board, go ahead and put
your onion and carrot mixture over the potatoes as they are in
the cutting board, and then put your raisins spread them out.
All right, and then take the wilted baby kale and spinach and
spread that out. So now you're looking at a cutting board, it's
you know, the full width and length of the cutting boards
covered with chopped potatoes and the layer of onions and a
layer of raisin and then the greens on top. Why do I do this?
Because now when I transfer from the cutting board to the bowl as
it falls off the cutting board, it's already partially mixed,
right? Because if you're going to throw these ingredients one at
a time in a bowl and try to mix it, what is that mechanical
mixing going to do to your potatoes, it's going to start
smashing all the edges, beating them up, and the potatoes are
going to beat them and they're going to start being partial
mash, right? So one thing that I'll get into is you want to
start your mixing process on the cutting board, right? No
matter what it is, if even if you're making a tuna salad, you
know, you add mayo, whatever tuna salad, whatever, if you're
cutting vegetables, start adding your dressings and other
things on the cutting board if you can, because as it transfers
from the cutting board into the bowl, it's already half mixed
and you've saved yourself or you've retained the original
shape and texture or the stuff that you see in a food magazine
is how do they get it looking so perfect? Well, they didn't beat
it up. That's why, right? The economy of movement. So and also
you have some vinegar mixture leftover. You can add that to
the entire thing. Now, if to taste now, this is where the
taste comes in. So the even getting it off the cutting board
into the bowl is not going to guarantee a full mix. So I have
it in the bowl. I have another bowl or remember the pot that
you made the potatoes in? You rinse that out and you transfer
it from the bowl into the pot again very gently. Okay, I see a
lot of young novice cooks when they make something like a salad
or a mix. They get in there with a big spoon and what do they do?
Right? You know, just like television. They start moving
the thing. Yeah, yeah, you don't do that. The best way to mix is
to transfer from container to container let and gentle gravity
and the tumbling will actually give you a wonderful mix and
still retaining the look and the ingredients. And there you go.
This is a five star meal. If you put this together, and you slice
the meat thin, and you and also I have some very peppery
horseradish that comes already in a jar. Fresh ground
horseradish is the best. And whenever you have horseradish,
by the way, that comes pickled in a jar, you know, with brine,
you want to have a small strainer, don't spoon it out
onto whatever mixture or serve it, you always want to put it
in a strainer and drain it. If you don't have a strainer, you
could use a small towel or some dry it off, right. And I mixed
that with some sour cream. So it's a creamy horseradish on the
side, which goes well with the potato salad, and the beef. And
if you put these two dishes together, it is a five star end
of summer steak dinner.
There you have it.