Ocelli in the Greek rated Y, and here we are again.
How are you doing?
Oh, what do you think?
What do you think how I'm doing?
What do you mean how I'm doing?
You're still on this planet, right?
You're still on this planet, so how could you be doing?
Yeah, right.
That's right.
I use that a lot, by the way.
You know, people give me a little bit of a confounded look or they're wondering about
something that's brought up in conversation, not necessarily by me.
I look at those.
Hold on a second.
Have you been on this planet for more than an hour?
And that really, you know, they're never going to hear it, right?
No one.
No one talks like that.
So what it does, it's a pattern breaker, right?
It gets snaps.
Because people run on autopilot, right?
You know, I think about, you know, well, look, yeah, I'll just keep it at that.
I don't have to explain that.
You know what autopilot is, right?
To a degree.
Almost anybody who has been on this earth a while, right?
If you've been through your adolescence, your childhood time, and you're into adulthood
at some point, you've run on autopilot.
Yeah.
So when I come around, it's like, all right, turn the autopilot off.
You need manual controls now, right?
And they're not used to it.
And it's like, yeah, you're flying and you think the autopilot's going to do everything.
That's why you get that strange look when you actually provoke them to think about something
for a moment.
Like there's this weird twist in the face because it's uncomfortable for a moment, right?
You know, because they're not used to it.
Well, let's talk about the autopilot.
How does it work?
It's a whole bunch of sensors that give back feedback to an algorithm.
Yeah.
And that's how we work.
We have a whole bunch of sensors, you know, and most of the time, a perfect example, if
you ride a bicycle or drive with a car or a truck or whatever, you could be doing other
things, you know, once you're an experienced, quote, unquote, operator, right?
And you know, you could be, I shouldn't say this on the phone, eating a breakfast or whatever
while you're driving.
And at the same time, you know, you don't miss a beat.
You hit, you know, you slow down, speed up, make a turn, stop, you know, obey the traffic
signals.
No problem.
And if you're really not conscious of it, you know, if I'm sitting next to you, I say,
how many, how long were you at the traffic light and was it a stop sign or traffic light?
How many pedestrians were crossing in front of you when you whizzed by?
They don't know.
It's like you don't know.
So, so it can be, autopilot could be very critical, but again, it works on sensors and
algorithms.
Right.
So how many lefts did you take?
How many rights did you take?
You'd actually have to recreate.
I don't know.
Yeah.
No, they don't know.
That's good.
But they're doing it well while they're doing it and they're not on autopilot, but they
are.
And I mean, in other words, what they're operating, the machine, the device is, has not offered
autopilot feature.
They go into autopilot on their own.
Their mind seems to go somewhere else.
People say, right.
And your mind is not necessarily on this.
Your mind goes somewhere else, but it didn't because it's still there.
I mean, obviously you have to be using it partially, but you're not feeling it so much.
You don't know.
Actually, they do go by feeling because what happens here, the emo, let's say you're a
truck driver.
You get in a truck, your emo changes and it has to change.
Even if you're pissed off about something, you still overlap the emo that it takes to
drive a truck.
And the emo then puts the, you know, the autopilot going, right?
That's why I'm going to, well, how many times have we talked about the emo, like full episodes?
And I don't think I, by the way, the O and G is not included.
I don't think I really brought up the emo during the O and G a while back.
Did I?
No, not during those runs.
We never got into it.
No.
Yeah.
Right.
But in these runs at least three.
Yes.
At least three.
Pretty heavy.
Yes.
Yeah.
One thing, just to, you can't say this enough.
When you say emo and expand it into emotions and purposes of emotions, it has nothing to
do with what we've been raised on about emotions.
Nothing to do.
Actually, this little point I gave about the autopilot is an emo function.
It is an emo.
Give you an example.
In basic driving school, they tell you if you're emotionally wrought or upset or mad,
don't get behind a wheel.
Right.
Right. That's true. Yeah. No, if you're upset, you should not drive. Right. I mean, I've
seen that before when people are profoundly upset. They've just gotten some really bad
news or whatever. No, don't go driving right now.
Well, what does that have to do with basic motor skills and rationale? A lot, because
it's an emo function. Yeah. Well, that's the thing is that, look, the weirdest part about
this is it affects everything. And yet nobody ever gives you any sort of map on it. They
just they recognize it's there, generally speaking, not not in the conversations you
and I have had, but they'll generally recognize it. They're OK. You have your feelings. You're
in your feelings, you know, whatever. They got lots of all the hold on back. Let's go
back in the past. You interviewed what he goes by Miller, Richard, Richard Allen, Miller,
Ram, Dr. Ram. They call him Dr. Ram. Sure. All the stuff he talks about is email based.
You know, you've got this and that. I'm not a fan, by the way. I've been on private Skype
calls with him and that's why. But anyway, I'm not a fan, but I've heard him talk about
he doesn't simplify it enough like we are. I'm not saying we're better. Actually, we are.
But let's just say it this way. Yeah. His whole premise is based on that. You know, when he
says he was training the seals or whatever and he says it's all by the gut. Yeah. Well,
it's not. The gut is still physical. It's the emo or resides. Actually, you know, do
you want to know where it projects from? We never got into this right at the base of the sternum.
Like you just just drag your hand. Maybe I'm not using the right technical term. Actually,
believe it. I have to look that one up. Drag your finger down your your chest right where the bone
with the rib, the top ribs meet right before the stomach starts right there is where it generates
where it comes from. Right around where the diaphragm is about. Well, hi. Just as soon as you
vertically drag your hand down your chest, you feel all the bone mass as soon as you clear the
bone mass and it gets soft and tender. That's where it is. OK, that helps, you know. By the
way, the third eye thing is not what they tell you, either. It's, you know, a Vindhi point.
They put in Hindu culture, any culture. They put the spot between the eyes. Right. Vindhi.
OK, well, it goes the third eye energy goes right through. So it also is in the back of your head,
not just the front. People think it's you say I was to be sitting a socket on the front of
your head. Right. They think of it like a third eye in the center of your head. Yeah. Yeah. Or
it's a socket. It looks forward. No, that's it's actually an axis that goes right through the head
here at the point where you would see in Hindi culture where they place the Vindhi mark.
Vindhi. Right. The red the red dots. Yeah. By the way, I had a cat that had a little it was
white and had a little dot right there called Vindhi. But anyway, why not? So. So, yeah,
these things have locations on the body. And does that help? OK, so if you know where it is,
does it make you more proficient? No, it doesn't actually, because it's nonphysical.
But every nonphysical thing, let's say you're going to broadcast. Right. It's nonphysical.
But you can actually go back to where it's broadcasting from. It is a physical antenna
pointing the type of antenna it is. Right. Well, it's got a point of origin from which
right energy is. Yeah. You know, emerges from first. Right. So and then it's then transferred
out via this, via that. Like you can see how it goes through a pipeline, basically. So that's
pretty much what you're doing here. Right. Yeah. By the way, the email part where it's right there
at the base, at the top part of the rib cage or bottom part of the rib cage. Did I mention that
was for men? No, I didn't. No, you didn't. Yeah. Mostly it's for men. For most women. It's there
also for women. But most women, it's the womb. It would be the top of the uterus where the where the
two fallopian tubes come out. I think that might be slightly lower than right on way lower. Yeah.
Yeah. It would be right about where if you stand up, put your thumbs on your hip bones about an
inch down below that. Oh, OK. OK. Much lower. Sorry. Yeah. Way lower. Yeah. Yeah. And there's a
reason for that. Again, I think I got into the reasons. It's similar to the reason why if you
look at the human bladder and anatomy on a drawing, it's has a symmetrical arrangement around it.
And it looks just like a uterus. Well, since the most men and women, since most things are cyclical,
one would almost think that maybe it would come from the the general area on the male then,
you know, if it's too, too far, too far removed. Remember the male's genitalia. Let me just say
this way might be contrary to scripture for most people. But the male genitalia are an afterthought.
Women came first, not men. And proof of that is that the testes are outside of the body for
temperature control. Why? Because the body's too hot for testicles. Right. So it's an afterthought.
So certain things are backwards. Well, no, I've never seen that represented in any of the stories
right where you have the you know, the male than the female. Always the male is created first.
Well, let's just put it this way. If we go back to the biblical nomenclature. Yeah. Day six,
man and woman were made together. Doesn't tell you who was made first, does it? No,
they were made together and they were told to go repopulate, replenish, and they were giving
a blessing. And when I say when man was made to anyone, they go back to the Judeo-Christian
ethic, even Islam, where you have Adam. You know, he's the sucker. You know, he's the guy that was
made way later. Right. You know, he got punked. You know what I mean? OK, don't know. We're not
talking about the one in the garden. We're talking about. Right. The one before that was
we're talking six day, man, not a day, man. Yeah. Yeah. Because a day man is the one that they say
they took the rib from. They always say, yeah, yeah, it should have been an arm and a leg cost
too much. And that's why women are the way they are. They're made from a cheaper cut. You know,
so anyway, anyway. No, really. I mean, think about it. It doesn't you know,
it doesn't mean men are any better. I'm just saying Adam is made from a cheaper cut,
you know. But anyway, the whole well, if he wasn't, he wouldn't be fixed as a gardener.
That's was that was his job to mow the lawn, cut the shrubs, take the garbage out. Right.
I mean, you know, anyway, they didn't have, you know, girly magazines back then and they didn't
have Netflix back then. So they made a woman. Yeah, they were supposed to be the what was the
word, the term they always use for it, where you're supposed to take care of everything.
You're like the caretaker. Yeah, there you go. Was the idea behind it. What was the word that
you stewardship steward pretty much made? I think he was more like the janitor. Maybe,
maybe. But either way, it's about me. Yeah. I don't hold him in high,
high esteem, by the way. I don't venerate that guy, by the way, at all.
But that's another thing. Maybe a Greek, you're taking a little personal here.
Prove it. You know, I'm like, no, it's just sorry. So I voice my voice, what my opinion is. How many
times do I say this? My opinion? Almost never. Right. So, yeah, so that'll be determined. But
all right. Either way, you know, the Christ said, I'm the first Adam and the second Adam.
The first Adam is six day man, by the way, not, you know, the second one. So he was there for
that, too. But this is not a discussion on on those ancient writs, but it's I don't know what
discussion do we ever have? That's a discussion about anything. Anyway,
this is kind of like members of the way they talked about Seinfeld. It's the show about nothing.
Well, this is the stream of consciousness that you can never quite nail down.
You know, it's the same. Well, we brought yeah, we brought that up before intent and will. Right.
Will is always around. But your intent is only when you're conscious and working on it. Right.
That's true. So the thing is, you know, you know, you've seen even it's been immemorialized in film
where you have these prisoners, prisoners of war, and they have a will to break out of the prison.
Right. There's so many films done, especially in the 60s and 70s. Right. World War two stuff. Right.
There was a lot of those. Yeah. Yeah. So they have an intent to not be there. But the will
is to break out. And whether there are you ever notice like there'll be a scene where they're all
sleeping and someone wakes up and automatically it's like, what do I need to keep doing? Dig in
this tunnel. Right. That's will. Right. Day or night. Oh, sleep or awake. Right. You see,
it's it's will is very, very deep and very, very heavy. But that's I think we'll work on that as I
develop more of a how would you say when you have a foundation on it? Right. To discuss, because
right now I'm just pulling these things and saying, hey, these things, maybe if we can measure them
better, we can manage them better. Right. These are these are all rough drafts that we're
we're getting from, you know, feedback, you know, from the chat room and emails and whatever else
it is we get from people giving us an idea what it is they're hearing and what it is they want
to hear about. So we're roughing out a few things here, really unrated. Why? Which eventually
can turn into much more solidly organized stuff later.
And we were like, right. Just to say we saw anybody listening here, feel free to communicate
with either one of us right on what you'd like to get into. Oh, absolutely. And, you know, we've
given out the emails before. And obviously you can contact, you know, where where you are. You
should be all uncommon. Uncommon sense. Radio one at Gmail dot com. That's the personal email.
That's number one. Numeric one. Uncommon sense. Radio one at Gmail dot com. Numeric one for the
Greek. And I guess you're just once they land on Ocelli dot com, they'll they'll sniff around,
right? Get it. You can click a little email thing there or you can send to info at Ocelli dot com
or you can send a blind JFK researcher at Gmail dot com. I read all those. So, you know, in any
place, everybody knows, you know, to to address when when they're writing to me about this,
they always say, you know, put in the title rated Y. So they've already figured that one out all by
themselves. I didn't even have to tell them. So, you know, and speaking of figuring it out,
I just want to throw this in just so we got that. I just want to say two things. I was driving on
autopilot. Not really. But anyway, I heard put on like an oldie station and the DJ says, oh,
I just read an article that the dinosaurs 66 million years ago were destroyed by an asteroid
and asteroid. The reason they died is because the plants couldn't grow because there's no sun for two
years. I always remember it being 60 million years. Now they're making it 66 million years.
Right. You see the numbers are developing. How did that six or six million years? Yeah,
it's all BS. But yeah. Yeah. So so and this guy's like, well, you know, these nerds,
they know how to figure things out. You know, I'm like, oh, my gosh. So the program is still going.
This was also after I left having a conversation with someone and this has happened in the past
few days when something when I'm in several different situations, different people don't
know each other, different situations. And I hear the same thing. I kind of bring it up on a rated
Y. Right. It's interesting. And what it was, was this is in two different conversations over a
span of a day. Some things were brought up. The subject matter is not relevant, but this is
relevant is they said, Greek, you're the only other person I ever heard say that. Right. Not
not you're the only person heard say that the only other person these people were specializing
in what they did. And I just want to bring that forward, because one thing about what we're doing,
the project here is most likely you're here. You hear things that no one else you won't hear from
anyone else or very rarefied. Maybe there might be some specialist. Right. Yes. That might do
something and come up with something and we might bring it forward. But we never get into the
conventional stuff. Like, I think right now, still, there's a big shit sandwich going on in
the Middle East. And if you actually study it, you know, the the Hamas is real thing.
This is the fall of 2023, which, by the way, we predicted was great accuracy, how it would go
down is following all of the rote media script lines, you know, the typical psychology and all
that stuff, right. And, and, you know, how the way the public is controlled through the media
is through scandal. Right. So even when there's no scandal, the absence of a scandal is actually
a scandal. You see, because people are used to it. So they're looking for something and it's becoming
so played down. You know, the dinosaurs, 66 million, 60 million, you know, so what's happening
is you're going to start seeing great reveals and a lot of stuff you hear with rated Y, O and G
and others, I'm sure that no one's paying attention. You know, in other words, the power
people in power, the puppets in power, I should put it this way. The puppets that you're being
told are in power are don't care anymore. No one cares anymore. And I wouldn't say it's going to
fall apart, but it's on autopilot. And it's really, really low grade presentation all across the board,
everything. Right. So it's, it's not not anything you should focus on, like, you know, here's the
thing. Fortunately, I don't get a lot of messages about political situations. And actually, I don't
get any because people that are, you know, they know, at least I've been fortunate, right? Right.
So if you don't have your own personal affairs in order where you have happiness in your personal
life, personal could be whatever, you have no reason to be worried about what's going on in
the world. Right. And we're talking about even hard times, you know, you can always find bliss.
I think I brought up the analogy once I know someone who manages personal funds, like,
who's that guy? He was in the 3 billion in personal funds, which is not a lot,
but it is a lot for one guy and his assistant to do that is 3 billion in personal funds.
Larry King emerges that he Ivanka Trump when she was alive. These are the people that he
started off by managing a Marcos. So the one with all the shoes.
Oh, yeah, yeah. Okay. So Imelda Marcos.
Imelda was one of his clients and they passed away. So he started off with her and then expanded
into Larry King and Ivanka Trump, who I think they beat her up, threw her down a staircase last
year or something like that. Well, not Ivanka. You mean Ivana with Ivana Ivana, the first wife,
the real tacky looking one, the bleach blonde hair. Ivanka is the daughter. So sorry. Yeah.
The real the first wife that had the bleach blonde hair was obviously very tacky. Right, right.
They beat her. Yeah, that one. And so anyway, I bring this up because it's funny. Of course.
Right. Yeah. Yeah. Because I'm bringing this up because I see these these people are a spotlight
or are really wonky. You know, they're not really doing this. Absolutely. They're totally like that.
They're not like what they're shown at all. They're actually the opposite.
Well, because it's very much like in 1984. And I know you don't you don't really love the parallels
with the 1984 type stuff because that leads to a whole lot of trite crap that a lot of people
spit out. But it's true about this. You mean Orwell's? You mean the book? Yeah. Orwell's
book. Right. OK, got it. You know, because I was around in 1984 was a good year, actually.
Oh, yeah. No, I so was I. But Eric Blair or, you know, whatever his name really was. It doesn't
matter. Nineteen eighty four stands up in this Goldstein and however many minutes of hate that
they put up on the screens absolutely stands true. That's that moment of outrage. That's
that moment of scandal. It's irrelevant, really. They tell you this is the enemy. They tell you
this is the one to be spurned. They tell you this is the evil one. You're supposed to get angry at
this guy, Goldstein. Nobody knows. But none of them are what they what they say. But I want to
go back to the financial guy. So when the whole thing went down in a way, he's like, oh, my
personal money, you know, the personal funds management, his own personal money went down by
like 50 percent. And he said, how am I going to survive? And I'm like, survive? What do you mean?
If everything is gone, all the shops are gone and I'm out of food and I'm crossing the street and I
see a blade of grass coming out of the median, I know I could survive. I don't think you're using
that word survival properly. No, survive is really a bizarre topic with those guys, because I mean,
like I was looking at a TV show recently where they have these billionaires battling with each
other. It's a fake TV show or whatever. But very interesting. The guy is defeated. He ends up with
$100 million. You know, and I'm not going to make it. Yeah. I'm like, I'm going to have to
rebuild from that hundred million dollars. Really? You could you couldn't spend that if you in other
words, living a regular human life. You couldn't spend that in a lifetime. I couldn't spend that.
My grandchildren wouldn't be able to spend that living. I mean, even with inflation, we'd probably
just about run it through in two generations if we just lived, you know, normal lives.
By the way, since we're jumping around in tangents back around that time, I was doing some
work with the mines and prospecting. I figured out a way to get around the BLM and all that stuff. It
was fun. And because I'm by the way, if people with problems in business and industry, sometimes
when they get ahold of me, I said, well, we could figure a way around that. I don't know exactly now,
but we will. But anyway, we got around the BLM rules, mining, all that. And we were still allowed
to do it. You know, we just went around the rules with technicality. Well, there's a guy that went
out. This is near the border of Idaho and Canada. I'd say about half an hour south of Canada. And we
needed a core. There's a mountain outcrop. And we sent someone that could take a core sample because
it was hard rock mining. You get it dig into the mines. You know, they have just like you dig a
well. You know, they send a big, long rod through and they bring up a core about two or three inches
wide. And you can and it has depth markers. So you know how deep you know what you find at whatever
depth. Right. It's like drilling with a post digger, but really quickly and pulling out just
that chunk. Exactly. So he gets up. There's no road. So he finally he's an expert at getting
something with tracks. You can't use wheels, these tracks, you know, like a tank or a bulldozer
got up. There was equipment set up. We didn't hear from him for about two weeks. And after that,
he's like, OK, I took some core samples of where you guys wanted. And he says just the core samples
that I pulled out of the mountain has enough material that I will be wealthy. My children
will be wealthy and my grandchildren will be wealthy from the metals that he pulled out just
from doing the sampling samples. Right. So essentially that mountain, that outcropping
was all platinum, all platinum. He pulled out like 400 pounds of platinum material. Right.
Almost pure. Right. And that whole project went south. And the project kind of went on. But
Monsanto owned. It turns out that this got out. It was a battle. Monsanto knew it. Monsanto was
right at Monsanto. One of their large agricultural processing plants was about a half hour east.
They had known about this for a long time. But when they found out someone went up there to
a core sample, they know what they found. And they moved in and then like nobody can go there.
Monsanto now strangely owned by Bayer Aspirin. But go ahead. Yeah. Yeah. But this is 2008.
And remember, Monsanto is part of DuPont and Monsanto got bigger than DuPont. That's where
the children get bigger than the parents. Right. Oh, yeah. Well, that's why I crack up that Bayer
bought it, because I thought nobody as Monsanto. But please go ahead. Well, they're still trying
to figure out, like after World War Two, when they broke up Germany, who owns water or whatever,
because it took 30 years to figure the paperwork on that. Because here's the thing. There's when
I was doing the water of Andreas Vecca. He's a gold medalist. East Germany. He won several gold
medals in gymnastics. He was always like in the same place where we were peddling water. He was
peddling his oils. Andreas Vecca. So he had to have been a winner in like the 60s, 70s or 80s
somewhere. He was in the 80s. Yeah. We're about he's a year younger than I. So he was a gold
medalist in the 80s. And whenever Germany came up, he was did not want to he was from there.
He did not want to talk about it at all. Listen, guys, you guys want to talk about my country,
but my country does not have a government has not a government a long time because they have what's
called an interim government. Right. Just like, for example, like Iraq, you know what they did
to Iraq. That's an that's not a Iraqi government. It's an interim government. It's a puppet
government. And so the people are very, very bitter about what's going on still. And in other words,
the situation it's been about 80 years. Well, let's just call it 70 some odd years. Let's just
go from look, 50, 70 plus years. And it still has not been mitigated. Right. Yeah. Well, you know,
and that's an interesting thing, too, because people talk about this concept of terrorism and
where it is people would strike back if they were being oppressed and whatnot. And I say to myself
all the time, I'm surprised you don't see a lot more Iraqi terrorists all over the place.
There are no terrorists. So it's it's all fabricated. There are no real terrorists.
But see, if there were real terrorists, they would come from Iraq.
Yeah, right. But let me just say it this way. There might be some real terrorists,
you know, like home, you know, whatever. But you'll never hear about them in the news.
No, everything that you see on TV is fabricated that way. And I brought this up in some old guys
as well. You mean that truck that overturned on I-95 is fabricated? No, no, you're not getting
it. The stuff that has political motivation, the stuff that has, again, political motivation,
that means you have to mobilize an army or buy more missiles from Raytheon or do more stuff to
the airport. No, all that's made up. All of it. Because there really is stuff that has gone down
years and years ago. I've mentioned this many times. Someone with a camera, which, by the way,
by the way, those smartphones are not phones or cameras that happen to be phones. Right. Because
you look at the quality of the pictures they take. So how many times in the past 10 years have you
seen stuff on YouTube where like, why are these low flying helicopters all over in the midtown of L.A.
Right. Or in Chicago, you got these Apache helicopters going back and forth and some,
they closed off some streets and all that. And so they call the Pentagon, they call the D.O.D.,
they call the local military. No answer. No answer. No answer for like a day. Right. And then
a day later, say, oh, we were having a drill. Right. That's something that they write. That's
a real event. But you but did they come out and tell you it was a terrorist? No, it was a drill.
Coincidentally, when they tell you there's a terrorist event,
guess what was scheduled to happen that time? Anyway, a drill.
Right. 9-11 was a drill. The Air Force was doing a drill that morning. Multiple drills all over.
Yeah. The bus bombing in England about 10 years ago. Right. They blew up some bus. That was a
drill. 7-7. Yeah. The one in Spain. That was a drill. That was the train. That was a train.
There was the buses and it was the bus and the train was Spain and the bus was in England. Can
you write a children's song about it? Yeah, they did. They did both in England. They had the bus
and the train and the bus and the train. And in Spain it was just a train. Right. Yeah. But these
are all drills. So but but when it really goes down, guess what? They're totally silent. And
it's a drill. And again, does it make it to the mainstream media? It might for like half a second,
you know, or a minute, 30 seconds. By the way, all those choppers people record on their phones,
you know, that was a drill. OK, next thing. Right. So there is stuff happening, you know,
but it's not happening the way you write. And now, yeah, there's no reason to talk about the
covid scam and all that, because if you don't understand the AIDS thing, you'll never understand
the covid thing. That's right. There is no. Yeah. It's the treatment that makes you sick. So.
All right, man. Yeah. I mean, that's that's just the way it is. But but I'm telling you,
there were real terrorists, though they could come from a place where people have been stepped
on a while. And yeah, eventually they will react. Right. They'll lash out when you give people
nothing to lose. They might come and lash out at the people they think are responsible for that.
That's a real thing. But it is. But it doesn't happen because as you you have to be able to
afford an air ticket. Well, there's the other thing is sorry, but it's not walking depressed.
I mean, look, there's people in America. Look, I can't stand it. They go, oh, well,
all you got to do is move to another state. Well, what if you don't have the resources to move to
another state? They if they're going to if regular, quote, unquote, people that have been stepped on
anywhere in the world that want to do something here or Europe or whatever, you need a tremendous
amount of funds to pull it off and help from the inside. Right. So, again, it's artificial.
It just doesn't happen. But it does happen. There's some people that do some really stupid
stuff. And the helicopters flying low, mid city and all that. That's a drill. You know,
it does happen. I can investigate that. I still might be able to revive some contacts,
special people that but I don't need to poke around because it's intuitive at this point.
There you go.