As the Sonics are numbered, it's 232.
But anyway, who knows what what you counted
as?
How about that?
Greek, how are you this particular day?
Or actually, it's kind of getting dark where
you are, right?
It is.
Yeah.
We mean, this is the Sonic.
I think we just did it.
We just had a long conversation for a
while.
And now this is the Sonic.
I okay, I got it.
Well, if I record it, if I record
it behind the scenes one day, if I
recorded it, I turn it into something.
Okay.
So yeah.
By the way, it's the seventh month been
the seventh month for a little while.
People or the first month if you're down
under and yeah, how am I doing busy,
man?
But now we're here.
Let's get what we were talking about is
just growth generally a rated Y.
And and I kind of hit me.
This is like a extra private social media
of its own because we have no agenda.
And the only ones that well, there's the
Patreon, where people can and the Ocelli and
the Greek should tango chats where people could
put up stuff, but it's basically you and
I talking at everybody on a recording with
a subscription.
And the reason it says no agenda is
because we're not particularly covering any single subject.
And I was just wondering why we just
still have the same number of subs after
two years.
And it was like, that's just kind of
like sitting there, you know, but it's it's
fine.
Fortunately, I don't depend on it for anything.
That's good.
And yeah, I don't know what else to
say.
That's what we're basically talking about.
Right?
Sort of sadly, I do.
And that's the the other part of it.
But it's a little more significant to me
in that sense.
But what's odd about it is that there
are people that want to go on to
other platforms, say, and sort of bring this
to other platforms, but they can't do it
without us.
So somebody proposed, hey, I want to start
a signal chat.
And I'm saying to myself, well, there's already
a wide open publicly available chat at Chatango.
But does everybody know about it?
And also, yeah, it's social media, isn't it
social media, though, like the chat Chatango let's
I mean, like I said, we go through
expansive and contractive periods.
Back in the 80s.
I would say, you know, someone always ordered
chocolate cake after the air, some sweet, I
said, How long you been doing that for?
This is, you know, let me think about
it, like, four years, you got another three
years of that.
And so you go through seven years of
expansive, you know, you want sweets, and then
seven years, you crave chips and salt, or
crisps would be penny if you're British or
down under.
And then you go seven years of expansion,
seven years of contraction.
And here's the irony of it.
I know someone right now who might be
going through a contraction period, more focused, and
he got involved with this, let's say, a
corporate entity that normally to 20 or 30
million a year, and they did 84 million
by June of this year, right, right by
June, more than two and a half times.
So imagine, so that person maybe is, as
they're contracting, putting out the energy, what's the
op?
What's the thing?
The other thing going to do?
Expand.
Right?
I love watching it.
So what I'm saying is that person is
narrowing their focus more on innovation on tech
stuff, which is not what he's all about.
And why is he speaking in the third
party?
So yeah, so that's just basically the gist
of it.
What's interesting, though, I say by the fall,
we're going to do some people who are
interested in the Scalarator, the weather work, the
health stuff.
Just a couple of more announcements, things you
can make, things you can do.
I'll probably have a video of the Turbidurator.
Anyway, let's, so this narrowing focus.
And yeah, I consider this to be a
social media kind of aspect, you know?
So anyway, all right, so there's questions, there's
stuff in the chat.
Let's hop in, people, just, you know, nothing
really big.
But you got some questions?
That seems to be a pretty good thing
to work off of.
Yeah.
I have a few.
Do you have anything you want to get
to from the chat angle?
Right?
I keep saying that because that's the way
it's spelled.
Nothing that really, you know, since I'm on
the laptop, I sit down here and let's
see what's going on there.
Just perusing, just general stuff, just like some
minor questions, nothing big.
I mean, I think there's some stuff in
the news that people, you know, everything, just
to, well, I don't get a lot of
stuff in the, that's been in, there's a
lot of unanswered, right?
There's a lot of unanswered questions regarding things
that people are reacting to, obviously.
But there always is.
And sometimes it's more intense than others.
Quick question, though.
I mean, we kind of have a circumstance
here where we're not, you know, an open
air business where anybody can walk in at
this point.
We've kind of set up a private club,
if you will, in the social media world
where it's like, hey, look, if you actually
pay, you can get in, but only people
that pay do.
So it's not just walk in randomly.
You sort of have to find it.
To the public.
Yeah.
I would never do a YouTube.
I'm not condoning.
Look, I was speaking to someone in a
small group the other day that has a
YouTube channel.
And I give a measurable offer of my
disdain of YouTube, what I really think of
it.
Because, you know me, years ago, even this
was around Ocelli in the Greek back 10
years ago.
It was 10 years ago, maybe more, about
10 years.
It is more.
It is more by now.
It is more than 10 now.
It's definitely over the 10 year mark for
sure.
More than a decade.
A decade, a tenth of a century.
Right?
Minimum.
Is another way to say it.
So a hundredth of a millennium.
But here's the thing.
You know what I did back in 2014
or 15?
I went and read.
What?
What did I read?
Guess what?
I went to YouTube terms and services and
all their community or whatever stuff.
And I said, I'm going to go sign
up for something like this.
This is like the most fascist, god awful,
mind control, passive aggressive.
What's the opposite of passive aggressive?
Aggressive aggressive.
Let's see.
That would be the shit I've ever seen.
Active.
Active passivity.
Right?
Active aggressive.
Yeah.
That's I would never do that.
I mean, and also Facebook.
I think I put like I was going
to sign up for Facebook.
I went in.
It was like Theo.
I did a pseudonym like Theo something.
And then I went and read the, I
said, wait a second, what are you doing?
Go read the full length, all the legal
stuff.
I was like, oh my gosh, oh my
gosh.
You know what the hell?
I said, I would never do this ever,
ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever myself.
Now it doesn't mean I don't do interviews
or, you know, if you want to put
everything on YouTube, go ahead.
Like what Sam, he did Greek speak and
all that on YouTube and all that.
So fine.
I want nothing to do with it.
You know, I don't care if it goes
up to Mr. B.
East, you know, if you want to buy
me cigarettes and coffee, that's fine.
But, uh, no, uh, uh, that's why I
sold on do banking until I find someone
who wants to work with me.
You know, I don't want to be treated
like, you know, everyone's going to treat you
like an asshole anyway.
Why go into a trust agreement with someone
who tells you they are on paper?
Oh my God.
So no, I've got, there's nothing in the
chat.
I would, I would gladly.
I understand.
But I would gladly, uh, there's the joke
folks.
I would gladly do Mr. Beast though, because
that would be a collision of two worlds
that seemingly it's almost like this has never
been done before.
I'd love to see what would happen.
Uh, the, one of the most unthinking and
yet, you know, completely money driven circuit that
guy gives away houses, you know, uh, wild
stuff.
Yeah.
But I'm more of a, I'm more of
a diogenes.
Plato was crossing a bridge in a cart
and he saw diogenes under the river, washing
vegetables and Plato yells at him, Hey, diogenes,
we're going to go visit the King and
you're washing vegetables and, and he says, if
you knew how to wash vegetables, you wouldn't
have to go visit the King.
So that's my answer for the Mr. Beast
thing.
No, fair enough.
And uh, if you went to Mr. B
here, here's the thing.
I'm very personal.
If Mr. Beast invited you to his crib
and asked him, him to cook you a
meal, do you think it would be a
good meal or be total white, white people?
Shit.
Oh, I, I can't even imagine how bad
it would be.
It would ask him to make you some
pasta for zoo or something like that.
Would you know what it would be like?
The most horrible shit you'd, you would be,
yeah, run into the toilet and you wouldn't,
you wouldn't even be edible.
No Greek.
You'd be begging for the white people's shit
after what he puts in front of you.
Yeah.
To me.
So are we judging him?
So I judge people by their base character
on the, on stuff they can do.
Like when I meet someone and then people
ask me, how are they?
So, you know, I didn't think about, you
know, what did you think of so-and
-so?
I said, you know what, let me think
about it.
If they give up and if they invited
me over for a meal and they had
to cook me a meal, what would be
the outcome?
And that, and that's how I judged them,
by the way.
I know it sounds crazy.
So what you do, so then what are
they good for?
What are they good for?
And you pocket them there.
And so if someone asks me, well, how,
what do you think of them?
Well, they're good for this.
Very specific.
Okay.
Right.
Like, you know, even with people who's Chuck
O'Chell, he's got a good voice.
He's ready for prime time and I'm just
doing, he, you know, both of us speaking,
I'm this crazy guy and here's a guy
that was, you know, co-host and he
sounds like his voice sounds like it's ready
for prime time and that's it.
I don't say anything else.
Right.
Okay.
So anyway.
My skill is, is talent.
You know, you, you don't ask a hammer
if it can handle the nail.
You just know it can and you use
it when you need a hammer.
What I do is I always point out
what I know.
Yeah.
Uh, I never thought about you cooking a
meal though.
Actually I never have.
Honestly.
I never really did.
I need a few more minutes on that
and I'll answer you for you to cook
a meal.
What would it be like?
But that's like a, um, a general overall
thing that I can imagine or, you know,
is, can the person handle the kitchen?
Well, see, that's, that's a lot, by the
way, there's a lot of cliches around the
kitchen, right?
Of course.
I, you know what, I think I have
the answer that you would give regarding me
cooking a meal for you.
I think you would, you would, uh, allow
it a little bit reluctantly, but only if
I did it in your kitchen.
Oh, I never thought, I don't think of
it in my kitchen, but that's fine.
Oh, well.
Theoretically.
Give me an example.
When I was out at the mines, when
I was out at the mines, uh, Placer
mines, uh, off of exit 10 and I
10 just before California on the right hand
side, north side, um, uh, everyone would work
and then they had to drive to the
Texaco or the nearest truck stop and get
hot dogs.
And this is like for a month straight
eat food at the truck stop.
And it was, it was more like a
seven 11 truck stop, not a sit down.
So microwave pizzas and all this stuff.
So whatever, whatever you can grab and go
and throw in a microwave and there are
things that are designed just burritos, burritos, hot
dogs, pizzas, singular hot pockets and no restaurants.
Yeah.
Singular.
Oh my gosh.
And so I had a bag of rice.
Yeah.
I had a bag of rice, bag of
beans, cans of beans, condensed milk, pots, camping
stove, veg.
I remember I had, it was winter time,
which means it's in the fifties, sixties and
seventies.
Um, I had one of those, uh, heads
of lettuce that you buy.
It's still growing.
It's in like on a plastic thing.
You know, it's like five bucks for a
little head of lettuce.
You're like, wow.
And it's still growing.
You turn it upside down.
It's got the root ball, a little bit
of one of these little maxi pads with
moisture.
I kept that thing alive on my dashboard
for a month.
So I would just take one or two
leaves of lettuce off and within a two,
two days after that, two more leaves would
start to blossom out.
Right.
Okay.
And I kept it going for, yeah.
Anyway.
So, um, yeah, I was going to bring
up the fruit, uh, aspect of it.
Okay.
Remember we, uh, two Sonics ago.
Yeah.
Okay.
So basically with fruit, you have a block,
you have the branch and, and you have
blossoms form on the stem.
Um, when the center of the blossom would
be like the, the female over ovary, let's
say, and it's fertile.
When the blossom is fertilized, the pedals fall
off.
Blossom essentially no longer serves a function, uh,
quickly in the center part expands in some
fruit.
The stem is the ovary or the stem
is the fallopian tube because the ovaries different
than the flow.
There's a technical, no, no, there's nothing in
of tubes, but no, the end of the,
the, where the stem, where the blossom is,
let's say is, uh, almost, um, on the
end of the female counterpart.
Okay.
So the blossom of the center, the center
of the blossom, I misunderstood not the pedals,
but the center.
Yeah.
Is that's pollinated.
Right.
When it's pollinated, it starts to become a
fruit very much like when a woman's ovum
or any other species is pollinated or fertilized.
Right.
What's interesting is, is the, you have an
umbilical cord, which is also by induction in
the human and in the animal, by the
way, they say nutrients go down the umbilical
cord.
But if you study what's in there, it's
mostly plasma, very, very little nutrients.
It's a type of plasma, just like we
spoke of that.
Um, if these medical quacks ever figured out
that all of the blood cells have serial
numbers on them to, or designation points, just
like you would put a designation and address,
right?
Like you see, they just see red blood
cells.
They don't know that this red blood cell
goes to your big toe.
This one goes to your eye.
This one goes to your ear.
This one might go to your brain if
it can, if it's good enough and it's
going to hang around long enough.
Right.
Um, they, they don't understand that they never
will, by the way, it's, it won't be
allowed.
Um, so back to the fruit.
The explanation that we're upside down plants, right,
again, takes hold, uh, but not, not as
a piece of fruit, but just the, the
overall archetype, these things are working through, but
back to the umbilical cord, the, the fruit
that grows on the end of the tree
is essentially growing from the most minuscule.
If you ever look at the stem that
the fruit hangs on, it is so narrow
and so thin and how much water develops
in the fruit.
It's on, it's an order of magnitude of
what can physically travel through that stem.
Nothing travels through that stem.
By the way, anyone, I think I want
once matter, if it was here, anyone who's
cut down a fresh tree, green tree, do
you see how tight the wood is?
Even softwood.
Do you see, can you imagine water migrating
down that branch that would, even though it
is porous?
No, it never happens.
So where does that water come from and
where, how does the fruit develop so robustly
with such massive water quantity, right?
And that's the, that's what I've been studying
because that's going to lead to a lot
of answers.
You see, years ago, I knew people in
the dead row chronology that were graduate degree
students.
They, they, I told them, I shooed them
away.
Just like when we have a neighbor whose
cats come over here to eat because we
have the good food and we brought it
up to her and she goes, just shoo
him away.
Just shoo him away.
Well, I had to shoo these graduate students,
particularly one away.
And the way I did that is I
said, you guys are learning about trees and
know everything about trees.
Right.
And I asked him, well, he said, yes.
I said, well, can you explain how one
blade of grass grows?
I'm on a cot.
Right.
Okay.
And he looked at me and says, how
dare you talk to an academic like he's
an asshole?
Because they don't know.
They don't know how even a blade of
grass, which is the simplest form, right?
So when you start to look at the
aspects of how water is produced by biological
and all that, a fruit is in your
face, like an exact, it's like a cartoon
version of what's happening in our bodies and
all living things.
You know what I mean?
By a cartoon caricature.
It's like certain features, uh, prominent are very
exaggerated, exaggerated.
Yeah.
So exaggeration and yet it's a very shallow
representation of something.
It's not the actual thing.
Right.
That's what I'm right.
Yeah.
The common denominator is what I'm looking for.
The fruit is just so much an exaggeration
of what's going on with induction and it
needs to be watched.
But I'm not talking about going, you know,
if you're an urbanist going to a supermarket
and the fruit that's already, I'm talking about
watching it grow.
Right.
So, um, yeah, I'm going to sit around
and watch paint dry.
Right.
Um, yeah.
Watching the fruit grow and the changes in
shape, color, density, all that stuff.
And we know it's extremely dense when it's
not ripe.
Right.
So, um, and green, you know, uh, the
hard, very, very, uh, very rigid, very, uh,
you know, uh, young in its presentation as
a fruit.
I mean, some fruits are like rocks, you
know, uh, in, in their characteristics.
Right.
But, um, it makes me wonder one thing
that red Fox, one thing in this red
Fox, why is money green?
Of course.
Uh, right.
Uh, good.
Good.
The Jews pick it before.
It's right.
Cause the Jews like to pick it when
it's before it's right.
Yeah.
Okay.
So the question though, that I have is
just real quick in this explanation, wouldn't a
cactus be even worse for, or more extreme
because you know, they, they give you this
weird explanation for how a cactus ends up,
you know, retaining water.
It's the same, but it's the same.
It doesn't read.
Okay.
It needs water.
Just like you need food.
You don't use it directly.
It doesn't transmit.
See, they're, they're trying to keep you in
a physical world that if you can't put
it in a beaker.
So if you need a certain amount of
nutrition, which is easy to figure out, you
don't have to cut anyone open or do
too much math.
You just lock up a bunch of people.
You feed this group of people, one ounce
of food a day.
The other one, two ounces, all the way
up to 30 ounces, 40, 60 ounces, you
got 60 groups of people and you see
who does best.
And then that would be the average of
how many ounces of food you need every
day.
Right?
Well, that's using easy to do a study
like that, but that's using ounces and literal
weight as a scale.
That's not the only, right?
Yeah.
So once you get, so let's say we,
we figure out it's 16 ounces a day.
You do, by the way, you need two
pounds of water and one pound of food
for each prisoner.
Or if you're going to keep people in
a confined area, you must supply them a
minute.
It's the minimum 16 ounces of food, solid
and 32 ounces of water a day.
So if you had a thousand people, you
need a thousand pounds of food a day
and 2000, uh, what would do the math?
That's a quarter.
Um, uh, so you'd need 250 gallons of
water a day for a thousand people.
So, um, yeah.
So if you guys plan on keeping any
prisoners anytime soon, there's their math.
So what I'm trying to say is all
that food, let's say 16 ounces a day,
they, they, they don't acknowledge anything unless you
put it in a beaker, right?
And you can measure it.
So if the people need to survive 16
ounces of food, you put that in a
package and you say, okay, how does this
food get into their body?
Right.
And if you do the math, um, they
eat all the food and then you measure
what they excrete through feces and urine.
You'll see a very tiny amount about, um,
the majority, the majority is out like three
quarters of it.
Can I, can I leave a question in
the year real quick?
Because it relates exactly to, it's a direct
question from somebody that relates exactly to what
you're saying.
Um, they wanted to know that since calories
are an invalid way of measuring things, they
see we are logic there and understand and
acknowledge it.
Uh, they were wondering if there is a
way to calibrate it because it seems as
though it would take, uh, more than one,
uh, more than one, let me see what
it says here.
More than, oh, hold on.
Hold on.
Let me, let me finish my thought and
then we'll finish the question.
Is that all right?
Certainly.
Let's just, we'll make this very fractional.
Okay.
So if you look at the percentage of
how much, how little actually is taken into
the body and then you write, do the
math, is it where, well, we don't really
need that much then.
Right?
We do because the body is very selective
in extracting energy and that amount that is,
does not come out of the body actually
is converted.
It's called link low, low energy nuclear reaction
and L E N R.
So you could look that up.
Um, there's it because it's induction.
In other words, the material aspect turns into
energy and then turns back into material in
the body, very selectively in cells and other
things that have to happen that way.
Right?
So you can't put that in a beaker,
right?
That's why very often people would ask me
about technology.
I'm not impressed until I can, well, during
the days of the fax machine, isn't this
great?
We got fat.
I'm not impressed until you could fax someone
a turkey sandwich.
If you can fax me a turkey sandwich,
then I'll be impressed.
If you, and then it became, if you
can email me and eat a turkey sandwich,
I'll be impressed or peanut butter and jelly
sandwich.
Now, right now, if you can, are you
impressed by that?
No.
If you could send me a peanut butter
and jelly sandwich on zoom or teams, I'll
be impressed.
I'm not impressed by any of this because
it's still using quantities, but right here's the
part that I never really get into is
perturbations in the ether and the wire in
the air.
The signal is not physical at all.
There's no electrons moving anywhere and we're using
it.
It's in our faces that we're using non
-material energies constantly to produce pictures on the
screen, information and all that.
But they have, they will not bridge the
gap only with maybe 3d printers or a
fax machine as a page.
You can use something you could print.
They will not bridge the gap and be
able to teleport you something through the airwaves
or the wire.
They, you're not allowed to do that.
That is a big, big no, no.
Yeah.
I object.
I object to your even calling a 3d
printer or something as a step forward because
it's no different than the transmission of what
was a Xerox, which is not the same
as a photocopy, but when they used to
be able to transmit Xerox, you have to
load it with something.
Not only that, but you're sending information from
one device to another and telling another device
to do it.
So literally a 3d printer, you load crap
into it and it's preloaded the Xerox machine
or the three.
So you have to put material.
I'm talking about the actual material taking form
from what was sent through the wire or
the airwaves.
That will never happen.
The 3d printer is no different than the
fax machine or the teletype before it because
it's only telling a device that has the
material elsewhere to recreate something similar through a
signal.
So the only thing that's been transmitted is
the signal.
Run out of paper.
Yeah.
The fax machine runs out of paper 3d.
No, no.
So, okay.
I went through this whole diatribe.
All we need is, in other words, we're
never going to get the transporter, right?
For Star Trek or you see it in
sci-fi, it exists.
It's not that difficult to do if you
copy biology, right?
Pouring a coffee here, if you'd like some.
So it's not that difficult to do.
What's difficult is the mind.
You know, it's just like, um, um, John
C.
Lilly, the province of the mind has no
limits other than the limits we set upon
it.
Right?
So the whole thing is about limiting.
Right.
So what you're saying is thus far, all
we have thus far, all we have is
the transmittal of information and telling another device
to recreate something.
And it doesn't matter, by the way, if
it's a radio, even when I send my
voice across from one radio to another, my
radio is telling the other radio speaker, recreate
my voice.
Now it happens quickly, but basically that's not
my voice actually over there.
That's a recreation of my voice on that
speaker.
Right?
Sure.
But, but here, let's, let me just take
it another step further.
The bandwidth required, you have an empty box
and when you send someone a signal, you're
going to need the peanut butter jelly sandwich
on your end, right?
It disappears on your end and it's reappearing
on my end.
We have the bandwidth for that, right?
We have the bandwidth and the connectivity for
that was what I'm saying, but the device
necessary to completely turn that peanut butter and
jelly sandwich into energy and send it to
me is more difficult than what the body
is doing.
Because otherwise, if he, if it was, if
it copied the body, you'd put the peanut
butter and jelly sandwich in the transporter and
it would turn into feces, right?
But 20% of it would be gone
coming over the signal.
And then on my end, it would end
up as a, as a, a peanut butter
and jelly sandwich facsimile, like goo and only
20% of it.
Are you, are you with me?
So these things, the reason I said this,
whoever's following what I'm saying is going to
be, holy shit, Greek, you think too much.
No, I don't think too much.
Get that out of your head.
We were not thinking correctly, right?
So we don't want to follow the human
body directly.
Right?
Imagine that.
So we want the whole peanut butter and
jelly sandwich to be sent over.
So anyway, okay, well, so the question about
calories, let me just do a recap.
It's a unit of measurement has to pertain
to the, let's say the physicality of what
you're talking about.
Right?
So if someone says, you know, cut me
a board, uh, 23 inches long, you don't
say how many pounds of that do you,
do you want, right?
It doesn't work.
So a calorie is defined by a thermal
unit calories, actually a thermal unit.
We've been so brainwashed.
You think it has something to do with
food, right?
It's a thermal unit.
That's that metric that is the amount of
thermal units that are required, a thermal unit
to raise one gram of water, one degree
Celsius, right?
Um, or one cubic centimeter of water, one
degree Celsius.
And I got, there's a joke about it
and if you read old encyclopedias anyway, so
that's all it is.
So what they, the calorimeter is very, there's
several ways of doing it, but what they
do, they want to find out how many
calories are in a banana.
They put it in this tube when they
purge, they seal it and there's a valve
on there.
They pull a vacuum and then they purge
it with oxygen.
So it's pure oxygen in there.
There's something that looks like a spark plug
and they go boom.
And the banana turns to ash, completely burned
off.
And that whole device is submerged in a
given volume of water, how many, exactly how
many grams of water.
And they do the math.
What was the temperature change in the water?
There's so many grams divided.
This is how many calories.
It's very, very old experiment, right?
Now that's why they say you're burning up
calories.
The body doesn't work that way.
Now if you find yourself, the joke here
is if you find yourself pooping charcoal briquettes
or ash, then calories apply to you, right?
And I don't think anyone ever has.
So calories is a misnomer for applying to
food.
Because if you eat a banana, let's say
it's 70 calories, and you poop past that
banana, is that poop ignitable and burnable in
that calorimeter?
Sure is.
And if you do the math, you're going
to see they only used a small portion
of it.
The rest of it is still in this,
right?
Anyway, so calories do not work at all.
It's a misnomer.
And they put this stuff in front of
you.
And there's a book written, there's a lady
in the 1920s who came up that we
should apply this to food, right?
Some idiot.
And so because of that bitch, we got
a misnomer, just like the food pyramid and
some other idiot, right?
So anyway, I hope that answers roundabout and
gives an example to people.
But would you finish that question, by the
way?
Yeah, sure.
The question, I'm boiling this down real fast
because it will be better off.
They're basically saying, look, if you take one
of these ways of measuring, you would obviously
need more than one because 100 pounds of
brick is definitely not useful in the same
way that 100 pounds of rice is, or
et cetera.
So the quality and some of the characteristics
of what it is you're doing.
So they're saying, is there more than one
measurement that could be useful here?
Like say one or two ways of measuring
something that would create the thing that they
say is useful as a calorie count.
And you said- There is, but it's
not calories.
Yes.
Right.
It's not calories for sure for anything alive.
Calories are only for when they invented the
calorimeter.
That's it.
It's only for that.
And they're trying to apply.
Just like I put up the thing about
blood glucose measurement, they still don't know how
to do it, right?
But they're condemning millions of people with their
treatments.
And it's deliberate, by the way.
And as part of the conversation, look, you
can poop charcoal if you ate charcoal.
That's possible.
Yeah, there's no conversion, but if you measure
the amount of charcoal you ate and the
amount you pooped, it would be identical.
That's which leads to, is it biocompatible?
Years ago, I had a prized chess set,
checkers, sorry, and one of my sisters was
a real nag.
She's about four years younger at the time,
and she grabbed a couple of checkers pieces
and swallowed them.
She goes, you can't play now.
So what we did was we made sure
that the big brother had to go through,
you know what, to pick out and clean
off the undigested corn and chess pieces.
How much by eating that plastic did you
gain?
Right?
None.
Now, you didn't gain anything, any nutrition.
There's certain things that, for example, you ever
heard of something called margarine?
Your body will poop 100% of that.
That's alien.
That's just like eating plastic.
So if you ate a tub, an ounce
of margarine, you would poop out an ounce
of margarine.
There's no use for it.
Only some moisture would come out.
There's a bunch of foods out there.
As a matter of fact, you know, most
of the things added to American foods would
be, if they were not added to food,
they would be considered hazardous substances if used
anywhere else, right?
So you could put as much of it
as you want in the food, but if
you're going to drop some on the sidewalk,
it's an EPA violation, right?
So the same was with water.
The EPA had water toxicity parameters, and if
you had water that exceeded these parameters, it
was a violation.
But if you look at an assay or
a lab report of the water in Phoenix,
Arizona, it was worse than the water that
they called you a violator for if you
just dropped it on the sidewalk.
The hypocrisy.
But it's still going on.
Anyway, I would say that the easiest thing
to understand, it's not quantity, it's quality.
So what you do to measure what you're
going to eat is by first seasonality.
If it's hot outside where you are, and
it's going to be hot outside, because that's
a predominant, it's not just heat, because it
could be wintertime and you could be in
an overly heated office.
You've heard of people, especially when it's hot
outside, oh, they over AC.
I've walked into, it's 110 degrees here.
You walk into some big stores and it's
like a refrigerator, right?
I'm talking about the predominant energy.
So when it's winter season, you don't want
to eat things that come from a hot
climate because it's going to convert into your
body and change your blood type, quality into,
not type, but blood quality, maybe effect on
the type, to being in the tropics and
you won't be able to warm up.
The opposite is true.
If you're in a hot climate and you
eat things that come from cold climates like
salmon, you will not be able to cool
down.
Do you remember when there was the big
salmon craze 20 years ago?
It's good for you, eat it, and then
they killed it because they said they put
color in it.
They killed it by turning it so they
could see if they could control you.
I would walk into people's homes here in
the desert and they had the AC turned
down to 65 and they were still sweating.
For me, I keep the AC at 80
or whatever, and it was because, I said,
you're eating tropical, you're eating Arctic fish.
Oh, I love it.
In the middle of summer in Tucson, that's
the worst thing you can do.
That's the first thing you can do.
There's no quantity there.
Get away from the quantity.
It's the quality of what you're doing.
Obviously, in most cases, the quantity will be
based on your size.
If you had people that were a foot
tall and you were to go buy a
dinner plate set for them, remember, they're only
12 inches tall, the whole human.
You were going to go buy a dinner
set for them.
By the way, I was in Los Lunas,
New Mexico, 10 years ago, and there was
a little old lady going through Walmart and
she was buying little doll sets, little cups
and plates and stuff.
I said, oh, it's for your granddaughter?
She goes, no, it's for the little people.
She has little people visiting her.
Anyway, yeah, so if you know someone or
a family that's only 12 or 14 inches
tall and you wanted to buy them a
dinner plate set, you know what the dinner
plate set would look like, right?
Real small, right?
Yeah, sure.
You'd fill up that little tiny plate with
food and they would be very satisfied, wouldn't
they?
Mm-hmm.
Right?
Now, we got someone that's 12 feet tall
and the dinner plate looks like a big
banquet plate, two feet in diameter.
You have to fill that for them to
get satisfied.
You get my point?
The bigger you are, the more food you're
probably going to require.
The smaller you are, the less.
So that's the quantitative aspect, yeah?
That's the only quantitative, but the main overarching
thing is seasonality, and squeeze in between quantity
and quality, the seasonality would be the type
of energy.
When I start discussing energy with people, which
I did recently, they didn't understand.
They got the seasonal thing.
You have to be completely brain dead to
not get the seasonality.
Usually when you bring up the seasonality metaphor,
it rings a bell with mostly everyone, right?
Unless they're already on a negation, they're like,
oh no, anything this guy says, I'm going
to say the opposite, right?
So there's people like that also.
The other thing I start out with is,
I went to this restaurant, and the food
was salty that I ordered.
A simple dish, and the person that was
with me, their food was salty also.
Everything was salty.
Waitress comes and says, how's everything?
I said, everything's really salty.
The cook has a sweet tooth, doesn't he?
She goes, yeah, he does.
He's always eating candy bars and cake and
dessert.
How do you know?
Well, because he's got a sweet tooth, he's
loading up on sugars, and in order to
balance that, he's putting the salt that he
should be taking to balance him out into
everybody else's food.
Now what kind of balance is that?
Is that really making balance, or is that
the universal principles trying to make balance, but
it's screwing everything up because the person is
overdoing the sweets?
Well, they're doing the right thing, but they're
applying it to themselves.
They're applying something to themselves to others.
They should be applying it to themselves, but
they're applying it to everyone else also.
Who knows if they were also eating, but
they were dishing it out.
So even though the universal principle was still
overall satisfied, it was causing chaos in our
realm, you see?
So it's like when you're wealthy enough, going
to the Super Bowl is not a thrill,
right?
Having personal hunting parties where, what's a personal
hunting party?
Okay, they even did a movie that was
released and then withdrawn.
When you see homeless people disappearing, what they
do, they have these vans, they pick them
up, they offer you money, food, or whatever,
they take you to a place where they
clean you up, have you do some rudimentary
exercise.
They feed you, they promise you money and
all that.
Then they take you to another place and
they tell you, give you some rudimentary weapons,
and they tell you, run.
Just run.
Okay, do I need to get more detail
on this?
Okay.
I think you can put that together.
Yeah.
Okay.
So the Super Bowl doesn't do it.
Human hunting parties don't do it for you.
Hey, how about we get a bunch of
journalists ready and we go start a war?
Because every war is started, then the reason
for it comes later, right?
War is propagated, right?
Now, that's a lot more fun because there
you can do more wagering, death pool betting,
and all that kind of stuff on a
big scale.
And that's what's going on, by the way,
on a big scale.
So when you see war, you're actually supporting
it by watching football because you're just a
scaled out, you know, your sport competition thing
and your political competition, there's just a bunch
of wealthy people.
I just like to see what happens when
you bring mayhem into another, right?
Anyway, make a long story short, and without
getting philosophical, the quality will never be beat
by quantity, right?
Like, for example, go get Hermes green crocodile
handbag, it's 100k, right?
How many handbags, purses, can you buy reasonable
ones for 100,000?
So let's say a reasonable handbag is like
200 bucks, a quality one, let's say 400,
500, right?
Yeah, top shelf, 500 bucks should cover a
coach purse, say, yeah, go ahead.
Yeah, you can get a coach, I remember
a coach, like you can get, yeah, for
like 250, you get a pretty decent one.
But so let's say 500, right?
That's 200 purses for the cost of one,
right?
Why?
You see, why does it stand out so
much, right?
Now here's the thing, if you had the
same exact quality as that 100,000 dollar
purse at the 500 dollar level, it's the
same thing, isn't it?
It is.
You know, the perception is different, and that's
exactly what quality does.
Once you become quality-minded, you actually live
on the cheap.
Living on the cheap means you're not expending
energy, wasting energy, worrying, being ill, right?
So when you understand quality, real quality, not
perceived quality and what's social, you know, so
what do they call it when you buy
an expensive handbag to show off or whatever,
right, or expensive car, right?
If you want the quality, you don't care
about the price or whatever, you can do
it on the cheap, right?
So this is really where it's at, and
they're not going to ever, this is never
going to be public.
You know, there's people that buy expensive cars
and drive around like on the main streets
at night where everybody is, so everyone could
look at their car, and I always point,
you know, people look.
I said, look, this guy is out here
driving senselessly, you know, obviously he's trying to
get attention in his Ferrari, and he invested
all that.
He might enjoy driving it, but he's doing
what he's doing now.
So people who don't care about him at
all will give him attention.
What kind of a pathetic state, spiritual state
is that?
Could you imagine doing something to get attention
from people who don't care about you at
all?
Wow, what a twisted world, right?
What a twisted reality, which is very common,
by the way.
How many times have you been on the
strip at night and see guys just coasting
in their very expensive cars, and everyone's pointing
at the Lamborghini, Ferrari, Rolls-Royce, or whatever,
right?
A lot of people call it a penis
substitute or a midlife crisis mobile or whatever,
because what they're doing is...
The bottom line is, though, they're getting attention
from people who don't care at all about
them.
Oh, right.
The bottom line is, yeah.
So the thing is, when you understand what
you should be caring about, you'll find out
you can do it really on the cheap.
I mean, it doesn't...
You can live...
Okay, let's just...
You can have an exceptionally high-quality life,
full of, like, high level of fitness, vibrancy,
you know, what they call health, and be
joyful on the level of any other qualitative
thing you can measure it by, right?
On the real cheap, almost just at the
same level as it would be, quote-unquote,
what normal expenditures would be, whether it's your
food, your clothes, all this stuff you can
get.
Always seek quality over the quantity, because I
think when you have the car that we
just mentioned, cruising, or the Hermes green crocodile
handbag, or these Rolex watches or whatever, that
is no longer just a qualitative statement, because
let's say a $10,000 Rolex watch with
the jewels and the stainless steel, that's about
less than $200 worth of material.
Why not just get a $200 watch that
tells time just as well as a Rolex?
You see, so now you have the quality
timekeeping, right?
So you can do a very high-quality
existence on the cheap, is really where it's
at, being here, because the rest of it
is just a waste of time or getting
attention from people who don't care about you
at all.
And I think that's one of the cruxes
of what I speak on, right?
We kind of went into a short thing
about home economics, how you should set up
your home and things like that.
Anyone can do that, right?
And you'll probably be healthier and better fitness.
I have to use that word health, because
when I say fitness, most people are still
wrong.
How many miles did I do on the
treadmill today?
Did I go to the gym, right?
How many push-ups can I do?
So, you know, be optimum.
So you cannot optimize with quantity when you're
dealing with your own situation.
You have to optimize the quality first, right?
Before you order something up, you should know,
is it the right thing that I'm ordering?
And there is a better way to do
it.
Anyway, you got any other questions or anything?
Sure, I do.
The last part of that whole question, though,
and a long thing that they put in
is, they were making a joke and said,
according to them, I should just be able
to eat dirt and do just fine because
all the nutrients are in the dirt.
No, but they're making a joke, where it's
like, why not just eat dirt?
Does it work that way?
Is it biocompatible?
And it would be too active.
Dirt is too active.
Like if you eat, there's certain cheeses now,
like I used to like Maytag blue cheese,
and they spray it with bacillus, which is
the stuff that you find that they say
causes the cold and all that.
And it was just, I had some recently,
and they don't ship it to hot climates
in the summer.
It's like $50 a pound or $30 a
pound Maytag cheese when you get it here.
And oh my gosh, they really messed it
up.
And I looked up online what they were
doing, and the younger people took over.
They're spraying too much bacillus, basically bacteria on
it for their packaging.
And it really upset my stomach.
It was too active.
Called the culture was just too strong.
And I've had beer like that.
I don't know if you've ever been around
people who do brew their own beer, and
they just quite didn't heat it up enough.
And the yeast was a little too strong,
and I was burping, farting, and hiccuping all
at the same time.
Because it was just that yeast was still
too active.
Yeah, right.
This microbrewery, guys, it feels like somebody's trying
to blow air directly into your gut is
what it feels like, because it's like it's
constantly expanding.
If it's not done, yeah.
So yeah, it's bubbling.
It's like, oh my gosh.
Especially when you hit the dark cavity in
your body at that 98.6 mixed in
with everything else.
So when you eat dirt, unless it's really
sandy, you're going to experience a very active
thing, and you will get something out of
it all right.
Now, not all dirt is the same.
The most dirt, by the way, is mostly
silica sand, even though it doesn't look like
it.
It's a very high amount of mineral and
metal and quartz and things like that.
So you're not going to get anything out
of it.
But the reason I went through all that
is because there's no such thing as a
bad question.
Actually, the opposite of a bad question is
another bad question.
But anyway, so there's no such thing as
a bad question or statement.
Fair enough.
For future Sonics, yes, I would like to
hear more about Donald Marshall.
They were responding to- Well, just go
to StOlga69 YouTube, StOlga69, just like in the
number 69.
He did a cover where he, save yourself
the trouble.
There's a bunch of the trouble of going
through all the videos and Donald Marshall speaking
what he did.
Daniel, he went and edited pretty much anything
and everything that could be found on YouTube.
And he's got three videos, I think, several
hours long of everything compiled according to category
and subject.
He's got several videos.
And Donald Marshall actually gave it a thumbs
up also.
He's kind of behind the scenes.
There are other people that have been speaking
on the human cloning.
He gives examples of how a lot of
popular people, Britney Spears and so on, even
do videos where they show cloning centers in
a cartoon kind of thing, like they want
to break free.
It's not only the cloning center, it's the
time slam, what's that, right?
And the little drill that they tell everyone
are great, aliens, forms of aliens and all
this underground stuff, which I'm interested in because
it ties into the species invasion.
We're supposedly going to have around 2046.
It's also in the book of Revelation, 200
million creatures come up to the surface.
So it all ties in together.
But yeah, I don't really endorse Donald Marshall,
but I find a lot of the things
that he says are useful and actually factual.
There was, no longer online, because around the
time of Donald Marshall, you could still find
human robotoids.
And there were several people, I wouldn't say
politicians, but government people and journalists, recordings from
the 80s, of them talking about these human
robotoids.
And they call them human robotoids, they're just
biological clones.
So when you hear robotoid, you think of
nuts and bolts, right?
No, it's actually a human clone.
And there was one guy, I forgot, I
don't know who it was, but he was
pretty prominent in the DC circuit, let's say,
I guess you could call it a circuit.
And he said, we have a problem with
these human robotoids.
This is late 70s, late 80s or early
80s.
He says, we can have someone, let's say
the president of the United States in a
robotoid form, go to another country, say something,
create an international incident, right?
And it's not the president, right?
It's a clone.
And boy, I wonder what they would say
if they were alive now.
And this recording and these little snippets in
the media, this was mainstream, by the way,
not alternative.
It was online and you could hear the
recording and now I can't find it at
all.
If anyone wants to look for it, I
mean, that's fine.
And yeah, it's a lot stranger than we
can do on our own.
So just take in whatever you can take
in.
Fair enough.
Some people say that we're gonna look back
on the days when people use terms like
NPC, non-player characters, and think the same
way that there could be a literal way
to look at that.
And there's also a symbolic way to look
at it.
Anyway.
Yeah, back in the 80s, by the way,
I hung around with people that were on
the Ken Kesey's Magic Bus and were around
Marcel Duchamp and some prominent New York madams,
not the ones in the media.
They would refer to people that were, they
didn't use NPC back then.
They just said that person's not conscious.
Right.
It was a common thing that they said.
They have no consciousness or very low conscious
individual.
Basically, they're asleep, but they're awake, right?
Well, the Hollywood madam still doesn't, yeah, the
Hollywood madam still doesn't give people up.
Although she's back kind of in circulation because
Charlie Sheen just released a two-part documentary
about his life.
I don't know if you got anything to
say about Charlie Sheen, but, cause some people
claim he was caught up.
Yeah, sorry.
Everyone in Hollywood's caught up.
No, I mean, I have a relative who
was CEO of 20th Century Fox and then
CEO of Paramount Pictures and they're not the
same person.
I mean, they're not, it's so funny.
Years ago, they were doing a Republican, let's
say more than 10 years ago, they were
doing a Republican fundraiser.
And then the last fundraiser he did was
for Joe Biden.
Right, so it's all just crazy.
There's nothing, but no, no, it's just a
disgusting mess.
But I thought the Hollywood madam, wasn't that,
there was another madam that says she was
not suicidal, a little short brunette lady, but
then they found her hanging, right?
Yeah, that's the DC madam, if you will,
but the Hollywood madam.
That's the DC madam, yep.
Well, this is what I got from the
madam.
You know, like prostitutes, right, are more informative
and helpful than any attorney would ever be.
So I'll tell you what she, they had
a place in this guy, Oleg Cassini, he
was a designer and he used to call
him No Legs Cassini because he would come
in in a wheelchair.
And all they wanted to do, these higher
up people, let's say, that they would entertain
or serve, they would just sit there and
talk for two hours, nothing.
It's, you know, you think, oh, I'm gonna
go see a call girl or go to
whatever madams, they think it's gonna be involving,
yeah, it usually is.
But very often, more often than not, these
people would just sit around and talk.
They wanted someone to talk to because it's
ultimately confidential, right?
Forget about the confidential.
And the thing is, you have confidentiality with
attorneys and psychiatrists or psychologists, but they're idiots,
right?
Well, they're idiots and they have an out.
They literally have an out in their supposed
agreement where I can go to the cops
if, not so with the call girl.
Yeah, that's right, they say that.
Not so with the call girl.
And they do, just like the Catholic priests
used to, yeah, not so with the call,
Catholic priests used to take confessions for the
two so they could supply the surgeons with
experimental.
But anyway, but here was more than that.
He says, after a board meeting, they would
call a particular call girl to meet them
at a hotel and discuss what decisions they
should make.
That's how involved some of them were because
they were pretty, you know, think about someone
who is, if you want advice from someone
who's very worldly, has seen a lot of
things, most likely it would probably be an
older call girl or a madam, right?
In terms of human character and all that.
So anyway, I just wanted to throw that
in there.
I'm not gonna mention the madam's name, but
yeah, okay.
Fair enough, but you know, if you're dealing
with, it's all got to do with sourcing.
Look, these women spend time around guys who
can afford to spend $10,000 on them
in a night.
So that means there's a certain level to
the player that they've been exposed to constantly.
So their information is in that.
It's not even the money.
Well, but it does give an indicator as
to, it's not the guy who can afford
100 bucks and drive up on them.
That could be anybody.
This is- It is, but what's even
worse is I was reading something recently and
this case, it was a minor case, and
it was like 1.2 million in legal
fees.
And I'm like, oh my gosh, are you
that stupid to be attorneys a dime?
You know, it just shows you.
I mean, oh my gosh, the world is
so screwed up.
So, you know, and here's the thing.
Sometimes I'm like hopeful that there's an attorney
that knows something or, you know, in law
at all.
And I'm like, oh, this guy sounds okay.
And then within two minutes, they prove to
not know anything at all.
It's really disappointing.
So, okay, what else, what else?
The same with doctors, by the way.
Of course, speaking of prostitutes, that's my editorialism.
But anyway, this question.
So what's so special about the historical, they
call, the historical figure, they call G-E,
you know, J-E-S-U, you know
what I'm talking about, in Christianity?
Nothing in general.
Why was he put?
Okay, why was he put on a tree
and stoned?
What did he do to deserve such a
cruel or cool treatment, they say, but I
think they might have meant cool.
That's the myth.
That's the whole, it's not a myth, but
it's if you follow the, what people that,
whether, it doesn't matter when the books were
written, but were they in sequence?
Yes, and all that was prophesied in the
Old Testament.
There's no crucifixion, Roman crucifixion prophesied, but if
you read the book of Isaiah and the
Psalms and all that, it's very clearly a
stoning.
But, and remember, I did put in the
chat recently, the biblical text is cumulative, so
kindergarten to, let's say, 10th grade or something
would be the Old Testament, and the New
Testament's 10th grade to 12th grade, right?
Something like that, right, or college level.
So when you go to college math, do
they say, do they start all over at
first grade math, or is it cumulative, right?
So if you read the, that's why they
tell you, just read the, like, if you
took everyone that was five or six or
seven going to school and put them in
college level learning right away, you know, they
wouldn't know anything at all, no matter how
much, because they don't have the basis to
do anything with it, and that's exactly what's
going on.
But the New Testament is an absolute mess,
but if you understand the history and the
corruption, first of all, it's adopted by the
most corrupt institution in the world has ever
seen, the Vatican, right, which is an entire
culture.
It has nothing to do with religion.
It just happens to be also a religious
institution, because the reason they used religion is
to control, it's a control mechanism, right?
So just like science is now.
They adopted it, and they changed things in
there.
There were several, years ago when I was
looking into this, there were very well-recorded,
what do you call, inventories of what was
in the Vatican Library regarding the New Testament,
and very little of it is ever brought
out.
There's a lot more that they're not gonna
release, little leaks here and there, but they
do date the original text down before the
first century, you know, first century, so they
are contemporary, late contemporary, but I'll tell you
for sure, if you don't understand the law
and the culture in the Old Testament, you
will never understand anything in the New Testament
properly, and there is a proper way, let's
say a more proper way.
The most famous one is when the Christ,
they brought the woman that they were going
to stone, and he says basically, whoever is
without sin, throw the first stone, and a
typical moron would say, oh, that's because he's
compassionate.
No, he was actually going by the book,
because the stoning, they want to stone her
because that, why didn't they want to crucify
her, the Roman, or have her flogged by
the Romans?
Because they were applying Judean jurisprudence, right?
So, so it was the Christ.
What is the ordinance of an execution?
What is the ordinance of accusation as a
witness?
There was no witness, because in order to
be a witness, you have to, you can't
have any warrants or outstanding parking tickets.
You have to have a clean record yourself,
right?
And I'm not talking ever doing it, but
there has to be settled, right?
So they had unsettled things, not that they
never did anything.
No, they were unsettled.
They were still outstanding, right?
And only the witnesses commenced the execution.
This is all in the Old Testament, but
if you don't know the Old Testament, you
think it's compassionate.
And in order, if there is no witness
to a woman with adultery, they would sweep
the floor, the dust, and put it in
a cup and have her drink it, right?
If she loses loss of, loses the use
of her leg or legs, she's guilty.
This is like witchcraft, right?
Think about it, magic, right?
No witnesses.
We take the dust from the temple floor
or, you know, and we put it in
a cup with a liquid, and if she
drinks it and she's guilty, she falls to
the ground.
If she's not guilty, she walks away.
That's like an elixir-type magic, witchcraft-type
stuff.
Doesn't it sound like that, right?
So that's why he was writing on the
dust.
It's very specific on the dust on the
floor.
He was bringing up the ordinance, right?
This is the most, but we don't have
to go that far because you don't have
any witnesses, and there's no one here really
standing up to accuse.
He was just going by the book, and
I'm telling you, if you go back and
read it, and you'll see, like, he's very,
how about the woman pleading with him to
heal the daughter, and he's ignoring her, totally
ignoring her.
And they're like, why do you ignore her?
Because I didn't come for her, you know?
And then she basically says, don't you feed
the scraps to the dogs?
You know, she basically had her lower herself
to a dog, and then he says, go
home.
So this is already very tight.
It's very by the book.
It's very, very rational and logical if you
understand the Old Testament.
He was not someone that was very kind
to the people in public, by the way.
And anyway, I'm not gonna get into, here's
the thing.
I hate to sound like the only person
who's ever read the so-called Bible and
can explain it.
But apparently, it seems like that's so.
Well, there were many- Everyone else is
taking nitpicks with agendas.
I mean, Jesus, like they say, right?
Yeah, by the way, you just walked past
something that caused that electronic noise.
But anyway- Yeah, like, geez louise, yeah.
There were many replies to this in the
community.
I don't know if you want me to
skim through them and give you an idea
of what the replies were, but one person
said that they think it was actually the
punishment for blasphemy.
And that's what was prescribed based on a
certain version, blah, blah.
Okay, but why blasphemy, somebody asked.
And then they gave him, you know, look,
go read.
Okay, I was asking more about the real
story of this guy in the Old Testament,
not the biblical Christ.
Blasphemy is still very generic.
Okay- Well, that was an accusation, and
according to Judean law, again, because you cannot
say that you're God without proving it, right?
And that would be enough.
Yeah, it's very complex, because remember, they had
lost authority.
Pontius Pilate was the ruling authority.
He's the only one that did the ritual
of the red heifer, which is the washing
of the hands.
We have no account that any of the
Judean authorities washed their hands of anything, did
we?
It's very technical.
I mean, it's quite the discussion, but you
have to know the details and what these
things mean, right?
So, anyway, keep going.
Yeah, that you had spoken previous, Sonics, about
the J-E-S, you know, character being
a prototype, and, you know, that came back
from death, you know, show that as possible,
a divine being that man killed.
I thought maybe he was Yahweh reincarnated, but
maybe not.
Let me interject something.
We have control over the small things, but
not over the big things, right?
The big things in our lives, right?
Like Tesla coming up with the Tesla coil.
He probably had no choice in that.
That had to happen, right?
So this is also a proof from the
other side that they have control.
That's why the John C.
Lilly stuff, I like a lot, because the
ECCO, which is the Earth Coincidence Control Office,
they control the big long-term events.
We control the small ones, right?
So there was something about a Messiah being
stoned to death according to the law of
Moses.
That's why Moses made the seven-branch lampstand
in the likeness of an almond tree.
We know it was an almond tree.
There's so many references.
It's in the first chapter.
Jeremiah, Jacob, also in Genesis, on and on
and on.
Yeah, it's very technical and overlapping.
What do you call hyperlinks?
When you have a link and you go
to, imagine you click on a link and
it takes you to another page that's full
of links.
And then each time you click on one
link, it opens to another page with links
and some more information.
This is what the biblical text is like,
believe it or not.
Yeah, I've had that experience online, actually.
It becomes exhausting, to be honest.
Yeah, but every little detail has to be
minded.
I mean, what does it mean?
Now you're starting, this is what the rabbis
did, but you're never gonna get an honest
review of what they actually, you know, when
they write stuff back in the days, the
rabbis like, let's say, commentary on whatever, it
has to sit for 100 years before they
publish it.
They have to mull it over.
So, and you know how much editing is
done in that 100 years, right?
Oh, of course.
That's why even in contemporary historical writing, there
used to be a standard of wait 75
years before you actually release an account of
anything because, yeah, you need to actually go
over it.
And take the mic for a minute and
a half.
I'll be right back.
Yeah, sure.
Further replies in this, you know, went back
and forth.
I find it interesting when a conversation is
generated from one of these comments or questions.
And, you know, look, guys, if you wanna
continue on that, no problem, just let me
know and we'll see where else we have
to go.
But there was also a reference to the
Godspeak podcast, I guess, which was a previous
thing, a previous Sonic the Greek did regarding
this.
And I guess it was a podcast on
Islam.
I don't see a link to it in
the Patreon, you know, back and forth here.
But anyway, it's interesting that if you go
back over some of these Sonics, I've discovered
anyway, with ones that contain valuable information, one
listen is never enough.
You listen to it with a different focus
on a different day and you may come
away with different information.
It is possible.
And I think that happens also with any
text that has complexities to it, like the
Greek is talking about that.
You know, look, you click on a link,
you might end up with more links.
More links, yeah.
Well, the thing about Islam is they really
played the population when they noticed there was
no direct organized that could be massive, and
it is massive.
There are more Muslims in the Pacific, by
the way, you know, Rim, than there are
in the Middle East.
Most people think there are more, I think
it's a two to one in Asian countries.
There are more Muslims than there are in
the Middle East or what's Southwest Asia.
But what they wanted a organized enough, formalized
religion to counter Christianity, right?
That's what basically was.
So when you fall into, you got played,
you know, as a group.
But in itself, it's written on like a
third grade, let's stops at like second or
third grade level.
Like, you know, when you give up coloring
books, you finally get a pencil, but this
is like when we were growing up, right?
When you remember, you just had crayons and
now you have a pencil, but you never
get to a typewriter or whatever.
Oh, there was also the switch.
Yeah, there was also the switch from the,
when we were kids anyway, the big fat
pencil to now the skinny pencil.
Yeah, right, just, yeah, cause it was right.
So it was put together to offer an
opponent, an adversary to the Christian expansion, which
it didn't, you know, expand beyond.
Remember the, we had the Crusades, you know,
to keep everyone entertained and whatever reason it
gives.
But what's interesting about the Quran, you could
tell it's written in rabbinical fashion, first of
all, how do I know?
Well, you have to go to New York
and you need a lawyer, so make sure
you get a good Jewish lawyer, right?
If you wanna write a holy book, make
sure you get a rabbi to write it
for you, right?
Cause that's what they do.
But the positive thing, well, the other thing
is there's no discernment in the Quran, very
little.
Like in the biblical parlance or the narrative,
there's a lot of discernment.
When it prohibits something, it says, well, it's
things that are like this, right?
In the Quran, for example, with food, it
just says swine flesh and found dead, you
know, roadkill.
No swine flesh and no roadkill.
But in the biblical text, if it says
something, it gives you discernment, right?
So if it, right, if it has four
legs, it needs to chew the cud and
have a cloven hoof.
And it gives examples, right?
So if you go somewhere where, right, we'll
give the example of last time.
You've never seen the animal before, but it
chews the cud and has a cloven hoof.
It's permissible, you don't find that in the
Quran.
So, but the thing about the Quran, it's
extra, it's like tough love.
Actually, Muslim means to be submissive, right?
And it does hearken on Elohim, Al-Allah.
It's not Allah, it's Al-Allah, Al, right,
basically.
It's put together, in the beginning, it was
a very loose weave of all these groups
of people that venerated different things, right?
And they try to organize and formalize them.
And it's interesting, if you look at the
most fervent early on Muslim countries, most fundamental,
it's almost like they were forming a border
wall against Europe.
Because as you go east, it becomes more
loose to the point where if you get
to Afghanistan and Persia, they're not even Muslim
at all, and they should, they're not at
all.
That was forced on them by the CIA,
right?
With the Ayatollah, that fundamental stuff.
And then it picks up again in Malaysia,
places like that.
So it's very interesting, it's geopolitical stuff.
No religion, by the way, is a religion
that has legs to stand on, it's all
social control, period.
That's why it's real funny when you see
like a white guy or a white girl,
they're like, oh yeah, I converted to Buddhism.
I didn't like Christianity.
All they're mentioning is all the, it's like
saying, I used to be Democrat, now I'm
Republic.
What about the Constitution?
I don't know, man.
You know, there's no, people get lost in
the sauce.
There's plenty of people that will never seek
meat and content, they'll just seek a label.
It's just a label.
Because actually, if you read the Quran, in
essence, I'm paraphrasing, it tells you that God
didn't give his law in the Quran, he
gave it to Moses.
So you have to go look at what
Moses was given.
Wow, I'm paraphrasing, it's in several places.
So if you're actually diligent about it, you
would have to put down the Quran and
go read where the law is, right?
And that's what I did initially.
I just read the Bible and where the
law was, right?
So, and I had a firm standing on
understanding that before I went into prophecy and
all that other, what they were saying there
in the New Testament.
It was quite a few years where I
just was studying the law part, the legality
of the law part, you know.
So to open, but so yeah, so this
is really the basis of all these discussions
is it's very hard to discuss this with
someone that, you know, if you bring up
the Exodus, let's say out of Egypt, yeah,
I saw that movie with Charlton Heston, yeah,
right?
This is what most people are gonna, you
know, or yeah, I saw those planes go
into the buildings on 9-11.
I saw those planes, really, you were there?
No, I saw it on TV.
Oh my gosh, oh my gosh, you know?
So you can't, that's what I hear mostly.
Mostly, most people are like that.
They'll say, yeah, I saw the planes go
through buildings like they were there and they
weren't there at all.
So most people talk and talk.
By the way, I wouldn't say expressly, but
I could say expressly avoid talking on religion,
Bible stuff anymore and getting into all that
stuff because you, I mean, right?
The last thing, right, I want as an
example, I'm not saying the people that are
commenting, you know, if we talk about Exodus,
they saw the movie, right, or how many
Jesus movies have they done, right?
We talk about that.
They saw the movie, you know, or the
planes on 9-11.
I've had someone insist that they saw the
planes on 9-11 until I finally got
it out of them admitting that it was
on TV, right?
So I just don't talk about these things.
It's just why bother, right?
That's an old motto I used to have.
Why the fuck bother?
So there you go.
So look, here's just the last thing to
sort of cap this if you don't mind
because it's at the end of all that
with the conversation and the same, excuse me,
the same person who started it says, one
more thing, are these guys like Yahweh coming
back anytime soon?
I would love to see them getting bored
with humans a bit.
They're just scrolling on their phone and talking
about Trump.
Cats are more interesting.
I want to see some action.
Hope these guys come back while I'm still
here, this person said.
Yeah, you and me both.
But the thing is, action is something, okay,
good or bad, it's almost the same amount
of energy out.
But imagine you gotta go help somebody who's
in distress and you're gonna be there for
a while, quite a few hours, most of
the day.
You just don't wanna run out in your
sweatpants, right?
You gotta bring your keys, whatever else you're
gonna bring, some food, whatever, whatever.
Let's say you're gonna go to a happy
occasion and it's gonna be the whole day.
And still, you can't just run out.
You have to prepare and set aside.
You gotta sacrifice time that you would have
been doing other things.
So whether these guys, the Elohim and whoever
else is up there, decides to make a
big move, whether it's positive or negative, it's
gonna stop what you're doing.
It's a major interruption, disruption.
So look at it that way.
So I always look at it, like I
always said, I don't go to weddings or
funerals because both of them are a disruption
in my life and they're meaningless anyway to
most people.
So I don't go to either one.
So look at one.
One, go wedding is what, right?
You're gonna have a, right?
And the funeral is what?
It's gonna be like, ugh, right?
But I don't go to either one.
It doesn't matter if one is happy, one's
sad.
It doesn't matter because both of them are
an interruption and a disruption and basically bullshit
in the end.
So if you could see it coming, I
would avoid it.
Not because it's bullshit, because it's gonna be
bullshit for everyone else.
You're not gonna understand it.
No one's gonna know what's going on.
They'll probably end up killing each other, whether
it's good or bad.
But the thing is, that's why you don't
see it coming.
You don't see it coming.
And that's what I like about what Jason
Brashears is showing of archaics.
He's showing the middle of May, 2040, 2046,
but it's not like you're gonna flip a
switch.
Years before that, there's gonna be weird stuff
and it'll be confusing.
And if enough people understand what he's saying,
you'll have a bunch of people saying, if
he's saying what he's saying is true, let's
say the middle of May, 2040.