Sonic event number six here on Ocelli in the Greek rated Y. I'm obviously Ocelli
because that's the raspy voice that you're used to if you subscribed here.
And sorry for the delay recently, just going to address that, but we did have a
minor delay, uh, all my doing and it is all changed and fixed up and good to go now.
So anyway, we'll put that out of the way and talk about some of the stuff in the
chat room, which is available.
If you're not aware toward the bottom of the landing page, if you're a member and
also, uh, give me some feedback about the way it's set up now, hopefully it is easy
to navigate.
And if there is any suggestions, I'll be more than happy to take them because I'm
handling all that and try not to bother the Greek with it because he's got other
stuff to do like Greek speak and, uh, addressing directly.
Some of the stuff in the chat room is going to be interesting today because they're,
they're some of the most often brought up, um, points of query questions, points of
interest.
I would say every time somebody hears Greek speak Greek, um, anyway, how are you doing
today, by the way?
Oh, well, we're doing it right.
Number six.
And, uh, the delay was a sort of a delay, but not too bad.
Hopefully.
Uh, yeah.
Chat room, by the way, let everybody know that the chat is not, uh, inclusive with the
subs or the subscription.
Anyone can access it.
So if you're a sub and you see the chat room, you can send a link to someone else as
well.
Oh, isn't that, isn't that how it works?
Yeah, that is how it works.
But the thing is, uh, it's not something that's advertised anywhere.
So yeah, you'd have to actually share the direct link to go to just the chat room, uh,
which is available on chat tango alone, but they won't get the content without
subscribing.
Cause you gotta be able to enter that page, but sure.
But they'll get it.
They'll get a feeling of what it's like to be, uh, getting the Sonics as well somewhat.
Uh, but, but it is open.
It's, it's not, say it's not just inclusive it's or exclusive it's open.
So just wanted to put that out.
So if someone runs into it in the public and they're not a part of the Sonics, that's
fine.
And they can go in there anonymously as well.
You don't have to sign in.
I know a lot of people don't like to sign in and all that.
You don't have to, you can go in there anonymously.
Uh, and there are people who have, uh, participated anonymously.
I'm sure you've seen that.
Right.
Yeah.
And it is moderated to some degree and, uh, you know, so we don't get any like, you know,
porn or advertising and things like that.
So, uh, yeah.
Uh, basically the topics on there.
I think you, you might've, uh, looked at that and said that these are the things that
have been reoccurring from early days of Greek speak.
And by the way, regarding Greek speak, just before we get into the chat thing, I've been,
uh, ruminating on this whole project and trying to find a, a, a, a, let's say a format
to land on.
And the easiest thing for me to do since I'm kind of like this walking encyclopedia is to
delve in very deep on certain subjects and, uh, probably end up, uh, sending to you Chuck,
uh, hour long or two hour long solos that you put up, uh, that are, that'll be, uh, let's
say titled and time, time mark to a degree.
So when I'm getting into a subject like water or getting into a subject like food, I will
express, for example, okay, we're getting to 18 minutes.
Now we're going to talk about bread.
So it'll be easy to refer back to and things like that.
I, we spoke about this in the past and you may not get the intro or the outro, or you may
not hear Chuck, but it's still part of the project, uh, uh, only because it's easiest for
myself to do that.
I can sit down and do one hour, almost pedantic sounding recording on water that I think
will benefit whoever gets it or food or a money system or history or the gods and all
this other stuff.
So, because it'll get really rough on you if we start doing it, uh, whether it's a one
hour, two hour or truly in the Greek, it gets pretty rough, uh, to have, you know, to the
format that we're using right now.
You know what I mean?
Cause it's really hard to go back and forth if I'm getting into the groove, you know?
Oh, right.
Well, so you get on these runs and, uh, it's, it's very interesting.
In matter of fact, that used to happen in private, uh, Skype discussions where you had a
little group together and we used to have these discussions.
Uh, I, the one I remember best was, uh, it was about healing and wounds and things like
that, uh, which, uh, which I participated in with you, but, um, great, great stuff.
Anyways, that, Oh, you know, you brought up water and, uh, I did recently add the, uh,
the, the old one that we did a while ago about water, which the information is really
solid and interesting.
I added that to the rated Y playlist, um, in, in the absence of the, uh, uh, you know,
sonic recently just to, uh, provide something that they might've not heard unless they
were a subscriber at my site previously.
Uh, I figured that that was fair enough, uh, to let people know anything else you
think they'll add to the mix to give more value.
That is fine.
If you know anything, even if it's not with, um, what we're doing, if you find
something unusual enough, cause I think the folks here aren't unusual things, not
normal, right?
So yeah, uh, we'll, we'll continue the water.
We'll go a little deeper.
Uh, I could tell you right now, uh, myself and, um, recently regarding the water, uh,
there's a fellow making the rounds, Jonathan Buttes, uh, B U T T S, and he's pretty
popular and someone hooked him up with me.
So do you want to speak to him?
And I said, sure.
Well, we started off basically, um, having a short meet and greet, but ended up being a
three hour call going back and forth.
Uh, he is like the water guy right now out there.
And, uh, humbly saying, uh, by the end of the conversation, he said he learned a lot
by, uh, having that discussion.
He was very grateful, but what, what, what I could distill, no pun intended from the
conversation, both from his experience to more than two decades in mind of more than
two decades with working on water is, uh, I'm just going to give the short of it
because this is good for people to think about if they're interested in hearing the
water stuff.
There's a, the hydrogen economy, you know, using hydrogen and oxygen instead of
petrochemicals and petrofuels.
Right, right.
Well, one of the reasons that will never be mainstream and will never become popular
and will be suppressed is this.
When you're putting a regular fuel, whether it's propane or gasoline or whatever in
the engine, you're completely depleting the fuel on the exhaust pipe end, right?
You can't really take that exhaust and run it back through the system.
Well, if you have a hydrogen and oxygen generator, particularly the right kind,
let's say, which I will talk about how to make, uh, when you run that through the
engine, the engine with some modification will run.
Okay.
Well, what no one knows about or talks about, there are very few that know about
this.
What comes out of the exhaust pipe is about 99.9% of the same amount of hydrogen
and oxygen you put in on the front end.
Now, what they tell you popularly is, oh, you just burn hydrogen in your engine.
You get water as a by-product.
Well, yeah, you have some water vapor, but let me just say that again.
If you are using hydrogen and oxygen or what they call cracking water to power your
combustionable engine, you will have 99% of that coming out the exhaust pipe.
What do you do with it?
You see, this is something that you can go on every hydrogen, oxygen, HHO, water
powered engine, water powered car website.
No one mentions this for two reasons.
One is there.
The main reason is because they're ignorant of it because they just came across the
technology, decided to make a website and make a car run on it.
The second thing is that if you start making that notion popular, I think it'll
bring more of a shit storm down on you than you would readily expect.
So I just wanted to put that out there because what I just said is not as, is not
public at all and easily verifiable.
So let's go back to the chat.
Yeah, go ahead.
Well, yeah, let's do go.
Let's do go back to the chat because, again, I brought up the water and that'll be a
future installment of maybe a solo one, maybe one of these discussions.
We'll see.
Probably a solo one.
Yeah, but this way it'll be, it'll be deep and you can, you could do what you want
with it.
When we have our discussions, it's more, it's easier listening, I think.
Maybe, depends.
Anyway, it depends on who you ask, I bet.
But either way, let's, let's go to this because, again, right, what did we start
out with?
I think very first time that we got together, in fact, was, well, what time is
it?
Lawful timekeeping and all that.
Now, that was, again, discussed in the chat and they were talking about the moon
and they were talking about by observation, what is it you can see?
Things like this.
And this, this goes into, well, a whole lot more than just the, you know, what, what,
what is it we used to call it?
The wind-up toy or the digital representation thereof, right?
Or atomic clock or whatever, hourglass, water drops.
Either way, an accounting, right, an accounting of time.
But what, what is lawful timekeeping?
You, you've been over this a hundred times, okay, because I know you went over it
with me, you went over it in brief.
Not too long ago on a radio show you were on even, again and again, and, and here we
are still dealing with the, you know, the wind-up toy and, well, daylight savings
just happened, as a matter of fact, not, not everywhere, but, you know, in some
places, right?
So we all have to retranslate what time it is in different places.
So, yeah, let's just, let's just go to that and that will lead us into some
discussion of the gods, I guess.
Well, yeah, well, the easiest way, when you say lawful means it's universally
applicable.
So if you, if you're dealing with something, let's say, let's, let's go around
it to go back to it.
Okay.
Universally applicable.
Let's say you are interacting with something, a methodology or whatever, and
you have to buy it, right?
Or you have to get it from somewhere, someone, you know, or you have to be
licensed to have it.
Or is that universally applicable?
No.
Right.
So if it's a, if we're talking about a windup toy or a clock, you make your own,
you're probably going to buy the parts, buy the technology or buy a clock, right?
Or one of those flip calendars or a cell phone, whatever, whatever time keeping
method you have, you're probably going to have to go into some commercial venue to
get it, right?
So if that commercial, if you don't have access to that commercial venue, or if
they stop making it, is it still universally applicable?
No.
You see, so lawfulness also with other law forms is universally applicable.
Lawful timekeeping in its applicability, for such a thing, that's the right way to
say it, is strictly by using what is available to everyone from an observer's
point of view.
When you're using the atomic clock, the windup toy, the digital, whatever, it's
still observational.
Let's say you're in a lab and you're doing an experiment, you want to do time, you
still have to bring in the observation from that time piece, right?
So time is always observable.
So in this case, leaning on the premise that we're going to be using the
astronomical bodies for timekeeping, that takes out the commercial aspect, doesn't
it?
Well, entirely because it's accessible to anyone.
There's no license required.
You don't have to get any special permissions.
It is simply look up in the sky, right?
Yeah.
And if you're poor or rich, you have equal access, right?
So that's what I mean about universal applicability.
So in essence, this goes with every law form, by the way, and I've discussed it
before in depth, which we probably will again, what law is.
And actually, it goes back to the gods.
But OK, so the universal applicability of that timekeeping using the astronomical
bodies is the most viable also, because as time, because of its reliability, as
time changes, those bodies tend to keep their motions intact.
Right.
I gave an example years ago, you could still probably find them on eBay during
Stalinist Russia.
They had a 10 hour clock or a 20 hour clock.
They still have them on eBay, you know, and they had a 20 day calendar and all
these things. Right.
So that was for what?
That was for the USSR under Stalin, right?
But it didn't apply, you see, universally.
So the universal application of using the astronomical bodies, meaning the sun, the
moon and the stars, is what makes it lawful because it's accessible to everyone,
whether you're, let's just say everyone on the planet, let's say what we call the
planet. And that's what makes it reliable and that's what makes it lawful, period.
Right. The other problem that you have with that is the influx of culture, every
culture, every critic, every, as the ages change, they rely on a different aspect of
the moon. For example, the new moon now is the dark sliver that you view in the
West. Well, that really is not a reliable timepiece because can you measure that
down to the second or to the hour?
You really can't.
It's a generally it's over a three or four or six hour period.
It's very nebulous.
But if it's the full moon, which, by the way, if you look in the biblical text, you
could do a search. It does tell you the new moon is the full moon.
It is. There is a verse that actually has that in there.
But if you use the full moon, you could pretty much use your sundial.
Right, because the full moon will cast a very sharp shadow, you see, so that in an
essence, you know, if most people say new moon, they think it's the dark moon.
So these these these short little steps go into what it means to be, you know, having
a standard. Right.
The other standard would be a starts at solar noon.
Now, without going into history, fast forward into current academia.
When you take, let's say, astronomy or astrophysics as a curriculum, you will have
for about 15 minutes in every curriculum, even community colleges for about 15 minutes
or one chapter in the textbook.
It will tell you that the full moon, I mean, sorry, at solar noon is when the day
starts. The day starts at solar noon for astronomical and scientific purposes.
It's even in the college books, not midnight, because that's like I said, the
culture wants you to have midnight.
All right. So when you look at the language, right, when people fast for a day, they
break their fast at the end of the day.
So when do you have break fast?
Right. At the end of the day, which is the morning in the Bible, you have it was
evening. It was morning.
It was the first day.
Well, when does OK, so if the day starts, it goes from evening to morning.
That's the end of the day.
So the end of morning is the end of the day.
Right. And the cycle repeats evening to morning again.
Well, when does morning end at noon?
At noon. You see this with people today with the clock.
You ever notice like you get on a conversation and they'll say good morning, but it's
twelve oh one and they'll notice it and they'll say, oh, I'm sorry.
Good afternoon. Right.
I've heard this my whole life.
Right. You know, it's twelve oh three.
Oh, I'm sorry. It's good afternoon.
OK, so going by the clock now, the wind up to twelve noon by the clock could be off by
forty five minutes to an hour and a half, depending on the season, because it's close
enough. So you have the solar noon is when the day starts.
Also, if you remember the old banking convention, if you grew up in the 60s or 70s, by
the 80s, they stopped this.
If you deposited a check after noon on the clock, they counted it as the next day.
I don't know if you guys remember that.
Oh, I do. Anybody here old enough?
I do. Yeah, because they that was the banking convention, because the banking, believe it
or not, goes back to the system of banking that's being used today, which we'll
probably discuss a little bit today as well, is is very ancient.
Right. And it doesn't go back to a lot of the people always try to leave, like the
Jordan Maxwell's and all the David Ikes and all these other guys always tell you it's a
Babylonian system.
It's not it's not a Babylonian system at all.
Some of the culture is borrowed from Babylon.
It's an Egyptian system.
But just to not lean so negatively on those guys that I just mentioned, Babylon and
Egypt were sister cities, just like New York and London are very close.
Right. So if something happens in New York regarding culture, fashion or finance, it's
going to affect London.
Right. And, you know, like you have in the fashion industry, the triad of Paris, London,
New York. So in fashion, something affects Paris.
It's going to get those other two cities as well.
So that's the relationship with Babylon.
But it is not a Babylonian based system.
And I think I've gotten into that in the past.
If there's interest on it, I could show how with more interest go into depth.
It will require me for me to do a bunch of research to bring references out.
But essentially, for lawful timekeeping, understanding the crux of the matter is this.
The full moon determines the month and the solar noon determines the day.
And this is basically for record keeping.
This is how you keep your records, basically, in terms of lawful timekeeping.
But if you live this way, you will find yourself in more harmony versus disharmony that
the collective that only knows midnight and whatever.
Actually, they have no reckoning for the month.
What's interesting is you see in just popular culture browser news pages, full moon
tonight, right? Yes.
The most people relate to that would be like, oh, it's so beautiful or some crazy
things might happen, man, because people act weird during the full moon.
That's the extent of it.
They have no idea what that really means in terms of any other aspect.
Right. So they're completely disconnected from the monthly cycle.
There's, of course, there's the monthly cycle that women have or the female of our
species, let's say, and other species.
But that's it. They're completely disconnected.
They're also completely the collectives completely disconnected from solar noon being
the beginning of the day where if they well, what they're connected to is midnight.
But if they were connected to solar noon as being the beginning of the day, they would
have a radical sense of change in there and reharmonizing, you see, completely.
I mean, once you acknowledge to yourself personally that the day starts at solar noon
and you admit it to yourself and you acknowledge it, you will notice a different
focus, a subtle change within your life that will put you in harmony with everything
else that follows that, which is what what else follows this lawful timekeeping?
Well, the earth, the weather, the whales, the bugs, the dogs, the cats.
Right. Well, I have noticed that people that are most interested in cultivating plants,
if they take this into their minds, it's very helpful, actually.
Because farming is you cannot separate any good almanac as a lunar cycle for planting.
Right. That's what I was going to bring up.
Exactly. And there's a reason for that.
And it doesn't make sense if you look at the Pope's work schedule, because there is no
ending or beginning that makes any sort of sense according to the way they have the
months laid out there.
Because look at where your moons lay, you know, even the calendars that show you where
the moon begins, ends, is at a halfway point, all of that, there is no logical through
line there. They have a what you'll notice is that for about two or three years, they
have a pretty close run where the full moon comes up the first few days of their
month. Right.
Well, we're at that point right now.
Again, yeah, you'll notice there's a run on that.
And by the way, the intercalation I just wanted to bring up where you have a 13th
moon, that's intercalation.
That's that's not really making things fit.
That's just running the cycles as they are, meaning you'll have a longer monthly
cycle within a year, which regarding the months you will have, you will have 400 days
in about 390 days in a year from the what where you have the lunar division.
But the year based on, let's say, what they talk about the sun going around the sky and
coming back to where it was is still around 360, 365.
And this is this gets complicated.
But keeping intercalation keeps things very neat, meaning when do you have a 13th moon?
Right. And maybe that's that's actually maybe something I should get into on a short,
fast sonic and to give the emotion of the moon being independent.
So I always balk at when people are, well, they were on a lunar calendar.
There's no really such thing as a lunar only calendar.
Right. Because then when does your day start?
You still rely on the sun.
But the point of the intercalation of having a 13th moon is not even to make things fit
neatly. It's just to respect how that cycle has its own cycle within a cycle.
It's kind of like a planetary gear.
When you open a watch, the back of a watch, you see all these gears intermeshing.
Right. And they're all different sizes.
Right. Well, with the moon having an intercalation where you have a 13th month, which
was last year, by the way, is like imagine the gears not being circular, but being
elliptical. That's the easiest way to imagine it.
Right. So instead of having circular gears on the back of a watch, some of them are
elliptical or the one that's lunar is it has an elliptical shape where the sun tends to
be more circular. Now, there's different ways to explain this and there's different
there's no why on that, but it just happens to be that way.
And it works out fine.
You know, once you understand it, I have typically found that there's three to four
minimum of actually three, most likely four 13 month years every 10 years or every nine
years, I should say. So about just about a third of them.
Right. So that's pretty much on the lawful timekeeping.
And basically it's not something you can fully grasp and then use it.
It's one of those things that it's kind of like a bicycle, you know, you have to the
more you ride it, the better you.
Right. So just start acknowledging when these things are happening and then it'll
start to click and make sense to you because it's more than just being cognitive,
you know. Right. So you can I could lecture on this for hours to someone who is not
aware of it. And even though they think they got it, let's say they scored really well
on a quiz. Right. And they've never observed it or used it before.
They'll be they'll be befuddled, though they will still won't get it right because it
takes the experience. So it takes anywhere between one to three years to kind of get
it. It's one of those things like a bicycle.
If you've never ridden a bicycle before, do you say, well, I'll just save it for that
day. I'll I'll get on it on next Thursday.
I've never ridden one before.
And I think by the end of the day, I'll be fine.
No, it doesn't work that way.
Right. You have to practice.
Yeah, well, people call it practice, but it's just the more you develop, you refine
your your actions become, you know, you're not thinking about them anymore.
They're just actions you take.
And that's kind of the way it goes.
Right. I mean, some people call that muscle memory or whatever, where it's just you're so
used to doing something, it becomes, you know, secondary nature like it's.
Yeah, it's recognition.
Cognition means to know, let's say.
And when you say recognize, it's literally saying recognition means you're re-knowing.
So when someone says to you, do you recognize this?
And it's familiar. What you're doing is comparing it.
It's just like imagine an AI camera looking at an object and comparing it to another
reference of that object.
Right. That's what's really happening.
So when someone asks you, do you recognize this?
What you're really doing is taking whatever input you have, visual, audio, whatever
touch, and comparing it to your previous knowledge of what you think the subject matter
is. Right. And it's never exactly the same.
And you just keep adding to your knowledge base.
That's why that's where that's where recognition comes from.
It's never exactly the same.
So if you're reading Braille, for example, you're not going to be using your sight.
It'll be purely touch.
So recognition is not only visual, it's audible, it's touch, smell, taste.
So whenever we sense something, it adds to our previous knowledge of that thing.
Once we know what the subject matter is and where we should access it.
So that's how the time keeping works for every month and every day that you start
acknowledging that you're seeking to use the astronomical bodies.
You will be learning more and more every day and every month.
I've never seen. And here's the here's the other thing I did.
No one held me by the hand and said, Greek, this is lawful timekeeping.
Believe it or not. So in the beginning, when I first was searching this,
I thought I was inventing stuff.
Right. Because I can't be midnight.
You can't you know, it's got to be sundown.
Well, it can't be sundown because you can't. Right.
So when I can't be the sliver, the dark moon, it's got to be the full.
I'm like, what? I couldn't find any information on this at all.
Anywhere. Just little pieces here and there.
So I say, what am I doing here?
Am I inventing some kind of a system where the day starts at noon and the full moon is
that am I like being inventive?
So I said, let me just go out there and see how this works and now start probing
little pieces of history and see how it fits.
And believe it or not, everything fit together really well.
So that's the sad thing I've always told people, go try to find lawful timekeeping.
You're never going to find anywhere that the day starts at noon.
The full moon is the new moon and how to reckon everything, you know.
By the way, just an interjection on lawful timekeeping.
Look up on references and they tell you the lunar month is like twenty eight point nine
four or twenty nine point three days.
Yeah. OK, it's never.
Well, if that's because they do the day starting at midnight.
But if you start the day at solar noon, it's exactly 30 days, 30 or 31 days
in the summertime, in the summer months.
Hmm. Isn't that interesting how just acknowledging solar noon as being the beginning
of the day, you end up having a perfect 30 day lunar count.
Is that amazing? So it's very interesting that.
Yeah. I mean, especially because it seems like, well, that's fairly close to what the
Pope's work schedule looks like.
But it's what's 12 hours.
Yeah. About midnight to solar noon.
Right. It's 12 hours front or back, but it's still 12 hours off, which is 50 percent of
the day. And they're already telling you it's twenty eight point nine or twenty nine
point one. When you add 50, right, it ends up being 30 with that math just
mathematically. So what were you going to say about the Pope's work schedule?
Well, it almost seems like somebody took a snapshot of one proper year and decided to
keep using it, you know, is what it seems like.
Well, you mean the current one from the Popple Bull 1580 something, but they started
around five the year 500 A.D.
They had it pretty much it took them.
They couldn't get this on everyone until the sixteen hundred, seventeen hundreds,
really. It's fairly, in other words, the calendar that everyone uses everywhere in the
world right now hasn't been used the way it is for more than 150 years.
It's very recent. To prove this, you could look up on a browser.
You notice I don't say Google this.
Well, I hear a lot of people say, why don't you Google this?
But anyway, it's still going to go through Google.
But good research.
Just do a quick browser. Why does George Washington have two birthdays?
And he does, because at that point they they decided to eliminate a week.
So he has two birthdays, the one that was inscribed when in real time when he was born.
And then when they changed the calendar in 51, they 1751 again, they went and changed
what the day he was born retrospectively.
So in other words, we don't really other than myself and maybe someone else I'd never
heard of is talking about the importance of lawful timekeeping and all this.
But if we went back in history, 150 or 200 years, it was a mess.
It wasn't standard like it is today.
Well, at least it's standardized.
Right. At least it is.
By the way, even if you go back and read, I was big on I was like, I'm going to prove
the American Revolution never happened, as we're told.
Right. Kind of like I'm going to prove the Bay of Tompkins or whatever was a false
flag. Right. Kind of thing.
And it was it didn't really happen the way we were told.
But and at that time, I was a little confused because you would have
something dated as June on the top.
But the paragraph in the opening of the article would start reading in this fourth
month of the year or whatever.
But it's June. Yeah, right.
You see. Right. Which, according to the Pope's work, schedules the sixth month.
Now it is. But then they would consider June to be the fourth month.
So this is how I put it all together in terms of this.
These things were known and changed.
You see, it's very subtle.
Here's the there's something that I if I were to pretty much nail down what we're
doing with Greek speak always is from the beginning, even before I started even
speaking publicly on the Internet.
I used to speak at venues here in Tucson in the early 2000s.
Peak perception, can you keep your your perception at a peak so when you hear
something or see something, an idea, see any otherwise will entertain any idea.
Right. It doesn't mean you have to accept it.
I can. If you told me, you know, this is the moon is made of cheese.
I'll listen. You know, you can't just say it's made of cheese and stop.
You have to back it up somehow.
Right. Right. I'll listen.
It doesn't mean I have to accept it.
Right. So you keep your perception peak.
And then the other thing is you have to realize, just like I said earlier, I
thought I invented this thing with lawful timekeeping because I couldn't do one
stop shopping and find out that the day started at solar noon and the full moon
was the first day of the month.
Nowhere. So when I started piecing it together, well, it can't be this and it
must be that I thought it was only one on the planet.
And actually, I am that can put it in one spot like that.
Right. So it kind of made me realize that I have to get away from that and go
back out there and see, do we have enough hints we could piece together that the
full moon is the first day of the month and the day starts at solar noon?
And the answer to that is hell, yeah, because throughout history and even today
in academia, as I said, you will find that.
That concept, again, that the day starts, the month starts with the full moon and
the day starts at solar noon is is firmly implanted, but it's very, very, very
subtle.
OK, well, what do you mean by it's very, very subtle, though?
Oh, you won't find it all in one place.
Yeah, OK, so it's scattered about, but, you know, so it's not all in one.
Like you said, look, you're not going to find one book, let's say, that's going to
explain this to you.
Yeah. And you don't even need a book.
You can do it in a simple phrase.
All right. Fair enough.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's just astounding.
But then again, you can apply to any law form, you know, they have laws of physics,
right? Right.
So but they and they attribute it to Isaac Newton.
All right. Well, there's an entire category that's called non-Newtonian physics
where liquids don't behave the way right.
Objects don't in motion don't behave the way that Newton said they should.
Right. They don't fit the standard formulas and all that.
And what's happening as time goes by, the non-Newtonian aspect of our reality
is starting to overcome the Newtonian aspect.
Right. Right.
So which one is real?
You know, the subtle again, back to the subtleness of it.
If you're follow if you're a part of the collective and you're doing the Pope's
work schedule on the clock, you know, the day starts at midnight, you're going to
be disharmonious and you're going to be seeking you're always going to feel like
superficially may not be admitted by those in the collective, but they're always
going to feel an emptiness, like something's missing, something's not quite
right. And you hear this all the time, by the way, from the collective.
Right. And one of the main things of that is that you're disoriented
because orientation is an orienteering and orientation has to do with
maps and how to navigate.
And one of the things about navigation is speed and time and where you are in time.
So feel sorry for them or not.
The collective will never, ever be in harmony for one of the reasons
simply is because they will never, ever encounter or contemplate or partake in
lawful timekeeping.
I know it's kind of a big statement to make, but I assure you part of the whole
that they sense in their spirit and their mind and their existence is lawful
timekeeping because they're totally you know, their lives run on time.
Right. Well, yeah, essentially everything you do begins with what time do you have
to do it? When do you when does something happen?
What is the time that you have to depart or to go to, you know, work or whatever it
is, everything is based on time.
So without it, let's just say you wanted to abandon timekeeping altogether.
You can't and function with others.
Right. I mean, just but the thing is, the time system that they're using is
disharmonious with the physical environment, the natural environment.
Right. And when you say natural environment, it's, you know, living objects and
nonliving objects. Right.
So they're completely effed.
We could we could. This is not a child's program.
Right. Not at all. They're fucked.
Yeah. Basically, just from that aspect alone.
Well, there's an entire reason you can keep going down the line.
Speaking of something going down the line, just to diverge a little bit.
We were talking about months and days and all that.
This past Thursday on which it's twenty twenty three March.
Right.
Mm hmm.
Nineteen thirty three March Thursday was also the ninth.
This year was the ninth on a Thursday.
And what I've been doing to be going around, I said, you guys ever heard of the
Fourth of July's people out for about a week now?
And my favorite answer when I ask someone, have you ever heard of the Fourth of
July? They're like, yeah, I heard of it.
It's the day that comes after July 3rd, meaning like they don't give a shit.
Which I totally agree with.
Right. Yeah.
But I said, have you ever heard of March the 9th, 1933?
You're like, no.
Well, that's when this country, this country, meaning I'm in the U.S.
of A right now in Arizona state.
You notice I didn't say state of Arizona.
It's not the same thing.
And that's when this country pretty much got a
what do you call when you shoot someone right between the eyes or right in the
head with a large caliber gun?
Dead. Pretty much.
If you will. The death shot.
OK. Death shot.
Yeah. Now, let me let me mention something here.
If you put in March the 9th, 1933 and you're in the U.S.,
they're not hiding this, by the way.
Google will start from the top 10 pages down just talking about what's called the
EBA Emergency Banking Act.
And they want it. They want you to read it.
It's only two and a half paragraphs.
All right. So if you understand legalese, you could realize how screwed you are,
especially when they reference the statute of 1917.
What's that?
Well, you go back and read that. That's pretty long.
But I'll give you a short thing on it.
That's when they did trading with the Enemies Act.
Well, when you're at war, you can't trade with the countries we're at war with.
But in March the 9th, 1933, they went and amended that.
And guess what they did?
They included U.S. citizens in the trading with the Enemy Act.
That now U.S. citizens are enemies of the United States.
Why would they do that?
Because if the people ever found out what they did on March the 9th, 1933, it would
be like the end of a Frankenstein movie.
And right. You know, he shows up.
People showed up with pitchforks, right.
And torches, right. Going after the castle.
Okay. So how did they hide it from the people?
By publishing it.
It doesn't make any sense what I just said, but I assure you that's what they did.
No, it makes perfect sense.
It reminds me of what Alan Dulles said about the Warren Commission volumes.
Of course, publish it. That'll make sure that no one reads it.
Exactly. You know, and that was Alan Dulles, who, if you don't know who he was, you
know, go ahead and look that one up somewhere.
You know, I'm not going to use the Google phrase either.
Yeah. And what's more important about Dulles that I believe it's not just him alone.
He was part of the Dulles brothers, wasn't he?
Yes, he was. Right. John Foster and Alan.
Yes. Yeah. It wasn't just one.
Yeah. So it was twice as bad.
Right. Mm hmm.
Yeah.
Very interesting subject there.
But OK, it's fascinating to me because I've heard others
say that indeed, if you are partaking in certain
things in society, you are literally an enemy of the state.
And yeah, it was declared that way.
Now, let me just say what I've heard other people say.
I'm not saying that it's accurate.
I'm just saying that it reminds me of what they were saying.
They never explained it, though.
Yeah. Yeah, that's we can't we can't.
It's very simple why I say sort of I can I can give you a very strong defense for it.
Let's replace the the word state with, I don't know, ice cream shop.
OK, ice cream. OK.
Enemies of the ice cream shop.
OK. Of the ice cream shop. OK.
So the ice cream shop, like the state's been there, it's been a fixture in society
for a long time. People regarded in favor.
They've some venerated, some don't like it, whatever.
It's been in town for a long time.
Well, they get into some shady business dealings to the point where they have to go
bankrupt. But the and now when they do declare bankruptcy with some shady business
deals with some private bankers, the private bankers and then have a meeting and say,
OK, we're bankrupt. All right.
All right. We're just going to say, uncle, do what you want.
And they say, well, you know what?
Why shut you down and tear down the business?
You're part of society.
You're a fixture here.
Everybody. People don't really know what's going on.
You know, why do we want to alarm the community and shut down the ice cream shop?
Why don't we keep it running?
But instead of just declaring tell the people were shut down for a few days for
bankruptcy, we're going to stay open under what's called a receivership, because
when there's a bankruptcy, you liquidate everything to pay the creditors who you owe
money to or the creditors can opt to what's called a receivership.
Keep the business going.
The current owners or principals or administrators are replaced with our people.
Everything that comes in comes to us.
So and whatever we want to give to those who run the shop, we give and we stay in
place. That's the state.
It doesn't exist. It's in receivership to the private banks.
And this has been very clear in March.
The ninth took till 1934, 1938.
With the precedent of Tompkins versus Erie Railroad, they changed the entire
judicial system to law of contract.
So it really took till after the World War II to be in the situation that you're in
right now. Now, let's go back to what I was saying.
By the way, you know, I haven't really hammered on the receivership for a long
time, but was that easy to see?
Yeah, I was thinking back to the the pizza shops, actually, that, yeah, well, you
and I are from a similar area in the country.
You remember the pizza shops that got taken down, right?
The whole pizza connection thing.
They almost all of them went into receivership afterwards where the pizza shop
shut down for a couple of days, just like you described with the, you know, the ice
cream shop. And they went into bankruptcy and they were all taken out because they
were involved in this, you know, heroin trafficking and whatnot.
And then they reopened and it was under new management.
Right. The name was a little different, but pretty close to the same.
The pizza, you know, the name remained the same.
Right. Some of the employees even remained the same.
Sure. The location, all of it.
They didn't change much, but there was new people running it.
And they were now not, you know, the previous owners were no longer the owners.
They took them away or whatever.
And now it was different people doing the business.
It didn't change. Yeah.
Yeah. It's called receivership.
It's very common to talk about bankruptcy.
People have heard of it. Very few people know much about it, but no one talks about
receivership. And that's the most common outcome for most large bankruptcies.
We're not talking about corporations that are just on paper, you know, that get
dissolved or banks and things like that.
But here's the important part, is that what the analogy that I gave is pretty close
to any as accurate as any as anyone would study this technically legal, the legal and
lawful aspect of bankruptcy to receivership.
I give that analogy. It resembles as close as possible to what is done.
The other thing is the way because it was public, that means it's illicit.
In other words, because all everything that I said and this has happened to every
country, by the way, and some form or another in Canada, it was done before the US.
It was done in England before World War One.
Yada, yada, yada, yada.
You go down the line and you'll find every country has the same situation.
Right. Since the eighteen hundreds till nineteen fifties with a lot of the countries
in Asia. OK, same thing.
But because it's so public and no one seems to care or know and it's so insidious at
the same time, you can consider all the states and governments to be running as an
illicit operation.
No, no, no, much worse than what you find on the dark web, you know, like hit men for
hire, prostitution, child trafficking, drug trafficking, all this stuff that you find
in the underworld is being done right in front of your faces out in the open and no
one seems to care. You see what I mean?
So it's an illicit operation.
Now, when you're running an illicit operation known as the modern state or all those
other things I mentioned, you find on the dark web, let's say you're running an
illicit operation out of a warehouse or a house or something.
The people that are part of the organization that are dealing with the public or
interacting with the public, the less they know about the inner goings of the inner of
the inner doings of the inner organization, the better.
Right. Because if the people that you have working for you, let's say, know a lot
about what's going on, it's going to slip when they interact with the public.
So it's best for them not to know the less they know, the better.
Where am I going with this?
When you go speak to a politician, any politician, they don't know any of this that
I just mentioned, the bankruptcy, the receivership.
They might have heard some, but they don't know anything about it.
Right. You speak to an attorney, you don't know anything about this kind of stuff or
law. Right.
You see. So this is done deliberately.
So one of the failures that you have in society is the people that people look up to
as professionals know nothing about what they're supposed to be knowing about, because
if they did, it would they call it a Freudian slip.
It would trickle out into the public and then you might have a movement on your hands.
Right. So but it's interesting.
I've challenged many people over the years who have family members, let's say, who are
doctors and lawyers.
I said, go ask him this.
He's a doctor. And it's by the way, ask him this question.
And you know what? I'll tell you what answer he's going to give you before you ask him.
So they go, guy's dad or whoever is a doctor goes ask him a couple of questions from
Greek speak. And the guy responds back exactly the way I said he would, as if they're not
even as if there's a pre-programmed life form.
So the same with lawyers and all this other stuff.
It's very easy to to see what's going on and how ridiculous it is from that aspect.
OK, so I just wanted to bring that up because, you know, one thing we might in the
future talk more about current events, because people here come here for Greek speak,
which, of course, is why you should be coming here.
But I know that you're also aware of what's being put out in the media and alternative
media, which is the same, by the way, because alternative media looks at the mainstream,
what they're saying, and they try to dissect it and tell you what's really going on.
And they're really not because they're just either they do that or they attempt to just be
the contrarian to which is, you know, just as pointless because, you know, well, I'm just
going to reject everything that they said because no, no sort of, you know, analytical
approach to it. Just well, we'll just take the opposite stance.
Well, that's that's important that you said that analytical, very important, because that
analysis is part of rational dialogue, rational, you know, interaction and logic, right?
Being rational with someone, but they're not.
And recently I came across a few things that I might be speaking on in public on a venue.
I'm not sure which one it is.
I'm not sure if it's set in stone.
If it was, I'd say who it was.
But it's a pretty popular Internet platform and most likely the talk will be about the
mass media. And my point of view will be very different.
You've heard of like all these organizations that are challenging the mass media like
Veritas or Loose Change back in the day with 9-11 and all this other stuff.
OK, the reason they're failing or seem contraire and are easy to be laughed at by the
collective. What do these organizations do?
They present the themselves against the mass media using rational logic, evidence, right?
Proper timeline.
Right. And they're being ignored.
The problem with the reason why they're being ignored is because they think by doing
that they will get headway because their opponent, meaning the mass media, is rational
and logic. They're not.
So the way you deal with the mass media and their followers is the same way that you
would deal with people who are insane.
So what I did before we started, I thought about this because I've been thinking about
it for a few days. I went online and I did a quick browser search.
What do you do with someone who is crazy or how do you treat crazy people?
And there's a whole bunch of articles by psychologists and psychiatrists.
Right. And you could I don't have to go over it.
You can imagine what it is.
Don't deal with them.
Don't tell them you understand.
Don't comply.
Keep them safe. Right.
Keep them contained. General stuff like that.
Right. That's how you deal with the mass media.
They're crazy. The way you would deal with them because they've already shown that they
cannot deal with rationale and logic and evidence and real timeline.
And they can't do.
So that's crazy people.
So the way you deal with mass media and their followers is no different than the crazy
bag lady walking down the street yelling at the telephone pole.
Exactly the same.
So once the quote unquote people in the alternative media notice this, this is one way
to deal with it. I think it's a major be a major milestone if they start doing this is
to not let's say something happens.
They come up with their own website or whatever venue they have and they start saying,
look at this thing happened in the news.
What about they didn't talk about this, this, this, this and that.
Yeah. You're presenting rational logic, evidence and a real timeline, all this to someone
who's insane. These people are crazy.
What are you doing? You need to be calling the paddy, you know, a wagon.
The guys in white uniform need to put them in a straight jacket in a padded room so they
don't hurt themselves. Right.
That's how you deal with the media.
So initially, the only way to deal with the mass media at this point, because they cannot
deal with rationale and logic is, first of all, extreme sarcasm.
Right. Avoidance and containment.
Now, it would be very difficult to physically remove them from the planet because most of
they've also captured the allegiance of most of the population.
But the most rational way to deal with the irrational is find out what protocols are in
place on how to deal with crazy people or insane people in that essence.
What do you think of that? I think that's fascinating.
And not in other words, don't present evidence, don't present a rational argument.
It's way past that point.
Now it's lock them up, you know, keep them keep them away from the children.
Right. Imagine if you've ever been around before where a quote unquote crazy person goes
buck wild and starts running around.
We're not talking about the guy on the Staten Island ferry with a sword, but let's say a
guy starts picking up garbage cans and throwing poop at people.
Right. Yep. I've seen that.
What do you do? First of all, you stay clear of his range.
Yep. Right. Try to get some help.
And how are we going to put an end to this?
Right. Not present to him a report on that.
You know how this is bad for you.
That's way past that point.
Right. Right now, somebody has to come and contain him.
Somebody who is equipped to do so.
But they're not. Yeah. Well, we've talked about that to the mop up crew.
Which leads us to the gods, doesn't it?
Well, it definitely does. Real quick before you move on to there, though, I was just
thinking that in in media recently, there is this instance of a bank failure.
And I don't know if if you paid any attention to it at all.
Five minutes was all I needed.
Yeah. Well, I was just curious about it because I was thinking to myself, it sounds
like you're describing what is actually unfolding there, regardless of what they're
explaining about it. It appears to me as though you're describing something that's
happening there with this bank, which is funny because, you know, on the one hand, the
perception is it's a small bank, which is not of any consequence.
And yet they're reporting it like worldwide.
Well, yes. Silicon Valley Bank.
Right. OK.
Do you know what hidden messages are?
And you know what? What is it called when they tell you something?
A preface is something that's going to come in the future.
Foreshadow. Right.
OK. But it's none of that.
It is and it isn't.
What they're trying to tell you in so many ways is this.
One, there is no money since 1933.
It's been the system has been done away with.
That's why, for example, you pull out a bank note.
It doesn't say Central Bank.
It says Federal Reserve System.
Doesn't say bank anywhere on the bank notes anywhere.
It's a system. You're way past banking.
There are no banks, I assure you.
Your bank is all all banking that's been done for the past 90 years has been done on
a temporary emergency fashion.
OK. I don't know how else to say that.
In a temporary emergency fashion would be like there's a disaster and the Red Cross
shows up and they put out some with their vans and they're folding tables and
they're rinsing off wounds and putting bandages on people.
Right. That's it. It's a temporary whatever, you know, like a I don't know, how would
you like you go to a set of a restaurant?
It's just somebody setting up a booth with a skillet out in the park and charging two
dollars for rice and beans.
It's a temporary kitchen, right?
It's a temporary situation.
None of those banks are, as a matter of fact, they're not even listed as banks, only
in name only. You could call anything a bank, like, for example, Federal Express.
Are they part of the federal government?
No, no. Can can you open federal hardware store?
I believe I can. Yeah, I can just call it that.
Yeah. Yeah. Is any people are going to discredit someone thinks part of the federal
government put a picture of George Washington?
Well, they got you fooled. OK.
Banks are not banks.
They're not corporations.
And they're not trusts.
What are they? It's very clear.
It's right on there. The main bank that's registered is an N.A., N dot A dot, which is
a national association, which a national association is.
Let me give you some other examples of national associations.
What category?
Boy Scouts, Girl Scouts, Sierra Club are national associations.
You want to think of a few more.
There is just look up what is a national association and give me a list of them.
I'll repeat it. Sierra Club.
Boy Scouts, Girl Scouts.
Now, why are they listed?
In the same category as the Boy Scouts, the Girl Scouts and Sierra Club, Wells Fargo City
Corp, all these banks, why are they listed like that?
You see what I'm I mean, I'm not going to give the why on that.
I know it's rated Y, but it's ridiculous.
Right now, you have other corporations, you have banks that have corporations using that
name for other purposes.
So you don't have any banks.
What they are is credit.
OK, here, you know, I think I've given the example if I minus a thousand dollars in my
checking account, can I write you a check for ten dollars?
No. If you gave me if someone gave me a thousand dollars now, remember, I was a minus a
thousand dollars. Can I still write a check for ten dollars?
The answer is no. No.
Let's say there's no fees.
Let's say. OK.
All right. So why is it that every government is able to pay government employees and send
out bonus checks or relief checks?
When if you go to their website, their treasury, they're all in trillions or hundreds of
billions in the minus. How can they do that?
How can they write your check for any of that?
Why am I the only one bringing up this simple third grader point or fourth?
What was it in the fourth or fifth grade in math class?
One day the teacher gets up.
I think you're a fifth or sixth grade.
And she says, this is how you write checks, boys and girls.
Do you remember that? Yeah, actually, I think it was fifth grade.
Yeah. Yeah, that's it.
And nobody. OK, so you've been exposed to this since 10, 11 years old.
And how come no one is bringing this point up about economics here?
So where are they getting the money?
They're taking it from your signature when you go to a bank and say, do you give loans?
OK, if I'm pre-approved for a ten thousand dollar boat loan, will you show me what
account you get the money to give me the ten thousand?
No, they can't. None of them.
Right. I don't know if you've ever been to what's called a mortgage signing or a
promissory note signing.
Yeah. Yeah. You've been OK.
You've noticed that they come when the victim is ready to sign three, four of these
bankers are usually to come up and they cover all they cover all the paperwork with
blank paper except for where you're supposed to sign.
Yeah. Have you seen that?
And they're all like they're getting this dopamine rush.
OK, right. OK, give me an example.
And I want to dwell on this long, make this too long.
But I knew a guy who had a petrochemical company was selling it to the Germans for
50 million. And he says, hey, listen, the bank just called me.
I'm staying over there in Houston, Texas.
And actually, it was thirty six million for this one.
And the bank says they want me to come and sign a check.
And I said, wait a second, aren't you selling it to them and the sale is going
through? Aren't they supposed to send you money?
Yeah, that's what's supposed to happen.
But the bank, as a matter of fact, they called me up.
They said they want me to come in and sign a check.
And this is the third time I'm doing it.
And I'm like, oh, shit, I got to see this.
So we go to the bank and three of these jerk offs come around.
They're all like they're zombified eyes.
Well, this paperwork and they actually have a big check and they cover it with
paper. You can't see what it says on top.
And they have the guy sign it.
Why? Because the German bank doesn't have any money to send.
So in other words, when this man who is supposed to be receiving the funds from
another from the transaction is actually creating the funds with a signature
several times. I said, how many checks have you signed?
This will be the third time. Do you know that you just basically gave the bank a
hundred million, thirty six million times three hundred eight million.
And they're just going to give you three.
Are you looking at what's going on here?
Yeah. But, you know, I know what you're saying.
Greek is the truth.
And I know you know your stuff.
But I never heard of that before.
But now that I see it happening and I don't think anybody else knows this is
happening, so I guess it's OK.
Wow. That sounds crazy, doesn't it?
This is the world you live in.
Right. Well, yeah, I've seen this thing before where you sign a check and it never
made any sense to me either.
I never purchased a home myself, but I've seen and I say to myself, but you're
getting a loan.
Why are you signing a check?
Right, well, the promissory note is different when you well, here's the other
thing, let's just throw this in.
If you have a deed of trust or more, it's different with every state, supposedly.
But if you have a deed of trust, when you right before the sale happens, it says
for consideration of ten dollars, you own the home fee simple.
Fee simple means you have to give a fee to the king.
That means you own it. But now you're going to give it in a mortgage.
So you don't get a mortgage, you give a mortgage and you cannot give a mortgage
for something that you don't already fully own.
So what's really happening is that you fully own the house.
But the and then you putting it into a mortgage, which you can't pay, you can't
pay a mortgage, it's called you could satisfy a mortgage when you pay a mortgage.
You don't pay it.
You actually going on a contract, you're going to give so many payments and then
they have to give you a letter of satisfaction because you can't there's no
money to pay. So it's really, really a level of insanity.
By the way, if you do have a deed of trust, read it.
The first line on all of them says you own the house free, simple, but now you're
going to put it into a mortgage because you're just a nice guy.
We found a way to get out of that, by the way, I could tell you what it was.
The mortgage contract and the deed of trust is a trust.
You're making the mortgage, the people that are dealing, the mortgage company, the
trustees and you're the trust store.
You're full of command of it.
Why don't you just being the trust or why don't you file a record in the public
records that as the trust store of the trust, you're not happy with the trustee
and you're firing them and appointing someone else like your dog and you just
fire them because when you fire them and they have a legal notice, they can't come
back and foreclose because they can only foreclose if they're an active trustee.
So you fire them before that and just make someone else the trustee.
Now, we had about 100 people do this around California and Arizona, and the
district attorneys of those states physically went to the people's homes and
asked them. They thought they were in trouble.
And they asked them, you didn't do anything illegal, but we want to know who
showed you this.
But do you see how simple the rationale is?
You are the trust store.
The mortgage company is the trustee, the trust or can fire the trustee anytime and
appoint another trustee.
Right now, if someone's fired, can they come back and collect the paycheck, let's
say, at a job? No, no, that's it.
They're terminated. That's terminated.
So so that's how you get rid of them.
And it's so simple.
And yeah, so, yeah, the banking situation, this is not going to change is going to
get worse and worse with the digital currency.
You know, with the digital currency, if you want to go and buy, let's say, potato
chips and they decide that you shouldn't have potato chips that day, the sale won't
go through. Right.
You understand. Right.
OK, so it's we've talked about this before, quote unquote, Mark of the Beast
thing. You won't be able to buy or sell.
It's a roundabout.
It's not the mark of the beast, but it's a roundabout way precursor to it.
Well, it's a control. It's very much like what they do with the.
You know, with the Department of Agriculture credits, which are actually, you know, what
they call food stamps, right, or still call food stamps, even though there's no
stamps anymore.
EBT card.
EBT, right. So the thing is, the Department of Agriculture issues a credit and that
credit can only be used for what it is meant to purchase.
Right. So you can't go buy cigarettes with it, say, you know, technically directly.
Right. Right.
It's very similar to that. Very much so.
Yeah. But, you know, the people that use those, the people are commented on by those
that those that don't use them say, oh, they're living off the dole of enough for
taxpayer dollars. No, they're not.
When you have an EBT card, the moment you sign for it, those funds are created on the
spot through J.P.
Morgan. It's right on the card.
It says this is all administered by J.P.
Morgan. Your signature is where they're getting it from.
And that's from the gold clause.
Right. When they took in the gold to print bank notes.
OK, how did they bankrupt the U.S.?
Real quick. They 16th Amendment Federal Reserve gets invited.
So they have elastic currency.
You know what? Elastic currency is a rubber check.
Right. Elastic.
Get it. Currency checks because their notes and rubber check, by the way, most young
people don't know it. But years ago, if you said I got a rubber check, that was a bad
thing. So basically, they're telling you that we're going to have a private
organization do the money for us and 16th Amendment, which wasn't ratified properly.
But it doesn't matter because Congress hasn't really been in lawful session since
1861 when the Civil War started.
There was a quote is there's a Latin term for means dead on arrival.
Whatever that term is, it is what they put in their books.
So they still meet formally twice a year or whatever it is, Congress and Senate.
But it has no lawful effect since 1861.
You could look this up.
All right. Well, anyway, what happened was they bring the Federal Reserve in and they
said, you give us your gold and silver and we'll print notes at a rate of six
percent. OK, so as they're continuously giving the Federal Reserve the gold.
And the silver, they're printing bank notes, which do say redeemable and silver.
I think you sent me one once, Chuck, a couple of years ago.
Right. OK, well, the problem they forgot, which a ninth nine year old could figure
out, is that what happens when you give them all your gold and all your silver?
You still owe them six percent, don't you?
Yeah. Are you going to pay that now?
Right. So that's what the bankruptcy of 1933 was.
By the way, if you go in 1933 newspaper articles, there make no bones about it.
You could look it up right now.
Newspaper articles from 1933 front page or articles is saying, oh, yeah, Federal
Reserve just shipped 80 million dollars worth of gold bullion off to France from
the U.S. left this morning.
They're shipping it all back to Europe.
There's nothing in Fort Knox, by the way, or anyway.
So this is how it was. So by 19, they had the Banking Act.
The Depression was completely fake, which was admitted to by Bernanke, by the way.
Do you remember Bernanke, Federal Reserve chairman?
He did a public speech that lasted about two minutes apologizing for putting the
U.S. into the Depression.
Right. It was totally orchestrated.
OK. By the way, if you're this dumb, meaning the population, you deserve this, by
the way. I don't know if that from Greek, from the Greeks point of view, if you're
so freaking stupid and dumb and ignorant, you deserve what's coming to you.
Right. You deserve that kind of treatment.
So I'm not I'm not this is not a sympathy call here.
Right. I'm just talking about the collective.
They deserve everything and worse, actually, which they're going to get in the
future. But so so this is what's going on.
It's very, very much out in the open.
And that's the short of it.
This happened with every country.
Other countries are slightly different because their money laws, if you had a
Napoleonic style law, it worked a little different, but generally the same.
Right. You know, a lot of countries, by the way, were running under Napoleonic law.
Right. So anyway, that's that's all I got to say about that.
That's my story. And I'm sticking to it.
There you go. How much how much further can you go with it once you get to that point
where, you know, look, if you're dumb enough to accept this, then you kind of deserve
it. So but it's interesting because I don't think anybody talks about how these
things were publicly admitted to.
And then just, OK, now we continue on, you know, like that receivership, the pizza
place is still there, you know.
Yeah, the state is there. That's why they said earlier, state of Georgia is not
Georgia state. Georgia state is what you see on the map and everything that part of
it. State of Georgia is the corporation that manages it.
I was telling someone yesterday when, OK, all this anti-police stuff, right.
OK, where did the history of the police?
They came out in the mid 19th century.
They started in Massachusetts, New York, New Jersey, Delaware, Maryland.
Right. And then it's why?
Because those large cities got involved with private bankers, Rothschild types,
Rockefeller types. There were no Rockefellers then, but sort of.
And they mortgaged City Hall and they more most of when it reached to the point where
one third of the entire city was mortgaged out to these private bankers.
The private bankers came to the state or the city and said, hey, look, we pretty much
own most of your property here or half of the property that's worth owning.
What if something happens like a riot or crime or whatever?
Are you able to protect it?
And they're like, no. All right.
So why don't we start what's called a police department?
Right. To protect our property.
You get it. So that's where the police come from.
So whenever you see police, they represent the private bankers.
That pretty much bankrupted or our own City Hall and all the important stuff in that
city, that's why the police have you know, they have to stay within city borders
usually. Right. Right.
OK, now the sheriff is no better because he's working on the state level.
Right. And then you have federal marshals and they're no better, too, because the
Fed, the 1933 March the 9th is all about the federal government going bankrupt.
So they're working for the banks, too.
That's what the marshals were about, by the way.
Texas Rangers were different.
They were lawful. So all this history.
So in short, a lot does a lawful society that uses lawful money have police?
No, there is no police present whatsoever.
So whenever you see a police department somewhere, that means that you're pretty
much bankrupt under the pirate threat through to the private bankers through banking
acts. Well, and they're they're there to enforce policy, which is what the name
sounds. Sure. Sure.
The policy is to protect and serve usually.
And they were put there.
By the way, this is something that 99 percent of the people ever told us to had never
heard of it. But when they do like a cursory research, they find it to be 100 percent
true. So, you know, anybody could be hired by them, by the way, you know, in order to
be hired by the police, you have to be you can't be too smart.
Right. This is very well known.
The same with politicians.
Oh, yeah. Whatever. Military also.
So we're pretty much whatever in that conditions.
So I'm not anti police.
I'm anti what brought that on.
Right. So whatever.
Well, now, look, the idea that someone should keep order, I guess in a lawful society,
you don't require anybody to keep order because it's already orderly.
Well, who's keeping order and for why?
Like I just said, the police were set up because the private bankers already took over
most of the important parts of the city and they put them in there to protect their
private interests, because let's say the bankers own City Hall through private
agreements and most of the important properties and there's a riot and the riot
results in the destruction of those properties.
When the property is destroyed, what's its value?
Compared to what it was before it was destroyed, you see my point, they don't care
about order and they want to maintain the property value.
Right. You see what I mean?
All right. So, OK, thanks for bringing the here.
Here. This just brought us a new it sprouted a new moment.
OK, the police are there to maintain property value, period.
That's it. Think about it.
All right. When you're in the ghetto and there's a shootout, what's the police
response? Never.
They never come. Right.
Maybe in three hours.
Right. If you're in a wealthy neighborhood, Golden Ghetto, there's a shootout.
The police are like they were like dropped out of the sky.
They're there in three minutes.
Right. Right.
Fifteen cars for one gun.
But if you're in a ghetto, really, you know, they're not coming.
They're not coming. Right.
They're not coming or it's like two hours.
They show up to clean up after.
There's a mop up crew for you because that's about what they come to do.
Yeah. Usually the ambulance shows up before the cops.
And I've seen the ambulance circles around and leaves.
Are the police here yet? No, they leave.
They wait for the police to come before the ambulance shows up.
Right. Somebody's got to protect them.
Mm hmm. Yeah, it's pretty bad.
So, yeah, you see what we got out of all this talk here?
The police are there to maintain property value, period.
By the way, I've had that conversation, this type of conversation with people
that work as retired judges, city comptrollers.
I used to have lunch years ago on a weekly basis with the basically the fiscal
manager of the city that I live in.
We on a weekly basis, actually her husband.
OK. Right.
And I was on a call yesterday that brought up that I was recommended
by Catherine Austin Fitz as someone that, you know, to come for legal information
and financial information on the working of the system.
And I was like, oh, my gosh, you know.
So there's an interesting point.
So, look, you know, you've gone around a whole bunch of different subjects
which are interconnected.
We didn't really discuss the gods at all.
But yet.
Yet. Right.
We all know this is important.
This is important. Oh, no, no.
I'm not saying any of this isn't important.
This is very important. All of this is necessary.
You know, and the the mosaic, I like to think of it as a mosaic.
You know, you assemble something piece by piece and is being assembled here.
And I like the way it's going for sure, because I'm actually learning and
contemplating new things, even though I've heard some of this before, to be
honest with you.
But but now you're fitting some pieces together differently
than than you had before.
Maybe that's how I'm going to get to the why eventually.
Right. Because it's going to make a lot more sense.
But no, the gods, I think we're going to have to reserve for another day,
you know, because because we've gone through a lot here and definitely talked
about the the the system in general, how it really works
versus how it's been represented, whether it's in the media or by the labels
or, you know, here's the government assignment that they give you and what is
actually going on receivership.
There's a concept to wrap your mind around if you haven't already.
What do you think the general idea here with this particular presentation is,
though? I mean, I'm trying to come up with a it's definitely
part of it, but easy.
Yeah, good. Easy. We got to tie the gods into it real quick.
When you talk about the gods, the way they relate to humans, they know all this is
going on, by the way.
What the gods did is they set this up as a human terrarium.
You know, a terrarium is where you set up a condition.
You put plants and animals that one feeds off the other so you don't have to keep
watering and feeding it every day.
You pretty much set up a balanced ecosystem.
You close it. You look at it.
You don't have to interact with it that much.
We're in a terrarium. All of these things are set to go for a certain amount of
years or quote unquote ages, and they have to run through.
Right. So the key point was setting up a terrarium.
One thing feeds off of another.
Right. I think the banking talk and all this stuff that I was talking about is
showing clearly how that's happening.
One thing feeding off of another.
Right. So this is how the gods have set it up.
And like I've said, just to finish this, how do you set it up there?
The gods, first of all, they're not your friends.
They don't like you.
They they've set you up this way, but they also know nothing bad.
Ultimately, on the on the highest level, nothing bad could ultimately come to you.
No matter how bad it seems here, you're going to be OK.
You're in an intermediate.
They set up humanity to be in an intermediate point.
An intermediate point is like you've heard of spring cleaning, like a really good
spring cleaning. You take a day off, you take all the furniture out of the house,
you dust everything, you throw away all this stuff that you don't you don't think
you're going to use. You probably take everything out of the closet.
Maybe you don't. I do. And I wash everything again, even though it hasn't been
worn. Right.
The spring cleaning.
Right. So we're in like this spring cleaning part of humanity and slip in going
on for six thousand years.
It started off with a bang and it's going to end with a bang, which is not too far
away. So in essence, you
have, by the way, you have everything you need to answer prayers and to manifest
things. That's why I keep saying they're not listening to your prayers.
You know, I mean, what does it mean?
Indefinitely, none of the gods are going to help or listen to you.
Prayers. But in general, no, they don't listen because you have they've already
given you everything. Kind of like you ever see an experiment where they put a monkey
in a cage with different objects and they put the banana in a box
and in order to get into the box, you need a key and they put the key off to the
side. And there's a whole bunch of people watching him.
He wants to get the he smells a banana.
He wants to get in there. And he goes over to where there's a row of different
objects, the keys in the middle.
And he picks up the object right next to the key.
And everybody, the scientists outside are yelling at him.
No, no, no. Put that down.
Put pick up the key.
The key will do it. And the monkey looks at him kind of bewildered and then goes to
even further away from the key.
You're like, oh, shit, this is kind of dumb.
They're not going to. The scientist is not going to go into the cage and pick up the
key and give it to the monkey and show him how to open the box.
Right. You see my analogy here?
Yeah. Yeah. OK.
In other words, everything is already here.
It's a matter of if you must find it.
This is mentioned in Scripture, the biblical text many, many, many times.
They'll say that if you read in the King James, the Lord hides things.
So the sovereigns are meaning the higher ups of the world will find them.
Right. All these things are hidden.
It talks. There's over maybe 50 references to how what we need is hidden here.
Right. Right.
So and if you're going to pray, you have to pray properly.
It gives you instructions on like how they do in church and all this other religious
God. That's the opposite.
Look, and to finish it off, whether you're talking about the Bible or the news or
whatever, any organization that picked up a body of work, in other words, if you
look at the newspaper and they're presenting, whether it's written or video, you
know what the television show they call the news, either way, you know what they're
going to report to the public is exactly opposite of what the journalist brought to
them. Informate the investigative journalist found it's going to be completely
reversed. That's why I tell people, listen, I find the mainstream media to be very
accurate diametrically.
So whatever they tell you, it's the opposite.
So if they say it was a terrorist attack, it means it wasn't a terrorist attack quite
accurately. Right.
You see, the general scope is very accurate.
So whatever they say.
So if they say there is a bank crash, that means there wasn't a bank crash.
You see, you see what I mean?
So they're actually if you look at the opposite of what they're telling you, it was
a pandemic. That means there was no pandemic.
It was a biological, chemical, energetic attack.
Right. We'll get into that in the future on how people, let's say, and during the
pandemic, they're at a here in Tucson and witnesses, they're at a convention, the
jewelry, the mineral show, one of the biggest mineral shows in the world.
Actually, it is the biggest mineral show in the world in February, a month before
they declared people were some were experiencing flu like symptoms and haziness
of thought. And they would fall out.
A lot of them died, by the way, couldn't breathe.
Guess what they did about two days before.
All these symptoms were reported at the gem show, they turned on about six or seven
5G towers in that neighborhood, these people had the initial doctor reports was
radiation poisoning, by the way, other parts of the country.
It was biochemical attack, different symptoms, right on and on and on and on.
So it was energetic weapon, biochemical and other places.
It was just the hospitals being incentivized to murder people, put someone on a
ventilator, you sedate them, don't give them water, don't give them food for a week.
What's going to happen? Yeah, of course.
Right. So it was like a three or four prong thing.
So was it a pandemic?
Absolutely not.
Did a lot of people die in several ways that they look like they got sick and in
hospitals? Yes, absolutely.
No. Here's the thing.
Find out if anyone died outside of a hospital from the covid thing.
Nobody. The only ones that died outside of the hospital were the ones that were hit
with energetic weapons.
It's pretty easy to do, by the way, which one day we'll talk about that.
Well, I think in part two, there was just there is a natural cycle, it seems to me,
as though, you know, illness does spread over certain time periods.
It's just naturally unnatural.
In other words, there's a curse that's been known in ancient times that if you are
extremely let me just say this again, extremely sexually promiscuous, the gods
don't like that and they will smite you with some kind of disease.
This is what I just said has been written since the ancient Sumerian times.
This is not a Christian thing.
This is not. OK, let me repeat that.
If you're extremely sexually promiscuous for a long enough period of time, you will
get some kind of a disease where your groin will rot off.
This has been known since the beginning of time.
You see what I mean? I don't think I've ever seen.
I'm not saying sex does that.
I'm saying, you know, I'm just thinking to myself, I don't think I've ever known
anybody whose groin is actually rotted off.
Well, it's an example.
Yeah, but I heard it hurts when it years ago used to be called the clap.
Right. Oh, yeah.
No, that. But, you know, the truth is, I haven't known anybody who's caught that in
a while. At least I don't know.
That's right. It's a it's a hygiene thing.
But, you know, there is there isn't no there's no natural disease.
But if you do things really wrong, like, for example, if you naturally drink a bottle
of scotch every day, your liver is going to dry up and kill you.
Right. Naturally.
Right. Yeah.
Because the scotch is pretty natural.
Your liver is pretty natural.
Can you say you die to natural causes?
Of course. Yeah.
So is your behavior within that natural world that leads to disease?
You see what I mean? Yeah, of course.
What behavior you choose.
Yeah, yeah, no, I got you.
So it's about behavior and the answer to that.
Of course. Yeah.
Yeah. And it could be weaponized.
You know, there there is a way to create a plague or a disease.
It's not in the lab. If you took the worst bio.
By the way, there are there are publications, if you could find them now that I've
looked at where they had actually found like the worst diseases in the world, people
with them, especially the Japanese, did a lot of study on this, mainly the Japanese,
the Americans, the Germans, the Swiss, the Swedish, that that part of the world.
They have tons and tons of reference books where let's say you pick any bad disease,
anything right. They would take blood and lymph fluid, saliva, urine and share it with
someone who did not have the disease and they wouldn't catch it.
Never, never, never, never, ever.
But when there were certain people in proximity would get the disease, go figure.
Right. Amazing.
And also when the people were sick, let's say you had three people that were categorized
as having the bubonic plague.
They would take the blood lymphatic fluid, urine, feces, stool and study it, catalog
everything they saw. Then the person next to them with the identical diagnosis, they
would look at their blood, lymph fluid, feces, urine and they would look and catalog
everything in there and they didn't match.
So there's nothing biological.
They'll tell you, obviously, 19 Arab hijackers vaporized the World Trade Center with
box cutters. Right.
That sounds pretty plausible if you're retarded.
Yeah, it's the same thing.
It has to be done the same way.
Excuse me. Drink coffee and talk at the same time.
Not advisable. It has to be done the same way.
When you look at a cross section of the human intestine and a cross section of a car
tire, how nothing penetrates structurally.
I was talking to someone recently about this.
So one holds a high pressure air.
How could. Well, exactly.
The car tire is designed to have maintain a very high pressure differential from what's
inside the tire to outside.
If you look at the human intestine, it's exactly the same thing.
But the pressures are not that high.
Nothing passes through that.
So it has to be through induction.
So the way disease is transmuted back in the old days was by induction.
And we can get I don't know if I get I don't know.
There's very few people that are able to speak on this, how to create a plague.
It's not it's not that easy.
What I'm trying to say is you can go in the laboratory, like I gave the example earlier,
taking samples for the sickest people or even ones that are not sick that you think are
going to be sick. You could put that in a laboratory, freeze it and then put it in the
water or spray it on people.
A few people might get sick a little bit, but it won't turn into a pandemic.
I assure you that for sure, that the way you create a pandemic is by the way the human
body works, by induction.
And we'll leave that for another day, but I'll give you a hint.
It's going to require at least 30 to 100 people and it's going to take about two to three
months to do it. And I could lay it out, lay out exactly how it's done historically,
but not in the sonic.
And also, I don't know if it's a good idea to do that.
Well, yeah, fair enough.
And look, again, we've been through a great many subjects and sort of laid out the
symptoms of what is what is happening here is still and only just slightly touched on
the gods and their role in this, which, again, I'm always amazed at the people that, you
know, try and tell you that, you know, God loves you and this.
No, there is. There is one.
But that one can't help you very much, can he?
Well, that's that's the thing, you know.
Look, did you hear that Vinny Short, Vinny Eastwood thing I did?
I heard one of it. Yeah.
Because, you know, Vinny, Vinny glazes over when you get into any of these subjects.
Right. I mean, I love Vinny for whatever, but I got to just say it as I see it.
Right. So when I saw him glazing over, I said, OK, you know what?
There are many gods, but there's only one of you.
Think about that.
Now, fair enough.
So, you know, I'm just I'm just thinking about how to wrap this all up, actually.
And it's a wrap.
That's it. Pretty much.
There you go. Let's just say we're.
Yeah, let's just say we'll put a bow on it.
And until the next one, number seven.
There you have it.