51, this Sonic event, pattern break, there you go, anyway, I got a couple of things on
my mind, I might kick it off and I'm not even going to ask the Greek how he's doing.
So how's that for a break in the pattern?
Yeah, well, what's doing is, you know, people thought 33 was the Freemason number, it's
really 51 that they used to communicate a lot.
They use the 33, like there's 33 million people positive for COVID, you're going to
start seeing the 51 and the 15.
So it could be 1.5 billion 5.1 million 50, you're right, you see what I mean?
Just the five and the one in days and in numbers, quantities or whatever.
That's their signaling.
Yeah, they're pathetic, by the way, they don't do this too much.
Yeah.
They also use 15 days as a count quite often.
By the way, I've noticed that often where it's a little more than two weeks, so it
doesn't give you the two weeks according to your calendar.
And you got the 15 days, which is interesting because they don't count the days properly
anyway.
But, you know, but they're 15 days, but always the one in the five.
You're right.
That is interesting.
Well, well, look at the past few years, the stuff that's in the news.
Johnny Depp, 15 million dollar lawsuit, right?
This goes across Hollywood, medical, financial, everything.
That's the way they signal to each other, meaning that we got to.
The reason I said they're so pathetic is because, you know, people refer to them as the elite
and they have all these fancy cars and mansions and whatever.
They're actually trapped.
They have nothing.
They are intermediates between those who rule the surface and the surface inhabitants.
That's one thing like the Musk and the Jeff Bozo and Bill Gates.
Those people are completely enslaved.
They have nothing at all, no freedom at all and no character to speak with.
You know, like like a Russian Dimitri, he basically says, you go down to the, you know, the bad
part of town and you meet some gangster.
He's got more charisma and character than any of these people that they're showing you
as being elite.
Right.
True.
Yeah.
So, yeah, they're pretty pathetic.
And I have a second hand knowledge on how pathetic they are and some first hand knowledge.
So when they're called the elite, it's because they're the ones that it's kind of like the
hot sheets.
You watch what they're saying.
But the people really have the people have the because they're messaging, they're not
doing anything.
I'm sorry.
When you when you said hot sheets, I thought of the Inquirer and stuff in the movie.
Yeah.
That's exactly what they are.
They are just the hot sheets.
In other words, they're what and the people themselves lack so much.
But anyway, the bottom line is this, that if you let me just fast forward to the point
like the money system, the medical system, if enough people wake up, you know, you get
nuked.
Right.
So let's say a bunch of Americans say we want lawful money.
This is bankrupt.
This is fraud.
They'll nuke you.
In other words, they'll use your own nukes on you.
Right.
Just like.
It's very simple.
That's always when a mass murder occurs is right at the time that people start to go.
Wait a minute.
I think we're getting the idea of what's actually happening here.
And then a mass murder occurs.
And I don't mean these little ones that are only, you know, a couple dozen people get
shot at a Walmart.
I'm talking.
You mean like a Civil War revolution type thing?
Yes.
That's when they try to clear the slate and go, hey, turn on each other and shoot each
other for a little while.
Oh, yeah.
No, I mean, like what they'll do is they'll divide the military.
They'll find out.
Right.
They need a small percentage because mechanized.
You don't need one person can operate a device that could kill 20,000 people or more.
They'll just find out who will do anything for money, you know, and, you know, they just
print money.
Right.
And they the military, all this crap about their, you know, humans are morons in military
or are weaponized morons.
Right.
So you never thank anyone for being in the service, because when they're talking about
the enemy, they're talking about the civilian population.
So people don't know this.
This is a fact, by the way, what I'm saying, and it's the truth.
Stick to the facts.
Now, the truth is way beyond what most people will ever comprehend.
But what what they do very simply is get a few desperate people or, you know, really
greedy, which is easy, which is most of the people.
And you just unleash them on the rest.
It's very simple.
Right.
We haven't seen that type of self-destruction on a society yet.
I don't think it's going to happen here, but it's all set up for it.
Right.
Yeah.
Look, all that stuff is definitely set in place.
And one of the weird things that did come up in the chat, and I don't want to turn to
the chat too much this time, but I did think about it a little bit because somebody asked,
you know, about crop circles and this and that.
And alien presentation is one of those interesting topics where I think a lot of people are right
and wrong about it all the time, because I don't think they recognize what type of entities
are interacting on this planet already all the time that are in a way alien to us.
But they're not really aliens.
Yeah.
They've been here all along.
No, they're alien, but they're coming from different places.
They're coming from a reality that we don't see.
They're coming from the underground and they're coming from above.
Greek speak is alien to an academic, right?
Yeah.
But after you live somewhere long enough, after you work somewhere long enough, I mean,
you become a resident.
You become part of it because you're immersed in it.
I mean, so how long is it that, you know, these entities got to be here interacting and doing
things before you got to say, look, this is kind of their home, too.
Because they don't want the entities, though, because the entities are going to wake people
up and say, hey, you've been frauded in the most.
So in other words, they're using like low grade fraud scenarios on you, low grade pranks.
And you guys don't even see it.
You know, like the financial system is a low grade prank.
The medical system is a low grade prank, like stuff third graders do.
Right. Well, yeah. If you're going to keep laughing at the whoopee cushion, why get into
the, you know, extemporaneous humor of somebody who's going through it?
Well, you don't need it because.
Well, yeah. Well, here's another way to say it.
Like someone who could be easily controlled, ain't worth controlling someone who could
be easily manipulated, ain't worth manipulating.
In other words, you ain't got much.
That's not much of a person.
Right. Go ahead and manipulate someone with strong character.
See what to see what happens.
Well, boy, that's not. So in other words, the population at large across the world.
So I used to think it was Americans.
Right. See, and the only place I ever hear people say like this outside of you, the only
place I've ever heard people speak like this is among the gangster population, because
this is exactly what they say.
Look, I don't care about controlling this guy, that guy.
I don't care about any of that. That's nothing.
That's easy. You know, you want it.
You want to make something really happen.
Here's who you get to get a hold of.
You know what I mean? So someone like the mass, the mass population is easy to control.
They're not worth anything. You know what I mean?
It's just the puppets, right?
No, you know, something.
But it's changing your pocket as opposed to actual power.
Well, that's what I say about suckers.
Someone says, well, you know, I'm going to do business with him or so and so because
they're a sucker. And I'm like, oh, no, no, no, no, no.
You got it wrong. If they're already established as being a sucker, see, they're going to
lose their money anyway.
So you better do business with them because they'd rather fall in your wallet than
someone. It's kind of they're going to lose their money regardless.
So wouldn't you rather have their lose their money with you?
There's some other guys that you're never going to meet.
That's going to work with you. It's like, oh, I never thought of it that way.
I said, ah, now you're starting to think, listen, if there's gold bars laying in the
street, you might as well pick them up because somebody else will.
If you don't, I mean, actually, there might be some times you don't want to pick them
up, but that's another story.
OK, yeah, especially if they're American, because they're probably tungsten inside.
Right. See, now there's trouble.
Yeah, I thought, well, by the way, I thought the Americans were really pathetic.
Right. But then I started meeting people and traveling, not that much travel, but
meeting people from all over the world, like like 130 different countries.
I've got catalogs like, where are you from?
Yemen? Where are you from?
Bangladesh. Where are you from?
Here. I was like, oh, my gosh, I've met people in over 100 different countries, you
know, and, you know, amazing how many countries are on the continent and they're all
pretty much the same.
There's a slight flavor variation like Baskin Robbins.
You know, you're getting ice cream, you know, you're getting sugar, you know, you're
getting, you know, dairy and you're right and you're getting the same logo.
That's the same with people. You got 31 flavors, 170 flavors, 200 flavors, but it's
the same stuff.
So then I retracted my way of my approach because it was get out of America time.
Right. This is a while back.
And and it's like it doesn't matter where you go.
It's just a variety of this stupidity and they don't have to be that way.
That's the crazy thing about it.
Speaking of things that don't have to be that way, I want to just segue into the
weather. Yeah, absolutely.
One of my uncles once told me the only difference about people around the world is
really the way they make their bread.
That's about it. Yeah, very much.
And sandwiches are what they call a sandwich, which is what you put in the bread.
Yeah. So, you know, and that that is funny to me.
But OK, yeah, let's let's move on to the weather, because that is an interesting
topic in and of itself.
It's constantly used to engage people in fear porn, you know.
Now, watch the weather. Watch the weather.
I'm always what I saw this big time.
They're pushing this thing called Hurricane Lee.
It's let's give a time mark.
Well, it's about the 10th day of the seventh month.
Hmm. Right.
Yeah. And so well, according to the Pope's according to the Pope's work schedule,
that's almost accurate because, yeah, it's it's a day of atonement kind of thing.
Right. OK, so so anyway, just to give a time marker would be the ninth of September
to twenty three.
Right. Two thousand twenty three.
Yeah. So someone said, listen, can you do something about this?
And I'm like, what's this?
Hurricane Lee. I said, look at it.
And by the way, this is a funded project, by the way.
And so that got me, you know, when someone wants to separate themselves from their
funds to do something on weather, I'm all for it because I like to do the weather
anyway. But one of the reasons I don't do it is because I don't get anything for it.
Right. And it takes a lot of time.
So I looked at it and I said, wait a second.
This thing is kind of minor.
It's got everything going right.
And it's being pushed in the media like they have it prescripted.
Right. You know what I mean?
So this is pretty you can.
Well, I don't watch the media a lot, but I could tell when they're reading.
Well, they're always reading a script.
But this is really, really strong on the prescriptive thing.
Right. And I'm like, why are they prescriptive?
And then I'm watching it. I'm watching it goes from a minor storm to a category five
in like 16 hours.
Right. And I'm like, that never happens.
It never happened in history.
And I'm like, OK, let's go for it.
Well, wait, pause right there, because how ridiculous is that in reality?
Because the way I understand it is it takes, you know, like a full day for a full
category, according to their measurements, three, you never get more than one
category change in less than a day or two or a day and a half minimum.
That's what I was trying to say.
OK, yeah. So I am right.
This one this one from below one or one is storm five in a little bit over 12
hours. I mean, that's literally like tropical storm to seriously dangerous hurricane in
24 hours, which is like not that's unprecedented, basically.
Well, this would have been an unprecedented above like the French category, meaning
higher than any category.
This is would have been another Katrina or Sandy.
OK, right. This was as I see it.
And I saw it in the media.
What's the way they were portraying it?
You know, the way they portray 9-11 COVID, they were doing the same emo behind it.
Superstorm, super event, you know, a bunch of things all coming in and make sure to
interrupt other stories to push it.
Right. Right. So I was looking at this.
I was like, oh, they're using the formula, which is like DEF CON, you know, whatever.
I don't know. The higher number is more dangerous for the lower number.
I don't know. Whatever. But anyway, they were pushing the DEF CON thing, you know.
So this is yeah.
So this is the high speed boogeyman, not like the one that's meant to simmer there for a
long time, like this is high speed and high speed.
So when it does a lot of damage, they're like, we told you so before.
Of course. Well, that adds to their credibility so that next time they want to cause an
alarm, they can, regardless of whether it's legitimate or not.
So, yeah, OK, gotcha.
OK, let's go back to some vintage cartoons, which still exist today.
It's called Spy vs.
Spy. You remember that?
Oh, yeah, sure. Yeah.
OK, anybody look that up.
Spy vs.
Spy. This is what's going on.
Mad Magazine, Black vs.
White Guide, a whole thing.
There's actually they made video games out of it, all kinds of stuff.
Yeah, go ahead. OK, so still, yeah, it's still extant, you know, because I thought
I remember having Mad Magazines from the 50s, actually the 60s and 70s.
They always had a section for Spy vs.
Spy, right?
It's 80s also.
I don't know.
So it's extant, it kept going.
It didn't fade out. Yeah.
Interesting. OK, so this is Spy.
So what happens is I take out some devices that I know work really well, years of
experience, two decades of experience now, actually three decades of experience.
And I said, what is the most, you know, Occam's razor?
You know, what is the most minimalist thing?
Sometimes that works the best, right?
What is the what is the simplest explanation that usually explains a lot of the
complexity? Yeah, I got you.
OK, so I went after two ways.
I said one thing is affect the environment, affect the storm, do both.
Don't just go after the storm.
So what I noticed after about eight hours of starting the op with two devices, very
crude devices, but they're very technical also, meaning that the proportions and all
that. And so what I did was I noticed that when I first approached the project, it
had two counter rotating arms that had the classic hurricane.
You know, the international symbol for hurricane is the two rotate counter rotating
arms with the center, right?
I right. Well, as soon as I started, I noticed that within five or six hours, one
of the arms disappeared, the one that faces west.
So I got rid of one of the arms.
And if you get rid of one of the arms, it's not a hurricane anymore.
Right. Well, it can't spin.
It needs both.
Yeah, wobbles along.
It's kind of like a wheel with a flat side on it.
Right. Exactly. You can see it on the thing.
So I took one of the arms out in less than a day.
I was like, oh, my gosh, this thing is really subject to it.
So this thing was artificially started.
And so I knocked it down and then it went up to a five.
Well, while I was doing this, it was it was it had already become a five.
And I knocked one of the arms off.
OK, so just for clarification, were they predicting it was going to be a five or did they
already say it was a five before?
Well, this thing is this thing is propagated, if you know what I mean.
No, no, I understand that. But what I'm saying is they're reporting.
Were they saying it's going to be a five or a five already?
Well, no, no. They just said Tropical Storm went from category two to a five in real
time. OK, fair enough.
So but you could see it was all very much like, you know, you better read this right
now, you know. So, yeah, it's just like the 9-11 or, you know, the typical fear stuff.
Right. Right. Right. OK.
So it took the I said, OK, I've got resonance with it.
And then after about 18 hours, I saw that it went totally flat to the side that I was
affecting completely flat.
I look like a dumpling, you know, a dumpling lays flat on the plate and it's round on
top of this thing, a dumpling turned sideways.
So I'm like, wow, I really got resonance with it.
And then they started pumping it again.
The altitude went up very, very high.
In other words, instead of it being at a moderate altitude, it went way up because it
couldn't it doesn't want to move into the zone that I put in front of it.
And they kept pumping it and pumping it and pumping it.
And one of the side effects of very strong weather ops, whether I'm doing it or
others are doing it, is makes the ground shake.
OK, so then Morocco hit what I was doing, caused about seven tremors in Puerto Rico
because I predicted I sent a message is going to be tremors along the line from
Tucson, Georgia, northern Florida, Cuba, Puerto Rico.
Look along that line.
Right. OK, so that means the center of the shaking event is somewhere in the ocean and
it's causing tremors in Puerto Rico.
Is that right? No. And what causes tremors is the where it hits the ground, where it
concentrates. So the tremors that were created because of the op I was doing were
happening in Puerto Rico because that was right that's in front of the hurricane.
That's why it has never stopped.
But what they were doing there at the center of energy was affected Morocco going
through the ground. So these guys are hitting this from Europe.
In other words, whatever they're doing, the main point of influence is east, not
west. So which is five versus five.
Again, the black, right, the black and white, the white guys on the west, the black
guys on the east, whatever, whatever.
Right. So I call it spy and spy because when the Morocco earthquake happened, it gave
up. It gave up where they're producing their influence from.
Right. By the way, this is I'm serious as a heart attack on this.
And I could back up everything I'm saying.
If you can go more and more and why the earthquakes happen.
It's not necessary. I did predict earthquakes along the line from Tucson all the way
to Puerto Rico. And there were seven tremors in Puerto Rico after I predicted that.
Right. OK, there's an earthquake map, by the way, live gives you up to the minute,
supposedly earthquake with a map.
So so everything's working fine.
But they made the big one in Morocco.
So what does that mean? Now, they really they saw the thing go down and they're
like, oh, what happened? Let's boost it up.
They know what they know. I'm doing it.
And all communications are being monitored.
So it's spy versus spy.
Well, what is the spy versus spy?
Like they go shake hands and each one's got like a bomb behind his back.
Right. Right.
You know, or something. And it usually doesn't end up well for one of them in each
in each skit. Right.
But they come back every year.
That's why I would run on mad TV every week.
Also, you know, which was like, yeah, they did that, too, where there would be like,
you know, a two minute thing where just really quickly what happened.
They would throw a bomb at each other over a wall blindly, whatever.
And yeah, one guy gets got.
The other guy laughs and then they start again next week.
And then next week, the other guy wins. Right.
Right. Yeah. So this is very, very interesting.
And I'm watching this and I'm still influencing it now for the past 24 hours.
It's moved like 10 miles, which it should have moved a couple of hundred.
The big hurricane. So it's stuck there.
It's it's well, everything in nature has to move, you know, like a shark.
If it doesn't move, it, you know, can't live.
Right. It needs for. So it's bobbing up and down.
You could look at it on the satellite maps.
They don't know what to say about it.
They don't know the track.
But my goal is to have it completely gone by what they call Monday,
completely fizzled off, not going up through Atlantic
and making storms in Boston or Canada or wherever.
No, it'll be gone, gone, gone.
I once did a very, very intense abatement of a hurricane
that was going to be another kind of sandy thing back into 2014
and in Louisiana.
And I went very, very strong on that.
And it became sunny skies,
but you can still see the eye of the hurricane on the infrared.
So there was not a cloud in the sky,
but they were baffled on why the eye of the hurricane was showing up on infrared.
But it was totally clear sky, not a cloud, no wind, nothing.
Think about that.
That's you could find that article.
I forgot the the name of the storm around 2014 is supposed to hit New Orleans.
They started evacuating and they're like, what do you mean evacuate?
There's not a cloud in the sky. It's not even windy.
And there's nothing on the weather.
What do you it's all prescripted, right?
Yeah, well, so I have evidence of the ethereal effect versus,
you know, what you can see.
OK, so I figured I'd share this because I know that amongst the listeners
is about half a dozen people that dabble with weather. Right.
So and I don't it's not good to talk about it while you're doing it too much.
And I am talking about it as much as I think is safe at this point,
even though it sounds like I'm being a little whatever, no hubris here.
But these things are this is what I tell people say.
Oh, Greek, you could do the weather.
That's bullshit, because if you could control the weather,
you'd be a billionaire.
And I'm like, what kind of plausible logic is that?
I mean, that means you don't know where you live at all.
Usually I tell people that your your self-esteem is so low
that you never thought you could meet anyone that had those kind of skills.
You should think more of yourself.
Yeah. And who's to say you're not a billionaire anyway?
I don't know. Yeah, I know.
But the thing is ridiculous.
You know, I mean, this is the plausibility of the masses is just absurd.
And even friends and family, by the way, you know, they're part of the group, too.
You know, that's why I always say there's a lot of evil people.
I go to a regular group of people.
I see there's a lot of evil people in the world right now.
I'll agree. Yeah.
And but it's never their friends and family and they all agree.
It's never anybody they know.
But you just said a lot. There are a lot of them.
So where are the lot of them?
If it's not anyone, you know.
Oh, my gosh. You got to start about reevaluating who you're around. Right.
So where's your evidence for it?
If you're not running into them, where are they?
You know, I can't be your friends or family right now.
Sure. Yeah. Right.
So they can't, you know, just like I think one time we were going to do
an interview with somebody and before we started recording, I said, oh,
she's the kind that you pull the string behind her neck and she talks. Right.
I don't know if you remember that.
I wasn't happy about the right situation.
But in other words, if you want to know what I think about you,
just listen to what I just said.
So, you know, hidden,
you know, that I don't have, you know, right.
So no, I know you're pretty straight about it.
I mean, you know, I get it. It's it's.
Yeah. So this is what I'm trying to do with the weather here.
That's why, you know, normally I wouldn't go on such a dissertation
on what's going on. But it's funny.
It's funny to watch what they're doing.
You know, I'm using basically like 100 bucks worth of equipment.
They've got about two, 300 million worth of equipment.
They probably have 30 or 40 or 100 people. It's just me.
Yeah. Kind of funny.
Well, it's really funny because, I mean, the stuff that that I have heard
about you working with is hilarious, too, because it doesn't sound
all that expensive to manufacture, even there may be precision involved.
But I mean, it's not like super expensive material.
It's not like you need, you know, diamond studded laser guns or none of that.
OK, I know the stuff, the water devices I make are they're cheap,
but it's it's kind of like Steinmetz and Henry Ford.
Do you know the situation there?
Ford started investing in big AC motors for the factories,
which makes sense, right? In the 20s. Right.
It's cheaper than right.
Cheaper than horsepower, steam power.
And they kept blowing up because they had certain components in the wrong spot.
So he called Steinmetz to come and show him where they should,
you know, how to rewire it.
And this is the 1920s.
So Steinmetz goes over there, puts a couple of chalk lines
and some marks on on the thing.
And, you know, it's a motor.
It's like as tall as you are. Right.
And he sends forward a bill for 10,000 bucks.
And he's like, Ford's like, what?
You're only there for an hour.
And he's like, yeah, well, you let me break down the bill.
It's a dollar for me coming out there and spending an hour.
But nine thousand nine hundred and ninety nine dollars
to actually put the chalk mark where it needs to be.
All right.
You get it. Oh, I get it.
So if I'm making a piece of pipe that costs 50 to 100 bucks,
let's say everything, and I'm selling it for five grand, let's say. Right.
It's just a piece of pipe that dirty water goes through and clean water comes out.
You want to do it yourself? Go ahead.
No, it's the Steinmetz thing.
Yeah. So it's actually replacing 15 or 20 thousand dollars worth of equipment,
which which if you so it's cheap, actually, in that perspective.
And that 15 or 20 thousand dollars
worth of equipment needs over a thousand dollars a year.
Maintenance plus personnel.
Oh, yeah. No. And I've had to move those massive
AC units before.
They are taller than me by a couple of feet, actually.
And, you know, it's a couple of us to be able to move them
just to get them out of the way to install institutional windows.
And, whoa, that stuff is heavy and difficult.
And oh, yeah, well, yeah, that depends on what I'm talking about today.
But yeah, it's the whole thing about a hundred years later.
Those things are still huge and ridiculous.
Well, they are. Yeah.
They're not still not building them right because all the technology
that's on the surface is trickled down.
In other words, the society that runs this society is 6000 years ahead.
And over the years, especially the past 200 years,
they decided to trickle down certain science and engineering
that will bring them only 2000 years ahead.
You get it?
Well, they what they did is they said, look, here's some of the toys.
Yeah. Not the real tools, but have some toys.
And that's about what they did.
And that's what you do with children.
You give them some toys. It keeps them busy.
So anyway, good.
Yeah, I know.
So, well, it's also that they're keeping a lot of the time
travel, teleportation and the phasers.
I really want a phaser. Oh, man.
You know where you point it and everything you're pointing,
anything you're pointing out turns to a pile of dust or evaporates completely.
Man, I want a transporter.
And are you kidding me?
Those phasers. Oh, man.
I want both things.
I want to talk about anger management issues.
Anybody's anger management issues will go away if you have one of those.
But anyway, instantly.
Yep. Yeah. Instantly go away.
Trust me.
If you got anger management issues and you got a phaser, those issues disappear.
Anyway. Yeah.
So, yeah. What were we on?
Technology trickle down. What else is trickling?
Maybe you brought up something in the chat about crop circles.
Let's address that real quick.
Well, crop circles, aliens, other entities coming from elsewhere.
One thing at a time.
Let's be super linear on this, because the alien thing depends on who's
who's using that word.
OK, if you're in the military, anybody that's on the military is alien.
Right. You got enemy alien. Right.
Yeah. True. So. Yeah.
So anyway, crop circles, I came to a conclusion in the 80s
and I'm still sticking by it.
Ninety nine point nine, nine, nine, nine, nine, nine, nine, nine
percent of all crop circles show up in England.
Right. They try to deflect that fact
by doing a movie with Mel Gibson called Signs.
Remember? Oh, yeah.
He was in the US and they're putting crop circles down all over the world.
They're trying to deflect the nature of it.
Because, you know, it's there's more value in the mystery
if people can't don't figure it out because they figure out there's no mystery.
So if you go back in history, it was the mowing devil.
So it's very simple.
The when these underground critters or people or whatever
bipedals or whatever, tripedals come up from the ground.
They do this as part of their culture.
And they go back underground.
And guess where they are? In England.
In England, these are this is a characteristic of those
that live underneath England or above that.
It's geographic, cultural.
It's, you know, how culture reflects geography and vice versa, right?
So certainly certain certain geography of certain cultures.
That's just the culture of those that are not seen in and around.
It must be. You know how these legal documents
in and around or near and about England.
That's it. That's all it is.
Yes. France included in that as well, because there's a lot of things
about the underground in France.
I mean, the stuff that people everywhere in the entire earth is underground
everywhere. Native Americans will tell you about the ant people right here.
And where I'm at right in the southwest.
Oh, yeah. And everywhere in Russia, they have the abominable snowman
and other creatures.
The elemental. Yeah, right.
The element is big.
All of the ancient kings got their wealth by dealing with the underground.
You know, when you see those big stones and all that gold that they have,
you know, stones, meaning jewels. Yeah.
Because really, they don't have stones.
If they had stones, they'd still be king.
But hey, jewels and stones can often be interchangeable.
Good. Yeah. Yeah. So there you go.
And yeah, that's they get a lot of stuff.
And in return for the poor peasants, you know,
they're just, you know, who's going to who's going to ask any questions.
It's kind of like the authorities have authority because they have might.
Like, for example, there was a shooting in France.
You mentioned Paris and
a big one, you know, is one of those stage things.
But they did pile up a whole bunch of bodies at the end of it. Right. Yeah.
Well, this has been confirmed from several sources.
And only Damagard mentioned this brought it to my attention.
And I said, this guy sounds like he's hyping it up.
I didn't look into it.
And it was true in terms of what other sources reported.
Make a long story short.
There was a big shooting in Paris about a decade or less.
The bodies piled up.
They didn't mind showing that
a woman exchange student from Mexico City, Mexico.
Her while it was going on, calls her family,
who was very concerned because they knew she was in Paris.
And she said, oh, I'm fine.
I know that all hell's breaking loose, but I'm fine.
I'm at the police station.
Well, guess what?
Two hours later, they find her body and piled up on top of the rest of the bodies.
Uh huh. Well, is that more of a look?
Now we have a good excuse to get rid of the inconvenient whoever.
Or is that, you know,
oh, no. Well, see, the problem with Oleg, I got to tell you, is quite often
I've gone to check some of his so-called facts and he's full of crap.
Yeah, yeah. That's that's that's what I'm saying.
So you got to look to me.
Everything's full of crap until it's not.
It has to be.
No, look, occasionally he's gotten some things right.
But I'm just saying the majority of it.
I go as soon as his name's on it, I go, all right, let me go check.
Yeah, but I looked at this.
This was quite interesting.
OK, and it disappeared.
You could still probably find some of it.
And this was almost a day after the event I was looking at,
or two days after is one of the things where you got on an interview.
Let's say that week.
So I find it very interesting.
But when I heard that happen, it kind of it's very sad,
but it also made me happy to see that it went public
because I know of these things happening from, you know, past experiences,
hearing things, you know, what the police would do, right?
What? Supposedly. Right.
It's all orchestrated, right?
So, you know, the Martin Luther King.
But again, some people take advantage of things, too, where, look, a riot happens.
So it's a good opportunity to get rid of somebody
and just act like it was part of the riot that took him down. Exactly.
You know, so things like that happen as well.
That's why I asked, was it one of these situations
where they're just getting rid of the inconvenient?
Because that's what they'll do.
You know, in this case, what the feeling anymore that I got from it,
let's say the intuitive feeling is they just needed the body count.
So it's like, hey, you come here.
It's like a Patsy.
Do you think the best Patsy is the one that you haven't dealt with?
Because the less they know, the less they'll talk.
The best Patsy is when you're ready to pull an assassination or whatever.
You drag him into it while it's going on.
Immediately, he doesn't know anything.
The poor guy's trying to wave down a cab.
Well, right. And you arrest him as the assailant because he's got nothing to say.
And that's the thing.
He winds up getting killed before he even realizes.
It's like, what the hell? You're like, there's no grooming.
See, what I'm trying to say is that I think a lot of the hypnosis
with the trigger words and all that still confabulated because it's risky.
If you like do MK Ultra with a trigger word on someone,
you know, that's only like still 60 or 70 percent effective.
What if 30 percent of the time it doesn't work?
And they come out and say, oh, no, I'm not a Patsy.
I work with the CIA. No way.
They're just going to pick some random.
They know with with Oswald, they had some grooming with Oswald to a degree.
That's why he said, I'm just a Patsy.
They don't even want to hear that.
That's why I've been saying that right now.
Actually, I've noticed since 9-11, especially
and especially since the Boston thing, the the the flash bomb,
they told you it was a pressure grill just because I saw that while I was
that's that's just a flash bomb.
I was around military people.
Yeah, that's a flash bomb we use in training.
So but.
Since then, they make sure that no one in the public eye is read into anything
because of the Freudian slips that can come right.
So when you see these politicians telling you or the sheriff said it's a terrorist
attack, they honestly believe that
they no longer allow anyone that's read into it to be on camera.
Well, because of the slips that could happen.
Well, not only that, but you could have somebody turn around and decide
differently, you know, all of a sudden, if somebody escapes,
who wasn't supposed to escape and they have knowledge, you got a problem,
you know, because they could reveal something that's true.
You got to have the completely unaware or the completely brainwashed
up in front of the cameras, because that's the only way.
Look, it's just like an actor. What does an actor do?
Well, they convince themselves that they are that character, right?
They go into character.
They are that person.
They have to be that way in order to present something
that is remotely presentable, that makes sense.
That's like believable.
So you need people that are all on board with being that character.
What's the best way to do it?
To have them believe nothing else.
They are that character.
So you make them into that character and you don't tell them
any of this, that it's a movie, that it's a show, that it's not real.
You don't do that. You can't do that.
This is what they do.
They used to because they they knew they could scrub them off.
Like a good example of this is alleged, but I don't know if you've heard this.
When the Apollo thing happened, there was a lot of actors and crew.
And one of the people involved was a relative of someone
who was in the comms division.
And Nixon was a big diehard.
Nixon was like, you know, we'll go to the moon, but we can't show any pictures.
And Nixon said, oh, you have to show pictures.
You have to show.
Nixon was really big on showing pictures.
Right. But after they did all that stagecraft, some comm got out
that Nixon's plan was to erase all those people that were behind the scenes
because he didn't want it ever leaking out.
And they ran to Cambodia because Vietnam was going on the same time.
So they figured if they go nearby, they'll be safe.
So Nixon found out through other intel that they're in Cambodia.
So he says, let's start bombing Cambodia to get these guys.
This is how stupid it can be.
Right. So they actually start carpet bombing, because if you see
where they were carpet bombing Cambodia during that time, didn't make any sense.
It was it was little little enclaves and places where tourists went or, you know.
Right. And the weird thing about that is the justification in public is, well, OK,
the Viet Cong are retreating into Cambodia after they stage an attack.
So we have to bomb Cambodia.
And the American public goes, OK, makes sense.
But if you look at the map where the carpet bombing happened,
it doesn't make any sense at all.
There's no continuity because they had intel on where these guys were hiding out
or trying to restart their lives.
Right. There's a couple of border areas that get hit.
But the majority of the bombing.
Oh, my gosh. Yeah, you could tell it was they were actually it was very strategic.
In other words, it was surgical.
Yeah. Right. But it was but it didn't make any sense.
But once you start to hear what I just said, it says, of course, it makes sense
that they would do something like that.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. No, I get it.
But what I'm saying is at the time, the American public.
And that was the thing that was supposed to be public doesn't count.
Yeah. That was supposed to be one of the things
they were going to impeach him on is bombing Cambodia.
And I mean, you know, Nixon's response, the president can bomb anybody he wants,
which is true. He did.
Well, yes. Yeah, that's true.
But yeah, you know, they call the president commander in chief.
He's not unless Congress declares war.
Yes. True. So it's all it's all mixed up.
It's all jumbled up.
It's kind of like I've seen people go into court and they try to cite the law
and the judge will listen.
He says, that's not what it says, like right in front of you.
It's like that's not what you call it.
Deflecting when it's when you're speaking to someone and they deflect.
That's very hard to deal with because then it then it fucks with your reality.
It's like, wait a second.
This person said it's not like that.
I know it's like that my whole life.
Now it's not what the hell's going on.
So it's very, very difficult.
The deflection part.
So all you got to do, you know, someone reads something as sure as day
and you tell them that's not what it says.
And they're like, huh?
That's like a real mental screwball right there.
And this is what they've been doing to the public for so long.
They're used to it and they resonate with it.
That's all they do.
So. All right.
Well, I don't know.
Let's just make it a short one.
I just wanted to maybe interject what's going on.
I hope this abatement of Lee is successful.
If it's not, we'll see also. Right.
So we'll definitely see.
And look, there's plenty more fear porn to come anyway,
because we have to get ready for the twenty twenty four events.
I'll close this one by asking you this,
and maybe we'll we'll do it in the future, Sonic.
But in the year that they call twenty twenty four coming up, I've already got
usually people talk about this toward the end of the calendar year.
But I've already got requests from people.
And by the way, I know that some people get get the hell scared out of them
when you start talking about weather on these.
And they've told me that in the distant past, even on previous sides.
There's just a couple of people like, man, he starts talking about whether
I get creeped out.
Look, it is OK. Well, just get a handle on it.
Yeah. Yeah. Get a handle on it.
But, you know, I think in the near future, I might want to ask you about
that calendar year of twenty twenty four, because
I think there's a lot of plans here.
There's a lot going on.
Well, it's going to wrap up what I've been saying about this seven year period,
which ends by twenty twenty five. Right.
That's why I was asking you about it.
So and I recall that this is when certain things should begin.
And you and I started talking about this kind of stuff.
What? Six, seven years ago, where you were telling me all about
a bunch of different events that we're going to begin to really roll out
around that time.
And I'm saying to myself, well, maybe it'll be talk about it soon.
We're here. Yeah.
And well, let's see if it happens. Right.
But the thing that I'm saying is that they will not make sense
and they will be immediate and very fast.
And they'll they'll take place and hold and it'll be seem like it's normal.
And it's it's not normal, you know, just the way things are.
And a lot, I think the people have been primed for that with what's been going on
for the past two or three decades anyway. So.