Ocelli and the Greek rated Y number 16 the sonic event this one is okay put it
into a little a little bit of a different order and I guess the the
Greek says to me wants to recap the last one just a bit and I I think that we're
going to wind up revisiting that subject a bit more in the very near future but
you know the the the Christ concept and that what I always refer to as a
construct but I know it goes a lot further than that and obviously if you
listen to the last one you know but anyway yes so we want to we want to
recap that and then move on to something else so Greek yeah how are you this fine
day doing okay yesterday was like I say in Spanish the 15th and here's the
synchronicity we didn't mention we recorded at least on my end it was what
they call April 15th which has a lot of date other historical memorializations
around it but the 15th is also the day the Christ was born by the way right of
the seventh month right there's a lot of religiosity around there trying to make
their own Christ's you know you've heard of that there's even songs about that
right well yeah and I've also heard about September 11th which septum would
be correct in the seventh month and give or take maybe the 11th wouldn't be too
far off yep it was uh it was the 15th day of the month of the seventh month
around 3 BC but on September 11th as it's reckoned on the Julian Gregorian
calendar because you know how Microsoft runs layers like if you have a
Microsoft computer chances are you're still running protocols from Windows 95
yeah or 98 or 98 you'll see in there sometimes yeah yeah it's still an Emmy
and all this is still running under there that's how the Julian Gregorian
calendar works Julian is basically a day count Gregorian was a monthly count
sort of a monthly count even though it's still considered arbitrary well
without getting into the calendrical yeah September 11th reckoning but
biblically in terms of like a date stamp you the way you do date stamps
chronologically are using astronomical features and secondly would be a feature
that would not change right so it doesn't have to be an astronomical
feature you could pick something else that doesn't change well based on the
geology geographic changes on the earth you know if you look at a map from the
1500s there's no Great Lakes right if you look at the map from the 1500s
Antarctica is not covered with ice yeah I was just yeah I was trying to think
to myself what would be geographically something that doesn't change yeah you
know you're not gonna get it I'm not coming up with anything for 500 years
but but several thousand years you could still rely to a certain point if
you start going back five six thousand years the North Star was different it
wasn't Polaris it was trick it was the draconian Draco which is also a time
when that dragon of old kind of realized the population of humanoid types were
were gaining and eventually they'll stop fighting and work together for a common
reason boy what the what the hell is the Greek talking about okay so so yeah
just go back to what we as those said the sc6 or I'll go different day this is
number 16 so we want to get something different and so let's just say to recap
what it was thinking it's always a question and a subject that's not not
going to go away about the Christ right this is what I have to say about it I
think before we got on I started saying you know here secretly I'll share some
everybody cover your ears I'm looking to meet someone that's like me like the
Greek but not a carbon copy not a clone but someone that's like me so we get
together and jam all right what does that mean so imagine you're Eric Clapton and
you're doing guitar lessons to nine to thirteen year olds and that's all you're
doing you're going to go nuts you want to find a Jimi Hendrix or a Jimmy Page
so on and so and there's some quote-unquote kid in Tennessee right in
the eighth grade that could play guitar that we never heard of they could play
guitar better than all those guys you know what I mean right but we never
heard of them so secretly all right you could ever uncover your ears guys all
right so that's what I'm looking for but at the same time when you start
operating on a certain level in life everything is part of the scenery
there's a level of indifference let it be it's there for a reason right it's a
manifestation it's not a cause all to in itself right like that you know the word
accidents I hate that word because there really isn't an accident if you look at
something that's supposedly random or an accident really really closely you'll
find out so many reasons why it happened that are actually logical and
coherent that that word accident no longer applies you know what I mean so
everything is there for a reason everything's supposed to be that's fine
so everything is part of the scenery and the scenery that I've been discussing
for three decades now is akin to observations of a cult-based society now
does a cult have a number limit on it it's probably if it's what do you gotta
have two or more people three or more people for a cult what do you think a
hundred or more people is no real right no there's no real numerical yeah how
about how about several billion or hundreds of million does that make it
not a cult anymore no the language changes people stop calling it a cult if
it gets big enough but other than that yeah right but I don't know if it's
quite like a ship or you know the difference between a boat and a ship just
the ship is larger right well the real easy way to give it is the way I've
been saying it I used to use that analogy a lot no difference to a boat
in a ship and yeah ship is larger but this is the the underlying concept that
you could put a boat on a ship but you can't put a ship on a boat okay right
you see a big ship you got little lifeboats on it right but you can't put
the Titanic let's say on a lifeboat right so it's in so certain things go
only one way and being happy with that by their description all right so we
have this cult and also you know I'm not going to get I could get into what a
cult is if we were doing the old ONG I probably would right right and probably
come up with some new stuff but essentially one of the most critical
things that you'll notice of a grouping known as a cult the thing that sets it
apart from other groupings haha it really doesn't because they're all cults
right is that you can't question anything and you can't ask for any more
information that's already been given right so if something isn't given it
doesn't exist and if it's an insistence on its production is pursued the
individual insisting on it is ridiculed or eliminated or worse right
marginalized would be a something in between okay so you're living in this
society so the stuff that I've been putting out for all these years publicly
privately in person on the internet whatever before Skype there were
conference calls I don't know if you guys remember that I've got a conference
called number right yep yep and everybody 99 sorry of which 99 people
okay kind of thing and sometimes I get on these early 2000s conference calls
and I announced myself and be someone like you know from the Carolinas Oh the
Greek is the Bible guru I love the Bible guru I was like oh my gosh oh my
gosh you know you know I mean so it's the Bible guru oh my gosh you know it's
like wait okay enjoy the scenery you see what I mean so all right so what happens
here is the efforts that I've been making especially on the last one when
we finished the recording I said you know I kind of let my mind go after I
started stop talking about the building because deliberately I wanted anyone
listening to that to feel annoyed right you know pregnant pauses and just kind of
like oh right because that's what it's a subject that is going to annoy anyone
the reason why it is so is because the cult aspect being aside it's because
it's a it's a subject that is a reflection on one's ability to see
everything as part of the scenery or not go back to what is written by this
individual and by the way there's a lot of spiritual wisdom writings
knowledge writings not information but knowledge I think I covered a little bit
the difference in information and knowledge what easiest way to do that
you have information which could either be a liar or truth right but the lie with
knowledge if you know it's a lie it's the truth now you see what I mean if
you know a lie is a lie is it still a lie well no because it will know because
it informs it but it does inform you because if you're aware of what right it
is then you know where to place it I mean that's the way it is exactly like
the people that believe who shot they told you who shot JFK and what happened
on 9-11 that actually think it's they don't they never really go beyond
thinking if it's true or not they just accept it that's just information but
once you know it's a lie that's the truth of the matter you see so so the
aspect of knowing only has truth by the way information could be you know what
they call misinformation and now with the that disgusting YouTube platform in
Google if you put out anything let's say even licensed doctors can't talk about
what happened on right they say it's medical misinformation right so the
truth is now misinformation right so but you have knowledge of that and the
people of knowledge of that say when you watch a YouTube video don't say this
because I'll get the channel whatever you know nuked or turned or a block to
I don't what they call it strikes or well there's lots of different things that
happen but either way they know that it'll be suppressed yeah yeah so they
know the truth so so so knowledge is only about truth and where information
is not right so what's happening here there are other wisdom writings that you
could find but there's something about what you find whether you I'm not
talking about whether you believe it or not whether it's real or not or whether
it was written by Shakespeare or not or whatever there is a level of wisdom that
wraps around the cortex of the brain or the part of the mind or the part of your
self that is profound when you read for example the being known as the biblical
Christ from the prophetic nature from the prophets all the way to what was
written in the New Testament regardless if it is what it is right so so there's
a so whether you're getting that information from the Bible or the Christ
it doesn't matter right because it's something that has to be known and that's
that's really what it speaks on so here's what I really want to land on the
recap is you have this cult known as humanity and within there you have a
department or a section that is known as religion and this tends to fall within
those categories right right and that goes with everything like if you want to
know again about 9-11 or JFK or how the human body works they tell you go look
at the category of medicine and what you're going to get is major league
bullshit right that's part of the scenery so when you let's say indulge in
Greek speak and you get the hints that I give and you start looking at direction
you see that it's diametrically opposed to what's put out to the rest of the
people well now you're getting knowledge because before you thought the
information was good enough but now you see there there's contrasting
information on the same thing so you're gonna have to figure out on your end
that now you're delving in about knowing not just being informed right so
and that's all I got to say about that on the recap okay I would suggest yeah
I would suggest that uh it's a never-ending subject so why why go why
go down that you either know or you don't know right and and just just to
finish it off like this I'm an Old Testament kind of guy because they
choose to be I never said because it's the only way to be that you ever heard
me say that no never right even if you read the biblical text it tells you if
someone has a certain covenant you know respect it basically right respect it
that they have that covenant but it doesn't mean you're gonna let them walk
in and trample mud into your brand-new carpet right if that's part of their
covenant right no no for instance look I mean you're just real basic all right
somebody chooses to live in in such a way that they are barefoot everywhere
they go well that's that's fine that's their way of choosing to live but when
they when they come to your house and you say this is a note take your shoes
off and cut before you come in there and you have their shoes up but here's the
reason why you tell people to take their shoes off before they come in so they
don't trample the stuff that was on the sheet but now they're barefoot they
don't come inside at all till they wash their feet and correct that's where
they don't have shoes to take off right see the reason you have a no-shoe house
is to keep the street out of the house but so that's another perspective that
makes that to me being barefoot is not good but you know what I go sometimes
several days without wearing shoes because I want to be grounded right as a
matter of fact if you have minor pains aches health issues I'm gonna say it
works for everyone go ahead if you're living in Canada where they have like
nine months of snow or ten months of snow or whatever I don't know you might
adjust if you're if you eat enough pine needles and burdock but what I'm saying
if I have any minor quote-unquote discomforts if I walk barefoot for three
days I'm talking winter time too they go away goes away my fortitude and my
strength inner strength and physical strength goes up marketably enough to
say that it'll help by doing that well you know I have chronic pain and to be
honest with you sometimes when that becomes particularly intense I do find
it useful for a couple of days at about the beginning of the day the truthful
beginning of the day around that solar noon time if the grass is available if I
can just go and walk in the grass barefoot and kind of just stand there I
don't have to do anything other than it is it is helpful it it it turns it down
it doesn't get rid of it it's not like a cure-all or anything but it does allow me
to have greater control over the pain level throughout the rest of the day if
I start my day that I give a real interject a short interjection if you go
into biology class 101 and University I don't know if they still do this this is
stuff that I studied 40 years ago they get into what's called protozoa just
protozoa study you know which is single-celled organisms and you have to
bring in your own samples and what they direct students on doing for amoebas is
you get some grass and you put it in a jar of water clean water rainwater
distilled water you wait three days you take the water out filter it and got
your amoebas right right but here's the thing no matter how close you look at
regular grass before you put it in the water and the water that you put the
grass in there's no amoebas present anywhere right but they never tell
people that the amoebas are actually let's say the genesis of the amoeba comes
from cut plants or especially grass a monocot in water they're generated out
of nothing and amoebas are their own distinct life-form it's not like right
you know part of the grass it's completely different than the grass and
the water right you see so when you're stepping on the grass that energy that
forms the amoeba will help perhaps stimulate cell formation in the body I
suggest that you walk on gravel dry gravel wet gravel doesn't matter dry
gravel is better because the piezoelectric effect most gravel has
enough quartz in it you know that crunchy sound you hear when you're
walking on gravel and if you're not used to it you're like oh oh you know even if
it's rounded gravel because each one forms like this little massage section
in the bottom of your foot and remember each one of your feet is taking half
your body weight or your full body weight when you're walking right right
crunching that quartz together if you know piezoelectrics is you know you
don't know what it is do this but don't do this because anytime you buy a
blender they have that red octagon we talked about yesterday on the I've seen
that by the way on instruction manuals now you open it and they have a red sign
it says stop on it right I don't know if you've ever seen that recently in
printers and things get yourself yeah get yourself a blender and you'll see the
red stop sign on the instruction don't do this and they show you the blender
with sugar cubes in it a lot of times you want to tell you don't do it do it you
know it's just like people that were anti-depressants have a orange sticker do
not take with alcohol you ever see that right it's really bright dang you know
caution really I said oh you know that means you got to take you let me get a
couple of these you got to take when we have alcohol here we definitely have to
take it with alcohol right because they don't want you to have a good time just
like they they tell you red meats bad for you why cuz it's delicious when it's
charbroiled right yeah I think they have to stop putting those I think they have
to stop putting those orange stickers on the painkiller bottles actually yeah
that's right because they figured out that no one's watching it when they see
it it actually means get the alcohol all right so what you do is you get the
blender and you put sugar cubes in it turn off all the lights if it's if you
can't go into the closet and close the door or put it in the cabinet close the
door with a camera hit the go button low medium high and it will be a light
show not because it's sugar it's because it's in a crystalline form when those
crystals are smashed have you ever seen there's a YouTube video sugar cubes in a
in a blender I never seen it no I haven't oh yeah it's kind of like you
know those ultraviolet lights those purple black lights yeah and white
lights right yeah lights up like that it looks like a lava lamp but you know with
sparks yeah okay and that's sugar cubes right and that's a blender imagine you're
walking on gravel what it's doing right and also that electric field that
develops pumps goes down into the earth and the earth reciprocates reflex right
just like pushing on a waterbed okay you push down on one side it push comes up
on another and then when you let go comes up where you pushed it right
complex electrical fields you can measure up to 2,500 volts walking on
gravel okay right at a low current so barefoot can't take the shoes off to
come in the house washing washing your feet we're gonna talk about hygiene
what's is the third time's a charm we taught tried maybe two or three times
already that's true but yeah okay but let's but let's let's just cut to the
chase right and like you say all the time why not give the important part
first in case the battery dies on the cell phone yeah it's yeah ultimately it
has nothing to do with anything physical you're not going to quote-unquote be a
bathing or washing away anything that is physically been told to you that causes
harm organic or inorganic it's a state of being it's it's an independent state
is what it is so people get sick and they're looking for a bug that caused it
right well the presence of the bug is not what causes it right because first
of all if you pick up a certain pathogen in the inside the blood of the they say
we did a blood test we found this right right that means the body created it
unless it was directly injected into the body you know hypodermic Lee right so if
the body creates it well your own body it's your own damn fault then right so
what happens when you have let's say E.coli or something in the blood those
are not harmful it sounds crazy right what is harming you is that E.coli being
a living organism eats and poops right okay okay so you when you have a garden
and you have a goat if you let the goat go in the garden for a few days and you
come back on your way to the garden you're gonna see these little pellets
everywhere they look like little brown pellets right and you're gonna go and
you see your gardens gone it's missing what happened to the garden well the
pellets are what the goat makes right and the the poop and the garden is gone
because it's what the goat eats right so you got E.coli let's say what they
identify as E.coli in the body it eats doesn't it yeah so what is it eating
things in its indirect environment and then it after it eats what does it do
that's to get rid of the waste product right so what it ate has an effect on
the body right what it removed took away right the actual digestion process
has an effect on the body then the poop that's eliminated into the body has an
effect on the body right because most things inside a waste are not alive
although sometimes there are things that seem to be alive it could be it on
another level it is yeah okay we'll talk about silent spaces maybe if we could we
have time sure this is gonna be a short one folks okay so it's not the bug the
presence of the bug it's what it does and doesn't do and when it's finishes
when it finishes doing what it's doing that you have the illness but remember
if you have anything found in the blood the body created it right right so this
is basically it so in a sense that in a sense give it another analogy there's a
couple and I know them very well and they know Greek speak very very well and
he never gets sick winter summer whatever and she always gets sick in the
winter right and he's always telling her did you wash your hands or when she does
something with food or whatever she leaves a little bit of a mess a little
bit of a mess you know or when she goes out and whatever she'll come inside and
you know not you know be conscious of it and she's she constantly gets sick
every winter just about and he doesn't and it's they both shower twice a day or
once a day they both have similar hygiene general hygiene habits but one
gets sick and the other one doesn't almost like clockwork and when the the
guy it stays really on top almost from a nagging perspective on her she doesn't
she happens to skip a year and not get sick because it's not the major things
laundry and washing your hands when they're dirty or whatever but it's the
real minor minor minor intricacies of hygiene that makes her susceptible to
getting colds that last for weeks and months and he does you see because
typically when you tell someone to go wash up or have to wash up there is a
visible presence or noticeable presence of a requirement to do so right that's
pretty obvious like today I was working on some stuff I said I got grease on the
keyboard shucks you know right but you know right so yeah that's noticeably
right the stuff I want to talk about on hygiene is the stuff that's not noticeable
and what's not noticeable is the interaction that we have as a living
being that has other living beings that have other living beings when other
living beings inside of them like the Russian dolls right and there's a chain
reaction that sets off whether they're all going to behave and you're going to
live peacefully or whether you're going to be in trouble or one of the orc
because by the way when the E.coli is thriving if you asked if you interviewed
the E.coli how are you doing they're sitting we're doing great now let's zoom
out and interview the person who's got that ask them how are they doing they're
gonna say feel like shit right right so so one of them is in harmony and the
other one's not so it's about keeping everything in harmony because you know
there's so you could go look I remember it was real spooky in the 70s on the
science magazines they would show these creatures that look like they're from
outer space on a smooth wrinkly surface almost like a crater and you saw like
something look like a look like a stalk or a trunk of a tree coming up and you're
like what the hell is that and say that's your skin magnified and that's a
dust mite living on your skin remember that right right yeah and so you can't
get rid of those actually the more you wash the moisture and heat makes them
grow even more I was like ah right enough to make you crazy right so it's
not the presence of it it's what condition it's in is if it's working and
are you actually creating them there was a TV show in the 70s if I remember where
the guy ends up going into the shower and they get they tell him exactly that
and he ends up smacking his skin all over the place trying to just yes in some
cases it's for some people if they can't handle it's better that they don't know
it right right so I mean think about the information that's that's the thing
that's where faith and knowledge also is another thing I talked about
information but faith you notice there's a modality in society they everything is
done on faith the money the science like trust the seance I mean trust the
science and all this other stuff it's all based on faith you can take you
expect me to take it on faith alone yes absolutely right so when then when it
comes up to matters of faith what kind of quality information you think you're
gonna get on that no good because everything else is fake I still can't
believe by the way we're talking about hygiene that in this day and age I grew
up hearing that that people still think they absorb I mean no one is really okay
all right everybody just take a break I just take a break for a minute because I
just got hit with something that I you know let me put it this way how many
people don't have access to what anatomy looks like like cross-section
of intestines cross-section of skin walking through like I think high
school biology they have posters where they show the cross-sections of these
things right of course medical or everywhere everywhere and it's studied
why isn't there at least a small movement of people saying that hey how
does anything go through that there's no way why why isn't there like need I say
one other person saying that what's going on here but I said just had a
moment it's like if I can't if I don't spend 99% of my energy holding my
mentality together I'd go insane if I focused on that right you see what I
mean okay anyway let's just jump out of that because it is insane it is
completely insane how that's not being discussed or anyway and by the way
one I'm sorry the same conundrum I face all the time though when with the pieces
of paper you know why does this have value okay I get what it symbolizes but
in reality the thing in and of itself doesn't have value it's a piece of
paper you know well no the paper could be fine because you know you can get a
piece of paper that says that you just got five numbers in a row and you could
go pick up your $350,000 prize yeah but that's because it represents
something else it's you know but there you go exactly it's really the
merchants fault it's up to the merchants to educate give you an example the
education's end time in history is never done in the schools you know I'll give
you a quote who said this everything taught in school is a lie Socrates said
that 2,500 years ago okay so I don't want to hear about people saying how since
Ronald Reagan the education system has gone down it's kind of propaganda is that
right so anyway it's the merchants because back in the days you got
information on the market you ever heard he's getting on a soapbox right yeah
that's at the market because when you the soap maker showed up everybody went
and bought the soap and boxes empty boxes on the floor you pile stack them
up and you rise slightly above head level so people could hear you right
it's because the soap maker sold out first right okay is because it was yeah
it was not like common anyway so many things came to mind just with the soap
maker there but get it the subject design okay so yeah so uh so these
things like the couple that one gets sick the other one does it they both
have observably similar hygiene levels but it's not enough for one to stay to
avoid quote-unquote yearly cold let's say that lasts for weeks basically look
the act of induction has to do with what it is that you're involving yourself
with right this is how this fits together in my mind is that yes and so
what what you choose to interact with causes induction to occur that's what
the bottom line is whether you take it in it goes in the body now you're
interacting with it in an intimate way intimate right but if not the things
that you're encountering one way or another all together whether it's the
air or the people or whatever sure these things all it's induction it's contact
but but try to try to attach it conjunct it with dwell time certain things have
an immediate dwell time contact time other things have a longer dwell time in
order for it to induce just like the induction stovetop you know the glass
stovetop pot of boiling water the pot of boiling water put your hand right on
the stovetop it's room temp put the ball pot right over it starts boiling again
but if it hadn't gotten to that boiling how long even with an induction top you
put you know tap water or room temperature water in a pot you don't
turn it on and it starts boiling immediately you have to wait the dwell
time of induction for it to get to that temperature okay so there's an aspect of
that as well not never discussed right so you get poop on you dog poop on your
shoe it will get into your blood if you leave it on there long enough even though
it's on your shoe quote unquote a barrier right because of the depends on
the object to what kind of a field effect does it have I think we spoke about how
people think neodymium magnets the really strong ones are better and depends
on what you're doing they're so strong because they have a
condensed field density and it's very small around the magnet but it's very
powerful once you get into it it's the cheap ferrite magnets whose field
actually goes far beyond the body of the magnet that is actually more usable for
water you see so you have to comprehend what you know again you know saying
neomagnets or dog poo or whatever an initial reaction is again borrowed from
what you've seen other people say and all you have to do is fool a few people
as long as they're sociable and good communicators you'll have the entire
society saying what they say in no time right right pretty much I remember that
with back in the 80s Jenny Hilfiger her brother's Tommy Hilfiger she they
thought she was going to be the big designer should put up all this clothes
and stuff and I've go down to Times Square people that were very not just
look good like models and hang out in Times Square and the thing was you just
didn't have to be quote-unquote good-looking like a fashion model you
also had to be a good communicator so when some thought someone asked you
something you would convey enthusiasm you'd be good communicating to where
they could where they should look forward so they can't forget no don't
forget the name and tell your friends you have to be a good communicator to
convey all these points in a very short interaction right so I've seen that for
also people promoting clubs back in the day in New York you gave you put out
these things called flyers right or concerts you know small and you just
didn't give them I mean you wanted them out there in society but it was a plus
and a real plus if you found someone who was a good communicator so not only
did they hand you the flyer but they are all actually to make you feel
enthusiastic about it right right and this is the mechanism that's being used
against you with information and there's no mechanism as such regarding knowledge
so back to the hygiene and the dwell time in the contact yeah the induction
is everything is touching everything let's just think of it this way you
hear people say oh you know I can do someone who had skin problems and kind
of looked at and said you know what you need more time in the Sun they were
terrified they were like no no going in the Sun causes skin cancer right where
do you think they got that from if that were true 90% of the population would
have been gone 90 years ago because 90% of the population spent 90% of
the time in the Sun 90 years ago right so regardless so anyway person goes in
the Sun and they get that solar energy we're no matter whether you think it's
just right above in the sky really small or 900 million miles whatever they tell
you 9 mean 80 million whatever yeah it doesn't matter you see it you're still
getting it and you know basically cleared up on them right so you're
touching the air which is touching the rocks which is you know everything is
touching something else because it's proven that air can act as a solid if
you're moving fast enough go down a car I roll down the window in a car that's
going you know 100 kilometers an hour and stick your palm out forward you feel
a force right right pushing it back right or sailboats or whatever sail the
size of sails are designed by you know how much the boat weighs and that's how
much air will catch right and so it'll counteract right so all these things have
mass and weight and are capable of inducing I think Chuck you said the air
very much so and like sunlight and all any anything you can imagine the humidity
in the air here's another thing the the water droplets in the air they're not
gas by the way water does not have a gas phase I heard people say water has three
phases liquid solid gas it does not have a gas phase there's a vapor phase it's
the only it's the only element understanding call it a compound it's an
element that cannot be sublimated sublimated means turned to a gas you
know like carbon for example sublimates goes from solid to gas but there is a
gel state they never talk about okay so hygiene what where where is the subtle
the real subtle aspects first of all it's a there is a mental aspect to it
that one must decide whether they want to lead a clean life which is when I
bring up I'm an Old Testament person to someone who's semi-educated as one
older woman and she says yeah my grandmother and my mother always wanted
us to eat clean when I told her I was an Old Testament kind of person so right
away she referred she got that as clean food you know and you know the diet what
dietary recommendations are in the Old Testament right right so it doesn't mean
you know clean the way we I mean what a cow you could have cow goat sheep and all
that but choose the cut right but cow could be dirty what is what you can have
a steak and drop it on the floor it's no longer you know it's we mean clean what
does that mean clean in in the Quranic let's say Islamic cognate it would be
considered permissible not clean it would be called halal where unclean they don't
say that it would be unpermissible which would be haram right so they don't use
that term so if there's a way to get away from discussing hygiene clean and
unclean you notice I haven't used those terms right but essentially that's what
it is there is a state of mind that one must have that the only way this is what
I've noticed all these years the only way one can achieve good mental hygiene
physical hygiene spiritual hygiene is that is through an indifferent approach
that you view everything happening around you as part of some kind of a
surrounding that has to be but it doesn't mean you don't have to influence
it okay right and it works this way let's say you want to go to a roller
coaster ride and they stop you and they say you have to wait for the next one
this one's full okay or you have another occasion where you go to the roller
coaster ride and they say okay come sit down but the moment you sit down they put
that rope chain across and they say okay that's it ready to go everyone's on and
you're the last one to get on the road right right or how about you go to the
roller coaster ride and you're the first one on there and you're sitting there
while you get your seat waiting for it to load up completely you see all the
different possibilities with the same roller coaster ride sure right and then
there's a point where you can say I'm never gonna go on that thing they make
makes me miserable right and still observe all those conditions or not so
there are so many I gave that as a because that's how I am I would never go
on any of those rides they make me miserable if it had a steering wheel I
might right I used to hang out with skydivers and they're like oh yeah well
just you could do it for free you want you know I said no why would I engage in
something that makes me miserable why intentionally I know it makes me
that's like oh yeah but all the cool kids are doing it go ahead stay cool you
know okay so viewing everything as scenery and objective also gives you
more clear head clear thinking give me an example you have someone a certain
personality or approach oh my gosh I'm dirty oh I gotta wash this off wash it
off wash it off wash it off oh maybe I gotta watch it again watch it again I
think get it off hey you know what I mean yeah a neurotic kind of thing do
you think they're gonna maintain hygiene no matter how hard they try
you know they can't because there's no way they can't no matter what they do
they're gonna wind up dirty so in their nose right now by the way the recording
the Skype is that we're reconnecting so I don't know if you could hear me or not
you probably could I can hear you fine you're fine okay yeah because I have a
big screen and a tone that's telling me that it's reconnecting so I'm gonna keep
speaking no interruption other than what I just said so you heard me you hear me
give the impression of a very nervous person do you think that they could wash
and have the best hygiene in the world do you think they're gonna be helpful or
have a healthy appearance no my answer was no because they're in a constant
state of believing yeah that they're not yep so yeah yeah or their approach to
the hygiene is actually making them more unclean than they were before you see
what I mean now here you got these children you know between let's say five
and nine years old at a first time at a farm and they're running around and you
call them in for lunch and here comes the boy he's barefoot he's got mud all
the way up to his knee on one leg the girl's got mud on her dress and dirt on
her face and all that are they unclean are they dirty no you see what I mean
they just need to be washed off a little bit or you know it's a big difference is
so so how do you approach the hygiene if you view your surroundings as constantly
being dirty you're going you're not going to do well either but you know
what there's a fine balance where they are right depending on what you want to
do and what you're going to prepare yourself for for example if you're going
to lay down and sleep your bedclothes you know you spend one-third of your
life sleeping let's say generally you know and right now for me it's about a
quarter of my life could you know divide the day right how many hours I sleep
let's say I try to get it down to less than that but it's you know so anyway
your bedclothes sheets and all that should be clean I used to wash them every
other day everything just goes right in the laundry so you have four or five sets
right you just keep them rotating sure that's a pretty whatever it's just like
to think think of your bed sheets and your clothing as very similar to your
clothes the clothes that you wear you know I mean sometimes I wear from
welding and hammering on stuff I wear the same jeans for a couple days but I
don't keep wearing them to where they're so stiff I take them off and they stand
up on the corner by themselves right or they smell bad right so consider your
bedclothes your towels things that you come in contact with and all that as
being fresh and clean most people of course you know know this but I'm
leading somewhere else with this one one thing would be a disservice to talk to
speak on hygiene without mentioning basic hygiene protocols where they
involve soap right I want to just say this several examples I've been around
quote-unquote by the way let me just put this out because the mindset is
important if you ask me what a version of hell would be for me is to live in to
spend the rest of my life for a week living with a middle class or upper
middle class or even better than that or whatever it doesn't matter
Midwest American white family would be a nightmare for me because of the culture
right I would much rather be around with Polynesian cannibals that I warded off
and told them that I was the wrong blood type or whatever right okay it is a
complete nightmare to be around quote-unquote white American people
because of the level of brainwashing that they have everything they say and
think comes from the TV culture or school university church kind of culture it's
all the same it's all exactly that you know they're all in agreement right
right of course yeah they're all in a hundred percent agreement so give an
example once this is not everyone but this is just an example it's very
typical boys having a bowl of cereal spills it the mom wipes it up the chunks
of the cereal and the milk and then she goes under the sink and pulls out a
bottle of what's called fantastic all-purpose cleaner sprays the table
down well it still has setting of other people eating and wipes it I was like oh
my gosh she just chemical bombed the kitchen right no regard because she's
been told that whatever it needs to be clean and she has been brainwashed right
that you do you see the picture you know again yeah I don't know if you ever
sprayed that stuff those household cleaners what it smells like and what it
is right yeah it goes everywhere while you're eating okay so I just want to
bring that up as an example because this is more common see I thought that
was a very unusual it's happened many years ago but it's not it's very typical
it's very common but I'm very common what I want to suggest though since the
spray bottle was brought up whenever you're using soaps that you buy and
purchase whether it's laundry soap anything that's in a liquid not a bar or
powder dilute it several reasons why they're always concentrated now when I
said all the soaps are always concentrates not as much as laundry soap
like when you buy a gallon of laundry soap there's only about two tablespoons
of real detergent in there the rest of it is fillers and water and the reason
they do that is because that industrial detergent is so powerful that if they
sold you a small container instead of the gallon and told you to put two drops
in a big tub of water how many people would really do that some people would
say look at this tiny little container I think I got to put the whole thing in
the washtub right they'll never be able to wash it away those commercial laundry
soaps have a tiny amount of real detergent in them the same thing with
liquid bleach it's only 2% sodium hypochlorite right if they sold you
sodium hypochlorite real bleach in a gallon that would be enough for ten
families for a year if they used it every day you know what would happen
very dangerous same with hydrogen peroxide and all these things the reason
I'm saying to digest all to digest to dilute all of your other soaps is
because they buy in bulk and if they and they're selling you a concentrate even
though it's been diluted from an industrial purpose perspective it's when
you buy it it's still a concentrate because if they made it less concentrated
now the cost of the shipping is more than the cost of the package and also
they'll be buying less of it in bulk and the price will actually go up right
so you think most people say well if they made it more dilute the price should go
down no actually it'll go up because now they're just cost all their cost is in
shipping and they're not going to get as good of a price because you see what I
mean kind of goes in reverse at a certain point so okay that's one point
dilute all that stuff because the more diluted is easier the less water also
you're gonna need to wash it off and wash it away give you an example what I
do here one instead of going into the the dynamics on how I got into this
conversation how important it is because I see examples constantly around me
I want to just bring up what I do and in this case do what the Greek does right
a lot of times I tell people don't do what I would do right you'll get in
trouble sometimes I just do what I would do right and in this case do what I would
do what I do is whenever I have any kind of a liquid soap in a bottle with a cap
I immediately replace it with a spray and they're all number 28 threads pretty
much okay yeah the 28 bottle cap right okay and dollar store or real cheap
spray don't get find out which spray nozzle works for you okay so I have a
hydrogen peroxide bottle I use that a lot for cleaning you know the woman with
the fantastic on the breakfast show because the milk it gets sour you want
to clean it right right right I use hydrogen peroxide for that it has to be
in a dark container so let's say the pet throws up I grab of inside the house or
something I grab a plastic bag wrap it around my hand with a paper towel so when
I pick up the stuffed paper towel I have the paper the plastic bag as a barrier
wrapped around my hand another plastic bag ready to go I spray with what the
other hand hydrogen peroxide over the area right it's an oxidizer and see if
things foam up or not you wipe it down and you wipe it again and now you have
plastic bags to go throw away outside by the way your inside garbage can is not
magic if you have a cigarette ashtray or pet vomit or poop or bad food stuff
you don't put it in your kitchen wastebasket it's not like this container
that if you put it there it's gone forever no it's still in your house
outside outside with all that stinky stuff and stuff that's very active
active garbage okay if you have to keep active garbage empty containers in the
house give them a little short rinse or spray peroxide or whatever the other
thing to do is if let's say you have a milk container and it's got to be
inside in the garbage when it's empty just squeeze the bottle and before you
let go of the bottle put the cap on so when you tighten the cap on as it tries
to expand what does it do inside the bottle tries to create a vacuum so it
won't expand keep expanding it'll expand within its own sphere and the vacuum
prevents things from growing okay so it'll be much fresher than if you just
put the lid on a few days later you try to open it it's like all these
toxic gases come out right oh absolutely yeah I do that just to save space but yeah
but it has the same effect yeah it's for from a sanitary point of view as the
bottle tries to expand well it will it's in a vacuum you know so it'll keep
self-contained it won't be gases trying to escape in the room so I use the
hydrogen peroxide very often in the kitchen let's say I did some food prep
and I've got like a butcher block countertop on one side a ceramic on the
other I've got a sink or whatever the spray either on the cloth I use
microfiber cloths cut in quarter quarters as a washcloth or on directly
on the counter and wipe the hydrogen peroxide with water right and that's I
don't use a commercial soap that Johnson & Johnson sells or whatever there's no
the hydrogen peroxide is a form of water by the way right it's very clean this
doesn't leave a residue doesn't have a fragrance doesn't cause cancer right on
and on and on very very clean it's also a very powerful oxidizer right okay so
the other thing dishwash soap get the stuff that doesn't have fragrance if you
have the stuff that has fragrance mix it slightly with the one that doesn't have
fragrance there are seventh generation I think is a brand they're all over the
world fragrance free dishwash soap what that does is if you have soap dishwash
soap that has a fragrance in it you'll notice that when you're done with your
dishes and drying them or whatever they there's a slight fragrance on the dish
still right yeah and it will it affects the flavor of food and all that that's
why if I go to someone's house and I bring a sample of water and they give
me a glass I pour a little bit of my water in their glass shake it around and
dump it out so what you do that for to get the soap out there's no soap in my
glass you know I'm like yeah there is you know I take it as a presumption so
what I found is I have for mechanical work dawn or equivalent dollar store
equivalent is just as good for cutting grease if you ever been to a mechanic
shop you'll see they have commercial dishwash liquid everywhere yeah right
because it cuts grease really well and it was a marvel that it came out and
became popular in 70s this is the fragrance in there will not be relieved
but I found that if I have what they call the natural vegetable based soaps with
no scent I have a container of water where I first you put your I put equal
parts of the non scented soap with the scented soap and then I into the water
that's already in the container you want to add it to water if you add the water
after it'll foam up you won't succeed in getting any water in there so always add
your soaps concentrates to water I noticed that if I do that it prevents the
scent from the scented soap to migrate and linger and it actually washes it
away so what I do for dishwash soap is I have a spray bottle that I fill 75% of
the way up with water and then I add the two different types of soap and not even
a quarter teaspoon of each and that and so instead of adding typically like you
see people add dishwash soap to a rag or a brush never do that I have it already
pre-diluted in a spray bottle and what's great about that if you have a
sink full of dishes and they're rinsed you got the spray bottle to spray the
dishwash soap on all of them and get to work without the tap running right mm-hmm
see how convenient it is and and by the way this this you will if you buy a
dishwash soap or whatever size every month or every so often you'll be buying
it only twice a year now and you'll get things just as clean so the soap if I
start promoting this the soap mafia which I'm sure exists yeah won't like it
right okay so you're gonna save on soaps now so far we haven't left the kitchen
there's something called borax 40 40 mule power it's a born aided yeah soap
it's mineral soap okay I can't extol the virtues of it enough you can even take
it internally the stuff that they sell in the car in the box right is in turn you
can take it it's pure enough it has some calcium residue in it I've said it
doesn't have heavy metals it doesn't have any zinc it doesn't have the reason
why I'm saying is in other countries where they do have a borax type solution
I found zinc and other things in it that might be toxic but the one that you get
here basically it's the mind in Nevada the borax some people take it a small
amount of it in water and it says it gives them a lot of mental clarity and I
did research it and some people say yeah it does open up blockers in the
brain and things like that so I more power to you so what I do is I have a
half-gallon container that was like from cranberry juice or something or some
orange juice from ten years ago I saved those you got it if you guys know what
polyethylene bottles are the ones that coke bottles and the soda bottles come
in yeah okay those are five layers of plastic it's you know when you buy
distilled water or a milk container it's not really see-through it's that soft
plastic that's single-layer low-density polyethylene the Pepsi and the coke
bottles are supposed to hold 300 pounds pressure and they're five layers of
polyethylene and it's it's really clear very very strong and they don't break
down in the Sun if you leave it in the Sun and squeeze it'll make our squishy
sound you'll see the layers delaminating by the way that's what train cars are
made of that's why I gave the analogy if you're if you got a two liter of coke in
your shopping bag and you walk into the house and it falls and it's the sidewalk
you just pick it up put it right in the bag it might dent but it doesn't ever
explode or pop open I've seen them run over by cars and they didn't explode as
long as the cap holds on that's how the railroad cars are made so when you hear
of a spill well you know anyway I've got one of those bottles and I've got some
water filled up with water with let's say a half gallon of it gets a half a
cup of borax powder and I shake it up and I keep it under the sink so remember
when I said earlier I put diluted dishwash liquid in a spray bottle well
the water base was that diluted it wasn't water from the tap or filtered
water it was water with borax in it it could be two tablespoons to a quart or a
half a cup to a gallon play around with it don't shake it up if you if you're
going to pour it into a spray bottle and you take it out from under where you
have it in storage pre-mixed make sure the sediment stays on the bottom don't
shake it up and then pour it in it'll clog your sprayer and you won't be able
to unclog your sprayer you have to throw it away so if you see sediment on the
bottom of a pre diluted borax solution don't shake it until you're finished
using it so let's say I have the half gallon bottle under the sink and I pour
that into my dishwash spray bottle I don't agitate it I just want the clear
liquid that's on top and now when I'm done pouring in my spray bottle I
noticed the level has gone down significantly I go to my tap and
replenish it you could replenish it three or four times before you have to
add more borax to it when you replenish it put the lid on and shake it up you'll
it'll look like one of those snow globes in there you know all the stuff settling
and flying sorry leave it under the counter wherever you have it and that is
a wonderful wonderful clean now I don't need to get into boronated water but by
the way where they blow the nukes and they tell people it was a terrorist right
you'll notice that they where they had the underground nuclear in a pot they
put a memorial and it usually has a water pool like the one in the Murrow
building in Oklahoma City yeah they have a pool there they also have a pool
there's one place in I think in Middle East they said it was a car bomb they
now have a pool as a memorial there there's a reflecting pool at 9-11 there's
a reflecting pool at they're proposing another one at the Kennedy site by the
way oh well I don't know if they blew a nuke there but they recently blew a nuke
at a cow ranch by the way a dairy cow ranch they killed 18,000 cows you see
that explosion you know how you know it's a nuke a micro nuke it said you
have what's called a pyroclastic flow just look up pyroclastic flow it does
not happen with standard chemical explosions anyway yeah by the way we
never got into how the Boston bombing was to take the new movie the attention
away from the fire at the library at the Kennedy Library did we ever get into
that no I don't think we did yeah okay all right so they that water that's in
this a reflection pools is boronated water so in case there's a leak of
radon gas coming through at high pressure that smells real bad it'll
smell like chlorine gas which they did have a leak like that at 9-11 by the way
a few years ago it's a really bad smell coming out World Trade Center area what
it smell like like really strong chlorine gas that's ionized radon gas that could
kill you by the way mm-hmm yeah so they that's boronated water all those pools
have boronated water because it has it has an ability and affinity for what
we're talking about here to absorb that real nasty stuff okay so that's pretty
much a basic hygiene protocol because you know it's really hard to discuss
hygiene it's the consciousness of hygiene and everything that you do
actually without bringing up use the use of soaps and I know just about everyone
who is listening to me majority are using soaps the way they come in
packages right you can dilute laundry soap just dilute it all right and the
only thing I have to say about bar soap ever is don't drop it so anyway yeah
that's it and so all the liquid soaps dilutes shampoos now they're very
technical if some shampoos especially the high-end ones if you add water you
ruin the formulation too much water won't work and they might you might get
get separation a lot of them have certain things that need to remain in
suspension if you add water you'll notice it to start separating and it's
not a good thing especially if you're spending like $50 for an 8 ounce bottle
of shampoo and by the way that might sound unnecessary but a $50 8 ounce
bottle of shampoo is worth every penny I'm telling you just like I think you
and I was talking yesterday I'm working on this amp and it sounds like a Krell
KSA 50 we're looking at Krell amps and they're like 30 grand and I said you
know what it sounds expensive but it's worth every penny it's kind of hard to
tell people that want one and can't afford it or don't want to afford it
because you can't afford it if you work on three jobs for a year right yeah well
in certain things like the Bugatti Veyron is another car it's a three
million dollar car but it's worth every penny why because it goes from zero to a
hundred back to zero in five seconds right most people don't they only tell
you goes from zero to fifty or zero to a hundred how about no I used to I
remember being around people souping up cars I'm like yeah for it's fast but how
does it stop oh we had a real problem we felt we're gonna die I said see see if I
were to soup up a car I'd do it all on paper and the first thing I started would
start wrenching on is the brakes before I did the engine to get a brake system
that would be compatible and the Bugatti Veyron is the only one that can
do that zero to a hundred back to zero in five seconds right so so it's worth
every penny there's nothing else that can do that not even close so there's
certain things that sound exorbitant and if we lived in a different society we
wouldn't see it as you went oh I want that I can't afford it wouldn't be that
way and it would be you would just make one yourself or know someone that makes
something like that or it wouldn't be just this one so I wanted to bring up
the soap thing because I know it's something that sits in the bottom of my
back of my head I have never been to anyone's house by the way that handles
soaps and solutions the way I do and also has sharp knives in other words if
I go to anyone's house and I recall neither what they call the food prep
area and ask them where they keep their knives none of them are sharpness
serrated edge knives are not considered sharp knives they're serrated edge
knives right okay and if you use that and you think you're happy because it
cuts everything your cutting board looks like the fuzzy dice people hang on their
rearview mirrors on those hot rod cars you know I'm talking about you will not
have anything that looks like a cutting board it looks like faux fur okay and
that's really nasty so for obvious reasons hey I've got faux fur as a
cutting board you want to come over and eat no really here's another thing we're
gonna do one on food but this I'm very well known for this if you invite me okay
when I first met my wife we were still dating yeah meet at 6 o'clock to have
dinner and I show up at 5 to 6 and we had to go somewhere else because you're
almost late or I was 5 after 6 and she says you're late what were you doing I
said I had something to eat and she goes what we're going up for dinner how dare
you have something to eat I said you'll see and we went over I never knew these
people but I said who are they Mexican Italian white Chinese versus they're
white okay I ain't no white people's house so anyway we get there you know
American white you know and or English white in England I wouldn't do that
either or whatever you know so we get there and like an hour like we leave how
do you feel she goes oh I feel kind of bloated I don't feel that good having a
more time she goes I think you're right yeah this is by the way this is normal
you know how many Rolaids and Pepto-Bismol commercials were beat you
know everywhere how many even now if you turn on television how many indigestion
and stomach problem right you're gonna get right commercials for drugs for that
right never addressing the real reason right right the other thing is when I
used to get invited to white people house for dinner let's say invite me over at
5 o'clock I show up at 4 o'clock with a bag on my side in my bag there's a
cutting board my knife some seasonings that I use and salts and things like that
right so I have two bags one you know I'm a
gracious guest you always have to you know give something as a guest you know a
bottle of wine or some desserts or something right the other she goes
what's that and I said you know I show up early you're kind of early and yeah
thank you very much for this bag what's that yeah where's the kitchen where's
the kitchen I say where's the kitchen like well why just sit down a living
room we'll have dinner ready in about an hour when everybody gets here I said
no no where's the kitchen let me see the kitchen I said what are you making what
are you making oh yeah why don't you want to sit down in the living room okay
this is what you want to make time okay let me see what you got and I start
cooking and making the meal myself I spend the first 10 minutes making it
getting it hygienically correct by the way you know they'll be like a potted
plant in the corner on the countertop and you know pot of plants that had that
little district just strain underneath to you know the little dish if you take
that dish out hold it to your nose it smells like puke right because that's
what plants do plants love that you know if you put plants and shit they thrive
right and if you don't put plants and shit they create their own shit right I
don't know if you're familiar with this but anyway I take the potted plant and I
put it on a chair all the way off to the side so no one sits on it and I wipe
that area with hydrogen peroxide and I start wiping the whole countertop down
right and and get things ready and I make dinner and everyone loves it now at one
time I got busted and my wife also she still laughs about it I went over it we
were invited to someone's house and woman's name was Sandra and Eric anyway
it was really cute I showed up early I said where's the kitchen and she says I
know what you're doing you're gonna sit down I know what you do you're gonna try
over here and try to cook my meal but I'm gonna make my meal right and I was
really proud of her being confident she knew that you know word got around that
if you invite me over to dinner I'm gonna show up early and I'm gonna cook it
right okay so but she did the right thing I critiqued it I critiqued certain
things I said is it clean in there you know and I'm not you notice how I'm not
I don't sound like who was it the odd couple Felix or whatever he was the
hypochondriac you know right he ever touched anything with a handkerchief I'm
not like that at all right if I see children on a farm playing in the dirt
in the mud and by the way you know cow patties are sterile right you know cow
and horse patties are in war times of war if you someone had an injury and it
was going to go infected you took cow patty or horse patty and put it right
on the injury right because the as urea in there that sterilizes prevents
anything bad from growing gangrene and things like that right so anyway if I
saw children playing around in that stuff I wouldn't see it as being dirty
as an unclean unhygienic way as a matter of fact children that were you'll never
hear of children that grew up on farms having quote-unquote allergies not until
recently it was always the children that were from the cities that had quote-unquote
allergies right and severe so you this this clean part here the hygiene part
it's a mental state you must view the world as a surrounding in order to
achieve hygiene and what that means is if you're always viewing everything as
part of the surroundings and the scenery is there anything you're you're able to
pick up more information and you're not going to really skip over things you see
what I mean or negate things because it's the scenery it's just scenery and
things that you might end up when you start doing that you might end up taking
things subtle things that no one notices a little more to mind and things that
people think are really important you will discount right because remember
what people don't pay attention to or do pay attention to is from the
brainwashing that they've gotten you see they don't view most people don't view
their environment and their surroundings as scenery you take it very
for example recently someone wanted to get into an argument with me because he
accused me as being a Republican because I said I want nothing to do with it I was
like what are you talking about dude March the 9th 1933 there is no country
you're living in like aftermath you did the government doesn't even exist
legally it doesn't exist in law and it doesn't even exist legally you have
these private attorneys pushing making doing all this crazy stuff to give the
impression that the government exists legally he's saying it's illegal no it
it doesn't exist legally to be legal or illegal there is nothing going on it's
all the show and they accused me as being a Republican you see because they
couldn't factor in what I was saying they just had to go to their defaults
they didn't even analyze what you're saying they just went to one of the
adults yeah yeah one person was honest though an older guys like 76 years old
he said Greek I'm not saying we're saying is wrong but it's I don't really
want to change what I've been taught I'm happy with what they taught me wow that's
great and he was very not noncombative just recently you don't want to talk
about it but you know I'm gonna have to stick with what I thought I'm happy with
that that's cool that's admirable it's honorable actually the Bible biblical
teachings are very much like that but you know what to expect from that person
right you're not gonna expect anything gonna be like very low level very low
quality constantly right yeah but you know what it is at least mm-hmm so in
essence the hygiene thing I don't know how to put it otherwise other than the
getting into which we'll get into more hygiene regarding regarding cooking
because a lot of that you know you know you keep them meet separate vegetable
separate these things separate why right and all these are and also prep and all
that the thing also I want to get into I talked about bedclothes laundry is
important what's more important than getting the getting laundry clean is
important but what's getting laundry clean is getting any kind of soap
residue out I always tell people if you have a way to peek into the washing
machine as the cycle is still going it doesn't have to be spinning but while
the water cycle the wash cycle is on do me a favor every third or fourth load
that you do don't put any soap in there and just throw it in there with some
baking soda or something watch how much how much how sudsy the water gets right
where do you think that came from you didn't add any soap to the load right
right so where's all that soapy suds coming from guess what right in there to
begin with yeah you're wearing it yeah so there's ways to alleviate that
there's so many things you know on the practical hygiene but I think that's a
wrap for today fair enough I mean every now and then I take clothes and I just
put them in the bathtub so to speak and I just wring them out and I know that
that soap comes out of them you know that's what that discoloration in the
water is if you do it if you actually do this if you just take your clothes just
you know when you're done wearing them or whatever and you don't think they're
even very dirty just throw them in there I mean the color of your sweat is not
that odd color you'll notice it's the it's it's soap I mean you can smell it it
can be yeah in some cases it's other things depending on what you're working
on but or working with could be your own body yeah but I'm saying if you just
if you just sat around all day okay and then you throw your your pants and your
shirt in there all right not not not stuff that was you know and and you
didn't get a lot of food on it you didn't get anything with any sort of
color on it or any sort of scent on it you know what I mean you'll you'll get
soap out of you out of your clothes you will yeah because it was already there