So, there we go, a little pattern break, rated Y, 87, there we go, 87 is the sonic, now you
got to be real careful if you put that out in a public podcast and really don't tell
anybody, you, the subscribers, that we used it, because if we used it, they could come
after us.
Well, sort of, it's 17 years, it's copyright no more, unless they redo it and resell it,
I don't know.
No, they didn't.
That's one of my favorite lyric songs, I said, just play this, just to do something different.
Look up the lyrics on that, by the way, anybody.
Yeah, it's a Night Flight cover, and we played the YouTube clip here, but tell you what,
check with your friends who are actually competent when it comes to all the crap that they write
that they call laws, because it is insane, the level of copyright law and stuff that
they do now, not just the automated, you know, things like that.
Well, this is actually a cover, actually, it's not, hmm, let's just say this way, the artist,
it's a YouTube channel, let's see who he has drawn a cover.
On my old YouTube channel, just real quick, on my old YouTube channel, right, I covered
a Black Sabbath tune in 1993, I took the recording of that, which was a live recording,
and put it up on my old YouTube channel, and with the new arrangements in 2022, just before
they deleted my channel, guess what, they caught what the song was, and they threatened to
hit me with it if I made any sort of profit whatsoever, even if I monetized it, or whatever
from it, and it was using me playing the song, it was me singing, it was a Black Sabbath
cover that didn't really sound like the original, but was, you know, based on the original,
like a fair cover is, it's recognized, it's different.
I get it, they're just milking for what they can, because they know they don't have a lot
of time left.
Right, right.
It's always, that always happens, yeah.
As you reach the end, things get contracted, and then they expand to the point where they're
out of control, which is coming, and so right now they're just, you know, they know they're
going to lose it, lose everything, so might as well get as much as you can before, that's
the capitalism, you know, when you're done using it, or you can't use it, you destroy
it so no one else can, right, so.
Oh yeah, absolutely.
Although today, you know, if we wanted to, we could draw the Steamboat Willie version
of Mickey Mouse and use it, but not the later versions.
Anyhow, I'm just throwing out, I'm throwing out ridiculous covers.
It's all about how you, how you posture it, right, the posture and the presumption, so
you can't prove that it's exactly the same one.
Anyway.
Well, that's what I'm saying, is now if it's recognizable to a certain degree, the algorithm
catches it, and then they drop it into this, you know, book-length laws, allegedly, right,
that tell you the rules about all this stuff, and at the end of the day, it is exactly what
you said, but the funny part is, they made it so complex, as with most things, that common
folk can't understand it, and it just makes it functionally impossible to utilize stuff
from other artists.
But do the artists still get paid?
That's another thing.
Are they still getting ripped off?
Another whole conversation, when we're talking about the flow of energy tonight, probably,
that could go into this, right?
An artist creates, and then an artist is supposed to be able to, what, be able to spread that
around and benefit from their creation, their hard work, their craft.
Well, sort of.
It's what programming you have, because listening to someone who's a business advisor, and he
interviewed someone who was a CPA, and it's like, oh my gosh, what rubbish, he's talking
about, you know, paying taxes.
How can you pay taxes on money that's created out of thin air, right?
So it's not paying taxes, it's something else.
Then he says, the reason why medical school is so expensive is because the doctor knows
he has to pay a lot in insurance.
That's all the doctor knows.
Isn't he supposed to know how to perform his duties on the, you know, so you see, everything
is so askew.
Everything this guy said was an idiot, by the way.
Idiot just means, like, self-centered.
He's like one of the best CPAs in the country.
Everything he said was patently false, but to the normies, it would sound like he is an
authority on what he's saying is true.
Right.
So, right?
A consistent idiot is at least better than, or slightly better than, a broken clock.
I mean, he's right more than twice a day.
Well, I've been doing this for a while, looking at these so-called experts, and nothing that
they say is in context of reality.
It's in context of what the normies believe, and it's insane.
It's just pure insanity.
I think that's why we do the Greek-speak aspect, but in terms of the artists, like Picasso said,
the meaning of life is to find out what your gifts are, and the purpose of your life is
to give them away.
There you have it.
This is one of the best artists, supposedly, of the modernist movement and cubism, so what
about the artists getting paid with what?
You know, it's just bizarre.
So, the thing is, it's just like we're just, before we start recording, talking about fine
chocolate, right?
Right.
You know, it's really like a medicine.
You know, one of the things that I attribute getting over the circus flu with was I slammed
like three pieces of chocolate, very dark chocolate truffle of high quality, and I just went to
bed for six hours, and I got up feeling great.
I feel like I shook it, right?
Right.
So, it was definitely a frequency change, right?
I think I brought up, past Sonic, this is very serious to consider.
When you, let's say, acquire, contract, and do something, an illness that makes you feel
very sick, and you actually behave like you're sick, almost kills you even, what that ailment
is trying to do is change your DNA, not the DNA that you hear about.
It's trying to change your genetic sequence, because genetic sequences are constantly firing
in your body.
And, you know, you can recreate a human just from a hair or a nail now.
Years ago, you needed a sufficient amount of blood or a certain amount of tissue.
Now, it can be done from the slightest bit.
I bet it could even be done from just fingerprint oils, right?
So, your genetic material is constantly moving, some of it very quickly, some of it much slower.
And an illness goes after that coding, right, after the code.
That's why I also, suffice to say, paraphrase, what did they call those last series of injections
that they wanted everyone to get?
They were mRNA modifiers, which is coding, again, RNA, DNA.
You know, the difference between DNA and RNA is RNA is pretty much indestructible, right,
as a protein.
That's where you get your RNA is where you get what they call mad cow, and, oh, what's
the formal?
Prions.
Right, the prions.
Very toxic.
Yeah, it's a bent protein, basically.
So essentially, I kind of went really deep on this circus flu thing, and I was like,
what is this thing trying to do?
Because whenever I get something, I've never gotten this ill ever in my life, other than,
you know, when you're really young as a child, and you have the flu, you know, and the stomach
bug, you know, really young, and you remember that, right?
Yeah, absolutely.
Well, I've never gotten anything like that, and I pondered on it, meditated on it.
You know, I hope everybody here knows that meditation doesn't mean to empty your mind,
right?
Right.
Like paying taxes, right?
No, like emptying your mind.
It's the opposite.
You have to focus on something, and you look at it from every facet.
When I pondered it for several weeks, and it got really intense, I was like, this damn
thing is trying to change my genetic code.
It's trying to turn me into something else.
Maybe turn me back into a frog, right?
Maybe.
Anyway, yeah, I just need to bring that up, because you could tag that concept along with
all the other concepts that we discuss regarding the human body, and I did post a couple of
weeks ago a Michio Kushi video in the chat, the Otelian, the Greek Chitango.
Actually, we just had someone who's been listening, subbing for a while, but didn't know about
the Chitango.
He actually posted that he just found out about the Chitango recently, and I posted
a Michio Kushi video on there.
He's a master teacher.
I posted it here on what they call January 24th, and just watch like the first 12 minutes
of that, because when we brought up talking about the movement of energies, we also did
a sonic on Feng Shui, or if you're from Texas, it's Feng Sui, but watch that video.
It's posted there.
I can give you the, let's just click on it and see what it's called, Formation and Function
of the Spirit.
Right.
Audio note for the listener, by the way, it is Otelian, the Greek, all one word, dot Chitango
with one T, dot com.
That's where you can find the chat, where people are interacting, and it's open to the
public and all, but unless you know about it, you don't go there, so I'm trying to make
people aware.
The video is called Formation and Function of the Spiritual Body and Chakras, and Faya
Kushi is his son who posted it.
Now, the reason I wanted people to see and follow just the first 12 minutes of that is
to get a feeling of what a master teacher does and is in terms of, and what I'm going
to do real quick here for you, Chuck, since we're on, I'm going to do a quick screenshot.
You may not be able to see it, but maybe if you follow it along later, we could talk about
that video in the future, or yeah, very interesting, because that ties along with everything.
What he's basically showing that if you're into the model they tell us about the sun
and the planets and all that, he shows how the energies move, and it actually forms a
human body, right?
So when you talk about architecture, when you talk about energies and all that, it seems
like accommodating the human body is what, or the human behavior is what you're trying
to do, and that statement sounds like, duh, of course, Greek, right, but there's an archetype
that lies below all of that notion, right, that has to be considered also, you know,
like a fractal.
Well, and that's the consideration I want to ask you about at this point, is that, you
know, is it really about accommodation of the human body, or is it simply that the commonality
of what is available as building blocks tend to fit together the same way, you know?
If nails work really, really well to put oak boards together, they might also succeed in
putting other types of wood together, simply because they're fairly effective.
Or nailing you to a tree.
Yeah, or nailing you to a tree, sure.
All of these things work well.
I'm going to interject at this before we go on the state of feng shui, yes, I've brought
up a little, okay, if you want to study feng shui, as it would be called with the native
tongue on the Cantonese side, or feng shui if you're from the American South, you know
how all through Greek speak, I'll interject, we'll bring up a topic, and the thing to interject
is stuff that you're not going to get anywhere else, right?
Because we can go ahead and talk about all the basics, it's a complete waste of time.
Even if there isn't, like microbiotics, for example, if you go online, or even get books
on study of macrobiotics, you're really not going to get much at all, very little.
You could, if you have someone that has like more old school understanding of it, guide
you through.
But you'll read a 300 page book and get a little bit out of it, and you'll think it's
about this, and it really isn't, right?
But here's the interesting part about the energies, there's a synesthetic part, which
synesthetic is like using dowsing and all that other stuff with feng shui that carries
over when you said about nails.
One of the things in the black hat feng shui, what they say is when you have a business
that's successful, you eventually might think of expanding and opening another one, right?
And in order to carry that success over, what you do is you remove a nail from the building
that the current successful business is in, and move it over and put it into the next
business to carry over that energy.
Typically a nail, you can also do like a shaving, a wood shaving, or a piece of tile, or something,
but a nail holds things together, right?
Has more energy, it's always under tension, right?
And compression.
So they suggest you take a piece of the area that you were successful, and move it over
to the new area, so that also carries through, like a germ, when you germinate, right?
Just bring a small amount over.
And also, by the way, among learned people, let's be honest, they do actually have a version
of this when they seek to build something of significance, whether it's in the fictional
world of Star Trek, or it's the buildings in Washington, D.C., they take a cornerstone
from one place, they take a stone from one place, and lay it strategically as part of
the foundation to another building.
I know I'm probably not using the proper term.
Or the entire, a lot of European cities brought stuff from Egypt, right?
Right, well they'll bring things from a location where something occurred that they wish to
carry over, and literally make it part of the new location.
Ship building, they do the same thing.
Like I said, represented in the Star Trek world, a piece of the legacy ship that is
named after, you know, that it's named after, they make the Enterprise ABCD, they take a
piece of the original ship that carried its name, and place it somewhere in the construction
of the ship.
Sure, an artifact, yeah.
By the way, do you guys know there is an atomic museum in Nevada, somewhere outside of Las
Vegas?
And a lot of people are still scratching their head why they have artifacts from the World
Trade Center on 9-11 there.
They don't really just, they can't come out and tell you, right?
No, but what else would you put that there if it is indeed an atomic museum?
See, but there you go.
If you have, and that's something to note though, if you ever take a look deep into the
construction of certain things, if you find that there's almost nonsensical ceremonial
things that are added to the construction of it, it gives you a big hint about the
intent that they're carrying from one place to another.
And literally, there are parts of Washington, D.C., you know this, where they've literally
made parts of other buildings part of the foundation of said new building, right?
So again, it's one of those things you do.
And if you think about it, it's part of the natural world.
I mean, indeed, you carry through genetics, which I think is poorly understood, you carry
parts of the original code, right, from somewhere else into something else.
People talk about their ancestry and all this.
Well, that's what it's about.
You're literally carrying a piece of them.
Like a weird concept to think about is that at some point or other, you resided, a part
of you that went into making you literally resided in the body of your grandmother.
Well, water.
Well, how much water do you need to carry over to have that water be the same water?
Well, water is poorly understood, again, and we could go to that, but as far as the second
water, the literal thing that I'm talking about is you actually at one point lived in
your grandmother's body.
How do I know that?
Because the literal ovum part, right, the part of the woman that goes into making the
baby when it links up with that other piece, is what?
In your mother's body your whole life.
She's born with it, right?
Well, yeah.
And she, right.
Well, it's the water.
Just a tiny amount of water carries the memory.
It's not necessarily the sperm or the ovum itself.
It's that those sperm and the ovum are containers for the water.
Oh, yes.
But a way to understand this.
And the water working with the rest of the structure does what it does.
Yeah, but a way to understand this, which is not usually considered, is that literally
if the ovum, if a woman is born with all of her ovum intact that she's going to have throughout
her lifetime, then that means it started in your grandmother's body where she had it.
And then she was born.
She comes out.
She makes you.
That's literally part of you.
And you're right.
It is the container.
And it carries the water.
And it's, you know, very small.
So the idea of cutting the goose open to get all the golden eggs at once was probably an
affirmation of what we're talking about, right?
Well.
Supposedly you have all the eggs at once, right, and give them off at a certain time.
Well, that's the idea.
We don't really know.
We have to just trust.
But here's the thing with medical stuff.
I would trust the the anatomy more than the process side, than the physiology side, which
is unbelievably contorted and dysfunctional.
And misleading the way that they've recorded it.
But initially, even when they were just cutting people open and being surprised about what
they found inside, even back then, you could trace what it is I'm talking about.
So and literally, you could find this sort of concept in books from a time period where
you would say they're at least, you know, somewhat informative in the late 1800s, 1920s,
the latest.
Yeah.
But but I just point that out as a concept of in the natural world.
There is, you know, the idea of a piece of something literally ends up being the next
thing and carrying over.
So there is clearly an energetic order to this in nature.
And the energetic happens in between.
You have the space in between the material.
The energy happens in that area.
People think there's energy and matter.
No, there is matter doesn't have energy to carry it.
Right.
But it doesn't have any aspect of energy.
It has.
It's a state of energy, but it's not energy.
So the energy is carried in the spaces between the spaces, between the spaces of material.
So you have space, right, which is undefined is.
Yeah.
So you have this another.
It's a field.
And that's why I say there's some yeah, there's some validity to the concept of epigenetics.
Back to your genetic discussion here, where you were saying, look, it's not about the
genetic code just as it stands, but what it does, because there is genetic presentation
and epigenetic literally means on top of the genetic.
It is the switches and the things that are happening that the reaction and the actual
process that goes on.
Well, that would be again, the feng shui and the architecture, which are feng shui is
considered to be geomancy, right?
Geomancy, which is, you know, working with the earth.
Right. And, you know, you could really mess up people with bad architecture.
Right. Look at like Skinner boxes or college dorms.
Right. Absolutely.
Yeah. So you could really squeeze them.
Right. That's typically when you look at the architecture, it's squeezing people into
spaces that make them uncomfortable generally.
Right. And when they get outside of the uncomfortable space and the outsourced now is
uncomfortable because visually it's askew.
You know, I think my criticism with architects is it's all about ego.
And I've witnessed this on many levels.
Right. They they they do things for their own ego and their portfolio.
Right. And of course, the bigger it is and the more expensive it is.
Right. So they have no interest in making it inexpensive for the client or or better
functionally, because you and I talked about that where you were pissing off architects
because basically you're like, look, save money.
And also this functions.
But that functionality is also indicative of what it is you're passing on.
Right. Because if you make a workspace, a living space, something that is
comfortable, that promotes, you know, an ability to get a good night's rest, that's
well constructed so that it would be it would be a living space within the workspace
that I wouldn't integrate.
I would always have a separate demarcation.
Right. And even that consideration right there is part of the process, because other
people might say, look, we just need a big space, you know, which, by the way, I'm
looking for a space, by the way, a workspace for, of course, you know, the water
stuff that we've been talking about a lot here and, you know, and others.
Yeah. Because, you know, working a workspace that you work in is fine, like an
artist studio. Right.
But if you have a workspace where you invite other people to come and work also, it
gets a little tiring when a company, you know, it's over where you would live.
That's why it's important to have if you're going to live work in the same space, to
be able to demarcate an area which is more private.
So like we talked about in past Sonics, doctors that have, you know, the front of
their house is devoted to the doctor's office and they live in the back, this kind
of thing, or even hairdressers.
Same thing where they have like a, you know, the parlor is called the parlor.
The parlor is up front.
Right. So anyway, I'll shut up now and let's get back to this.
But I just wanted to point out that that, you know, and throw these ideas on the table
for you to to explore is that not only is there a concept here for you to work with,
but it already exists in nature.
And the idea that, you know, going with the behaviors of going with the river, so to
speak, you know, is a hell of a lot easier, but also a hell of a lot more efficient of a
way of accomplishing things if you're kind of going with the flow of the stream as
opposed to. Well, hold on.
You're going to have to also determine what kind of a river it is.
Very few rivers run, let's say, from north south to north in the world.
Most of them run east, west or west east and a river.
And you have to understand the quality of the river.
So a river that runs, for example, west east will not have fertile banks.
It's either one. A river that runs from south to north, the western bank will always be
fertile in a river that runs north to south.
The eastern bank will always be more fertile, actually, that it could be either.
But most likely it will be the western bank.
But typically you'll see it on the west on all rivers that run up and down.
So you have to know where and how rivers work to figure out where you're going to put
yourself. Right. Some rivers are not.
Actually, conducive, you know, how people would settle around rivers because of the
water supply and the transportation and whatever.
Right. Right. Some of them are not viable.
So you have to make, in other words, the determination of architecture and fun and
geometry, where to put things on the land is a tough one.
And I've seen this recently with giving some water devices.
Someone has a water company and they misappropriated about four of them.
In other words, the water that people that had these wells at certain times of the year,
they'd have dark brown, rusty water coming out of the ground.
And they thought Scalarator would fix it.
And I'm like, no, it's not going to do that much.
If it would fix that, I wouldn't be talking to you.
I'd go to the Pacific and I would desalinate it.
Right. Right. Right. With the device.
So there is a device that could do that.
And, you know, that's called a Turbidorator.
But that's not going to be offered or really gone into in much depth in the near future.
There's no reason to because very few people have that kind of water.
And that was my point.
Why would you settle with a well?
First of all, right, you're in the wrong spot.
If you if your water source is that bad, you have made some really bad decisions or
you didn't drill deep enough.
And which is fine, because if you can't afford to drill deep enough now, you might
afford to afford it later, have them come back and drill deeper.
Because the truth about water in the earth is the deeper you go, the cleaner the water
gets. And if you go deep enough, you don't even have to pump it.
It comes up like a spring.
Right. There's a guy who talked about that primary water.
You have to go some sometimes you have to go more than two miles deep, which is not
that crazy, by the way.
Two mile deep well is uncommon, but it's done quite often and it's expensive.
But you would do something that would bring up quite a bit of water.
So there are these considerations and how much input and how much energy you're going to
put into something to get it to work for you.
Right. That's why when you look at a lot of the.
Ancient cities like Rome, we still have a the wishing fountain today, people drop
coins, they have these features of fountains in public spaces, make a wish, throw a
coin and they still do that, but they don't most people don't understand the origin of
that. This is, again, making an effort.
We've discussed this. I'll bring it up again.
Yeah. Because the Rome was growing to a point where it needed to sustain a bigger and
bigger population every year, they had contractors, people the government contracted
with to find water sources and build aqueducts and bring the water into Rome or
channel the water into Rome.
Sometimes it was done underground.
And before it was incorporated to be civilly and socially responsible before it was
incorporated into the general water supply, they would specify that the contractor with
the new water source would build a fountain and the water would go through a trial
period with the public for a certain amount of time before it was integrated into the
public works. So what they did was they threw metal pieces of metal into these fountains,
these test fountains and invited people to do so.
And if you threw, let's say the most typical thing that was metal was a coin.
So sometimes they would put the coins in there and examine them a week later and they
would be very heavily encrusted.
So they would judge that water as being fair and not very good.
Sometimes they would throw coins into the water and the coins would dissolve.
And that water was definitely not good for you because.
Right. Right. So so the water, the wishing well fountains that you see today as
features in place, public places, the main purpose of it never started out as a
wishing well, whether it was a lot, probably OK, never started out as a wishing.
Well, it was actually it had a scientific and civil purpose to find out if the water
quality was good enough. But then again, there is a slight amount of intent that went
into wishing because if the population was growing and growing and water was becoming
more scarce because of the growth of the city, you really wanted that new water source
to work, to be good.
Right. So you almost wish that it was good.
You say so the the civil part, the engineering part, people don't remember, but they
do remember the part where you just make a wish.
Right. You say much like most of this.
They remember the ritual, but not necessarily the practical purpose or the idea behind
the ritual. Well, there was.
Yeah, the the purpose was all practical and it and it had some ritual.
But then the purpose then it became all ritual, which I've discussed many times.
The woman who wears an expensive fur coat that drives a hundred thousand dollar SUV to
her, that's a ritual. She knows if she turns this round thing in front of her to the
left, the car goes to the left, goes to the right, push one pedal.
The car stops to push another pedal.
The car goes. It's a ritual.
She doesn't know anything about the machinery or how to fix it or if something goes
wrong, what went wrong, nothing at all.
So how much of your life of what you're doing is ritual?
And I would suggest even people who are listening about 90 percent of it is like we
started off. I was listening to this idiot CPA, supposedly best CPA in the country.
And he keeps talking about paying taxes.
How are you going to pay taxes when there's no money?
It's all credit. Right.
So actually, that's a ritual.
And actually, the the head of the IRS has gone on and said that many times.
He says, here comes April and the Americans have a ritual where they go and all pay
their taxes. It's a ritual.
But what really is going on is no government in the world right now has its own money
as it's supposed to. It's using money and borrowing money from a private banking
cartel. And just like anything that you use that is private, they require a report on
it. Or, you know, what have you how much have you used and a fee?
Just like, for example, you need a jackhammer to break a sidewalk.
And because you know, you need a jackhammer, a big, heavy one, because you tried it
with a mallet and you tried it with a sledgehammer.
So your neighbor said you got to go rent one of these tools.
And they're like three thousand dollar tools.
But you could rent it for a day for seventy five bucks.
Right. So you go and get the tool.
You break up the sidewalk, you bring the tool back and you just wave goodbye.
No, it doesn't work that way.
You you show what you you know, they examine the tool.
Right. And they make a report.
Yes, it's in fair condition.
And you have to pay rent on that.
That's exactly what's going on with the money system.
Every time you use the money system, you must have a report to send back to the
originator. Right. The private.
Right. And then you have to return back to them.
And they are they know that even though they can print money as they want to, to a
degree. Actually, they do use collateral.
Right. But they can make it as much as they want.
Actually, if they want to print money, all they do is send you a check, by the way.
And when you sign that check, that money.
Right. We've gone over that.
There's no need to go over it again.
They can't use the money that you there's no government that could use any tax money
because it's just it's it's what there's nothing there.
It's just a ledger.
Right. They can make their we don't need your ledger.
We could use our own ledger.
Right. So why do they do that?
Is to create a sense of scarcity, like, you know, how there's discussion about
scarcity in the world. There is no scarcity of anything.
There's plenty of food. There's plenty of metal.
There's plenty of everything, plenty of cocaine for everyone if they want.
If they wanted to give every person on the earth a eight ball of coke once a month,
there's plenty of that to go around.
Right. Plenty of beef, plenty of veg, plenty of everything.
What there's a scarcity of is the credit that people use to exchange for these
things. Right.
That's why they have to keep this panic situation going where, oh, climate change
or terrorism. What's the next thing now?
You're going to have terrorism again pretty soon, by the way, in the Middle East.
Right. And all this, I've talked about that, you know, which we will get into the
future. So all this stuff ties into the ritual, which ties
into the original engineering, why fountains were people put coins
in fountains. Right. Which ties in originally to the design of a city, to
architecture and feng shui.
So how do you bridge something that feng shui or architecture was a very
geomancy, was a very exact science, practical.
But now when you bring up feng shui to people, oh, it's a what do you call it?
Airy theory. Oh, you know, it's mysticism.
It's superstition, new age superstition, urban legend,
myths. It's just like the wishing well at the at the mall.
Right. Right. People don't know the history of it.
Right. So when you bring bring these subjects up is no reason to do an entire
talk about architecture or geomancy, which is feng shui and all that, because
you can find that information anywhere on your own.
What you won't find is is the how serious this was and how much of a basis it
was for doing anything that was regarded to that subject, which which doesn't
carry over anymore.
It just doesn't carry over.
It can't. It can't into this society.
Why? Because you're overburdened with fictional things, right, that you have
more you take more seriously.
Right. So it's it's a kind of an interesting contrast.
But we go ahead and tell you in the Greek and Greek speak or whatever the stuff
I always try to make a penetrating move into the subject and also make fun of it.
Right. But you also and also give like people, you know, I always make up.
This is something that comes up a lot with brochures and archaics that everything's
underground. You know, all the elite.
Well, ever since I've been doing Greek speak, even before the Internet, I would always
describe people as surface dwelling earth inhabitants.
True. Right.
Always. Now, wait a second.
Does that imply we mean surface dwelling earth inhabitants?
Well, wait a second. What are you talking about?
We mean, like, where else are you going to live?
Right. We can't fly around in the air.
At least we can't. But they are.
But the reason why I was always specifying that is because the real society is not on
the surface. It's all underground.
And the reason why is it's a level of intelligence.
And I've gone through this before.
And this ties in with architecture.
I just built a new house.
OK. And to go with the new house, I just order all of your furniture.
So here comes the delivery truck.
OK. And OK.
Delivery truck comes on.
Neighbors are all over that big gas truck in that brand new house.
OK. I order all the delivery people in the furniture truck to put all the furniture on
the roof because I'm going to be living on the roof on my brand new house.
So how it goes. Nope.
Inside the house, the earth is your house.
So where do you with the intelligent people, industrious people live inside the earth,
not on the surface.
You see how it works. Well, I've always asked this question to people that go in depth
about the underground cities, the underground bunkers, the underground reality, you
know, and I've never seen it for myself.
But I would say, you know, look, here's the big question for you, though, because a lot
of them don't have an answer as to the following.
If you built all that stuff, is it just sitting there empty?
Never. You can't build a new house and leave it empty for more than a year to start
falling apart. Well, that's the thing, is that everything needed to be, let's just say
you built an underground.
It's lived in. It's always lived in a certain degree.
Yeah, because otherwise you don't know if anything functions in it does begin to fall
apart without people being in it.
I mean, unless it's under.
Yeah. And the energies are totally different.
I don't know if anyone here has been in a two mile deep hole in the ground I have in
Globe, Arizona. It's actually a secret goldmine.
And it really was a secret because every time we went down there, I went there twice
and they started digging in and they found that there was mining done there beyond
history that we have.
They had cut some. This is two miles deep.
And someone had cut some timbers that were a foot, foot thick and two feet wide and 20
feet long. Where do you get trees that size?
You can't get even trees that big.
And they were using that to support areas that they blasted.
So the way it works is you work all week and you take the weekend off.
Right. That's normal.
Right. OK. So you work all week.
Yeah. And on Friday night, what you do is you blast, you blast underground because
that dust is so fine.
It takes two days to settle.
So when you come back on Monday, everything's settled.
Right. There's dead bats everywhere and stuff.
And you go and you find more stuff.
Yeah, it was very, very interesting experience.
But what I want to bring up forward for the sonic on the experience is when you go
really deep like that, you wear a sensor.
It looks like a pager and it's a CO2 and an oxygen sensor.
So if you know, if the CO2 goes too high or the oxygen goes too low, it notifies
you very basically like beeping.
Right. So it's not just lack of oxygen, but too much CO2 could also kill you, by the
way. Right. Of course. Yeah.
So that has both of those.
So anyway, you go down there and you feel the energies are completely different.
You feel completely surrounded.
And once you've experienced going deep into the earth like that and it was two
miles as as you walk, not straight down.
So I would say it was more than a mile deep or because it was a very steep, deep
decline. And there is you would have to get off and go vertically down a 40 foot
ladder and then go across again, almost like the pyramid.
You know, you would walk in the pyramid.
So what I would suggest is the feeling that I got from under there, if the
cavern or the space was big enough, you could definitely the the energy is
completely different than what you feel on the surface.
I mean, the intrinsic energy that your body feels.
And I could see how it could be a welcomed habitation.
No, definitely. This is all great, interesting stuff.
One thing that I would like to get to, though, is one of the other things that was
brought up in chat, if you don't mind, and that is, you know, the connection to
the older sonics about about the biblical stuff that you just mentioned.
We're going to see some terrorism, you know, in the Middle East.
Yeah, sure. Let me just let me just paraphrase.
Sure. The person there made a list of several items which I've covered in detail
quite a bit. But I am reconsidering all of it and really because of the archaic
chronology. Right. And looking at the sources of the biblical stuff and all that.
Now, the thing that I always this this is how, you know, you're dealing with a serious
biblical conversation.
The first thing, whenever you look up anyone or anything or anywhere, even school
academia, once they start having a biblical discussion, they must say that you must be
aware that the biblical text has never been translated out of Hebrew and Greek.
Only versions of it.
Right. So you got to start there.
Right. Because those are the languages of preservation, as you saw.
Exactly. And so if you have it in any other language other than Hebrew and Greek, it
probably it's probably 30 percent errors, direct like fatal errors, bad errors.
Right. So we have to go back to the to that.
Now, when you even even when you go back to that, I've had notes on this, but I never
quite look at it, whatever.
It's the Judeo-Christian authoritative aspect.
But I've been looking recently and many parts of the Book of Revelation and parts of
Genesis are found in other texts that predate the Bible and other cultures.
So can you say that it's written by Moses directly or Revelation
written by John directly at this point?
No, I wouldn't. Yeah, it is taken from other sources.
Do you know what you might know?
Yeah. Do you have the original letters that were written because you have a
compilation of not even that directly word for word, many verses from a completely
different text. So you can say it's a compilation.
Does it make it invalid?
No, it doesn't make it invalid.
Now, again, just to preface, whenever you have a biblical discussion, you must preface
that it's never been translated out of Hebrew and Greek.
So you if you bring up verses that you find in English, you must go back and examine
what was language of preservation.
The other thing this is shifting to the personal reason.
This is the Greek. The reason why I revere the Bible, because that's where I get my
law from. Right, right.
Right now, and I still know the laws of the state better than almost anyone I've ever
met, because all you have to do is read them with comprehension.
I do understand them and they're not they're not in conflict at all, by the way, if you
look at it carefully.
And just a hint there is the definitions of all of the state state and federal
statutes. The first usually first three sections or five sections are definitions.
When you read the definitions, you'll see what applies and what doesn't apply when.
But I use it for law.
So in other words, what's law?
What you eat, what you wear, how you keep time, how you deal with your family, how you
deal with neighbors on and on and on and on and on.
That's where I mean by law.
So that part doesn't really change much.
And that holds very well.
What I would look at some of the questions that the person put up there or the points
to discuss are very much chronologically based.
So one thing that I've mentioned is the seven year periods.
Right. And Archaic's gets into it being on the Greek Olympiad four year periods.
But I've also mentioned there's four and a half year periods, but still we're looking at
it two different ways. What I've always mentioned is a new period is going to start
around twenty twenty five in the fall of the fall or of twenty twenty four and the
spring of twenty twenty five.
And at that point, it'll be unmistakable that the Middle East is going to take the
lead in the world scene and be making.
That's where all the ruckus is going to be coming from.
And I mean, ruckus, which, by the way, coincides perfectly with the fact that during
that season is precisely when more than half of the world's election processes are
going on, by the way, just which is on the Greek Olympiad, what Archaic's discusses.
So I give him a lot of credit on that.
It's actually quite brilliant.
But what I've said, even if you heard Greek speak from 2010 or 2012, I did lay out all
those periods in the twenty twenty four.
Twenty twenty five is when the Middle East Union or Middle East focal point, you know,
it's remember when I say union, it's a loose confederacy.
It's not like the EU or the United States or Mexico.
But by the way, Mexico is also established by the way.
It's right. It's just how the US is various states called the United States.
So is Mexico. But anyway, you could look at nothing, nothing in that way under a federal
system. But it is going to be a center point.
So at that point, I can't prognosticate anymore.
And I've gotten all this from the biblical text, not from any other text.
Right. So you have to commend that aspect of it, you know, instead of looking at us.
But now I'm looking everywhere else, especially the Phoenix event and the recurrence of the
various things that he's bringing up.
And most of it seems to be fairly valid.
But again, I don't know.
All I can do is report what I found out.
And again, we'll go over the how about on the next Sonic, we'll go over the points that
the fellow mentioned, because we could go into depth and I think we should go into depth.
But so far, I'm quite confident.
I mean, this also ties in, which we didn't cover yet, which is about dreams also.
Right. If we really found out what was really going on in dreams and I mean, like more, you
know how we just found out what the wishing well fountains were really for initially.
Well, if we get that deep into dreams, I think we've really hacked this reality and there's
no need to be here anymore at all.