Rated Y Sonic Event 113 and here we are looking back a bit on some interesting topics and a little
bit of feedback that we've gotten. Well, I guess a few people want to talk about the consumption of
pork and cannibalism. Just cannibalism, yeah. By the way, there's some videos, I don't know if
there's some old film of people, these white guys, rich white guys, trust the fairies. I used to tell
people what's reason what's the trust the fairy and what's somebody who lives off of a family
trust, right? Fun babies. Yeah, trust fun, baby. Yeah. So and the cannibals were telling them
basically through the translator, don't talk to him so much because we'll eat you. You know, it's
like, you know, look at that guy over there. So yeah, it's so they're protected in certain islands,
by the way, right. And you're told that if you go there, you're on your own, we're not going to
rescue you or whatever. But also, you know, Episode 13 and 31 brought that topic up about pork. Yeah,
if you eat pork, processed pork, you know, like sausages, ground pork, pork ingredient note,
or even a, what do they call it when they wrap up the loin pork loin, right? Oh, the pork loin,
or maybe yeah, the most likely you've about 10% of that that you've consumed is human.
But how about hot dogs and bologna? Oh, absolutely. Absolutely. sausage sausages, hot dogs. Yeah.
Okay, fair enough. Jimmy Dean's is known for it's very well known. Very well known all of the
major pork processing plants, their wastewater treatment areas for their human body, human teeth
are usually found teeth. Well, yeah, because those are the hardest thing to grind up, right? The teeth
but most likely cheese and hair. Yeah. So they'll always find there's like a
what's the big one Tyson that Tyson's chicken and the other one. Well, there's Jimmy Dean. And then
there's what is that other one? They have like these runoff areas where the water from there
is processed and runs off to the river and certain times a year when it dries out. There's all human
teeth. Oh, Johnsonville. Yeah. Johnsonville, maybe, because they're pretty big. They're all
you know, by the way, you know, all these companies that are supposedly competing
are on. It's a show for the public. You know, they're all in meetings. And they're all together,
you know, based out of the Central Bank conglomerate. Well, I'll tell you one of the Oh,
by the way, one of the funniest things that doesn't involve cannibalism is that, you know,
a lot of times people get like the French fries, they think, you know, Oh, well, this kind of French
fries better than this one or that. They're almost all made in like the same exact three factories,
like whether it's a McDonald's. It doesn't matter what it is. It doesn't matter what it is. Like,
for example, well, excuse me, I'm gonna mention a very wealthy person, when they started doing
all the sanctions against Russia. So that hasn't changed. And just a few companies that are public
eye and a couple of billionaires business got disturbed. But all the major trade that happens
with Russia still going on. It's all it's all public eye bullshit. Right. So by the way,
I want to interject this regarding money, we've been speaking a lot about money lately,
just the system, because it's something you can actually, it can be done very methodically,
you make a checklist of how to handle it. And it's it works very nicely. But, you know,
I talked about when you when you get a check, a personal check or a corporate check,
money is never transferred from that account to your account. It's created with your signature
when you endorse that check. And on the other side, their own bank pulls the funds to give the
illusion that it was transferred never was right. Right. Okay, this is evidence. When you see a
financial instrument, and it says pay to the order of pay to the order of means green light to do
what I just said, when you get a postal money order, or certain bank checks, doesn't say pay
to the order of it just says pay. Right? That's where they can still do that. No, they actually
do have to take it out of the other account, or some account, according to the routing number,
but they can't create the funds from your signature and the other signature. So the
simple down, they still do that the order of is the big difference, because it's pay or pay to
the order of Yeah, when you see when you see a financial instrument that says paid to the order
of, that's when they're really ripping everybody off everybody, the payer, the payee, everybody,
when you see pay, go right now pull up images, a check, you'll see pay to the order of,
and then pull up a postal money order, it doesn't say pay to the order of
No, it doesn't. Let me let me look at the back says pay order. Yeah. You know,
the actually front of the money order. This is all in the front. Been a while since the back
is always the back. Yeah, well, the back is the it says endorse do not write below here,
because that's where they do all their launches or launches when you transfer. But if you look at
a cashier's check, or a postal, specifically a postal money order, it will not say pay to the
order of it just says pay. Because it's a carryover on how the stamps are monetized,
which is a whole other thing. Anyway, I just wanted to bring that note up right away,
you should probably see a postal money order. It says pay, but a regular checks is paid to the
order of Yeah, I'm just trying to make the image big enough for me to see. Sorry.
I'm fine. Okay. Well, anyway, the listeners got it. So back to the eating people thing.
That's a very complex subject, because here without even covering it. I talked years ago,
about how it's going to make a comeback in the open, just like the woke stuff is it'll
be attached to the woke stuff if that movement survives the next year or two. And but but here's
the thing. Doritos Frito, you know, the real Frito Lay and Pepsi already admit they're using male,
male fetus liver cells as a taste. Oh, yeah, that's the fetal the fetal tissue that was
discovered as part of the sweetening thing, right? Yeah, that's still enacted. So that's
there's about a dozen companies, prominent companies that do it. And there's like two
dozen companies that you don't know about that make profit, you know, other process stuff.
So you're already if you're eating like any Frito Lay products or Pepsi products,
you're already experienced with cannibalism is like the newer the newer postal money orders
are very complex, actually. Yeah, it's just it's a bullshit act because there's no money. It's all
credit still but but still, it does say pay. See, it's that's the SOS. They got your SOS is the
shiny object syndrome. Actually, now they got this thing endorsement and they want a signature
or stamp. Okay, and then they got another whole box for a stamp. It's weird. I never saw him like
this. It doesn't matter. You can create a promissory note on a piece of paper. And it's
just as good. I can write an IOU. Yeah, I can write an IOU on a piece of toilet paper. If you
accept it, you wouldn't be very durable, but any durable paper durable, right? Yeah, is what
actually there there is a few states do have paperwork codes like how you need to do paperwork,
what it should be on the size, the color of the material, right font. That's why it tells you only
fictions corporations trust. Government agencies are in all caps, right? Right, right. It's the
it's the printing and style manual. I think Ohio has it. Kansas has a few of the older states.
The busy, busy industrial states because in industry, there was the two signature and the
single you know, you know about the two signature instrument and a single instrument, single
signature instrument, right? You know, there's a whole thing, right about that. And it's leading
setting people up just for the fiat to accept it just like when 911 came, they accepted Muslims
because since the 80s, they were showing back to a few all these movies that of course, you know,
from that part of the world is where the right so it's a predictive programming, but back to the
cannibalism, which is basically what's going on with the money system. The cannibalism is not a
deal because I mentioned, you know, how many cells do you have to eat? It's like a little pregnant,
right? How many human cells from another? Do you have to eat to be considered to be considered
cannibalism? Right? Well, yeah, and there you go, because a drop of blood and that's the thing is
that even if it's just in another product, right, which well, in other words, yeah, cannibalism
doesn't mean you have to hack the meat off the bone. Is it bone in bone out to lay? Is it the
cellular tissue that they're using in Pepsi colas and products and Frito Lay products? Right? Now,
if you're straight up eating, you know, processed pork meat in hot dogs and all that stuff, you're
straight up that straight up cannibalism. It's been prepared by others. aspect of it is the
ritual, though. How long has that been going on, though? Because it seems to me as though always
food was different going on. Yeah, but there's a change in food during the course of our lifetime.
Wouldn't you admit that the food supply is generally sort of shifted? No, not regarding
this topic? No, not at all. No, the major change in food, we'll get I have a point to make. Okay.
But the major change in food is just the toxification. There was a in the 1700s. I
don't have the data. But in the 1700s, there was one of these proclamations done in secret.
It did get out and it was known at the time about it's like an Alam and terrorist proclamation,
whatever, to get rid of seeds like certain grains that were you know, you could live off of like
super grains, right? Stop growing them and grow the animal. You know, I've always said animal grade.
Right? I always talked about the you know, most of the food is animal grade. It's not the stuff
that humans cultivated. It's high nutrition, right? If you look at ancient culture, when you were
hungry, you just wanted some bread. Right now, if you just are hungry, you don't ask for bread,
you ask for chicken wings, right? But no, you don't ask for bread, because it's not enough,
right? So they were using, they were cultivating grains that were slower to grow,
certain seeds, and those were all gotten rid of by the 20th century. So triticales typically,
but that's another that's another discussion, the food stuff, you know, I could get into food,
you know, and that's something to think about, though, is that when you read a story about where
somebody just eats a piece of bread, and that's what they're eating, like, that's what they're
asking for when they're hungry. Yeah, you don't ask for that. Now. No, but but that's because
that piece of bread actually was adequate. Yeah, it was adequate, more than adequate,
more than adequate because of the stock of the grain and all that. So this is all these grains
are gone now. Well, even though they're still around, but they're not used. Yeah, well,
even the old timey concept of you give a prisoner just bread and water, right in a cell that
actually wasn't so bad if they had clean water, and that bread back. Yeah. That's why all this
stuff from the New Testament, you know what I say about the New Testament, right? So,
you know, the about the the focus on the, you know, the blood and the eating this,
I don't believe that was actually can it's been put in there. But that's something else.
You think that was it? You never hear me when I talk about scripture. I don't I don't really
lean on I don't really get into the New Testament at all, because it's not worth getting into if
you're going to get any kind of knowledge base. If you're going to be an airy, fairy cultist in
the human cult, then all you need is the New Testament, right? I'm not talking the New Testament,
or because a lot of the ritual is so corrupt. Yeah. And a lot of the rituals that they carry
on with today are all designed off of it. Right? Yeah, it is. And the only thing that was actually
recorded that was around for the New Testament was maybe like maybe 200 or 300 words out of
the Book of Matthew. That's it. So, you know, so don't say I'm knocking the New Testament
because canon is canon. In other words, if they put it all together and say that's canon,
my purpose of talking about scripture is, do you know what it says, regardless if you believe it
or not? And the answer is no. The population does not know, even though there's everyone has a copy
of it. Right. So why don't we start reading just like the money system? Why don't we start just
reading what it's about or anything? The human body. Right. Anything. It doesn't matter. See,
I'm not a proponent for anything. I'm just saying that if you're going to discuss something,
are you discussing it or are you discussing something else? And the issue here is always
discussing something else. And this is something I wanted to discuss tonight. I keep bouncing
around from the money to the cannibalism. There's not much else to talk about on the cannibalism,
but you've been warned sufficiently. If you listen to Greek speak, first of all,
pork, a pig does not have a cloven hoof and chew the cut of an Old Testament guy. So it's out.
Doesn't matter what it tastes. It tastes like whatever. If you eat pork, I'd say about if you
ate 100 pounds of pork, 10 pounds, I assure you, is human flesh, 10 to 10 percent, at least minimum.
Wow. Processed. Right. Okay. And whatever. So all this stuff. But you've been warned about this
stuff by me over and over and over. By the way, this is very well established, by the way,
what I'm telling you, that's canon. And you would say ground pork products. You've eaten
human DNA. You know, they say they find human DNA in it all the time. This is open.
But bacon. This is not. Yeah. But bacon and pork chops, those are supposed to be solid pieces
of pork. Those are most likely you can't get away with that. Yeah. It's the process part.
Okay. So it's not just about pork. And then of course, there's the ritualist
side from the Christian. I didn't say Judeo Christian, mostly on the Christian side,
because of what's been put and called the New Testament. They're focusing on that. It's very
easy. But here's what I wanted to discuss as a group of people that get together and organize
or whatever or have relative amount of imagination and reason. What's the purpose of humanity?
What what these what's the don't they stop and gather and ask themselves, count me out,
by the way, on this thought. I'm not part of it, but I'm just saying you have all these people.
It doesn't matter if it was just a few million or tens of millions years ago. And now it's in
the billions. And it's not eight billion, like they say, by the way. But anyway,
is it? Why are we here? Why are we here? What should we accomplish? I mean,
yeah. Why are the people ever getting together and saying, what's our objective here? What's
our goal? What are we? What's our goal? You know, organize. What's our mission statement?
What is our purpose? What is our purpose here? Yeah, our purpose. Not not questioning the purpose
past tense. But what are we going to do? None of that. There's none of that at all. It's all about
food, clothing and shelter, is it not more generally food? Yeah, well, that protection,
which eventually leads to where's the organizing principle? Okay, so that must exist. So here comes
religion, nationalism, and all that. So that's fine. Because religion, nationalism, you could
name a few other things, culture, whatever, is an organizing factor for these people.
So it puts the organizing principle in place so that you have a purpose.
Okay, yeah, because necessary. But then it's go look at the quality of those things. Go look at
what that resultant is. And that's not being questioned and saying, Hey, I'm not saying that
nationalism is bad. It's actually vital. In many cases. It's proof right now, when people buy
a German branded product. They say make sure it's made in Germany. That's the better one,
right? Or whatever. It depends. And the thing about it is that one one thing that's an absolute
truth, though, is that every one of these nations on a long enough timeline fails and disappears,
though, doesn't it? Well, yeah, that's exactly well, if you look at there's a thing with
corporations are all corporations, by the way, you know, like, all these things like nationalism,
religion, all that stuff, those are anything that's a state of mind, even though it's not
tangible can be sold, right? Right. So they call it IP now, intellectual, intellectual property.
Yeah. So if you go back to the aspect of corporations have a lifespan of about 20 years,
it's very easy to predict what's going to happen to something like Amazon or, you know, Elon Musk,
I hate, you know, when I say Tesla, I hate combine use talking about the car, or Elon Musk,
because that's like degradation of Tesla's name. You know, it's amazing that they did that, right?
They vote Nikola Tesla's name to, you know, attach it to the concept of newer technology.
It's a total corruption. It's not has nothing to do with Tesla at all. His principles, at least.
By the way, most people don't know I've been following Elon Musk's organization since the
beginning. And back in 0405060708, somewhere there, most people that are fans of him and Tesla
don't even know this. He had a set of engineers, 910 engineers, really brilliant guys. And they
went to Washington, DC for a meeting, and they flew them back on this little twin engine old
plane that crashed and killed all of them, right. And then when that happened, then it they got
Tesla became what it is now more focused. At that time, they made like just one little sports car.
And they killed all their top people. And they got reorganized into what it is now,
right? Very typical, you know, type stuff. So what is the organizing principle? If you look at the
things that I mentioned religion, it's really keeping people dumb, all of it. And if you look
at nationalism, it's one of the causes of war. And one of the causes for war, not as an aggressor,
but to also be warred on, you know, the people talk about, you know, everyone hates the Jews,
but everyone really hates the Germans and the Prussians. All the nations around them were like,
how do we get rid of these Germans, right? You know, about Morgenthau's, it's the pastoral
policy in the 1920s, which means Germany should be everyone, all the Germans should be killed,
and all of Germany turned into a big pasture. So this was in the 1920s. And this is the same thing
they talked about the Asian people. So you know, it's Yeah, the true nationalism. So anyway,
these organizing principles, set, let's set them aside, what other organizing principles do humans
have in general, and I'm telling you that none, they really don't. It goes down to the food,
clothing and shelter thing. Again, you know, it's really piss poor. It's a so here's the other part.
Well, everything else is just a fabricated fictional identity. By the way, if you guys
can hear chirping birds, I just want you to know you listening. That's some migration. It's a
natural soundtrack. And I don't mind it. I'm just letting people know that the chirping birds are
not being added. Yeah, it's amazing how penetrating it is. No, no, it's not. Yeah. So good. So the
other aspect of it is the we call it the I call it the typical the container, the body, we're in the
soul, the body and the spirit, the mind, right? By the way, in popular, not so popular, you know,
like Kardashian, regular TV, but in stuff you see on YouTube and other places, and in print,
they're starting to not say mind, body, soul, mind, body, spirit, they're delineating it,
it's soul, mind and body or body, spirit, mind, they're no longer, there's less mixing of the
terms now, soul and spirit, they're starting to separate it out. They're not they're not
interchanging soul and spirit. I've started to notice that. Right? I've been doing Yeah, I've
been pushing that for 20 years, just like you shouldn't call children kids. Right? So that
watch for that, by the way, in the near future. Oh, here's another thing.
That was piss poor to begin with, because kids is
well, it's all piss poor. I just brought up the point that you have no organizing principle,
by the way, on a trivial, these are like 15 tangents. I'm entertaining here. Sure. I was
getting some had a list of, of getting stuff like bartenders, keeper, Bon Ami, dishwasher, soap,
stuff to clean oil stains out of the driveway and the bathroom and all this stuff like that.
Walking down the aisle where they have dishwasher soap, and you wouldn't believe what I saw.
They actually have dishwasher soap in a spray bottle now. Hmm. Yeah, I figured out Yes,
I'm going to figure it out. Wow. I haven't seen a Greek speak. I've been doing that for two decades.
Yeah, I haven't seen that on a shelf yet. I'm sure it'll get here eventually.
Yeah. Yes. Anyway, we you know, you just you and I, I think I talked about it.
On the O and G beginning. Yeah, but definitely on this one.
No, it's a great. It's actually a great idea. It makes perfect sense.
And well, you won't buy as much. So you're not gonna run out of just soap like you normally do.
Was it being done by a nationally recognizable brand?
Yeah, one of the the blue liquid? Yeah.
Okay. All right. Fair enough. I just was
Yeah, so I don't know whatever the dawn would be.
Dawn is one of the biggest ones. Yeah. And they have a whole thing about,
you know, not actually wasting their stuff.
You can look up dishwasher soap in a spray bottle, and it'll come up now.
Oh, I will.
Where if you did that a year or two ago or more, nothing.
No, what they had is this squeeze bottle that resembled a ketchup bottle
is what they had. No, no, we're talking about a
aeration sprayer. Yeah.
A bonafide sprayer.
What I'm saying is about two years ago, that was their new innovation was the
squeeze bottle, like a ketchup squeeze bottle that sits the other way.
So the spout is down, but it doesn't
Yeah, we should do a little handbook 101 things that people don't, you know, haven't
figured out yet. Right.
Anyway. Might be a bestseller.
That 101. Yeah. Dalmatians. Yeah.
That too. Back to the container, the human body,
the avatar or whatever. That has its own mind.
Like, for example, if you watch cat videos on YouTube, when a cat is spooked,
they always go through the same motion.
Right. When a dog's fish, they all have similar motions that they share
because they are that particular species.
That's the particular body.
Now, if you get to know the fish or you get to know the dog or the cat or the
chicken, by the way, chickens, they you can name them.
They'll they'll answer to their name.
You know, they'll call you when you call them by the name.
They'll come right.
Same with cows, by the way.
I wouldn't have thought of chickens as very expressive, but OK.
No, they will. They will.
Yeah, they're yeah.
Well, there's a chicken that plays checkers.
That's legendary.
Yeah. But that's because, yeah, training.
But still, OK, each animal has its own body and it does its own thing.
According to the body set up, it's in the way, let's say it's wired.
The the makeup of that body, what it's allowed to do, like a cat has got like
30 millisecond reaction time.
A cobra is 35 or 40 second reaction time.
What I mean is what I mean by that is if a cobra tries to strike a cat, the cat
will get out of the way.
Right. Right.
Where humans is not is not that fast.
And the cobra will strike faster than you get out of the way.
So in other words, cats are really downplayed.
You know, they're really extraordinary, you know, in reaction time and other
things like that.
And when they do get spooked, whether you know a cat or don't know a cat, you
could look around and you see they all have similar reactions.
The same with any other animal based on its body, separate from its spiritual
content. You know what?
What type of spirit?
Because if anyone who's had dogs or cats, let's say I'm using these as main
domestic animals, you'll notice that some are smarter than others.
Oh, always just like people.
Right. Yeah.
So like when my dog is I can I can always know because the ears perk up.
Right. Most breeds have the ability to perk up their ears.
They kind of stand up straighter.
Well, it's more than that.
Whether they can do math.
I had a dog, Butters, who could do math.
He's named after the South.
He's a gorgeous terrier.
And people thought I had trained him in the order of the formula of the math
questions that I gave him, like like, you know, two plus two, five minus three.
People thought that I gave them in a number of barks that he gave an order.
I said, you do it.
You do it in any order you want.
Here's and he would do it.
He knew math.
Any number between one and ten plus or minus.
Right. That's pretty.
Very, very.
Oh, my gosh.
Really smart.
And and I thought he was wonderful, but I'd never called him a smart dog until I
started showing him off and everyone else thought he was smart.
So I said, if everyone said he's smart, then I can call him smart, too.
No one will argue.
But what I'm trying to say here is that being in the human body, it has certain
tendencies, the body itself, the body has its own mind.
And I think just to recap, you got someone who's really sucky about being here and
he decides one day he's going to kill himself or herself and they're going to go
by drowning or whatever.
Jumping off the building is a little different while they're drowning.
Try to commit suicide, their body's like, I don't want to die.
My whole job here with this soul metabolism to keep this thing going as long as I
can, I don't want to die.
That's why a lot of people renege, you know, on the suicide.
They're so glad they were saved.
Many.
But if you jump off a building, it's kind of hard to change your mind unless you're in
the cartoons, right?
Yeah, well, the body.
So in other words, the body has a mind of its own and makes a decision to resist.
Yeah, that's right.
That's what cancer is.
Cancers are when you're you can eat certain things in the body's like, you've been
doing this for so many years, I can't adjust to it anymore.
So I'm going to put a block to block the energy.
It's called a tumor or whatever manifestation.
And because you're not listening to me, it's very subtle.
And it's funny how you have all these morons on YouTube or whatever, you know, subtle
energy healers and all that.
You bring this up to me like, oh, you know, so I don't endorse any of them.
But, you know, I'm not saying don't listen or whatever.
Yes, but I don't endorse them.
You know, I'm very careful about who I endorse.
And so far, I don't know who to endorse.
So, you know, you don't give us the Greek speak seal of approval or I could tell you
their stock prices go up and down with me.
That doesn't mean I endorse them either.
Right.
So and I don't buy their stock, you know, calling it a stock prices away, you know,
a stock falls right now and stock goes up.
So what I'm trying to say is there's the human body has its own attributes, just like
all dogs and all cats and all snakes and all that have like an attribute because they're
in that body that always tend to react very similarly because of the body.
So this body, if you go and look at, let's say, a lot of the lore, the religious lore,
holy rites, it's about separating from the body, right?
Like denying yourself things, right?
Like the Buddha, right?
Okay.
I don't have to get into examples.
If you're older than 13 years old, you know, you've heard it, right?
Denying yourself of worldly pleasures and all this other stuff.
Why?
Because they've realized this and they're trying to it's not create a struggle.
But if you have no need, if you see that you've separated yourself from you're not going to
ever engage in the struggle to get it right.
So if you say money, I don't need a wealth or anything like that.
I just need to some shelter and some basic food.
You'll never engage in that struggle, right?
What they call the rat race.
By the way, only rats could be in a rat race, right?
Sure.
But you and just like rats, if you confine them, you know, what do they start doing?
They start eating each other, right?
So, you know, the corporate culture.
And this is taught doesn't have to be that way.
So when you when you look at the progression of consciously saying, well, for example,
I'm going to be celibate, right?
So I never have to engage in sex, let's say.
So I never have to think about being a good lover.
I never have to think about finding a mate, right?
Or going on dates or having.
Right.
No, you don't have to direct any of your energy, your thought, your resources toward
people have with all that is out.
You'll never.
Right.
So if you say, I just I don't want to be poor because poor is a sense of
extreme deprivation or deprivation.
I don't want to be deprived.
But I have no interest in earthly wealth or money or just go day by day.
Plan accordingly, whatever.
You'll never enter the struggle of, you know, how am I going to increase my fortune?
Right.
Well, you're not looking for it.
So that's the better that's the perspective that was trying to be shown.
It's not, let's say, in certain ancient writs, it's not to deny yourself because you're going
to be suffering some kind of discomfort, you know, to to voluntarily go into discomfort.
It's not that at all.
It's to avoid the struggles that are inlaid, depending on what culture and society you
live in, to participate in those struggles and end up being, you know, spending energy
on those struggles.
So now that you're not spending energy, whatever struggle it might be, it might be relationships.
If you decide to be celibate, if it might be increasing wealth, if you decide that you
just need, you know, your most basic sustenance and basic things, whatever it might be.
Yeah.
That allows you to focus your time and energy on other things that no one else is focusing
on.
And you will seem like a master's miracle.
You know, you'll be able to come up with stuff.
Right.
And right.
You'll be a sage.
You'll be whatever.
But the thing is, this is never really taught the way I just said.
It's always people think that they have to suffer.
Suffer means to make the choice to go through something.
Some kind of discomfort.
And that will make them.
They're actually old, older traditions and quote, unquote, religions, not rits that,
you know, to bring pain upon yourself was, you know, a virtuous thing.
No, it's not about that at all.
Isn't this because people have this concept that unless there's punishment connected to
something, unless there's a penalty that people will.
Well, that's motivation.
Well, that's what it's turned into.
People do things because they if they don't do that, there'll be a penalty, not because
they're doing it because it's the right thing to do.
Right.
Like whenever I bring up the money system and taxes, even people that are in economics
and like it's fiat currency.
Why do they they don't need taxes to pay?
Taxes never bought in 90 years.
No one's taxes is paid for anything.
Well, I get you ever notice to create scarcity.
Well, you ever notice when you bring up the concept of, you know, like, well, gee, you
know, why wouldn't you want to commit murder?
You know, out of most people's mouths, first thing is the penalty.
Well, I don't want to go to prison.
I don't want to be put to death.
OK, there's the plain Jane murder, which is it.
So you can't do it in your neighborhood or to a family member.
But if you put on a uniform and go to another country, it's OK.
You get a medal for that.
Right.
Yeah, of course.
But that's my point here, though, is that when when you say to someone, why wouldn't
you kill or to in the Bible?
You know, that's glorified.
Right.
Well, I just said, you know, the second part of the first part's not.
It shouldn't be any of it.
Right.
That's it.
But then there's capital punishment.
You know, your life is taken if you take a life.
Yeah.
But that's the thing is that people say that that's the focus, you know, not because you
just shouldn't take a life, but because there's a penalty like you ever notice that that's
the primary concern.
I don't want to go to prison.
I don't want to.
I don't want to be executed, you know, taking life.
Any life, even in war, nationalism or army and all that was made the norm.
They would be so it would be so rare that someone would murder someone.
It would be so rare unless it was an accident.
Right.
And then you'd have to go to a city of refuge.
An accident is not a murder.
Yeah.
So there's a difference.
Yeah, that's right.
So but but you've actually it would be considered murder in this case because that person's
demise came to your do from your doing, even though it was unintentional.
Okay.
So what I would say there is then that's taken care of a city of refuge.
But as long as there's armies and killing that way, there's always going to be a problem
at home, right?
Where are you going to have to deal with that?
So this is a really screwed up part of again, what is the collective unifying message?
What is their statement of belief of humans in general?
Well, we just said earlier, it's nationalism and religion.
But if you look at that stuff, oh, my gosh, you'd have to be insane to follow that.
Any of that.
Oh, yeah.
It's all going to contradict each.
Each thing winds up contradicting itself.
Yeah, and it's not for your benefit.
It's for someone's organizing principle.
Right.
You know, to take advantage of you.