Sonic Event 40, Ocelli in the Greek, Rated Y, and here we go.
We were just talking before I pressed record about how, well, it looks like the majority
of things that you see out there that are distributed en masse are what?
And we all know this, don't we, Greek?
What are they?
Well, what do you want to call them?
Hmm, scripted, artificial, there's a lot of adjectives we could put on them.
Are those accurate, those scripted and artificial, would that be accurate?
Yeah, it follows cycles.
You know, people, people, you know, they say history repeats itself.
It really doesn't.
It's cyclical, and each cycle is slightly different, kind of like the wash.
Things, certain things come out, certain things stay in.
You know, for sure, any more than 100,000 people, it's all scripted.
You know, audience, just like a company over 100 million has somebody in there that's directing
it that you wouldn't know of.
And make no mistake, I mean, they create these things because they know there's a waiting
audience for it.
I mean, nobody produces stuff like that, you know, with big budgets and mass scale to give
it to nobody.
They know who they're delivering to already.
I mean, yeah, you know, it's like pushing cattle on a ranch.
A lot of, you know, when you want to sell a really good quality beef to others, you
don't push cattle on a ranch with quads.
It makes them nervous.
The meat gets tough.
You still use horses.
Yeah.
So anyway, if you could figure that analogy out.
I got you.
And a new generation of cattle doesn't mean that the techniques actually change.
Right.
Well, some of them, they use quads and they do make them, you know, traumatized.
Well, yeah, I mean, the the the local whatever Save Mart, you know, knockoff grocery store
allegedly has to get their meat from somewhere.
And if they can do it cheaper and more efficiently, regardless of the quality, well, again, there's
a waiting audience for it.
So anyway, Greek, what is on your mind this week, though, as far as because, I mean, I
can ask you questions about current events, but I doubt you're paying attention to most
of them.
Although I found it interesting, the current scripts, you mean the current script.
But there was an interesting glitch in the script recently, and I want to get your thoughts
on it real fast.
And then I'm sure you can roll into many other things.
OK, so alien disclosure, you know, like the whole time you and I are similar age whole
time we've been alive.
There's been this push and pull and all they're trying to hide things and disclosure.
And we're going to invade Area 51 even a couple of years ago.
Right.
I mean, all this stuff going on.
Guess what?
A guy went in front of Congress and said directly, I'm a whistleblower.
I know that the federal government is hiding alien bodies.
I know they're hiding alien technology, that they're reverse engineering.
Now, I'm not talking about a TV show per se.
One of the things that is up front, they tell you it's scripted.
I mean, this was in Congress, in public.
A guy said this.
We've had aliens here.
We have alien bodies.
We have alien technology and we're trying to reverse engineer it.
And I'm here to tell you that the government's hiding it.
And a guy told that to Congress.
Now, did that make better headlines around the world?
It did not.
But it did happen.
Sorry.
Well, the language.
Well, let's say you're let's say you what you just said is verbatim and let's say you're
paraphrasing either way, it depends on what your definition of is, is all right.
So if he's a whistleblower from the military, anything that's not, quote unquote, part of
that branch of the military is alien or or what do you call it when it's military approved
when something is, you know, they have that stamp on it.
It's not mil spec.
You know, what are they?
There's a term for it in the military that, you know, the the clothing, the stuff has has
to be approved.
Right.
Yeah.
It's government issue.
Right.
So government issued language.
If it's not within any of the departments of the military and those concerning them,
it's alien.
Right.
So it could be from another country.
The other thing is, well, we can get into that.
But reverse engineering is another thing.
It's just like the legal language.
The other thing is they're putting this out as misdirection.
Everything is misdirection, even though the actual happenings of the event is right in
front of you and more than plausible.
9-11 is a good example.
All the religions are good examples of Kennedy assassination, economic crashes.
Those are all things that are real.
But but the narrative that's put in front is completely false, but it also serves another
reason.
Well, like you said, when when they tell you that, you know, it's been a terrorist attack,
it was a drill.
When they tell you it was a drill, it's a terrorist attack.
There are oppositional languages that are put out to immediately quell anybody taking
a serious interest in something for it being the thing that it actually is.
I'm going to quickly actually share an article with you in the when I get a chance here,
you know, just to have you take a look at it, if you like, because it was printed in
The Guardian, just so you know about this.
But the funny thing to me, again, is that we didn't see this blasted everywhere, because
again, when you and I were kids, OK, there were certainly plenty of people out there
saying, you know, the truth is being hidden.
The X-Files was produced.
You know, we had Leonard Nimoy doing in search of when we were much younger, so on and so
forth, where people were saying, well, the moment the government admits this, this will
be a big problem and so on and so forth.
And now it seems like the event occurred and well, sorry, I want to interject.
There is no government. There is no government in law.
We don't have a lawful or even legal government anymore.
It's it's in receivership.
You know what I mean?
It's like, let's say Ben and Jerry's got bought out by a shoe company and the whole
thing was reduced down to whatever.
And, you know, frozen pops made with sugar, water and milk.
They could still use the label Ben and Jerry's because they actually bought the legal
rights. But it's not Ben and Jerry's.
OK, so the people under the government label have made rights, have allowed this
presentation to occur from a guy who is allegedly a former part of that.
You know, in the article, it says he was part of military organizations and
agencies. Anything that's not part of the departments is alien.
Yes. It could even be civilian if it's civilian deemed.
It's the civilians are typically not deemed aliens, but they can be given that
category like the Japanese were.
Remember, they put them in and the Italians and Germans.
Right. Right. That would have been even though the Japanese were born here, they were
put in internment camps and they were classed.
Their citizenship was pulled.
By the way, your citizenship means absolutely nothing.
That's a privilege that could be pulled any time.
Of course. So, OK, so now we just just repeat rehashed from the Guardian, even if
you're paraphrasing, just brings up again the emphasis on what I stated.
Well, if you want, I can read to you the bullet points so that you don't you don't
have to suffer it. And then no, no, you don't have to.
I've seen it. This has been coming for a long time, by the way, and it's going to get
worse. What they want is to get you looking up when things are really going down.
And then when the thing when the people find out that everything's going underground,
then the stuff in the sky appears.
So it's basically trauma.
Yes. So the purpose of the public showing then is just distraction as far as you're
concerned. It's to keep you looking at this circus so that you don't pay attention to
what the actual clowns are doing.
Yeah, well, they're more than clowns.
But what they are is imagine you have someone who just hates dogs, just totally
reviles dogs. And you put him in charge of the largest dog kennel.
How do you think. Right.
How do you think it's going to be run?
And what do you think he's going to do on his private time when he's at the kennel?
Well, it's going to be a noisy as hell kennel, first of all, because they're going to
bark at him nonstop.
And the other thing is, if he can find a way that he's not under surveillance, he's
probably going to sit there and try and secretly kick the dogs and then tell his boss
he doesn't know why they're getting more and more hostile.
Yeah. So that's what that's what we you know, it's it's it's such a run of fiction.
You know, the fiction, you know, both fiction and truth have a bearing on reality
because if you pick fiction like most people do, you could run your everything
happening is real.
But if you pick the truth, let's say, you know, then still everything is real.
So you can create your reality from fiction or you could create it from the truth.
Right. So both are correct.
I get that. You know, the only thing that I see as a negative is when people start to
identify every single thing absolutely is unreal, because then they miss real things
that occur and they decide to pay attention to nothing.
It seems like, oh, did I just describe most of humanity or.
Well, here's the thing.
There's a difference for people not to be confused.
If you have two people coming with two distinct, different accounts or narratives or
stories and they both say they have the truth, it can't be true.
Only one of them is true or both of them are false.
But in the structure of reality, in other words, what impulses people rely on.
You can your reality could base be based on pure fiction.
Look at attorneys and doctors.
Right. Their reality is based on pure fiction.
And there any success they have, let's say, in the medical is a testament to the
robustness of the human body, able to resolve such abuse.
Same with the legal.
So really cooperate in fiction.
Yeah. Coincidental as opposed to causal is what you're saying.
Like the fact that somebody got healed is really because their body healed
themselves. They didn't actually take care of the problem with their ridiculous
nonsense. No, they actually thwarted the healing process.
So if they didn't have that, it would if they would have recovered much faster.
Yeah. But this is the way so that people could take that fictional route.
Right. And still make it part of the reality.
Like if someone says, I'm in debt, why are you in debt?
Because I have three credit cards and I can't make the payments.
And that is their reality.
And they're stressed from it.
And material things around them change because of it.
And I'm telling you, that's all fiction.
Right. There is no debt.
It can't be right.
And it's a it's a law.
It's a legal and lawful impossibility.
That's why when people go to court over credit card debt or any other debt,
it's not whether they were lent any money.
It's whether they agreed to do something.
You see, you've got to be so it preempts that, you know,
the one thing that I'm going to be getting into is
the process of things, because that's one thing that's missing out there.
Well, I think anything we talk about is is because it's missing.
It's like, oh, the the world is full of square holes.
And it seems like we're the only ones that have the square pegs in most subjects.
It really sucks. You know that, right?
Oh, absolutely.
Because you can't go out and consume information
because you just too many questions.
And I mean, I'm saying that humbly, by the way.
But but here there's a process to everything.
You know, like there's the the secret Coke recipe, right?
So if you get the recipe, don't mean, Jack,
the recipe could be a paragraph long with bullet points.
But the process manual is 200 pages long,
meaning when do you add each and each ingredient?
What temperature does each ingredient have to be at?
How long do you stir given ingredients and then add the next ingredients?
You see? Yeah, it's a process.
That was something I recognized even as a child when somebody said, look,
as long as you have the recipe, you can do this or that.
And I said, no, that's not true, because here's the thing.
I mean, look, everything pretty much that you have a recipe for
that was ever shown to me had water. Right.
So I would say and of course, water is one of your focuses
because it is one of the essential elements to everything.
Here's the deal.
How about what temperature should that water be at?
How about, you know, not only how much of it, because I'll tell you,
well, look, it says three cups of water.
And I'm like, yeah, but hot water, cold water, this changes things.
Well, the process. Yeah, it's a process.
And there's processes that are always being negated.
So back to the alien disclosure, whatever Congress should show.
By the way, if you are a competent observer,
how this country was set up with the branches of government and all that.
And this was very well covered, by the way, in federalist papers
and other commentaries back in the day in the in the United States of America
is that the way that it's set up makes it really easy,
gives so much wiggle room to turn this into a completely tyrannical shithole.
Right. It does. Yeah. Yeah.
So basically, you know, everyone focuses on the president,
but it's really the Congress that enacts things right.
President cannot enact anything.
He can just sign a bill.
Well, that kills me.
That always kills me because literally it says that they are the ones
who legislate right.
They're the ones who actually create the legal structure.
Well, in actual. Yeah.
Yeah. Like if you go to, you know, like all of these alphabet
agencies are completely unlawful.
None of them are lawful.
And they only have to deal with the executive.
They're all functions of the executive.
Right. So they should only be dealing with the employees of the executive
and the other branches,
because the other branches supposedly get their check signed from that.
So the interesting part here is, like, for example, to pick up
one of these strong arm agency known as the IRS.
If you go to the IRS, why are you doing all this unlawful stuff?
They'll say, well, it's because Congress talked to Congress.
They enacted us.
And if you go to any of the congressmen that are competent, they'll say,
well, they threaten our lives and they threaten the lives of our children.
So why would you suscept the whole nation to what is it?
Four hundred, five hundred people in the Senate and the House of Representatives.
Why would you subject all of the people to the vulnerability?
You know, so all you got to do basically is threaten the lives of 600 men
in Congress, you know, both both houses and their children.
And they'll do anything. Oh, my gosh, that's a flawed system.
That's a very flawed system.
Very easy to leverage.
You can control the fate of 300 million people by taking control
or getting leverage over at the very least.
Just, you know, what? Half a thousand people, 500, a little
a little more than half a half could vote.
Right. You only 40, 51 percent.
I think it's more than 51 percent has to vote to enact something.
But it depends.
Like you have you have some things that can be done with 51 percent of the
you know, the majority, whatever they deem to be a majority.
But, you know, back to the the alien thing is there's a process here.
Everyone's looking at the formula and the recipe, right?
OK, very basic.
But there's a process to all of this.
And that process started.
Guess when? 1940s, 1950s.
And here, well, mainly out of Hollywood.
But it really started in the 18 late 1800s.
Right. With the science fiction. Right.
Right. That's when I started creating the legend that captured the imagination
and things like comic books, in a way, were sort of generated
to to do that, to bring people to other sorts of realities,
alternate realities and alternate constructs.
So really, you first see aliens being introduced to people in literature
because that was the most easily distributed aliens.
Yeah. Extraterrestrial aliens.
Correct. Off world things were introduced in that literature first. Right.
I mean, going back to H.G.
Wells, going back to many, many lesser famous people.
This is what they did.
They created a whole huge universe of legend around it. Right.
Mm hmm. OK.
And you notice they never focus or give too much on the serpent, the reptilian.
By the way, I'm just going to throw this in here.
The earliest, oldest beings in this, quote unquote, known reality are not human.
They're reptiles, Soren.
You want to call them Soren? That's fine.
OK. You want to call them draconian reptiles?
Anyway, that's another discussion, isn't it?
It kind of is.
I mean, it does go along with this.
But, you know, it's funny because a lot of people will immediately leap
to the Nephilim and the, you know, and that forms are hybrids.
Right. Say, yeah.
Again, I would defer to you got to get the chronography and chronology together.
I would defer to Jason Breshears at Archaics for chronology on that.
When all that stuff.
I mean, I consumed most of his stuff on the chronology.
He'll do long videos on stuff sometimes.
And I just got to I'm like, all right, all right.
Just just just stick with the chronology chronology.
You know, it's just stick with that because the rest of the stuff,
you're really falling flat on your face.
But so so everyone has got a piece of the puzzle.
You've heard of that. Of course. Yeah.
But you can't you can't whittle the you can't cut the piece to fit.
Right. Either fits or it doesn't out of the box. Right.
Right. So I would go on the chronography on that,
which is very close to what I've been saying.
But I wasn't aware of so many repeat disasters as they are.
You know, I was aware of maybe a dozen of them
or half a dozen of them that have been covered up,
especially in the past two millennia.
Like most people, you know, you've heard of the Black Plague and all that stuff.
There were several of them.
And also people, the world did almost come to an end around the seventh
between the sixth and the seventh centuries.
So, I mean, physically, I mean, it was just horrible.
And that's been covered up.
It's called the Dark Ages, right?
Well, it's dark. Yeah. Yeah.
So, yeah, you have that recurring.
And then also you have things that are also repeated like the flood.
Now, I do believe that we can see archaeologically
that there were several floods in various places.
But it's not just about the physical reality of that.
It's about the stories that spread and became part of the canon
in religions, in legends, in everything. Right.
There's a flood story that goes on.
Yeah. Science pretty much tells us it's all been happy dory going back
for two hundred thousand years and all this other crap is total bullshit.
But by the way, the biggest flood known was the one that happened
in Genesis chapter one, verse two, where the earth became dark,
weltered and wasted.
And then about sixteen hundred, eighteen hundred years later is Noah's flood.
So when you say the big flood, most people refer to the one that,
you know, hearkens back to Noah.
But the one before that, before Adam and Eve, let's say in the story,
that was the biggest, worst flood that destroyed the surface and all that.
So those are those are your two floods, by the way.
The one in where the earth became wasted, weltered and wasted.
Tohoho, Tohoho, right? Right.
So, yeah. Yeah.
So there's two major floods in the Bible.
And the first one, which is not viewed as a flood,
it's in the second verse of Genesis, was the worst possible thing.
And then the other one, which was local,
pretty much was the Noah's flood.
But yeah. So, yeah, all of these things.
But back to the process idea. Right.
I'll give an example of a process.
OK, so let's think of a process.
Let's let's say something called respiration, right?
Breathing. Well, the process on that is in many parts.
You have inhalation, right?
Then you hold the breath and then you have exhalation.
So just by saying respiration,
you get the idea that has to do with breathing.
You know, it's it's a technical term, right?
Respirator. Right. On all this other stuff.
Yeah. Coming from the Greek roots.
Actually, there's a Greek root for the formation of that word.
Yeah. Yeah.
Might be actually a Latin respirator or respite, but might be Greek as well.
But anyway, you see that now the process on that is inhale,
exhale basically than the holding time in between. Right.
And then we have what rate of inhale and what rate of exhale.
Right. Are you standing still or are you going around jogging around the block?
You see? So the process of it is very rarely discussed.
So basically, they're talking about respiration, but they're not telling you
about the how the aliens inhale or exhale. Right.
So how did they get it? Who are you?
You know, you're a whistleblower.
Did they get given a cogent history, like in other words, a history
that seems tangible?
Oh, no, probably not.
You know, anybody, you know, so the whole thing is a shit show
and it's going to get worse.
And here's the you know what you know what the worst part is.
It's going to get religious soon.
It's going to get the God is the G.O.D.
or D.O.G., however you want to spell it.
Sure. Is is going to be brought into the picture
like it never has in recent history.
And then it's going to get really, really rough.
So I said something that stopped a whole panel of people
from chattering back and forth needlessly on one of these.
You know, let's invite you into a group discussion shows recently.
And how did I do it?
Because I said that, you know, the fascinating thing
about the alien construct and all that is that by most people's
estimations, their idea of God is an alien to begin with
and isn't actually on this planet at the moment, huh?
And it literally stopped all this chattering that was going.
Well, here's another if you want to go.
That's like second, third grade.
When you get to the fourth grade, fifth grade.
Yeah. And you start studying all the old documents.
I'm not I'm not disparaging you.
There's a second or third grade.
I'm just saying that's what the way most people want to handle it.
Yeah, it's years ago on the private Skype groups.
And maybe you and I, maybe not.
The gods are human.
Sorry. Sorry, people.
Well, they just happen to be humans with extraordinary abilities.
Right. So just remember that.
Oh, no. You and I, you and I were on.
We didn't do a lot of the private Skype, you and I.
But the few that we were on, I remember that.
And I remember saying something about, yeah.
Well, where do you think they got the idea in the Bible?
Yeah. Where do you think they got the idea for Superman from? Right.
You know. And well, yeah, that gets complicated.
Yeah, that's that. Definitely.
Yeah, it's the see a culture always wants to define itself
somehow, and the easiest way to define itself is to create a myth
that structured a certain way that produces a certain narrative.
And then you associate with the character or that narrative of that myth.
All right. And when you talk about.
Yeah, no, I was just going to say when I brought up before and I said the flood,
I didn't mean the singular flood, by the way.
I meant the flood, which is constantly mentioned
and seems to be universally the same thing, when quite honestly,
a lot of these people are writing about things that happen to them locally.
Remember, we didn't quite have television back then or whatever.
So if something happened in Asia, they might not have witnessed it
and what they call Italy today.
So but the thing is that that story would carry
and it would become universal over time.
And in some cases, you have the flood as there's this one thing
that's represented in the literature that's not necessarily the same thing.
But what you're talking about in the scripture.
Yes, that's exactly how it goes.
But what I'm saying is you could have, you know, a seemingly world
ending event that occurred just in this valley that the majority
of the inhabitants would never leave during their entire lifetimes.
But they would think the world ended because the whole world was not.
It did world world is basically a society.
So, you know, you have different worlds without the let's see, attachments
that could be created with airlines and ships and communications.
Yeah. Most people, their world was whatever it was,
meaning their everyday function and even even their thought, you know,
well, far flung mobility is a fairly recent event in this current,
you know, timeline as far as our history goes.
Yeah, there was a time after the Dark Ages where there was worldwide travel
using aviation.
The Vamanas, you'll find in the Hindu society
still writings on that.
They were revived going back.
OK, Bob Lazar, the area 51 whistle, but whatever guy that guy element 115,
that guy, if you look at his stuff, there's hundreds of hours,
let's say 100 hours of his stuff for for a minute and a half out of those 100 hours.
This is what I got out of it. That was worth it.
So where did they find this stuff?
And he says, archaeological dig.
But no, you could talk to a thousand people that are into Bob Lazar.
And you'll ask, well, where did they find the flying saucers?
And they all shrug their shoulders.
I don't know, but he does mention it was found in what?
An archaeological dig deep underground.
So that's all you got to know.
Well, another fascinating thing is I was recently explaining to somebody that,
you know, when do you think rocket technology and,
you know, other technologies of flight occurred?
And they go, well, it must have been the early 1900s
because of the Wright brothers, blah, blah.
Or maybe it was as far back as Da Vinci, you know, whatever, because airplanes.
Right. Or maybe it was Da Vinci because Da Vinci had designs,
but he didn't realize them.
And some of those things look very weird that he's got, you know,
but rockets are stupid, by the way, they might be stupid.
But you do realize they had these schematics for this stuff.
There's manuscripts out there showing schematics for this,
going back to like the 1300s.
Well, the culture that developed the the propulsion method,
you know, the high speed chemistry that's used in rockets
never thought of putting people on that.
Now, that was the in Asia.
They've had it for more than 2000 years,
you know, gunpowder and all that stuff.
Right. High speed chemistry reactions.
No one in the ancient world ever thought of putting only the twisted
meat eater minds of the Americans in part, part, part of the the Nazis.
Right. Revived it.
No, they they had it set up in this 1300s manuscript
that somebody discovered only a few years ago, according to what I read.
You know, they were transporting things, not people,
but they would actually be able to safely send things over long distances
with that high speed chemistry as far back as that.
You know, I mean, look, maybe. Yeah.
But it's it's a dumb idea.
Listen, I'm not saying it's smart.
I'm just saying that it existed.
A lot of people think it started with, you know, the Nazis,
Wernher von Braun, blah, blah, blah.
And I'm like, no, these ideas were around
and people actually were trying to execute them much earlier in history.
The airplane didn't start with the Wright brothers either.
You know, et cetera, et cetera.
So I'm just saying that this concept of here's your innovator,
here's the guy who created radio, here's the guy who created wireless
and whatnot, usually is very ill-informed official.
Well, it's usually tied to an official story, which is
which is the worst possible source or worst possible.
That's why it's reinforced as such. Right.
I think you go on a YouTube or something and you look up moon landings
and they'll plug a Wikipedia, like a blue highlighted box
underneath. Here is your real information to go along with this thing.
It was dumb enough to go when they first started doing that years ago.
I was trying to click on it to try to get rid of it.
I found that it became a feature. Right.
So, yeah, there's a lot of features.
Yeah, they did that to me.
There was like 300 of my videos where I discussed aspects of the JFK assassination,
not always discussing conspiracy laden aspects either.
In some cases, forensic science or, you know, here's how the ballistics worked
or here's how, you know, this this person with this science
explained and examined this or whatever, very basic and academic, you would think.
And in some cases, there would be one of those little disclaimers
under there with a Wikipedia entry.
Go look at this and you go there. And what is it?
Lee Harvey Oswald is most likely the guy who shot Kennedy on.
Yeah, well, it's pretty blatant.
They had already set up a kill zone.
It was very specific and very highly agreed on.
Right. Because of the speed of the vehicle and the location.
And I believe that it was overtly known by many people by, you know,
who and how it was done and witnesses. Right.
But it just never got out.
Another example, it ties very nicely to the JFK is 9-11.
Like, for example, that's not a terrorism.
It was sabotage.
In other words, the nuclear demolition feature,
it was installed into those buildings via tunnels
way before even the the the the building permit was issued. Right.
So in other words, if you have a nuke in a in a urban environment,
it could it needs to be maintained.
But if you want to set it off, you need what's called a trigger mechanism.
Right. And that trigger mechanism is held by the Department of Energy.
And once the Department of Energy approves it, they call up the OST,
which is a part of the Secret Service.
The OST stands for Office of Special Transportation,
and they physically pick up the trigger from the DOE
and physically deliver it on site where there are DOT and OST and FEMA
and every the companies, EG and G, that do monitoring.
OK, so I can go on and on and on.
Yeah. Yeah. You're describing these people are talking.
Yeah. No, you're describing literally a part of this process.
There is a whole part of that process there where there's special
transportation units.
People might not be aware of this, but that'll handle special technologies
that handle particular types of people.
And a lot of these agencies are not, you know, things that you know of right away,
but they are, you know, branches of, say, the Secret Service.
The military has special transportation groups for certain things.
Beyond transportation.
I just went through a litany of groups and agencies,
and there's got to be more than two people in each one of these agencies
that knows about it.
How come they're not speaking?
And where are the witnesses?
Because they go home.
Let's say they have a wife or a dog or a cat or children or relatives.
Aren't they going to say anything?
They're going to say something.
Where are those people?
How come no one's speaking?
Right. There could have been there could have been 50 or.
Well, here's I'll stake my life on it.
There are at least 50 people that witness where the gunshots came from
and even saw the shooter that we never heard of.
You know, meaning witnesses that never got a chance to go public. Right.
And not immediately. No.
And some of them, people like me had to dig up later and get stories where,
you know, we had skittish people that maybe wanted to go on the record,
maybe didn't, et cetera.
So it was it was a weird situation, actually, with those people.
And this is what I say to those people and all people.
If you do if you don't do it, look, if they dislike you enough,
they'll blow your head off or find an excuse to kill you.
But don't you want to kick them in the shins at least once
because you're going to go anyway?
Yeah, do it. I really wish that I could have convinced.
As a matter of fact, there was a lady.
I'll tell you a quick little strange anecdote.
Just real fast.
There was a lady that took, let's say, photographs.
Let's say photographic evidence.
She had taken herself, you know, very much like some of the other people
who filmed the events there.
And when she brought it to go, develop it like a normal person would.
The film didn't come back to her.
And she had a a person from the government waiting at her house
when she went home after not, you know, sorry, your pictures didn't come out
to tell her that.
Yeah, she was definitely not going to get those pictures to come out.
And if she goes back and checks, they will have lost her film with good reason.
And it's interesting how the tracking, you know, everyone's concerned
about tracking today with technology.
So it seemed to have existed pretty robustly back then.
Yeah, they seem to know where everybody went.
And I mean, that's not I'm not talking about the sheriff's department
or because I've been through their documents, all that I'm talking about
in black type stuff.
Yeah. An agency that is not really named.
Some people say, oh, that must be the FBI.
But that's not the kind of badge they flashed.
The alphabet agencies are in your face blatant.
We're going to strong arm you using these alphabet agencies.
But there's a lot.
There's an entire society or group that is brought up from childhood
and within their culture to hate humanity, even though they're humans themselves.
And that's who's running all of that.
And everyone is under that system and being observed by them
at various times, especially if you're near a significant person or event.
Right. So I've had someone I know that I worked with in some capacity
in a business capacity.
She would be in places and she'd be calling me and she says,
I'm at Hunter Biden's house.
I'm like, don't call me from that.
You know what? Don't call me.
I think when we were doing what Charlie and the Greek, I told you about her.
I said, she's visiting the vice president's son and he's really horrible person.
And I don't know if you remember that back in 2015, 2016.
Yes. Well, 2015 before.
Right. And I was like, oh, and I was like, don't call me because you know what?
Happens if you try to make right.
They get all you get everybody. Right.
Yeah. Well, that's the thing is you get swept up in the we talked about that
surveillance off air, actually.
Yeah. We weren't recording at the time.
We were just we used to just have these conversations.
Yeah. I think I gave you the dirt on Hunter Biden before even anyone who he's
who even cared about.
Yeah. I didn't even know that he had.
I didn't know that.
Bob, I see. I knew about Bo Biden, but I didn't know about his brother.
That was the Bo Bo died.
And it wasn't he killed in one of the wars, Iraq or something.
I think he died of cancer.
He actually died of cancer.
Yeah. Right. From one of the burning pits or something.
Right. In the burning pit. Right.
All the chemical exposed, which is a real thing.
People were exposed to a lot of nasty.
Yeah. Yeah. And it's all I mean, it's just so bizarre.
You know, by the way, anyone who's got three brain cells together,
you just need two. But the third one is like a spare.
Yeah. It's been in any military knows that it's all bogus,
unless you're in like the French Foreign Legion or something. Right.
It's all bogus.
So the only movie that I've ever liked about that was Jarhead,
where the sergeant is telling them, remember,
you signed a car when they told him to do something and they were hesitant.
He'd say, you signed a contract.
Remember? Oh, yeah. Contract. It's all business. It's all.
Yeah. Humans are morons and people in the military are weaponized morons.
So what are you going to do? Right.
Not much.
But I still stick with when I start talking to people
and I see there's a hint that they're going to fade off.
I say, have you been on this planet more than 15 minutes?
You've been more than 15 minutes on planet Earth.
I kind of repeat it like that
just so they make sure that they heard me right.
And they're like, yeah, of course.
Now they're not going to glaze away.
And after two minutes of Greek speak at a hardware store,
they're like, by the way, have you heard this before? No.
Have you run into anyone that said stuff like this before? No.
I said, yeah, you know what? You probably won't ever again.
So anyway, yeah, it's really sad here anyway.
But you have to make the best of it.
Remember, you live in this is an amoral society.
Amoral means there's no right and wrong. Right.
You're encouraged to follow your dreams. Right.
Or follow. Right. Whatever you want to do.
That's encouraged. Right.
You notice that's encouraged first before being good
or being lawful or anything like that.
So that makes it an immoral society.
When you tell children in a society at large
that follow your dreams and do what you want to do.
I'm not talking Alistair Crowley stuff now.
Just generally first first before doing the right thing or being lawful.
That's an amoral society branded. Right.
You see. So. Yeah.
But, you know, the only difference there is when somebody says, you know,
you should do what's right or you should act,
which, again, is the definition of first, though.
First is follow your dreams and do what you want. Right.
First, I think of how many.
Well, statistically, if you look at it, you'll hear follow your dreams
and do what you want to do more than do the right thing
or more than be good or more than be lawful. Right.
A lot more. Yeah.
Well, that's why, you know, quite frankly, again,
even though Alistair Crowley was a Crowley, excuse me, was a plagiarist,
he did state the truth when he said, you know, do what thou wilt
shall be the whole of the law.
Well, that's in this situation to a certain degree.
Yep. To a certain degree.
But there's a lot of there's a lot of conditions that are left out.
So he was a you know, he's a well was well known, well established.
He was a foreign agent. Right.
Oh, well, a multiply useful to multiple agencies
at the very least.
And anybody who became his consort of one type or another also. Right.
I mean, blatantly with the Michael Aquino's of the world and all that, too.
Yeah, that goes into the the parallel society and all that leaking over.
Just like if there was a more advanced parallel society,
they would get lackeys or people from here that work as slaves.
There are those that come from another society that lives in the underworld.
It could be on the surface, but be considered the underworld
that leak into this society and get notoriety. Right.
Like the ones you mentioned. Oh, yeah. Sounds to me like.
But they're the lackeys, though.
They're not the high functioning ones.
Yeah, but it sounds to me like, you know, you know, the phrase
as above and so shall it be the same below.
However, they say it.
It's kind of interesting to me, because it seems like that's actually the way
the ethereal or spiritual or whatever else.
That's exactly how that works.
Well, we're in the middle.
There's it depends.
You know, you could say as above, so below, meaning of the sky or as above.
So below, meaning on the surface underground.
Of course, it goes.
You see, you know how they say there's two sides to a coin,
but everyone leaves out the reeded edge, the edge of the coin,
the third side, which determines its value.
So all of these things have ratios that are unacknowledged.
That need to be looked at.
Yeah. Yeah.
And that's what Greek speak does really.
Sad to say.
Sad because it's a.
It's kind of like a place where the onus is on the Greek
to come up with this stuff to a certain degree and and make
and find it, make it a working knowledge.
You know, not talking about things that aren't pertinent
and not useful. Right.
That's the hard part.
You know, actually, you always want to make it working knowledge.
Well, the difficulty level should be described
thusly, given the metaphor you just laid out, which is this.
You know, you flip a coin, right?
What do they tell you to call heads or tails?
But occasionally, ever so occasionally,
it can land on that beaded edge.
There is another option.
But the rarity of that is just about the rarity of the truth or reality.
Yeah. When it comes to this world.
So there you go.
That's that's the rarity of actual morality.
That's the rarity of actual, you know, knowledge,
as opposed to all the noise and nonsense, isn't it?
Sure is. Hey, how about we jump into the chat just for a moment?
Oh, absolutely.
I was thinking that we were almost at the end here.
But let's go to the chat. Go ahead.
We are a question keeps being brought up about the silver,
the silver and the water.
And one of the things that just rang out, I have gone over it loosely.
Maybe I'll try to tighten it up.
Why do you need electricity?
Actually, you don't.
But electricity is the most convenient way to do it.
It's regarding the aqua sargentum.
This is not colloidal silver, by the way.
Colloidal silver is toxic.
And I believe it's toxic in any amount.
Right. Because if you understand how the body works with induction,
it will create instead of using the energy of the silver,
it will try to create the metallic silver, which is toxic in the body.
You want the the quality of the silver without the quantity. Right.
So the reason why electricity
is preferred to be used is because of the push.
How do you the silver metal, whether I'm not going to say coin form,
but pure silver metal, if you want to get the quality,
the bacteriostatic, fungicidal
and other qualities of silver into the water
because the water is the most biocompatible agent.
How do you take that field or that effect,
nonmaterial effect that silver has and get it into the water?
Imagine the silver material itself is like a dolly or a trolley
or a truck or a box.
And the field is in that box.
How do you get it to go into the water?
You have to push it or dump it out. Right. OK.
And electricity is what pushes just the field.
If you just use the right subtle amount of electricity,
it will push the quality and leave the material behind
and push that quality and imbue that quality into the water.
In view, I always like that word.
I wonder if it's a French word.
And then the so the silver
positive qualities that we are looking for, no pun intended,
you know, positive and negative electricity.
So once those qualities are imbued in the water,
then the water being the most appropriate by a lot
biocompatible agent will then imbue it and transfer it to the body.
I am open to other ways of doing it.
Wilhelm Reich mechanical movement creates some energy build up,
which then creates an energy discharge.
Mm hmm. That's why this is the years ago.
Those that had silverware, real silverware,
were not as prone to things inducing things,
diseases and contagions like others did.
So, yes, drinking from a silver goblet using a silver spoon is beneficial.
But still, if you understand how friction works on a most finite level,
if you're using a silver spoon for years and years and years,
especially if it's plated or a goblet, you'll notice that
after years and years and years of use and wear, some of the silver is gone,
whereas material is gone, isn't it? Mm hmm.
So you're taking the silver again.
So the best way to determine how to push that field off
is a slight electrical push, because everything in the world
works on pressure mediation, the things where a higher pressure
will always go to a lower pressure to what find equilibrium.
Yeah, so that's basically it.
Also, just a reminder, I am nearly done with a standard
aqueous Argentum kit.
OK, I'm not I'm not really offering these,
but I did offer one one request from someone I value.
That is also a sub I've known for a while and it will be on their way.
And why not?
When I'm making one, I can make two and I can make another one for myself.
I offered to do a giveaway.
So I just wanted to put that out again.
There will be a giveaway based on all of the subs on Rated Y
that Chuck will pick at random.
All right. So and I've been going through actually doing a bit of a audit
just to make sure about who's on the list,
make sure that there are duplicates and everything to prepare that
for a random selection.
And really quickly, I just while you were talking, I figured I'll go look
because I love etymology dot com. OK.
It's really a valuable tool.
And early 15th century, this is a verb in view
to keep wet, to soak, to saturate, also figuratively to cause, to absorb.
OK. And the it says that
it has a Latin and a French origin, but it's somewhat uncertain
from possibly from the Latin in vibrate, in vibrate.
I am B. I. B. E. R. E.
Which I believe is in beavery.
But anyway, drink in, soak in is in quotes next to it.
And it also says to see him vibe.
So it might have also been influenced by the English word for for that as well.
So there you go. It's a it's sort of a loosely.
Yeah. From Latin and French.
All right. So we don't have a misunderstanding.
Remember George Bush, the junior, the small bush?
Yeah. He said the reason why French
aren't good at business is because they don't have a word for entrepreneur.
I love that.
Yeah. You know, that's the kind of stock you have.
That's what they think about.
You know, when they are really stupid leaders,
which they all are at this point and have been.
That's those that are in control, trying to show you what they think of you.
Yeah. I mean, my favorite from him will always be, though, the whole,
you know, fool me once,
fool me twice.
You can't get fooled again.
Yeah. Like you couldn't even keep that very simple.
You know, I think
he couldn't do the fool me once.
Shame on you. Fool me twice. Shame on me.
He couldn't do it.
He just that's why I've always said if you vote at elections, you get what you deserve,
you know, because the voting does not elect the electors elect.
Then they tell you that the Electoral College does.
So if you vote, you get what you deserve.
Voting just means that you are giving your endorsement to the process
that whoever is an elector is going to do the right thing for you.
This is how ridiculous it is.
So it's really it's really for you to select the elect,
which was another word for the elite, by the way.
And I guess if they called it that nowadays, people might see it as a conspiracy.
And indeed, guess what? It is a conspiracy.
So the elite, excuse me, the elite, by the way,
they just happen to be in the position they are.
And they just happen to hate humans or hate people.
Yeah. And that's the if you understand that deeply,
you'll understand the condition that we're in.
And yeah, so.
But there was there was a class concept called the elect, though.
I mean, there really was.
That was a proper way to describe people that were what in an elevated position
in society, they were the elite, so to speak.
So, yeah, you could actually and I always find that fascinating.
And just as fascinating as the people go, they stole the election.
Who did they steal it from?
It wasn't you because you didn't own it in the first place.
And that's right. You're not an elector.
Yeah. Show up at a voting booth, say you were here not to be a voter,
but you want to elect.
I had someone do that once in Arizona and they had him stand over here
and they had him sit there for like two hours
until a bunch of men in black type people came.
They had to call them up and they came and they started asking personal questions.
So this was a long time ago, maybe 2008 or something like that.
So, you know, in other words, what they asked was not illegal or unlawful.
They just wondered where the hell he came from.
And I said, you should have just told him you're just visiting this planet, you know?
Yeah. But, you know, people are afraid about being confined, you know.
And back then it was a little more common, I think.
I think it still happens today.
But, you know, they do have these ways of what was that
that term they use for a little bit of rendition, right?
Where they rendition you, which I always found hilarious
because it's a rendition is to, you know, you do a rendition,
you're doing a version of something and they're taking you, they're snatching you.
How is that a rendition?
I guess, right.
You rendition is usually a reduction of something.
Not what the way they're using it.
But anyway, I just want to go back to the silver real quick, Chuck, because
people are going to be I noticed for years, people will be wrestling with ideas
that drive things home very simply,
especially when they it's not that they're disregarding ideas.
It's that everything that's put out is so contrary.
In other words, the convention that the body absorbs things. Right.
And if this is good this way, more of it is better, you know, or whatever.
The the thing is to make knowledge as functional as possible.
Like, what do you see?
Want to get into also in the future about how to look at things,
you know, when someone hands you something or when someone points into a direction
and says, do you see that?
It's like, how do how do you actually look at things?
Right. You know, basically on a construction site,
you ever see a carpenter to hold up a board and look a certain way,
see if it has a bow in it or where the crown is. Right.
You know, things like that. How to look at things.
I've noticed that most people don't have that skill
or how to make it, let's say, work between the senses, between the ears
and then what comes out of their mouth to communicate.
So all of these things.
What I would suggest, though, is that once you understand induction,
where there is no material aspect to the process, it's all energetic
and you can pick another word.
That's why I lean on saying the body works by induction
instead of just saying energy. Right.
Because that word energy has been abused. Yes.
And then you understand that the food or the intake or whatever,
let's say a remedy has to comport to that.
It cannot be wholly material. Right.
So again, and the other thing is pressure mediation.
That's what makes anything fly or move. Right.
The high pressure goes to a low pressure to make equilibrium.
The one thing I'll get into in the future is also what equilibrium
in the body really is and why there is no such thing as health.
Health should always be a consideration on what you what condition you want to be.
And I think we've briefly covered that where someone says, what's healthy?
I said, there's no such thing. Are you healthy for what?
Do you want to climb Mount Everest next week
or are you going to be sitting at an office job?
There is no such thing as good health.
It's what condition you want to be in.
Are you running a marathon? Right. What are you doing?
Are you a single mom with five children?
All those things require different health conditions and fitness.
The word instead of health should be fitness.
What level of fitness are you looking for?
So all of these things that make a functional knowledge. Absolutely.