The sonic event 2-1-3 and this
is Rated Y so but you already know
that because the only way you get it
is by subscribing on Patreon.
Greek, how are you today?
Oh, that's a either a colloquial question good
to say I'm fine, but otherwise I'm doing
okay fair to Midland actually too great depending
depending.
Yeah, mostly dishonest answers come out of that
question from people, you know, they just they
just respond out of reflex.
It's I can't yeah, how am I doing?
Well, let's say what am I doing?
Let's do it.
We're 213 times.
We've met already here.
All different lengths of all sorts just organically
banging out something.
I mean anywhere from two hours to 26
minutes.
I think they've been you know, so anyways,
you got you said you got a lot
of stuff, right?
Want to try to battle through it or
I do I'm going to get to everything
as quickly as possible.
So here's one.
I've read a small book from Michio Kushi.
Okay, Greek mentioned.
He's a very dogmatic about some things.
Okay.
What about cannabis?
Because he's really condemning it as a bad
substance in his book.
So what do you think of cannabis?
There's the question overall.
Wonderful, wonderful, wonderful plant depends on who's using
it and how you're using it because you
can go to the variety of hemp, which
is a superior fiber to the oils, which
are superior oils.
They are superior, you know, when certain oils
have a too low of a flashpoint to
cook with or go rancid or this or
that.
They have the entire hemp genre cannabis superior
oil extraction.
You can it can be eaten as a
supplement as an herb.
It can be smoked.
It's really a miracle.
It's a miracle plant.
Extremely versatile.
It also seems to filter out bad things.
You know, if you plant it around other
things, it seems to suck it up so
you can get rid of it and you
can just sort of burn it off if
you want.
Yeah, it adds nitrogen.
Sometimes it takes nitrogen.
So I would say that it's fine.
Now, if I smoke it, it turns me
into a piece of the furniture and I
prefer like, you know, the THC part and
there's a CBD and all that.
It turns me into a piece of the
furniture.
And whenever I feel its effects, I'm waiting
for it to wear off.
I'm more I feel better not doing it.
Right.
But that's me.
That's me.
But just like anything, too much is too
much.
And everybody's different.
You know, I mean, for me, it's any
amount, though.
Even taking a puff off of even back
in the back of the day, I did
a lot.
And even like when I was still in
bed, I'd reach over and grab a roach
in the ashtray and puff on it before
my feet touched the bed.
So I would start my day off.
Right.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, you're describing my teen years.
But go ahead.
Yeah.
Before I even got out of bed, you
know, you finished off, you know, as I
was going to sleep, I smoked.
Right.
So, yeah.
But then I realized, you know what, I'm
better off without it.
And one of the realizations was I was
with a band and we're like, oh, this
is really good.
We let's record.
And they recorded and it sounded so bad,
so incoherent.
Now, let's fast forward.
We'll get to the good part.
There was no good part.
It makes you think things sound amazing until
you stop, you know, feeling the effect is
what the fun part is.
And with musicians, I notice that all the
time.
But, you know, yeah, I think it's great.
You're like, oh, no, you're just not listening
to the part where we've got really good.
No, this is the best part.
No, it's terrible.
Stop getting high.
We were creative.
Where's the rest of the tape?
That is the whole tape.
Yeah, I know.
Anyway, on the topic of plant energy.
So otherwise the plant itself is wonderful.
But go ahead.
Sure.
On the topic of plant energies.
Now, somebody wrote a whole long thing about
how they've been doing observations based on the
ways that you've described plants and energetic motions
and how, you know, things dip and everything
else.
One interesting one is okra.
It is a prolific producer, can grow taller
than corn, although not ideal.
The flowers point vertically.
The fruits grow vertically.
Any fruit left on them dies, will stay
on the plant.
The dead plant will stay upright all winter.
Pods dry.
It's like a hollow stalk.
Yeah.
Like a sunflower almost.
So he's describing this and using the same
observations that you use with the plants and
just wanted you to know that somebody is
picking up on that part.
Well, that's good.
And also that real slimy mucus texture that's
inside the fruit, very similar to papaya seeds,
if you've ever or some melons, that real
slimy, heavy texture goes almost from like a
male, you know, semen texture to light, light,
like a thick liquid gel kind of stuff.
Whenever you see anything that has that, it
promotes vacuum in the body.
It's actually producing the stuff the body produces
to induce and protect itself from vacuum.
So, yeah, it's quite interesting.
So it can be used for healing.
It's very.
The only thing is, though, when you have
a plant that produces that slimy texture, papaya.
I recently got a big papaya, cut it
open and put it put it in the
blender, just papaya, a little juice juices itself.
It's really cool.
And you could drink it because there's no
fiber in it, really.
And I felt really good from that.
And but it gave me a little bit
of a sore upper intestine.
I did too much of it, I think.
But that when you when you clean the
seeds out, anything that has that slime like
okra, papaya was the two things I could
think of.
Melons kind of have it.
It depends if it's really ripe, it's dry
on the inside.
Right.
Like cantaloupe or whatever.
But typically, if you can get anything that
will that will induce and promote vacuum in
the body.
The only thing, though, is that it does
it very rapidly, almost too quick.
All right.
So you're better off, again, using something that
isn't so.
But let's say someone is losing vacuum.
Like, well, how do you diagnose that?
Right.
That papaya and okra or whatever supplement would
be good or fresh.
Anyway, I was going to say, why not
create a condiment out of the papaya, in
which case you could utilize it just a
little bit along with your food and then
you can take in a little bit.
And it's actually papaya and it's called but
you can buy papaya and it's a meat
tenderizer, which can be considered a condiment.
Well, I didn't know that, but I was
just thinking, why not create a condiment?
Sure.
It doesn't change.
One thing with these kinds of things that
like papaya and content in papaya, fresh papaya
is 100 times more potent than when you
dehydrate it.
Yeah.
So they synthesize it also.
So the crystal kind of looks like MSG,
almost like actually MSG is a very weird
looking crystal.
It almost looks toxic.
Yeah, it does.
I'm not taking notes.
I was thinking segue, but tangent.
If you look up the word economics, ecos
means house and nomosnomics means law.
And I was speaking to someone earlier about
all the ideas that I have, you know,
and why not do a small two or
three part series called microeconomics.
And I'll throw people off because when you
take economics, they think it has to do
with finance.
Well, it does.
It does as well, but very small.
Remember home economics, right?
Yeah.
And the terms macro and microeconomics do exist.
So you're going to have to redefine it
probably.
Yeah.
Microeconomics, basically when you're around your dwelling, covering
all the various subjects from cooking, cleaning, repairing,
maintaining hygiene, because, you know, the condition of
your dwelling is part of your hygiene.
Imagine walking into a dwelling place, apartment or
house, and you haven't met who lives there
yet, but the place is like a real
bad mess.
You don't say this person also has bad
hygiene, right?
But it's tied in.
You know, you can say that and be
pretty accurate.
Well, you don't expect a perfectly clean, absolutely
pristine person to walk out of a disaster
area like that.
That's what's true.
Yeah.
But typically a disaster, you know, grime and
stuff, you know, a really dirty car, dirty
house, also associates with the person's hygiene.
So microeconomics would be how to stay on
top of these things.
And one of the reasons I was bringing
this forward is because as our environment is
changing, you know, the simulation, let's say, the
way things are accredited to us.
Things that I did in the past, like,
you know, mow the lawn, fix this, paint
the fence, you know, just giving examples here,
sew up some pants you don't want to
throw away, repair some shoes, takes so long
to do now that it's almost not worth
doing.
It's like, why is this taking me so
long?
Why is it taking me half the afternoon
to repair these cargo pants that I like
where before I would just like to sit
around and do it in 15 minutes?
Why?
I mean, so things like even just cleaning
house takes so long to do comparatively, something's
going on in our reality, right?
So I wanted to maybe bring these things
forward so if other people are experiencing chores
and things that normally, you know, were done
automatically seem to take so long now, maybe
it would help.
So we'll just put that, you know, we'll
see if we get any feedback for the
microeconomics course.
We'll do it with you.
We'll do it right here.
It'll be available to whoever is on.
I'll go down a long list of things
to cover in your in your everyday surrounding
life, workplace, home and all that.
So let's go back to the questions.
So it could be, you know, the Greeks
on that class.
Literally.
All right.
Literally what is, but we may call it
microeconomics.
It's, you know, micro meaning close, right?
More small.
But it's either way.
I wouldn't feel bad about going to home
ec either.
Just just because it's shorthand and it would
make.
I like home ec is better.
It probably explains more.
I think they stopped teaching that, though.
Or let's say part.
I don't think that's part of any curriculum
anymore.
It might be correct me if I'm wrong,
but I think it was done away with
a while back.
It may be a little more rare than
it used to be, sort of like civics
classes.
Anyways, it's interesting that Iran's leader gave 2040
as the end of Israel, which is also
the Phoenix year given by archaics.
In Iran, they display on one of the
main squares a countdown screen that goes all
the way to 2040.
Are you aware of this?
And what are your thoughts?
I wasn't aware of it, but you'll see
if you go and put in the what
happens in the year 2040.
I remember articles from MIT putting stuff out
that society, as you know, will end in
2040.
I knew that in 2005.
There was stuff in the 90s saying 2040
was the end of that.
So when archaics came out with this 2040,
I was like, oh, yeah, I've heard that
before.
The 2012 stuff was a fashion, right?
Everybody, you know, the only thing that would
happen after 2012 is 2013.
So and I told that to people because
the Mayan calendar can't be reckoned cross calendrically
with the Gregorian calendar.
There's no cross.
You know, there's no cross reckoning.
You have to do the counts independently.
And archaics gets into that.
If anybody's heard me before archaics came on
the scene, they know I was on board
with all that.
But not specifically the Phoenix.
I was not aware of the Phoenix other
than when he talked when I first heard
of him speaking on the Phoenix.
I said, oh, that's the great crossing that
I've read about.
There's a crossing that happens or an object
goes from north to south and also reading
Charles Fort.
But Charles Fort never showed a periodicity.
He just talked about the phenomenon.
So, no, it does.
It makes sense.
I do recall, though, reading an article a
long time ago at MIT Computer.
All right.
Calculated 2040 was the end of everything as
we know it at the end of, you
know, whatever.
And I was using biblical reckoning.
Nineteen ninety eight's end of time.
And you add thirty three and then you
add another three and a half to that.
So that would put us in the year
30, 20, 33, 20, 34 from biblical reckoning
that we have in the Middle East Union
or a lot of hoopla in the Middle
East.
That Middle East would be world focus and
dominance by starting in twenty twenty five.
That was my shtick on that from the
information I had.
So, no, I think it's brilliant.
I think the periodicity is more important because
when you what our brochures did by nailing
down the periodicity of one hundred thirty eight
years.
Right.
Is really what you need.
If something has a periodicity, find out what
it is.
Right.
So there's no guesswork.
So it's got a reoccurring time span.
Get to know that.
Yeah.
So you can.
Yeah, that's more.
That's, you know, like the bus schedule.
Right.
It might be a little early, a little
late, but, you know, it's coming at.
But generally speaking, it runs out right at
about the hour.
And, you know, it's you've got to be
there before the hour to make sure you
catch it.
And, you know, if you're a little bit
past the hour, you missed it.
I mean, that's kind of sticklers about getting
it out on time.
So I think it's a stickler thing, the
Phoenix 2040, I think.
But typically there are signs way before.
So we'll see that.
And yeah, we'll see.
I think as as year as more time
goes by, it'll be quite obvious, more obvious
what's happening.
But I think they're going to do an
artificial shutdown because they don't want to they
want to be in control.
So they'd rather say the end of society
happened in 2036 than 2040, because then they
did it.
Right.
You know, the ego thing.
So, yeah.
And plus, you don't want to do it
on even year because then it becomes more
obvious.
Yeah, they're going to try to shut it
down before the Phoenix comes, because, again, like
Brashear says, when they do reemerge after the
disaster, they don't want to see anyone with
any kind of advantage here.
They want to be able to come back
up and dominate.
So they want to disadvantage you before we
can you before the blow.
So it's funny.
It almost sounds like that nonsense Boogliosi invented
about Manson coming out of Death Valley with
his followers.
Anyway, Greek, can you tell a bit more
about how to diagnose the difference between circus
flu in quotes versus loss of vacuum?
I use circus flu as the example you
gave us about not feeling well.
I call it the circus flu.
Yeah, because it came on when my niece,
Wendy Blades, came to visit.
And the conditions I've explained of a traveling
circus.
Also, she's a blood relative.
Sister's daughter.
My sister's daughter.
Right.
Very close.
And it her frequency.
She was adapted to it.
I wasn't.
And it slammed me.
It's all frequency.
Of course, we, you know, hugged and kissed.
Right.
No exchange of bodily fluids, but close proximity.
Was enough.
And frequency.
And yeah.
But a loss of vacuum.
Okay.
Loss of vacuum.
Your body.
In order for a living thing to be
alive, it has to have a biological vacuum
induced.
Meaning an inward pressure, something that sucks things
together to hold them together by a negative
pressure.
And it's very slight, but it's biological.
Right.
When that goes, the thing starts to decompose,
where it doesn't matter if it's a bacteria,
plant, animal, human, fungus, whatever.
Once I shouldn't say fungus because fungus preserves
itself by becoming a crystal.
Because it's a crystalline form.
So fungus is an entirely different thing, which
would be a very good study because it
seems to be able to bypass the necessities
of the biological vacuum.
But what happened was with the circus flu,
it disturbed the body's ability to maintain the
biological vacuum, that the biological vacuum started to
deteriorate.
That's what poisons do.
So all the cells go into just like
you have these metronomes, you know, these things
that keep time, just like timing in an
engine.
You have mitochondria, external internal impulse, mitochondria inside
of the cell all the way to external
forces like nitrogen.
We're nitrogen breathers that require oxygen mixed with
the nitrogen in order for it to work.
We're not oxygen breathers.
Remember when NASA, they gave them oxygen, everyone
got sick.
You get pneumonia if you just get oxygen.
We're actually nitrogen breathers that requires a percentage
of oxygen for it to work.
So because we convert the nitrogen to oxygen
in the body with a catalyst of some
oxygen.
So all these influences, it's not one thing.
See, we still have the mentality that you
take this pill or this antidote or this
and that's it.
It's a very complex system if you don't
understand it.
The only thing is when you do understand
it, it's simple to you, but complex to
those who don't again.
Right.
So there's someone who understands this biological vacuum.
And here's the thing.
I have people in the field say in
medical field and biology say, Greek, you're the
only one talking about or emphasizing the biological
vacuum.
Hey, I'm not saying you're wrong.
I'm just saying you're the only one like
there's something wrong with that.
Right.
So by looking at it, it requires timing.
Like, for example, when you have a timing
chain or a timing belt that turns the
cams on an engine, if you don't know
anything about it, you can look this up
and see how it makes sense.
The teeth on the teeth on the cogs
for the cam have to be exact, exact
fit on the chain.
You know, it's called TDC, top dead center.
Everything has to be aligned perfectly.
If you're off by one tooth, it's hard.
You know, you might look like you have
everything aligned.
But if you don't check those timing marks,
that's how I work is slightly.
Obviously, I think it's on that.
It's not one tooth off.
The engine will run rough, really rough.
It'll vibrate.
So it's it's a timing thing.
It's a pulsation thing.
Well, almost almost anybody who was a kid
and had a bicycle would also identify with
the same problem with the chain.
The second you bend a part of the
sprocket.
I mean, it's a nightmare.
Right.
Well, yeah, yeah.
But the timing, what I mean by that,
see the poisons in the body like that
you can administer to kill someone like cyanide,
arsenic, things like that.
Yeah, it goes after the cells ability to
produce phosphorus.
Right.
That's what they say.
Chemically, it's partially true.
And there's an ignition cycle inside the cells.
And if you disturb that, I believe all
these these things act as engines to keep
the biological vacuum going.
And it's not necessarily a force, but it's
a force when it's in motion.
In other words, once once it gets going
and it's in balance, you have what's called
a very fit or healthy organism.
Anything to disturb any anything in that clockwork.
Right.
And the simplest example of that is when
you break the skin, you've breached the vacuum
and the body right away gets the signal
to send fluids and swelling and all that
to stop it.
Right.
But the circus flu and the vacuum is
a very I don't see a direct correlation.
But, yes, that's what it would do.
I've coined it the circus.
Actually, that would be interesting.
You know, we can we've coined a lot
of stuff.
You know, the last thing I remember going
on a tangent here again is when you
see stuff and it looks fake and I
call the aftertaste, you know, so the circus
flu could be something that might sound too
comical for people.
But that that's that comes from pure induction.
Right.
So, yeah.
All right.
I can get it.
You know, I've got a lot of thoughts
on these things and anything, you know, the
biological vacuum, because I'm actually working on it
and researching it.
And anything, any question on it will actually
let you know where I'm at with my
research.
Also, I kind of give it away.
Yeah.
So anyway, it's a big field and and
I've been getting some messages of some people
looking into it.
But we're in a culture that completely denies
it.
You know, I said, if you ask, check
GPT, is the body under a biological vacuum?
It clearly says no.
And then comma, there is a pressure in
the body that, you know, it's like, oh,
my gosh.
Yeah.
Well, anyway, look, there's a lot more to
get to anyhow.
Look, you've got somebody who lives in Southeast
Asia.
All right.
And they describe something called D.E.N
.G.U.E. Not sure how to pronounce
that properly.
Fever, which is caused by mosquito bites now.
Yeah.
Fever that dogs get that pets get that
here.
Well, yeah.
Well, they're concerned about getting it there because
it causes chronic problems.
It's pretty painful.
All that.
OK, so do you know anything of this
type of illness?
It looks like there are no preventative measures.
You find out only when you get it.
What would you take in this case?
OK, we're baking soda help or something like
that.
The best thing is find out what the
people who are, quote unquote, an air quotes
immune to it or don't have it that
are near places that you could get it
and eat what they eat.
Like, for example, the water in the Ganges
River, you know, people use for drinking water
and you'll see people defecating in it and
dead bodies floating in it.
Right.
But they don't get sick because if you
look at what they eat, they have these
intense curries and intense herbs that they eat
in the Indian diet.
So if you're going to go there and
find out where the gangue fever is prevalent
and what the people that are in that
prevalent zone eat and eat that before you
go there.
OK, well, this person lives there and seems
to say that, like, it's just not preventable
for people there.
Oh, I see.
So it might be outbreaks and things like
that.
Baking soda, definitely, because that would change your
frequency big time.
And they asked about them as well.
So.
I don't know.
Yeah.
That's experimental.
It's experimental.
But I would definitely do the baking soda
water.
OK, I would do I would do also
the quinine water, you know, the tonic water,
the tonic with the quinine in it.
OK, yeah.
Yeah.
And I would do I would do whatever
local citrus is there.
Incorporate that into my diet.
Also good.
I have small various varieties of limes and
citrus.
Yeah, that quinine tonic water is also good
for cramping in the lower in the in
the lower legs and stuff like that, too.
It helps.
And also learn how to make the aqueous
Argentum.
You know, it's basically it's not colloidal.
So sorry, not colloidal silver because there's no
silver content.
But you use a one volt battery single
cell with silver to make it put it
in the water for just a minute.
Yeah, I put a few people together about
that and I haven't heard back yet.
Hopefully there'll be some stuff and gave the
schematic which you passed to me.
Anyways, question number two from the same person.
I heard the Greek saying many times that
he enjoys kratom.
I also like it a lot, but I
have a hard time dealing with the taste.
Do you have any good recipes to make
the kratom more tasty?
One time I was at a bar in
Thailand where they mix it with ginger, lemon
and sparkling water and it tasted very delicious.
You could do it that way.
What I do is I have a small
wooden spoon.
It would be comparable to a quarter of
a teaspoon.
OK, and I just slam that in the
mouth and then immediately have something to wash
it down with something warm like coffee or
tea.
Don't do soda or juice with it.
It turns absolutely rancid, you know, because of
the acid.
It's very alkaline.
Right.
So.
So water, warm water.
Definitely.
I've tried other ways and definitely for me
is just slam a little bit of powder
in the mouth and wash it down with
a body or room temperature liquid.
That's not acidic like a tea or a
coffee team.
That's that's not hot, obviously.
Yeah, because you have to slam it.
Otherwise you got a mouthful of powder.
That's the way I like to do it.
Yeah.
I don't like to have it mixed in
whatever.
If you mix it in any kind of
a juice or a soda or something that
has, you know, the acid and the citrus,
it nullifies it because it's it's an alkaline.
Fair enough.
And nobody wants a mouthful of powder or
muddy powder.
Anyways, if someone was to get a loan
from a private trust, would the holder of
that trust be able to access the borrower's
line of credit?
It depends on the what access, if the
trust is set up as an intermediary, meaning
a banker.
All right.
If they're an intermediary, they have access to
the O.C. 10 or an O.C.
7 operating Circular 10, which is a window
of the Federal Reserve or an operating Circular
7, which is different.
You know, it depends.
A trust is a trust.
You know, I mean, everything is in trust.
If I hand someone five bucks to go
to the store, someone asks them, do you
have any money?
They say no.
And they sit there, they have five bucks.
They say, I have no money.
Well, it's not mine.
You see.
So trust is very, very wide thing.
But if they if they're an intermediary, like,
you know, with a license or permission to
do so from all the securities agencies and
the Federal Reserve.
Yeah, they can access your line of credit,
but they usually can't do it with just
your name.
They what they would do is they would
negotiate whatever you give them.
But to access a line of credit, they
would you would have to give them some
kind of a credit number, like a Social
Security number, and they'd have to have access
to the window.
So the general answer to the question is
no, because of insufficient details.
All righty.
Somebody asked for you and me to pick
two songs, a piece that that we appreciate
most.
And just easy.
Yeah, good.
What I could do one I've been listening
to a lot lately.
Band on the run.
Paul McCartney.
That song is about the simulation.
It's like, oh, stuck in these four walls.
Here we go again.
Mom.
All right.
You see his mom again and trying to
break out, you know, the jailer and the
sailor and the right and the judge.
And here we go crashing into the sun.
The rain crashes into the sun.
Hope you're having fun.
All this stuff.
Yeah.
Breaking out of this reality.
Here we go again.
Kind of thing.
Oh, clearly banned on the run.
Listen to the lyrics of that.
Holy shit.
And then it would be listening to a
lot lately over and over is two albums.
One is Physical Graffiti and Houses of the
Holy, both from Led Zeppelin.
Those are more than just two songs, but
band on the run, man.
Another one that's good if you're feeling like
nitty gritty boots to the ground here.
It's Bruce Springsteen Badlands, probably the best song
he's ever done.
But, yeah, that's for that genre.
See, for me, any music that sounds good
is good.
The genre is irrelevant, but I've just gave
out what I've been very impressed with lately
is band on the run.
Listen to, you know, you just put in
band on the run song and look at
the read the lyrics.
You're like, oh, my gosh, that's about breaking
out of here.
You know, keep you keep being sent back
here and these guys break out and it
pisses off the authorities because you broke out.
Right.
So, yeah, that's really good.
And again, Houses of the Holy album and
Physical Graffiti album.
Yeah, Led Zeppelin.
I'm a little bit different than you, obviously.
Look, I appreciate a lot of stuff by
Motorhead and Black Sabbath.
My favorite song is Under the Sun.
And take a listen to it.
You'll figure out why.
But also, I got to tell you, I
have a great appreciation for Alice in Chains
in general.
Previous Alice in Chains, not the new stuff.
And Rage Against the Machine.
I like them.
It's very interesting.
It's like a fusion.
And I appreciate it.
And, you know, the message is.
I used to, when I did bicycle racing,
I got into mountain bike racing.
I put rage in the machine riding off
road, you know.
You took the fear away.
Here's the thing about fear.
People talk, don't have fear.
It's stupid.
It's OK to have fear, but don't let
the fear disable you.
And can you operate at your best and
still be in fear?
You know, people say don't fear.
That is a terrible thing to say to
people because it makes them.
That is that's what the collect that's what
they put out to the collective to disable
you.
Right.
Don't have any fear.
It's can you operate under fear?
And I think Rage Against the Machine is
something that helps you operate under fear.
Yeah.
But here's the thing.
I think it's great to punch straight through
it.
You know, do not allow it to dictate
your actions.
It just yeah.
No matter how fearful you are, you can
still function.
Yeah, absolutely.
Yeah.
Anyway.
OK, this is an odd question for us,
but here we go.
Why are they demonizing the white race?
Oh, that that's happened before.
OK, these these things go in cycles.
They just read about was it Morgenthau?
And who was it who wrote the pastoral
policy for Germany that Germany should be turned
into a pasture?
And all the German people eliminated.
Oh, right.
And the Huns and they used to be
the Huns.
The white people were called the Huns.
So there was posters throughout the US during
World War Two.
Let's let's go fight the Huns.
Well, that's what they called the Germans.
Yeah.
Which is really weird.
It's really an anti-Aryan, anti-German thing,
more than anti-white thing.
Which is crazy because Attila the Hun, according
to historians at the time, was right here
and seven feet tall.
They didn't know what race he was.
They looked at him and went, we don't
know where the hell this guy came from,
even.
And they live on the backs of horses,
these Huns.
Yeah, that's what they told us, because if
you start if you get too much stuff,
you connect the dots and get a sense
of real history.
Right.
Yeah, of course.
Breshears, right now, I think Breshears is at
the top of the mountain with that.
He's putting out some really good stuff, you
know, archaics for history and all that.
Yeah.
OK.
So here's here's one.
I hate this question.
I'm just going to read it.
Hi, Greg.
After the Christ laid down his life and
was resurrected, do you think that it gave
the higher level gods no reason to interact
with man as they did in ancient times?
Yeah.
Yeah, absolutely.
I think that did.
OK.
Yeah.
We're living in a quiet time and the
quiet time.
There's many quiet times that we've gone through.
This is a quiet time.
OK.
When you say the war is for meeting
a quota.
Are you talking just as a money making
racket for the military industrial complex?
Or is there also a killing quota, too?
Killing quota.
OK.
Also, why didn't you use a neodymium magnet
in the scalarator?
OK.
Like Ken Wheeler.
I think somebody's busting your chops, but go
ahead.
Yeah.
Neodymium are really strong.
They give you because they're very high density,
which means that it's the same amount of
magnetism in a much smaller area.
Right.
And we don't want that because, first of
all, we're not even using the magnetism.
We're using the the block what's known as
the block wall, which is the potential.
That's where the two parts of what people
refer to as magnetism.
The poles, which are not poles, is a
vortex going right through it.
But we don't use that.
So we need that that extension from a
less dense field.
Now, the neodymium, because it has a higher
dielectric property, even though it's a metal, it's
a centered metal.
It does have more magnetism as well as
higher density.
And it just doesn't work as well as
a ceramic with a lower density because we
need that.
We're not looking to have a small magnet
that could lift anything or use.
We're not looking for the magnetic part.
That's the thing.
Right.
I assure you, I'm the other than a
couple of people that do.
What are those catskin that catskin MRIs?
I was just going to say, what you
don't need is the MRI giant, what they
call a monster magnet.
Right.
Yeah, there's no there's no one discussing the
block wall.
The only reason they don't even know what
the block wall is.
They just they just discuss it because that's
where the transmission.
That's the that's how they define, you know,
where they're going to overlap and focus getting
their images.
That's the break the for them.
It's just a break where the field changes.
Right.
They don't understand how to use it.
And that's why I'm talking publicly.
There's nothing.
I'm the only one that's emphasizing the use
of the block wall bar none, period, in
the world right now.
I enjoy monster magnet, the band as well.
Back to that question about music.
But anyway.
Yeah.
But the reason we don't use the NEOs
is because the density pulls everything in too
close.
And we want it to extend out further
into the flow.
Because remember, using it to treat water, which
is incredible, by the way.
I don't think I've gone into too much
detail on it lately.
But I had it sent to someone, a
lab in Louisiana.
And I was like, you know, I kind
of get a weird feeling.
This is, you know, let's send it to
my house.
I think I don't know if I said
this on the Sonic.
And it was a Tuesday and I sent
it priority.
So it should get there on a Thursday
from Tucson to Lake Charles, Louisiana.
Right.
But anyway, I checked tracking.
So it leaves Tucson that night.
Next day it's in Houston.
And then it goes from one place to
Houston.
It goes to Austin.
Then it goes to Dallas on Thursday or
Friday.
Then it goes back and then it goes
finally goes to Louisiana.
I'm like, wait a second.
Supposed to be delivered Thursday.
It's the weekend.
It's still in Texas moving around.
And it gets delivered to this person's house
at Sunday at five o'clock p.m.
Right.
Who the hell gets mail?
And I said, listen, you know, please photograph
the box.
I want to see if it's been tampered
or anything because I'll do better.
I'll do a video.
So I did an unboxing video and it
wasn't.
It just everything was exactly like I had
packed it.
And I didn't put any kind of a
trip in there or anything to see, you
know, because you know how years ago you
put a string on top of your door
to see if someone's come in.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
So I didn't do anything like that.
But it was pretty much whatever.
But I hear at the post office, they
have these small needles that they randomly penetrate
packages with.
That's why they keep asking, you know, liquids,
no liquids.
Right.
And it sniffs and then it just sniffs
it and it doesn't really get reviewed.
It just goes on file, you know, just
like all of our conversations.
Transcripts are being made and they don't really
get reviewed.
They just be put away, you know, maybe
randomly get reviewed.
Well, they're stacked in a database somewhere.
So what I presumed happened is they probably
broke out one of these new two million
dollar X-ray machines and it was a
little too close and blew up the X
-ray machine.
That's what I'm presuming.
That's why it didn't get there.
I didn't make a stink about it.
It should.
You know, I paid postage to get it.
They're always priority two days and it didn't
get there till Sunday at five o'clock.
I didn't get back to the post office.
What's the delay?
I was just watching it on the tracking.
I thought it was funny.
It was kind of like one of those
wily coyote maps, you know, and a roadrunner.
That's what it looked like.
And so I just wanted to put this
out publicly because I don't think I have
before.
It's it's been quite an adventure working with
this.
Yeah.
And I've watched stuff disappear and reappear in
tracking before.
It's funny.
And in Georgia, I'll let you know that
they do have these weird Sunday night late
deliveries, but only mail that they've monitored or
redirected in some way.
So further on, one of the labs, I
kept asking them, how's this fantastic result?
So we'll send me something in writing or
a lab, right?
You do reports.
We will finally get back to him and
say, oh, we don't have it anymore.
It's in our other lab in Illinois.
And I'm like, what?
OK, so I call them.
They're like, well, what do you plan on?
So you got a report.
We'll get your report.
By the way, this is a couple of
months ago and they still haven't gotten me
a report.
And I said, what do you what are
you planning on doing for post-preparation after
the water goes through?
So what do you mean post-preparation after
I said, don't you know?
I said, what, what, what?
He says, well, we have our control samples,
which didn't go through the scalar.
Then the water that went through the scalar.
I said, yeah.
And he says, you know that after about
48 to 72 hours, you have precipitants in
the in the test samples.
So in other words, you see these jars,
three jars that didn't go.
The same water didn't go through.
And the three jars where the water went
through.
Stuff starts to come out of the water
and settle at the bottom of the jar.
I was like, oh, my gosh.
So it's actually the water puts the water
in a mode where the water starts to
clean itself.
That's interesting.
Yeah.
That's why they were wondering.
I say, what do you propose to do
for that post-preparation?
You know, for the stuff that falls on
us, I never knew it did that.
I just put it on homes.
So we have excellent water.
I don't capture the water later and see
stuff, you know, for three, four days.
What falls out of it, you know, never
knew that.
So that's why that's cool to go to
a lab.
Right.
Now you can and can discover something occasionally
through the.
Yeah.
So I didn't know it did that.
So there's this huge potential for that, you
know, for many, many different things.
And it's it puts the water in a
state way beyond what's considered to be H2O.
Water is not H2O at all.
It's fooled.
Everyone's been fooled by that.
You can even ask chat GPT.
Water is not H2O.
So, yeah, water is not H2O.
But for chemical description, that's what we use.
Make a long story short, not getting into
it, it does still learning about what it
does.
And it just increases the quality of the
water, just like if you're not feeling well,
you're not going to do stuff around the
house.
But if you're really fit and you do
and you're doing well, you're probably going to
do more.
And the water is that way.
It puts the water at a higher level
of fitness.
And one thing that I've been telling people
lately is anyone wants to get into water
healing spas, you don't have to travel to
these places where they have, you know, these
movies, natural spas and take a bath to
get rid of your skin disorders or muscle
or joint disorders.
You've heard stories, right?
Yeah.
And some what some of those springs are
pretty good.
I mean, they are.
But now you can you can you can
do it yourself.
If you set up the sclerator right anywhere,
you set up anyone who has one.
If you fill a bathtub, the water looks
blue, turns blue.
Just just with the lights on or low,
it doesn't matter.
Oh, yeah.
With certain light, the world.
So, no, I'm talking about any light.
The water starts to look like tiny bowl
blue.
I've gotten pictures.
People who had the scars and look at
the water.
Look how blue it is.
I'm like, yeah, it shows up in the
picture really well.
How does it look in real life?
It's just like that.
I'm like, perfect.
Yeah.
So where if you don't run it through
the scale, you get this grayish, you know,
a tap water.
Looks like, you know, blah.
Right.
So it looks dirty even when it's clean.
OK, so can you please ask the Greek
if he has any thoughts on gene keys?
It's a system that blends Western astrology and
I Ching.
Nothing at all.
I was just fascinated by the nine star
key because it's a collection of data for
thousands of years.
Now, whether it's been misused or are we
getting an accurate whatever?
No, I just I find it to be
fairly accurate, especially with people around you.
But no, I don't know about a crossover.
No, I'm not an astrology type person.
Fair enough.
Just got two more.
I got a short one and a long
one.
So go with the short first.
What are the Greeks thoughts on Wim Hof
breathing techniques and cold showers?
Thank you in advance.
Never heard of it, but I have heard
about the cold bath dipping and all that.
That will make you extremely young because the
water, cold water is extremely lean.
That'll really tighten young men.
It'll tighten you up.
It'll it'll.
And, you know, when you give me an
example, when you this is not a direct
answer, but when you subject yourself to cold
and you're shaking, that's shaking is the releasing
of yin.
Right.
The yin energy has to be released because
in order for you to become young from
being exposed to such a yin energy or
principle, let's say of something being cold, which
is extremely lean, it'll make your body young
to balance.
So you you're you're actually shaking is releasing
yin.
Also a sneeze when someone sneezes, it's a
release of yin.
Like when you eat spicy food or put
spicy food up, you know, the snuff or
whatever makes people sneeze from back in the
day.
Snuff boxes.
Right.
Yes.
That was because spices are very yin.
So it over yin.
It creates a reaction that releases you.
So sneezing, shaking from being cold is a
release of yin.
So, OK, so the cold, what it'll do,
a cold shower, cold bath, these ice baths
that people do.
It's fashionable wherever it's going to really seen
if you're on any kind of medication, prescription
drugs or even taking vitamins or eat fatty
oils or processed food, it could actually force
a rapid response of release of yin.
It could actually hurt you or damage your
organs.
So you have to be really fit and
balanced to do those things.
And if you're doing those things to be
fit and balanced, you're kind of like experimenting.
You might hurt yourself.
Right.
That's what I'm saying.
The body always reacts better to a warm
shower and a hot bath.
It doesn't matter if it's cold or hot
out.
You always react better to a hot sauna,
a steam room, hot bath, hot shower than
anything cold.
And that's what I recommend.
I would never recommend anything cold on the
body because it forces a rapid release of
yin.
And knowing that the day and age we
live in and all that, most people not
being as fit as you could be because
the environment is so toxified.
I wouldn't do anything, any kind of a
cold treatment or anything.
The only cold treatment I would do is
if you had a bruise, you know, the
cold pack.
I have a cat that's having a hard
time adapting to the desert heat.
So I have to do cold coat on
him.
I have these these ice packs that I
rub on his coat, cools him down because
he's really hot and itchy and he's having
a hard time.
He's like one of these cats that belong
in the forests of Sweden or Norway or,
you know, cold.
He's like imagine a husky in the desert.
Right.
So, yeah.
That only that like I've used cold packs
before.
I've had a skin manifestation that was so
itchy.
I was like that that's a young manifestation
breaking through the skin.
I need to put ice pack on that.
And it just made it stop.
And yes, knowing diagnosis.
But again, just to I would like to
emphasize and underscore that my recommendation for any
kind of a treatment doesn't matter if it's
hot or cold.
That is a hot bath, hot shower, steam
room sauna, never a cold shower, never a
cold dip because it forces a rapid discharge
of yin.
Yeah.
Somebody once asked in one of these little
community chat things about like, you know, why
is my dog so miserable?
And I took a look and realized, you
know, they had a husky living in Florida.
And I'm like, are you stupid?
I mean, that dog is not supposed to
be in Florida.
It's very literally made for cold weather.
He's literally designed for cold weather like that.
That dog belongs way north up in Canada
somewhere, you know, at least.
Yeah.
I've seen them pulling with those sleighs, you
know, and they're just happy as anything like
minus 20, you know?
Yeah.
But you bring them into, you know, 102
degree weather.
They're sitting there panting, like trying not to
drop.
Anyways.
Yeah.
So this is a long one, Greek.
But bear with me because it tells a
lot.
OK, well, you can abridge it, but go
ahead.
Yeah, I'll read some of it, but not
all of it.
OK, I understand the frustration with the so
-called doctors.
They're terrible.
I went last week for a health check.
I never go to doctors, but I had
to do it because of work.
Basically, the only thing they do is measure
blood pressure, high blood pressure.
Before going there, I spent two hours walking
around the city and it was almost 40
degrees outside.
So my heart was still beating at an
increased rate.
The doctor instantly suggested blood pressure medications.
So no, thanks.
Just give me my certificate.
These doctors are really clowns.
Is that the only thing they taught them
in college to measure blood pressure?
What a joke.
I went to check the definition of blood
pressure.
It says the force that blood exerts against
the walls of the arteries.
So ultimately, here's the questions.
How do they measure the force?
Same way they measure gravity?
You could look that up.
Look up the history.
I've had several people in the medical industry
that I've told, when you look up definitions,
you're going to get the political definition.
You're going to get what they want you
to do.
If you looked up COVID four years ago,
it'd be very different than if you looked
it up 15 years ago or now.
So you have to look up the history
of the blood pressure cuff and blood pressure
measurement devices history.
And they'll walk you through what they were
trying to do and what they developed to
measure those things.
And they'll explain how it evolved into what
it is now.
You're going to be scratching your head and
you're like, they did all this for what?
For nothing?
Yeah.
Basically, this is the same thing from listening
to Brandon Joe Williams.
When attorneys get out of law school, or
when you get out of law school, you
still don't know how to write a court
case, a lawsuit.
You still don't know how to write a
lawsuit.
Now, what they do is the same thing
they do.
And I've seen nursing school books.
They spend most of their time talking about
what chemicals are inside cells, which none of
them could confirm any of that.
It's all bullshit, right?
Because I've told you that the way they
find out what chemicals are inside cells is
by first crushing the cell, centrifuging it, and
then assaying it, either combining it with caustic
chemicals, acidic chemicals, or burning it.
So when you do all those things, you've
changed into something else.
Like, you can't tell me orange marmalade is
orange, and you can't tell me that a
pickle is a cucumber, even though, right?
It started off as the same.
They want a cucumber in their hamburger?
No, hell no.
I want a pickle, right?
Not the same thing anymore.
So it's all a distraction.
The medical thing, hospitals, because of the hospital
business and all that, is a farce.
I cannot emphasize that.
You could look this up.
I don't know how much of it will
still be left online.
Socialized medicine countries have, and they go on
strike occasionally.
When they go on strike, the morgues are
literally empty.
When the doctors go back to work, the
morgues begin to operate at regular capacity again.
That's all you have to say.
Now, walking around.
So go look at the history, because I
can run down the technical stuff right now,
what they're doing, and what it actually measures.
It measures literally the pulse, the time in
between beats.
And there's an algorithm for it.
And it's all BS.
Because, excuse me, if you're going to talk
about blood pressure, it better be negative pressure.
Right?
Because it's moving.
People think, like, remember in the old?
Well, the timing between beats is easy to
see because they used to, when people wore
watches, they would look at their watch, and
they would watch the second hand, and look
at it.
Yeah, right, exactly.
The timing in between, and there's a motion
in the cuff disturbance of the pressure.
But here's the thing.
They've got everyone programmed, including these idiot doctors,
that we're pressurized filter bags.
We're filter bags because we absorb things, right?
And we're pressurized.
If you're going to talk about pressure, it's
got to be negative.
And if you're talking about filtering or absorption,
it better be using the term induction because
nothing passes through any of the tissues at
all.
And so, yeah, are they moronic?
Yeah, just like, well, here's the thing.
You can go to a banker, a Series
7 licensed broker, stockbroker.
Someone's been working 30, 40 years in banking,
investment banking, and they don't know what negotiable
instruments are.
They don't know.
They can't define it.
They can't define anything.
They don't know what the Federal Reserve is
doing.
They don't know what monetization is.
They don't know anything at all, just like
attorneys don't know any law.
They just write nasty grams, right?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, so no one knows anything.
So my question to the person writing this
is I really appreciate that, but it sounds
like you've been on this planet for 30
days only.
In other words, what I recommend to the
person who wrote the question in the email,
by the way, I highly appreciate it because
you're sharing an experience, is don't be so
naive, and you should take a more sarcastic
undertone, not an overtone with this, which you
actually did.
I'm giving you high marks for this, by
the way.
Don't take what I'm saying as whatever berating
you or anything.
I'm actually giving you high marks for bringing
this forward because you actually brought out what
you did and what they did, and clearly
they don't know what they're doing, and you
notice that.
The shame of it is that the people
around you don't know that what you know,
most likely, I'm presuming, and the person that
you went to, right?
So here's the thing.
By the way, one suggestion I would make
is when they said, I suggest you to
be on blood pressure medication, just say, give
me the script, right?
In other words, go along with them, with
those idiots.
When you're dealing with illegal morons, you have
to rebut everything they say.
Don't rebut the doctors that much because they
have a lot of legal power also.
You might tell you one thing and send
something else to your employer.
So say, give me the script and I'll
consider it, and then they feel like, yeah,
I got another one.
You don't want to wake these idiots up
because it's actually, they've chosen to be asleep,
these medics, right?
And they've chosen that life.
They know it.
None of them are happy.
Trust me, I know that.
If you know any of these medical morons,
they take more interest in hobbies and other
pastimes than their career.
They have to for their sanity, right?
So, yeah, they really do.
If you know anyone who works as a
doctor, they have any pastime, whether it's a
sport or whatever, pastime, hobby.
They take it very seriously because they have
no way to define themselves.
Now, you have the surgeons and the interns
who take a tremendous amount of time that
is taken from them to work there, and
that's all military.
That's all based on military protocols.
But anyway, I'm glad you shared that.
But again, to go back to what blood
pressure is, just like diabetes and all that,
study the history of it.
How was blood pressure equipment developed and why?
And you're not going to get into a
big thing about it.
Wikipedia will do that for you really quick.
It's fine.
And you'll see that they started off with
something that was a notion and a theory,
and they pursued it disregarding the facts.
And they made it a fact in people's
minds, even though it doesn't exist.
There you go.
And look, I actually missed one question, didn't
realize it, but I double-checked and found
it.
So here it is, the last thing that
I need to ask you, which is, Greek,
what does it mean in this current reality
to, quote, seek enlightenment, end quote?
Well, here, I'll use this.
You ever hear people say, oh, he's very
spiritual, and I'm like, and?
Right?
Well, spiritual could be, is that like, let's
say, demonic spiritual or angelic spiritual?
Spiritual just means not physical.
It could be like Linda Blair and the
Exorcist, right?
Or it could be, you know, what was
that funny movie they did about a guy
talking to God, right?
With George Burns.
Remember that?
And then they did another one.
Oh, yeah.
It was called Oh, God.
Oh, God.
Yeah.
So which one?
They're both spiritual movies, by the way.
Yeah.
Right.
Oh, God is a spiritual movie.
And so is the Exorcist.
And then they did the second one, Oh,
God, you devil.
And George Burns played both God and the
devil.
Remember?
Yeah.
So, right.
Right.
Yeah.
You showed up in a different colored suit,
I think.
He had a red suit on, like, and
lit his cigarettes with his fingertips or whatever.
Right.
So the thing about that is, like, when
you say revelation, it just means, or apocalypse,
this just means to open.
So when you enlighten, to put light on
something, it could be anything.
I mean, what does it mean?
It could make you very upset.
Like, if you're in a relationship and that
person is cheating on you for a long
time and you have no suspicion of it,
and you find out that that's happening, that's
enlightenment, isn't it?
What do you do now?
What are you going to do now?
Now you have, you get into confrontation, right?
Or you just let it go.
But either way, right?
In Spanish, they call that a cover on.
So, so what are you going to do?
Right?
So when you, when you go into enlightenment,
that just means you're going to be putting
on light on things that are pitch black
and you haven't seen before.
And it's not always good.
And in this particular reality that we're manifesting
right now, the trivial things, that's why I
want to do the thing on home economics,
can be very good when you become enlightened.
But the big things, the overarching things that
government, religion, you know, the mainstream religions, finance
and all that, you start enlightening yourself on
that, you're going to see it's super, super
dark, darker than anything you've seen online.
Worse.
Yeah.
So that's why years ago I've been telling
people, they got some pretty crazy theories on,
you know, wild shit on the internet you
could look up, but I'll tell you what,
reality is 10 times even more wilder than
that.
That's why it doesn't get out.
So.
And that's why, you know, that old advice
about it's always dangerous to wake a sleepwalker.
I absolutely agree with it, you know, because
there's a lot of sleepwalkers.
Listen to Robert.
There's a, there's a channel.
No, I call it no thinking a lot.
It's new thinking allowed.
He used to be on, uh, what's his
name?
I forgot his name.
He used to have a, uh, back when
public access TV in San Francisco, he's a
paranormal researcher, a parapsychologist.
Uh, anyway, it's called new thinking allowed.
Uh, two months ago you interviewed Robert Temple.
Listen to that interview with Robert Temple.
Robert Temple is a little bit of a
flake, but his information seems to be pretty
good about the astral journeys that he goes
on and he's told to come back and
tell people on earth.
And when you die, you go up to
this other place, right?
And there's nothing to do there.
Right.
So, uh, and he's quite surprised and how
they show us a lot of the stuff
in film, but Robert Temple interview on, uh,
no thinking, new thinking allowed new thinking.
The reason I call it no thinking allowed
is because he's an academic and he, you
know, he props up academia.
So academia is no thinking a lot, but
it's new thinking allowed.
Robert Temple from two months ago, he did
another interview about a year ago, but the
more recent one is more.
And it's interesting when he starts talking about
one of the guides that like used to
come down to earth, doesn't anymore because the
evil on the earth has reached a point
where they have to stay up in the
stratosphere because the lizards won't let them come
down to the surface like they used to
at all.
Cause the lizards are running everything.
And he cuts soon as he said that
he cuts them off and he says, well,
that has nothing to do with astral travel.
So we're not going to talk about the
reptilians that run this place.
Uh, yeah.
So anyway, you know how academics can be.
Of course I asked that doctor with the
blood pressure, uh, you know, where's the, you
know, anyway, you can imagine querying them, you
know, so there you go.