Rated Y, Sonic Event 144, and here we are in that month that they allegedly call September
on the Pope's work schedule, but that is not the topic of tonight's discussion.
Greek, what is the topic and what is the really special surprise we have
on this particular event, I should say? Yeah, it's always a surprise, but we,
as we mentioned in the chat about a week ago, we have Dmitry Kholosov with us tonight,
and it's early morning for him. And if people are, I think most people already listening to
Greek-speak are very familiar with Dmitry's disclosures from myself promoting his work.
And maybe when we start, Dmitry, let us know, Dmitry, for someone who's listening for the
first time, where can they quickly go, so while they're listening, if they're not in a car driving
or something, to find you, where would you like them to go? What do you mean? Like on the internet.
I have a YouTube channel and I have a website where all my other links are published, so you
just can give them my website. Yes, if you like, I can read them. Say hello to everyone. Yes,
hello, Dmitry. Yeah, you just did. So because it may be if someone is listening that they don't
know who you are, they can go immediately before we start speaking. But I think you're
pretty famous in this circle here. So hello, and how are you? Give us a brief, whatever you want
to say before we dig into things. No, I'm okay. Thank you so much. I live in Bangkok, Thailand,
and now it's nine o'clock in the morning, so it's not too early. Okay, great. We always wanted to,
we have some shared contacts from back in the days with the Veterans Today people,
and that's when I found out about you around 2011 or so. And ever since then,
I try to recollect on my end what the disclosure of the nuclear demolition, because I was in New
York City all my life, but I was not in Tucson, Arizona since 1999. But I have a lot of context
there. So I kept digging into just people who witnessed it and other things from being in the
building trade, like white-collar construction, and piecing things together to validate
all of the things that you brought up. But we had some questions, by the way. Again,
there's no reason to go over from the beginning all of your things, but some people were asking,
you might have addressed it in a recent video, Dimitri. These devices are placed as fixtures for
nuclear demolition and skyscrapers, not just posthumously in the World Trade Center, but also
many other structures throughout the world, also, if they're crazy enough to do it in a civilian
environment. And do you think they've been taken down since 9-11? Because maybe the people working
there are saying, oh, maybe they're really going to do it? Do you have any information you could
share on that? Okay, from the beginning, when I was still in the Soviet military,
that was at the end of the 80s, I heard, or I learned, I mean, that under the World Trade Center
twin towers, there was such a nuclear demolition scheme. But I have never heard about any other
building, only about these two towers. And the building 7, by that time, was not even built yet.
But when I published my first version of research on that, it was, I think, in 2007,
or maybe earlier, 2008, a lot of people began to contact me, and they want to disclose some
information that they knew. And from these people, I learned a lot of new things.
So first of all, I learned from them, why actually that thing was there in the first place,
because before I had no explanation why that kind of thing should be under the buildings.
So from some people who contacted me from America, I learned that it was because of the
requirements of the building code of New York, and some other cities,
that the Department of Building cannot issue permission to build a skyscraper,
unless the developer provides an explanation, a workable explanation, how it's going to be
demolished in the future. Because the twin towers were the first
steel buildings in the world. Because prior to that, the buildings were made from bricks
and concrete, so they could be demolished by ordinary explosives. But the twin towers were
first steel buildings in the world, so they didn't know how to demolish them. And because
in the mid-60s, the nuclear explosions were fashionable, not evil yet, like now.
And also I learned from some people who contacted me then,
that there were similar nuclear demolition devices under the Sears Tower in Chicago,
and under the United Nations building in New York. That is for sure. And also I heard
that there were some other skyscrapers in America, but not many of them, maybe two or three more.
And what is most interesting, I also learned from people who contacted me from Japan,
that in Japan, under some buildings, there were also nuclear demolition devices
that were managed by the Americans. And in some buildings in the United Arab Emirates,
and in the Petronas Twin Towers in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. That's what I learned.
And what I learned also, that after the disaster on 9-11, because that nuclear demolition turned
to be a real disaster, all these kinds of things were removed from everywhere, and
the information of that was completely classified. That's what I know. So I
believe now that there are no more such things under any building in the world.
I see. Dmitry, at the beginning, I took note that you stated you were in the Soviet military,
and then you started talking about where you heard things. So what I didn't understand at
beginning is, do you mean that you learned some of this through your military experience,
or is it just coincidental that you were in the military? In other words, was this information
available to the Soviet military as far as you knew, or did you learn this in a civilian capacity?
No, I learned that in the military capacity, because I used to serve in the Soviet Special
Control Service, which is the organization that detects nuclear explosions.
Right. He goes through this in his video. Yeah, I just wanted to get a little snapshot.
And while serving there, I just knew about the nuclear demolition scheme of the Twin Towers
in New York only. You were in a control service, Director, at 12. I think when you do the
long first video that you then modified later, you give a good background on that. That's why,
again, I started off with whoever hears from you for the first time, they should invest the four
hours at least. It seems like a long time for Americans. They're used to sitcoms half hour,
right? No, they're not used to four hour. So I recommend they go and listen to that before here.
True. But I just want a snapshot of the of the initial contact, because I heard from I heard
from various things there and I wanted to get the initial idea. Then how did those other contacts
occur where you were contacted from other places? Was that in the military capacity as well?
Or did that emerge after you started making these statements? And therefore, people started
to contact you to snowball your your sort of discussion and make it grow. I was wondering
about that, if that's the way that that occurred or if it was still military. He answered that.
Yeah, he answered. Yes, it was much later because because I learned about the nuclear demolition
devices under the Twin Towers in New York in like in the end of the 80s. So a long time ago,
there was like 12 years before 9-11. But my first research on that was published in 2007.
And I discharged from the military in 1991. So it has nothing to do with my military service anymore.
Yes. I just wanted to see where the separation was, because I wasn't clear on that. My apologies,
Greek. I just want to be clear. And I think this should be with with clarity, because this is
fascinating. We're talking about and if you don't understand the different directorates,
the listener that is, you should also take a little bit of background study and understand
what he is talking about as far as who he's working for at that time, because it is it is
something that not every American is certainly read in on regarding this. So I wanted to point
that out as well. So, Dimitri, this is fascinating. Please continue about the nuclear devices. And you
said that as of today, you would say that they do not currently exist. But but what do you have
any idea about the initiation of that program? Is there a difference in its true origin? And say,
when the Soviets learned about it, were they behind the curve, so to speak? Or was it something
newly discovered? Are you aware of that? No, it was not newly discovered, because I believe that
in the 70s, it was not even a secret knowledge. I think many people knew about that in the 70s.
So they just try to hide this now. But I think if we if we have a time back machine, and we
appear today in the 70s, I think we will find this information easily. And it was not even
classified. I mean, about the nuclear demolition of the buildings. See, Americans? Yes.
I don't know the big deal, though. Americans would certainly find it fascinating that this
was an open secret is what you're basically saying. And as far as most Americans are concerned,
no, it wasn't because this is, you know, way out there. There was nuclear devices literally
in the buildings. That's it. You know, that is something, you know, I'm just saying it's one of
the things that stem from Project Plowshare. If you study that, yeah, there's plenty of released
videos right now. And one thing, Dimitri, there's some people that don't understand,
again, if they watch your videos, they'll understand about how the mechanism works.
You know, it's not that we've been brainwashed only with atmospheric nuclear detonation,
never what happens when it's underground or underwater. But I would suggest people look
at there's a video been released, military video, declassified, where they blow,
I think it was thermonuclear underwater in the early 60s. And you can see as the wave passes
over the water, the battleship actually disintegrates, turns to dust and collapses
also. So that effect also happens on the water. So there's a lot of information. And Project
Plowshare was promoted for mining and many other things as a good thing, because it was very cheap
and very fast to do. So it wasn't much of a secret. And really, but I want to share a few
things with you, Dimitri, and maybe get your response, if that's okay, things that I found
on my research. So, everybody's still here, I hope. Yeah. Yes, I am. Okay, Dimitri. I believe
so. Yeah. All right. I don't hear Dimitri, but that's fine. Yeah, I'm here. Okay.
I was waiting. Okay. Well, the statement is like, when let's go.
Let's say from this point of view, in the 1980s, in the middle of the 1980s, I worked as a draftsman
internship, engineering company, Amman and Whitney. And that was the time where they had
draftsmen going there 24 hours a day, because they had to update drawings on the Statue of
Liberty restoration, right. So we had going in at one in the morning working till five drawing,
this is before computers. So one of the old engineers in a wheelchair asked me,
this is around 1985 86, I believe. He asked me what I did when I'm not drafting, you know,
guy so young, what are you doing here in the middle of the night, you know, I said, Well,
if I'm not here, I'm riding my bicycle down by the World Trade Center, you know, and he says,
don't don't go there. They have nukes in those buildings, he said to me. So at that point,
that stuck in my head. And I was like, Oh, this guy is like a crazy senile old man, right.
And at the time, I was propaganda is I didn't understand because we were told about the
nuclear core being a ball. And I thought it was in that bronze sculpture that they had in the
courtyard or something hiding something like James Bond movie or something. I had no idea of that.
And then later on in life, I had experience working with what's called the Port Authority,
which those buildings were under. And I found out that the Port Authority has its own authority,
its own jurisdiction separate from the rest of the country. So even a federal, let's say agency
comes in there, they have to get permission to do anything with the Port Authority. And the other
thing I found out from being around nuclear engineers, when you say what is the biggest,
baddest agency, American agency, they usually people say, some kind of intelligence agency,
like CIA or something like that. But I found out from speaking with nuclear engineers,
it's the Department of Energy is the most powerful agency in the United States regarding these things.
Also from a commander, someone who worked as a nuclear engineer, a nuclear submarine that was
armed with nuclear warheads. When the anyone a low ranking person from the Department of Energy came
in, even the commander of the submarine was at attention, they were very much afraid of these
guys. So I started piecing all of this information together to see how it all you know, in other
words, you can get information from many areas. But if you don't know, specifically that they
were brought down and basically vaporized, because the there were also videos that I found where they
interviewed some doctors about survivors. And back then, and one of the interviews, the doctor
says, imagine being near a nuclear bomb. That's what happened to the people in the building. So
they actually knew there were many, many, I would say 1000s of people that knew about this, if not
many hundreds, and it's still quiet. No one has pieced it together like you have. So it's more of
a statement I want to make than a question. Because what you did you especially with your
anthology, the four hour video, you pieced it all together. So if you watch that, there's really very
few questions, right? Because of all the information you provided. But if anyone has experiences, let's
say, like the ones I mentioned, if you were paying attention, you can see how plausible it is, you
know, you can we see the signs, but we don't know all the specifics. So there was not a question,
it was a statement. And one more statement, Dimitri was speaking to people that lived in New Jersey,
downwind, where the wind was across the Hudson River, weeks and weeks after the catastrophe,
the people living there were calling the environmental agencies saying that smell,
we have a very bad smell. And the environmental agency would ask like smells like what and they
said, like electrical fire. And they say, well, there was a lot of electrical wires in the
building. That's why it smells that way. But from speaking to people that were in that area at the
same time, they said the smell was very acrid, like very high smell of ionization, like ozone,
like burning electrical wires. And I also researched that. And I found that the military
that went to Hiroshima to clean up if you read a lot of their books and letters that they wrote
in Japan, even though it was a surface device, they also had the same thing, they couldn't stand
the smell. So all of these things put together with your work, for me, makes me feel like,
you know, this is a complete almost story, you know, people I knew in Jersey City, in fact,
because I was in New Jersey, as I stated before, did report the most common word used was ozone,
burning ozone is what they would say. And that's what they described it as. And we also experienced
that dust that really caked windows and cars and all kinds of things just across the river in
Jersey City, Bayonne, various parts there that are just across the Hudson Creek. So I was one of those
people. Yeah, also for Dimitri, we want him to speak more. But who was that stewardess that you
spoke to? What was her name? She used an alias, but whatever. Rebecca. Yeah. Have you ever heard
of Rebecca Roth? Dimitri? Yes, I could. But without any details. Okay, her details was that
her main platform was, there's no way that an airplane can go through a building like a hot
knife and butter. There's no air. There's no way there were airplanes. Yeah. And she was a stewardess.
Yeah, she had many new people internally in the airplane companies and had access to some data
that was collected. That's most likely classified after she got it. And one of the things was two of
the things was many people wrote affidavits, or were calling the authority saying there's going
to be an error that morning, an airplane crash because they saw American Airlines planes flying
at treetop level. And so those she suggests that those planes were flown and landed,
at least some of them at Westover Air Force Base in Massachusetts, because it has a 10,000 foot
runway, and it's less than 20 minutes away from New York City. So more than one plane was seen
on that route. The interesting thing that she found out also by investigating this,
on September 10, everyone on the military base was ordered to stay in hotels.
Right. So very interesting, right? Correlation. That's basically the crux of her work. And
there's no way that airplanes could have gone through what the no airplanes basically was the
idea from her. A few other details about her just just for the record is that she was also a what
they call a purser. And she had other responsibilities outside of being a stewardess.
And she familiarized many people with various things like the procedures that would have
occurred under certain circumstances, if there was a hijacking, etc, and all that.
And she revealed a whole bunch of interesting details there that,
quite frankly, you never heard, despite the fact you had heard from stewardesses and things,
she gave a different level of information. And it's really fascinating. I spoke to her
several times about it. She wrote three books that I recall about it. Yeah. Plus,
very little left online, I think from her. But yeah, in other words, her work,
combined with Dimitri's work, she doesn't understand she has a very slave mentality.
She doesn't understand the money system or the oligarchy and things like that. So
she might make statements that seem like, you know, you can change the world, right?
Which is not possible. So. Right. So if you don't mind, I can maybe correct something.
Please do. What I what I understood from your explanation that she she suggests that the
two passenger planes that supported to penetrate the steel twin towers were in fact,
diverted to some military base. Yes, that's correct. Yes. Okay. But in my in my opinion,
according to my research, it was not so. Because if they really did this, that will be too many
people involved. And after that, they have to get dispose of the huge planes and there will be a lot
of witnesses in the military. I think it's not it's not the proper way to do. So what I found,
according to my research, is that the both planes that were supposedly hijacked were diverted to the
Atlantic Ocean and they fell into water and they sunk at great depth. That is that is almost certain
because the first the first American fighter jets that were sent to intercept the hijacked planes
were didn't fly towards the New York. They flew towards the Atlantic Ocean. And this one is very
obvious because that is recorded in all official documents. And there was a lot of critics at the
initial stage. You remember, maybe they criticized the US military for just stupidity, why they send
the aircraft over Atlantic Ocean. But in fact, they were planes that were flying towards the
Atlantic Ocean. So that's everything. And there was information that transponders of the two
planes that were supposedly penetrating the Twin Towers were still transmitting signals from
underwater in the Atlantic for some time before the batteries died out. So that's what I know.
Well, from the standing, I didn't know about the transponder. That's great. Also,
they cannot use missiles because of the transponder, they have to use cannon fire.
From the standpoint of, you know, intelligence and the control of the after, you know, the after
action. This makes a whole lot more sense, actually, because you have the ability for containment,
you know, it's a generalized term, but you're able to contain a great many more aspects doing
it the way that Dimitri describes it here. Which just, you know, simple logic should tell you that
but that's what the military does. They like blowing things up. And yeah, being very terminated
was called termination with extreme prejudice. Yeah. Right. And it also there's nothing else.
Also, if you can simultaneously remove things from the scene, so they're taken out of sight,
and also completely remove them from any discovery afterwards, you know, that would
sink to the ocean, you're never going to see it again. It very simple. That's just the more
efficient way to dispose of evidence. I mean, also, I want to get with Dimitri, it's not just
Dimitri's research and expose on the on the 911 catastrophe disaster, but how they're using,
let's say, micro and mini nukes through these supposedly terror events that they called a car
bomb, like Volgodonsk in Russia, right? The Chechen rebels, right? And also in Arabia, Saudi Arabia,
the Lebanon and places like that. So any more information about that, Dimitri?
Yes. There were quite a few so called car bombings. I mean, that they were reported to public as a car
bombing, some of them suicidal. But in reality, this was just a cover up for the explosions of
the mini nukes that were hidden somewhere underground, probably in some pipeline.
The well known ones are bombing of the US Marines in Beirut, Lebanon.
Ah, the Marine Barracks.
That was one of the well known ones. And the place, by the way, was called Ground Zero
also by that time.
Yeah, I actually want to ask you about that term, Dimitri.
I was going to ask you about that term, actually, right there, Ground Zero,
because this became the commonplace term with the media. And indeed, the site in New York City
was then named Ground Zero. And many people have said that is the most obvious revelation that
comes from this construct, because they are showing you that that is the term used for the
position where nuclear detonation occurs. Ground Zero. Very simple. They're telling you this
directly, in fact, in public, right?
If it's used in a technical in a technical way, but the culture has adopted that term now for
many things.
Yes, but let me correct it, because before 1991, before 2001, before the end of the year 2001,
all American dictionaries, big or small, actually small dictionaries usually do not include Ground
Zero, but some of them, but the big ones, like an abridged dictionary, all of them
have a definition of Ground Zero as a place of the nuclear explosion, or its projection onto
the Earth's surface. No other meaning, absolutely not. So all additional meanings, like figurative
or colloquial or extra meanings, were ascribed to the Ground Zero term only after 2002.
And this was a great effort by the US government, which ordered all dictionaries to be reprinted
with updated definition of Ground Zero. So now, because they were caught red-handed with that
single definition, and if you imagine what can happen if someone complains about the nuclear
demolition in the court, and they bring some English on abridged dictionary, which is admissible
evidence in the court, and say, look, if they call a spot of World Trade Center a place for
nuclear explosion, then it is. So they had to modify the definition of Ground Zero since then.
So from 2002, and mostly from 2003, they began to reprint all English dictionaries
with expanded definition of Ground Zero. So they ascribed from 2 to 7 different new meanings to
this Ground Zero term, trying just to dissolve the original meaning.
Interesting. I want to make a correction. One thing we speak here for many, many episodes here,
Dmitry, is I can tell you specifically for the United States, we were supposed to have
three branches of government when you said court, you know, the legislative, the executive,
and the judicial with the courts. And the whole world has followed this, but in 1938,
they dissolved. There's no more judicial courts, even in the rest of the world. If you look at
what they call the judicial system, whether Russia, Iraq, anywhere, it's run by the attorney
generals, which is part of the executive branch, and it's confirmed by the legislative, and very
little court is left. Everything is basically military tribunal now. So no court will take
anything unless it's to benefit them. It's all biased. So what we're doing here, we can say
we're a judicial court, and we're having court right now is better than anything that we can get
from the authorities, because they have eliminated the judicial branch, except for some Supreme
Court justices that sit there, which is not even really a court. It's an appellate court. And you
see, it's not a court of record again. So one of the things that most people are under the illusion
that we have a judiciary in the world, no more, it's all executive. That's why you cannot go,
there's many people that have tried to do things like that, in minor, and they always get kicked
out. There's no more of that system. So that's part of that, you want to call it new world order
or whatever. It's very surreptitious. They've done most of the biggest changes in our society in front
of us, and we still call it what it used to be, almost like the way they changed ground zero
definition. I just wanted to bring that, because I know you also helped out Victor Boot
in legal proceedings. Let's just call them legal proceedings, and you see what they do.
Yes. But to correct this, I would say that even before that time, the courts used to look like
more neutral, but they were not completely neutral even before, because all judiciary in
a sovereign state delivers judgment in the name of the sovereign. For example, the US courts
deliver judgments in the name of the United States, obviously. The courts in Russia, they deliver
judgments under the name of the Russian Federation. The courts in some kingdoms deliver judgments
under the name of His Majesty the King. So from this point of view, the judiciary is always under
the sovereign. So they cannot deliver judgments that are against sovereign, and you also cannot
bring to the court illegal suits that are against sovereign, because they judge in the name of the
sovereign anyway. Yes. We have certain procedures here to do that, but they never make it through,
because ultimately it's about contract law. The evidence doesn't matter. It's what contract is
being argued, which is initially the charges of the plaintiff, and it always works in favor
of the plaintiff, which in the case you mentioned is the sovereign. So again, it ends up being very
similar. But if you look back in history, there are some, let's say, judicial cases that were
against the sovereign that made changes in laws, where that doesn't happen anymore.
Yeah, maybe in the past, but surely not now. Yes. No, not after 1938 here, or anything. That's why
people, when you go to court, it's not what you think. Just like anything, you know, the media is
not what you think. You know, the doctor, the lawyer, none of that is operating the way they
tell us. Again, which goes back to the work that you've done, because if you look at, would you
call it brainwashing, the 9-11 official version, or just give the people, like pigs, throw anything
and they eat it? Which one do you think it is? Because it doesn't look like it was a big brainwashing effort.
It's very difficult to say. Depends on how you think. I think they simply not respect the people
anymore. So before, like let's say 70 years ago, they still think that the people are people. But
now they think that people are just slaves, so they don't even bother to explain them anything.
A very poor quality effort. I think it's dependent on how you judge that scale, Dimitri,
right? I mean, if there is a certain level to which you decide that information can be disseminated,
then who do you disseminate it to? Do you control the direction it goes?
And also do you control, because the official explanation and all that,
sure, they gave you pretty pictures and even a comic book version of it.
Sure, here's your 9-11 explanation. I don't know if you're aware of that, but they actually
produced a graphic novel, if you will, of the official report. So this is a mark of exactly
what they are imparting to people, right? What quality are they giving? You know by the quality
of what they're giving. What's the phrase I'm looking for here, Greg? You know them by their
works, right? The public is very ridiculous. I mean, I don't know how it is in Bangkok,
the public mindset, but I don't think it's any different anywhere you go in the world.
The majority is very gullible, let's say. It doesn't matter where you are right now in the
world, unless you're going to some tribesmen live in the mountains, you know. Yeah, I think so.
No, but if we talk about Thailand, Thailand is still, they have some, I mean, many citizens,
they still have some active position, I would say this. Oh, yeah, okay. So it's not so bad,
but it's going the same way anyway. Yeah, yeah, pretty much. So, Dmitry, in terms of your work,
I know you have the YouTube channel in Russian, and you have one in English. You work more on
the Russian one, because that's your first language. Yeah, and I do try to watch those,
but I don't speak any Russian, so it would be great if you did some more on the English.
I will try to do, because actually, you know, because firstly, English is really not my native
language, and in fact, I never learned it, I just speak like this. But if I continuously do English
things, I mean, things in English, that will be easy. But when I do often things in Russian,
it's very difficult for me just to switch the mind to speak in English, but I will try my best.
I mean, from now on, I will try to record more videos in English and put them there.
But the problem is that to have a good video, I need someone, some people to talk with,
or at least I need a list of questions, because even in Russian, most of my Russian videos are
not monologues. I just obtain a list of questions from people who are interested
in my opinion on certain things. And then by answering these questions, I have an effect
that I have someone to talk with, because when I'm completely alone, like a monologue,
I just don't like it. So if, for example, you want to record a video with me, I mean,
the video conversation or something like that, and I can place it on my YouTube channel,
I will be very pleased with that. So you would be amenable to, I happen to do other
radio interviews of sorts, you would be amenable to doing, say, a series of interviews with me
that we could turn into a video for you. Okay, that would be great. I will make that arrangement
with you after we're done speaking today, if you don't mind. Yeah, yeah, I think I think that's
pretty much it. I wanted to just really, like I said, to have Dimitri to honor his work.
But we don't do that anymore. Only the Freemasons have honorary dinners, right,
Dimitri? They honor somebody. So the best we can do is maybe bring you on our podcast and
hear your voice just to honor the work that you did. I personally honor you very much.
Right. And I'd like to... Sorry to interrupt you, but the recording that we do now,
I also can put in my YouTube channel. So that will be one of the things.
Okay, that's up to you. Or we can do another one with Chuck that would be more,
more whatever. Yeah, we'll see. We'll talk about it. We'll talk about it after we're done with this.
I'd like to point out to longtime Greek listeners, you should absolutely recognize Dimitri's name,
because he has been mentioned several times, often, as a matter of fact, anytime 9-11 is mentioned
any of the Ocelli and the Greek shows. I absolutely know that his name will come up.
And there will be show notes posted with this Rated Y Sonic event that will give you his website
and YouTube channels so that you can go and take a look at the four hour video
and other work by Dimitri all on your own. I wanted to let the listener know that,
and again, I know that you've been... I don't know if you're aware of how many times you've
been mentioned, Dimitri, during discussions between myself and the Greek, but a couple
hundred episodes ago, seems like and is, you know, even way, way back, I believe you were
mentioning Dimitri's work, even in the American Freedom Radio days, Greek, weren't you?
Mm-hmm, yeah, pretty much, yeah. Again, thank you for coming, Dimitri, and
maybe do some more things with Chuck. Yeah, absolutely. Okay, thank you for inviting me.