Sonic Event 61, Ocelli in the Greek, rated Y. So, why? Let's get into it. Why? Because
we love you. Where did that come from? Oh, that's right, it was a TV show.
Oh, please, please, no, I'm not kidding. I'm not in the mood tonight for that. That's fine.
I just wanted to throw it at you because I knew you weren't expecting it. A little break in the
pattern, right? That's fine. It's nighttime here and I'm laying down because I just can't stop
yawning. So, anyway, yeah, Israel, we said let's just do a quick update. It's a project.
Well, we got to open up on it because it is now. Now, here, part of the project I would like you
to address right out of the gate, then, is the fact that it is on so many people's minds. It's
occupying a lot of their thought. And is this not in and of itself part of the purpose of the
project? Go ahead. Yeah, that's right. It's a project. It's a media project. It's a financial
project. It's a cultural project. All these will eventually become religious. Pretty much like I
talked about for the past three decades now, the Middle East Union, but it's not going to be like
the EU. I did speak on private Skype calls with someone who had visited Israel a month ago for a
month, and he was amazed at how accurate the presumptions and prognostications that I made
were regarding everything military politics and how things are being set up or not set up. And
it's basically to abuse the consciousness to the point where people feel like they're losing
control because they will lose control to a new type of system that's emerging. And this is a
matter of people utilizing the vague concepts of end times stuff, right? In the mind, I'm not saying
not take that seriously. What I am saying is the interpretation that people carry around with them
where they're waiting. Yeah, that's what's not to be taken seriously because the Christian mindset
now has got to be a bit. If you're listening to me, hopefully you don't have any of that
Christianity, churchianity, stuff that they talk about, you know, out of your mind,
the Jesus, all that stuff. Yeah, well, straight out of the gate, if you've gotten, you know,
if you actually have gotten through the 60 pieces, or even a good chunk of them,
you should already be aware of that. You know, this project loss, it's a project,
this project is cumulative. We never really started from the beginning. The first couple of episodes,
we kind of got a little deep into the spirit. And so just to show the separation, which is
interesting, one of the videos in the, in the chat, it was, I believe, the DNA that was transmitted
over wire or air, basically, a DNA sample could be reproduced anywhere in the world,
using, you know, radio, basically, or signal or, you know, a connection, you like a phone or
something to another part of the world in distilled water. And it's kind of mystifies a lot
of people, it's magic, but it's not, that's how the body works. Because the signal being sent over to
to the receiving station has some form of amplification when it gets there, like an
op amp, you know, some kind of amplification on that side, and that amplification produces
enough current voltage information to do what to the water induction. And that's exactly how
so the way the DNA is sent across the world, and supposedly magically appears in water,
how incredible water is, yes, is the same way that the food gets inside the body when it's
in the intestines, exactly the same method. That's why speaking, if I get more to the point
where I want to keep working on these projects, we'll like we've talked about the water device,
we're going to be talking about induction devices, but I, for personal, everybody cover your ears,
I feel like I'm condemned to be on this planet with morons. And it's kind of like walking
waist high in mud, versus walking on a road. So I want to cross the street, I want to go here,
I want to go there as a metaphor, you want to sit on the ground, you want to seek dry land a bit.
Oh, my gosh, everything. It's like three steps forward, two steps back with everyone.
And here's, here's not an excuse. But I think an explanation, and it ties directly to what you're
saying. And that is, look, I think back often to the old tropes about the guys who used to scream
that the CIA was, you know, broadcasting, you know, radio waves into their brains directly.
And people used to make jokes out of that, they could actually do it, we come to find out, but
it's far worse than that. Because any, if we were to break this topic open, just for a second,
just peek at it for a second. The truth is that this very baseline, this very absolute, like
essential piece of reality that is the induction, induction in so many different ways, what you can
take in psychologically, spiritually, physically, etc, through the air, the water, the food,
through the communication of information, noise, everything.
It's non physical. Well, it's not electrons moving through anything either, you know,
well, but they've put their, okay, they're not using the electrons, but what but they are
utilizing physical things. It's pressure, it's a pressure gradient in the ether.
And it's a mass grid, so that all bases are covered. I mean, the way I see it, maybe I'm wrong.
But look, the way I see it is they've covered all the physical ground they can,
because look, if your your interaction with this world is you would have to agree,
based on what it is we breathe, what it is we consume, right, and put into our bodies,
because that begins another process, and does literally build us right through induction.
So we're literally getting it from cradle to grave.
Well, it's ether. It's the ether. Well, it's not see what
Hmm. When you're inside the video game,
they don't talk unless they're trying to do an advertisement in the video game,
they don't talk about the video game in the video game, right? It's like the guy
who wrote the book, the simulacrum that they showed in the matrix is when you're in the
simulacrum simulacrum, you don't talk about the simulacrum. Well, of course not. Because when
you're in a movie, you don't talk about that you're in a movie, it's actually been broken
and done several times, right? But it's not remembered.
No, absolutely. But that's the thing is that this is about that, you know, what they call
a fourth wall break, where, indeed, you're supposed to be just immersed. And therefore,
it's part of the accepted reality. You know, john can take on an army of people going back
to Keanu Reeves, john wick can take on an army of people. Is that possible? Yes, maybe. But
you're supposed to believe that that's not only possible, but an accepted part of that reality
that he is the, whatever they call them, they had a name for him throughout it. But I don't
know if you ever saw those movies. But you're aware of the concept where he's this like unbeatable,
super killer guy, who's dealing with, you know, the great secret organization that is actually
responsible for all the assassinations and murders that go on on a real level, they exchange
gold coins, which is true. You know, all that is true. But see, while you're in the movie,
you're supposed to take it as Yes, it's a movie. But it's the immersive experience.
That's not Deanna. Well, that's john.
You know, let me just say this. I'm yawning, because I did some pretty hard landscaping
past two days. And in Tucson here, it's used to be an ancient seabed. And when you dig down,
it's like medium mortar. It's like, shovel, you break shovels, you have to use picks. It's
very hard, right? Anyone who's into engineering, it's the ground is in the 200 to 400 psi range,
right? Like, it's a little softer than pine, right? So anyway, planted for bougainvillea
trees. But here's, here's the metaphor. There's a Frank Herbert do metaphoric, it ties into
everything we just said, including the DNA and Israel and everything, what is a gift, not a gift.
When you make it when you make the object, that's a gift, really, really heavy, very heavy. When you
give it to an ordinary man, you'll notice its weight, and he'll drop it. But if you give it to
a good man, he'll continue to carry it until it crushes him. Right. So tie that into what I was
saying, I'm not saying I'm a good man, but I'm crushed. Because I just have to like, here's the
thing. And this is not this may be a little more personal than I ever say I want to talk about.
But I'm always looking for people to jam with, I'm always looking for people to have, you know,
comprehension and all this other way. But after a while, you just start selling saying to yourself,
just like everyone else has come before anyone else has realized what's going on here. Do nothing.
Do nothing, just abandon, just do nothing, just live. Right? Don't, you know, but I'm still
working on stuff, you know. And so when you get to that point, that it's like, Oh, man, you know,
it starts to begin to feel it feels like a condemnation, you know. So anyway, but yeah,
it's it can crush you. And it could kill you. It's very easy for people to kill you with words.
Also, when you start paying attention, right, when you understand the importance of words,
and what people say, and how they structure it, and communications can kill you.
That's why, for example, when you look at the NPCs in the society, when they see the media,
let's be pumped out right now, they don't see through it, they see like body counts,
oh, how bad even though they're not real, by the way, right? No one's really counting bodies,
by the way, when they when the body count changes day by day, no one's out there tallying anything
up. It's all made up, by the way, right? Right. You know, if you talk to anyone who's ever been
in a war, no one's counting bodies. The only time bodies are counted and not even reported
are when people die in hospital or in medic, in the hands of medics. By the way, the only way
legally they could give a body count is when a die, they die in the hands of a medic or recorded
by a medic. Right? Well, it's generally accepted almost anywhere that the only person that can
sign off on a thing without doing a postmortem examination is a doctor or even that, you know,
in a vac, what do they call those military hospitals? Like mash? Oh, yeah, the master
triage. Yeah, right. Yeah, you could be declared dead. But so all these body counts that they're
giving are totally illegal. Yeah, you don't get an official count. When you're declared dead in
the triage or whatever, you only get the official count can only be had when a doctor signs a slip of
paper, which says this person legally, you don't have to be but you have to be given the authority
you could be if it goes through power of attorney, right? Well, yeah, they can hand it over. But
generally speaking, what I'm saying is that what's universally accepted is and I know this by
example, just to throw in, yeah, just to throw in 911. Again, you know, the initial corner report
for the cause of death of the victims in the buildings was vaporization. You know what
vaporization means? They have these things instead of smoking their vape, you know, the vape, you know,
vapor is vapor. It's, it's not particle, you've been completely dematerialized, right,
basically into a gas. Well, you've learned from a solid thing into effectively steam. Yeah,
there's no blood. Yeah, there's no blunt force or building collapse that can vaporize anyone,
but a nuclear demolition would anyway. And when a lot of the families were inquiring,
they changed it. So I don't know what something else. Well, that's why those reports read as
preliminary until that's why they read that way around. Yeah. But either way. So either way,
don't don't fall for it. So here's the thing. When you start to become more critical, you
it's good. But you become more sensitive, like something that people joke around about.
I'm not saying this has happened to me. I'm just giving an example here. There's something that
people would normally joke around. If you become more objectified, and more, let's say,
word citing and what's going on. And if you let's say the brunt of a joke or something,
it could be very hurtful, right? Well, this is common. Yeah, we don't want to make anyone the
brunt of a joke. Yeah, real simple is somebody, you know, recently just died from cancer.
Somebody makes a joke about cancer or somebody's hair falling out during chemotherapy or whatever,
you'll notice a shift in that conversation all of a sudden when they recognize,
oh, wait a minute, I just said something and his wife, girlfriend, brother, son,
recently died. The whole cancer thing is pretty wild, too, because it's, it's not what people
think it is. Oh, no, I'm just using it as it could be anything could be about drunk driving.
And recently, somebody was killed by someone who was intoxicated. Let's grab a drink. Yeah.
Yeah, you don't want to you don't want to hit a bump and spill your drink, right?
Yeah, you don't want to be the guy going, no, I, you know, stupid joke, right? I
just pay the piano. And my sister has no hands. I'm not drinking and driving,
you know, because I drink and I go driving, you know, things like that. Yeah, exactly. And then
you do that in front of, you know, they just had somebody they care about run over by a car.
Yeah, they go, wait a minute, you know? Yeah. Yeah. But the here's the other thing. I was
very intelligent engineering type person research discussion. And he kind of some reason the flat
earth globe Earth came up, right? Okay. And I was like, you cannot function that way,
you have to have an overview of the condition of the mind. And what do you mean? It's like,
when you want to objectify, let's say the shape of the Earth, for example,
does it you know, you're about flat Earth is going to be objectified either way.
Once you are living in a subjective reality, actually, you existed in a subjective reality
before you started making the effort to objectify it, right? So once you start trying to objectify
something that you accepted is subjectively true, on your when you start changing modes,
and you start looking at objectively, it starts to become subjective.
When you be so in other words, when you are living a subjective life,
everything around you seems to be objective. But once you decide to start making the decision
to start objectifying things, the things that you look at become subjective. It's strange,
it's kind of like you want to be real, you want to do a precision measurement on cutting a shelf.
So instead of just measuring it inches or half inch or quarter inch, you measure it down to
32nd or 64th of an inch. And you can check it twice and you cut it. And you come back and you
try to fit it and it's really off, worse off than if you just made a rough measurement. And you're
like, holy crap. If I just made a rough measurement, it would have fit better. I'm trying to
make this precise measurement and it's worse. What this doesn't make any sense. It's not like the guy
that says, Look, I cut this board three times and it's still too short. I don't know why. Right?
No, I'm talking about when you start releasing subjectivity and choosing objectivity,
you'll notice that the things that you're trying to objectify cannot be objectified,
and they become more and more subjective. Right? This goes with people. This goes with things with
science and all these other things. So well, another thought is, regardless of whether you
think the earth is a flat or round, right? How do you make anything at all level? Because the moment
that's my point. Yeah. If you want it to be round, it will be round. If you want it to be flat,
it will be flat. But architect that a far architects in agriculture rely on it being
flat and it's in the center doesn't move. Right? We're map makers. And sometimes aviators and
navigators find that it's round. I've witnessed the curvature from doing survey. We tried and we
started off four and a half miles apart and we used the Adelaide, Philadelphia rod, you know,
to measure to meet in the middle. And we were off by seventy five feet over four miles. And they
did the math and all that. And they're like, yeah, it's some of it's the terrain, but it's
the curvature of the earth. So we did it again. You ended up being off. That's why in a lot of
maps you'll notice a step in the borders of states and counties. They're not pieced together evenly.
And also we try to lay out a large triangle at one hundred and eighty degrees, you know,
and it couldn't couldn't do it. It was always slightly greater than one hundred and eighty
degrees because of the curvature of the earth. But water is level. Right. And a plumb bob is
plumb and level. And the agriculture I've seen ditch canals in Blythe, Arizona, run for seven,
eight miles, ignoring, you know, we're talking about only eighth inch drop every 20 feet.
And they that decline was good enough for seven or eight miles. But if we're going against the
curvature of the earth. So. Right. And so it acted completely flat. So I don't know if you
want it to be flat. It's flat. You want it to be round. It's round. So you cannot be objectified.
In 30 seconds, I can tell you that a guy who made a living as a military sniper,
who was actually a fairly well-known one, sort of explained something similar to me,
where, look, at a certain point, you have to accept the curvature of the earth
because it depends on what you're doing. That's a sniper. So that's what I was getting to,
is that it depends on what you're doing. You can deal in straight lines in some circumstance
and in others. And that makes no sense to me. I'm sitting there saying, well, look,
either you have to deal with it or you don't. Right. But he's telling me that regardless of
what I think, that's not how it is. I've been on the flat portion of I-10 and took out some
binoculars that knew the object was 36 miles away and I could see the flat road, no curvature for
36 miles. Right. And so there's no way, you know, there's eight inches every mile or anything
because it would have to have dropped off. But in other places, like I said, I've actually
physically measured the curvature, could not could not make a triangle. Right. To literally
put a bullet through a dime at a mile away. Guess what? You need that curvature.
Or not, depending on how you're raised. Well, most likely the flat earther will end up by the
round earther compensating and one not compensating for the curve will both get it. Yeah. The weird
thing is what I was going to point out to you is that the guy who mechanically has to use it in
order to accomplish his task. Right. He's putting a bullet in a very precise place from a distance.
If that could be a mile. Yeah, that's what I'm saying is a mile away. Five thousand feet plus.
Yes. There at that point. Easily. It's I mean, maybe it's before that, after that, too. I don't
know. But what I what he gave. I've heard of three thousand yards, mile and a half being the record
or something like that. Some crazy like that. Yeah. Well, but that's the thing is he was telling
me that a mile when you get to the mile, you have to account for this this way. And it wasn't even
like I was trying to have a flat earth discussion with the guy. This is what I'm saying. This is
the whole thing I've been trying to objectify now for decades. And you are when you start off.
Don't mistake this for objectification, but it seems like it. And this is an error that I've
made. Like, for example, when people talk about stuff in the Bible or the money system of law,
what you think you're going to go objectify and you start reading it and you're like, wow,
this is contrary to what everyone's saying it is. Right. So because you find the information
that has been put out about something to be contrary to the way people are using it does
not mean it's objective to objectify either. All it means is that no one knows what the rules are
and no one's following the rules because they don't. Well, if they seem like they're following
the rules, it happens to be a happenstance because they can't tell you where they got it.
Right. And can't show you where they got it, regardless of any of those subjects, even scientific.
But it seems to because of their subjectivity, they think they're objective. They're not.
Things are still working. It just seems that people say the system. How can you? The system
has all been laid out on paper. Like if you say religious system, it's laid out in books.
If you talk about financial system, the Federal Reserve puts out publications in history of how
it does it. But if you ask people how these things work and what they're supposed to be based on,
no one really knows. Yeah, it's an old, weird concept of, you know, the whole thing with the
lasers and the lights where they say just by observation, it literally changes the characteristic
of the thing through observation. You say to yourself of complex diffraction. Yeah. The
particle or wave theory. That's another thing that that that came out. That's part of quantum,
which is which is not quantum. It's fine perturbances in the ether, as Ken Wheeler might
say. But I wouldn't say. But what I'm saying is that we are subjective beings in a subjective
reality. And you should still. All right. So am I saying do not objectify? No, definitely
attempt to objectify, because what you'll find on the way is priceless. Right. And you actually
could be used in your favor many times over. You'll have a deep understanding. But once you
start seeing that none of these things are being used and known by others, typically the typical,
the average person who uses them, talking about professionals now even. Yeah. And the system still
holds together. That means that it's subjective system all the way down. You could say it's
subjective or you could say that those hard and fast rules of the reality are definitely dependent
on circumstantial issues. So as long as the people think they're objective but remain subjective.
Okay. Henry Ford said if people found out how the money system works, there'll be a revolution
overnight. Right. Well, how did he propose people find out? He never said that. Well, the money
system. Well, it's very easy. You just go find out how fiat currency works. Right. Yeah. And it is
based on ledgers. Right. On their thing. But the way that they produce the money is completely
unlawful, even in their own text. Right. And they even give you a remedy for it. But no one seems to
apply that or know that. But once you get into that and you study it, it baffles the mind on how
people defend something that is working against them. And it's the same thing with the medical
and the religious system, like the Christians. How can a God that's so loving that created
everything, send someone, condemn them to a fiery place. It doesn't make any sense. Right. Right.
So which he doesn't. So by the way, in the scripture, there is no place where you condemn
to. That's fire. I got you. You know, an odd thing that occurs to me. Are you familiar with
Larkin Rose? I've heard of the name. OK, but I don't know what he does. He's a writer. You know,
he's one of these guys irrelevant because there's just one particular key piece that I think would
be of interest to you. Have you ever heard of the Jones Plantation? No. OK. You mean the one down the
one down where everybody took took the punch? No, this is a this is something that's created.
Not not not that fictional. No, it's it's not a cult or anything like that. It is fictional,
but it is metaphoric and makes some of the points. Oh, yeah. Yeah. I think I might have
heard of it. And there's a slave that they use as an example. Well, not only the example,
it's more complex than that. If you actually go through it, there's like a 13 minute version of
this cartoon. But they recently made it into like a full length movie, independent movie.
And is this how they everyone wanted something better? In the end, they showed you basically
the leaders showed them that that's not what they wanted. And whoever spoke out against it was bad.
Well, that was part of it. But OK, so I did come across something like the overall thing is about
the concept of, you know, slavery still being the condition of most people. They've just simply
changed the way it's done. And yeah, I mean, ultimately, I'll tell you what, don't worry about
it. I'm going to I'm going to send you something when we're done talking today. I got you. They
have not changed. Here's the thing. Yeah. Take advantage. Yeah, good. I'm glad you said that.
I'll tell you why. And you'll see why. Because we've been told that slavery is black people
that are in chains with whipping scars on their backs, photos and all these stories. Right. Yes.
But saying that I'm not denying that. No, slavery was very complex then. It's very complex now.
Right. And so it has not changed. Right. What our ability to see it to its core or how it really
functions has never been brought to light. It's always been a legal condition. You and I in the
old O.G. years ago, I said, you know, slavery is a lawful condition that is bound legally.
In other words, you can have slaves in law, but you have to bind them legally. So whenever you
have a system. So in other words, the legal system is for business entities and slaves.
That's what this. So if they only have a offering you a legal system in your society, that means
you either have a business or you're a slave. If you're dealing with legal or illegal, you know,
the you know, that sick bird and illegal. Yeah. Yeah. So so there's no law. Talk about law. Now
they do talk about law and they think they, you know, whatever. I talk about law and order.
Yeah. The thing about American slavery, first of all, that was done.
That was not done the way we were told, by the way. And the setup, there was a big setup that
was done for a reason with that. And that's why if you if you study what Abraham Lincoln
wanted to do, it was not a race issue. You know, anyway, there's Yeah, here's the other thing.
I want to mention this because I've had some conversations with people much older than myself.
And one of them was an engineer who designed a black man who engineer engineer designed most of
the highways in Atlanta. And I said, Oh, damn you, because it sucks. You know, because Yeah,
but it was a good idea. It was the best engineering we had at the same at the time.
Oh, yeah. For God's sake, though. Yeah. Yeah. If you go to that part of the country,
like five, you have to go through Atlanta, right? It's 90 minutes away from me. It is
not pleasant. Yeah. Anyway, yeah. Anywhere you go south or nearby, you have to go through this
anyway. But he was upset because the civil rights movement was backwards. And so was this is not
race. This is just politics and legal and slavery all mixed together. It's not just about race.
But he was not happy about the civil rights movement. And but and he was very happy about the
what's it called, where you have to hire what they call minorities, affirmative action would have
action. Yeah. And he says both of those are misunderstood. I think I went over the affirmative
action. Do you remember the reason what the real reason for affirmative action was because he was
part of it. You're part of this study. I you know, I vaguely remember this. I remember being so really,
I was so shocked over the idea, although you were correct, that slavery was like,
you know, this is no, this is an example to show how the race and social status and slavery and
people that are caught up in it are being used for both good and bad. Now, affirmative action,
we're told that which is true to a degree that certain professional jobs were lacking in
minorities. And minority, by the way, is not the color of your skin means if you're competent or
not, like, you know, you're a minority or a minor when you're less than 18. Right. So let's say you
did a newspaper route for, let's say, from 13, you could start legally, right, working paper,
searching 14. So 16, and you saved up enough cash to buy a brand new Cadillac. So you walk
into the Cadillac dealership with a bag full of cash at 17. And you buy the Cadillac and drive it
home. Do you know that you have to bring the Cadillac back and give you your money because
you cannot enter into a purchase and sale legal agreement at that age, you have to be 18 or older?
Well, yeah. Okay. There's certain places where they've played with those numbers a little bit,
like, yeah, it could be 17 and a half. Now they're trying to, which, by the way, when you turn 17,
you're in your 18th year, by the way. And they have this other thing where, you know, you get the
agreement, like those that want to get married at the age of 16.
Yeah, certain states. Yes. But the point here is, if you're a minority, you cannot enter
into contracts and make decisions for yourself, right? That's not on your own. Because even if
you get married at the age of 16, you have to have a parent sign off on it. That's, that's right.
That's right. So, okay, so what was so this is I just defined minority. So you don't want to be a
minority based on what they tell you does means you're incompetent. You're not competent to make
decisions for yourself. Yeah. So being called a minority because of the color of your skin,
or the race or whatever they put in the birth certificate is an insult. You should not be
called a minority to your face or in society. That means that you're perpetually never going
to mature. Because that's one of the things that happened during the with the 14th Amendment.
But here, let's go back to the what is it the right to hire if you're big, a company that gets
the government to have to have an affirmative act. Yeah, right. So from this person who was
part of the studies, black men, he basically said that affirmative action all the meetings
that because this went on for years before they put it in place. I think it was LBJ put it in,
right? Or Nixon, I think it was LBJ. The Civil Rights Act that was passed immediately after
Kennedy's assassination was yeah. So yeah, so this anyway, by the way, that's a minor thing.
But the reason why they did that, because they noticed that Americans after World War Two had a
big boom in industry. But they had a run of about 10 or 12 years of that boom. And then they started
noticing they were falling behind in engineering and business principles and all this. And they
looked at themselves and they said, Well, just a bunch of middle aged white guys. The reason why
we're falling behind is because we need some cultural diversity. We need some new blood in here
because that white bread, middle age, you know, 35 to 55 year old white guy, grown American
is stagnant. So we need to bring people in here from Asia from, you know, from everywhere,
you know, Europe, African continent, whatever, whatever, Latin America to liven it up and spice
up because we're losing our industrial advantage. It was not because Oh, look at these, quote unquote,
minorities, you know, we they have to the goodness of our heart, we're gonna give them
an extra. Yeah, it was not out of the goodness at all. It was because they knew that if they
didn't do that, they would fall so far behind. It would be like, what do you call it when you
have inbreeding, right? Oh, yeah. But yeah, it was a mental inbreeding. They were suffering and
they knew it and they had they were wise enough to see it then. It was like the it was almost
like the opposite of the woke movement in a way they wanted to firm things up, not loosen things
up. But the other comment he made was the civil rights movement destroyed the black community
potential of the black community in America, because no one ever talked about when you hear
about the black communities in America, the first thing the average American goes to their mind is
to the ghettos. They never talk about the affluent black communities like Mariana, Georgia, and Kew
Gardens and Queens and all these other places, right? For your forest. So nowadays, they never
to Chicago is the first place usually, and then it's on to another urban area where
there is high crime, etc, etc. That's where their initial thing is.
It gets never talking in the American mind and media never show the affluent black communities
never, not at all, always the ghetto and when and the hip hop music is the culture, right?
And all this so that so he's like, Oh, my gosh, all this. He was correct. He says when the silver,
they're going to show the worst of the worst. And that's going to become the culture. And you know
what, he was right. He's very unhappy man. And he's in his 80s. Now, I guess about it. He saw
a different vision back in the 60s, when we were shown that in the 60s, it was so right. So look,
they're beating black folk up, you know, sick and dogs on them and stuff and fire hoses, right?
He says, that's not really what's going on. This is that's not really how we're heading. And that's
how we really are. You know, a bunch of protesting people were up and they're up and rising that,
you know, the developing communities, you never hear about that. Or you hear about,
oh, we can't go to schools, white folk, and we can't send the buses that and by the way,
the Rosa Parks thing is bullshit. There's always been over 100 people that have done that. But Rosa
Parks was the one right? She's like the George Floyd. You know what I mean? For some reason?
Yeah. Yeah. So all this stuff. It's fake. Are you surprised that we're getting a fake story
and all this stuff? By the way, just to bounce back, I should have started with this, the American
slave that they show you a black man in chains with marks on his back, right? You know, there
were black slave owners that had black slaves. Yes, of course. Yeah. And there were affluent
black communities in America in since the late 1600s 1700s affluent blacks here that own black
slaves. Yes. And also slavery wasn't on the black market. It wasn't like they're shown today. You
know, it was, you know, it was a it was just like the way you go cop an eight ball. Right?
Two levels of it, just like pretty much like you have pharmaceuticals today,
you can get your heroin in a pill form through the pharmacy, or you can go by dope.
You know, right. And when I say black market, no pun intended, it was actually done in a secret
way. They were trafficked. Basically, it was human trafficking to the extreme. Right? Of course.
Yeah, and indentured servitude was also a form of slavery, which is slavery. And they were
put there. That's where you get the term white trash from. By the way, it's from the indentured
servants. They're mostly whites, and Irish that came over and all that. Right. So you had a
contract. Yeah, contract. That's right. Yeah. Yeah. And you had to work and but yeah, and you
had it was 10%. You gave 10% of everything you produced, you know, and now it's like, well,
IRS wants 30%. So, oh, my gosh. Yeah. So you're far worse off in many ways. The only way that I
see people being better off as information exchange, but they're not doing anything with
it. They're just so subdued. You know? No, that's why I think you'll actually enjoy the Jones
plantation thing. So yeah, someone brought it up to me a few years ago. I kind of glanced at it.
But yeah, I'll take a look at it. newer version of it. I think you'll you'll appreciate it.
Like I said, I'll hook you up with that afterwards. But this concept, this idea of
free range slavery is something I've talked about for several years. And it's very difficult for
people to wrap their minds around it. Because no, I have choices. But you and I have been over this
about the choices, right? With that are being presented to people. We've been through.
Well, it's not it's Yes. And you know, hold on. This is the choice. The choice is,
are you doing a restricted endorsement? You know, with conditions? Or are you doing unrestricted
endorsement? unconditional? In other words, when something is brought forward to you,
whether it's legal, commercial, religious, are you just unconditionally accepting it?
Or are you looking at it and saying, Well, I might go down that route under these conditions
are met, or I'm restricting this, this and that. By the way, there's a lady who was part of you
know, the Patriot movement, you know, your straw man and all that stuff years ago,
the 30s started, they didn't know, they were very effective in the 90s. And the Jesuits came over
and said, Oh, your judges get beaten up by these patriots, just ignore them, throw them in jail,
right? The legal fiction thing. Actually, I don't have to appear in the court.
That stuff. Well, the one of the ladies knew that it was really they were cracking down on it just
to maintain power. But she knew she stuck to her guns. I forgot her name, Tammy something.
This is in the early 2000s. She gave a lecture on this. Even in prison. It's a contract when they
went into went into prison, it would jail ship to the prison, you have to sign a new contract,
which basically says they retain the right to do that under 14th Amendment, which basically says,
or 13th Amendment, and 14. There's no more slavery, right? Just citizenship. And if you're
convicted of a crime, you know, right, you're it's slavery is basically allowed. So she went through
and started crossing. They give her something like 17 years she had to do or 12 years.
She started crossing out all the stuff in the prison contracts that put in a cell by herself
and two attorneys came in and said, Well, we saw what you did to the paperwork. So you'll be out in
60 days. Wow, you know, and nothing to do with seeing the judge what he has to say or no,
she just started crossing stuff out on the paperwork. Right? Amazing, right?
Well, definitely. Because it's mind blowing that you know, you can get out of that because
you'd simply didn't endorse stuff, which is Yeah, that's right. She started making restrict the same
thing with a check, you know, 12 USC 411. It's very powerful.