Hey, here we are again, and Rated Y,
that's what's happening.
And Greek, first, how you doing?
But second, I know you got comments from
the chat, so we'll start there, but again,
how you doing?
I'm doing okay, and I'm hearing double, you
know, seeing double.
It's really difficult.
I have to figure out if someone knows
anything about Jitsi.
Why is it, on my end, I hear
everything repeated twice?
It's worse than an echo.
It's actually duplexing at full dynamics, all right?
An echo tends to be lower in volume,
but this is just as loud, and it's
twice.
So hearing you once is bad enough, Chuck.
Twice now?
God damn it, man.
What the hell is going on here?
My apologies, double.
Sorry.
Yeah, no, that's fine.
You know, I just had to say, you
know, the setup was perfect for that.
So on the comments, yeah, on the chat,
a lot of people are having weird stuff.
I'll tell you, talking about why it's weird,
and you know, I talked to those two
weeks ago.
There was something that happened in our reality,
like a soft edit, soft reset, Mandela effect
for everyone, but not a Mandela effect where
everyone gets together and says, remember when this
was this, and now it's that?
No.
Certain things change.
People, a lot of people are reporting strange
behavior in people they know, kind of like
invasion of the body snatchers or watch the
old film was better than the new one.
But the new one with Don, I think
it was Donald Southerman in the 70s was
pretty good, too.
Right?
Remember that?
Yeah, that was great.
So I would say that this is a
similar situation, but let me just tell you
what happened today.
This is happening every day.
All the cool kids wear black, right?
When you go out or whatever, you know.
So I looked at my wardrobe and I
said, I don't have any black shirts, you
know?
And so I said, OK, I'm going to
go to my favorite store, which is called
Speedway Outlet in Tucson.
And the reason I like that, it's near
the Golden Ghetto, where all the wealthy people
live in the foothills.
I used to live up there, by the
way.
And when they die, all their father, you
know, I've mentioned this many times before, usually
around giving background away, I go to the
specific ones better than a Goodwill or anything
like that.
When these old people, they're alone in these
million dollar mansions, not million dollar millions is
not much anymore, but very big homes retired
from being in industry in Chicago.
They have nothing to do here.
No one wants to visit them.
So they walk the malls.
Right.
They even open the malls early at 7
a.m. for the old people to walk.
Right.
I mean, you've heard of that.
There's even a short documentary on that.
I mean, because that's like extinct in most
parts of the country, the mall walking thing.
But they still do that in Arizona.
Yeah.
Yeah, they do.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
So anyway, when the old bastard dies, the
people come over from the East Coast, Chicago,
New York, whatever.
Like, oh, yeah.
Look in their chops.
Let's sell this house.
It's worth five million bucks.
And, you know, they do an estate sale
or whatever.
What about his wardrobe?
Now, here's the thing about his wardrobe.
They walk around the malls and they go
to dealers and places like that or Nordstrom's
and they buy a bunch of stuff and
they go home and hang it up and
they never wear it.
So I like going there because typically, you
know who died because you'll see four or
five shirts with the Nordstrom Brooks Brothers with
the tag still on it and they're all
the same size.
So I'm like, wow, you know, this guy
has the same build as I do wherever.
And this guy just definitely someone just passed
away.
Right.
Is what I say when I see the
rack full of, you know, so anyway, I
go there to get some black shirts today
and there's two high end black shirts, like
a Nordstrom and a Claiborne with the tags
on it.
Nine bucks, six bucks or like 50, you
know, really expensive shirts, let's say, here to
buy shirts.
And I was like, this is too easy.
It's like I put an order in.
Since when do you put an order in
for something, you know, out out there, you
know, make a wish, let's say go out
to a second hand store.
And the items that you wished before you
left your house are in a second hand
store.
Now, this is not unusual.
This happens to me quite often when I
use Craigslist on that way.
I need some wood shutters.
I don't need the shutter.
I just need the slats.
So I think about it and I go
to Craigslist in two days.
Guess what?
Someone's throwing out a wood shutter.
Right.
On and on and on and on.
Some people would call it a manifestation.
Yeah.
Some people call it manifestation.
But manifestation.
That's right.
But I think it's more than manifestation or
very different because I already have selected these
two places.
Manifestation is true.
Like, you know, you'd be driving on the
road and see it on the side of
the road.
Right.
You just fell out of the sky.
But what's unusual about this time is it's
not in season.
In other words, picking up these two black
shirts.
And I got some other stuff also.
And also other things that I've been doing.
I put a man I've been manifesting things,
but not in the way when when these
things were mounted, the black shirts and a
few other things manifested recently.
It wasn't in the way where you're amazed
or this feeling like, look how fortunate this
is.
And wow, isn't the universe a cool place?
You know, nothing like that this time.
When I got the black shirts and a
few other things, it was like, of course,
of course, of course.
None of this amazement and look how fortunate,
you know what I mean?
There's a certain feeling you get when things
manifest like, isn't it a coincidence?
None of that.
It was like, of course, you know, there
was no other way.
Yeah.
So I'm getting this thing that, you know,
people say you ask for things and they
manifest or whatever.
It's almost in a way now like you
just ordered your lunch and they tell you
to sit down and I'll bring it to
you when it's ready.
Kind of different when they bring you your
lunch.
You're not surprised because you just ordered a
dummy.
They said that we're going to bring it.
Right.
It's very different.
Yeah.
It was a general manifestation.
I was just thinking, I think to yourself,
you're hungry and somebody hands you the sandwich
you wanted.
You go, great, thanks.
That's what I wanted.
And you move along with no with no
previous communication.
Right.
Yeah.
But this time it's different.
What's been happening the past week and things
I've been coming up with, by the way,
I'm always coming up with new inventions.
And it's like, of course, it's not like,
oh, wow, you get this feeling, you know,
like this lofty feeling, you know, when you
get really good news, how you feel.
Right.
The reason it's good news.
The reason it's news is because you didn't
know about it till then.
Right.
And it makes you feel in a certain
way.
So none of that anymore.
Now it's like, of course, I mean, this
is I knew this was going to happen.
I knew this was so it's a very
different it's a very fine adjustment in what's
going on.
The other thing that I've noticed is that
people that normally wouldn't speak on these things
are speaking on them now.
That's the other main thing that I've noticed,
you know, the manifestations or whatever.
But there's a few things the chat's been
hopping lately.
And when I say the chat, it's the
what is the chat again, Chuck, please.
Oh, it's the chat angle.
It's really in the Greek.
Yes, that's right.
Which, by the way, because I don't have.
Yes.
Just really quickly for you listening on the
Patreon, there is a link in the description
to the Patreon to go straight to the
chat if you're not familiar.
So, you know, there you go.
Yeah, I've never been to the Patreon one.
As a matter of fact, I'm not a
sub and I don't have access.
That's just fine.
It's just fine.
Keeps me neutral.
And I don't know what's going on there.
But the Chitango one, Ocelli and the Greek
Chitango dot com, I believe.
Yeah, this is the chat I'm speaking on.
Few other things going on there, things we
brought up before.
There was a video from Middle Nation Shaheed
that Ed posted.
I haven't looked at that video.
I really like Shaheed.
I'm glad I'm glad people are enjoying his
stuff.
He's always too political.
I don't think he understands fundamentally how the
economic system works, which I'd like to inject.
What people don't know is the significance of
the Federal Reserve Act, Section 16, Part 1,
Chapter 1, 2 and so on.
That is the fundamental.
That means that if you go to the
central bank to get their money, their private
money, you have to provide collateral.
And when you hear that word collateral, people
think I got to go hawk my ring
or, you know, they own the car till
I pay it off.
No, no.
Collateral for the central bank is the application
that you fill out.
This is so hard.
This is the basis of the entire financial
system, other than the monetization of unconditional promises
to pay the actual funds themselves, you know,
with numbers on them come from the application.
That was so hard for people to understand
that because they don't want to admit how
shitty things are, because how many times how
many people have applied for something and gotten
denied or applied or said you're approved and
then they continue like business as usual and
they don't even know that what they applied
for had a dollar value and whoever whatever
financial institution was handling that application got all
of that and you got nothing, which is
one thing I want to mention.
Slavery today through the credit system quantitatively and
qualitatively is a thousand times worse than it
was when you had a shackle on your
neck and you were working in the fields
all day.
Now, on the on the sheet, I'll tell
you what, on the balance sheet, because if
you have a shackle on your neck and
all you know is yes, no, sir, whatever,
and you're picking cotton, sugarcane, bananas, working blacksmithing
or whatever, you could figure whatever a blue
collar salary would be today for an entire
lifetime is the value of that slave.
Right.
How could that slave generate any more than
that?
Right.
So when I say because blue collars are
doing labor and that kind of stuff, there
are a lot of slaves, by the way,
that lived in splendor.
They wore tuxedos, by the way, you know,
and further because whatever task they performed demanded
that attire and they ate really well and
this and that.
But let's look at a typical.
Yeah.
You're right.
Gloved house guys and stuff like that.
Yeah.
A carriage, trains, houses, homes, mansions, estates, all
the way.
So ships.
So when you look at what a blue
collar worker does for a lifetime, whatever, a
million bucks, that would be what the slave
would generate in capital their entire lifetime.
Right now, I assure you, whatever you've earned,
whatever you've done in life or accumulated, if
you've ever dealt with the credit system with
corporations that have OC-10 and OC-7
access, which is the Federal Reserve window, right,
which is not really a window.
It's just someone who's authorized for the Federal
Reserve to do this.
If anything, you've signed applications for schools, for
college that generated the full amount plus interest
over and over and over and over and
over.
I've heard people going and applying for five
or recently five or six jobs, professional jobs
that pay over one hundred fifty, two hundred
thousand a year.
And they all got denied.
She got denied for all of them.
I said, you generated a minimum of two
million dollars and had to explain it to
her.
And it was really hard for her to
get it, even though I had her all
defined.
So imagine someone who's job hunting, quote unquote,
I don't know, a hundred thousand median median
salary, let's say, and they apply for five
jobs.
It's not unusual for someone over a period
of several months to apply for 10 jobs
online or whatever or in person.
Right.
It's not unusual.
I've heard that.
Yeah, that's that's a big amount.
Yeah, they've generated millions for whoever did this
thing called job fairs.
I've been talking about this since way back
when I got a revolution radio about all
these job fairs lately, right after the financial
crash.
This is after 2008, 2009.
What they're doing is they're trying to suck
out, wring out the towel.
They create these job fairs and all the
big companies go there and they have thousands
of people applying.
How many are hired?
None.
Ever.
Why?
Because they need the applications.
Right.
And they go to the Federal Reserve and
they monetize it to make it even worse.
The Federal Reserve says that once your application
is collateralized, you can come back anytime and
get some more.
Wow.
Right.
So this is so the on the balance
sheet, a typical citizen, resident, whatever you want
to call yourself, human man, woman that deals
with the credit system via applications.
It doesn't matter what you're applying for.
Even an Ace Hardware rewards card, right, is
an application.
If you multiply that, how many times you've
done that in your life and how much
has been extracted?
It's way more than somebody picking cotton or
picking sugarcane.
Right.
I mean, you have generated most people have
generated more money via this process, the application
process than they ever will make or have
in their entire life.
So for the benefit of who?
So slaves are receiving the application.
Yes.
So slaves have gone up in value.
But who's collecting it is the question.
Yeah.
The greatest value is you don't understand how
this works because what's beautiful about it now
from to benefit the bankers.
The beauty is it's been going on for
so long that if you explained it, even
on the radio or TV and show people
would still not want to believe it.
Just like I mentioned years ago, I spoke
to a college professor about somebody else was
arguing about the moon landings.
And I said, what if the astronauts came
out and told you they never go to
the moon?
They never went to the moon.
I would still think they went to the
moon.
Right.
So most people would think an application is
just an application.
So that's why for 20 years I've been
saying the population is toast.
They're they're toast.
Don't even consider it.
It's what you're going to do.
So anyway, I wanted to bring that up
in terms of because that that's going to
get even worse.
And just to tie that in, you know,
that Doge thing that Musk was doing.
Oh, yeah.
I when I first heard that, I said,
he's just going in there perfectly pilfering people's
QCIP numbers, which is the Convention of Universal
Security, whatever investment protocols, because they could everyone
anything.
Look, how difficult is it really if you're
in the in crowd with, you know, the
cool kids to get Social Security numbers from
people?
Very easy, actually.
If you get a ticket, a traffic ticket
has a Social Security number right on top.
Right.
Of the ticket.
So it's not that Musk needed the Social
Security numbers.
He needed the QCIP numbers at the Treasury
issues for the transactions on how those Social
Security numbers were used.
So now he can go in showing security
interest.
So, you know, I must go in and
pilfered another like 15 or 20 trillion.
And how do you know he was doing
that?
Because there's this thing called a guilty conscious.
What was he exposing?
All this financial fraud while he's pulling the
biggest fraud.
You see now there's a lot under your
eyes.
There's a funny thing.
A question I forgot from last time was
somebody was, you know, looking at the Epstein
stuff because it's been in the news.
You know what I'm talking about, right?
The Jeffrey Epstein stuff.
Oh, that distraction, that's really bad.
They really that's really tasteless.
It is.
But they were looking at something different here
because there is a part in his history
where he ends up being a billionaire.
And before that, he was not.
And the funny thing is, nobody seems to
be able to know where it is he
came up with this.
So somebody including a mansion on Park Avenue,
a duplex or something like that is what
you're referring to.
Like he was a New York socialite.
Yeah, but he had a little bit of
money.
But then all of a sudden he's able
to buy islands and his islands go up
and like all of a sudden he goes
to a whole other level, even if he
robbed, you know, Lex Westler all the way
through.
Yeah, yeah.
He's what he's what you call a straw
man.
In other words, he had people behind.
Straw man is an entity that you have
to transfer property and show wealth, but it's
not really their wealth.
It's very similar to do you remember about
a decade ago, a whole string of rappers
came out and said, oh, that all those
cars and cash and houses, you see, we
rent all that.
We don't own anything.
We don't.
We're really broke.
Remember that?
Oh, yeah.
Well, correct me if I'm wrong, but yeah.
Yeah.
Well, correct me if even better than that,
though, was when Prince went on The Tonight
Show or whatever and they go, oh, isn't
this great?
Mariah Carey made twenty million dollars and Prince
went, yeah, Mariah Carey, you want me to
really break this down for you?
And Leno or whoever's like, yeah, go ahead.
If I sell 20 million albums, how much
are you going to give me out of
each album?
And the guy, you know, Leno's knows nothing.
He goes, I have.
Oh, you're going to give me half.
OK, so if you were able to do
that, you know, because obviously you see the
look on his face.
He's like, that's awfully generous.
But OK, we'll work with it.
So imagine how many I got to sell
in order to make that money.
And if I've already sold 100 million and,
you know, that's what they're showing on the
books, even Mariah Carey got ripped off, didn't
she?
And like you hear this stunned silence among
everybody.
It's like, but everybody forgot about it.
It's like Prince told you that the money.
Well, here's the thing.
Following the money and all that stuff doesn't
work anymore because of the straw man concept.
You put a front man up.
Right.
And by the way, I just went through
the whole application.
For example, Chuck, if you went out right
now and applied real estate to and applied
to buy five, 10 million dollar mansions for
50 million total.
Right.
And you're going to get denied for all
of them.
You know, you just created 50 million for
the for the financial companies.
That's the thing that I have a hard
time wrapping my mind around, because I know
most people do.
Yeah, I mean, I'm being honest with you.
I've listened to you talk about this and
I go, how did the point is, I
don't know how to access it.
See, I can imagine how that works.
But no, no, no.
You don't understand.
You're going to say you got a homeless
person that has access.
Let me put it in perspective.
Yeah, there's a homeless person.
I haven't talked about some interesting for the
mob.
They needed a front man when the popular
cordless tools were green before they went red
and before they went yellow.
Well, right.
Because when you when you were in the
black market, when you have a truck load
of cordless tools, that's where the yellow ones,
you know, that's the D wall, whatever is
in vogue.
This is in the day when the green
ones were invoked, the Makita.
So I needed a front guy.
And I and they were like, you know,
this is real.
He's got a chiseled chin.
He's a homeless guy.
Hangs up from the bodega on Vanderbilt Park.
And I'll go talk to him.
And all he did, this guy needed was
like a couple of good meals, a shower
and a shave.
And you put him in a suit.
You could go sit down and, you know,
whatever.
Right.
Like a Gary, a Cary Grant or whatever
kind of face, literally looked a lot like
them.
Right.
So I talked to him and he says,
you know, I used to be one of
the best pilots for American Airlines.
He pulled out his wallet.
He has photographs.
He had his he had his American Airlines
pilot license, everything in there, you know, legit.
This is my house in Nevada, you know,
with a kidney shaped pool.
This is my wife and children, you know.
And I'm like, holy crap.
Right.
So when I say homeless people, I know
when someone tells me they met a homeless
person, my accounts are very different because I've
always run into homeless people that had one
hell of a back story.
Right.
But let's say right now you run into
a homeless person that's just down and out,
never had any money, but they have access
to their social security number.
They can go to any clean them up,
stick them in a real estate office.
And the moment they apply for a 10
million dollar house and get denied, the financial
company that got the application has conditions is
by filling out this application.
You give us a right to sell this
information.
Right.
And use it any way we want to
benefit us.
That's some of the common verbs that you
see in there.
They take that application.
It doesn't matter if you're has nothing.
See, they got everyone brainwashed that what's your
income to credit ratio, that your income is
irrelevant.
They take the application and they get 10
million.
It backs up the finances of the financial
company.
That's why when you look at this goes
on the pro form, does not go on
pro forma accounting, which means forward accounting.
This stays in their assets.
Like, let me give you another example on
how to how to think about this.
Right.
When you say you have a hard time
with it.
And I'll just say this publicly, it's because
you don't think about finance, financial stuff or
the financial world often.
Just like, for example, if I start getting
into right now automotive, what's the timing on
this particular engine?
And should we really do it at Top
Dead Center or should we not?
You'd be like, I really don't get that.
Right.
Because you don't do mechanics talk.
Or many subjects.
So the financial stuff is a subject that
is not popular to discuss.
But once you understand the financial subject and
you see what's going on, it's way beyond
any horror movie or what would you call
it?
Sci-fi movie.
It's way beyond sci-fi, way beyond it,
because it's not discussed.
It's actually frowned upon to discuss.
There's an old thing I'm trying to old
saying that, you know, when you're around wealthy
people, never talk about money.
Right.
I think you understand that they never talk
about money.
Only poor people do.
Right.
So, yeah.
So but the workings of the financial is
very different because I'll tell you what, I
have never met a billionaire and I've met
quite a few that know how this works.
Not not a one of them.
So and that's why, for example, when you
go on television and I'm just giving a
broad thing on what's going on that you're
not going to hear anywhere else.
When you go on television, they got these
little short and long documentaries on these very
wealthy people and they give they tell you
a story on how they got there.
Bullshit.
They're all bullshit stories.
They don't even.
Why?
Because they're making up a bullshit story.
No, they don't even know how they got
there.
They don't know.
They have some kind of foggy idea that
I was working hard trying to sell books.
You know, I'm going right with that one.
I'm working hard.
And then we said, yeah, or whatever.
Or we were working on software.
And then suddenly the story falls apart because
it's like there's no way.
How did you get from here that no
one knows?
It's like they're living their life in the
fog and so is everyone else.
Right now, the thing is, when you start
clearing the fog so you can still see
through a fog, the visibility is limited.
But when you clear through the fog, you
are able to see great distances and see
more detail.
And that's what that's where rated Y comes
in, basically, because right now I could tell
all the subscribers here, you, me, everybody you've
ever met is living in a fog.
There's ancient talks, you know, we're living in
illusion.
We see through a dark glass.
So to say it's totally fair to say
to everyone that you're all living in a
fog.
So but the key point here is what
is a fog?
It's a cover.
It's something that obscures.
How do we mitigate that?
How do we get around that?
How do we fix that?
Right.
There's many ways to do it, but no
one seems to do it.
Right.
So again, with the financial stuff, it's very
hard for you to believe.
First of all, I'll tell you why it's
First of all, you haven't looked into it.
And even when I looked into it 25
years ago, I was like, this is crazy.
This is worse than any horror movie or
sci fi.
And I've been I've on the record on
conference calls since the early 2000s and on
Revolution Radio and American Freedom Radio back back
in that time.
You know, your application is where all the
money comes from.
First one, by the way, saying this publicly
over and over and over.
And it was like, oh, right.
So where I want to go with the
financial stuff.
First of all, it's hard for you to
get it, because when you look into it,
even if it's written in stone and you
have someone from the Federal Reserve explain it
to you three different ways, you're still not
going to get it because it has to
sink in.
The second thing is it's hard for anyone
to get it is because who are you
going to go tell?
Who are you going to talk to people
around you?
They're going to think you're crazy because I
filled out many applications.
I got filled out applications for the worst
one.
You know how I've talked about if you
haven't dropped out of school by the eighth
grade, you're a sucker, really.
You really are.
I mean, let's say you skated through high
school.
You better have been cussing out being there
and damning that you were there.
But if you believed anything past really the
sixth grade or the eighth grade, you're an
idiot.
And they know that.
And what they do is they make you
go to secondary school, college.
And what a fucked up mess that is,
because you go to college.
What do you do?
You apply to go to the college.
The college sends that application.
It has the same verbiage that I told
you.
They're going to use it and they send
it over, even though it's against the law,
because the 1974 Privacy Act says anything has
to do with education.
They're not allowed to share.
Right.
So you go to Harvard.
It's that was at 50 grand a semester
now or something like that.
Seventy five.
I think it's more like a year or
so.
Yeah, we're good.
Yeah.
All right.
So it's a hundred.
Right.
So let's say they ask you on the
application specifically, how long do you want to
attend for?
Two years, four years.
Masters.
Why?
Because attending here, you're a sucker anyway.
But why?
Because they want to know how much to
ask the Federal Reserve for.
So if you go apply for Harvard, they're
going to go four hundred thousand dollars, pull
that out of the Federal Reserve.
And then when they got it, they're going
to say, how are you going to pay
for education?
Going to get a loan?
They've already gotten paid.
Everyone who's ever gone to college used to
go back and subpoena and do a forensic
audit on their application.
And they will see the full amount plus
interest was pulled.
So you are a sucker if you did
that.
Now, you didn't know.
It doesn't matter.
Right.
It doesn't matter if you knew or not.
It's just like it didn't matter if if
if they peed in the punch bowl.
Right.
Did you drink it?
Is the is the issue?
No, I don't want to know.
Right.
I don't want to know that someone peed
in the punch bowl.
But what are those creatures called attorneys always
say?
Right.
Ignorance of the law is not an excuse.
Is that what they say?
Well, and they're the most.
Yeah.
And they are the most ignorant of all.
Of course, I'm still haven't met any attorneys
that know any law at all.
Right.
Even Supreme.
I recently posted in the chat that Senator
Kennedy was grilling Supreme Court justice candidates and
none of them knew any law.
And whatever they thought they knew was really,
really almost irrelevant to the question.
He really like Jonah Bases put put as
the senator put his foot up their asses,
you know, deservingly so.
And I posted in the chat.
See, they don't know any law because I've
I've been in graced or disgraced being in
the company of a Supreme Court judge twice,
not once, but twice.
Right.
At lunch.
And to prove it, to prove it, I
invited people.
I said, I asked him, is it all
right if I bring some friends over?
Sure.
Bring them over.
Because he was 93 years old and I
invited deliberately everybody I knew just to witness.
If I say I had lunch with a
Supreme Court judge that not once, but twice.
Can't catch your breath there.
Excuse me.
Yeah.
All right.
I'm fine.
Choking on a piece of tobacco.
OK.
Witnesses.
So take a second to take a drink.
Let's say this.
You know, the closest thing I ever came
to that is I interviewed Henry Reid, you
know, from the Roe v.
Wade decision.
So I've only ever been in the presence
of somebody argued in front of the Supreme
Court, not a Supreme Court justice.
But you've been in front of quite an
interesting group of people.
But what I'm saying is that even that
sounds crazy, too, because people that are around
those types of people say, oh, how wonderful
they are.
And I'm telling you, this guy didn't know
any law at all.
One of the people asked him, what about
jurisdiction?
He said, well, if you're in my courtroom,
I have jurisdiction.
And a bunch of questions about law.
And he says, I don't go about the
law, about the law.
I make decisions.
This is purely.
All right.
So what I'm saying, the financial people are
going to be doing the same stuff to
you.
Like, what do you think this application is
worth?
Anything are you talking?
You still have to pay for it.
You want it for free.
You know, all these distractions.
Right.
The only thing I can say about Henry
Reid is that he was able to recount
exactly.
And he did this because I saw a
recording of somebody else asking him the same
question word for word, exactly the same rehearsed
response is what he gave to somebody else
like a year later, because apparently that's what
he was good at.
And that's just a district attorney, by the
way.
Yeah, they specialize.
They specialize.
Yes.
That's why they ask you get an accident
lawyer, get this kind of trial lawyer, get
this whatever.
But overall, you know what the crux of
the law is in America is that there
will be the government or legislature will make
no law that will interfere with the agreements
and contracts.
That's why it's always you agree, you agree,
you agree.
And they get stuck on that.
You know, the Ninth Amendment is the best
amendment because it says they can't infringe on
any right that you already have as long
as it doesn't hurt anyone.
Right.
The Ninth Amendment is the amendment, by the
way.
Forget about the other ones.
The ninth means you have all the other
ones plus ones that you haven't even figured
out yet.
Right.
In other words, the Ninth Amendment allows you
to extend, let's say, cell phone use.
Right.
There were no cell phones back then.
It allows you to apply the Ninth Amendment
to the use of a cell phone in
certain situations where you would be banned to
now, let's say.
Right.
I'm not saying be belligerent.
But you need to be at this point.
Another thing that I'm mentioning is that the
police are completely.
Let me just say it this way.
You know, people.
Oh, I was arrested by the police.
So the police came to my house.
I thought, you know, the police is not
a noun.
It's a verb.
Yeah.
Do you know that?
Well, it's not a noun.
And now we've turned it into a noun.
The way I understood policing, by the way,
was to clean up an area of refuse
is to police an area.
That's one of the police.
Yeah.
The history of the police has two two
deep histories.
New York, Massachusetts, New Jersey is Jersey again
in the mix.
Why do they have to throw Jersey in
the mix every time in the old history?
Right.
But it's in there.
And so anyway, a lot of immigrants.
I think a lot of immigrants landed there
because they looked at the city.
They said too many people.
So they just drifted away from the city
and said, OK, there's less.
This is better.
It is.
But, you know, it's in New York.
When you're on the West Side, you see
the Palisades, right?
That's Jersey.
True.
Right.
So anyway, they were looking for what they
already had a police force set up private.
By the way, slave trade has always been
illegal.
I think I mentioned that.
Right.
But for runaway slaves that were in North,
that's what they're originally for.
They were like these gangs, like just like
bail bondsmen.
You know, a bail bondsman can break into
your apartment, wait for you to come home,
hit you with a stun gun, put cuffs
on you and bring you to jail.
Right.
If you try to skip bail.
Or whatever.
So, yeah.
So got that from Jackie Brown, by the
way.
By the way, that's what they were around
for.
And they were loose, loose knit groups.
Very similar to what was that group before
the FBI?
The pill was a pill kit.
What were they called?
A tip security.
Pinkerton.
Yeah.
Very much like that.
Yes.
Pinkerton.
Thank you.
So when the banks are becoming popular and
lending money to the states and the cities
and they started owning everything in the city,
they were like, if there's a riot, this
is our property now because you agreed to
it.
We need to protect it.
So they gave money to these slave hunters
like Pinkerton types and local police that were
there to really go after melanated people, really.
And they still are today, by the way.
And and they funded them by the banks.
So it's a completely illegal operation all the
way through and through.
It's kind of like saying like churches are
pagan, right?
People don't understand that.
Right.
But when the more you look into it,
the more you see how true it is.
But my point here is it's really shocking
to bring to bring out what's going on
to the lady, the common people, because they'll
see it as being uncommon.
Right.
Knowledge.
And they can't handle it.
That's why I've always said in Sonics, always
forget about the masses.
They're done.
They were they were born to be done.
They're filler.
It's kind of like when you go to
the pet shop and they got the feeder
fish and the feeder mice on one end.
Right.
That you're supposed to buy those little animals
to feed to the other animals.
Right.
They're not pets.
You know what I mean?
This is what the masses are.
And it's it's gotten to that point.
But anyway, I just want to express these
these things, because these two things, the legal
aspect of how things are run is all
by agreement, not by a contract, basically not
by law.
They could use the word law as much
as they want.
And when they say law enforcement, they mean
they were telling you that because you agreed
to it, the law says that nothing can
get in between the agreement.
Right.
So but things are going to get weird
with the financial stuff.
They're not going to be repeating crashes, by
the way.
You know how they had the crash of
twenty nine, the one in eighty seven and
then the 2008.
Notice how different they all are.
Right.
You know, when people start making comparisons to
the crash of the Wall Street, which was
not actually in the twenty nine and they
don't make comparisons to eighty seven and 2008.
So the next financial pinch is what's what
it's going to do.
It's going to break this bubble that exists
and there's going to be a redistribution and
a devaluation of whatever.
Do you remember when we were speaking after
Covid?
I said, if you're not doubling what you're
taking in, let's say you rely on what's
called income.
You better double it as fast as possible
to be where you were before that.
And it's not going to go back.
In other words, certain prices are going down.
But the the getting the idea of things
are more expensive.
And I went through that in between the
70s and the 80s.
Remember, there was a time in the late
70s when everything got expensive.
Right.
Yeah.
Let's say that way.
That was stagflation.
And I'll tell you something.
That's one of the most relevant things you
ever said, quite honestly, is if you don't
have double very soon, you're done and you're
right, because that's exactly where we find ourselves
today with the prices of everything backed up.
And, you know, quite honestly, if you're trying
to exchange, you know what they call currency
to, you know, take care of the things
you need, your actual needs.
Yeah.
Double double is right.
And real quick, I wonder if we're looking
at a financial crash, by the way, in
twenty twenty nine, like we saw in nineteen.
But yeah, you can't crash.
OK, it already crashed.
It already crashed.
So what you're looking at is credit.
It's so you can't crash credit.
All you could do, like Greenspan said this,
what you could do is restrict its flow.
But when you restrict the flow of credit,
just like the black market, you know, if
you want to increase the black market, you
make regulation.
You want to kill the black market deregulate.
Right.
So when they when they the way they're
going to decrease the flow of credit is
by denying people access to credit, but keeping
the application and they themselves are going to
get the front end loaded, all this tons
and tons of credit, but they're not going
to give it to the people.
And the reason they're going to do that,
you're ready, is because when it's not distributed,
you don't have inflation.
So you're going to see financial companies becoming
if you think they have a lot.
Now you're going to watch, let's say, banks
or financial institutions or balance sheet for the
next few years is going to double and
triple.
So let's say this company is worth 500
billion.
By next year, it'll be 800 billion and
then a trillion and a half as the
credit is being restricted to the people.
And what that's going to do, it's going
to because there's less credit, the prices are
not going to go up as much and
they're going to have access to a lot
more.
So they're going to be able to be
very, very extravagant.
This is how you hear that people get
wealthy during hard times.
This is how they do it now with
the credit.
Right.
So one thing to do, I suggest to
people is when you do applications, you have
three days to send them a letter that
you're retaining security interest and you want to
have a meeting of the minds on it.
Number one.
Right.
Number two, you give them an outline on
how you want to divide the application.
Doesn't matter if you denied me.
There's no look.
What's the basis of denial credit report?
You know, credit reporting agencies were started by
a bunch of mom and pop.
I think one of them was a mop
company, MLP, that we close with.
Yes.
Yeah.
And what they noticed, what they noticed is
back in the days, they're all people.
This is a while back.
They started.
But in the 60s, civil rights movements, when
they bought the credit agency agencies and said,
I got to keep these niggas from getting
access to credit.
You know, that's how they that's how they
think.
Big middle aged white guys.
So what they did was they studied the
history.
And years ago, when there was silver and
gold back money before the bank lent you
money, they actually sent a foot soldier, a
bank person, like a scout to go out
into the neighborhood and ask the neighbors about
your character.
Do you remember hearing about that?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Back in the day, we're talking about back
in the day.
Now, they used to have a clipboard.
He's from the bank.
Don't talk to him.
Right.
You know, and the stuff like that.
So now what they did is, well, now
with the credit, everybody's going to get access
to credit.
This is crazy.
So let's create these credit agencies.
And yeah, one of them was a mop
company.
The other one was just mom and pop.
And they're and they and the financial institutions
give you that as an excuse.
I said, that's fine.
You can deny me all you want.
My my I'll return the denial back to
you.
I'll sign that monetize that.
And the other thing is, let's just talk
about the collateral that you're holding.
Unjust enrichment is the case.
So I'm kind of like overtaking the sonic
this time talking about.
It's not about money.
It's about knowing how things work, which can
easily lead into the body, the human body.
Let me just mention another thing.
I've been looking up some people recently that
I went to high school with.
Right.
Put someone's name in.
And they most likely have a social media
page, believe it or not.
Right.
Yeah, true.
And you look at it and then and
then and then you see a fucking obituary
for them, you know, heart disease.
Are you ready for this one?
Diabetes.
Right.
I'm like, oh, my gosh, I went to
sixth grade with this guy.
And he's dead because he trusted the medical
establishments.
And just like the financial people, I assure
you, you go to any bank or whatever
manager you talk to, they don't know any
of this.
When you go talk to those medical idiots
that your company tells you to go to
or whatever, they don't know what's going on.
They don't know there's no such thing as
all these diseases.
And the treatment is actually the part of
the mass poisoning.
Right.
They don't know.
But if you go, I can tell you
who does know each hospital, you have the
administrative staff.
Right.
And the administrative staff, based on the size
of the hospital, has, you know, how many
people there's always at least one or two
people in the administrative part of the hospital.
I know exactly what I'm talking about, how
the treatment, how they're killing people there.
And that actually expanded during the covid time.
A lot of the nurses and people that
were working in hospitals when they were killing
people in the hospitals with all these ventilators
and drugs and sedations and all that there
were to prevent a nurse rebellion or what
you call a mutiny.
The administrative people came out and started breaking
the news to all of the nurses saying,
hey, if you like your job here and
you want to make a lot of money,
just do what we say.
And guess what?
A lot of them did.
A lot of nurses quit also, by the
way.
But but the majority, let's say 51 percent
stayed, which is very dangerous.
You know, when you think about 51 percent
of the staff that works with people in
the hospital are willing to kill you for
an increase on their paycheck.
Wow.
You are living in one hell of a
society, I should tell you.