Sonic Event 12, Ocelli in the Greek, and welcome to it.
Anyway, glad to have you along, and Greek, how are you this, well, let's see, it is the
evening, it is, it is dark outside, yeah, 29th of the first month, 29th of the first
month, right, now that's not what the Pope's work schedule says, but, no, they do line up,
that's, I mean, you can't get away from the moon, or the, you know, the moon function,
which is the month a lot of people think it's a lunar calendar, it's not, it's not a sun
calendar, it's a, it's, you use, it's kind of like, you know, with the clock, you know,
you have the long arm and the short arm, right, and the long arm moves more than the short
arm on the clock, right, so the short arm, let's say, would be the moon, and the long
arm would be the sun, so it's a combination of workings, but I would suggest it's, we're
going into the second month in a few days, today would be what you consider a Sabbath,
let's say, the seventh day of the week, which is on the 8th, 15th, 22nd, 29th, so that's
just a recap of a recap of a recap.
Right, and, of course, if you've listened to previous Sonics, actually gave a really
great piece of advice about where to mark a day, after all the day, when does it begin
at solar noon, and that is more sensible, I gotta thank you, actually, for that little
adjustment in my mind, it is, it's been very helpful, it's, I don't know how to explain
even how it's been helpful, but it's been more helpful, I've been better off with that
in my mind.
If someone complains about sleeping until noon, you say, I slept until the day started,
right?
Well, there's that.
It's a good thing for the ghetto, you know?
I understand that.
But I'm not trying to get anybody's approval, I'm just saying that in general, I felt less
resistance in my day handling it that way, beginning my day, or my work, or whatever,
at solar noon makes more sense to me.
Right, and it's for this world, when the world changes, it'll be different again.
Well, look, if you're in a different place, what did they used to say, when in Rome, right?
Do as the Romans do.
Well, this world will change, also.
We won't have day and night, as we do now, in the future.
That's another discussion, and I can't give it as surely as I give other Greeks speak,
but we could presume, based on what we've been told about it.
Speaking of which, what we've been told about, we were probably talking about hashing over
a few things, and where should we start?
Maybe the thing that got you going just a minute ago was the difference between the
state and the government.
Well, yes, and the reason is that, I've heard you mention this, and certainly it makes sense
to me, but I have no idea how to explain it, and I don't have a reference for precisely,
you know what I'm saying?
Easy.
Okay, a government is the function, a centralized place, usually for people to meet and greet
or distribute things, right?
Like, if everyone needs a road, instead of giving it to someone here, all the money to,
or whatever, to build the road, you form a council or a place where the money goes there,
and it's public, and everyone knows what's going on, and then when it's time to build
the road, someone from there, meaning the government, or the public, has everything
above board.
That's basically how it works, however it's set up, and a government can be also a monarchy.
It could be with council.
Usually all governments are pretty similar, it's just that they decapitated, like in the
middle 18th century, 1700s, they began removing monarchies, because the monarchy represented
like the divine family, right?
I always felt a discomfort with that, because what was it?
You're anointed leader, and here we go, right?
So, these people claim to have been anointed, now that only means to have oil placed on
your head, as far as I could reason, but it implies that you are, what, touched by God,
right?
Well, yeah, and it's more than that.
It's a lineage thing, unless it's established, and then there's a lineage from that, but
one thing I would suggest is the entire universe runs on an imperial rule, where you have ...
Hierarchy?
Yeah, let's say you have a king, and you have other people below the king, if they're so
spread apart, because of their distance, they could also be called kings, but they're really
not, because they answer to a central figure themselves, right?
So this is the imperial overall overarching, you see it in Star Wars, you see it in other
places like that.
The model of the imperial model is the most respected and top individual, it doesn't necessarily
have to be anointing, as we see in, let's say, older religious texts, or things like
that, it's just a domination, it could be the first one, meaning the universe, and on
and on, right?
A creator being appointed by agency, let's say.
So in essence, the decapitation ...
Wait a second, because appointed by agency, let me dig into that a sec, because I think
of it in some cases where fiefdoms are sort of established, right?
And you have somebody who, by force, or ... let me think here ... like Alexander the Great,
for instance, right?
He would conquer places, and you had to change names, and you had to change certain things,
but he didn't change all their customs, and yet he would be considered the overall ruler,
but in some cases he would leave, say, the previous rulers in place, but they were subjugated
under him.
What about that?
They did not, let's say, advertise the subjugation as much as their handing over authority.
And they were still the kings as such, but he just was above them.
Not always.
In other words, the way we brought up Alexander, what's interesting, it's not like the Americans
are doing now, going all over the world as a police enforcer for the UN and the monetary
central bankers.
Well, and then they just leave behind an outpost and then comes in the banks.
Yeah, they came in and they offered culture first, and if you took the culture, you're
okay.
And then if you didn't take the culture, they offered you military help, ha, ha, ha.
Get it?
Military help was taking out your military.
So it was indirect.
The history that we're getting is not very good.
Most of the famous battles that you hear were when you had these clashes, let's say, between
the Persians and the Greeks, and the various movements back and forth.
Those are like, that's not how things start.
There's a lot of, how would you say, ambassadorship and dealings and negotiations, and when they
fail, they would fight.
But also the fight was considered a rite of passage.
Like sometimes they would have their heroes go and fight, right?
Instead of the entire army.
Well, yeah, like, look, what do you call it, Achilles, right, famously would be offered
up as the hero, and then they would put him up against their best soldier.
And the battle could be decided that way, in an honorable way, and that was that, right?
Right, and that was based on culture, again, not necessarily just pure might.
So pure might never works, because eventually it's shown for what it is, and people just
eventually will not comply with it.
Well, it's also difficult to maintain a stranglehold.
I mean, look, even if you attempt to maintain a stranglehold, but you don't want to kill
the thing you're strangling, kind of hard to do, right?
I mean, just practically.
Well, we could discuss the history, we weren't there, we can only surmise what we're being
told about it, it's not true, but if we go and study how the cultures mingled and evolved
after the conquests, we see it's a very different way than we imagined it happening.
But one thing, let's just fast forward to the modern era, because making it more tangible
is probably simpler and easier.
I want to give the example of what happened in Switzerland around 2002.
Well, what happened in Switzerland around 2002?
You'll see on September 10th, 2002, Switzerland finally joined the UN.
Why did they wait so long?
The reason why is because the status of the government in Switzerland is the government
in Switzerland considered the people, their citizenry, that's where the citizen with a
capital C, let's say, not a US citizen, it was the only country in the world that held
this, they considered that each citizen was free on their own and a sovereign on their
own, and whether they had seven or eight or 20 million people living in Switzerland, I
don't think it's that high, the government considered them to be a free people, each
individual one, so they could not directly go and join the UN, because each person that
lived in Switzerland had to get their own ambassador, so you couldn't send eight million
or 10 million or 20 million ambassadors to the UN, it didn't work that way.
Well, that's impossible if you've only got eight million people, I mean, what, unless
everyone is going to serve as their own ambassador, which is not...
And they could not, the government said we cannot represent our people because each citizen
is free.
So what happened after 9-11, they really came down on Switzerland and said, listen, you
need to change the status of your people, so they become, you're the suzerain and they're
subjects or, you know, in other words, change the definition of citizen so they become property,
so then you could just represent one representative, just like, you know, General Motors can send
one representative to represent their cars, because the cars are not people, they're property,
right?
Right.
So, yeah, so whenever you see someone joining a worldwide organization, meaning a country
or a government, that means that their people are now considered property, because if they
weren't property, you couldn't properly represent them.
So what they tried also was a series of elections, if, mock elections, like if we were to make
an ambassador for Switzerland, everything that he would say in the UN had to be voted
on by the population.
That's really impractical.
So if Switzerland got an ambassador to go to the UN and he had, let's say, two paragraphs
with five points on it, everyone in Switzerland had to publicly vote on what he should say.
So it became impractical again, right?
So they couldn't work it.
So the ultimate thing was, after 9-11, they sent people in there, because 9-11 was a worldwide
thing just like the pandemic was, and they went in there and they said, look, just change
the paperwork so that people agree to becoming property, right?
Just when I mean property, I mean like property, you know, just like inanimate objects, slaves
is another way to call it, a breathing, you know, property.
And they did that.
It was very, I've been researching that.
It's very interesting to see how they did that.
They did it through subscription and pledging.
And they sent out postcards and things that you signed and sent back.
And if you didn't send it, if you sent, here's the thing.
I want to give the, show you how the legal system works.
Okay.
What I mean by pledging.
When you're pledging, it means you're in a situation where you can't win.
That's not the direct academic definition, but pledging is really, if you have to pledge,
you end up in a situation where you're always going to lose, and this is how it works with
the legal system.
Okay.
I'll give an example, and I'll go back to Switzerland with the cards that they sent
to people.
All right.
The Titanic, which was really the Olympic, which sunk for insurance purposes, right?
Okay.
All the people on board that died.
By the way, I just want to put this out there, and I can't give any more details, so I'll
give what I know about it.
Crashing into an iceberg does not sink a ship.
You could look at modern day icebreakers going through ice, and they go through at like 20
knots, and they're not, I mean, yeah, they're reinforced and all that, but they break the
ice.
Okay.
What I mean by that is if you were to go up to an iceberg right now with a big bend, a
saw that's 10 feet, a blade that's 10 feet long, and you cut a chunk of the iceberg out
that was two feet by two feet by two feet, right?
Pretty big chunk, right?
If I pick it up, Chuck, let's say I do it, and you're there, I'll pick up that two foot
by two foot piece of ice and smash you over the head with it.
You're going to laugh.
You're going to say, I don't even feel anything because it's lighter than snow.
It's not like what we're used to living back east where things freeze up, and it's really
hard.
Your wheels could get stuck in it, and it takes a chisel to break.
No, nothing like that.
The icebergs are not made of ... Anyway, just like the World Trade Center wasn't brought
down with jet fuel, right?
Okay.
Anyway, this is the Titanic.
Cunard, which was White Star Lines, the attorneys said, wow, we've got 1,500 people.
By the way, when you see 5-1 or 1-5, that's an Illuminati, Freemason number signaling.
That's why when you read the newspaper, it's like Area 51.
When you look at the popular news, especially around Hollywood, this guy has a $15 million
fine, or this one is 51 million, or it's 5.1 million.
People look for the 33, but also look for the 5-1.
1,500 people supposedly perished on the Titanic.
The legal department went into full steam to release the company of liability of being
sued, because it was clearly a mechanical failure, what they tell everyone.
If there's a mechanical failure, you're in a hotel and the ceiling collapses, you can
sue the hotel, right?
People didn't commit suicide, so they could sue the ... Okay, so this is how they got out
of it legally.
What they did, and this is what pledging is, pledging essentially is where you are counted
as a debtor, and a debtor has no rights, by the way.
This is how they established everyone that was aboard that ship to be a debtor.
The attorneys quickly got together these little postcards, and they sent whoever they could
through address, through the mail, a one-cent laundry bill to everyone that was on the ship.
Now, here's the deal.
Whoever paid the one-cent admitted that they were a debtor, and if you didn't pay the one-cent,
you acquiesced to being a debtor, to admitting a debtor, so basically the legal department,
when they tried to sue the White Star Line, they said, they have no legal standing.
Okay, okay, so let me just make sure I understood what you just said, okay, because it almost
sounds ridiculous.
It is, but that's how the ... Welcome to the legal system.
I got you, but I just want to be real clear here.
So all right, if I send you a bill for, let's just use the dollar.
Everybody says, oh, one dollar, right?
You know, oh, the guy was able to buy a house for a dollar.
He was like, okay, we'll use the dollar.
So I send you a bill for a dollar.
What I'm doing now is trapping you in a situation here, because if you received it, if I can
prove that you received it, right, you don't pay.
If the proof is brought up, but in this case, it's not.
If you paid the one cent laundry bill, all they do, it didn't matter, because it just
showed that you're a debtor, because if you weren't a debtor, they wouldn't have sent
Why would you pay the bill?
Well, why would you pay the bill if you didn't know it?
So obviously, you owed a debt, boom, okay.
But on the other hand ...
Because it was based on a pledge, not based on a true bill.
These were not true bills, so now we're going to get into some crazy legal stuff.
Well, just hang on before we get out of that, because like I said, if you paid it, then
you obviously admit that you owed it, because you had to satisfy it, therefore it was a
debt.
I get that part.
But if you can't show that I received that bill, turn it around, you sent me the bill,
how do you know I got that bill?
Well, if it doesn't come back, then just like if you don't show up for a court date,
they find you in default, right?
For example ...
So I'm in default, even if I don't know I got this thing, because they issued it.
I mean, that's what it comes down to?
Yeah, pretty much.
That's what pledging is about, right.
Okay, well, that sounds to me like you have no ...
If you deal with the legal rascals, they don't go by law, and it's pretty clear.
They don't have to say it, but they say it a thousand different ways without saying
we don't use the law, right?
Actually, they do sometimes.
I've seen a federal case where someone was bringing up laws, and the judge says, stop,
you're using law.
You cannot use law in this courtroom, but it never becomes public.
I've actually seen a statement by the Supreme Court that effectively said that it doesn't
matter that scientifically or whatever that ... The whole thing about declaring a tomato
a vegetable, right?
Oh, no, no, no.
I mean, this has nothing to do with the subject matter.
Oh, no, no.
The operation.
Yeah, no, no.
I'm pointing out the way the operation works here is that they put this thing through,
and they basically admit it doesn't matter what the thing actually is.
We have issued a precedent.
That precedent says this, therefore, that's it.
Well, the thing is, the Supreme Court is a hoax, by the way, how the people have it
in their mind, because it's just an appellate court.
They cannot make a decision.
That's why they don't say Supreme Court ... They say rulings, and it always has to get kicked
back to the district court that it appealed from.
It's a completely flawed process.
It's incomplete, but that's how people accept it.
Well, I was just trying to approach it in this way, because you're setting a precedent
by doing this with the bill, right?
The laundry bill.
You're setting some kind of precedent here.
It's just that I don't understand how, if somebody's not informed about being a debtor,
and it's not a true debt ...
It doesn't matter.
It's whoever has the more competent records, and in this case, the people that are being,
let's say, a claim is lodged against, they have to prove that the claim can't hold.
The way you do that is by having a more competent record.
Usually in court, when it comes to financial stuff, the more competent record holds, but
I just wanted to throw this about legal precedents, by the way.
They don't go by law.
In 1938, they said that case law will do, so you see the attorneys, they always list
these cases, right?
They say that this guy lost, right?
Well, the thing is, if you study a lot of these cases that they cite, the guy lost because
he had a flat tire, and he couldn't make it to court on time.
Oh, no.
It doesn't matter why he lost.
It's just a matter of if he lost, and they just make the, look, this case is like this
case, therefore, done.
That's pretty much what they do, right?
The system of pledging was also brought forward to Woodrow Wilson, who actually, most of his
administration was run by his wife, the biggest mass murderer in world history, by the way,
and then FDR, by the way.
Of course, you know what?
Because of the American army flu, they call it the Spanish flu, he's the one that approved
it.
I think Stalin's a close third in modern history, but yeah, go ahead.
Yeah, close third, because Woodrow Wilson would be over 100 million, and Stalin would
probably be in 50, 60 million.
I think more recent records would prove out that he's at about 70 or 80, but go ahead.
Yeah.
Anyway, so this thing, what they did with Switzerland is they finally got enough people
approved that you could call Switzerland now a piece of property that could enter the United
Nations Club.
Okay, so how do you change?
I'm sorry.
It's very hard, so I've got to ask these questions, and I'm hoping that it'll help somebody else
hearing this, because it might fly right by somebody.
How do you take a state of ... Forget the word state, excuse me.
How do you take a circumstance where you have people that are recognizable as their own
free sovereigns?
Because you hear this word sovereign a lot.
Well, they hear sovereign citizen, which is an oxymoron.
Oh, no, not just sovereign citizen.
You hear sovereign, sovereignty, the discussion of you can be a sovereign.
There's a whole community of people out there that have these discussions constantly, and
it's not just the American sovereign citizen movement.
I'm telling you, worldwide, people discuss this, okay, about sovereignty and being a
citizen of the planet, and things like all these different machinations about it.
But again, you had a circumstance here where in Switzerland, the individual living on that
land could be recognized, and it was the only place in the world where they could be recognized
as a sovereign.
They are-
Right, by their government.
Their own ruler according to their government, right?
Okay.
So, in that case, how do you transform that into ... I mean, is the answer as simple
as it was pledged?
Mm-hmm.
I mean, okay.
You didn't know what you were signing up for.
But here's the thing-
Basically, they sent out a bunch of postcards.
Yeah.
No, I get that, but-
And whether you sent it back or not didn't matter.
Yeah, understand, I'm not trying to fight with you.
I'm trying to understand this, because again, I'm still stuck on this laundry bill.
But here's the thing before I send it.
I haven't found the direct way that they did it, you see, because I wasn't there.
All the research that I've been doing, what was going on between September 11th, 2001
and September 10th, 2002, all I saw was certain activity as such.
People were getting extraordinary things in the mail.
That seems really minimal, but they were not.
To me, they were extraordinary.
This strikes me as extraordinarily important.
This is why I'm asking so many questions, okay?
Because this process, if this is the case, this sounds to me like you could do anything
to anybody-
Of course.
... with this kind of methodology.
And I mean, it doesn't matter.
I mean, moral parameters are irrelevant here.
Here's the worst part.
Before this happened, before Switzerland joined the UN, most other citizens of other countries
didn't know how important it was to be part of Switzerland or one of the people of Switzerland.
They thought the people of Switzerland, meaning the whole world, was in a similar status as
them.
Like, oh, why aren't they in the UN?
What's wrong?
They didn't comprehend.
So doing this to the Swiss was quite easy.
They didn't complain, by the way.
Yeah.
Well, general consensus with Switzerland previous to this is very simple.
Look, they're landlocked.
They're in a circumstance where they're constantly surrounded by people that are in conflict.
So what they've had to do is become amicable to everybody in a certain way.
So neutrality, right?
And basically not going to war.
That was the most clear, observable thing about them, right?
I mean, I'm talking about the pedestrian view of this.
Sure.
But there's a very simple, practical answer to that.
The reason why Switzerland was kept out of everything as it was, because it's the most
ancient, known, still functioning access to the underworld, openly functioning.
You could access the underworld, the underground civilizations from anywhere if you know where
to access it from.
But Switzerland was revered as the most, let's say, open and it was kind of like a hub, kind
of like a Grand Central Station for going into the underworld.
And I'm not talking about the ethereal underworld where, we're talking about the underworld
that you can see with your eyes.
No, you're talking about a third dimensional, physical.
Yeah.
It's a city where the underground, the beings that have been living there before us, let's
just say.
That's why when you look at, there's a fellow that used to have a YouTube channel.
He would walk around.
He declared himself homeless, but he wasn't poor and he had all the camera equipment
enough to have a YouTube channel and he walked Switzerland and he'd go through the forest
and he'd see just in the middle of nowhere, no trails or anything, a beautiful, ornamental
iron gate and you'd see the U.S. Confederate flag on a building in there and it's been
flying for 300 years.
So where did the U.S. Confederates get their flag?
So all this stuff.
So, for example, the flag of Greece came directly from the VSO, the Dutch East India Company.
Most of these flags were put in place by the Dutch East India Company all over the world.
If you look at, for example, the way anyone looks up the Dutch East India Company, that
is a model of the modern state.
There's a graph, how wealthy was the Dutch East India Company and they have a graph in
today's money, let's say, valued or price and then they have next to it a graph of all
the largest corporations today and this is still bigger.
I think you have to add up like the top three or four largest corporations to get close
to where that was.
To make it commensurate with the size or wealth of that.
Sure, yeah.
So what they did is they would hire some pretty barbaric people to go in and deal with the
natives but usually they convinced them to transfer the paper money so then the Dutch
East India Company would pretty much give them ledgers and paper to get their goods,
whatever it was.
Right.
Pretty easy.
So ink was important to the Dutch East India Company, paper was important to them.
Pretty interesting course of events.
No one really talks about it but it's such a behemoth of an organization.
But in other words, the state here, so what happened was Switzerland went from a pretty
much a sovereign state, not a sovereign state, sorry, a sovereign people with a government
to a sovereign state.
A sovereign state, when you hear sovereign state like the UN is sovereign states, it's
kind of like the word federal reserve.
It's neither federal nor does it have reserves.
So sovereign means that they're a corporation and a state means they're part of a member
club.
Okay.
Like the UN is a members only club for sovereign states to bring their property.
So in essence, the government is what people use as a function, as a central authority
because it benefits them, right, to have that.
It's a neutral central authority and also you can put certain things on it to perform
certain duties like issue money and hold a military and defend borders and whatever,
right, form an army and a navy.
But what I'm suggesting here is since the Dutch East India Company and recently what
happened in Switzerland is that the UN, all it is, is a member for these states which
are not really states because they come in holding people as property.
So when people become property, you're a slave.
But that's a bad word to use, right?
So anyway, they kind of coached it that way.
So in essence, a government is a centralized authority that is there to benefit you and
a state is what flavor it takes on and usually the flavor that it takes on is what's been
tried and true throughout the world through recent times and borrowing from ancient history.
And the main way that it's being done since the early 20th century is through a system
of pledging.
There is a speech that was done to – it was a written speech.
I think it was Mendel House did it to Woodrow Wilson and he says that now we're going
to – this is right before the Federal Reserve Act or during the Federal Reserve Act passing
1913.
He says we're going to establish a system in America that the people will be required
to pledge their biological property to us otherwise they won't be able to work or
live here, right?
This is like I'm prefacing, okay?
So this is the type of state that you have.
So usually what happens is the system of the state, right, which you got a flavor of.
I think the people listening kind of understand enough of it, is over – has taken over
the government's functions and any lawful authority the government has.
So what they've done with modern states, which is the system of pledging where the
people are no longer – they're no longer people, they're property and they are represented,
right?
It's a representative form of government, indirect.
By the way, today when they speak of people, they're speaking of themselves, meaning
the administrators of the state, not you.
You have no rights in legal or law.
That's why when you go to a court, it's all case law.
They can't use law.
Then they do quote the law but it doesn't apply because if you look at the definitions,
it doesn't apply to you.
So it's a long story.
I'm not saying that the laws don't apply to you.
Go do what you want.
But I'm saying that the way that it's being run, no, they don't apply to you, right?
Just like if you go to a doctor and he puts a cuff on your arm and inflates it and looks
at a fancy dial and tells you you have whatever blood pressure, that doesn't apply to you.
That applies to him.
Well, even though it doesn't – okay.
So even though it doesn't exist, let me ask you a strange reversal question.
Theoretically, if there was a collective organization, right, that actually represented the will
of the people and that's what it did, would we still use the same terms to describe it
that we use today?
Sure.
Well, look, for example, the Federal Reserve is not federal and it has no reserves.
You could actually use that to let's say describe and somewhat explain the monetary
system of the US Treasury when it was substance-backed.
So if you went to a place where they held the gold to back up the money, you could say
that's our Federal Reserve.
But it's not the Federal Reserve, right?
Okay.
You see how the name becomes – we see this often where a name – well, like, you know
what an example would be?
Windows.
Okay.
Right?
Windows.
Is it an architectural term or a computer term?
Well, both.
Very different.
Same word.
Same word, right.
This is how it's based.
Religions, this was all perfected with religious schemes through the centuries, by the way.
Religious schemes through the centuries went from gods to God, right?
So God is not the gods, but we only have records and dealings with gods, never with God.
So which one is it?
Well, now you're confusing me, right?
Good.
If you're confused, you're doing great.
You see?
That's great.
Okay.
So in essence, this is something that has gotten to the point where the concept of an
egregore where most people – let's say a group of people get together and they have
a thought form, a meme, it actually materializes, right?
By induction, let's say.
This is what's going on right now.
So there's no way you're going to change this or break free from it.
The thing is you stay out of its way and don't get involved unless you want to because if
you want to get involved with their actions, you can prosper materially within their credit
systems and all that, right?
It's called working the system.
You hear that all the time, right?
Oh, yeah.
Right.
Yeah.
I mean, I've shown people who are millionaires years ago how to go get what they call food
stamps or EBT cards.
I said it has nothing to do with your income.
No one has any income until you write down that you do.
All of these government benefits they give to quote-unquote people that are of low income
or poor, let's say, has nothing to do with how much you make.
That's just like addressing.
It has to do with the birth certificate.
So I've showed people that were millionaires but they don't own a car dealership.
I said this is because they wanted to learn how the government system works.
So just go in there and just give them a certified copy of the birth certificate and
say you need this particular – don't even fill out the application.
Just hold the title up, whatever benefit you wanted.
You go into a social security office, they have all those benefit packages you sign up
for, right?
Right.
Just grab a bunch of them and put a diagonal line through the face on everything and staple
your birth certificate at the top, the one that you get, and say you want these benefits
applied to this document right here and you should give that to the clerk and they don't
know what you're talking about.
You're talking to someone too low on the totem pole.
Usually they tell you you have to wait until the person that knows what you're – comes
around.
When you finally see them, an administrator, you hand it to them and they'll look at you
and they look at the paper.
They look at you, look at the paper, look at you, look at the paper, okay.
I said I don't think it's going to happen.
One day I was telling them, I said, I don't think you're going to get those Arizona
teas you like drinking all the time and butter and whatever.
I saw him one day with an Arizona tea and I said, yeah, is that a new flavor?
He says, yeah, a new flavor and I got it from my EBT card.
By the way, you can't buy butter with an EBT.
This guy's a millionaire.
It has nothing to do with your income.
I mean millionaire in social standings, right?
I understand.
It has nothing to do – it's all a – you know how I said they put out – what did
I call it?
Markers or metrics.
You know, like in the world, if you use the word I believe in God or Jesus or have a
nice day or debt, those are metrics and the more people that use those words, that means
that those people don't know anything what's going on and you're safe, meaning you, meaning
the administrative side, right?
If you see people using language accurately, those are the dangerous ones, right?
Because you know, the pen is mightier than the sword.
So anyway, I just wanted to cover those things because the state and the government are completely
two different things.
Just like when you say you're Christian or Jewish or whatever, to me, if you – usually
when someone – I said, yeah, are you religious?
You believe part of any religion and when they say what they are, whether Christian or Jewish
for example, I ask them again, are you sure you're Jewish or Christian?
You know, you're part of that faith and I ask them again and if they say it two or
three times, yes, I am.
To me, I translate that in my Babelfish Universal Translator.
It says this person doesn't know a damn thing about the scriptures of the Bible at
all.
They have no comprehension, right?
Because there's no way you can have comprehension of what they call the Bible, even the piss
poor King James Version and call yourself a Christian or Jewish.
There's no way.
It's not possible.
So, it's a metric.
You know, they were fed that line, you know.
An example of that is there's a couple of people I've run into.
Some even have YouTube channels and some that I know that are experts in the Koran and know
it really well and are faithful.
But if you ask them what religion you are, you know what they say, no, I'm not part
of any religion.
You say, come on, you're Muslim.
No, I'm not Muslim.
You get it?
Okay.
So, if someone says, I'm a Muslim, it means you know nothing, you have no comprehension
of the Koran.
Do you see how easy these metrics work?
Well, yes, but it's a little unclear.
I'll tell you why, because you kind of ask me this question when you and I first met.
I was just thinking of that, about, you know, what it is I consider myself.
And I told you I really don't have one of those labels.
It doesn't, none of them make sense to me.
I said, if you had to pin me down to a singular word, I might use the word pagan, but that's
only because that's the most easily understood version of what I might be.
But I don't subscribe to any of this stuff.
Yeah, exactly.
It's just a matter of, I've studied a lot of it, and I don't claim to have full comprehension
of, well, any of it, really.
Well, really, the religion is what you do regularly, and it also, how do you interface
with the non-material things?
Well, right, but you weren't asking about my...
But you, see, religion is your regular habits, but you weren't asking me about my regular
habits when you asked that question, you see.
That's why I said I don't have a definition for you, because, you know...
Oh, sure.
But the reason I'm saying this, because this is...
I mean, religiously, I'm a smoker.
I mean, you know, I smoke.
Well, I'm not a smoker, because in order to be smoking, you have to be on fire.
If you're using cigarettes, you're a sucker.
You're sucking.
You're not smoking.
That was the next part of our conversation that day, was, I recall this.
Right, because in order to be smoking, it means you're on fire, and I don't never look
forward to that kind of condition.
But they call this, generally speaking, they call this act smoking.
That's another metric.
Like, back in the old days, they'd ask you on the airplane, do you want smoking or non-smoking?
And I'd say, which one flies better, right?
Yeah, good question there.
Yeah, so, anyway...
Yeah, so I do actually suck on cigarettes regularly, and that's a fairly religious activity.
Yeah, and I think we've explained there's no lung cancer attached to tobacco use, right?
Any more than anyone else, right?
So yeah, it was the nuclear testing, the eye-breathing, the ionized particles, and this is easily
substantiated.
If you can get occurrences of lung cancer since the 1950s by state, there's nothing in
California to mention.
Everything is downwind, meaning from Nevada to the east, east of Nevada.
I'm only the second generation of my family born in this country, right?
So I've got to tell you that, although men seem to die in my family line fairly young,
I'm actually a rather old man.
However, the women, regardless of whether they were smoking or sucking on tobacco,
some of them lived to be, you know, 100, 90, 103, no lung cancer, and smoking every day,
you know, commonly smoking.
Things like lung cancer or cancer and blood pressure and certain things like diabetes
and religion, those things are all fictions ingrained in society.
What's interesting is we're taught by academia to view the ancients as being ignorant, and
by showing what the ancients partook in, what thought forms, and actually they were far
more advanced.
Geographically, but I'm just saying geographically, I take note that the family members that I
had did not get these things that weren't born here.
If they were children elsewhere and they came here, they participated in these activities
another 80 years and lived that long.
Sure.
Well, the yattricide, you know, being death by doctor, well, yattricide could also mean
killing the doctor, but the treatment is the disease here.
Now, I've been doing some studying recently, recently, let's say a year ago, and I put
it down after three or four months.
If you can get by the Google algorithms, you could find some pretty good information.
There's about a million people a year that die, they say, from direct medical neglect.
You've actually lowered the number to 300,000, which can't be.
Which can't be correct at all.
And I'll tell you, I've had people argue to me that they've done research enough, and
not just through the internet or through algorithms, that I count as fairly intelligent, who have
argued to me that, quite truthfully, regardless of the body counts they give you for wars,
in the 20th century, regardless of the bloodshed, which there was a significant amount through
conflict, more people died through what they would call medical misadventure or death by
the doctor, then all of those wars combined, if you combine the figures, you'll have a
higher number in medical deaths.
Oh, sure, by far, even, you know, Vietnam, they said it was 50,000, it was more like
150,000.
Yeah, 58,000 is the official count about, and yes, and then they say about a million
Vietnamese on the other side, and both numbers are drastically underreported, yes.
Yeah, it's also legal, technical, if you're in a helicopter and die in the helicopter,
you're not in Vietnam, right?
Right.
And the same thing with all the wars, but the casualties are high, but they're supposed
to be high, and it doesn't matter whose side, as long as you have casualties, that's the
whole idea.
Right, nobody ever talks about the Korean conflict and the body count there, which even
according to the official numbers is higher than Vietnam, but it is a different, it wasn't
protested the same way, it doesn't get the same attention, but again,
Yeah, it was just an extension, the Korean conflict was an extension of the
World War II, what they call it.
Yeah, there was a small little cessation of hostilities, let's say, but it was the continuation
because the Japanese pretty much showed their power by creating the 38th Parallel with nuclear
landmines, which by the way, there were publications called the, I think the Atlanta Constitution
newspaper, you could look it up, 1946, they talk about the nuclear landmines that they
sent Army and Secretary of State observers, Japanese says, you think the two firecrackers
you dropped on us is a big deal, and what, send some observers, we're going to show you
something here, because they were stopping the Russian advance, right?
Douglas Dietrich is pretty good on all this stuff, I don't endorse him, but he's got good
information, so if you could listen to his stuff to a degree, if you could stomach him,
and then go on with your own research, that's a good place to start for World War II.
Regarding the access to the underworld, by the way, I was thinking, is it Joseph Farrell
that maybe has some stuff online about that, or is that, or am I mixing you up?
No, believe it or not, Donald Marshall, which is the cloning center guy, yeah, but he won't
talk about Switzerland directly, but he does reference this kind of concept, yeah, it's
also, remember, this is, it's kind of like, what are these sublime, you know, there's
two types of censorship, you get a FOIA, and they put the black marker through it,
it's obvious, right? Then there's the subtle censorship, where after 9-11, the FBI hired
a few hundred people, maybe a few thousand people, to go around wherever they can and
buy up all the old dictionaries, and have them republished, changing the definition
of ground zero, right? So, it wouldn't be so technical, meaning it's, ground zero is
a strict technical term that defines a place above or on the earth that is for atomic or
nuclear detonations, and then they try to change it to make it a social thing. I think
I went real quick, Diane Sawyer, a day later, the term ground zero was not used until later,
there's more confusion, they're saying it wasn't Diane Sawyer that coined it, but I can't
say it was, but she was looking for someone to interview, and the area was blocked off,
and it was nighttime, and black SUVs with men in black looking guys, meaning black suits
with black ties and white shirts and sunglasses at night, and she's looking for someone, she
says, oh, you're going in there, where are you going? She goes, ma'am, we can't speak,
we're here to look at ground zero, and she says, oh, did you hear them? It's called ground
zero, and it started right there, so basically, you know, the probably Secret Service, whatever,
you know, group, international group or whatever, to go and see what's going on from a distance,
because what's interesting is they had the, anyone that was from any higher up government
agency was in full hazmat suits with breathing tanks, so reporters and firemen were looking
at these guys coming in, you know, they looked like they came out from underwater with breathing
tanks, and they're like, how come we're out here with these little particle masks, and
these guys from the FBI are in breathing tanks, what do they know that we don't know, right?
Yeah, well, very good question, but also, that means that Weird Al Yankovic's usage
of the term ground zero is more accurate than what you have today, quite frankly, he did
a song called Christmas Time at Ground Zero, and his usage, it still exists, they didn't,
you know, scrub that, but it's just kind of, you know, he's a goofball, so it's okay.
Did he mention anything nuclear or atomic? Yeah, that's what it's all about, is it's
Perfect. Yeah. That's what it is, yeah. Yeah, but it wasn't, it was done before 9-11, obviously,
so, yeah. Oh, retrospect, okay. Well, here's the thing, they're all these things that you're
told, what they are, they are real events, they're just not what, you know, so when they
tell you there's a terrorist event, it's not terrorist at all. It's a, it's a, you know,
it's a exercise. There are real things that happen. It's sort of like false advertising. Yes,
indeed, there's a story. Yes, indeed, they sell products, but it might not be exactly the product
that they're telling you they have. Sure, there is real terrorism, but it doesn't make the news,
because it's, it's viewed as weakness. I was in a hardware store recently, and I told someone
whose history, retired, you know, retired history teacher, works at a, as a clerk at a hardware
store, easy job, right? And I think you mentioned this guy before. Yeah, yeah, and I basically got
into, he got into the military, he did military history. I said, well, you know, 9-11 was to show
you that the military is not going to protect the country, right? That was a clear signal. That's
why, you know, they let that happen, right? He was like, what? You know, they already told you
several times, the military is not going to protect you. And they kind of left it at that,
you know. That's how I view it, you know. And also, when the military failed, why didn't they fire
everyone in the military and bring in all the Allied military temporarily, right? You see,
wouldn't you be fired? Like, if you were running the cash register all day, and it was minus $120,
at the end of the day, at the till, you're going to lose your job. It's not like 50 cents or $2,
right? Right. So if you let an event like that happen, you would have to disband your entire
military and call your allies to come in and fill in in the meantime, until you set up a new one.
That didn't happen. So it's clearly, evidently telling you that, you know, Americans are okay
with it. And that's what they do with a franchise is when you have a whole bunch of, you know,
you have a clearly there's, you know, serious shortages, they'll turn around and bring in a
bunch of guys from other places, let them wear it for a minute, because they're not familiar,
they can't be responsible for it. And then they'll investigate and figure out what went on.
Yeah. So the Americans obviously backed up. They're okay with it. They're not being protected.
They're just just fine with them. It's not fine with me. But it's fine with everyone around me.
That's why I always say, if they want to stop what they're doing, and turn this place into a
paradise, hey, listen, go have at it. I still I want nothing to do with it. If they want to go
ahead and kill each other, hey, go have at it. I want nothing to do with it either. So my thing
is nothing to do with any of the social creations that are taking place. Because it just can't be
good no matter what label they put on it. So in essence, if you were to, let's say, sum up what
we're trying to say, if this is Planet Earth, Inc, or One World Corporation, like One World Inc,
like I think, what's his name?
A lot of people use the term New World Order. Are you talking about that?
Yeah. It's One World. It's Earth, Inc. It's incorporated. And what's interesting about that,
you have these big companies, other than the DTCC, the Deposit Trust and Clearing Corporation,
and they have 24 quadrillion or 2.4 quadrillion on their balance sheet. I think if you put a
price tag on the earth, it wouldn't be more than 100, more than 1000 trillion, it would be way
below that. 2.4 quadrillion is 2.4 thousand trillion. So that means that they're monetized
on their balance sheet, the rest of the bodies in the solar system. You see what I mean?
Unless there's a whole lot of resources here that we don't know the value of. I mean, is that
possible too?
That's possible. But they're pretty much stating that overtly, that's what they have. They're not
telling us exactly where this goes. I'm just surmising. I think Joseph Farrell is talking
about the monetization of space. And there are international treaties that say that basically
slavery is okay up there. Have you heard of that one?
No, I've heard about it. Yeah, the space treaty stuff is very, very intricate and interesting. I
don't know where it all leads, to be honest with you. But I've heard it discussed. Yes.
Yeah. So this is basically the situation. But the government and the state, and by the way, they
do make a very succinct point to say the state, like if you apply for anything, a registration,
birth certificate on their application, the very last line where you sign it, if you look very
carefully, it says everything on this application would be used for the good of the state. Have
you ever seen that? Anyone look at any government application for anything, a vehicle
registration, driver's license, birth certificate application, it's always on the bottom line,
right by the signature where you sign, right?
I can't say that I personally observed that, but I will be on the lookout for it.
Yeah, maybe during this recording, I'll do a screenshot and send it to you. It's pretty easy to
find. Well, here's the thing. I'm not very familiar with, it seems like the Google, I am familiar
with the searching on the internet. But the, what do you call them? Oh, algorithms have gotten very
harsh and very, very censored. We did a recent Freeman talk, and most of the talk was about chat
GBT. And I'm suggesting that it's not an AI, but it's just a distraction in a sense as part of the
censorship tools, right? You could either show people you're taking information away or give them
a lot of information in the wrong direction, or many directions. If you can't baffle them with
bullshit, dazzle them with brilliance.
Well, yeah. And you know, as something else, two quick things I want to mention here before we get
away from it is one of have you gotten your your Bing bot yet on because we're talking right now
we're using Skype to communicate.
I was on Bing recently to do a search and it jumped on Skype and I removed it.
Okay.
Is that what you're referring to?
Yeah, but I see I didn't use Bing to search for anything. And I now have a couple of people who
told me about being just popped up as sort of a contact on their Skype.
And it was a better just to if you're looking at current events, I do Middle East and Asia current
events past week, past day, whatever. Okay, they have a much better image collection than Google
does, by the way.
Okay, fair enough. But I really I've avoided Bing for I forget what the reason was, but
something.
Oh, it doesn't matter. Remember, all the patriots who go duck, duck, go. And it turned out that
they're the same algorithm as Google.
Yeah, they're powered by Google anyway. So I don't know. Yeah, exactly. So no, but at some
point, I think I started avoiding Bing for one of those reasons. And I don't even remember what it
is now. But it was just strange that it added it to a car like it, it created a contact for me on
Skype. And suddenly I have this Bing bot asking me, you know, do I want information on like very
odd things? And telling me that it's there to help me.
So, yeah, it's just a it's just part of the look, I found it. I was very accusatory back. I think by
2010 2011. The smartphone thing was taking off, right? Yeah. And I everything that you see that
people comment on, I was commenting, commenting on back then before it became, you know, like, in
other words, people are going to be looking at this all the stupid rectangle all the time. Oh,
yeah, right. Even when they're next to each other, blah, blah, blah, they're gonna rely on it. And
then when it's taken away, then they'll beg for relief. You know, this is a very common thing
that goes on.
It's a common trope now. But honestly, yeah, there was only a very few people talking about how this
was going to become extremely dominant. And quite frankly, I kind of didn't feel as though people
would be dumb enough to be fully distracted by it. Yeah, I know. I keep having this idea that people
aren't as stupid as they are. And I'm always disappointed. And I just felt like there would be a
certain segment of the population that would be sucked into this. I didn't think it would be as
widespread as it is. But I saw it coming.
tattoos and the smartphone I was pretty vocal on I said you as the time goes on, you won't it'll be
very hard to find someone that doesn't have a tattoo. And I gave reasons for that. It's part of
the setup. So when you say the gender bending and LGBTQ RST, yeah, YZ and all the marriages and all
the same side of those stuff. All this is set up.
Yeah, even back when you and I first started talking, you were very, very, very much on that.
And I kind of didn't feel like that was going to be as dominant as it is. The tattoos I sort of
understood because things become trendy, and then they become commonplace. And then they're no longer
trendy. It's sort of like, you know, the the earring in the ear. You and I are similar age. So the the
pierced left ear, right? This was a big statement at a certain point when we were younger, wasn't it?
Yeah, a little diamond or whatever. I never never did any of that or tattoos. I have no marks. Yeah,
I did. But anyway,
no, that's fine. They were removed. I suggest people have them removed. If you can. Well, it
depends, you know, because that's going to be an important way to sort out society, not now, but in the future.
Yeah, near future. Right?
No, we went over it back then. But I do recall you talking about that. I had something else in mind, though, that I
wanted you to try and put in context, if you don't mind, if you're aware of what's going on with this, which, you
know, sometimes, look, we can't keep track of every sort of news trend. But and this isn't political or
anything, or maybe it's not. The train derailments. Have you taken notice of that recently?
Yeah, it was a ferry derailment as well in the Ohio River recently, more recently than the train derailments,
plural. Yeah, that was a setup because here's the thing. Okay, this is how the Okay, how do I put this? Right?
Very simple analogy. I go to the store and I buy a two liter bottle of soda. It's got compressed gas in it, right?
All right. Okay. And I have it in the shopping bag and get out of the car falls and hits the deck. Does the
bottle break and explode? Or does it get a little dent? I pick it up, dust it off, put it go wet, walk back
inside the house, right? That's how these things work. Most times, most times. Yeah, but unfortunately,
sometimes the plastic breaks and you got a mess. Really? I've never Well, that's pretty big height. I'm
talking about like, you know, waist level down. No, no beer can. I see this. Yeah, I see this all the time,
actually, that you have. Yeah, they see that analogy. Yeah, they seem to be making them thinner. Now. I'm
just saying they seem to be making some of these thinner now. So sometimes the thing just bursts open.
Well, trains. Yeah, they're, they've been scrutinized. They've been doing that kind of, they've been
developing railroad car technology, tanker car technology for over 100 years, right? And it's not going to
spill when it falls off the tracks. It seems like it should not. Yeah, it seems like it should not. And it's
not one big tank. Like a like a, what do you call an inflatable mattress, you make a hole and everything
comes out, there's a series of tanks and levels of absorbers and things in there to prove if there is a breach
to contain it. So it was deliberate, right? Just like years ago, when there were fires here in Arizona. A lady
was really distressed. She has a cabin up there in the in the White Mountains, in the well north of Tucson,
Catalina Mountains. And she says, my daughter reported she was some parks department guys are putting propane
tanks out in the forest and shooting them with a gun. So you know, and then they find some poor drunk homeless
guy and blame it on him. Right. So also with the deer biscuits that have they put deer feed out that has mad cow
disease, let's say, you know, deer meat in it. So the deer get right. So anyway, right. Pretty interesting how how
these things are. Don't be naive. And I've been saying this for a long time. If you go online and find like the
most outlandish, outrageous conspiracy theories, stories that are way beyond anything believable. The truth is
even beyond that. I haven't found any. You see, it's so mild, even the worst conspiracy theories, quote unquote, are
still mild compared to what really is going on and accepted and done by those that you trust and whatever.
Yeah, well, so far, the more out there theories about this, because we are seeing a sort of a more common occurrence. I
mean, look, anything that is created by man has a failure rate, right? So it's possible no matter what the technology
is, we may see a failure like this with the with the trains and such, right. But like you said, 100 years already, they've
they've been working on it. So they're upgrading all the trains. Yeah, the trains, the compartments. Even when people
see a gas truck, they think, oh, it's one. It's not one big tank. You know, they only really explode in the movies.
These things are very well made, usually. So you don't have that. Yeah.
No, the chemical rockets are not these tubes. If you cut one open, you'll find spheres in there because you can't get
5,000 pounds of pressure in a tube, it has to be in a sphere. So very often, these things wash up on beaches. And people
think it's alien technology. They're just rocket fuel tanks. You know, they're in other words, it would look like a bunch of
Christmas ornaments, round balls inside of that tube. Right. Right. So just getting a little more technical, just going one
more step beyond what's being shown. You know, it doesn't take much or you can have someone like me that susses things out
very quickly do a sonic and you can then look it up if you care. But, you know, right. But what why did you bring up the
train derailments? Do you think what was the what was the worry? What do you want to go with that?
Well, because look, people are talking about it. And and now, you know, turning it into well, was it because you know, Trump
deregulated stuff? Or is this happening? Because there is literally a terrorist because you brought up the terrorist attacks
that there are terrorist attacks, but they're not talked about. Because some people are saying that that's what's actually
happening. Yeah, but are they talking about that? They could have easily covered up the train stuff? Yeah, it was real. They
could have they want they want you to believe a certain narrative, a certain thought. It's here. Here's the other thing. When did
you ever hear something that the Patriot community or the mainstream media put out this is coming and it came never, never, never,
never happens the way that you're being told because you're so distracted. And you know, people's vantage point is really low. In
other words, if you're looking at each other, in essence, and watching the news, alternative or mainstream, you're it's too low of a
vantage point, you have to get up in a helicopter and see the town from above to get a sense of what it really looks like. So yeah, I
think, yeah, you know, we can always discuss politics and current events, but it's not it's not the way it's being told. Oh,
and the real stuff is where it's quiet. And right now, it's really quiet in the Middle East. And in parts of Asia, the Pacific
Rim. So that's where you're going to watch. Well, not when but when things start coming out of there in the near future, don't be
surprised. And of course, Israel is, you know, I think, I think we've mentioned on previous sonic Israel's being set up to fail. And
then it's going to get really hairy there. So right, well, there's currently according to reports, and they're not well covered
here at all. But if you dig a little bit, you'll find that there's this issue about the judiciary, and them protesting in the
street, and some of them refusing to serve in the military now, even though that's supposed to be a compulsory thing. If you're, you
know, it's still voluntary, though. Well, that's the other. Do you know how you volunteer when it's compulsory, even since World
War One? Well, even even when you have a draft, that's the case, because people say, Oh, what about a draft? No, actually, you're
still having to sit there. And at some point, you agree. You don't know when you're volunteering. This is when you volunteer when
they've got you in your underwear. You have to if you don't show up for draft inspection or sign up, you'll be arrested. So you show
up. And when they do the medical exam, they have you sit in standing in boxers or briefs. And they have everyone in a line and they
have you standing there long enough where you get irritated and they have a sergeant come in and says, Okay, everyone is ready to join
the US Armed Forces take a step forward. And what does everybody do takes a step forward, right? And whoever doesn't, they come up to
them and they stare you down for a minute. And they said, Come over here and take you in a room. They give you all your stuff, a $20
bill, and a bus ticket, go back home.
Even if you've been drafted, by the way,
well, this is pre draft, right? Well, you've drafted meaning you had to show up now.
So you were sent to notice? Yeah, well, you were sent to notice based on a numerical, you know, drawing and this and that.
Yeah, but you have to show up. Because if you don't show up, you default on that because it's your you know, you're residing there,
right. But I'm saying that even if it seems
like it's not voluntary, there's a point in there where you volunteer. The same thing happens with prisoners of war. Are you familiar
with the tactic use how they take prisoners of war?
Well, no, I'm not familiar with that. I'm just I just want to make this very, very clear is that even though you go through this
process, where you do have to show up because you've been summoned in a way,
that part is what they will prosecute you for if you don't show up. But just because you show up and go through the motions doesn't
mean that you're drafted at some point in that process. They, it has to be voluntary, just like in court, it's voluntary.
There is a there is a point there. And you described it the way somebody else actually completely independent from you described
it just now to me at another point. And I was kind of amazed by that. But then I kind of had that confirmed by somebody who does
those processes that Yeah, that's exactly right. If you don't, it's a little different. It's not always exactly as you describe.
Yeah, you show up in court, the court, but if you show up to court, it's voluntary, even if it's whatever it is, right. So but that's
tricky, because they understand that people are learning how to do it. And that's a maybe we'll do that on a one hour sonic or
something that needs to be its own thing. But what I'm saying is, is that during a lot of these processes, where people figure
there's absolutely no choice, there is almost always a point at which now would you call that a pledge? Is that the point at which
that's right, that's where you when you pledge, you give up everything. That's right. And that word is also being used as a meme,
like on Begafon's, you know, pledge $10, pledge $20, right, you know, the Begafon's on the radio or TV. Because that goes,
actually, it's a it's a term that's loosely used, but it actually is very important. Just like when you get a shopper's card, if
you go to one of these big grocery stores, they give you a card, you swipe and you get a discount. What they're doing the
full amount, let's say you go to Kroger's or whatever, a supermarket, and they have these membership cards, right, right. When
you swipe that the entire amount of that purchase goes on a credit balance sheet, and they can they can prove right there that
you approved that you bought that and this is the amount of credit that they are accruing, meaning the store, and they could
leverage that on what's called pro forma accounting. Boy, oh boy, do we I don't know if I want to go down there. But pro forma
just means percentage. Like for example, if you're a company like General Electric, and you're not doing well, you have a stock,
you buy a little company for a million bucks that makes 30% profit, right. And, you know, someone who puts like, you know, red
dots on semiconductor chips, you buy them for a million bucks, three employees, they make 30% profit. So at your GE meeting, you
say we just, we wholly, this subsidiary is wholly a part of GE, and it makes a 30% profit. Look at our spreadsheet now. It's great,
right. But it's gonna tell you it's 300,000 versus 17 billion in losses, right?
Right. But by the percentages, look, this one's making 30%. Okay, so that one lost 20. But this one's making 30. So
yeah, so they love doing that. So yeah, it's very interesting. You can do well, it gets gets complicated, but you could do a forensic
audit. Forensics just means evidence on all the stuff you spent, and have it monetized. And then they'll tell you don't ever come to our
store again, by the way, you know, because they, in other words, you find out how they're monetizing it, and you want a cut of that,
right? See, because they're giving you your cut up front, you know, they go shopping, you swipe the card, oh, you save $20 today, right? Or
whatever, you see. So yeah, this is all the same thing happens. When you have these job fairs, big companies like Raytheon, GE, GM,
they go to these towns, and they have a job fair, and they have all these people apply. No one ever gets hired at those job fairs. Even
government agencies do that. They go to colleges, right, and they have you sign up. And they, if you give them, what they want is the
money's signature, because the money is drawn off the signature. So let's say a big company like Raytheon or whatever goes to Kansas, and
there's a job fair, and 200 people fill out applications and sign it, and each application is a salary of 100 grand, that's 20 million right
there, let's say, or maybe I didn't do the math right, with signatures that they could go and monetize, because remember, the money comes
off the signature, right? And you see, that's how they create their funding. That's another way. Same thing with a university. When you go and
register to a college or university, it doesn't matter which one, you sign the registration form, they get the full tuition, they monetize your
signature, but then they ask you to pay for it again, because, you know, it's plausible. You know who knew this? Gaddafi. All the utility
companies that were internationally owned were still getting paid. He just told the people, look, you get a bill, just sign it or put your
thumbprint and send it back. That's all you got to do. They didn't get free electric or free gas or whatever. And the utility, foreign utility
companies were getting all the money, but they were like, wait a second, this is spreading really, what if people find out? Let's get rid of this guy,
right? There's many other reasons. But right, but that was actually, that was one of the things that they used to say about him, though, is that
look, he gives people free electricity, and he goes and he gives them a house. No, they have to do the same with any form that you find. The
funny one is the hospitals. When you go to a hospital, and they have you find that registration form, you say, well, look, I need a cash
receipt for this. And they're like, what? No one knows what's going on. But when it gets to an administrator, you basically, it's a long form, a
long yellow form. It's a carbon copy, pink, white, yellow, whatever, right? That goes under the QSIP convention, which is the Convention for
Universal Security Investment Protocols. But essentially, what's funny is playing around with the hospital, especially if you have a baby there, is
every time you fill out a piece of paper, you say, I need to speak to one of the administrators, and they'll say, why? You got to tell them why. You
say, because I need a cash receipt for this, right? So basically, there's no, you don't know the figure. The figures are between 50,000 to 5 million
for one of those applications, by the way, any hospital form. So the reason, and when they say, well, there's no cash, I don't know what you're
talking about. I said, well, I need something with your hospital heading on it that just say that this is an open cash receipt, that you received some
cash, that you're going to receive some cash value for this paperwork. Now, don't say on my signature. And they freak out. And they're like, okay, then
when you do this, they'll give you like, what's interesting, they because they have to have you sign another one when you're leaving. And when you
bring that up, again, it's you'll almost as if go to a hotel, and they give you a first class room. Right? And you don't get a bill, by the way,
usually, and if you get a bill, you just throw it away, because you have the cash receipt. Now the cash receipt, there's no number, it's just an open
check. So for example, if any money can be drawn from your signature, why do you need to put a number on it? You could, you know, it's a it's what do
they call it, like an open check, right? This is how we're operating, because it's not our fault, we're in this condition. You see, so it's very
interesting how it works. That's why the system is in trouble, because they're producing so much, let's say fiat currency potential, that they don't
know where to put it all. Right. So if they really let the public know what's going on, it would be 100 bucks for a gallon of milk very soon. So the
inflation that's going on right now is not so bad, because it should be around a minimum wage should be over $30 an hour and a gallon of gas should be
25. You see what I'm saying? But it's not so it's not so bad. I tell people they didn't put a cap on inflation since 2012. And now you're getting hit
with it. But it's it's Yeah, anyway. Yeah, it sucks. And the thing also mentioned if your salary is not doubling in the next year, and you're just
barely making it, you're not going to make it's going to be really hard to make it. So as salary has to double within a year, you know, depending on what
your salary is, I know some people make quarter of a million a year salary, you don't need quarter of a million to live. But if you're making, you know,
less than 50,000 a year, if you don't see a way to be making 80 to 100,000 in a year, you're going to feel it, you're going to be, you know, looking for
another way to do things. So it depends on what, you know, whatever, you know, overhead you have. So, yeah, I just wanted to bring up these little
points, because, you know, there's no way we could do any kind of Greeks Greek speak without rounding it off, you know, because typically, I'm very rough
around the edges. So you got to smooth it out a little bit. But here's the good news. It's all good news. All right, because you have a short stay here,
it's not that long. And you do what you can pick a set of laws and rules that you live by that you live by and stick with it. Because that's really your way
that that's your freedom. When you pick a law form that works, or especially an old law form, that is actually a freedom, inviting condition, right? So it's kind
of complicated. You know, the state has millions of laws, if you count all of the countries, all the different codes and all that, which one don't you know?
Right. But if you have, let's say, I use the biblical covenant, there's maybe a handful of things that you consider all the time. And maybe another few handful of
things that you might want to look up once in a while, but it's very open. So in other words, for example, with Old Testament laws, if it's not expressly
prohibited, it's indirectly encouraged, indirectly, right? So with that said, I wanted to bring up something that Nick put in the chat. A while back, he's seems to
be asking a lot about the New Testament, and things like that, which would be called the kene the afiki, right? In Greek. I recently been looking at again, I don't
endorse this person, but I do approve most of his message. If you want to get a handle on what I've discussed on other Greek speak stuff, mostly, maybe in other
places, maybe loosely, and calls, I don't think we've done much of it, maybe. If you want to find out what what was going on in the New Testament, you're going to have to lean
very heavily on the Aramaic because the quote unquote, apostleship and decisive discipleship and all that there's no john or Luke or all that those those sound like good old
boys, right? These these were Hebraic based people that spoke Aramaic. It was not Greek, the Greek didn't come until the end of that century, because it was an international
language. What was penned if it was penned, as we recall, it stating it was penned in Aramaic. So it was translated from Aramaic to Greek. So what I'm trying to say is there's
someone that wrote a book, and I've been looking at the Peshetta, which is the Aramaic form, there's someone who spent most of his life putting this together. His name is Andrew Gabriel Roth. You spell it just like it sounds
Andrew Gabriel Roth, got a bunch go to YouTube, if you want to listen to it. He's got a couple of books out, but he keeps every time he puts out I've been looking at him now I for a couple of weeks, because I wanted to see what was on the Aramaic
New Testament, and he seems to be the closest. Okay, I don't endorse him because he's Jewish. Right. And when I say Jews, I spell it J O O Z. Okay, so don't get on me. Right. It's, it's great. It's kind of like Linda with a Y. Don't say it with an I. Right. Okay. Right. You know, kind of thing. I heard you say it with an I. So it's with a Y. Right. So anyway, he's very Jewish. And meaning that Saturday, Sabbath, he
doesn't know how to keep time, right? Right. He keeps these rabbinical. But on the other hand, this is what this is how he won me over enough to mention his name. On a sonic, I found a short video, where he is, if he quoted what I had said, and there's the synchronicity, you got to appreciate synchronicity when it happens, right? And what it was on the short video, he stated, like, the name of the Messiah is not J. E. S. U. S. It's Joshua, if you're going to use it, Yahshua in
English. And there's no harm in using Joshua, because the sixth book of the Bible is the book of Joshua. So it's not like they can't say Joshua, no one will understand it or ever heard it before, because it's already been used. So if they were really trying to stick to something that was semi true, or truer than than not, they would have called in the New Testament, all the English would have been Joshua, not J. E. S. U. S. And when I saw that, I kind of play the
video again, I'm like, wait a second, how did me and this guy end up saying almost exactly the same thing? Right? So that's, he kind of won, won my gratitude on that. So that's why I'm putting him out. I've listened to a lot of his stuff in the past week and a half or so. And I would suggest that he leans very heavily on, well, on the matter of the New Testament and everything being based in Aramaic, and not Hebrew, but you could say Hebrew, and not Greek.
And then it doesn't mean the Greek is invalid. But I would say 40% of the Greek is invalid, maybe more than 40% is invalid. So if you want to get to the 90% point of what's written, you have to study the Aramaic. So if you got time, Andrew Gabriel Roth on YouTube, he's got some long lectures, I think some stuff went back as far as five or seven years. But again, he does not understand. He's rabbinical. He's been, you know, pardon me, someone asked me that I brought this
up to recently, says, Well, why don't you get in touch with him about timekeeping and Torah? I said, Are you kidding? Even if he wanted to do it, because he runs a ministry, he would he would be, you know, suicide for him. No one would, you know,
he'd be invited, he'd be invited out of any any grouping he has there, that would be his groupings that he have would dissolve immediately. So in the past, I've heard more than one person talk about, you know, Yeshua, which is a more proper way to look at it. And I've had people even tell me that, you know,
you remember Mel Gibson did that movie a while back, that he attempted to use the Aramaic.
Yep. And he is still keeping the Vatican censorship with the crucifixion, though. Right, right. Which is the other thing is just the the event there when you've got the the wooden cross and all this kind of
Yeah, there was no such thing. Right. Which, you know, again, it's a it's a tree. And anyway,
well, let's just do a fast recap. There's no guy nailed to a cross wearing a diaper, right? Right. And yeah, it was he was he was arrested by the Judean religious authorities. And he ran they ran him through from the Judean authorities to the monarchy that was suzerain to the Romans, Prefect Governor Pilate Pontius Pilate had the last say and Pontius Pilate told the
Judean authorities, you have your law, use your law. What law is that? It's law Moses. And there you go. So what's execution under law Moses simple. And if you look at what transpired, and how the event went from the third to the ninth hour people passing and this that and the other, it lines up with a stoning, not a, and it was an almond tree, because we're 36 references or so to the almond tree, not the olive tree. So
right. Right. Which, which, again,
Mel Gibson, Mel Gibson, you could not approach him either on this.
No, but he did. I'm just making the point that the attempt was there to use the Aramaic. But again,
Oh, it is it's still used today. Yeah. Like, in the modern Israeli, Israeli, Judea culture, you have a bar mitzvah. It's not it should well, if you're speaking Hebrew would be a Ben mitzvah bar is sun in Aramaic. So they keep some Aramaic terms still today because of the culture, right to bring out a mitzvah means a rule or to do. So why is it bar when bar like bar
Abbas, right son of the father, right? Not Ben Abbas. So it's kind of confusing. And by the way, just like are you familiar with early American history, they didn't know what to be the official language was Ben Franklin wanted it to be French, you know, of America, United States, let's say America. Oh, you remember that little country? We're talking about what should be our language? Greek? Yeah. Yeah. Hessian or, or, or French English was like, kind of like third or fourth, but it prevailed, right?
It prevailed, but then officially wasn't given the officially we didn't have a language. This is what I was taught initially in school.
It was going to be French, I think was the top contender or German or something, but it ended up being English. And this was it sounds ridiculous. Now, if you bring this up, right? So it just turns out that the language lengua franca that everyone spoke back then was Aramaic, not Hebrew or Greek. And there's some big differences in the text when you have translations, like for example, the, the generations, if you count the book of Matthew, the generations,
it says they're 42 generations, we only count 41. Well, because the last two are the men have the same name, right? And one is described as a Gowda. So anyway, Andrew Gabriel Roth gets into some of this stuff. Also, there's some interesting things that he that I wasn't sure, so sure about, I was going to order his book, but he just trying to publish another one, which is basically, what's interesting about writing books is as you learn more, and you publish,
you tell people will get this one, because it's more advanced and corrects what the previous one had. So yeah, there's always updated versions. Yeah, yeah. So it's a redo. So anyway, Andrew Gabriel Roth to get to a feeling of what he's saying there, and how their Christian community was never a Christian community until hundreds of years later. Yeah. So I just wanted to put that out for the New Testament, because it sounds very pedantic to go into correcting
notions that we have. And there's a lot of there's a Jason Breshears guy of archaics, and he just trashes everything, saying that the because the German academics 100 years ago said that it was all written at 300 BC for the Old Testament and the New Testament, we don't know. He leans on that without having comprehension. What my comment would be to Jason Breshears is, he says he's read the Bible 50 times, he has the notes to prove it.
Well, that means that you passed the sequence that I just explained, where Pontius Pilate reverted the victim that day, back to using Mosaic law, you didn't pick up on that reading it 50 times, that means you don't have any comprehension, and you're taking what some academics are saying about it, right?
Yeah, look, I've only actually read it, you know, cover to cover the King James Version twice. But I'm well aware of that. That's that's a key point that he they bring him to him because he's the ruler of that piece of land. Right? Because he's the governor. I mean, this is a very basic, really crappy understanding, I'm sure. But I think it's
Yeah, well, when you're in the military, you're given an area book.
Well, yeah, that's right. And the thing is...
He had the area book, he knew their laws.
Right. But that's the thing, they do give you a book where you're... Anyway, point is...
Well, he was also a historian and a friend of Claudius Tiberius Caesar, who was a historian also, by trade, even though he was the emperor. So it's quite interesting.
Right.
But all I'm saying is that in the story, okay, in the story, the way I understand it, is that he would have been controlling that area. So properly, they brought this person who was causing a disruption, he's there to maintain order to them, okay, according to the story to the governor, the guy who's in charge, who basically says, look, this I'm not even going to deal with, let the locals handle it and handle it with your rules, your laws, your courts, whatever it is.
Right. There's an exchange there.
There's an exchange there. And this happens, actually, this is not uncommon.
Well, yeah. So in other words, when you read crucifixion, it's inserted, right?
It has to be.
It's a hanging, you know, and a nailing.
Yeah, it has to be. Because according to that time period, there's no historical evidence that this would have been the way it was done, the way that they show it to you now.
Well, crucifixion, sorry.
Crucifixion, no, not the way that they showed you, okay? Not this whole building a wooden cross.
No, it's not biblical. There's lots of...
Yeah.
Crucifixion came from the Assyrians, and it was used throughout Rome, usually for rebellions.
Yes.
It was a symbol of torture, not of dying.
But you weren't building a crossbar, okay? And you used the things that were there, for the most part. I know in some areas they built...
Well, the reason...
Because you're given to understand, the way that these people try to explain it is that this is the way it was just done.
This was the form of execution. That wasn't the common form of execution, and according to their laws, it definitely wasn't the way to go.
Well, he could have appealed to Caesar, you see. Anyone can appeal to Caesar. It's a very lengthy process, but you're held in a carcer, as incarceration.
It was very common, by the way, by Roman prefects to just give them back to the population to use their customary laws,
because if they didn't, and they were going to use Roman execution method, the subject or the victim can appeal to Caesar, which is a representative Caesar, to Rome, in Rome.
Right.
It was kind of miserable to wait for such a thing, but the Romans were very open about this.
So one way to stop all that bureaucracy is to just give them back. It was very more customary to give the person back and let the people use their customs of whatever.
Well, it was more expeditious to do so, because otherwise it's a very long process.
And then you had the argument of, well, is this person subject to Roman law, because Roman law is for Roman citizens.
Well, you could be subject to Roman law and still be given over to the customs of the people.
Yes, but my point is…
Just to cut the red tape.
Yeah, but my point is that's a whole lot of red tape to open up.
If you stick to the Roman law and the person is educated enough to know that he can appeal to Caesar, yeah, that's a lot of red tape.
That means conceivably you could have 10,000 people and the carcers would overflow, where you just give them back to.
So it was more common to give them back to the culture and let them do what they will and then settle the books that way.
Well, it was expedient. That's what I'm saying, is that it was just something to keep things moving, which was really a primary concern of anybody who was a governor or a prefect or whatever it is.
It is to keep everything kind of, you know, to maintain order, which is the phrase I used before.
So what I'm saying is that I even understand that that's there and that this makes sense.
The way that you've explained this makes a whole lot more sense than most of the stories.
Well, it's a metric. It's a metric.
In other words, when you have people walking around with crucifixes thinking, that tells the elite that these people are ignorant, right?
Now we're controlling ignorant people.
The way you control ignorant people is different than you control people who are of functioning intelligence, because the ignorant people have also a functioning intelligence.
They're just so damn stubborn.
That's the one thing that I haven't mentioned very often, is, quote-unquote, people that are ignorant or, quote-unquote, stupid.
It's not that they're ignorant or stupid.
It's that they're stubborn.
They have all the faculties to be aware and to be conscious or cognizant of what they're doing wrong and what is more correct.
It's just the stubbornness, you see.
And then, of course, there's the NPC, which is just the filler, which is a whole other discussion.
That's a different story.
I'm trying to organize it in my mind on how to present it, because I think the easiest way to notice the NPCs is
if you ever go by a big store like Macy's or Bloomingdale's or whatever, and you have these high-end mannequins in the window, right?
In a high fashion, whatever, they have high-end mannequins.
Look at the eyes of the mannequin.
No matter how well they artistically put them together, they're still fake eyes, right?
Right.
So when you look at someone and it doesn't look like there's any light at all coming from them, that's an NPC usually.
But it's not that simple, because there are people that have small eyes that are not very bright that are not.
But that's a general thing, is look at the eyes is the quickest.
That's a fairly decent tell, let's say.
And the Scripture does not say, by the way, the eyes are the window to the soul.
It's the window to the body.
Which makes a lot more sense.
I find it interesting, though, just in general, because it's, look, here's another point, right?
You brought up the crosses and this, and they see people wearing them around their necks.
Kind of interesting, because you can find that there were, that's actually a very specific thing.
And clearly signals that your adornment doesn't represent the thing that you're supposed to be religiously attached to.
It's a different, yeah.
It's a sky symbol from ancient Assyria.
But most people don't know why they're doing what they're doing and don't care to know why.
No, but that's a clear signal.
I guarantee you nobody you see with that cross dangling from a necklace has any idea that that's what that is.
Well, that was customary in Assyria 800 BC.
There's a stone stele carving.
You could just write crucifix wearing, cross wearing in 800 BC in Assyria.
There's plenty of statues and markings.
But there's so much going on with that.
It's not just the crucifix.
It's the entire organization.
I haven't found anyone in that organization to be competent or that, with, competent, in other words, with comprehension of the fundamentals.
That's why you have all the denominations in every religion, by the way.
You know the Muslims also have their divisions, right?
So once you see this division also, it's another problem.
Usually I think the people that are, let's say, most functional in any real wisdom or knowledge don't profess any title.
I think I keep saying if someone really is a witch, they will never say they're a witch.
If someone really is a shaman, they will never say it.
If someone is a healer, they will never call themselves a healer.
Someone is a prophet, they will never call themselves a prophet.
You see how it works?
Or a wizard or whatever.
All of these things that require, let's say, the manifestation or manipulation of qualities, which are subtle energies, right?
Now it's okay to say you're a master carpenter, a good wood butcher, right?
You're really good at working with wood or whatever, so whatever.
But that is very material and it's technically accessible.
A lot of these other things are not technically accessible.
They're technically guided, but not accessible technically, right?
There's a difference.
Just like alchemy, you can guide it technically.
You know, you get a book on alchemy, you do these things, you should be an alchemist.
But not everyone is because it's just a guide, right?
So, yeah.
Anyone can pick up a paintbrush, but not everyone is an artist.
Right, and then you have two types of painters, painting houses or painting canvas, right?
And there is an artisanship to both, actually, because you've got to properly do things if you're painting a house.
I mean, you know, you can tell when someone who doesn't know what they're doing does it,
because the stuff falls off, it's a sloppy job, etc.
Sure, sure.
One of the easiest things, those things, painting, by the way, is technically guided and also technically, well, it can be achieved even with,
if you could paint like a picture, you know, no one's going to say that you're not very good.
You know, if you could paint realism, right, and that's taught.
I mean, that's strictly – paint by numbers, by the way, is a way to start, right?
But, yeah, that's why I've always encouraged weather work, because it's one of the things that is, say, quote-unquote,
no pun intended, ethereal.
It's a non-physical quality, like alchemy, to achieve it.
But I found that it's one of those things that it's kind of in between alchemy and learning to be a good painter,
that if you get enough how-to's under your belt and you practice a little bit, you will be able to work the weather.
I think you and I – I'm not going to put you on the spot, but I will.
You and I, back in the original ONG, under Danny Romero, he said his brother was visiting him
and there was going to be rain in Washington State all week, remember?
And he asked me to please stop the rain and make it sunny for a couple of days, and you were like, what?
And then next week we get on the call and Danny's like, thanks very much.
It was sunny for three days, even though the forecast had half-inch of rain every day.
Well, there's another gentleman that we both mutually encountered named Larry.
I don't know if you – we don't need to give his last name.
Yeah, he got it from one of my people that I was a student of, the Greek.
And he – Larry, that's the guy that'd go fishing and he didn't like the wind,
and we told him, put this tube on the boat and the wind will go away, and he said it worked.
That guy?
Right, that guy.
Yeah, okay, got it.
Yeah, because he didn't speak with me on that.
Briefly, maybe once on something for a minute, he was working around with some electronic stuff,
electrical stuff, I remember.
And I would suggest that that was someone who – I got into weather work who was on calls with me about it,
and he says, no, I'm not keen on that.
I'm not keen on that at all, and one day he had problems with too much rain,
and I said – he says, you know, I'm not keen on the weather, but I'm tired of this rain.
If that stuff works that you're talking about, I'll be willing to try it,
and he became really good at it, and he's the one that got in touch with Larry.
Oh, okay.
I thought that you had directly done it, but okay, either way, it was indirect.
I've got about maybe 100 people now since I started doing – I was vocal about the weather work around 2004,
so I could say two decades.
And also Trevor James Constable, I was – I would speak to him more than twice a week in the last few years of his life,
and he sent me a couple of – well, two packages of his notes and boxes that I have here.
He's a – I think one of the greatest weather worker people.
So anyway, I just wanted to bring up the weather thing because there are certain things that would seem ultra-fantastic
and, quote-unquote, ethereal or alchemic, but you can access technically pretty well.
In other words, the guide will get you there.
The guide doesn't always get you there with doing other things, right?
So there is – cooking is another one.
That's why I think I've been thinking about it more and more, should get into the cooking,
because 99% of it is the approach and discernment.
And of course, you have to have the tools working well, and you have to understand sanitary conditions.
I've noticed that most people that always complain that they have stomach aches or colds and things like that,
if I were to visit their abode, I'd notice they had very poor hygiene.
And it doesn't mean like flies and shit everywhere.
It just means they just didn't know what they were doing in the kitchen.
Right.
So, yeah, so maybe the food talk, because I'm always developing food
and the way to be a very good cook or chef, the things that are required.
Let's say if you wanted to be the best chef in the world, it's not just the training,
but you also have to have the best sense of taste and smell.
It's taste and smell that makes a good chef.
And when people say they learn how to cook because they went to cooking class,
well, I hate to tell you, but if you go to cooking class, let's say French Culinary University,
and you want to stake your life on becoming a chef and nobody hires you,
you end up becoming a cooking instructor.
So you're not really learning.
We used to joke around with those who can't do teach, right?
Right.
So, yeah, you're not going to learn anything from a cooking class.
Well, you might, but not the fundamentals on how to progress and make it a lifelong endeavor
where every time you make something, it's better and better and better.
And I don't mean like you forgot something on the stove and burned it,
but I mean developing the skill and, yeah.
Okay, what I wanted to also bring up was the world that we live in generally,
you have to remember, well, you know how I always say food, clothing, shelter,
make that the basis of your existence here.
Some people think it's really simple-minded,
but if you're trying to up the quality of your food, clothing, and shelter, it's not readily done.
You have to change the way you approach things, your lifestyle,
the way you think about, let's say, shopping, right?
You have to change the way you prepare things, the place where you live.
How do I improve the quality?
I don't know how, so you have to learn more about that, right?
So it puts you on all these tangents and adventures,
and on your way of learning how to improve the quality of your food, clothing, and shelter,
you will learn so many other things, right?
Just imagine how all-encompassing that is.
Just let's say you want to improve the quality of your shelter and you're in a building.
How many aspects are there to a building, right?
You got floors, you got walls, electrical, plumbing, right, all this stuff, right, architecture.
So you're going to have to get familiar with architecture and energy and all that.
Food, the same thing.
There's all the substances and seasons.
And then clothing, you know, what rules do you live by?
Like, for example, the covenant that I live by, avoid mixed fabrics, right?
So you get 90% cotton, 10% polyester, right?
Now it doesn't mean organic fibers only because 100% polyester is fine, you see.
And the interesting thing is, though, polyester with nylon is fine also
because they both come from the same stock, basically, right?
Okay.
So synthetic weaves are, I tend to say, are fine but not too distinct.
Like when you mix wool and cotton, well, one is animal and one is plant.
But you also see cotton and linen rarely, but don't mix that either, you see,
because they're very distinct, where the polyester and the nylon seem distinct
but they're almost from the same batch.
They're polymers, basically.
Actually, one, I think, is a monomer.
But no, they're both polymers.
Sorry.
So, you know, you get into all these things.
So you get, see, right now we just said, what do you wear in clothing?
I didn't bring up anything regarding fashion, did I?
No, not at all.
Not at all.
See, so it gets really, it gets, it's a very, they're all wide subjects.
But this is the thing.
What you will encounter, and this is a thing that I want to add to food, clothing, shelter,
is that man's world as we see it now under the influences that he's been under for,
let's say, specifically for the past 500 years, specifically, but further back from that,
is the introduction of toxicity in what man does.
It's almost like a self-sabotage but it's influenced externally.
And I mean, so when man tries to do something, right, it turns things toxic, like with energy, right?
So we develop these machines, industrial revolution, we need to power them with a prime mover,
usually steam, coal, oil, gas, toxic, right?
We just went over religion, right?
You have all of these ancient texts that impart wisdom and it becomes toxic, right?
You have people going to war over it, whatever, you know, you want to get into it.
Medicine, there's a need for medicinals and which medicine, okay, forget about talking about medicine being toxic.
Which one is not toxic?
Put it that way, right, that you get, you know, mainstream, right?
Very few.
So, you know, you see the politics.
Okay, so if politicians are part of government, okay, which politician is not toxic, right?
So research, you want to research things.
What kind of information are you going to get if you go on the internet now?
Yeah, what are your materials you're researching with?
Right, the other thing I've said for, I've been saying this for two decades and it's just from first-hand experience
that everything that could have been known was already known by the 1890s.
So, and anything past 1913 or 1920 is, you see the censorship coming in.
So what you're doing is trying to seek a balanced life with food, clothing and shelter and evolving interesting,
developing new traits in the way you behave on this planet, let's say.
Most of the time now you're going to be encountering not just on what to develop and how to improve
but to avoid and abate toxicity that's in the system.
Like, for example, with energy.
I have no problem directly with what they call fossil fuels, which are abiotic fuels, basically.
We've gone over this.
You know, like oil.
It's called petroleum.
Petro meaning rock and oleum meaning oil because it comes from rocks.
Just like corn oil comes from corn and olive oil comes from olives.
It's not a fossil fuel and all that, right?
Right.
Okay, there's nothing wrong with using that if the machines and apparatus that you're feeding it in as a fuel
are hyper-efficient, very, very, very efficient.
When you put $100 worth of gas, gasoline in an automobile, engine-driven wagon really,
only $20 or $30 of that gas is going to moving the car.
The other $70 to $80 is to heat up the engine, makes heat, right?
So all of these things, toxicity, if you understand medical,
when they're trying to pass a drug is how well does it go against placebo,
and many of them are almost as good as placebo.
So why would you take something that has side effects that could kill you
where you could take a sugar pill and have the same result?
Right.
So this is another big opening that you have to consider.
And the other thing to consider is just to bounce over to the input into our bodies.
You ever hear of people saying you need to detox?
Yeah.
Right.
Well, combine that with what they're saying about getting stuff out of your system
with what we've said about how the body does everything by induction.
It has nothing to do with you have bad chemicals in your body you need to flush out.
It's not physical, the detox.
It's energetic.
In other words, yes, those things will appear and manifest when you excrete things,
but it's not because you put them in your body.
They went through your intestines, and now they're in your blood.
No, your body created those things.
So maybe in the future we'll get more into what a real detox is and how it really works,
but once you understand on the front end how it gets into the body in the first place,
that word detox goes away and becomes something else, becomes more of a healing modality.
So I think we covered quite a bit on this one, number 12.
Yeah, absolutely.
Absolutely.
We started with pledges and kind of ended with the introduction.
Detoxing.
Yeah.
Of the idea of what a real detox might be.
Right.
Yeah.
So yeah, that's a fairly wide spectrum there, and of course government and a few other things
along the way got analyzed a bit, I think.
Yes?
Yep.
Yep, and I think, yeah, I think we're good on 12, and we'll see what happens on the lucky 13.
There you go.
Maybe we'll have to talk about that numerology on 13.
Yeah, let's try that, yeah.
Let's do that too.