Rated Y sonic event 9090 Wow, didn't didn't even think we were going to take it this far,
but it has gone thus far.
Yeah.
Anyway, here we are again.
And I got to begin with some of the stuff that we've been communicated with about in
recent days, but also think about the past, present, future.
By the way, all of that is simultaneous.
After all, all you actually have is today.
And how are you doing today?
Greek?
I'm doing all right.
Trying to get my voice back.
My team, my energy is is not being held in the body as well as it could be.
Also, it's interesting.
I had an associate.
He's 10 years younger than me.
Passed away this weekend.
Oh, yeah.
We had health health issues.
I used to joke around.
We keep eating out.
It's going to kill you.
I only did.
And I spoke to him two days before and he didn't didn't really have any signs that, you know,
he was ready to exit.
So but anyway.
Well, you know how eating out usually kills you, right?
It's because you pick the wrong woman.
But anyway.
OK, I'm trying to do your salacious joke moment.
You know, I love this.
Yes.
Listen.
Yeah.
My my lascivious comment for the show.
OK.
Anyway.
And now you have to ask how they like it.
I don't think you're good at it.
Right.
Let's see.
Let me just bring that up real quick.
Yeah, please.
What's this with women?
Think that all women think they're good at sex.
Right.
This is crazy.
I've noticed this.
But not all of them.
Some of them.
Most of them.
I say that I've known think they're good at sex.
That's ridiculous.
No one is you.
It's about communication.
Right.
So anyway.
Absolutely.
Speaking of that.
I think the great philosopher Eddie Murphy actually codified this entire concept perfectly
when he said that, you know, sometimes if you haven't been eating for a long, long time
and somebody gives you a saltine, you are grateful.
Oh, my God.
That's the greatest saltine I ever did have.
And all that.
And he related this to the idea that sex is great with somebody when you first meet him.
And then every once in a while you roll over after a little bit of time and go, man, I
just had some regular old crackers.
But anyway.
Yeah, that's kind of.
Yeah.
It's still relevant.
I get it.
Yeah, I get it.
And why is it relevant to this?
Well, you know, the one thing that's been effing us all one way or another, the way
I see it and and definitely fucking up the planet as we go, came up in chat right recently.
The construction of the church, the fact that it's a female in a sexual position and the
portal, the opening, which you can go in and out of is the back view.
You've got two openings.
Yeah.
The back.
Is the rear view.
Yeah.
The front door and the back door on the same side.
Well, I always thought of it as there's always a window above the door in most churches directly.
So you got the two that are close to the back door.
But it's a window.
Yep.
Well, depending on your perspective, they're either right next to each other or they're
on opposite sides of one another.
By the way, your voice sounds fairly young at this point.
I don't hear it with the yin energy, which would be no, no.
It's tough.
Ever since I had the circus flu, I call it the circus because Wendy Blades, the niece,
she's a sword swallower.
You can look her up.
Right.
And we look actually, Linda, the wife, said that we have a race was my sister's daughter.
OK.
But the circus, by the way, it's tied all together because church means Cirque, which
is Cirque like Cirque de Soleil.
Yes.
When I was speaking with her, there is a very high venerance and reverence to the circus,
by the way.
In other words, it's very much like speaking to someone that's in a clergy, not different.
In other words, the sentiment is the same and it should be because it is.
Well, they hold a specific place in society.
They are observed by a lot of people on very special occasions.
There's high emotion connected to it.
Usually there are pseudo supernatural supernatural suggestions connected to it, because what
do you often see?
Magic tricks, death defying stuff.
So they don't even have to do they've gotten so lazy.
They don't do that anymore.
Well, I'm thinking of the circus that I did see when I was a kid a long, long time ago.
Yeah.
They don't do that stuff anymore because all you need is one.
I think back.
OK.
When you were a kid, right, let's say back in the 60s, 70s and 80s, it was common to
hear of fatalities at the circus, you know, based on the performers.
You have one fatality now and they'll shut it down.
They'll shut down the entire venue.
I mean, not just your venue, but all the circuses now are bad.
Right.
You see how I'm going with this.
OK.
So, yeah, supposedly there's a video of the of the circus.
This one is Paranormal Circus, it's called.
There was an accident and I looked at the video of it.
That's not an accident.
The guy just kind of like flipped his toe on the tightrope and grabbed it and got back
on.
That's not an accident.
When I say here accident, it was like, wasn't the Willenda brothers or whatever one of them?
Actually, they were doing these acrobatics without without a safety net.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
Hit the deck and bite it.
Right.
One of the flying Willenda's did die.
I think.
Was it the 60s or 70s?
It could have been even later.
Was it later?
Wow.
OK.
Let's look at it.
I'm in front of the laptop right now.
Well, you go ahead and look it up.
But I remember that.
And also there is yet again the high tension of the animal training.
Right.
Which is, in my mind, a bit cruel.
But, you know, with the tiger, what do they call them?
Lion tamers.
Right.
Mm hmm.
There's always this let's play around with the idea that somebody could die during this
event.
Or at least that's the way it used to be, whether it was.
Yeah.
You're right.
Sixty two Detroit performance.
Sixty two.
OK.
I thought it was the 60s.
And yeah.
And that stuck with people for years and years.
That one death, by the way, that was like the don't forget the flying Willenda died.
And you know, what's odd about that to me is that, you know, in the 70s, again, there
were people trying to walk tightropes in between skyscrapers a little more often than you see
in today.
Yeah.
Petit Philippe, whatever his name was, Philippe Petit or something.
Shot an arrow.
Yeah.
That was.
He tried to do it on his own.
Shot an arrow.
But they pulled a rope and pulled the cable.
They stop it.
They said, hey, wait a second.
Let's just do a sanctioned event.
Right.
Yeah.
So, yeah.
He didn't know that there were nukes underground.
But well, yeah.
And a lot more death defying than even the the antics of what one of the most popular
iconic guys to get on a Harley in that time period.
Evil can evil.
Right.
Yeah.
That was a big deal.
I remember I was sweating.
The evil can evil bicycle.
They I think it was Huffy made an evil can evil bicycle and so it had the stick shift
like the Ross.
All right.
The one with the banana seat sticks.
Yeah.
It was really dangerous.
I remember once borrowing a bike and falling off in the six ships got me right where I,
you know.
Oh, yeah.
Right.
The family jewels.
You know, the prestigious thing that might not be so glamorous to ride if you actually
try to ride it anyway.
Why are we talking about the circus here?
Greek?
Well, it does.
Well, because it's like the church.
The church.
Sure.
It's the same.
It's the same thing.
It's a derivation.
Yeah.
What came first.
Right.
The chicken or the egg.
The circus or the church.
The circus.
Well, I would think the temple to Searcy is what came first.
Right.
Sure.
Yeah.
But the entire thing about the bread and circuses is still around.
And by the way, speaking of bread and circus, I've been trying to engage people in conversation
and just to get feedback.
And I'll do this with the listeners here.
What do you think?
OK, this is a total segue, but we'll go back to these subjects in plural.
Total segue.
But there is no scarcity in the world for anything.
Everything is there's more stuff than there are people to use that stuff.
And I'm not saying being wasteful.
So there's no scarcity.
What there is, though, is they've convinced everyone that they need to use what they call
their fiat currency.
More specifically, fiat currency to get that stuff.
So how about bypassing the fiat currency and developing a more cogent, a more a system
that's more palatable of trade and barter, not necessarily barter, because there's trade
on alternative trade, right, where you don't have to have.
Right.
Because, OK, when you're using they've got everyone using the digital money and all that
stuff.
Right.
OK.
So when it comes time to like the subs here, how would they sub, right?
If you're not using digital currency, right?
How will it be?
Another way.
Right.
So just to show you how prolific that we're working with.
This is the thing that everyone is really stuck in and they don't notice it.
I'm not over grandizing or adding more importance than needed or overemphasizing the quote unquote
money system.
But you're at a point right now socially that you are stuck in a system that could kill
you literally.
I mean, it will if there was no electronic money transfers or cash, how would people
get along?
And I mean that literally, how would they get what they need?
The state of confusion, right, would be so high.
And this was since 1929, because in 1929, if you looked at even old black and white
movies when they show a corporate office, like where the CEO or the boss was always
in the scene, somewhere in the office other than the big desk and the chair off to the
side was a tall, almost human size height safe in every corporate office.
But why?
Because at the end of the week, the workers would get a slip, they'd sign it and they'd
get their their pay, right, salary or wages in cash.
They didn't go to the banks with checks.
As a matter of fact, back in those days, if you gave someone a check, they thought you
were pulling a stunt on them.
Financial fraud of some kind, which it is financial fraud.
But so what they did was they stopped the cash on every week or every month or whenever
it periodically the someone in the office would go to the bank and get the payroll from
the bank.
Right.
Well, what what happened during the depression is the bank said, sorry, we have no cash.
Kind of like, you know, they did the fake coin shortage past couple of years.
Right.
By the way, with the fake coin shortage, if there was a coin shortage, you'd bring your
coins to the bank and they would give you five, 10 percent over what you gave them.
Right.
So there was no coin shortage.
Yeah.
Because I called the bank.
I said, coin shortage.
Yeah, we have coin shortage.
So if I bring you a dollar's worth of coins, how much are you give me back a dollar?
Well, there's no shortage because that's the bad.
Think about it.
That's terrible economics.
Right.
Because when there's a shortage, the price goes up.
So anyway.
Yeah.
What they did was no cash available.
So the workers didn't get for the first week or two.
Let's say you worked where you made electric motors.
Right.
So they gave you a few motors to take with you and barter.
So the guy, one of the guys, you know, of 100 guys that work in the electric motor factory
goes down to the grocery store and get some milk, flour, bread, whatever, and puts it at
the counter, ready to check out, let's say, and gives him an electric motor.
And he says, no, I don't want an electric motor for this.
The store or the grocery store owner says, why?
He says, I've got 15 of them here.
What am I going to do with any more electric motors?
Get out of here.
You see?
So there's a problem here that we are experiencing now, not because I'm not talking about factory,
but just generally, how would you get along if all if the Internet went down?
Right.
The Internet went down a and then B, there was no cash either.
How would you get along?
And the answer to that right now is you won't.
There is no system in place.
There's no backup system like, you know, again, let's segue again.
OK, the Internet works on actually knew one of the people that knew one of the people
that started the Sun Microsystems that did installations for all the routers that literally
were cables put underground, like under manholes.
Right. Back in the 80s to get all this ready.
And it was called the Janet system.
It was the joint academic joint academic network.
Janet, do you remember that?
No. Yeah. Well, that was piggybacked on the on the Internet.
Right. Yeah. Right.
So with with that system in place, where was I going with this?
The Internet being put in place, relying on such a system and then relying on dial up.
Right. But now there's no more analog dial up.
It's all digital. Right. So let's say the entire digital system goes down.
Can we make an Internet based on ham radio?
With a series of cells, you know, ham radio people carrying.
So how would you do extra long frequencies, which is ham radio, that extra extra long
like military, but they're long frequencies.
How would you carry your data on ham radio, which is very autonomous, very independent,
isn't it? Well, I talked about this on my show, believe it or not.
And, you know, covering the financial thing.
First of all, the coin shortage is just stupid because the fact is that long before anybody
even mentioned the words coin shortage, they weren't making as many coins as people
thought. Anyway, the stuff didn't exist anyway.
It doesn't matter if it exists because we've got a little different.
Coins don't represent a lean coin.
You know, coins don't are not notes.
Right. But the way they do that is by putting material that is worth less than the coin.
They have a problem when the material in the coins in your pocket has more value than the
coin states.
Right. If nickel went to, you know, five thousand dollars an ounce, you'd have a big
problem, you know, because there's very little nickel in it.
It's it's basically well, whatever zinc and copper.
It's inverted. Right.
But it's the same amount of material.
The penny and the nickel are the same thing.
It's just they're inverted. Right.
Right. It's kind of a penny silver.
Right. Yeah. But mostly pennies aren't copper either.
Anyway, they're either zinc or a composite.
But it's all it's mostly zinc with a coat.
It's the coating. So, you know, like that.
What is that gold coin? It's supposed to be a dollar.
Where is it that after that black lady?
What's it? Well, they made a bunch of them.
They made a Sacagawea that was gold colored.
They made the presidential coins that were gold colored.
And there's no coin.
It's OK. So you brought up.
OK, let's go back to the coinage.
Do you think coinage is the answer?
And then how do you get a coin over through the mail, I guess?
I don't know. Well, these things need to be considered.
Yeah, that's problematic, because I'll tell you something that happened to me
just this week is I was supposed to get a bunch of half dollars in the mail.
And, you know, I ended up with an empty package when it got to my doorstep.
No way. Yeah. Somebody stole
19 JFK half dollars that were sent to me.
Anyway, it's packaged very well, then.
Well, it was packaged pretty well, but you could feel it.
And, you know, it wasn't the best.
Yes, you should never.
Yeah, you should never be able to detect by feel alone.
I have someone that worked at the post office.
What they do if they think something is valuable.
They have a very fast conveyor, by the way, very fast.
But it changes enough hands that they radio down the conveyor belt.
And what they do is they turn around because they have camera surveillance
and they bump it with their elbow as it falls off the conveyor.
And another guy kicks it with his foot to the other side of the building.
And then later on their break, they pick it up.
You see how it's done.
Yeah, something looks like an accident.
So there's no obvious look like it's hard to track
where the hell actually happened to it.
Exactly. Yes.
Because even though they photograph, by the way, they photograph
almost every piece of mail as it moves.
I don't know if people know this,
but literally there is a recorded photograph of different stops
that your mail makes usually. OK.
Even if it's not meant to be tracked, doesn't have it.
Everything has a tracking number, but you don't have access to it
unless you pay extra. Sure.
The point is that everything is actually tracked.
So these guys who want to steal mail directly have had to become innovative
because too many of them got busted.
That's right. It has to look like an accident.
And then the person monitoring it is not going to go ahead.
And unless there's an independent audit, which probably won't happen.
But this has been happening for a long time using this methodology. Right.
And you never want to make things look like they do
when you're sending them anywhere anyway.
Like, for instance, if you take and you make, you know,
you wanted to send some cash notes in the mail,
what you would do is make sure that it's definitely not shaped like a like a dollar
or, you know, in that general shape.
And also don't allow it to look like a greeting card,
because a lot of mailmen will turn around and guess what?
Sure. Accidentally, you know, rip your card open
to see if there's something in there that they can cash easily or if there's cash.
I wouldn't blame it directly at the at the general group of mailmen and all that.
I think it's just a very small group in there.
And it's also intelligence agencies seeing what they could get away with, of course.
Right. Well, there's also that.
But it's a common thing that is occurring a lot more.
And yeah, sure. Which is the pitfall.
If you want to grade the quality of a nation, it's ability to, you know,
work is great.
Their postal system.
I knew someone. Well, back in the world, we're doing some business.
We had a post box in Mexico. Right.
And I went down there.
There were literally cobwebs and the place was dirty.
There was litter inside the post office.
Keys didn't work for post office boxes.
It was. Yeah, it was.
There's no uniforms. They don't wear uniforms.
It was really like a ragtag whatever.
So Mexico, if you want to make yourself look better,
get a better postal service anyway.
Yeah. Well, I've described to people before because I went to Italy
when I was very young and I mailed a letter
that didn't get here until two months after I came home.
There you go. Because it was stuck in the Italian mail system.
Why? Because the country was so corrupt
that their their their mail system was nearly paralyzed.
And I'm told that it's, you know, a little better today.
But I don't think it's a lot better.
It's EU regulations.
So overstep their national stuff might have been an upgrade, actually, for them.
But yeah, exactly. Yeah.
But anyway, back to so many things, sex, church.
Well, back to the currency for trade.
Yeah. So back to the coins, which I kicked off this mail discussion
by telling you I lost some coins.
Here's the reality with the coins, though, is that they present
a different kind of instability issue for value being exchanged.
Clearly, they're not just worthless paper. Right.
But at the same time, they're not paper at all.
And there's they don't state that they are lean either. Right.
The banknotes state that they're lean because they're not redeemable.
But they're still subject to manipulation based on the fact
that if they manipulate the value of the components that go together
to make there is no value, it's deliberate.
There is no value in the components.
Well, yeah, but since it was silver.
But there's some value to copper.
I mean, it's not great.
There's so little copper there.
Cut a penny in half.
Well, right. But they used to be they used to be made out of copper.
See what we're talking about now, though, you used to.
Coin was usually precious metal. That's right.
Yeah. Right. So, you know, what I what I want to just bring forward
is the thinking process on how if the system went away,
which it won't, by the way, will not collapse.
You'll have faults, you know, where everything's like the lockdowns,
you know, where things stop.
But it won't collapse.
Not until not until other things collapse.
Well, very much like plate tectonics and earthquakes.
Occasionally things will shake up.
Sometimes stuff will get destroyed or fall down,
but it doesn't completely destroy the place entirely.
Yeah. Yeah. But in the meantime, while the stuff is available, how about OK?
You know, I didn't even have to go through all that,
but I didn't see I didn't want to bring up cryptocurrency.
But cryptocurrency is doing that because, you know, we take Bitcoin, right?
That's all you got to say. Right.
I mean, it's places and right.
They even have Bitcoin ATMs and whatever.
So that's not what I'm talking about, because Bitcoin is still part of.
Obviously, it's an intelligence operation, right?
I mean, it's pretty obvious anything that is publicly known
that makes thousands of percent, quote unquote, profit is intelligence.
And if it's not, it won't last very long.
They take it over.
Right. And clearly, this is a beta test right now going on to see exactly
what happens when they come out with the so-called legitimate, you know,
CBDC, the replacement digital currency.
Sure. The government's not time.
It's just not time for it yet.
But eventually the governments will say, you know what?
Let's switch all the digital stuff and so on.
And of course, a lot of people are talking about that.
But it already is, Chuck.
It is all digital.
Well, OK, there's so there's what?
Three. There's less than you stole my punchline, but that's OK.
Go ahead. That's OK. Go ahead.
I'll stop. I'll yield.
No, no, no.
Listen, I have no problem with you stealing my punchline
because I've been screaming about this for a long time that, you know, people go,
look, Bitcoin is the future.
It's obvious.
And, you know, and blockchain technology.
And I go, yeah, but here's the problem.
I guarantee you that it's being rolled out to replace the stuff you have now
because you know what? It'll be less of a hassle.
You don't have to have a minting facility, right?
You can just do it with a computer and a story.
Couple of built on scarcity.
They only did so many. Right.
Oh, yeah. But once you see where it's a natural system,
there is no scarcity to money.
They can always mine more, make more the scarcity.
OK, well, just like you said, just go further.
You said with all with all resources, right, that the scarcity is artificial.
It is part of the manipulation. Sure.
It doesn't mean that here's the problem with the money, the way they do
the fiat currency, it's you cannot have infinite credit creation in a finite world.
Right. The world is finite, but it is abundant.
There's a difference between no scarcity because of abundance
and then finite versus infinite.
See, their credit system is based on infinite credit creation,
but it's a finite world.
And this is a parallel discussion to abundance and no scarcity.
When I say there's no scarcity, I mean there is abundance, not infinite.
Right. Because there's always going to be a finite number of people.
There's never the right.
You can't say there's an infinite number of people. It's finite.
So in other words, no matter how big that finite is,
the abundance will prevail to a degree.
But we have a system that mathematically works on infinite credit creation.
So now we have a bigger problem, which we'll discuss on a future thing.
The thing I want to put up is how do you structure?
Because it's not the barter and trade.
People could do that.
And, you know, that's very simple notion.
But how do you do it in an organized way?
We we don't have chaos. Right.
Well, you're aware of some of the efforts to do this, I'm sure.
Like the you know, the centralized notes that they came up
regarding your labor being transferred to your in Buffalo.
And also in Africa, they have the the Ubuntu project,
which I'm sure you've heard of, which is, you know,
the literal exchange of your labor skill.
So like, let's just say it's like the operating system.
I think it's spelled the same, isn't it?
Well, I want to scale a rater. Right.
So I come to you and I say, look, Greek, I grow rice.
So I'll tell you what I'll do.
How many bags of, you know, that fine rice that you like.
If you like the quality of rice, I grow.
How many pounds of fine rice would you accept in exchange for your scale?
Sure. And then I stock the rice and then I have to fight.
But then you'll have spending all the time, all your time
trying to figure out who is going to use your various inventories for trade.
You see. So that's where the inefficiency part comes in.
No, it could be. I get that.
That doesn't work, by the way.
I've considered that, you know, because if I OK, you want
and then someone else gives me something else, gasoline and have tanks of gasoline.
I have to. So instead of working on the scalerator,
I have to find someone to buy the rice and the gasoline or trade that.
So then you lose.
Then we go into another situation.
So how do we do it without being losing time efficiency?
OK, you you get you get you see where this is going.
So the main thing is, how do you set this up in a gradual, systematic way?
And also, how do you replace the Internet with ham radio?
Because I don't see any other.
But would you say infrastructure that could that could be as independent
as ham radio if you other than carrier pigeon or.
Well, I've talked about that on my show a bit, too.
And I mean, one of the interesting ideas was to create a modular situation
where you take something like the independent small.
And there's an independent small and radio wave band band wave
that's out there that you don't require an FCC license for or whatever.
Sure. If I set one up in my backyard and somebody within, say,
10 miles of me sets up another one in their backyard,
we now have an interconnected broadcast system.
Well, here's the thing with the FCC.
If you read it very carefully, it's commercially based.
Yes. What it does is it enforces that you might potentially infringe
on someone's ability to do commerce who has a license. Right.
Right. It's about interference.
But you don't need it.
You don't have to get a FCC license if you are not interfering
and also rebut the production of the presumption of possibly interfering.
There's a way to do that, by the way.
Oh, yeah. But these independent small, you know, transmitters
I'm talking about are automatically already there as something that has.
Oh, I get it.
Regulatory.
This is still something that has to be brought up in a see, even you and I
discussing it, discussing this is not our, you know, the parlance in our.
We can't really parlay because it's not our field, let's say specifically.
But there is no simple way.
Right. It's not like, hey, get a computer.
When you get a computer, download Skype and we'll talk.
You see how easy that is?
Well, it's only even if you don't even if you don't have a computer,
you got it already laid out. Right.
Well, but this isn't bad if you let me just carry on with the concept.
Right. If you go for the 10 mile idea or the five mile idea,
it simply means all you have to do is create a contact
with somebody who's five miles or less away.
Yeah, sure. Like the cell phone transmitter.
And if we all agree to be on a singular,
you know, one of these open frequencies, then we can create a network
as large as the entire North American continent without a problem.
Yeah. But only, you know, a thousand watts at a time.
No, that's fine.
Actually, you might want to use earth transmission.
So you're not using it.
You know, you're using two layer occurrence, the current electricity
that exists in the earth.
That's not hard to do.
If you look at the Tesla patents, ask people who have done it.
All you got to do is follow the patent.
So when he shows a certain kind of copper wrapped around a block of wood,
don't go to Home Depot and get a piece of plastic with copper wire.
You got to, you know, build it just like it is in the patent.
And guess what? It'll work. Right.
So this is not. Yeah, we don't need the power aspect of it.
Yeah, I wouldn't.
By the way, even now, if you ask me to set up a radio system quickly,
I wouldn't use it.
I would use the earth energy.
But theoretically, the reason why I present the AM version of it
is because it gives the consumer
very easy access, because all they have to do is find something
that accepts AM radio transmission.
And you have now.
It's getting harder every day.
Well, yeah, I want I wanted to go get a portable radio
just for a portable radio sake, and I can't find them in stores.
They're still pretty common, to be honest with you.
A lot of places.
I mean, I can go to a store called Roses, which is right down the street.
I don't know if you have those in Arizona, but
Roses, Walmarts, places like that often have some electronics
somewhere in there that is a freestanding radio receiver.
Alarm clock radio, I saw was the best at Walmart.
Well, see, now there's alarm clock radios.
And also when you go to like your family dollars and things like that,
usually in the electronics area, they have a couple of radios.
That place, Roses, has about I was at a family dollar.
Also, they had an FM converter,
but not a radio where you could put batteries in it and you're off you go.
And it was an FM broadcaster converter.
You know, it's attached to the end of a.
Cassette tape that you put in a car.
Yeah, so maybe I don't know.
Yeah, no, it's just Tucson where I'm at.
It is kind of accessible.
Like there are literally 25 different devices for AM reception.
I did this as a survey at Roses, about five at the Walmart,
about five or six at Family Dollar, about five or six at Dollar General.
I'm just saying it in general in the cheap.
They're still sort of available.
Their store is still sort of available, plus secondary market.
You go to a flea market, I guarantee you can find a radio.
Now, I know what your problem is,
because I went looking for a boom box and had trouble there.
You know, what I wanted is something that had a cassette, a CD and a radio.
So guess what? I just want like a group.
I mean, you know, what would be what I would want is a Grundig World Radio.
Oh, no, I love it.
Yeah. Grundig makes a world radio and it does.
Yeah, no, I loved my radio with the with the minimum of seven bands
where you have, I think it's five, five shortwave, one longwave, AM and FM,
although they call it microwave on the on the world radios.
But no, but see, there you go again.
And by the way, you can get a Grundig.
You just go to Jeff Bozo's Amazon.
I'm sure they're up there.
That's another thing is if you search on Amazon, I promise you,
you can find radio receivers of some type and they might be real simple
or little throwbacks to the transistor.
But I'm just saying is that the technology is cheap still.
For somebody who wants to receive it, if we, you know, created this network
and theoretically created a nice large web that that covered a lot of territory,
then you don't want to lead it with the intention that you want it as a backup.
But what I'm saying is if people just start talking about it,
it will come. It will.
It will somehow find a ground where everyone will do it.
OK, you don't you want.
How do I say this? I've said it before.
Any movement that's going to be successful has to be a leader of this movement.
Right. Oh, yeah. No one. No group. No. Right.
It's just putting it the consciousness out there.
Just just like the the church is like that.
You know, people don't know.
This is well, that's why I go back.
Well, that's why I like the concept, though, of this interconnected radio thing,
because it's not dependent on any one leader.
It's not dependent on any one area except you're responsible for your immediate area.
Yeah. But how do you.
But how do you. OK, just like the money system.
Yeah. Everyone is familiar with barter trade, whatever.
But how do you do it without instilling chaos and also losing time
on your own to barter more to for the things you just bartered? Right.
And I've gone over what money is and how it works before.
And there's no reason to recap.
But let's just tie it back to the church.
You know, any church as known, the standard comes from the Vatican. Right. Right.
That's the standard.
They standardized it.
And any form of religion is also Vatican approved.
It doesn't matter what it is.
That's especially in the Christian ethos.
So it is OK.
It is centrally based, just like the central banks. Right.
Approve whatever.
But from Buddha to Mohammed, it's all approved by the Catholic Church in reality.
But go ahead.
But it's not the central part that's bad, because if you look back at ancient times,
they did have centralized economies when it came to monies and measurements.
You know, you'll if you no matter what, if you look at the ancient
megalithic sites, they use the same unit of measurement. Right.
In other words, divided by the same unit of measurement. Right.
Yeah. The inch.
So they did have they did use.
They have standard things.
That's that's basically a centralized agreement.
But the current centralized systems we have, no matter what they are,
are not beneficial. Right. Not beneficial at all.
Well, that's why a lot of people like the concept of a gold coin,
regardless of what you stamp on it or whatever.
You can quantify it because there's an acceptable rate
for what the weight of this is.
So so much of an hour. Right.
Not the numismatics.
Then there's the numismatic side.
But that's not what I would consider.
That's another thing.
But those are, you know, slightly less pure.
I'm talking about stuff that was made either 90 percent or higher
of the element, you know, because you have to.
Yeah. 90 percent is practical.
The reason why there's no pure silver or pure gold is because it's too malleable.
Right. Right.
So you always figure it out.
A 90 percent rate value, you know, whatever weight is.
It's the value of it isn't 90.
And that's why only collector coins come in the 99 percent,
you know, because of that, which, by the way, you know,
they're still making collector coins anyway, you know,
which shows me that silver is not really in a shortage.
If they have to do, you know, reprints of the old dollar style
just to release them for collectors.
And even though they say USA one dollar on them,
they're not even accepted as monetized currency.
No, because, you know, because you're in your receivership.
It is. It's really screwy.
It's really, you know, OK.
And the people that work with this stuff don't know anything about my you know,
I've said lawyers don't know any law.
Doctors don't know anything about the human body.
What is what do you mean?
I went to a doctor and he patched me up.
Well, the emergency trauma medicine, believe it or not, whatever they did for you.
If you knew a little bit about the human body, you would have got it.
You would have recovered three or four times faster on and on and on and on.
So it's just like they can print a legitimate, you know, silver dollar,
so to speak, but they're giving you a twenty dollar
value in silver or thirty dollar value in silver
on a coin that says it's got one dollar on it clearly says to me
nobody knows exactly what they're doing.
You know, I mean, yeah, they're the programming is really the most important.
Yeah. Yeah.
So and meanwhile, even though it's got a 20 or 30 dollar value,
you know, let's just say pragmatically and it says one dollar on it.
What is the value of the coin?
Go try to buy one. They're about 60 bucks a piece.
So as I said, you know, no, it's it's convoluted.
That's my point.
The money system is easy to figure out
if you just focus on what's been written about it
or what you can get someone to deliver about it, because
it's bizarre.
You see, even no matter how bizarre a notion is,
if it could be like rationally explained, anyone could understand it.
But what happens is people, the mainstream, which don't count
anyway, the majority don't count at all, meaning number.
They believe that the money system has to follow the rationale
that they've been taught to follow.
And anything that's outside that can't be true. Right.
The same look at the human body.
You know, they think they absorb things.
They think that, well, my the thing that I say about the human body,
of course, is that they they teach.
Even doctors think that the body is a pressurized filter bag. Right.
And it's not so anything outside of that can't be true.
So now we go into cognitive dissonance.
So. Well, right.
And it stands to reason that this is the way things are, because people,
even only a couple hundred years ago in this place they call the United States,
were arguing over whether there should be a debt based,
you know, fiat currency or a credit based fiat currency.
It's actually not debt based, debt based.
All right. Well, the reason they call it that was the public debate
because the receivership, the receivership came from that.
What it is, it's a an elastic currency, meaning it's value.
A rubber check, right? Elastic currency.
Yeah. And the supply of the money is increased by lending.
That's the most accurate way to do it.
But when you say debt based, it means that, yeah,
the U.S. could not pay its debt to the private bankers.
So they put the U.S.
into receivership that they could not get out of. Right.
But that's the consistent way that it's run now for what?
One hundred and eleven years since 1913, since 1933.
March the 9th.
Well, yeah, but the the not the receivership, but the situation
with the debt based, you know, currency being consistently
that came in in 1913.
Previous to that, we had two other centralized banks which were dissolved.
And they actually had the public argument between 1800
and that 1913 time that, you know, some people know about, say, Jackson.
You know, I think it was called the Bank of the United States, right?
There there was.
And there was yet another one previous to that, which had a similar sounding.
You know, they switch the names.
The key is when you hear of.
Yeah, well, it's just like the People's Democratic Republic
or the Republic Democratic People's Army or, you know, they switch.
Well, just like if state of Arizona, which is the Federal Reserve Corporation,
then you have Arizona state like New York state or state of New York.
There you go.
There's a big difference, right?
You enjoy it.
You have the state of Georgia, which is the corporate de facto.
But then you have Georgia state, right?
Just like when you speak about the sports you want, you'll say Georgia state.
Right. Right.
Which is the real side, which has nothing to do with the capital venture
that was the colony of Georgia.
If you take a look at the papers of incorporation that came along,
it still is still a colony in Georgia.
Well, it's funny how the nor a lot of the northern states
are still called called plantations. Right.
Yeah. But the southern states are called colonies.
Right. Still the colony.
But the idea was that it was actually initially a corporate venture.
It was a private business venture.
Really? That's right.
With a governor. Yeah. Yeah.
What was the captain of the ship? Yeah, exactly.
So but anyhow, as these things have transitioned, the monetary system
is a parallel, almost metaphorically.
And synonymous with with with the trajectory of all things, isn't it?
Because it's based on a falsified system
that really contains no value, but has scales for one to use
that allegedly transition what your labor into something
that is useful to make exchange in commerce.
So that you know, this ties in with a thought.
Someone said our humans made the you know, we're created
or made beings genetically modified, whatever genetically
occurred, occurring occurrences, not modified.
In other words, we were probably heavily modified
and then we put back together. Are we an experiment?
I'm saying, no, it's not.
Humans are not an experiment at all.
But the social systems and the programming that's put on us is an experiment.
You see the difference, right?
So we're a substantiated being that's as I keep saying.
Let's say with the medical system or everything else they're doing,
it's a testament to the robustness of the human body.
Well, the question regarding that, just a little bit off track,
but relevant to what you just said in your opinion.
And this is about your opinion here.
I want to know about it here.
Or if you have a definitive answer, I'll take that as well.
Something that is empirical.
Is it possible, though, that we indeed are not simply the result
of a well thought out plan, but maybe the surviving experiment?
At one point, maybe we were an experiment
and we did end up thriving and being the most robust of the experiments.
You know, much like people talk about how Neanderthals
existed at the same time that Homo sapien was here.
And Chromagnon, Chromagnon, excuse me,
whichever the overlap was in the evolutionary naming.
Yeah, the Chromags are not none of that.
Archaics does a pretty good job on it.
I don't endorse him, but he does a good job with the Chromagnon.
They, you know, because it's been since the 80s when they found
there was a big leak.
It was in a magazine, too. I forgot which one it was.
Those were the days where you went to a kiosk and there's magazines.
Yeah. One of the science.
Yeah. One of the popular science or popular mechanics or.
No, no, no, no.
It was a European magazine or an Australian magazine.
This is before the Australian magazine that's popular stuff.
These days, I was going to say I knew it was from a foreign country,
but I'm saying a magazine.
They were quite advanced, the Chromagnons.
Right. And one of our takes videos talks about how they had
they had suspenders, pants with buttons.
And yeah. Yeah.
But my point overall, though.
Yeah. But let's say the robustness.
No, what I'm saying is that we are not an experiment,
but what they make us do, what what we have become to do,
I should say, is experimental.
Well, I think the biblical text describes and you can correct me here if I'm wrong.
But to my mind, the biblical text describes the idea that we were a creation
made from something that existed here already.
So it almost sounds as though there was genetic manipulation
for lack of a better term here.
And maybe there was more than one version.
You know, here's test a test.
Oh, of course.
And my and the my and Papa Vu, they made men out of wood.
But there were two.
I think they were made of metal first, but all they wanted to do was rebel
and they were made out of wood.
They were too cruel to each other.
So then they took some earth material and made them flesh.
And it's perfect.
The only thing is they were easily subdued or good slave race.
Flesh work, because it was more empathetic and could work collectively
and not spend its time on so much cold cruelty.
But right. So, I mean, that's kind of preserved in the biblical text
that there was sort of.
Does that seem like that's experiment?
There's my question to you is, is that experimentation?
And are we just the best results of the experiment?
There's no sign anywhere of experimentation.
There's trials. It's very, very solid.
I've referred to cloning.
Cloning is not as complicated, complicated, just like the money system.
It's not complicated at all.
Money is drawn from your signature, right?
Well, I was very, very simple.
It's very it's a very easy thing to do.
I don't want to start cloning chicken skin in my kitchen to prove a point.
No, no, please don't.
It was. Yeah, but it is.
It's a very simple process.
It doesn't require anything technological, just the right stuff.
Like most things.
Well, fair enough. But no, it's I insist that we're not an experiment,
but the social programming is experimental.
Absolutely. Well, just before we get there, just in your opinion
or if you have a empirical observation that that handles this,
is it possible, though, that again, those those evolutionary ancestors,
again, for lack of a better term, could they have been the experiments
that led to us? No, no, no.
It was hybridization. No, they were already pretty solid.
OK, actually, we've been you know, we've been degrading and a very easy
go find some films from the 1930s or 40s
where people are walking on the street, right?
Just like a documentary, right?
Not actors and makeup.
And then go look at a current video of people just walking in the street.
A documentary and look at the comparative analysis is structure,
the body structure, the posture, regular people, clear degradation,
look very different from what we see today.
And it's not just the and I could point out, I could point out
exactly what you should be looking for, the size of the ear,
small ear, OK, large ears, strong constitution
means you were born with a strong constitution that you can withstand more
a smaller ear.
Right. In general, in terms of average size is a weaker constitution.
Right. OK, so you don't recover as well.
Right. Look at the brow bone size.
Right. I was just going to say, look at the chin placement.
Placement of the eyes is significant, too, because it appears to me
as though there is more diversity
regarding eyes being too close together or too far apart,
which makes them less efficient for triangulation.
Sure. The mongoloid type.
The well, that's when they're too close together.
Yeah. So you can definitely see that there has been a transition here.
Yeah. Degradation.
In other words, the degradation is that we're weaker, much weaker
in terms of constitution, meaning you can only take so much
before you just peter out emotionally and physically.
OK, so back to it, though, you're saying that the physicality of humanity
is changing, is changing.
It is not it didn't start out as an experiment, but the social orders
and different things that have been applied.
Oh, well, yeah, the change is degradation and it's
the mind follows the body rule, right?
Weak mind and the body gets weaker, right?
And vice versa, vice versa.
When it's at a certain point. Yeah. OK.
So continuing on with this experimentation regarding social order
and things like this, the monetary.
That's where the experimentation is.
Yeah. And it's clearly, as many have stated,
one of the most unquestioned things in reality, right?
I mean, people will question God, the nature of the universe, everything else.
But think about it very carefully as you grow up.
The majority of people never bother to question the why or how
of the monetary system.
It is more often than not accepted as this is just the reality of things.
This is money. This is what you need to get things.
Very basic principle.
You might learn as a child that is less questioned again
than even what what an atheist might say is an invisible man
is angels, is spirits, well, unseen.
Let's go back to the money.
Maybe we'll wrap it up with this. Sure.
The scarcity people feel that things are hard to get or things are not available.
It's not true.
It's the funds to get those things that is harder to get than itself.
So how do you bypass that? Right. Lawfully.
Right. But it's not not how do you let's do a step by step plan
and get people to do it. No, no, no, no, no.
Which bargain? How do you organize your mind?
OK, let me just say it this way.
This is an email experiment.
OK, but barter and exchange is perfectly lawful to my understanding.
I mean, if you know, there are other ways to do it, because if you are using
if you, let's say, have a mortgage or.
Or a debt and on a boat and you pay it off, use what people say,
you don't pay even the paper, you satisfy it, right?
Even though you think that you now there's no more, you've paid off the mortgage,
you've paid off using regular terms, even though, you know, it's satisfied the loan.
They still have an attachment to it because you're using their system to get it.
So they always hold on to that. Oh, yeah. Right.
So you have to clear that part first.
But a direct and then yeah, but a direct barter either for labor
or for material goods, I think is lawful.
As so long as you have an agreement.
I mean, yeah, but well, the way the system stands that if you're bartering
something that at one point was purchased using fiat currency, it's open.
It's subject to seizure.
Well, I don't want to talk about legal seizure now, not forceful seizure.
Right. But you have to understand how the lawful aspect works.
And most people don't.
But see, if you and I, I think lawfully, though, that this is acceptable in this
scenario. Let's talk about the exchange of labor for something
other than the fiat currency or something that is applicable to it.
Right. Maybe I could decide that
to have someone do the labor to rake my lawn is worth giving them lunch.
I feed them a meal.
No, no. We're talking more on a system that's more
anyway. I, you know, you know, like someone, let's say a dentist, like,
you know, we haven't exchanged any money ever.
You know, I've known each other for almost 20 years now or 18 years.
Right. And we go back and we're never exchanged any of the currency.
Right. Right.
And that's that's just a very narrow aspect.
I'm speaking more on a broadband aspect.
Right. Well, how would it be done?
Right. Not on a narrow.
You know, I'm just saying that on an individual basis.
If you know that doesn't that we can't.
Sorry, I don't want to go on the individual basis
because then the preference aspect comes in too much. Right.
In other words, personal preferences.
That's like one of the keys.
You know, you know, since we were
doing O and G back in the day was a 2015 or something.
Gosh, it's what did I always start saying?
It's like, no, I don't want people calling in because, you know,
there's a reason for it.
And this is the there's several reasons when.
And by the way, this ties in with a recent thing that popped up on YouTube.
I guess they know we're doing something called podcasting.
Now that I have a smartphone,
it seems like when we do a recording, I'll get a YouTube thing, you know.
Right. Anyway, so I can't figure out how to deactivate Siri completely.
But what they one of the things was how to things to not do
if you have a podcast is tell personal stories. Right.
Do you remember back in the O and G in 2015?
I said like when no one cares about your own personal habits or personal
unless it matters to them specifically. Right. Right.
So whenever you that's why this whole thing about opinion,
even if you look at what were the the most popular opinionated,
let's say, what would you call a television show, a radio show, whatever?
A podcast podcast don't really do it.
Were the ones that were the most circus like.
Like, what was it? The Jerry Springer show.
The there were others of the Sally McBee.
Was it Sally, Sally, Jesse Raphael and all that. Yeah.
Those are all personal, very personal stories,
but they quickly degraded into circus acts, didn't they? Right. Right.
Well, podcasts are very personalized, but because there is no argument on them.
Drama lacks the drama. Yeah, go ahead.
Yeah. But if you but if you let's say you're doing a sonic event,
no one really cares about the personal aspect of of anyone.
And I've I learned this and this goes back to the barter and the trade,
why I don't care about the what we can be barter trade on a personal level.
It's how do you create a system in people's minds?
Because it's always has to be a general thing,
because when I used to speak publicly in person with an audience of 50 people
at a breakfast club, they would ask me to speak. Right.
When when I would stand up at the dais at the podium to speak with a microphone,
the host would get up or and say, OK, Greek's going to speak for an hour.
And then you could ask questions.
And the moment the people were told they could ask questions,
they all perked up because they're like, oh, good,
I'm going to act like I'm listening and when I wait for him to shut up
so I can get the microphone and say what I want to say. Right. Right.
You see. So when is he going to shut up?
Right. So I can get the microphone.
So it's not about what you say, I say, he says, she says, how can
just put out a general this is on the email, but this is also something
that is so simple that people naturally default to.
How often I've seen this all my entire life.
Whenever you've been in a car and it gets a flat tire, everyone is super chill.
Everyone, whether the passengers are super chill.
Oh, we got a flat. OK, let's get the spare.
No big deal. Right.
Could you imagine? Oh, no, we got a flat.
What are we going to do?
No one does that. Right.
There's just all right. We got a flat.
Let's get the spare. Like, no big deal. You see what I mean?
Then there's no reason for personal drama.
There's no reason for what you think. I think. Right. Yeah.
It's just who's going to get down and do it.
So just like the spare time.