The Sonic Event 112, Rated Y, and here we are once again.
So, Greek, how are you doing out there in outer space?
Yeah, the usual question.
Yeah, we were maybe going to talk a little bit about space,
going back to previous discussions.
If there is a substrate that's being ignored, if and when there is,
which there has to be, because light, magnetism, and other things
wouldn't work if there was no substrate, because those things are
things that are shaking something else.
Not a permutation, but a perturbation.
When you perturbate, right?
When you vibrate.
Effectively, a conduit must exist in order for something to travel.
A medium.
Yeah, fluid.
It's beyond fluid.
Just like gases were called ether a while back.
In other words, mysterious spirits, right?
Because they weren't perceived.
Now, there is perception of the ether quite a bit to the point where,
by the way, I think I did mention there is no intelligent life in the
Midwest of the United States of America, right?
You certainly did.
Yeah, there was bad weather again a few days ago.
True enough.
Yeah.
You know, there was a storm chaser I was watching,
and they just sit there.
Oh, they were driving by a neighborhood storm chaser,
their window down real slow.
See that up ahead?
And the family on the side was like, I hope it doesn't come here.
I'm like, oh, my gosh.
Oh, my gosh.
All you need is go to your water heater, break off the stove pipe,
and you could dissolve all that.
Anyway, we've already established as a fact and the truth,
because I'm witnessing it, there is no intelligent life there.
But the ether is a substrate and a medium, what they call ether,
from the work of Wilhelm Reich and Trevor James Constable,
myself and others, because now those guys are dead.
Now it's people like me and a few others that are left to advance it.
And what I see on the Internet is more
and more people picking up on the old stuff, right,
what was done years ago, what I did 15, 20 years ago.
But they're not even close to what can be done with it.
Well, wouldn't part of that problem be because of a misunderstanding
about the order of things to begin with?
No, there's no misunderstanding.
It's not a misunderstanding.
You don't think so?
There's no understanding, no acknowledgment.
It's very easy to understand.
There's no acknowledgment.
Okay, but here's my question about this.
How about the fact that most people believe that things exist in this order?
There's space, and then you can put things in a space, right?
No space.
No, no.
Then they occupy that space, and that's our 3-D reality,
according to most people, right?
Isn't that the way most people think about it?
Well, let's just say this.
When there is a distance between the boundary layers of two objects,
regardless of what material it is, we call that space.
Yeah, okay.
But now we're thinking about weather work,
and that's always been addressing the ethers,
and it's a non-perceptible medium that everything, right?
So light is when this ether is perturbated, when it's vibrated.
Well, is it fair to say that it's imperceptible,
or is it fair to say that you just don't have the right lens for perception?
Because most people are working on the concept that displacement.
The way that science allows us to perceive stuff is perverted.
We have a perverted mentality, and that's a proper word.
It's juvenile and perverted, just like someone who was raised on junk food.
Well, fair enough.
If you give them good food, the spectrum of the parts of their taste buds that would actually,
the receptors that would be needed or required to get stimulated would not be stimulated.
Well, everything becomes tuned in an entirely different way
depending on what is fed to the organism.
Okay.
But my point is that a lot of people think of things in terms of displacement, right?
Because in order for something, there's either space or there's an object
or there's a substance.
Well, that's a good one.
But hold on.
Let's use water.
Water, fluid, medium is a very easy one.
If you have, like last week, we had a medical person say that
they acknowledged the inside lining of the GI, gastrointestinal tract, all that is hydrophobic.
As a matter of fact, it rejects water, so how can any absorption take place, right?
Right.
So let's go the opposite way.
Let's say we live in a hydrophilic reality.
You know how they do animations in imaginary worlds.
Imagine you live – this is beyond fish underwater because fish have to drink water also.
By the way, when you poison a river, you notice all the fish don't die at once
unless it's an extreme poison.
The ones that die first are the ones that are thirstiest
because they're the ones that drink the water first, right?
So just like if you poison the air, not everyone dies at the same rate.
It's the ones that are taking deeper breaths and breathing more, right?
If you hold your breath, you won't ingest.
So let's say we live in an imaginary – OK, let's just construct an imaginary world
where everything is permeable to water.
So you've got sponges, cotton towels, paper, pumice stone, right?
It's completely absorbent.
Things that are hydrophilic that allow water to pass through them, right?
So you live in a world that's made of sponges, let's say, and paper and foam
and – oh, what else?
You know, flour, right?
I mean as in wheat flour.
Things that absorb and take on water very readily.
They don't repel water at all.
Imagine everything is like that in a certain universe, right?
Why would it have to be that way though considering that you're in a fluidic –
Well, because that's how – this is an analogy for the ether.
Now imagine that world and imagine the structure still holding its identity
but allowing water to fully permeate it, right?
A sponge, a cotton towel, whatever, right?
It doesn't have to be but it can't – let's say if it's underwater, it will be.
You stick a cotton towel underwater, you deep-six it or a sponge.
You're going to pull it out and it's going to be soaking wet.
Water will permeate, right?
So imagine all the materials and all the experiences and everything in the world
that we're in now is permeable to the ether, right?
So the ether is passing through it, filling it, right?
So now let's go back to the fully permeable world,
the world where everything is a sponge or a cotton towel.
The water will be held in the cotton towel different than the sponge
because if you look at the cotton structure, it's a little different than the sponge, right?
But it's still the same water.
Right, but it's holding it. It's not actually getting –
It's also permeable. In other words, if you lift the sponge out of the water,
you'll notice the water runs out even before you wring it out.
Same with a towel.
You drop a towel in a swimming pool and pull it out,
you'll notice streams of water coming off of it, right?
Yeah, it will pour off of it first. Yeah, right.
Yeah, and if you hang the sponge and the clothesline on a clothesline, let's say,
and come back a half hour later without wringing them out,
you'll notice the cotton towel is really heavy still
and loaded with water where the sponge is pretty much dried out.
Right, it's still holding.
Okay, so this analogy I'm giving to the ether being water and all things permeable,
the sponge, the towel, whatever, is all things that we come in contact with.
So it's really difficult to kind of understand that because we –
when we say permeable, we have to actually see a sponge or a cotton towel.
We don't understand that metal or diamond, let's say a hard material.
Everyone would say the hardest material is carbon, diamond.
It's still permeable to this ether. We live in this type of world.
Now, because it's so pervasive, we don't pay attention to it, right?
The same way like I give – the little philosophical tone that I give,
like maybe the last thing a fish thinks about right before he dies or she dies
is that they're in water, right?
Because you have this philosopher fish.
You have philosophers. You go to all the other fish, all the schools of fish, right?
They tell me, hey, guys, I think I got this theory. It's more than a theory.
It might be provable that we're all in water, right?
We're all like swimming in this thing called water.
They're like, oh, this guy is crazy. This guy with his crazy stuff.
Get out of here with that. You know what I mean?
So it's kind of – that's an interesting analogy.
So I would say that this permeability aspect is very difficult to get over
because we make containers to hold fluids and gases, right?
That shouldn't be permeable, and they're not for those things.
I can give an account from – this is a secondhand account from someone that worked with hydrogen.
You can replace gasoline vapor, gasoline in an engine with various other fuels, right?
So one of them is hydrogen and oxygen.
By the way, when you drive a gasoline car, they call that thing the gas pedal
and the brake and the clutch, right?
They call that thing the gas pedal.
That's not a pedal for gas. That's actually a pedal for air.
It's really an air pedal.
Whenever you use it – the only time it's for gas is –
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
We just got a ton of interference off you, like your signal just broke up.
I'm sorry.
Oh, that's fine. It must be on your end because everything sounds cool here.
Yeah, last thing I got was about the gas pedal, and then you went robotics.
Sorry.
Oh, okay.
It's really an air pedal.
Air pedal.
All right, let's just go back to the fuel thing.
So you have a hydrogen gas, which is like the fastest speeds per second, you know, once it's ignited.
You know, in high-speed chemistry, it's usually measured in meters per second,
feet per second expansion rate, right?
Or contraction if it's implosive, which is very rare.
What they did was they tried to take some buses.
This, by the way, also happens when they go high altitude.
I'll finish – I'll give you the details on that.
Make this a short story.
They basically took some municipal buses and said,
let's run them on hydrogen instead of this dirty diesel, right?
Okay.
So they filled up these tall tanks with hydrogen gas, and the engines run like crap, right?
One of the buses ran really, really well, right?
And they went over to the tanks, and the tanks were all at zero, the pressure.
The other ones were at 2,000, 2,500, 1,200 psi, right, of gas in the tank.
So the one that kept running really well, they're looking at the tank, and they're like,
there's no gas in here.
There's no hydrogen gas in here because everything is at zero.
The tank, the seal is broken or something, and the bus is still running.
It doesn't make any sense, right?
Now, okay.
So what – a couple of smart guys got together and talked to this guy, Joe Booker in Australia,
and this is what they came up with.
Why don't we take these tanks and cut them in a way where we can access the full diameter
of the tank because usually it's just a little hole for the nozzle to fit on top, right?
Gas tank.
I'm talking about compressed air, compressed gases.
Yeah.
So they cut the bottom of the tank off.
They made like a flange fitting, and they stuffed it with aluminum honeycomb, and they
pumped it up with 2,000 pounds of pressure of hydrogen, left it in there overnight, and
the next morning they removed all the hydrogen so there's nothing in the tank, and the
bus ran off of that.
It doesn't make any sense.
Not the way I understand things normally.
No, that makes no sense.
Raytheon – I read something that was put out by Raytheon a long time ago.
They tried to go out into space because space is not a vacuum, by the way, right?
So anyway, they opened the hatch.
We're talking about like high altitude, low orbit.
They can't really – there's no evidence that they've gone more than a few hundred
miles away, right?
From their own testimony.
But they go up as high as they can, and they have these pumps, and they suck in whatever
gases are in space.
They put it in the tank, and they bring it back to Earth, and there's nothing in the
tank.
They had pressure.
They had measurable things, but the tank did not have a leak.
So what happened?
That gas went right through the walls of the tank.
It's called imponderable fluid, imponderable gases.
So an imponderable fluid would be the most current situation with current science, which
is kind of a joke.
I spell science P-S-Y-I-A-E-N-C.
Yeah.
It's all PSIOP.
Well, how does a fluid travel through something that is not supposed to be forced?
There's a whole category.
It was very popular in the late 1700s up to mid-1800s.
It was called imponderable fluids.
An imponderable fluid in today's modern system would be liquid helium.
When you pour it into a glass – it's very cold, of course – it runs up the side
of the glass and overflows, even though you just have a small amount in it.
It runs outside of the glass and runs all over the table.
It doesn't want to be in a cup.
So they call that an imponderable fluid.
There are certain combinations of ammonia and other things like that that if you put
in a jar with a wax seal – I'm talking about a really well, hermetically sealed
jar lid.
Put a wax seal on it, epoxy seal, whatever.
You come back the next day and there's nothing in it.
Well, I shouldn't say nothing.
Half of the stuff is in the jar.
The other half is in the table.
And you look at the jar.
It's not cracked.
How did it go through the glass?
Those are called imponderable fluids, imponderable gases.
It means you can't ponder.
They have a set of rules.
This is what they call – they're not laws of physics or laws of nature or Newton's
laws.
Those are merely observations, right?
Because they practice exclusion.
When they find something that doesn't follow those laws, they don't tell you about it.
They exclude it, right?
So it's kind of like you see the legal system.
We can't allow that into evidence.
There's other stuff you could leave in, right?
Because if you show this thing, there's no case, right?
Yeah, right.
Yeah, that's the same thing with them.
If you show everything that can be seen, there's no case for Newton's law or laws of thermodynamics.
Example, when somebody asks, what law did I actually break?
And they go, well, we don't have to show you the law because – right.
Yeah.
Well, because – well, it's illegal.
Here's something, if you want to talk about the imponderable.
If you ever deal with those assholes legal, what you can do is also include – there's
no legislative act of any government that says that the bar association or bar agents
are to exclusively run the court system.
Who the hell put them in charge?
As a matter of fact, in the United States, you can still look this up.
The Department of Justice history.
Do a search online.
History of the Department of Justice.
Even Wikipedia and other websites say it's a historic anomaly.
We don't know where it came from.
It just came out in like 18-whatever and Grant signed it and didn't tell anyone,
President Grant or whatever.
So it's like who – where do these guys come from, right?
This is mainstream, what I'm telling you, right?
But the people love it that way.
For example, if you run through the system and are charged with a felony and you serve
prison time, everyone thinks you're bad because you're – they can indict a hand
sandwich, right?
Like Rod Class.
They can indict anything.
As a matter of fact, there's some old newspapers from the 1700s.
It's called Rare Newspapers and Magazines website.
They sell these things and occasionally I would do screenshots of what they were selling.
Under George Washington's regime, they would send federal agents out and they would
confiscate people doing trade and then they would – what did I do wrong for – nothing.
But this bag here, this bag of coffee, they actually list the items.
We're suing them for libel because those bags of coffee are libelous, right?
OK.
Yeah, this is how bizarre and this is – and the people love this stuff.
So they deserve it.
That's why they – like what did I say about the Midwest?
Right.
I'm looking at the Department of Justice website, right?
Department of –
No, not their website.
Not their website.
I've never been to their website and neither would I ever want to go.
OK.
No problem.
I was just looking at it.
I just typed that in.
That was the first thing that came up.
You want me to go to Wikipedia?
If you type in history of the Department of Justice, you will see the title moniker.
Yeah, that's what I did and it brought me to their website.
But you want me to go to Wikipedia instead you said, right?
No, no.
Just run down the websites and you know how they list a website.
They will give a sentence or two.
Yeah, sure.
So when I put in –
Just hear what they show now because what I'm telling you was pretty much up on the
internet for over a decade.
They're over –
Well, history Department of Justice, what I have is UnitedStatesDepartmentofJustice.gov.
That's the first thing that comes up, history.
Next thing is 150 years of Department of Justice.
That's under another .gov website.
Then Wikipedia is the third thing.
That's what I'm getting.
Library of Congress, the creation of the Department of Justice.
Anything, any salacious comment?
Well, I'll click on it.
It doesn't seem to have –
Really?
It just kind of has a general sort of description.
Let's see here.
It is a curiosity of history that while the Office of Attorney General of the United States
was created by the first Congress as part of the Judiciary Act of 1789, the Department
of Justice was not authorized until over 80 years later in 1870.
It's curious.
Yeah.
OK.
If you keep going, eventually you'll land into some details like where did it come from?
Who issued it?
Why was it signed in secret?
Not really in secret, but no one was told.
Yeah.
It says from 1797 the attorneys were supervised.
Only a few cases would arise.
1861, Congress finally agreed that the attorney general should have supervisory powers over
the work of the United States attorneys.
OK.
This is a weird sort of like –
It is, but the Department of Justice specifically is considered a historic anomaly.
I've come over, over, and over, and over on stuff online.
I never bothered to look at it in print because I was not that interested years ago when I
had access to more authentic, let's say, study material.
OK.
I don't consider after 9-11 stuff that's in public libraries or university libraries
that's considered up-to-date to be authentic at all.
You have to find the old stuff, right?
OK.
No, no.
I get that.
Yeah, because right now they reprint books, by the way, and leave the original publishing
date instead of including a new reprint date.
Right.
They can do that now.
They often do that.
Let's see.
Judiciary.
According to this, like the Judiciary Act of 1789 established the office –
No, that's different.
That's attached with the Treasury and all these other things.
Yeah, no.
We're talking about the Department of DOJ, which is a three-letter.
That's one of the earliest three-letter agencies, which is not part of the government,
but it works.
It's a quasi-government agency.
I got you.
No, it's just –
It's the –
OK.
Let's break it down.
It's the Bar Association, which –
OK.
Here's one thing.
North Korea, Iran, Axis of Evil.
Remember Baby Bush?
Oh, yeah.
Guess what their legal system is.
If you go, it's the North Korean Bar.
Yeah.
If you go to Iraq or Iran – I'm sorry, Iran.
It's the Iranian Bar.
Greece, the Greek Bar.
Russia, the Russian Bar.
It's the Bar Association.
In the UK, it's the Temple Bar Association.
Whatever.
Yeah, in Canada.
Yeah, also in Australia.
So this whole thing – but none of these governments have ever passed a legislative
act enacting that they are the only ones that can run these courts, but yet they do.
Yeah, yeah.
But you know what?
This is how the people like it, so fuck them, meaning the people.
This is what they want, Kardashian and all that other shit.
Yeah, I got you.
And the only thing they keep saying throughout all these websites, by the way, is that they
are supposed to supervise the attorneys.
Right.
Well, what they do also, they can't bring a case.
So you have to be an officer of the government to bring a case through them, and they're
actually bringing cases out.
It's just ridiculous.
It's a shit show.
It's a dumpster fire of a world.
The people – look.
Here's the thing.
When someone gets arrested who's popular, if just a few thousand people show up to the
jail, they'll let them out.
This is historically proven, by the way.
But the people are so brainwashed.
Let's say someone gets railroaded, right, into jail, a popular person.
It doesn't have to be in the show business.
If a few thousand people show up to the jail – I don't mean with picket signs and stuff.
Just say let him out, let him out.
They will let him out.
The same with the courthouse.
They will let him out because they're private.
They're not going to bring in an army.
They're not going to bring in whatever.
It's not a government thing.
It's just like someone being held at a frat party and they won't let him go.
The other dorm goes over there and says let him go.
They will eventually.
I mean in a very short period of time.
But the people have been pacified to the point where they're brainwashed and they think
it's a real authority.
It's not.
It's been acting like a real authority for so long that now it is.
Do you have any view on this?
I'm reading through some stuff while I'm listening to you, but this oddity about the
phrase that's on their seal, their motto?
No.
Yeah, I think they should print toilet paper with that stuff on it.
But no, I don't know.
Yeah, no problem.
But it's most certainly Latin, right?
Yeah, it's Latin.
But the weird thing is that people have written various times over the years to the Department
of Justice and asked them for the meaning of the motto that is on their seal.
And apparently every response they ever get back is they don't know what it means, is
what they say.
They're attorneys.
They don't know.
They're not supposed to know.
Which is funny to me.
But it's, yeah, it's equipro domina justia seplater.
Simple as that.
Sorry.
It's a bunch of nonsense.
Anything that comes out of them is nonsense.
It's all presumption.
It's legal fiction.
Do I sound like I don't like them?
It's not that I don't like them.
I don't like what they do.
I don't care about them.
Right.
I just don't like what they're doing.
And what's even worse, I don't like that the people are allowing it.
So the people are far worse than they are.
Don't ever don't ever ensue that.
What I'm saying is I don't like any form of leadership or system anywhere because it wouldn't
be in place for more than a week if the people didn't allow it to.
So it's the people that suck.
Right.
OK.
Little.
You see this since the 1950s, the little green men in space flying saucer land and they see
some idiot walking the street.
What do they say to him since 19?
Take me to your leader.
I got to talk to you.
Who the hell are you?
What are you?
Right.
So.
So in other words, this system of fiefdom where you have the ignorant masses that pretty
much will go along with anything.
I've said this a long time ago since the early Greeks speak that you can pretty much do anything
to the people and they'll go.
They'll go along with it.
You just have to go along with the convention that they're used to accepting.
Right.
And they'll go along with anything.
It seems like this system is pervasive.
If it's shown that aliens from another world come and do this in art, in theater, it shows
that it's an echo outside of this system.
Also, you know, one thing Jordan Maxwell said a long time ago, as on Earth as in heaven.
And so in heaven, they have corrupt bankers and corrupt leaders.
And right.
I've always found that curious myself, where it's like, look, above as below.
Right.
And so they say, as in heaven, as on Earth, blah, blah, blah.
So it's corrupt up there.
And if you read the biblical texts that tell you there's war in heaven, there's great
violence.
Right.
So what do you know?
You're going to want to die and go to heaven?
No, thanks.
I never understood.
I think the parties will be better in hell, by the way.
They have to be.
But anyway.
With a rudimentary understanding of Latin, though, it's kind of funny because even the
way that like if you try Google Translator even on their stupid.
No, no, it won't.
Yeah.
Well, you know, the NSA website is Illuminati backwards.
Right.
Someone told me to write Illuminati backwards and then he gave me the link.
Yeah.
And you click on it.
It's NSA, National Security Agency.
Are you familiar with that?
No, I've never heard that before.
Do that.
Just do it.
Go right now.
Do a search.
NSA website is Illuminati backwards.
It is.
OK, just spell Illuminati backwards dot gov or whatever dot org.
And it brings you to the NSA page is the NSA.
Well, this page that they put up.
OK, let's see.
All right.
Let's see.
You know what?
I'm going to try and punch it in because I went for results on it and there's a whole
bunch of discussion on it.
But does Illuminati spell backwards?
But in other words, it's evidence in the discussion, isn't it?
Let's see.
Does Illuminati spell backwards on lead to the NSA?
And the domain Illuminati dot com spelled backwards points to the website of the U.S.
National Security Agency.
True.
Even according to Quora and all those, you know, like debunking websites, even Snopes.
Yeah.
So they're valid.
It's true.
Yeah.
So it's kind of a joke.
I haven't I've learned in my, you know, I'm going to be in my seventh decade here soon
that don't take anything seriously here.
Hey, look.
OK, these systems of leadership exist because the people allow them.
What are most people? What's the most popular stuff on the Internet?
Weather, pornography.
What else?
Drugs. I mean, well, you know, I don't know.
Whatever. Right. What's.
Yeah. It was a 38 percent or 30 percent.
All stuff is porn. Right.
Well, there's a lot of porn.
Yeah. There's always food since its inception.
Well, I think I told you the guy visited.
This is back in the late 90s.
Tibet. Tibetan monks.
And they fired up some kind of satellite Internet thing.
And they left the computer there with them for 45 minutes.
They came in and every computer was on porn with the monks.
All the monks went to porn.
All the monks were on porn in 45 minutes.
Never saw a computer before.
But that's all it took.
So maybe they're right.
You know, getting high, being on drugs, having sex, you know, getting whatever.
You know, that that that thing that it's easy to make fun of the people for doing.
I think they're right.
I think they're right about it.
It's not just not my cup of tea.
Let's just say. Right.
But I think there's I think there's actually, you know, it's actually admonished in ancient texts.
Don't be like that. Right.
Yeah, of course.
Yeah. But but for for if you're going to be like that and, you know, it's the way to fit in or it's the norm.
I really don't see anything wrong with it because of everything else they're allowing.
You see, it's a package deal.
Why complain about Aleister Crowley considering the condition of the rest of the world?
Yeah. Yeah. Right.
So it's a package deal. In other words, it's really difficult when you don't take the package deal.
Right. It's what they're doing is just taking everything off the sales floor, whatever is ready, you know, take it and go.
No options. Right.
You know, so this is how it comes.
That's why I mean, often it's I'm just visiting here and I'm really pissed that they sent me here.
I must be here on it on an administrative error because because I can't find anything that I'm supposed to be doing here.
Really? Well, you see now.
And that's another weird concept that people often say, look, you chose to be here and this and that before you got here.
The memory wipe covers that really well.
Yeah.
They do say that your memory is completely wiped and that covers the base on that.
But there's also hints and clues that there is a thing they ran on Netflix.
Eighteen ninety nine for one season.
And I caught that I streamed most of it.
And in the end is great. Just the last three minutes of the last episode.
Right. It pretty much says it all.
I think there's a little short YouTube clip on that.
They're basically on a spaceship going through the universe and they're running simulations.
Right. OK.
And while they're on the ship, the whole series is about being on a steamship going across the Atlantic in 1899.
And, you know, what the setting would be like on a steamship in 1899.
They open a cabinet, they run into people and things and there's anomalous things going on.
You're like, what the hell is this?
That's because there's like a little breakdown in code.
Right. Like kind of like the Matrix code is changed.
Yeah. There was some failed TV show like I think in the 1990s where like they set people out into space in the 1960s.
And they continued the culture exactly like that because they were like the last whatever of mankind they thought or they could be very soon somehow.
And they were stuck in the 60s.
And then you go through the whole show and it turns out, by the way, that the capsule never left Earth.
But it was the weirdest thing because they did this whole thing to maintain who you could breed with and all this.
So they were generationally handling it and all that.
And one wonders sometimes if that's not the point of the simulation.
You know, like that's what it's really about.
And at some point somebody is going to open the door and go, you know what's actually going on out here?
Well, here's the thing. One other hint that it's a simulation is you can't do anything about anything here.
Right. And when these changes happen, you see it's the same people that are doing the other stuff that are behind it.
Right. Proof of that recently, also, there's many.
If you look at alternative media, some places, you know, half a million people showed up to protest, whatever.
And it's not on the mainstream news at all. Right.
So it shows you that certain things and then you'll have a place where there's 400 people protesting.
It's all over the mainstream news. Right. So it's all control.
Well, 15 people show up and they make it. Yeah.
And so anyway, just to go back to the beginning of what we started, that the ether is permeable,
giving the analogy of fully hydrophilic permeable objects and how they drain out water and how they all take on water.
What is it now? You know, this is something we can go on.
If people here have listened to Ken Wheeler, this is like Ken Wheeler 2.0 type stuff we can get into.
And I don't think it's necessary. I like to use more basic language.
But the idea of a magnet, the idea of light, the idea of hyper what I call hyper agitations like gamma,
you know what they call radiation, gamma, alpha, beta, all that stuff, right.
X-rays, what they call that hyper modulation and all that stuff.
All that's in the ether, in the medium, just like you would be a towel or a sponge in the water. Right.
And it would be hyper ultrasonic bath. Right. Kind of thing in the water.
So this permeability can be worked with, but we can't.
If you spent your entire universe as a towel or a sponge, many generations in the water,
it would be really hard to make something to measure the water that you're already submerged in, isn't it?
You'd have to separate it. That's true.
And after all, even if you wanted to wring out the towel, if you try and do it underwater,
you can't do it while you're still in the water, can you?
You could. You could. Actually, in a vacuum, actually in a vortex tube,
we vortexed some clay type sand so intensely, it formed these little balls in the bottom of the vessel.
And when we removed the balls from the water, cracked them open,
they were totally dry, powder dry on the inside. Right.
Because of the intense vacuum of the vortex. And this only happened once.
We tried to repeat it. It was very difficult. We just weren't able to repeat it.
But we had it with witnesses. So, yeah, it can be, but it's also very, very obtuse.
The ether, though, is what you have to learn to respect or what modes it goes into to control the weather to a certain degree.
And yes, the weather is very controllable, especially when you see the bad weather.
The bad weather is completely unnecessary.
So did I ever get into, by the way, why you should not redeem the great deserts of the world?
I never heard that. Maybe you did it with somebody else, not with me.
Yeah, I think we might have. All right. So this is from DeMayo.
You know, there's camps, you know, there's cliques.
I'm more in the Wilhelm Reich, Trevor James Constable clique.
School of thought, so to speak.
Yeah, and DeMayo doesn't like Constable at all.
So I don't really go towards DeMayo out of respect for Constable.
DeMayo's work is fine. He's very conservative.
But anyway, OK, why you don't redeem the deserts?
Now, if you redeem a major desert, well, what does that mean?
It no longer is a desert. You have regular rain, the topsoil, animals, plants, vegetation.
Allegedly, yeah.
One of the attributes of the deserts, the large deserts, right?
We're not talking about a little patch of dune somewhere like you have up in Oregon or something, right?
We're talking about the big ones like Namibia, Sahara, Gobi, right?
One of the attributes in climatology of these deserts is that during certain times of year,
major, major sandstorms occur that kick up very fine silica particles into the very high atmosphere.
When I say high atmosphere, I'm talking about where the very high plains lie.
And when they get up to that very high atmosphere, they migrate across to the great oceans and deposit the quartz into the oceans.
And that's why you shouldn't mitigate the deserts.
But Greek, that doesn't make any sense. OK, let's maybe give a little more. Maybe it'll make more sense.
Go for it, because I only have a hint so far. I don't fully see it.
Now, you know there's something called the food chain.
You go from the little bacteria to the plankton all the way up to the whale, which is not a fish.
But you know what I mean, right?
Smaller things are continuously getting consumed by the larger, smarter.
Yeah, and the whale, which is not a fish, but it is a water animal, closes the gap.
Most whales eat plankton.
They have the baleen gland, a baleen structure in their mouth that filters out all the microscopic plankton.
That's what they eat, the blue whale and all that.
So the biggest animal eats the smallest animal, the plankton, right?
What do plankton eat?
What do they rely on?
Not solely, but if you remove this from their diet, they perish.
Silica sand, silica quartz, silica compounds.
Where did those compounds come from?
The deserts.
So now if you eliminate the plankton, the big whales have nothing to eat.
But it's not just the big whales that eat the plankton.
No, but it's the small fish.
It's really small fish that eat the plankton, and then bigger fish eat those fish, and then bigger fish, right?
Okay.
It's kind of like an analogy of killing all the bees.
Right, okay.
Then you won't have any pollination, naturally.
You take out the smallest organism that's part of the food chain, and the whole rest of the chain collapses.
Actually, it's more critical.
A broken link in a chain is a broken link in a chain, but sometimes some links carry more weight than others.
Well, absolutely.
I mean, I guess that some animals could adapt if there's a loss in there, and that happens from time to time, right?
That has happened already.
Demeo went and redeemed Namibia for about a year, and you could look.
I think it was back in the late 80s or early 90s.
There was an after-newspaper article about how all the fishermen in South America are coming back with empty nets.
Right.
Right?
Oh, I remember that.
Yeah, and that was a big, like, oh, the fish are all dying.
Well, yeah, there's nothing to eat.
But then when the intensity of the project wore off and the desert came back into its normal function of producing the ejecting silica compounds into the atmosphere, then the fish came back.
Pretty quickly, everything recovers.
But anyway, I'm just giving this analogy because it's very useful.
According to people in the Midwest, this analogy would not help them at all.
Anyway, I keep harping on them when I see the bad weather.
Can't help it.