Sonic Event 123, Rated Y. Anyway, look, it's a little noisy over there, but that's okay.
We knew that was going to happen.
Greek, how is things?
It's going, yeah, it's all right.
Yeah, we had a little delay this week, but let's see how the internet goes, because they
were chopping lines here, the Cox Communications, you know, the internet, the cable people,
they don't have any crews.
All those crews, they put a magnetic, it's part of the subcontract, because they get
paid well, and they slap a magnetic sign on the side of their truck, right?
Yeah, exactly.
Everybody's a subcontractor, and look, you and I are in two totally different parts of
the country, but Cox Cable is the same thing all over.
Yeah, it's a guy that's just like, yeah, I do this, and sometimes I work for AT&T, too,
you know?
Right, exactly.
Yeah, this way, there's no pensions to pay, if the guy gets injured, get out of here,
get another one, right?
Oh, yeah.
That's what the Japanese do here, when they make car factories here.
And they don't even have to do the payroll stuff, either.
You just turn around and go, look, man, your taxes are your problem, and that's that.
Well, no one has to do it.
You can get hired and refuse the paperwork.
There's a lady that was doing a survey recently, about two weeks ago, can you sign this petition
for what?
Raising the minimum wage.
So the minimum wage, it should be at least $27 to $28 to live, right?
And I was trying to explain it to her, you know?
If you get hired, and you don't fill out any tax paperwork, and they fire you because of
that, you could sue, you litigate.
That's one thing that Brandon Joe Williams is into.
He's going to get slaughtered, by the way, I don't know if anyone watched his stuff.
But he's putting out good information that if you use most of it, if you actually do
what he says, you'll be okay.
But his litigation, he doesn't understand.
But anyway, I don't endorse him, just like Archaic, I don't endorse him, but you'll find
good stuff there.
Brandon Joe Williams, onestupidfuck.com.
Yeah, that's his website.
Anyway, yeah, there's a while back, if they ask you for a social security number and refuse
to hire because you don't have one or don't produce one, if you can get it in writing,
the full year salary is what you litigate for, plus treble damages.
So let's say it was back then, when I helped someone do this, it was a 30K job, and 90K
triple on top, not 60, triple damages.
I think they went for, but they did settle for 42,000, and it was with, and it was, the
employer could afford it, it was a hotel chain.
Not bad for not going to work.
Yeah, go ahead.
Yeah, and I said, well, all you got to do, I was telling people, is apply, go apply to
work, and I'll show you how you can make a quarter of a million dollars a year, anywhere
between 50 to 100,000 a year, just for applying to get jobs.
Not working.
And they're like, huh?
And when you explain it to them, they're, you know, but you don't apply like some mom
and pop, whatever.
You could do that too and hurt them, but they won't, you'll have to liquidate their store
and all that.
You go to the big companies that are always saying, we're hiring, right?
You just go keep, you just keep applying, and you just be very careful what you say,
very careful of what they say, and then use it against them.
And that's how you're going to change the system.
And the way, see, this system is set up, it's all fraudulent, right?
The money is completely fraudulent, the medical is completely fraudulent, the religions are
completely fraudulent.
I mean, all you got to say is Santa Claus, right?
And that proves that religions are fraudulent, on and on and on and on.
So any fraudulent system throughout history does collapse, yes or no?
Yes.
Right?
It always falls apart.
It seems to me every system collapses.
You don't even have to say fraud.
Every system seems to collapse, whether it's fraudulent or not, I can't even determine
because they all collapse.
But a fraudulent one will go much quicker.
Now, here's the thing.
If people followed everything that's in the laws, we'd be great.
We wouldn't be using money.
Anytime you want something, you sign your name and you get it.
That's why when I go out to the shops and let's say at Goodwill, do you want to donate
the change to this charity?
And I'm like, why?
Are their hands broken?
And that starts the conversation, right?
Because all you need to do is sign your name.
They're not following.
So if everyone, let's say, did what Joe Brandon says, go ahead and litigate every time you
write a check.
You know, I've gone over the banking, how it works, right?
That's why you notice everything, the prices have doubled nearly or gone up like 60 percent.
That's because of all those stimulus checks.
And I told people on private Skype calls to watch the massive inflation within 300 to
1000 days, which is within one year or three.
That's how they work on 90, 180 day increments, the financial rate.
And they work on quarterly.
Right.
So I bunched it up.
I said, they'll give them three.
Anyway, everything's got a three and a half year drift anyhow.
You know, that's right.
Sort of.
Yeah.
So.
So what better thing to be part of taking down the system?
Now, here's the thing.
Not not the way they say take the most patriots, which are idiots.
You take down the system by using everything that it has in there.
Just do it.
Like, for example, attorneys do not know any law at all.
Guaranteed.
There's very little exception.
Now, let's talk about the exception.
If you're one of the exceptional attorneys, not exceptional, but exceptions that do know
law and your colleagues find out that you're studying law, you can get rule 11 on your
ass.
You know what rule 11 is.
Look it up.
But anyway, and you will end up working selling cars.
Now, some people think it could be used cars or new cars.
But I've seen attorneys leave the field and they always go to selling cars used or new.
How come it is that it seems like everything is a Section 11, Chapter 11, Rule 11 that
puts you out of business?
Is that a coincidence or is it just me?
Because I notice whether it's the military or it's, you know, the financial is another
one.
But I'm just saying there's a whole thing about that.
Everything that puts you out of business, though, you have to do it under the 11th and everything
that puts you really there's others.
But yeah, I get what you're saying.
There's also about a decade ago, people seeing 11s all the time show up.
I mean, even the punitive stuff in the military, you go under Section 11, you're done, you
know.
Right.
Yeah.
All right.
Anyway.
Sorry.
I just noticed.
Yeah.
No, no, it's fine.
So.
So, yeah.
I want to get into something in chat.
A little segue.
Let me just open it up.
Now, I do read the chat every three days or four days, but I'm not writing in there because
it seems like everything that that I do, other than what I'm doing, seems to take forever.
So I don't spend time answering emails.
I don't spend time writing in chat.
I see.
I see what's going on, though.
I try to keep eyes and ears, you know, or someone say, how's it going?
Would you read the chat?
Let me know if anything addresses me.
But there's a fellow in the chat, or gal, I think it's a fellow, Sojourner Sleuth, he's
a New Yorker, New Yorker, right?
And he gave a bunch of stuff in there.
One of the questions, just the latter question, well, he talked about walking through Union
Square and someone got a flash of consciousness upgrade at 14th Street and 4th Avenue.
I guess 4th Avenue was the old Lafayette Street.
That's where the L was.
But I really like the 14th Street, Union Square, you know, Farmer's Market and all that.
I lived on 11th and 3rd.
Is that the L that went over to Bayonne or is that the other one?
That's still there.
OK.
It's still there.
It's a real Farmer's Market.
Yeah.
It used to connect to Bayonne, though.
The elevated train connected to Bayonne.
Oh, the train.
Yeah.
No, no.
The 4th Street, it wasn't.
It went up to 34th or 23rd.
It's pretty short.
But they tore it down in the 30s and sent the steel to Japan.
Right.
And then they threw it back at the Americans 10 years later.
OK.
Sorry.
But, you know, that's fine.
He talks about also the George Washington.
OK.
George Washington was known as the general.
If you read private writings of the revolutionary era, the American Revolutionary Era, and they
mentioned the general, the general, right?
There's referring to JW, GW, right?
Yes.
Always.
So from two sources, one is David Barrow, who does the lawful money, the saving to
suitors group.
He mentioned it.
And also about a decade before that, I used to go to something called the Saturday Morning
Breakfast Club.
It was a bunch of old farts, World War Two vets talking about how the country's on a
bad foot.
This is around the year 2000.
And how they're going to make it better.
And, you know, we should be following the Constitution, which, by the way, I didn't know it doesn't
apply to them.
But anyway, they talked about that George Washington had died in the war, frozen.
Now, the Battle of Brooklyn was in the summer.
So the first that winter, they were being chased around Brooklyn, chased around Manhattan.
Right.
All this.
He was something happened.
I don't think it was an assassination.
I don't quite remember all the details of the circus.
It went back and forth.
I didn't have that much interest in it.
He died.
And if he was found dead, frozen, solid, and they buried him right there on Montague Street
in Brooklyn and Brooklyn Heights, there's a memorial there to not just to George Washington,
but the Revolutionary War.
And he's buried under it.
So all you got to do is go there with a shovel.
Now, I think and there's some very cryptic as a plaque there has some cryptic things
in it, too.
OK, the whole thing was to keep the morale high.
So they got this poor sucker who looked just like him, but didn't have any teeth in his
mouth.
So the biggest priority was to get teeth in this guy's mouth so they could pass him off
as GW, George Washington.
That's why he's the only president in history whose medical concern or dental concerns have
ever been brought up.
So they give him the uniform that his wife got for him.
And oh, crap.
We got to put teeth in his mouth.
He walks like him, looks like him, probably smelled like him, but he didn't have teeth
in his mouth.
So the biggest concern is we got to get teeth in this guy's mouth.
OK.
Yeah.
And when they brought it, you know, there's also stories that George Washington freaked
out when they went to the Masonic Lodge and they bled him, his doctor bled him to death.
That wasn't George Washington.
George Washington was already dead and gone.
He was the guy playing George Washington, right?
That was brought to the Masonic Lodge and said, what the WTF is going on here?
Right.
Freaked out.
Back then they were doing more hardcore rituals.
Yeah.
I wonder if that guy knew even what the hell was going on, you know, or did they just say,
hey, look, we're going to hook you up with something for do do this and we'll hook you
up.
I mean, did they really let him in on it or.
I don't know.
But here the story was that it's all a fraud and it's true.
OK.
If you advertise you have the freest neighborhood or the freest city or the freest country in
the world, you're going to attract just as many criminal scumbags as you are people who
want a fresh start in that kind of situation.
Right.
Oh, always.
Yeah.
So the people who want to be honest, good people are not going to think of coming over here
and taking over.
So but at the same time, you attracted the biggest scumbags in the world.
I mean, the people left from the Vatican, people left from various underground groups to come
here and, you know, hide their way.
That's what the McCarthyism was about.
It wasn't just about communism.
It was all these were these people coming from that that are extremely Jewish and extremely
dedicated to secret societies and changing their names and all that.
Right.
So McCarthyism was correct.
He was like, we're losing.
We're going to lose our country finally here with this.
It's all infiltrated.
Right.
It's kind of like I knew a sniper for the Mexican government.
And we once talked about when it was even before Obama came in.
But just around that time, a lot of people were worried about immigration stuff.
Right.
It was a big immigration thing then also.
And I said, Armando, did I just mention his name?
Yes.
I said, what do you think will happen if Mexico and America go to war?
I said, America will lose in 24 hours because we already have almost half a million military
people here in the United living here.
I said, you think they're mowing lawns and working in tire shops or flipping burgers
and diners?
They're all military.
You know what I mean?
So like like a sleeper cells.
Right.
Smart strategy.
Look, I don't need to send an army.
It's already there.
It's already here.
Yeah.
They're trained, you know.
So and they just sit here and they live normal, quote, unquote, normal lives and they go back
to Mexico.
I mean, that's exactly how a mob expands into like they go, oh, gee, how did the mob get
from this state to this state?
Just like that overnight?
No, they didn't.
What they did is they sent a bunch of guys in.
They went doing business, didn't advertise who they were.
And it turns out all these guys actually know each other, you know, and then somebody
just kind of flips a switch and says, OK, now declared it's ours.
And yeah, it's the mob tactics is the same tactics as everyone else's.
Exactly. So anyway, yeah, go ahead.
So you were saying, yeah, they would take you overnight.
All right. Well, hey, is that all that was in the chat or was there any more?
Oh, other miscellaneous stuff.
But I think that's all for now.
So I'll go back and see what I could reference.
Anything. I mean, there's a cryptic thing about inventing as I wrote.
You all got a heads up on that last sonic.
And I guess that was sonic.
This is one, two, three. So it's probably one, two.
Oh, I don't know. I don't know what I was getting into.
But yeah.
So if Van Diemen, Van Diemen's land, if he can expand on it, that'd be great.
What the heads up was.
Yeah. Because I think I'm always giving a heads up.
I didn't think one specific thing was a heads up.
Why say it now? So clarify.
I'm thinking it might have been the one with the, you know, look, this is the way the
robot actually works.
And, you know, you were talking about with the the shots.
No, I think that. Yeah.
Was that before or after? I think, yeah, that might have been it.
That was the last one. It's all simple, very simple.
And, you know, you were talking about, well, look, if you just remotely make this
thing unfold, boom, it expands too much.
And therefore you have, you know, it's like, oh, yeah, right.
It's a slap against the cell that it's next to.
Right. Right. So I'm not articulating it as well.
But I'm just saying there's a huge heads up because nobody's saying that at all.
Something will double its size inside of you.
Right. What is it? Right.
It's clearly going to cause a disruption.
And gee, what what is a aneurysm?
Blah, blah, blah. All these different things.
They call it at the same. It's a bursting blood vessels.
And how are these blood vessels magically bursting?
Well, that can also be done radionically.
Like if they have your signature biosignature, they can do it.
They can create these conditions in you radionically.
Like Ruth drowned like Brown, but with a D drown.
Someone's in water. She was able.
She had a she radionic.
So Trevor James Constable took a lot of her writings and made them public.
She had a client who was going to travel.
She checked him out. He had a toothache.
She's go on your trip. Come back.
We'll take care of it on his trip.
He calls her, says it's really hurting.
She goes, let me look at it.
So he's somewhere in Europe and she's somewhere in Jersey, I think,
or Connecticut. And she takes an X-ray of his mouth while he's in Europe.
And she's in New Jersey using radionics.
And actually, she she developed it on X-ray paper,
but it was basically using radionics, basically coils and resonance.
Right. Witness pads.
OK, how it works. You could look up radionics, how it works.
It's sympathetic vibration. Right.
OK, so they can trigger your any heart attacks
and aneurysms that could trigger remotely.
Donald Marshall talked about this. Yes.
I've said many times, if you the reality of what's really going on
is weirder and crazier than anything you hear on the Internet.
So if we hear something really bizarre and crazy and filter it
and see if it doesn't put out by them. Right.
No, I mean, yeah, make no mistake.
Look, the old trope of having to wear tinfoil hat. Right.
Why were people doing that?
Because they were trying to block the microwaves.
Yeah, that was back in the day. Yeah, that was a long time ago.
But still, Delgado showed that in the 60s. Yeah, yeah.
But you do that. Yeah, exactly.
But it existed before that.
I'm just saying that that's how that trope came about,
is you had to block the microwave somehow.
And make no mistake, again, AM radio in and of itself
is a mild microwave signal. Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. It's a radius.
And it's the real it's the various transducers give you different fluctuations.
Right. So microwave is a smaller wave.
You know, it's not that small.
It's about an inch. Right.
Where the radio, the AM could be 30 feet. Right.
So but still, it has various implications
because you have quarter wave theory, which is the most efficient.
But that's the thing in the old days when we had, you know,
the crystal radios and everything. Right.
If you tuned to AM radio, you could possibly be hearing AM radio
four or five states away.
No problem, even though it's only supposed to broadcast in,
you know, their area or whatever.
If you use a fire hydrant, which is really well-grounded,
you could pick up China, China radio.
Right. I mean, you could see a shortwave tuning in.
But that's all just perturbations in the ether.
You know, transducers, you know, transducers like a speaker cone.
But instead, you know, it's moving at such a high frequency
that that ripple effect goes through.
And we're sensitive to that.
Fortunately, we're not that sensitive as many of the new agers
and alternative people say we are.
We're not that sensitive to it.
What makes us what's damaging is when it's pulsing at a specific rate.
Well, my point is that these things are traveling around all the time.
They always have been.
And even, you know, people talk about, oh, the cell towers.
Oh, you're crazy because, you know, these all these waves traveling around.
You are being hit with them.
Most of the time that you don't notice them because they're not.
Yeah, but it's radiation.
It's like, for example, I know people that work on nukes, submarines. Right.
And they have all this elaborate equipment that's been developed
by Department of Energy.
By the way, the biggest, baddest quote, unquote
air quote government agency is the DOE Department of Energy.
Not the CIA, not this, not the IRS, whatever.
It's the Department of Energy.
Anybody who has any dealings in military or that
well, knows what I'm saying is true, but it's not popularized on the Internet.
Right. The CIA, FBI, the logistical,
you know, the judicial executive.
No, it's the deal.
He is the most powerful agency in this country.
And it's not tell it's not, you know, known as such.
But anyway, people I know that worked on nukes, submarines,
they have all this elaborate equipment to see if the reactors are leaking. Right.
And then, you know, the equipment is here to measure
leaky reactors, very sensitive, whatever.
But they found the most reliable thing
to see if there was a leaky reactor is when it was docked.
If there were any, they looked at a clock and say, what time did you dock?
What time is it now?
And if an hour passes and all the flies disappear,
there's a leaky reactor, meaning all the flies, meaning like flies,
like, you know, the flies that that fly on shit, right?
Insects. OK, right, right, right.
So if you know, so if you're in a dock area
and there's a nuclear like San Diego's got a big naval port.
But anyway, if you walk on the dock near one of these ships or something
and you see all the flies are gone, no flies in the hot summer. Right.
That's a leaky reactor. I wouldn't stand around.
So that's something that you don't read about.
You just figure out, share that.
Speaking of sharing, I want to get into something that I haven't really discussed,
but I've alluded to, you know, with all the energy work, the health work and stuff.
You know, OK, how to get fit, because I know personally,
I mean, I'm pretty fit for my shape, for my age and the type of body that I have.
I'm not a mesomorph.
I'm more of like a thin mesomorph for people are naturally muscular.
What happens when they get older?
They get flabby and they fall apart.
Look at the ex bodybuilders, right?
So you want to be more on the fit.
Well, I have a more of a thin frame,
but I can develop muscle very quickly. Right.
So I always tell people, you know, in 30 to 60 days,
I can get in the best shape I've ever been in in my life.
And anyone can. And this is how you do it.
And I've been talking about this to people on and off my whole life.
Well, actually, more like the past 30 years, you know, as a fitness coach,
you know how to get in shape and all that.
Like one thing I have not gone back to is one of the emails a fellow sent me.
He works in the cycling industry.
And I think he knows who Eddie Merck says now.
And I'm not being sarcastic.
It's just like, please, people do your research.
But, you know, one of the questions in that email I didn't go go over is,
how do you, you know, excel yourself?
How do you excel on being on a bicycle performance wise?
And it's just did you do it all the time?
I'll give a quick example.
I was really into cycling. I was dissuaded from it.
Then I didn't know what to do in Manhattan in the early 80s.
I became a bicycle messenger.
So that means I was on.
And I'm not one of these guys that has a Toys R Us bike with sneakers.
I went out and got the best track bike I could afford and the best cycling gear
right away and got on the bike.
And I was on the bike between eight and nine hours a day, every day,
five days a week.
And aggressive riding, aggressive riding, not just tooling around.
And I found that in three months of doing that, I was in better shape
and fitness and skill level as people who were training to be pro cyclists
that were doing it for three or four years
because they were not doing it eight hours a day every day.
Right. They had jobs.
They had other things right to do. Right.
So I found that you just do it a lot like there's a there's Dan Pena.
I don't know if people know him.
It's funny. He calls people morons, but he's a moron himself.
That's kind of ironic.
But he talks about people go to him for encouragement.
So there's one guy that came to him in England.
He was an archer shooting arrows, right?
Bow and arrow sport.
And he was a skinny guy.
He always finished in the top 20, top 30.
Never, never even close to being contender.
And he says, what do I do to become a better archer?
He says, well, how many arrows are you shooting a day?
He says 50 to 100 to shoot 500 hours a day.
And you'll be the best champion in the country in a year.
Now, the guy was obviously you try to do that.
Your fingers are going to start bleeding, right?
At first. And yeah, and if you know, and he he got up to the point
where he was able to pull 140 pound bow, even though he only weighed 130 pounds.
Right. And he did win the championship.
He became a first place in England.
He got a hell of a callous on at least one hand doing that.
Of course. Of course.
So the same thing happens with the cycling.
What happened was I jumped on the bike.
The first week was just living hell, living hell.
The rashes and the blisters and everything.
It was just living hell.
By the second week, you started recovering.
Then a new set of things came.
OK, that is not the way to get into fitness.
But it is the way to become great at something and reach the top of the field.
You know, like you couldn't get any better than that.
Right. If you do something a lot and do it every day,
you're going to get good at it. Right.
So what what do I say to go back how I started?
How do I get the best fitness in 30 to 60 days?
If you have the body type, in other words, where you're inclined to be athletic,
more of a not a very lean, OK, very lean person
is someone with a very weak chin, very triangular face,
kind of bulgy eyes. Right.
That's a very lean that type of person.
When they get ill, they catch a cold. It takes forever to heal.
If it's a female, she has her period.
It's all month long, not just two weeks. Right.
You know, if they have an allergy, it's like six months to get rid of it.
You know, they don't heal well.
You know, very lean person.
I see this very often.
It's like I'll run into someone and I'll say that person's very lean.
It's like, what do you mean? I say, watch this.
When you get a cold, it's real hard to recover. Right.
And I'm like, yeah.
And if you have, you know, striking resemblance to a rodent,
maybe in their appearance, yeah, sort of. Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, exactly. Very similar.
There's other yin features as ones that it's inverted
where you have a very wide chin and a narrow like a pinhead.
Then the ears are very set back, not forward as another yin constitution.
This is called phrenology, where you face reading. Right.
But anyway, yeah.
But that point that you made, yes, is a very.
But you can also be young.
You have to look at the entire character also and the rest of the body.
Hmm. So if you have a proponent to being flexible,
being quick at recovery, you know, if you sprain an ankle or catch a cold,
whatever, you can recover quickly. This is for you.
So this is what's done.
There's people that talk about building muscle and going to the gym.
Everybody seems like they have to go to the gym, avoid the gym completely,
completely unnecessary.
It's the gym has become like playing golf in business.
Right. And certain businesses or whatever in business culture,
you play golf with the boss. You made it. Right.
So, well, after all, they take three, four minutes of the presidential debate
the other night to argue over their golf scores. So, yeah, good.
OK, so right now it's become in the past few decades going to the gym.
Right. Even corporations, they have corporate gyms. Right.
So that's the new thing now.
So you don't need any of that. This is how you do it.
OK. Basically, you use your own body weight
and you do the basic calisthenics, which are push ups.
Push ups, sit ups, pull ups.
Now, this is how you get back into.
So right now, I consider myself to be out of shape.
I drink a gallon of coffee a day, one and a half pack of cigarettes a day
and about 80 to 100 grams of kratom a day. Right.
All of that should have killed me a long time ago.
I'm still doing fine, supposedly.
So you include squat thrusts and jumping jacks, too, and all that kind of stuff.
Right. Yeah. Not necessary.
But you can do that because I'll get into how you develop a very quick fitness level.
So when you're doing, let's say, the easiest thing to
show that you can build the most upper body and getting fit is a push up.
Now, what's important when you're doing the push up, the pull up,
not so much to sit up because you might have to get up.
That's fine, is the negative resistance.
So when you're doing a push up and you're out of shape,
you can let yourself down, but you can't push yourself up.
Don't worry about it.
It's the it's the resistance, the negative resistance, letting yourself down.
Right. Not pushing yourself up.
That builds the most muscle.
So if you're out of shape, go ahead and try to do a push up.
And as you're letting yourself down, you know, your arms are shaking
because you don't have the joint strength. Right.
And your muscles aren't used to pulling on the joints and you vibrating and shaking.
Soon as you hit the ground, you know, your feet, you know, you're flat.
You try to lift yourself up.
If you're having a hard time, don't bother.
Sit up, get into that position and just let yourself down.
A pull up would be similar.
So let's say you grab the bar and you try to pull yourself up.
You're like, oh, shit, your back is cracking.
You're really shaking again. Can't do it. That's fine.
What you do is get yourself a little step stool.
Get on the step stool or short ladder that has the height of where the pull up is
and then just move it aside and let yourself down.
So right. So your negative resistance don't.
And if you can't pull yourself up, don't worry about it.
Grab the step stools, take a few steps up, get into the position
where the pull up is fully up and then let yourself down.
The negative resistance will build 40 percent more.
Strength at 40 percent faster.
Now, if you find yourself, let's say, doing pull ups, sit ups and push ups,
even just doing the negative part. Right.
Right. You're not pushing yourself.
It's the negative is the part where the right.
So each exercise is a different movement for the negative part.
You're not pulling your weight or lifting your weight at all.
You're just allowing your weight to go down.
That is that will develop more muscle.
Now, this is what happened with me.
What I found out, I started doing some push ups and sit ups and I'm out of breath.
Right. So I can't do the physical work that will tone the musculature
and the skeletal and all that.
I can't do it because I'm out of breath.
So that means that you have the first exercises I explained.
We're building up the tonality of the muscles and the joint strength. Right.
Or muscle strength and joint strength also.
But if you're running out of breath, that means it's a total separate regimen,
which is strictly cardiovascular, cardiopulmonary.
So you need to get your cardiopulmonary in shape first.
If you find yourself going out of breath where you can't do enough of these
negative or just full push ups.
Now, someone say I can do the push ups just fine, then do them.
But don't push yourself to where it's painful.
Right. You just do it until you feel like you can just get up and continue.
You don't do it to where you're struggling.
In other words, if you can do three push ups and fluid motion
or three pull ups and fluid motion on the fourth one, you kind of get stuck.
Don't force yourself.
Do not force yourself, because that will create a different type of situation
in your body. Just stop. Don't worry.
In two days, you'll do that fourth one or whatever it is.
But if you find yourself going out of breath, that's cardiopulmonary,
cardiovascular.
Don't worry about the sit ups, the pull ups or the push ups.
What you do is three times a day.
If you can go for a brisk jog, not a run and not a walk, but a brisk jog.
It could be when you start getting into shape.
Don't go too far away.
Right. So in other words, instead of running around the block,
you run down the block and back to your where you live.
So in case you run out of steam, right, you don't have to walk back. Right.
Slowly. So you just run that right until you find out what test,
what distance you need, because you don't want to waste time either.
But you do this three times a day, every day.
There's no rest day when it comes to what I'm saying.
You know, people, when they go to the gym and they do fitness,
they go, oh, I work out. This is my rest day.
That's bullshit. That's that's like set up for failure type.
That's like for the typical moron. Right.
They'll give you some reason that they got from some medical book.
That's not how it works at all.
When you get to a high level of physical development.
Yes, there is a rest day because they're working on an extreme level. Right.
And there's many more reasons than just, you know, letting the body heal.
But what you do is every day you do a gentle effort.
Actually, it's a concerted effort to do push ups, pull ups and sit ups.
Don't worry about the pull ups if you don't have a bar.
And and if you find yourself going out of your breath.
So let's say you can do nine push ups
fairly in succession where you're not getting stuck. Right.
So so you try to do the tenth one.
It's like, I can't quite do it.
That's right. Just roll over. Get up.
Don't force yourself with the show on TV.
We're going to yell at you. Do it. Do it.
None of that. None of that. No pain, no gain.
None of that's all bullshit. It's all bullshit.
Yeah. If you follow that stuff, you'll you'll be like a typical moron
and you'll say, why am I not? It's better at the gym.
What I'm telling you is I assure you, if you have a fairly decent constitution
where you what they call your God given whatever.
And in 30 days, you could be in the best shape of your life. Right.
I mean, in 60 days, I can get my body where I'd be on the cover of like,
you know, senior GQ or something. Right.
I'm serious. You can get in that good shape. Very fast.
It doesn't matter what your body type is, as long as you have quick recovery.
Like I said, if you're very lean individual,
you know, if you get hit with a winter cold or a flu or an injury
and it takes you forever to recover or heal from that, you're
this is not going to work for you. Right.
So this is what I'm saying will work for about 75 percent of the people,
maybe 50 percent of the people.
So just doing basic, I would call it basic calisthenics.
Don't worry about the jumping jacks
because the jumping jacks and other stuff that you mentioned earlier.
Yes, I'm not dismissing it, but that's more in between
the cardio and the weight. Right. That's different.
The jumping jacks were called the star exercise back in the days back,
you know, maybe turn of the century.
So of the previous century, when I started the century, I'm thinking 20th century.
Now you're talking to someone. They mean this century. Right. Exactly.
So, yeah. So basically, don't there's not that like you said,
the no pain, no gain is total rubbish. Right. Don't push yourself.
Focus on the negative side.
So it'll look think about how weird it is.
A lot of these parks have these
places where you could do these exercises like a run.
They have different par.
You know, they have bars for doing push ups.
Oh, you're going to do a push up, you know, whatever.
You have different heights. Right. Do the high one.
Get go get some of those push up bars that you hold on to or in a parking lot.
Don't you know, curb where dogs piss or something?
Don't do that. But if there's a curb, you know, where those parking blocks
where the cars pull up to, you could do it on something like that.
You get yourself a four by four, six by six railroad type.
Put it somewhere under your couch or behind the door and use that
for doing push ups is fine.
It's not what is going to get you fit is not how many full push ups you do,
but how many negative push ups you do.
Meaning letting yourself down on the push up is what's going to build
the strength immediately.
40 percent faster than just doing the entire push up.
So it looks like imagine I was saying going to a park
where they offer those pull up bars and you bring a little stool with you
and you get up on the stool, you get up in the full closed
pull up position and you just let yourself down.
Then you get back on the stool, pull yourself up on the stool
and just letting yourself down on the pull up.
Don't worry about pulling yourself up.
This is actually if you're overweight and your joints aren't that strong,
there's no way you're going to pull up 300 pounds or 275. Right. Right.
But if you get on the stool and let yourself down gently, right, you can do it.
And that's going to build a tremendous amount of fitness very, very quickly.
Forty percent more.
So so don't wait.
I mean, I can see that being on one of these YouTube videos.
Look at this guy doing pull ups.
He gets up on a stool, just lets himself down.
Everyone's going to make fun of that, right?
Oh, definitely. Yeah. Yeah.
So don't worry about work.
And OK, so here's the other way to think about it.
Fighting gravity doesn't make you stronger on the plus.
You know, so right.
So once you get down on the push up, you get into the finished position.
Now it's time to push yourself up, fighting gravity in the positive way.
Don't bother with that.
Just let yourself down.
If you're doing the push ups, you can only let yourself down
and you can't push yourself up. Right.
That's fine. Roll over.
No, no pun intended.
If you're that fat, let's say around.
Roll over. Sit up.
Get back into that position.
Just let yourself down.
You can't push yourself up.
Don't worry about it.
Just flop on flop down on the ground.
Roll over, get up and get back into that position.
Do that three, four or five, six times.
As many times you could do it before you start feeling like I can't do another one.
Don't force yourself.
What that's doing is that you're adapting your body and your muscles
actually react better to that.
Now, if you study how the professional bodybuilding and power training,
when you get to a certain max fitness level, yes, you have to break that wall.
Yes, you do. Right.
That's why they're young. Right.
But you're not we're talking about how to get really fit in 30 to 60 days.
Not you've been going to the gym for 10 years.
Now you're going to go for Mr. Universe.
You have to break through and lift even heavier.
But that's what people take.
That's what people take with. You know, that's all they have.
So someone's going to get fit.
They're going to look at these regimens that are applied to people
who do it professionally.
It doesn't has nothing to do with you or your physiology.
So, again, don't worry about the positive resistance.
The negative resistance is what does it.
I'm not saying don't ever do a push up or a pull up ever.
I'm just saying when you first start.
No, at the very beginning. Right.
When you're just. Yeah, yeah.
First, first, two, three, four weeks, first month,
you will get so fit so fast and it will show
that if you if let's say you have two people starting off
on similar appearances and fitnesses, I'll see you in two months.
OK, one guy goes to the gym because all the shit they do at the gym.
And you do this.
Oh, my gosh.
You compare after one month what the the two look like.
The guy goes to the gym, maybe be a little more broad shoulder
and look a little chunkier or whatever, but you will not have the fitness
that you will perfectly match.
In other words, all your muscles working together,
especially when you're working just on negative resistance.
So, again, I'm not I'm not saying just do negative resistance,
but just do negative resistance to start out to reward yourself
with a very rapid muscle, you know, muscle growth and development
at the very end and at the very beginning.
And the very beginning could be the full 30 days. Right.
So but if you find yourself going out of breath,
whether it's the full positive, you know, the positive movement
and the negative movement of either one of those things,
even just push ups would be fine because push ups does contract
the torso as well.
You're using abdominal muscles and that's how you keep your back straight.
Right back in the abdominals the same. Right.
So you can even just do push ups alone if you were to do anything,
because getting a pull up bar could be tricky in many cases.
And sit ups are not comfortable and they don't do much anyway.
So I'm not just saying do the negative part of the resistance,
I'm saying do both, but don't be dissuaded.
Focus just on the negative and you will see the rewards
because no one can tout the rewards of the negative resistance only
because no one goes for it. No one does it.
It's like, oh, I call you three push ups.
What about four? It's really hard, but I still try. No, no, no.
Right. So I just want to point this out because it's a some one of the things
it's something you can do to just feel like a more like you're going to
feel like you've achieved something because well, as we get into the future,
when the whole world falls back into barbarism, your physical strength
and physical prowess and physical condition will be very important. Right.
They even show it in horror movies or whatever,
whenever a crowd of people are running away and it's the fat kid that gets eaten
first. Right. Oh, whatever. Yeah. You see. So you don't want, you know,
but what I'm saying, you know,
when you're being chased by a bunch of hoodlums that are now cannibalistic
warlord gangs. Right. You know, there's an old saying,
you don't have to outrun the, you don't have to outrun a bear,
just need to outrun the other guy.
You don't, yeah. You don't have to outrun a bear.
You just got to outrun the slowest guy in the group.
Yeah, that's right. Yeah. So yeah, just I need to have, oh, whatever. Yeah.
So I'm bringing this up just because it's been coming up lately in my own
personal life. And, and I just wanted to share this.
Cause I never shared it like this because you're not going to find this anywhere.
It's just so stupid. How, once you do this, right?
Once you figure out what I've just said or employ it,
you'll feel like you're cheating. You'll feel like you're cheating.
Cause if you've ever tried to get in shape before with a gym or whatever,
and you're like, it's so slow. I have to be so careful. It's so hard to do.
And you do this. And in like two weeks,
you look tremendous and you feel great in a month.
You'll be completely different human being almost. Um, don't force yourself,
do the negative resistance, not only do the positive. You can do 10,
20 pushups, the full pushup. Fine.
If it gets to like 20 and he can't do it, stop. And if you want to do more,
do the negative only don't push yourself. Okay.
If enough people learn this,
we'll put all the gyms out of business because you'll end up saying,
you go to the gym for a month and I'll go do this for a month.
And you compare like, what the hell are you?
It doesn't look like you did anything. And look at me, I'm ripped, right?
In 30 days. So I just wanted to share this.
Because it's like, my gosh, you know, this information needs to get out there.
There you go.