Number 5, Sonic Event, Ocelli and the Greek Rated Y.
I am Ocelli, alright, that's all you really need to know about me.
What do we know about the Greek?
Well, you know, as you listen, perhaps you learn about him, perhaps you don't.
Perhaps you just get other rarefied information.
And you know, there's been some stuff in the chat lately, Greek, that is going to be part
of what is discussed today.
I'll leave that to you to decide where it is we go with it, but could be a really interesting
interaction.
And if you are listening to this, you're obviously subscribed to Ocelli and the Greek Rated Y,
but you may not have noticed the little chat box, which you can participate in, even anonymously
if you choose to, and it is there.
We're not running it, but we do have administrative privileges in there, so be sensible about
your communications in there, and enter your thoughts about what it is you're hearing.
Okay, now I've done enough of an ad for something that we don't need to do an ad for.
Greek, how are you doing today?
Yeah, good.
I could tell you I'm slightly anonymous myself.
I go as the Greek, but look, this is what I do.
I did find out I'm the only Greek I know.
So that's a good thing at this point.
But yeah, the chat's been very good.
Everything's been very civil, in air quotes, and we knew it would be, because when you
do things the way we're doing them now, they're going to end up better.
So yeah, look, this is Sonic 5, which is an odd number.
People don't like talking about the number 5.
They talk about 6 as being whatever, and 7 as being whatever, but 5 is kind of odd.
It's also the number that comes right before man comes on the scene symbolically on the
spiritual realm.
So being odd-
Interesting thing about number 5, though, is that people do work in 5s, right?
I mean, denominations of money almost always have 5s involved in the equation.
5 is a fairly good collection of something where you don't have a couple, which is 2,
and you don't have a few, which is 3.
You do have a grouping of something now, and significantly, I think the 5th Sonic element
means now there's a significant grouping of this series.
How about that?
Yeah, and also, well, look, odd numbers promote odd groupings.
Let's say you're buying terminals or things that comp light bulbs or anything that you
want to get in pairs.
Sometimes they'll sell it to you in an odd number, like 3 or 5, or like batteries or whatever.
So if you need an even number, you've got to buy an entire new package, right?
Yeah, true.
You notice that's being done in marketing?
But what's interesting about here-
Most devices ask you to use 2 or multiples of 2, so it's an even number usually, right?
Yeah, well, it's like I'm buying electronic parts and their terminals, which are positive,
negative, just even numbers, but they'll sell you an odd number, so you have to get an-
Anyway, but no selling here.
Here's the thing.
Being odd, referring back to the chat, let's just get right to business.
Cloning has come up, and I've brought it up, and I want to discuss that, and I can discuss
stuff, not just what people discuss when they spend too much time on the internet, but little
clues and cues and things, and I'll give a little more history on how I found it to be
very plausible and what is mostly available, but also it's mostly twisted.
You cannot discuss cloning without discussing things that are held in secret, but shown
to the public as something else.
Well, is that due to the fact, though, that there is a guaranteed spiritual element to
this, as well as the scientific and the supposedly secular, moralistic considerations?
I mean, is it because it crosses so many boundaries?
It's not something that can be relegated only to the spiritual and only to the scientific
and only to the political, et cetera, et cetera?
I mean, is that the reason why it's not really discussed in a serious fashion in most places?
I mean, even when you go to some of these publications where they're supposed to, it
seems like, eh, look, surface level, here you go.
I don't know.
Is that it?
Yeah.
Well, you know the Swiss Army approach.
It's the one little thing that does multiple things, but you can't use it as the main
tool, right?
Right.
But the Swiss Army approach is, there's always a spiritual component to anything, but
the main overarching Swiss Army application of the spiritual component is the overarching
spiritual aspect that there is a controlling body on the earth that is here to prevent
or implement methods and whatever in society where people never, will never, that's in
a sense, will never realize who they really are or what they're capable of.
That is the overarching spiritual element to anything, is that whether you want to look
at religion, look at what organized religions do, right?
Look at what science does, right?
Everything's materialistic.
All of the spiritual components to almost any subject in this incarnation, in this era,
this age, is to prevent people from understanding what they're capable of.
And it goes all the way down to the conversations.
How many times have you heard, that was a really, I can't have a decent conversation,
right?
Well, that is the result of this spiritual element, which is basically to present people
with, let's say, funneling into the lower aspect of what they really are versus what
they can be.
That's the overarching part of it.
It's funny, I'm starting to hear this sentiment now, and not quite articulated exactly as
you did just now, but I'm starting to hear it from some others who do seem to have some
level of awareness about the game being played.
I mean, let's be honest here.
There's an anti-human agenda.
It is certainly being run by a group of conspirators, okay?
And the thing is, realistically, the actual, you know, the big players, right, the high
rollers in this casino, are unseen.
They are unknown.
Their names are not publicized.
They're not on the idiotic rectangles.
They're not there.
You don't see them.
You do see their works, but you don't see them.
Yeah, and they never have been seen, by the way.
There's references, like you've heard of the Magi class and all that.
Even that's a little too much.
You know, people do research on the Magi, and the reason I bring that up is because
it goes back a long time.
Well, you know, we discussed recently, if you've heard their name, seen their face,
heard their voice or whatever, they're just a front puppet or a front man.
They're not the ones calling the shots.
But they do have some power.
So let's say, you know, the local authority, who's a puppet, wherever you might be, and
the lower, the less they have to administer, actually, the more, less of a puppet they
are.
Like, so for example, if you talk about the U.S., the worst puppet is the president.
And then as you go down, then it's the vice president and speaker of the house, your
main senators and main congressmen.
But as you go lower down to something called assemblymen, which are even lower than a
congress, they are pretty free.
They're not that manipulated, believe it or not.
Right?
Yeah, they can show up like once a week or once a month.
Yeah, they're not that important because it's kind of like, you know, there's a
biblical thing where the ruler of thousands, ruler of hundreds, and the rulers of tens.
Right?
So the tens would be very local.
Hundreds would be, let's say, on a state level.
The ruler of thousands would be on, say, a federal level, which I don't like that
word.
Anyone look up the word federal.
What it means is that you, it's a religious term.
Right?
So, but anyway, the aspect of today's discussion is that when we say something very
simple like, let's discuss cloning on this.
You really can't without discussing, let's say, nuclear agenda, the general propaganda
on society, the faceless unseen enemy threat, all of that.
And I want to get into some detail.
And the thing is, this is often discussed on the web, but I want to bring it from the
angle that we do.
And, and how it's actually knowledge of what we're going to be discussing of it
actually can be useful.
What do you think?
Oh, absolutely.
I think that over and over again, it is a repeatable.
It is a constant, even that there are, well, an array of invisible enemies, so to
speak, invisible.
Some of them imagined some of them quite not imaginary at all, but all equally
invisible.
I mean, even.
Well, here, look, I want to interject this step on you just for a second.
Let's go to the end.
You know, like sometimes I tell people, give me the important part first.
Let's say you're making a cell phone call and someone says, Hey, I got to tell you
something.
It's really important.
And then you lose, lose battery power or lose connection.
You didn't get anything.
But if you say the, the, the important part first and then tell them that was
really important.
Did you get that?
You see?
So this is the most important part.
And this is just analogous again with the invisible enemy and however it was
originally, let's say it was a threat from another country or an ideology.
It was the communist, the Nazis or the Arab terrorists.
And then it becomes more and more invisible.
Ultimately, even as simple as the next tribe, you know, the, the tribes that
will come from outside of the area, you've never seen them before, but
they're coming.
Little green men from Mars or whatever.
We'll cover that too.
So, so, but here's the ultimate thing.
I'm just going to give the important part here before we even get into the
whole sonic is once what's past the embassy, we went from a uniform or
ethnicity or something to identify to something you cannot identify.
And it could be anywhere like a 1984 type thing.
It could be anywhere, anyone, where does that lead to?
Here's the simple analogy.
And they've been putting this out for a while now, and this is what it's
going to lead to.
You've heard of the climate change, right?
Sure.
Okay.
And they're saying that it's manmade.
Ultimately it has nothing to do with climate change or carbon or anything
like that.
It has to do with making you the enemy because they're blaming it on you.
So ultimately you go from an enemy identifiable one unseen to one
invisible unidentifiable.
And it always ends up as you are the enemy.
And when you are the enemy in any, in an organism at war with itself is doomed.
And it's not only a war with itself on a familial or local level, but in
eternally, you see.
It's to the point where I can't take it anymore.
I'm going to go jump off a tall building or cut my wrists or blow my head off.
That's the ultimate goal of this, self-destruction.
Okay.
So when you hear climate change and they're blaming it on everyone, your
activities, you know, your carbon footprint, the next step is that you are
the enemy and we don't have to give you a reason anymore.
So end it now, right?
You see, this is a, basically it's the old Mission Impossible self-destruct
tape, right?
This tape will self-destruct in 30 seconds is the agenda, self-destruction.
Okay.
So that's the most important crux of this.
So let's get into it.
Coning.
Yeah, strategically it's sensible, by the way, because, look, if you have an
enemy that you can never escape because you are it, guess what?
Eventually exhaustion will set in.
Fatigue will take its toll.
So there you go.
You just blow yourself up and your problems will go away, right?
That's what the climate change is about.
Well, that's why the people basically become the enemy with these political
things, which are, again, more.
Well, we'll talk about that, what the politics really are.
I know everybody knows it's bullshit, but there's another thing there.
Let's get into cloning.
Sure.
Let's jump into it.
Okay.
Well, everybody's got the sense of what that means, right?
A copy.
But, you know, nature, there's a guy, Oshi or someone, some guru, he said
that nature doesn't make carbon copies.
And it's true.
That's why, for example, when something is cloned, with basic scientific
analysis, they could tell if the cell is an original or it's a clone based
on certain proteins that are present.
And I've been looking into this for a little while because I'm doing some
research on biopolymers, in other words, like plastics that are not made from
petroleum, but using more natural plant based materials, right?
So for structural stuff.
So I'm kind of like in a project with that for a little while because the
biggest problem with making biopolymers is making them chemical and water
resistant, right?
So if we go back to the cloning concept, first of all, I want to say that the
powers that be from the cosmic rule, they invented science fiction back in
the 30s, 40s.
I mean, yes, science fiction goes back to the 1890s, right?
They invented that to sort of put these thoughts in people's heads so the
thought was there, whether it's to be, let's say you have the white hat, the
positive part of the elite that say we want to help humanity.
We can't say this.
How many times have you heard someone publishing a book on something and
they'll say, the publisher will come back and say, we don't want to publish
it, but if you want to publish it as fiction, we'll publish it, right?
It's very simple.
The cosmic rule is once you're aware of an idea because of what's possible,
it doesn't matter if it's fiction category or fact.
You are made aware of that idea.
That's what matters.
So in science fiction, which I call disclosure, we've seen, let's say,
enough about cloning.
So we're not going to really go down that aspect.
What I want to do, maybe start out with when you start getting involved in
things that whether you hear about it or read about it and you say, that's
interesting.
I have enough free time to engage it.
A lot of people do that with Tesla technology and other things like that,
Victor Schauberger less so, but they get into little science projects if you
have the wherewithal and if you're that type of person.
So about a decade ago, I reached the peak with that and I had left Tucson
with a Victor Schauberger device, a water imploder that I built.
It took about six months to build and I was able to take tap water, any tap
water, and transform it into comparable to the best quality spring waters in
the world.
In other words, when you drank this water, it was unusually refreshing and
then within a few minutes, you became invigorated as if you had taken some
kind of a drug that would invigorate you.
Use your imagination, right?
It gave you incredible clarity and some people witnessed healings and things
like that, but just what the best water quality in the world would be using
tap water.
I was peddling this water in L.A., Hollywood, Beverly Hills area, Venice
Beach area, and all that.
It was interesting as word got around that we had the best water in the world
and we're able to transform any water into it.
So when you start getting involved with stuff like that, you have what I call
in air quotes, characters start appearing out of nowhere or someone knows
someone who knows someone who might be interested to talk to you kind of thing,
right?
So we had this one character.
He was quite interesting and his job was working for Coca-Cola, Pepsi,
and Nestle.
He was a free agent and he was a geologist.
What does Coca-Cola, Pepsi, and Nestle have in common?
They all need water for their drinks and things, right?
So he had a company and it was a surveying, it was a geologist, and his thing
was he was hired to go out up and down the west coast to find springs,
water springs, natural sources.
So then these companies would go in and claim the spring and pump the water out
for free, basically, and use it in their drinks, right?
Right.
So when he would find a spring that was extremely unusual, like the quality was
almost, quote-unquote, magical, like this incredible water, almost like drinking
it and you feel like you've done cocaine or whatever.
By the way, if you haven't done cocaine, don't do it.
I'm not a proponent of that, but if someone were to describe what doing Coke
was like was, have you ever gotten some really good news, how it made you feel?
Yeah, sure, sure, sure.
That would be what it felt like.
So drinking this water or cocaine, for example.
Right.
But anyway, this was his job.
I will say that naturally occurring, by the way, just some of this stuff that
they're doing.
One other thing that Coke and Pepsi and all those companies would have in common
too is the need for containers.
Well, they make them.
Yeah, the containers, I found out, well, because I was a proponent of glass,
but what I found with plastic containers, let's say you're just a side tangent,
but just people wonder about where they get those millions and millions of
containers per day or per hour, right?
When you're a bottling company like that and you use those plastic containers,
you don't buy the containers.
You buy a machine that makes them and you get bags and pallets of pellets,
and the pellet goes into the machine.
The machine is about maybe it will fit in a large garage, let's say,
and out in the other end a bottle is popped out, and that's how they do it.
You don't buy the bottles.
You buy the machine that makes the bottles on the spot.
I've seen them.
They're pretty neat.
And that's why there's always separate local entities, your local bottler.
It's a totally different thing.
Let's get back to the what, because I think I dragged this out a little too long.
Well, no problem.
I also wanted to just state that the guys looking around for these springs,
they do happen.
Like there's one near here that is the Creek Indians allow people access to it
or whatever.
Sure.
I want to stay on it and keep it to cloning.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But I'm just saying that naturally.
This is why.
I'm not trying to push you around,
but what I'm trying to say is that if I get into a water tangent,
we'll be here two hours later talking about water.
Yeah, no, I don't want to do water.
I'm just saying that there's a difference between naturally occurring
and something that you do by process.
But this is the point.
I'm giving a background on this guy because he wasn't just someone that was
hired by these companies to do that.
He had other things he was doing, and this is it.
So if he found one of these magical water springs that were extremely high
quality, he got into the office at the end of the day.
And what did he put on his report?
I didn't find anything today.
Right.
He kept it from these guys.
And I said, well, what for?
He says, because there are certain things that people are involved with,
certain people that require certain water quality of the highest degree.
And we started, I visited him a second time.
I said, okay, great.
Certain people.
Okay, so you're working for certain people already, but you're talking about
another certain people.
Yes.
Okay.
What was interesting about that is that we started getting into conversations,
and it got into what the subject is, cloning.
Somehow he ensued enough about it.
I said, do you mean like cloning, cellular regeneration?
He says, well, look, you know about Walter Russell.
I said, yeah, I've got one of his books, Universal One.
He says, well, you know, him and Victor Shawberger had correspondence.
I said, really?
And he said, well, what was it about?
He says, what it was about was to get these men to understand that the ultra
high-quality natural water had properties that most people are not aware of,
but are aware, again, by some people.
And the point was Victor Shawberger and Walter Russell were both given a task
to see if they can manipulate other waters to act like this water.
And the task was this.
He explained it to me.
I'm going to connect this.
They were told to take rose petals and place them in a glass of this water
and keep at room temperature without a cover and keep the rose petals alive
and looking like the day they were picked for over a year.
Think about that.
Anybody's gotten flower cuttings and things like that.
What does it look like even after a week if they even make it, right?
Yeah.
You've got to put it in water and you've got to keep switching the water out.
Yeah, and the florist keeps them under, you know, in a chill box and all that.
So the task with these guys was to put the fresh rose petals in a glass of water,
a container of water, open at the top, and keep them looking fresh for a year.
Walter Russell succeeded.
Okay.
How do you do that?
That sounds like magic or it sounds like really unusual stuff.
And the conversations were around that.
And, by the way, he did like the water I purveyed.
He says, if you didn't have the best water, like people say,
I wouldn't be here talking to you.
Getting approval from someone like that was very good.
But, anyway, we had roundabout discussions about things are not as they seem.
So here's the idea of someone putting in my head that you can keep rose petals looking like they were freshly cut
for over a year in an open container at room temperature.
There's something going on with this water quality thing.
Okay.
So fast forward, this was one of the main things that I recall.
Vinny Eastwood and I, back in 2011 or so, I was a frequent caller.
And, you know, you and I know Danny.
Danny knew about me.
He always said, oh, you should get a show here, you know, and all that.
I think you might know a little bit of the history before you and I even met with Danny, right?
Yeah, sure.
So he was fond of what I had to say and myself, and it was mutual.
So I was following Vinny Eastwood, and I was like, you know, I don't want to stick with Vinny too much because I'm not going in that direction.
I'm not into politics and making jokes about things.
I'm into sharing information that people can use.
So I kind of watched around a little while, and he had this guy come on once and do an interview called Donald Marshall,
a young guy who sounded kind of wacky.
He talked about his experience at cloning centers.
And I was like, oh, wait a second.
I know about cloning.
Most people know about it from science fiction and all that.
On some level, yeah.
Yeah, and here's this guy not only talking about cloning but an underground world, an underground society,
and he's giving it with personal experiences with great specificity.
But this is the other part.
When he said how does the cloning happen, it's basically the tissue is held in a water solution with some nutrients,
maybe some electrical impulses, and it's slightly agitated.
And I was like, oh, my goodness.
Okay, he's telling the truth because this stuff is really, really simple.
Right?
Even though his story was really far out there, just as far out as any science fiction,
maybe even further because science fiction doesn't get as broad as describing little real reptilians.
Right?
But at that moment, I realized also the culmination of other things that I've been looking at
and how ignorant people are of things and how things are being used against them because of their ignorance
and told that there are other things.
I started piecing the cloning thing together in my own mind and watching it very slowly.
If you want to dive into a subject and you just want to dive, a hard dive into it for a week,
you're not going to get that much.
But if you keep it active in the back of your mind for years and years and years,
you'll end up collecting enough information to piece it together and see what's plausible and what's not.
Right.
Which we'll get into because you and I were talking about the plausibility of what happened in Manhattan in 2001
and I want to get into that too.
I really do.
I got it.
It's important.
So here's the thing.
I'm going to jump out of the cloning and get back to it.
You cannot talk about cloning without talking about nuclear or atomic devices.
You cannot talk about nuclear or atomic devices and cloning if you're not talking about what the agenda is
will ultimately lead that people will believe that they are the enemies themselves instead of being paranoid.
So these are all inextricably inseparable.
The reason why is because all these things are being used without the people realizing
and taking advantage of their ignorance as them being projected as something else.
So going back to the cloning, a couple of things that I've had in the back of my mind that made it plausible
more than ever just on my own discovery without like watching a YouTube on some talking head
or someone talking about what's going on.
There was, it might still be on YouTube, a news, just a regular local news thing.
And it started off by saying, oh yeah, these burn victims that lost a lot of their skin have new hope
and we're going to go visit today.
So they basically it was a laboratory that was growing skin from the person's same skin
like basically cloning skin in a lab that would then be brought back and grafted onto their skin and so their body.
And it starts off with maybe a second and a half shot of a motion video of a man standing in front of a table
that was slowly oscillating, shaking back and forth through all these glass containers on it.
Nothing technical, almost like the rose petals in the water with no container, no cover.
And it looked like just chicken skin in there.
And then the camera moves to the guy sitting at a table who looks like an eight and a half by 11 piece of paper, jagged,
puts it on something that looks like a butcher block and scrapes the top off and holds it up.
And it's like semi-translucent and says, this is what we're looking for.
This is what's going to save these people.
And she says that, oh, this is made from the same, the person's cells.
So it's not going to be rejected.
We take a sample and then we grow it here.
And she's like, you grow it?
So this was a short news thing of how this laboratory is growing skin from their own skin.
So if they're showing this on mainstream local news, well, they're growing skin.
Can someone else be growing bones and eyeballs and feet and hair?
Of course.
I heard about this growing skin thing.
I had a stepfather in the 80s who had suffered severe burns.
And this has just been a matter of fact for quite a while that they grow some skin.
They take some healthy skin from somewhere, if you've been burned, right, and they grow it
and they bring it back and then they graft it over the damaged area and repair it.
And then it grows together and boom, there you go.
Yeah, and that's still the materialist low level, but on the higher level,
if anyone wants to look up chromotherapy by Dinshaw-Garialdi from the turn of the century,
and I have personal experience with this, and it's all been very well documented,
severe burn victims that they couldn't do anything with
and basically loaded them with morphine until they died from infection for not having 90% of their skin.
He would put them under an extremely bright, intense blue light alternating with yellows and greens,
and within two weeks they grew all their skin back and looked like they never had a burn before.
Which, by the way, his laboratory, Dinshaw-Garialdi of chromotherapy,
or basically color and light therapy, he was out in Jersey in the 1920s,
and his lab was bombed with firebombs, but the reporting here, like this in the newspaper,
was they interviewed the locals and they said, yeah, an Army airplane,
which was very crude back then, flew over the house and dropped a bomb on his house.
And that's why the lab, because this is clearly Army on there.
What year was this?
In the late 20s, early 30s, something. You could look up.
So that's really rudimentary aircraft there.
Very basic, because they had not gotten into aircraft until that time initially.
It was still a biplane or whatever.
There's still no Air Force yet.
No, Air Force was after World War II.
Right, that's what I'm saying. I mean, it's way before that.
It was the Air Corps. Yeah, so they still do that today, by the way.
This is kind of like the thing about secrets or whatever.
I don't know if you remember out in San Francisco, they said a gas,
it was very heavily covered in the news about 10 or 12 years ago,
a gas pipe exploded and destroyed a neighborhood.
Well, I've actually talked this to someone who was at the gas company
that comes around sometimes, and they're laughing.
They said, yeah, of course they would do that.
What they do is if you're like a political subversive
or they really want to get rid of you and they just can't take it anymore,
well, you know, like the reporter whose Mercedes blows up on the street
and they said it because he hit a tree or whatever.
Well, back then what they did with this woman in San Francisco,
they flew an F-16 and basically stung her missile into her house
and blew up the house.
You could see the crater. It's definitely a missile.
Before the smoke even cleared, the gas company is dispatched to go out there,
and what they did is they took some old gas mains that they had in their yard
and just started dumping the gas pipes on the street
to make it look like it was a gas pipe.
But clearly you see that conical, inverse cone blast crater where the house was,
and then about 100 feet away you see all these 30-foot or 20-foot lengths
of crooked rusty pipe laid out in the street.
There's no way that those lengths of pipe came out from that crater.
Just to show TV, this is how ridiculous it is.
Anyway, back to the cloning and how it has to be connected to nukes
and all this other stuff is very important.
But what I've surmised at this point also is that skin can be grown,
organic tissue can be grown simply by being in a certain quality of water
and agitated and nutrients and things like that.
So if we go back to Donald Marshall and see that they're grown in tanks
and this and that, I'm not going to get into his testimony.
Anyone could look him up.
His interview with Vinnie Eastwood is a pretty good well-covered one.
So I filed all this away.
Because to say you can clone and make another human is quite advanced.
We're given a documentary on how we've advanced from horse and carriage
to a jet airplane or whatever, but they left this out.
Wow. So why? Rated Y.
Another thing came up.
This was about five years ago.
An article, because I researched the Middle East.
Mummies were found.
And in the article it stated that these mummies were clones.
And I shared this with some people and they said,
oh, they're cloning mummies.
I said, no, no.
These are Egyptian mummies.
They said that the DNA and all that was a clone.
In other words, this mummy is over 2,500 years old
and it doesn't have direct human DNA.
It has the DNA of a cloned human.
So the Egyptians.
Ergo, they had cloning technology.
They had cloning technology.
And I was like, what the hell is going on?
I'm showing this article.
People say, oh, they're cloning mummies.
I said, no, no, no, no.
This mummy is a clone.
So it's really hard to make the connection.
So all these little things, I'm bringing up these points.
I'm not going to sit here and review what you could research on your own.
I'm not a big proponent of sitting and watching hour-long videos about cloning
because, you know, it's fine.
In other words, you're not going to get it all and sit in one week of looking at it.
You have to keep the subject open.
Well, right.
And I would also look at, look, slight diversion here.
But, I mean, the idea, the reason why somebody is saying, well, they're cloning mummies
is because that idea was already introduced in not just science fiction,
but I'll go for a silly example that just came to my head.
G.I. Joe, remember there was a cartoon series for a while?
Or, by the way, the cloning mummies of Jurassic Park, cloning dinosaurs, right?
So previous to cloning dinosaurs, right, G.I. Joe had this,
where they came up with a character that was meant to be cloned
from all these DNA samples of various people.
They came up with, I think it was called Serpentor or something.
Anyway, you know, because Cobra is the enemy, the snake is the enemy, right?
Anyway, we'll leave that alone.
But the point is that they introduced this in a kid's cartoon.
Okay?
In the 1980s, without a problem.
Where they're like, look, they're taking the Egyptian, the pharaohs,
and I forget who else they threw in there, but it was something like the pharaohs,
Napoleon, great conquerors.
It's everywhere.
They do start with the children.
You know, some of the highly advanced materials, like the metal,
you could crumble into a ball, and then it goes, you know,
you heat it with a blow dryer and it goes memory metal.
Yeah.
And the little levitating objects, right?
They always put it in a kid's toy.
There was kid's toys.
There's, as we say, kids, right?
People know what I mean by that.
In Japan, there was several people that have gotten in trouble between the 70s
and the early 2000s for taking a lot of these black project secret materials
and energy systems and putting them in children's toys.
And they had been, you can look this up, I forgot the name of the individual,
but he was put in prison and then he kind of disappeared.
He was working in these advanced material laboratories
and giving the he was actually charging it himself.
In other words, he was putting the money out to have the toy company make it.
So you basically had, between the late 70s and the early 2000s,
because of this guy, children's toys in Japan that represented, you know,
technology that's still not made public today.
So it is put out.
Then what a better way to do it.
Well, and they also normalized these things.
I point this one out.
I don't know what you think of it, but, I mean, what did they do?
They started with the drones.
Those were toys to start.
They were crappy toys, a lot of them.
But there were toys initially that had varying qualities that children controlled,
that they could fly around.
They put cameras on them, boom, drone.
And the drones have become more and more of a discussion and then sort of stopped.
But drone stuff, being out there in the kids' toys.
Now, I recognize there were military applications before that, but still.
Well, any application, you could spy on your neighbor.
Well, right.
But that's the thing, is they normalized this first with kids' toys
and then created the adult hobby version of it and blah, blah, blah.
But the point is that they were letting you know what was already in use in parts right there.
So I find that interesting all the time.
It was normalized that way.
So now somebody sees a little.
It's part of cosmic law.
Whether you put it out as fiction or as a toy, are you aware of it?
That's what it's about.
Right.
So here's the other thing.
I also had some, go back to the cloning.
Right.
I had some discussions with someone who, local, Raytheon is here,
and they make guidance systems for missiles and things like that.
And he's a language kind of guy.
So when they send, let's say, missiles over, they don't send it through UPS or DHL or whatever,
and you open the package when you get the missiles.
They actually send technicians to train you and set them up.
So he had several languages, and he would go to several countries in the world.
And the cloning issue came up with him once just about,
this was after the time when, you remember, Saddam Hussein had 14 body doubles and all that.
Well, I was in a discussion last night that Alexander the Great had body doubles.
Caesar had body doubles.
Everyone has body doubles throughout history.
This is a common thing.
Yeah, you can discover that constantly.
Any leader who is, you know, supposedly the idea is that since they're in danger of being assassinated,
body doubles are either recruited or created one way or another.
And it's, you know, sometimes they go on casting calls to look for people and whatever.
Right.
Sometimes, yeah, go ahead.
Or in a very superstitious society, they could be one place at one time,
and an hour later they're what normally would take two days to travel to appear there, right?
No, even if they're psychic.
Superstitious people would lend that to be godlike.
Hillary Clinton pulled that once when she was in Australia,
and then three hours later she's making a speech in the Netherlands.
And how is that possible?
Yeah, because it takes like 20 hours or whatever to get to the Netherlands physically.
By airplane.
Yeah, by airplane.
It could be underground railroad.
But here, this technical guy, we brought up cloning, and he says,
oh, yeah, of course they're clones.
He said, how do you perceive that?
What makes it plausible for you?
And he says, the minimalization of the security apparatus surrounding these leaders.
And we got into it, and I was like, of course.
So if you look at the security apparatus, we're not talking about, let's say, what they did to JFK,
but the typical security apparatus around these leaders and famous people,
if you notice, is at a bare minimum right now.
So what I mean by that is what they do is they put a clone out in public,
and if the clone is kidnapped, because the kidnapping world works by hire.
You can go on the dark web, not that I have, but I've heard this,
and if you want to kidnap someone, there are people for hire that do that.
They're usually ex-special ops military, right?
Yes.
Yeah, and the kidnapping is just the basic thing for ransom, for money.
So you have a minimal security apparatus, let's say a president, minister,
or whoever is kidnapped, and it's a clone, and they ask for the money.
All they do is push a button and blow up the clone.
What do they have left?
Nothing, right?
So the word has gotten around in the black ops, retired black ops kidnapping community
that don't bother kidnapping the president or prime minister or Johnny Depp or whatever,
because chances are if you grab them from public, it's going to be a clone.
You've got nothing.
So the kidnapping and the hostage thing has gone to a minimum with this,
and it's very clear to see the minimal security apparatus around these dignitaries
that go to memorials and things.
It's just like two black SUVs.
What the hell, right?
They don't care because they know it's not the real individual,
which leads to if it's a clone, how does it get up and make a speech?
Because what came up in the chat is yes, they could reproduce the body.
Notice I'm not getting into in-depth too much.
I'm just giving you my personal experiences with conversations
with people that made it more plausible for me.
Again, anyone could go and listen to the Donald Marshall,
which I don't wholly approve, but it's the best stuff out there and other things on their own.
But here's the thing.
What was brought up by an anon in the chat was very, very vital,
is that the consciousness transfer,
there's only one spirit of you.
Yes, there is possibly talk about being able to split you with split personalities,
but when people are asleep, if you've ever read Stalking the Wild Pendulum by Isaac Bentov,
one of the things that I've got out of that book was that your consciousness is always being used,
especially when you're asleep.
You're not using it, and the reason why you sleep is because someone else is using your consciousness.
And that kind of gets into the real woo-woo spooky airy-fairy zone for me,
because I need more than that.
Right, and we barely touched upon this when we were talking about external input,
and briefly we discussed sleep, and you kind of pivoted away from the topic real fast.
Yes, because I have my own personal experiences with that, not dreams,
and just being able to see things that maybe I shouldn't see or can see or should see,
however you want to say it,
that I have not been able to put together where I can express it in a coherent way yet.
But the essence of this is also our minds are always broadcasting and receiving.
And an example of that is you ever notice when people develop a teenage, adolescent almost body,
they've actually changed, they've gotten larger, more adult-like, they like to stay up all night.
And the reason why is because now because the brains are physically larger,
they're tuning into a different frequency,
all of the adults that are broadcasting all this garbage stop broadcasting because they're asleep.
So now the airwaves are clear.
And I find that to myself also.
If I'm pondering or contemplating something and I'm not making progress,
I deliberately set it up that I do stay awake all night when most of the society is asleep
because the airwaves are cleaner.
I mean, think of the mainstream individual, what they think of, and they're broadcasting this.
We're not talking about radio or speaking.
This is just in their minds.
You don't want that in the air.
I've always said I functionally feel better and do better late at night because of this.
Yeah, when all the radios are shut down, basically asleep.
Well, the consciousness transfer, what I've also gotten maybe about,
this might have been even during the time of the first ONG run,
I was speaking to someone in Texas because I've had a lot of interesting people
just come out of the woodwork on a Skype call or a telephone call, believe it or not,
or meeting in person.
And this one individual, first he says,
I'm probably one of the most dangerous people alive because of my criminal mindset.
I was like, what? I don't have a criminal mindset.
He says what he meant by that is that I have a mindset that allows me to go around obstacles,
things that are put in front of people, ideas.
I usually am able to drive around and see what's going on on the inside.
So we got into a few things and the cloning thing came up again.
And the consciousness transfer, basically, without getting into the little fine details
that may not be pertinent, what I wanted to get out of him is how is the conscious transferred?
He says it looks like a claw and it's magnetic.
You ever go to one of these carnivals or airport and they've got a thing you put a quarter in
and it's a claw, you move around with a joystick and you pick up a stuffed animal or a prize
and you drop it down the chute to get it?
I was like, yeah.
He says it's something like that.
And I was like, oh my goodness.
Oh man, how do you make something like that up, right?
And again, people don't want to give too much history or whatever,
but I've come across characters like that that have just come out of nowhere
and want to have a conversation and engage me.
If I ask, I know when they reach the limit and whatnot, but you know me,
I'm going to push it like, why, why, why?
Like a little child, why, why, why?
But in a way that makes things coherent, you know, not in an annoying way, hopefully.
So the cloning and the secrecy go hand in hand.
I want to tie this in with the nuclear aspect, the atomic aspect, because that is also secrecy.
How many times have you heard what the Rosenbergs, what they executed them in the 50s
for sharing secrets with the Soviets, right?
So they were trying to tell you it was very serious, even, you know, it still is.
The reason why this is important is just like I mentioned,
the cloning and the security apparatus, how minimal it is.
Because if you, let's say you're going to go kidnap a dignitary or a famous person,
you're probably going to kidnap a clone if they're just two black SUVs
and no security apparatus, right?
So it makes it worthless.
What they've done, and this is also with the agendas, ever since the 80s,
and by the way, I'm going to bring up Dmitry Kaluzov with a K.
Look up his stuff.
Again, I don't wholly endorse him, but, you know, the stuff that he says on this
is verifiable and validatable.
He has some weird ideas about certain things, but that's fine.
You pick and choose.
What he brought forward is that all these, like, car bombings and truck bombings
all the way to the World Trade Center are not possible, physically impossible,
as you're being told.
And they're actually nukes.
And, okay, I'm listening.
And when I started looking into it, it was 100% correct,
meaning that from a physics perspective, in other words,
when you go and study physics, there are certain linear,
quote-unquote, Newtonian values and things that are quite measurable, right?
Like, if you're working with electronics and you have a voltmeter
and you're measuring, like, voltage, amperage, and resistance,
that's very linear, but it works quite well.
The concept of blowing things up, which if you've ever talked to a mining engineer,
you know, the hard rock mining where they put dynamite to blast rock,
they don't like using terms like explosives or blowing things up for whatever reason.
It might be, what's that thing that listens to everything you say, right?
And they tag you if you use certain words, what is it called, echelon or something like that.
Yeah, that kind of stuff.
Maybe it's because of that.
But what they use, they call it high-speed chemistry.
And what's interesting is when you research explosives, I said the word again,
you know they're rated in feet per second, right?
Like, so dynamite's in the 1,200 to 2,000 feet per second when the reaction happens.
Then you've got C4, and then they go up to CDX and all this other stuff.
It's in the 5,000 to 6,000 feet per second, right?
So it's the higher feet per second that this has, the more powerful it is, right?
Is the idea.
Okay, so this is all linear stuff.
So if you show a crater, let's say they say this was a car bomb, okay, that blew up here.
And anyone that has some basic training in the field, usually from military or mining,
those are the easiest people to access.
If you tell him what it was, you know, soil instead of solid rock, let's say a paved road,
and the crater is 30 feet in diameter and 25 feet deep and it has this shape,
he'll pull out a calculator and he'll tell you if it's, let's say they tell you it was a basic explosive,
he'll tell you that in order to blow a hole like that, you need five tons of dynamite.
Okay, and then you go back, and what was it, what kind of a vehicle was it that had the car bomb?
It was a Nissan Sentra.
Okay.
You know what happens if you put five tons, 10,000 pounds inside of a vehicle?
Impossible.
Right?
Okay.
Now here's the other thing, and this goes on and on and on.
This is very, very typical.
I wanted to say the other thing and the thought escaped me.
Yes.
Okay.
With nuclear, there is a pact amongst them, no atmospheric.
There was something, a cartoon or a Disney thing called The Incredibles or something,
it was an animation, and there was this little fashion designer, they wanted uniforms.
She goes, no capes, no capes.
Anybody has a cape, right?
Okay.
Okay, so I always think about it.
No atmospheric.
That's the rule.
So when you bring up the concept of nuclear and atomic, everyone is just like that woman Judy Wood.
Oh, it couldn't have been World Trade Center atomic because you have blinded by the light.
Right?
Well, that's all atmospheric.
Well, since the 60s, the pact is no atmospherics.
Underground.
Everything underground.
Sewer pipe, buried, under a building, whatever.
Never atmospheric.
Okay.
Right?
Because it's very identifiable.
Now, here's the thing.
Nuclear devices do not explode.
They're detonated.
And when the detonation happens, Dimitri gets into it a little bit.
Basically, it's a reaction of radiation of x-rays and gamma rays,
and they are so intense that the reaction depends on what the environment does.
So if it's in the air, the air is going to catch fire and it's going to glow a bright color.
If it's underground, you don't see any of that.
All of the material, irrespectively of what it is, vaporizes,
and then the instant vaporization of 10,000 degrees creates a shock wave.
And then anything that is around that shock wave becomes dustified, very fine dust,
just from the shock wave.
Okay?
It doesn't have to lose its shape.
But if it's a building like the World Trade Center stacked up,
if you turned it into talcum powder, of course it's going to collapse the way it did.
Right?
Okay.
So what's interesting about this is it's always a two-step reaction.
There's something called the Vela satellite,
and it's up there to monitor explosions on the Earth
to see if they're chemical explosion, which is a single reaction, boom, or nuclear.
Nuclear is always a double flash.
You have the initial detonation and then the reaction, what's called an explosion.
It's always a double event, always.
So that's how they detect them, in the ground or in the sky.
It's always a double.
So when they show you something that looks like an earthquake
and it's just an incredibly vertical line, that is a nuke, right,
where a natural earthquake will have a rumble on a seismometer
and then build up to a large peak.
So these are very, very measurable.
And based on what size nuke they are,
they are always judged by going back to classic explosives and tonnage.
Why is this important?
Okay, let's just fast forward.
Now, I'm not going to get into the World Trade Center stuff,
the nuclear demolition.
Go listen to Dimitri Kalozoi.
I have a four-hour video, you can still find it,
on how the World Trade Center was done.
He gets very technical, but in common parlance, you understand what he's saying.
The Murrell Building and all these other things.
So it's very easy to determine what's nuclear and what's not,
simply by saying, if that was a Nissan Sentra with a car bomb
and it required five tons of TNT to do it,
and they tell you it was TNT, you know that's a bullshit story.
So here's how you identify,
because this might be in a neighborhood near you.
For example, if you lived in the Middle East,
they do a lot of these car bombs that shatter windows for a mile
and create these big craters.
Well, I don't know who's listening here who might be there.
You might want to not be there immediately.
And this is how, right?
If it's a nuke, because even the new nukes,
the eighth generation that they're up to,
do not put out the radiation as old atomics do.
And I want to go back to how do you prevent yourself
from being exposed to this anyway.
Before that, I want to get into one thing.
You know how the flat earthers are running around
saying there's no globe, right?
You're an idiot if you believe that it's round.
There is also a movement that says there is no nukes, right?
So with the flat earth thing, I say yes,
the earth is not flat and it's not a ball.
It depends on what you're doing.
If you're an architect and you're making level and plumb lines,
or agriculture, making a ditch five miles long,
you build all that as if the earth is flat.
You don't account for curvature, never, right?
But if you're a surveyor and you're making a map over hundreds of miles,
you'll notice that your buddy on the other end that's aiming at you,
you cannot form a triangle.
It's always going to show a curve.
That's why in certain large roads and cities,
the avenues go for a few miles and there's a jog in the road, right?
So if you're doing maps and other things like that, it's a ball.
But if you're doing agriculture, it's flat.
And architecture, it's flat.
If you're doing farming, it's flat.
The sun comes up on the east and goes down on the west.
The earth is not moving.
If you're firing projectiles, you also have to account for curvature too.
I've been told that by snipers.
Yep, the 45-degree rule and all that.
So it's both.
In other words, this reality that we're living in is malleable because of that.
So there are no nukes.
The underlying thing, when someone brings it up,
there's a lot of people, flat earther types,
there's no such thing as a nuke.
They're just using big
Okay, just like the flat earthers are right some of the time,
these guys are right some of the time also.
No, there are not nukes.
Because what they're telling you, they're splitting the atom.
There is no such thing going on.
And by the way, I had spoken to someone who was Army, Air Force,
that guarded a lot of the nukes that they had in the 80s.
And he guarded them.
And then he got more training and started maintaining them.
And I had a discussion with him that really got him upset.
And this is a discussion that went like this.
And this will cover that.
There are no nukes.
People are saying there are no nukes.
They're just using explosives.
And they're correct from that perspective.
They're not splitting the atom.
But I'll tell you what they're doing.
It's even more crazy.
It's just as crazy as the cloning.
What you've heard of, there's a nuclear core.
They got the radioactive material,
and they basically implode that with a small explosion,
and it sets off a trigger reaction.
Well, there's more of that.
What they're actually doing is what Tesla talked about
as finding a virtual ground.
In other words, when you have a positive or a negative,
you know the car battery won't work unless you hook up both or your flashlight.
Well, in this case, you have a situation where all you need is the positive lead,
and the negative takes care of itself.
The negative is the environment.
What I mean by that, very simply, is that this material,
these very heavy metals, when they're constructed,
this is what upset the fellow that maintained these.
And so there's no chemical reaction, not splitting any atoms or anything like that.
You're grounding the ether.
Basically, all the energy that we have, the universal energy, the ether,
is being grounded on this one spot because of the type of metal it is.
And proof of that is that you guys,
the efficacy of this device able to detonate is based on the beryllium reflectors.
If the beryllium reflectors are off and not as perfect as possible,
it will not detonate.
And he just got livid with me.
He says, you're not supposed to talk about that.
And the reason why is if you look at what they call a nuclear device,
no matter how small or how large it is, you have a certain amount of material.
A thermonuclear and atomic are different.
Different materials for thermonuclear, but atomic is very basic.
That material, let's say it's plutonium or uranium or whatever,
is surrounded, encased in a concentric sphere that is highly reflective beryllium,
which is a type of metal.
It's very light and very strong.
And it's basically a metal ball inside of another sphere that is highly reflective,
literally a mirror, and it has to be perfect.
So what they're doing is setting off a reaction that vaporizes anything around it.
And so it is not nuclear, like remember the flat earthers versus the globe,
you have there's no such thing as nukes versus there is nukes.
They're both right and they're both wrong.
What's happening, very simply,
is I don't know if anyone here has ever poorly connected or misconnected a car battery
and the wrench touches one of the terminals and you see a very bright flash and a poof.
Hopefully you haven't done that with a bus bar on a breaker on a house or something.
When you go back and look at that wrench that touched the terminal, it's gone.
Whatever touched it, depending on how powerful the battery is or the yield,
whatever part of the wrench or whatever tool touched it, it's missing.
It's no longer there.
What happened to it?
It's not like it broke off.
Let's go find it and stick it back on.
It's gone.
It vaporized.
That's exactly what's happening with these devices.
So the no nukes people are correct,
but they're not correct when they say, oh, it's just certain chemical explosives.
No, this is the ability.
They have the ability.
They who build these things.
By the way, hearkening back to Dmitry Kalazov,
the idea when they tell you these terrorists got some nukes,
that's almost an impossibility.
It's kind of like the super notes.
It's like counterfeiting money.
If there is, let's say, counterfeit notes,
it's usually done by another country because you cannot get that press to do it.
So what they call a super note.
So, in other words, to counterfeit money,
you must have access to this Swiss press that presses the notes in order to do it.
And the only way they could find this counterfeit is if the serial numbers are not recorded in their own files.
They call them super notes.
There was a whole bunch of them about a decade ago.
If you remember, hundreds all over.
And that was done by North Korea because they're a government.
They can afford one of these presses for their own money.
With nukes, it's the same thing.
There is a huge apparatus.
If you look and study the original Manhattan Project,
which, by the way, was a plutonium, not uranium.
So the uranium bomb must have been gotten from the Germans who were only doing uranium.
But anyway, it even looked different.
If you look at what they show you publicly about these facilities that develop nukes,
they're very large, elaborate facilities.
And it's not because they're a government project.
It's because the processes require that.
So if there is ever one of these devices, and there are companies that make them.
I can name some of them, but I won't because they're not that public.
But they're in South Africa, for example, and places like that.
Netherlands that make these.
And San Diego is another one that makes these, the reflectors and the cores.
One way to find this out is when you look at Google Maps
and you see a parking lot with 500 cars and just a little building.
There's no way all those people, almost one person is driving three cars to get to work.
Okay, you get it.
The majority of the facility would have to be underground.
Yeah, exactly.
And there are major companies that do this part of their gig.
In other words, it's like the Super Notes.
No one is going to counterfeit it with a color laser printer.
You need that Swiss press.
I forgot the name of it.
Maybe you might have heard of it, right?
There's a company in Switzerland that makes those presses.
You must have access to that.
So the mob is not doing counterfeit notes.
It's another country that's doing it.
No terrorists are building nukes.
It's some government-sanctioned corporation facility that's putting them out there.
How does this coincide with cloning?
Well, the security apparatus, they put these clones out, people with consciousness transfer.
Minimal security apparatus for whatever reason, even ritualistic purposes.
But you are told that it's not a clone, obviously.
They're putting out, quote-unquote, terrorist events since the 1980s.
You had the barracks in Lebanon.
Some of the military people sued the government because of that.
They said it was a milk truck that drove under,
and it was the largest conventional explosion known to man.
Bullshit.
All these things.
And World Trade Center, diesel fuel or jet fuel brought the towers down.
This is important because it's still being used against people.
Why?
And I want to go back to how to identify it,
especially if you're living in places like the Middle East,
but it is also here in the U.S.
If you hear of an explosion, quote-unquote, chemical factory, car bomb, whatever,
and you approach the area, you know, if it smells like a duck, looks like a duck,
sounds like a duck, it's probably a duck.
Well, you're going to be told that it looks like a regular whatever,
and it sounded like a regular whatever.
So the only thing that you have left to determine if it was a nuke that went off,
if it was a local explosion, is your smell, what it smells like.
And by the way, even with standard explosives,
they have spectrometers that actually smell the air to tell you what type of explosive it was.
Those do exist.
Just like the gunpowder testing, right?
So here's the thing.
When someone shoots a gun and they get caught even two days later,
they could still find residue, right?
It's that kind of residue.
It's a metallic thing that sticks to the skin.
But anyway.
Not with the publicly known GSR test, though.
That only lasts a few hours, really.
Yeah, it has to be a very good spectrometer that will get really fine.
Okay, so how can you tell?
It's the smell.
What does it smell like?
Okay, when these devices go off, it's called ionization.
So it's an extremely pungent smell.
Now, if you're familiar with what an ozone generator smells like,
I've brought this up to people.
Usually people say, yes, I've smelled ozone before.
But there's plenty of people who haven't.
So how do you identify the smell of it?
It smells like chlorine bleach, laundry bleach.
Kind of, yeah.
A little bit, with gasoline.
You know that sharp gasoline smell?
It's very pungent, almost an electric burn also does in ionize,
depending on the material.
You'll get that, right?
But it's pungent, and it's very distinctive,
almost like, you know, the old school matches.
When you strike them, it's got that matched sulfur smell.
Very distinctive.
Very rare that anything smells like that.
Right, right.
The same with ionization.
The closest you're going to get is maybe like a gasoline, sharp gasoline,
when you're, like, walking by a gas station.
Not when you're over, you know, that little wefting of gasoline
with chlorine bleach kind of ionization.
That's what it smells like, right?
It's very, very pungent.
By the way, World Trade Center, I think, Chuck,
you were there after the disaster, because it was really a disaster.
People were complaining in Jersey, calling the EPA,
saying it smells like an electrical fire.
This was two months later as the vapors were still coming down the ground,
and the EPA responded saying, well, there was a lot of wires in the buildings.
Yeah, pretty much that's a fairly good representation of what was going on.
But over in Bayonne and Jersey City and stuff like that,
just across from, really across the river from Manhattan Island,
yeah, there was plenty of complaints about that.
Yeah.
Yeah, and the complaint was it smelled bad because it smelled like an electrical fire,
like when electric wires burn and things like that, right?
Right, minus the rubber.
Which is ionization.
You see, that's the thing.
People, when they think about electrical fire smells,
a lot of times they remember the rubber, too.
Forget the rubber.
The insulation, yeah.
Yeah, forget that.
It's the rest of it.
Yeah, very strong ionization.
There's a book about the Marines that were sent over to Hiroshima
and clean it up in letters that they wrote.
I think it was Seven Hours to Zero or whatever.
You could research it.
A book written by Marines that cleaned up Hiroshima.
And what they all got sick from was the intense smell of ionization.
And some of them do say there was an intense smell of ionization.
It smelled like gasoline mixed with blood mixed with this, right?
And they're trying to explain how bad the smell was.
It made them ill, okay, because it was atmospheric,
so there's very little radiation unless you put the dust inside of your body.
Also, what they're doing with the clones and the nuclear devices,
telling you that they're car bombs or terrorist bombs,
is all of these events, subsequent events that might come forward,
and they're going to be using the pact that I mentioned earlier.
No atmospheric.
Must be underground.
So if you heard of the faked alien invasion, okay, this is how it goes.
They have nukes underground.
When they go off, there's a surface reaction,
and everything on the surface turns to dust.
It leaves a small crater, but people standing there will turn to dust.
Buildings, anything, irrespective of what it is, will turn to dust.
Which, by the way, that was the other thing that was a major complaint
that came across the river is this dust that just kind of rained down on everything
and stuck to everything.
It was very consistent, 50 micron or smaller,
and that dust was not asbestos or concrete.
It was steel.
It was a powder.
I don't know what it was consisted of, but I do know by looking at it myself,
it was powder.
Even today, back in like around 2012,
I got in touch with someone who had some of the powder from the World Trade Center,
and I said, put a magnet to it.
It's not a concrete dust.
It's all steel.
The tower is 90% steel that turned into that fine dust, irrespective of material.
If you're a human being alive, you will turn into charcoal first.
You go online and research.
It's called a WTC human refuse.
The bodies that they found were called human refuse, okay,
and you'll see someone laying down with a T-shirt and jeans,
and they're completely burned up black like charcoal briquette,
but their clothes are not scorched at all, okay?
That's another end of research.
Anyway, the interesting thing, the fake alien invasion would go thusly.
You have the reaction of these devices.
They could be very small, the size of a cell phone, which they were used.
There is a lot of reporting from ex-military.
They did have them back in the 90s the size of a cell phone,
which is they would get some rogue generals in Bosnia,
even though they had a ceasefire peace treaty.
These guys kept fighting, so they had to get rid of them.
He needs a new cell phone, so they deliver a new cell phone.
He turns it on, and it makes a 50-foot crater in the ground, right?
So this was used in the 90s.
That's how small they are, 8th, 10th generation, whatever.
Back to the alien invasion.
You see the vaporization. You smell the ionization. It's a nuke.
But, of course, somebody got it on film.
But when they put it on film,
you're going to see a flying saucer or something like that in the sky
shoot down a beam, and that flying saucer is not there.
And right before, the nuke goes off, and the surface reaction happens.
So the people on TV are being told it's a nuclear invasion,
and they're going to see the flying saucer above,
and then the ground vaporized below.
But the people that were there never saw such a thing.
You see?
See where I'm going with this?
Same thing at the World Trade Center.
Now, I know you and I could get into it.
I say there's no planes that went into the World Trade Center
strictly because it's physically impossible.
What I know from aviation, two things for sure.
When a plane crashes, even before the crash is complete,
on a large plane, even a small plane,
the tail rudder section breaks off from the shock,
no matter how fast it's going.
Even missiles, if you ever watch missile testing,
when the missile physically hits the target,
the rear tail section breaks off in a thousandth of a second.
It's just one of these phenomena that happen with flying objects.
The other thing was no one was looking up at all,
because a careening plane going into a building,
you're going to look up, anyone that lives near an airport.
I remember once going to an airport,
and as the plane comes really low,
like over the chain link fence to land at a big airport,
the cab driver has to look at it.
Even though this is his ride, he's exposed to this all day long.
You shouldn't bother him, but he still looks at it.
It's one of these things.
It's kind of spooky when you have an extremely loud, large plane
flying at low altitude, lower than normal.
You're going to look at it, always.
If you look at the 9-11 videos,
no one is looking up the street videos
until the side of the building explodes.
No one is looking up at all,
which is basically, from a human behavior standpoint, impossible.
Well, see, there you go.
The reason why you mentioned that we could get into it
is because you and I talked, without recording, about this.
What I tried to tell you is that I know people saw planes.
Now, why do I know that?
No, no, you know that people said they saw planes.
Right, but at the time, before the reporting,
before the second plane even hit, they had noted to me.
Now, I will tell you that they didn't note a strike on the building,
but they did note a plane flying in a place where it shouldn't have been,
where it wasn't normally, because in Manhattan,
most of the planes that go overhead are not noticed anymore
because you get accustomed to it.
But this was unusual, because this caused them to look up,
and then they heard that it struck the tower.
Okay, they heard it struck the tower, they didn't see that,
but they did see planes flying in unusual places
where they would not have normally been.
And that, I can report to you, happened before the media broadcast it.
No, it wasn't that.
This started happening because there was an immediate interruption
in certain communications,
and then we started communicating with each other
regarding why is it we're not having credit card payments go through,
why is it that banking has suddenly stopped, things like this,
and that was the explanation,
because this had occurred in the World Trade Center complex.
Now, I'm not saying that I know anybody personally
that says they saw a plane hit a tower.
However, planes flying in ways that, well,
eventually could be explained that way.
Yes.
Communications planes.
Usually, by the way, I'm glad you brought that up,
planes flying unusually.
If you are wherever you might be in the world,
and you see an unusual amount of what might look like unmarked planes,
helicopters, more planes than helicopters,
because they carry more equipment,
in the area circling or flying around,
and you're not near a military base, something's up.
And what these planes do is they control communications.
In other words, if they want to pull some shenanigans somewhere,
they may not want people there to immediately communicate
to others outside of that area.
And these planes do jamming and all kinds of other things
or can put in fake calls.
They're communications planes, basically.
Which, by the way, when the tower, the first tower fell,
which I don't think anybody would dispute that the tower fell.
Yeah, it dustified, yeah.
Well, it fell.
Whatever condition it was in, it fell, right?
But when that happened,
there was a significant interruption in communications,
which that was cell phones and all that stuff throughout the area
which spread well beyond the island of Manhattan.
So there was a large blanket effect here that took place.
Sure.
Yeah, but that I know, not because of reporting,
not because of research, but because I was in the area.
Yeah, I was camping in the woods.
I didn't find out until later, and when I saw that,
I was like, World Trade Center, holy crap,
because I was made aware.
Here's the thing I want to bring up.
I mentioned this before.
Yeah, just saying, I was at work,
and this is why I was in communication with people right away
because I was working in the retail end of fuel and stuff like that,
and you have constant communications with banks and things like this.
So that was part of my job, and this is how this happened.
Plus, I had a cell phone,
and I knew plenty of other people that had cell phones,
and cell phones were interrupted.
Communications between banks were interrupted.
Some places had satellite dishes that we were supposed to be interconnected,
you know, outside of those sorts of cell towers and things,
and guess what?
All of it basically went poof.
A bunch of it got interrupted.
Well, they said the tower, the main transmitter up there,
but their cell phones is not a, you know what I mean?
Right.
It was a bunch of crap, the explanation I gave,
but I'm just telling you the real-world event, though,
that was occurring had an effect that was, you know,
throughout the entirety of the area, not just in New York.
It was all the way into New Jersey and stuff like that,
and I've explained before I tried to get onto the island.
I wanted to help dig people out,
but the island was already sealed off by the time I got there.
The island of Manhattan is what I'm referring to, by the way.
But, yeah, but go ahead.
I just wanted to interject that and let you run with it any way you want.
Yeah, this is where we get into the personal experiences
to validate or verify what we're saying is not just something we watch the YouTube video on.
I'm not into letting people talk and then saying,
when do you stop talking, give me the microphone so I can talk.
I think that when the personal experience is very cogent
and attached to what we're saying to build it and to help others, of course,
if people want to talk about their personal experience,
how is it going to help me, right?
That's the main point.
That's a very old farming adage.
You go to a farmer and have a conversation.
He's like, boy, I got things to do.
You got something to tell me that can make my crops grow better?
You see, that's the philosophy that I have with it.
What I go with that is I'll give a little bit of how I piece things together
because this is probably how everyone can piece things together in their own way.
Do you remember in the 70s they had Carl Sagan do a show called Cosmos
talking about billions and billions of stars and all that?
If you guys are old enough, you'll remember that.
I remember.
At the time, it was fascinating.
It was in the 70s.
I was in my early teens or whatever.
Well, there was another show with a guy named James Burke called Connections
from the BBC.
It was a miniseries of 10.
I just looked it up this morning when I was thinking about what we're going to be speaking of.
They have all the series on YouTube.
It's called Connections, James Burke, I think.
It's how one thing connects to another,
how rope making in the 1500s led us to the automobile, right?
Sure.
Things like that.
It's still using the bullshit history that we're given,
but it just expands you from an extra category, cross-pollination of different things
that seem non-interrelated, right?
Okay.
So my experience with that was when the Statue of Liberty in Ellis Island
was being renovated in the mid-80s,
I took on occupation, almost like an apprenticeship,
of doing drafting in an engineering office, right?
I did this for a few months.
I was thinking maybe I want to go into that, right?
Because I always had a mathematical engineering mindset.
And what was specific about that was certain scaffolding couldn't be attached,
let's say, to the Statue of Liberty.
It had to be free-floating.
And how do you put up a 300-foot scaffold not attached to anything?
Well, when the wind load came, it would twist and rotate
instead of lean against the statue.
Anytime a bolt was removed or attached to the scaffolding,
it had to be documented and changed on the drawings.
And that's what I was doing.
It was maybe a dozen other people.
And the engineering firm at the time, we would be there at odd hours
because we didn't like being there in the main hours because it was crowded.
It was like one of these things where it's important,
so you have 24 hours access to the office, right?
You go in and do your thing.
There was an old man in a wheelchair.
He was the son of one of the founders.
And he says, well, what are you doing here?
A young guy like you should be out enjoying yourself or whatever.
I said, yeah, I do enjoy myself.
I ride mountain bike, which was a new thing back then.
I do trials, things like that.
And I go down by the World Trade Center,
and I ride my bike in that open courtyard area.
He says, oh, no, World Trade Center?
This is mid-'80s.
He says, you stay away from there.
They have nukes in there.
And I'm like, oh, this crazy old senile guy, right?
But if you watch the first episode of Connections,
this is where I thought the nukes were, being naive.
And when you get very little information,
you've got to piece it together with what you know,
which is usually false.
The opening of Connections with James Burke, the first episode,
it's him speaking, and he's in the courtyard of the World Trade Center.
And in the middle, there's a sculpture of a bronze ball about 20 feet in diameter.
And back in the 80s, you know, the Reagan with the nuclear scare with Russia
and all this other stuff, right?
That was like a second hype.
Yeah, the second hype, he was all threats back and forth.
Well, we were thinking, what are these nukes you're talking about?
Well, there's a core, there's a ball.
So when I went to the World Trade Center after this crazy old man told me that,
I said, oh, the nuke is probably in that bronze ball
because it resembles the bowling ball thing that they show on documentaries, right?
So I was like, oh, okay, maybe that verifies or validates it in my mind.
But in my mind, since the mid-'80s, I associated WTC equals nukes.
I just didn't know how, you see, until much later.
So this is my personal experience way before the fact.
But could I come out and tell you that, oh, there's nukes at the World Trade Center
that are going to be used to demolish it?
They're 200 feet underground?
No, I couldn't do that.
But we got a slight premonition.
This is what attaches it back to cloning, right?
There's plenty of stuff on there.
They're called MK Ultra fails where people are just acting too strange.
Are they clones?
Maybe, maybe not, right?
But without us, I don't think we were planning on getting into, let's say,
a quote-unquote debate about planes or no planes, and I don't think we need to.
I think that's up to whoever views it.
Absolutely, absolutely.
You know, about the Statue of Liberty thing, though, just really quick,
they started doing those renovations or preparing for them at least by 1981.
This was in the late-'80s.
They opened it in 86.
Yeah, but in 81, I know for a fact because I went there on a school trip,
and we weren't allowed to go into the arm of the lady.
You used to be able to go into the arm and actually go on the torch, right?
Well, hold on a second.
They say that no one's been into the arm since 1916
when they blew up Tom Island off of Jersey City.
No one talks about Black Tom.
Two million pounds of TNT?
Yeah.
Anyway.
No, that's true, but I'm just telling you what I was told when I was 9 years old.
I know, but this is kind of Mandela effect territory now
because I remember in the 70s being able to walk up to the arm.
It was a very tight, winding staircase.
Well, but the thing is it lines up more with you
because I was told that it's only recently you can't go into the torch.
Now, I was able to go all the way up into the crown.
I personally walked up.
They had us walk up the Statue of Liberty.
I have no idea why, but it was one of these things that we did in third grade.
Yeah.
As you get up, it gets narrow.
It's painted white, and there's a little marker graffiti on a lot of places,
and it's a narrow, winding staircase.
Exactly.
Yeah, right, but that was the thing.
We asked, can we go in the torch?
We were told no because recently they've closed it off
because there's going to be renovations.
By the way, you can see evidence of those renovations
if you watch old episodes of Saturday Night Live
because they always show stuff from New York, right?
They always show the Statue of Liberty,
and during a certain period they showed scaffolding around the Statue of Liberty.
So now I'm just pointing out that there's ways of looking at this
and verifying parts of what you're saying, that's all.
Sure, but the bottom line with this is the secrecy element,
and I think the thing that's going to probably be contacting
or people will have contact with more, hopefully not,
is the possibility of where nearby you're being told
that there was a quote-unquote explosion, right?
And I'm telling you that if based on what they're telling you caused the explosion
and what the explosion usually, what really is, is not as they say.
And the way you would identify it as what we just talked about
is by that strong ionization smell, right?
That might be the crux of it.
I can get into more supposition about cloning and consciousness transfer,
but again, going back to the chat about how they cannot recreate the spirit
and all that, which I think they cannot, as far as I can tell.
And I want to just attach this before we wind this down.
When you hear all of this talk about AI,
they're not talking about a machine that can think,
because your spirit is your mind, which is your intelligence.
They're thinking about how they can develop that, a spirit, a mind, from scratch,
or in situ, meaning in place.
All that AI talk is you can network computers to appear to have emotions,
but they're not going to be sentient machines like HAL 9000.
Even HAL 9000 in 2001 Space Odyssey was still just a dumb machine, ultimately.
Right. Ultimately, that's what it is.
So here's where the differentiation comes in.
Here's where, again, I almost have to look at science fiction, right?
And this is how it ties to cloning directly, again.
There is a difference between mimicking something and literally copying it and creating it.
These are three different things, to my mind.
So HAL there is trying to mimic.
It's a rudimentary attempt to mimic.
It's mimicry, right.
And now copying is a different story here, where you can actually copy it.
It is the thing, but it's only a copy.
So it's a good representation of it, but it's not the actual thing, like you were talking about.
Well, go ahead with the copy, just to interject.
When you copy, there's two ways.
There's a replication and a duplication.
Okay.
So a replication would be 99.999%,
but a duplication would be exactly like just what the word means, dupled two.
You've made another one that's exact.
Okay, fair enough.
So when I say copy, what I'm talking about is replication, where it's nearly there.
Very close.
Right.
Okay, so copying is replication.
Mimicry is a different story.
Go ahead.
The key is mimicry, just like when they tell you it's a car bomb
and it's a 30-foot crater that requires five tons on a Nissan Sentra.
No way.
Well, that's why I was trying to circle back to it.
Okay, so you've got the copying, as I said, but more accurately, I should have said replication,
because it's a replicant.
It's almost right.
It's almost there.
Right, versus a duplicate.
I think they have the replications.
I don't have the duplications.
Yeah, that's where I was going, because duplication is very similar to transfer
because it does recreate the thing, right?
Yeah, let's say, like, a duplicate would be, in a rough sense, but pretty accurate, identical twins.
Yeah.
Two different people, but they're identical, and they are connected.
Slight variation, yeah, and connected.
Slight variation, but they are connected.
Okay, but to actually do it so that you have something that is indiscernible from the original, that's different.
It's a duplicate, yeah.
That's a duplicate.
Okay, so really I need four categories here.
I need replication, duplication, and then transfer is a different category, is it not?
Yeah.
Yeah, you can rest assured that that's been done since the 1930s, as Donald Marshall talks about.
Okay.
Because I get that intuitively, and there is something about intuition that people have turned off,
and I suggest that you turn on your intuition again and start relying on it.
If you can bridge it with logic and reason.
Well, right, and I would say that because it's been so heavily repeated, the concept of transference is in existence,
because people talk about it all the time, even if it's, well, you know what, the spirit leaves the body, it goes somewhere else.
That's transference, whatever the system is, whatever the idea is, maybe that's natural transference, but that's transference, right?
So that happens, but this idea
No, they're mystified by it.
Okay, you're talking about the mimicry.
Let's go back with that.
When they say this guy's a magician, he's not.
He's pulling a trick.
He's not really creating a rabbit out of a hat.
No, but he's mimicking the appearance of that thing happening.
Right, by distracting you, just like the people, again, not leaning on it too much.
You can make anyone believe anything if you put them in a traumatic situation.
For sure.
Pickpockets do this all the time.
A pregnant woman that bumps into you really hard, nearly knocks you over, takes your wallet.
You turn around and you're like, wait a second, did she fill me up?
Who is that?
Oh, pregnant.
Oh, I'm sorry.
That's how the pickpockets work, right?
So it's just a distraction.
You can make people believe that if you traumatize them enough, during that time of trauma,
they talk about this in sex magic with orgasm,
during that time, there's a coherence that is incoherent with the rest of your existence,
that things can be injected into the mind that you will hold onto,
and you can even make believe that you saw it and you were there and you really weren't.
That's the concept of trauma.
So you could have anything happen, whether it's the World Trade Center or the alien invasion.
No one saw flying saucers, but if you were there and you just saw the ground open up
and justify anything that was on it,
if you go home and everyone says, here, look on TV, there's a flying saucer,
I missed that.
I didn't see that I was there, but I guess everyone says it was.
I'm still shaking from it.
I guess there was a flying saucer.
Idiot me, I didn't see it.
Well, you're going to graft that into your experience because now it's an additional piece.
You see, the memory is always subject to revision, too, because now people say they recall that.
They don't recall that.
They have taken in new information and grafted it or applied it.
Because they want approval.
Everyone's looking for approval.
Hey, honey, how do I look in this clothes?
Part of the equation, yeah, definitely part of the equation.
But back to this, when we're talking about cloning, though, this has come incrementally,
it seems, closer and closer to having command of replication.
I don't think they've gotten to replication yet.
I think, again, mimicry is on some level.
Excuse me.
Yeah, replication is one thing.
Duplication, right, right, right.
Thank you for correcting me.
The exact, yeah, because otherwise the article of the Egyptians being able to make clones
would not be identifiable.
No.
But it's close enough.
Here's the thing.
The tolerances are so low on this stuff that you can tell people, even people that were there,
convince them that you didn't see what you saw, and they'll go for it,
as long as it's coming from, quote, unquote, someone authoritative, right?
Oh, yeah, well, we talked about that before.
The financial system and the legal system is based on that completely.
Look, I've gone over this before.
I have a minus 1,000 in my bank account, right?
Remember, I think people here have heard this already.
Look, if you're getting government checks and you go to the Treasury website
and they're $28 trillion in debt, they can't write you a check for a dollar.
Even if someone gave them $28 trillion to go to zero, they still can't write you a check for a dollar.
If you're a government employee, how are you getting your salary?
How are you getting benefit checks?
This is so in your face.
It couldn't be any more.
It's a 2,000-pound gorilla in the room, and no one notices that.
These things are used as gauges, by the way.
They could easily, by the way, just like Federal Reserve internal accounting is not made public,
they could easily say you need to pass certain screening
and have a certain password to get on the Treasury website to see what the debt is.
They could do that very easily.
If you want to look up someone's Social Security number that you know you can't do it,
but if you're working in the DA's office, you could do that instantly.
They could make it so you don't have access to what the national debt is very easily.
It would be accepted.
The average person can only look up a Social Security number on somebody's debt.
But at this point, they could easily hide what the debt is
and tell you for whatever reason people will buy it.
But why do they make it public?
Because they want to tell you, hey, dummy, we're telling you this whole thing is so fake.
The people are acting illogically completely.
And by the way, you notice how the politicians never talk about the debt?
Never?
Because there is none.
It's all perceived.
That's the problem.
Because, look, if there really was a debt, it would work exactly like your average person's bank account works.
If you're $28 overdrawn, guess what you can't do?
Cash another check.
Or whatever.
It's so in your face.
So is the cloning in our face?
I would say yes.
Do we know enough about it to point them out?
No.
But we know enough about, let's say, it's plausible that it exists,
and that might be the way to explain some things that we see,
especially the minimal security apparatus around dignitaries and famous people.
Thank you.