The Sonic Event 75, rated Y. Anyway, here we are. So, looking back at a lot of different
things, not a lot of action in the chat room since we last spoke Greek, but how are you
doing today? I'm doing alright. You know, I just mentioned to you, the Sonic 73, I think,
was a doozy, I think, from memory. We really spent an hour almost talking about how energies
work, and hopefully it was helpful. And here's the thing. If, let's say, something is explained,
let's just use this general term. And when the thing is explained, someone doesn't get
it, or the people don't get it. It doesn't matter. You were exposed to it, right? It's
the start, right? So, yeah, you know how very often when people question, let's say, well,
an introduction to, let's say, something that's going to be edifying, they don't really
ask, do you know this? Have you ever heard of this? Have you been exposed to this? Right?
You see? Sometimes I get exposed to a more advanced lecture, and then I fill in some
gaps later, and then it comes, it's like, oh, yeah, that's what that was about, because
it makes more sense, because I get the more baseline information in later. It's sort of
cracking the ice.
Yeah, the reverse order of what they do in the schools, right? Where they give you the
book, and okay, we're going to teach you the basics, and then you've got to go. Not always
necessarily in that order is the best way to go, is it?
Yeah, I don't think they use that word anymore. I think they're allowed to use teaching anymore,
because they don't. I think they're getting more honest, by the way.
Yeah, don't say that.
No, no, no, no, it is. You just have to understand the premise. We've gone over before, the guy
who sued Fox News for libel, and the court case was thrown out, because Fox News is an
entertainment company, right?
Oh, yeah, several lawsuits.
So they can't make it.
Yeah, several lawsuits they've had to state that, oh, look, they gave us false information.
They're like, well, what do you want from us? We're an entertainment company. Exactly.
Yeah, yeah, but the people go and do stuff, so the onus is up to them. Now, what happens
is there was, okay, here's another example. One of the cabinet members in Obama's cabinet,
executive cabinet, right, basically was questioned about certain policies they put in place,
and he says, look, this is all policy. If the American people are too stupid to understand
it or what to do with it, it's not my problem, right? This goes on, you know, couple that
that our job will be done when everything the American public believes is a lie, couple
that with umpty, right?
Oh, yeah.
So, yeah, so going on, let's see, I want to go back to we did a few episodes ago, a
couple of episodes ago, something I got into barely, that was the one where barely into
depth, but very much an overview, like, for example, on the medical side, to treat it
organically, if someone has a brain tumor, that is something that's going to the most
young, contractive part of the body upward, that means it has to be extremely lean. So
you would counter it with something extremely young, which would basically be the quality
of if you want to find something that's very young, what could take a lot of radiation,
that would be a cockroach. So you want to make it even more young, you carbonize his ass,
grind it up, put it in a capsule, and that will shrink the brain tumor, like nothing
else, right? Organically, naturally, right. And it has nothing to do with the chemical
if you give this to a materialist, they want to find out what chemical is doing that, right?
But they don't understand for all the here's the thing, I've talked about this before,
you know, materialistic society, they're materialistic, blah, blah, blah, blah, science or whatever.
But you know, what's ironic about that they know nothing about their materials, nothing.
And what I mean by that, it's everything is basically a hydrogen compound or composite
compound, not the way they say compounds form. But when you put more of them together,
hydrogens, that is impressed them together, and they stay together, that's compounding,
right? And they don't understand that. And it's energy, not they see that they've able
to pull the wool over people's eyes that the elements are ephemeral, or empirical, actually,
which means you know, they don't change. They're actually ephemeral. They're all forms of hydrogen.
Well, here's what the biggest problem is, right? Is that, you know, even when people
take a look at okay, this worked, let's talk about the development of aspirin just really
quickly. Okay, they withdrew the chemical from a particular plant and said, Okay, this
is the chemical that seems to actually do the job.
Hold on, it was not the chemical at all. Let me just interrupt for a moment, like I usually
do. If you speak to any very experienced medical technician, aka known as a doctor, what they
always say, in one form or another, when, when parents with a newborn, not a newborn,
but a young child asks the doctor, is it okay to give aspirin? And they ask how old
if it's older than five, you say, you know, aspirin, in general, doesn't do any harm,
and it doesn't do any good. So what, what does it do? Nothing, because they took away
the essence, it was not chemical, but go ahead.
Well, but that was what they attempted to do, is to figure out which chemical creates
the condition that they want.
Well, again, no, the people that originally did aspirin understood the energy aspect a
little bit more, not much more, just a little bit, a little bit more, and it went away that
people, these guys do things that are in tradition. Aspirin is considered a traditional medicine.
And the reason, yeah, the reason it's not available is because it's traditionally available.
There were other things like mercurochrome, by the way, that are taken off the market,
they said, because it was dangerous. And the way they took it off, it was so effective,
by the way, for cuts and wounds and things like that. It was made out of mercury and
chromium, which are two supposedly very toxic things. When you put them together, it forms
another compound, looks like iodine. What they did is they dipped a baby, a newborn baby
in it, and put the baby aside, and the baby died. And so they said it's toxic, right?
Literally, they coated an entire young newborn with it, and that would be an unnatural condition,
right? So, yeah.
But it was extremely effective. Yeah, I treated many a wound with that stuff when I could
get my hands on it. A bottle of mercurochrome was practically an essential in my first aid
kit when I was much younger. It was perfect. It did the job.
Yeah, if you knew what to do with it. Most people didn't use it properly. They put it
directly on the open wound, where you have to close the wound first, and put it on the
bandage. You never put it directly. But anyway, it's not available anymore, so there's no
importance to get into it. But what I'm saying is most of the stuff that people, whatever,
it's all done by tradition. Why? Because 85% of all prescription medicines in less than
10 years are banned. That's a statistic. If you want to say, if you want to be very
conservative, and strike out derivations, 70%. Every 10 years, 70% of what's prescribed
now that was fairly recent will be banned as harmful and dangerous, because the chemistry
has nothing to do with it. Here's an example of the chemistry and the energy. Okay, so
you have a chemical A, whatever, let's say it's medicinal, and then we have chemical
A on the side, the same thing, but they look different. One is a powder, one is a liquid.
You know that the liquid one, in many cases, will be more effective, right? Okay. So taking
a liquid form, and then you have chemical A again, that's injected. That's a different
effect. Same chemical, right? I'll give you a great example that they tampered with,
screwed with, and continue, and it might as well be tradition for how long they've been
using it, is opium, because if you work with the initial, with the paste, if you work with
the stuff that you actually get out of the flower, it's a whole different world from
this garbage that they create now. Sure. Now you can judge that by its energy, and by the
way, you can synthetically make something that's very close to it just by looking at
it, not knowing the chemical constituents. So as the plant grows up, it still continues
to grow up, but in energy, part of the plant does not want to go further, so what does
it do? It forms a bulb. Right. Right? Instead of a, like imagine wheat or corn. As it grows,
it starts to get sharper and pointier. I mean, it's like, yeah, let me go, let me go, I want
to go this way, right? But with opium, as it's leaving the ground and going up, right, towards
the young, right, what happens is part of it rounds off, like it doesn't part, but the
rest of it continues, right? So what do you know about energy movement, right? Well, it
sort of hits, yeah, it starts to swell and bulge, and it almost forces itself back toward
the ground because, yeah, like your car, you have an accelerator and a brake pedal, right?
So once you start looking at these things, it's quite interesting that you can actually,
it's very difficult to do it alone, but you can actually do all of this in your kitchen.
Why do I say kitchen? You mean transmutation, was he talking about this? Alchemy,
transmutation in your kitchen, because usually requires heating, electricity, water, right?
That's why I say you can, if you can't make it in your kitchen, it probably can't be made,
right? So that's the aspect to that. But I wanted to get into something else, though,
because I know it's quote, unquote, the pagan holidays. And I always refer to them that way
because what they did, by the way, is they, you know, they say there's 12 months in, you
know, the 12 system, right? Oh, yeah. But it's really a decimal system because they're
ending the year in the 10th month. And they know, and everyone knows it's the 10th month.
They just don't acknowledge it, right? How do we, how do I know? Desi is December,
Dessa is 10. So, you know, yeah, exactly. So they're forcing a 10, a 10 denomination,
a 10-deca system on everyone. And it's, they'll say it's 12 months, but it's not
acknowledged functionally as such because they end the year in the 10th month, right?
And they call it the 12th month, but it can't be, right? From any aspect. What people do
now are celebrating, which I understand. I think even the narrative that I discuss, there's
a spring festival, there's a midsummer festival, and there's a fall festival. And then typically,
there is not much highlight on the winter festival because the winter in an agricultural
society is the time where you do things that you couldn't do while you were doing agriculture.
The busiest time in agriculture is spring, summer, and fall. Most important, I'd say
they're all just as equally important, but the fall is when you tally everything in and
you reflect and see what you did for the year. So when your seventh month is over in the
fall, coming on the eighth month, if you have a broken wagon or you need a new roof
or you need to travel, now's the time to do it. You plant your winter rye, you know, the
slow-growing stuff that doesn't need attention, and you travel. So it's interesting how they're
doing. I mean, all right, Sam's a summer holiday. When is the most traveling? Thanksgiving,
Christmas, right? You notice?
A lot of people travel in the summer, though.
A lot of people do travel in the summer, though.
Yes, they do. I think more people travel in the summer, but not in a focused week or a
focused day.
Like, everyone seems to take off a week or two, and it's always the end of July, August,
you know, depending on how far you are from the coast, by the way, or coastal area. Like,
if you look at the European coast, right, or the American coast, right, it'll be around
that time. Now, in the upside-down world, you know, the other hemisphere, it's the opposite.
They're in the middle of summer right now.
Right.
So back to the thing that I wanted to just bring up, cooking. I think we did also on
the inverse of this one on 57. It was 57. We talked about meat and potatoes, and you
never cook meat and potatoes together, by the way. You always have to cook them separately.
But I've been doing something with animal lately called low and slow, and it works with
everything, and I just want to go over it. If you're making a roast, I think, what do
they call a joint in England? It's called a joint, a roast. What I found out is the
usual Greek-speak stuff, and maybe I'll throw some beginner stuff in here. You never want
to put anything into a pot or a fire or whatever if it's coming out of the fridge. You have
to have it minimum, at least, room temperature. What do I mean? Like, if it's in the fridge,
it's at 4 degrees Celsius or 39, and now you want to get it into a pot at 200, let's say
the boiling point of water, Q12 or something like that. That's a huge temperature difference,
right? So the reason why you're doing part of the preparation is to have it out of the
fridge and close to room temperature, so you don't have that big temperature difference,
because that big temperature difference will actually change the results, by the way. So
for people that are afraid of all this stuff, once someone will say, well, I want to make
sure it's cooked because of the salmonella, I'm like, what? You can't cook salmonella
out. If you know chicken has salmonella or is suspected, don't buy it. You should never
buy, actually, in many things, it's unlawful to eat a diseased animal, you know? So why
would you, right, a foodborne illness and all that stuff, that has nothing to, right,
that's factory farming and people with poor sensibilities, like white people. Oh, did
I just say that?
You did.
Anyway. Yeah, it has nothing to do with the color of your skin.
Yes.
I met plenty of black folk that act like white people, not white folk. White folk and white
people are two different things, by the way. So, yeah, so anyway, and by the way, anybody
tuning in now, I've been speaking out, not really for, but mostly against white people
ever since I've been doing this Greek speak. So I'm not part of this too much white agenda
that's been coming out lately. They're doing it for a wrong reason. I'm just saying, like,
you got to get some tradition. You got to get some backbone. You got to get some, let's
just say this for everybody covering here, some proper hygiene methods, you know, proper,
you know, some stuff, you know, because I actually think that putting a chemical on
something is hygienic, right? So, yeah, learn how to use, right. That's all. OK, well,
not going into a tangent, but I want to say, OK, white people are the way they are, especially
in America, because they're depression babies.
What they did is they screwed people with the depression in the 30s. No one knew why
it happened. By the way, the only reason the depression, Great Depression was there was
no stock market crash. Yeah, it was a stock market crash. But if you read the newspaper
articles, bankers were not jumping out of the windows. The army was brought in to protect
Wall Street in New York then because people were going and throwing the bankers out of
the windows. Go find the articles. It's not. Yeah. Yeah. So what all they did see back
then, 20s, 30s, whatever, when people quote unquote got their salary at the end of the
week, if you watch the old movies with a company office, there's a big safe in the black and
white. Right. You know, let's go talk to the press. It was always a big thing. They didn't
use checks, credit cards and stuff like that. Very few people use bank accounts. There's
no reason for it. So back in the 30s, if you said, I'm going to write you a check, they
were like they were set it back. You're like, you're going to pull some kind of scam on
me. Yeah, that's right. It is a scam. All checks are scammed. Right. So everything was
done by cash. Yeah. All the way into the 70s and 80s. Quite honestly, nobody wanted a credit
card or anything other than cash. People looked at you straight. Well, you know, I actually
know one of my in-law relative relative is one of the first people to be issued a credit
card in the late 50s. And he was part of a it was an experiment like you can't like like
what I'm doing with water devices or at least you can't really buy them because, you know,
we don't know what they're going to do, really, even though they're pretty miraculous in the
way that they do what they say they do. So what they did with back then, when you got
a credit card, you got a call every week like, where'd you go? What'd you buy? What was the
reaction to the questionnaires? Because there's still feeling it out. Right. So but anyway,
everything was cash. All the banks did was when the secretary went to the bank to pick
up the cash to pay the workers, they said, sorry, we're out of cash. They withheld the
cash. Right. So if you worked in a factory that made electric motors, the only thing
they could do is, quote unquote, pay you with electric motors. So all these guys got electric
motors and they go to the stove to get some meat, milk and bread and they bring the milk
and bread to the counter and the story says, here's electric motor. We're not getting
cash. And the store owner says, yeah, look over here. I got 50 electric motors. I don't
need any more. Sorry. Bye. That's all they did. There was no depression. It was all.
And by the way, I think Bernanke apologized for for the Federal Reserve orchestrating
the Great Depression. So from that, there were a lot of people, by the way, that knew
what was going on. And there was like a sort of patriot type revolt going on. And then
they did World War Two. Right. To flush them out. Right. So. Yeah. So. Right. Yeah. So
like to me, nine. The covid was to flush out the 9-11 people, by the way. You know, that
sentiment that still lurked on. Right. So they fell for it. You have to change the
venue. Right. Well, as soon as you get basically people resisting the situation, you have
to do something to clear them out a little bit, because otherwise you'll get too many
of them will get together and you'll have an actual resistance. So, yeah, I mean, that's
what they did. World War One, World War Two, each one. It was was another like let's flush
the population. The truthfully, the young men who were of that right age to be in a good
mood to fight. Well, you got to do something with those people, because otherwise they
might turn against them to do stuff like throw the bankers out the windows. Yeah. So good.
Yeah. Yeah. Sure. Sure. So. So would that depression era, which was like, we don't
really know what's going on, but we have to go along with it. The canned food stuff that
that just no more traditions as as because we might it might happen again. And what happened
was the people were carefree to a point of negligence. You had World War Two and then
the boom, the commercial boom of the 50s and all that with all the member of the slogan,
better living through chemistry, chemicals or whatever. And and they forgot what was
brought over by the Dutch, the Scottish, the Irish, the Germans that, you know, I'm talking
about predominantly the East Coast. Right. Right. You know, that's basically, you know,
if you hear certain accents down south or in like near Tennessee or whatever, they're
actually derivations of like Pennsylvania of German and Scottish. And right. So, yeah,
some of these accents were just certain families that branched out and kept they spoke a certain
way. Right. So the East Coast of the U.S. is basically your Dutch, German, Scottish,
Irish, you know, pockets in the north and more in the northern east coast and south
of Italian. And right. Right. And such and such. So, yeah. So and then they moved over
to California. Right. But they got them after the migration happened. But it affected the
so the whole country, in other words, impoverished traditions and the culture of the people that
came here. That's that's where I quote unquote say the white, you know, they're white. You
can't cook. Right. If you're white, you can't cook.
Well, the first move was the first move was, look, you can't get the good quality food
you want to get because you don't have cash to go get it. So now you're stuck with whatever
you can get your hands on, because if you want to eat nothing or something that's crap,
people are going to choose to eat the crap. Well, then, yeah, they raided all the they
raided. They got old shoes, boiled it to eat the leather. I mean, I would I think that
was a bad direction to go. I mean, because you could always cultivate something. It was
the lack of knowledge. But what I'm saying is when I say white people, it's this culture
that came out from the Depression and all the steps of corruption till now. And give
me an example. When I first met the wife, we were dating and she goes, I want to introduce
you to my some friends. And I say, well, are they Mexican, Greek, Spanish? No, they're
American. OK, so she said, meet me at six o'clock and we'll go over to their house for dinner.
I said that. All right. Well, I show up at 10 after six and she says, you're late. Where
have you been? And I said, well, I had dinner. She goes, why do you have dinner? We're going
for dinner. I say, you'll see. You'll see. So we go over there, we sit down and eat dinner.
And I they give me some food. I just moved it from the left of the plate to the right
plate. She ate a whole bunch. We leave. She goes, oh, I don't feel well. I don't feel
well at all. And I'm like, I told you these are white people. You don't eat their food.
Right. You know. So and then it happened again. And she's like, oh, my gosh. Now that makes
sense. When she was growing up or whatever, that whenever there was a big dinner, nobody
felt well, you know. And it was like, come on, you got it. This is like, you know, really,
really like snap your finger to it, you know. And you see. So that's a real life example.
And she's a witness to it. And many others are witness to it. And also I've had some
response, by the way, from people with Greek students. I thought my mom's cooking was good
or my wife's cooking was good. I heard what you talking about it. And I started doing
some of the things I said. Oh, yeah. What I thought was good sucks. I can't eat it now.
And I'm like, yeah, yeah. What changed? Nothing. I mean, you changed a little bit. It doesn't
take a lot to make someone realize what they're used to is crap. Right. Now, I'm not saying
all of the white people food is crap. But if you use that as a rule, you'll be safe.
You'll be very safe. And if it's not crappy, it's an anomaly. So what do I mean by that?
Winter time, they're doing their holiday. So low and slow, low and slow. This is a mega
tangent went around the block twice, not just once. So what I've done recently is
some chicken. I've done some ribeye and sirloin steaks all the same way. Just remember this
forty five minutes to an hour per pound. What is he talking about? So let's say you have
a ribeye piece. It's three inches thick or so. It's about a pound and a half, two pounds
almost. Let's say let's call three pounds. It's a one bone ribeye porterhouse steak.
That's three inches thick. Same thing without the bone. You leave it out of the fridge.
You put it on a plate that goes inside a paper bag with salt on the paper bag and you leave
it there overnight. Right. There's the salt ionizes. Right. If you're in a room full of
salt, it smells like ozone. Right. Because the ions. Right. OK. So. So you let it dry
out and come up to room temp and then you put it in an oven. If you can make it work
this way at one hundred and twenty degrees at about an hour per pound. Now, most people,
when you put an oven at warm, it doesn't go below 150. Well, you're going to have to figure
out how to work that. Maybe leave the door slightly open, tune it down, turn it down
even more, you know. OK. And and you're basically at one hundred and twenty degrees. That's
it. You know, look in Tucson or Phoenix, if you close all the car windows in the summer,
it's one hundred and eighty degrees on the dash. That's too hot. Right. You know, cook
an egg on the sidewalk. I didn't think that was possible. I did it here once. It didn't
fry up like in a pan. But yeah, in three minutes, the egg was ready to flip over easy. Right.
So, OK, so really, really low. And you basically are warming the meat through. Now, the logic
between this and that is this, you know, like rare is less than one hundred and thirty degrees
mediums, 140 well done, 150 and up. Right. So why would you cook it at 350? Right. OK.
So what's going on here is you're basically warming up the meat and the fibers are instead
of contracting when they go into the fire and getting tough, they're they're relaxed.
It's like they're in a sauna and it starts to relax and relax and relax. Now, let's
say this three pound piece that I did last night and I've done this over and over with
steaks and all that, too. And chicken. Let's say this has been in through three hours.
It just looks basically this just slightly darker than it was when it was raw. And it's
at one hundred and twenty one hundred and thirty seven. I've tried also, which is fine
up to a hundred, but definitely not one hundred and fifty go below 150. This is not going
to work because it will get tough. So between one twenty and one forty. Now, if you if you're
one of these people that watches your food opening and closing the door, what does that
do? It drops the right. So you'll be fine. Right. If you. Yeah. So. So what you do is
when it's after the three hours for a three pound piece at one hundred and twenty degrees.
He told us that people are like, you're not cooking at a hundred. OK, what you do is you
do a very rapid broil on it. One minute to two minutes on each side. I use I have a
mesquite grill and I have a pizza oven. So the pizza oven goes to a thousand degrees.
The grill, it gets up to seven hundred. Right. So I light a fire on one side of it and I
bring the meat and it's like, wow, really hot. You know, one minute. Flip it around, flip
it around because you have six sides. If it's like a block, like a cube. Right. OK. You
got the top, bottom, left, right, front, back. Right. So and you just keep moving it.
So you got six minutes in there, one minute per side. You take it out of the fire. This
is all cosmetics, by the way. And you put it back where you had it for 120 degrees for
another half an hour. And with the flight, with the heat off and then you serve it and
it's for tender. You could do this with any kind of meat, by the way. Lamb, fish or whatever.
The fish doesn't have to be that long. Let's leave fish out of this for now. Yeah. Fish
definitely different. Yeah. To me. But you don't you can do it. But it would be 10 minutes
per pound with fish, not one hour per pound. You know, it doesn't need much. Again, the
worst fish you'll ever eat is something that comes out of the fridge and goes right to
the pan. Right. It'll never it won't even taste good. So you have to have things at
room temp. If you're afraid of foodborne illness or whatever, you must encase it with
salt. One way to encase it with salt is wrap the fish or the meat or whatever with paper
towel or napkins and then cover that with salt. Cover it with salt. There is no way anything's
going to grow on it if you're afraid. Right. OK. You know. OK. Now, also, what I do before
I do this, I have a big plastic mixing tub or whatever that I use in the kitchen. I put
baking soda, salt and water and I dunk the meat in there for a few minutes. Then I take
it out and dry it off. That removes anything that might be taking trying to grow on the
outside. Right. What about a pan? Nothing will survive. What about a pan of salt water
also in the oven? What do you think about that? Yeah. For for for resting. Yeah. Yeah.
That'll work. But you need it. You need proximity. It has to be close. You can't just be in the
oven. That's to be proximity. OK, so what you'll end up is having something extremely tender.
By the way, with poultry, I don't know. By the way, you know what inspired me the most to
cook is when I found when Scribd came out, Scribd, S-C-R-I-B-D. It was really you didn't
have to sign up. Anyway, I found some someone had scanned some cookbooks in there from the
15, 16 and 17 hundreds and there was no name on. There was a name to cook, but the file
did not have a name. So it was file six, four, nine, seven, four, three, two, one, nine, seven,
one, you know, that kind of thing, because I had it bookmarked. I remember years ago, a computer
that died out. So I'm reading and studying cookbooks. And basically, you know how expensive
books were 500 years ago. So very expensive. You know, a book could be ten thousand dollars
in today's money back then. Right. So obviously, if you wrote cooking instructions
and recipes on a book, these people were very, very wealthy. Right. And now they wanted to
keep it in case they had to replace someone and, you know, in the kitchen. And they took
the time. You got to realize, guys, when you look at and gals, if you read a book or find
something that Scribd that's more than or printed two or three hundred years ago, even if it's
scanned, that book costs about the two of those books. You could buy a new car. That's how
valuable they were back then. Right. Right. So I knew right away that this was done by
someone who was serious, serious business about food. Right. And I realized certain
techniques. A lot of it was, you know, there was something of the master roaster was about.
This was this chapter was to the master roaster. Right. This one was to the
sautee. And this chapter was for the baker. So it was interesting. You know, like, what's
your job? I'm a master roaster. I never heard. I mean, they call people chefs now, but they
don't call them master roasters anymore. Right. That's your job to roast. So I was fascinated
by it. And I just I can't recall any anything poignant that I could bring out and
say this. This is what I got from that directly. But the whole perspective
that I brought forward today and on other Greek speaks is what I got from there
specifically, because you want the perspective that I gave you. Now, if you go to a nutritionist
or cook hundred and twenty degrees for three hours for three pounds and then no, no, you have
to bring it up to temporary. It has to be at least three hundred. Right. No one is going to do that.
There there is a there is more of a low and slow trend that's been happening
again. People are coming to their senses. This is purely for pleasure, you know, for
pleasure, meaning eating food that is distinctively delicious and pleasurable to eat.
Now, one thing that I did get out of the the ancient books, let's say 300 years
is ancient, by the way, for a cookbook, is that the poultry must be dried properly.
So whenever you're dealing with poultry, most likely the audience will
be dealing with chicken or turkey and duck. It's almost traditional that you
should dry it out because of the heavy fat content. What what you do is you must hang the bird somewhere
or put it on a rack where it dries. I mean, literally where you touch the skin
and it feels like dry skin. Right. You know, dry skin, like dry, like, you know,
somebody says you got to put some lotion on your elbows. Right. That kind of that kind of dry almost.
Yeah. Yeah. You got to get some lotion on those elbows, man. Right. Or your kneecaps. Right.
That that's dry. Right. You won't get that chalkiness because of the fat coming through. But really dry.
Yeah. If you stuck a piece of paper to it, it will be just like sticking it to another piece of paper.
Once you get it to that point, what happens is the fats in the bird start to dissolve.
And what the fats that are layered within the muscle fibers, when they dissolve, they become
I wouldn't say acidic, but they release an enzyme that does what to the meat?
Tenderizes it. Yeah. Yeah. Inside out. And then you can do a fast cook.
So instead of cooking the chicken to death, you can just cook it for, I don't know,
a three pound chicken for 40, 15 minutes per pound at high heat or do the low and slow.
I dry the part of the poultry out so much that I just goes right away into high heat, browns right away.
So after like 10 minutes, it looks like it's done. But then you lower the heat and do the slow part there.
The reason I do that with poultry, because it's so willing to give up all of its juices.
When I do a chicken on a 600 to 800 degree grill, there is not one drop of fat.
You ever see like barbecue chicken, the fats burning everywhere.
I said I said or anything, if you're cooking any meat on a fire and it's dripping at all,
you might have one or two is OK drips. And I mean, not not three or four drips.
If it's pouring liquid out, guess what? It's pouring out all the flavor, all texture,
all the tenderness is coming out of the meat.
So I've been to barbecues and places where they invite me to eat.
And I see the person by the grill and all you hear is sizzle, sizzle, sizzle.
Five like you want. Would you like some barbecue? I'm like, I would, but not that one.
No, thanks. Because, you know, and I ask people, how was the chicken your wife just ate?
Oh, I was like eating sawdust. Right. That's because they lost all the moisture in the beginning.
Right. When I do it. Ha ha ha. Greek is bragging about his poultry skills.
Yes, I am. There is not one drop of fat or oil in the grill, no matter how hot it is,
because it starts off very dry. Again, if the meat is moist,
you're cooking to sear or to brown or caramelize.
It has to be way above the boiling point of water,
but nothing will get to that point unless all the water is gone.
So if you have wet meat in the fire, even if it's a frying pan,
it's going to be at 210, whatever degrees, 212,
for as long as it takes for all that moisture to boil off while it's still cooking the meat,
which is not a low temperature. It's rather high.
Low has to be below 150 or really, really high.
Now, if you put that meat in front of a thousand degrees,
it still will not go above 200 degrees until what all the water is gone.
So why don't you do yourself a favor and dry your meat off? Right.
So or the best way to do it is through time and convection.
Another thing that I do, Wal-Mart sells these little battery operated,
rechargeable fans or 10 bucks, 12 bucks.
You plug in USB and they run for like eight hours on low. It's fantastic.
There are four inch fans. We call those muffin fans or whatever.
You just put one of those fans in the oven or whatever or a box with the poultry
and you let it blow and blow and blow overnight.
And that will get it nice and dry. Also, again, with your salt.
Again, with the poultry, what I do is I Babscotch it,
which is I cut the spine right down the middle.
Now, it's easier to cut the left and right of the spine if your knives aren't sharp
or if you're using a scissor, if you're not good with knives.
I recommend getting a heavy duty kitchen scissor or the kind of scissors the paramedics use.
If you've seen those, they're designed to cut through leather and zippers and buttons.
They're very strong. Those are good.
If you've heard of them, yeah, they're easy to get.
Everyone should have one of those, by the way, because it'll cut through pretty much anything.
Right. And cut the spine out.
And when you open the bird or the duck or whatever turkey,
just up from the tail, about inches to up from the tail, left and right is where the kidney sacs are.
And you don't see them when you're cleaning out the bird because they're underneath the membrane.
And if you cook them in there, you're going to get that gamey liver flavor in your meat,
which is not that great. Right. Right.
Because if you're cooking organ meat, it needs to be cooked very differently than muscle meat.
Yes. So what you want to do is feel around where the spine left and right,
about an inch or two above, two inches above the tail there.
And you'll find a soft spot. Poke your finger in there and push.
And guess what? The kidneys will pop out.
And if you have a cat or a dog, it's a delicacy. Right.
And clean that carcass out really, really, really, really well.
There is, you know, and of course, you always want to get the best quality.
And I wanted to bring this up because it's become the low and slow method I've been using for a little while now.
It's become very important to me because the difference between doing the low and slow,
which is low temperature, long time, and then just a rapid high heat for color and flavor.
The difference between doing that and not is huge.
There's no comparison. You will not want to go back.
I mean, the right. I mean, it's not subtle.
It's not like you want it boiled, fried or grilled. No, no, no.
There's nothing to do with the style of cook. It has to do with what it does to the animal.
Right. By the way, if you go to a hardcore Chinese restaurant where everything's in Chinese
and you don't speak Chinese or read Chinese, they give you the English version.
When you're looking at beef category, it'll say muscle, muscle, muscle, kidney, liver, tripe.
Right. Because when you eat a steak or most things you're eating, what the muscle muscle.
Right. We don't call it muscle. We just call it steak or beef or chuck or whatever.
Right. So we just call it by the cut. We don't call it for what it is.
So organ meat is another thing that can be discussed.
By the way, when they fed animals that are supposedly carnivorous, just muscle meat, they got sick.
They need organ meat. Right. Tigers, lions, bears, let's say they go for the organs.
That's where. Right. That's where all the energy is. Again, it's about energy.
If you feed a lion or a tiger just muscle, they die of a certain toxicity.
If you want to meet, they always eat through the muscle and go for the organs.
Well, yeah. Well, the stomach area. Yeah. And then they save that.
In other words, when they're full on the organ meat, then the other stuff is put aside.
Right. Or it's left for scavengers, by the way.
Well, that's the other thing to do for it. Right. When you see the you know, the hyenas or the carcass.
Yeah. The other things that feed off of the carcass, the birds that come along and all that.
Yeah. And they're more they're more, let's say, set up to eat the muscle meat.
So I just wanted to bring that up because, again, I've done about five or six of these now in the past couple of months.
And it's there's no discussion. And I wanted to make that an addendum.
If you're doing, quote unquote, holiday cooking.
And I think the last time when we spoke about what do we do with these pagan holidays?
I was like, you can enjoy the benefits of it without the pitfalls. Right.
That's right.