Rated Y number 63 this time, and really quickly, before I even ask the Greek how he's doing,
I'm going to let you guys know something, just in case you can't figure it out.
We do have a chat room, which you can join.
It has nothing to do with anything, okay, anybody could find it, but generally speaking, you
guys who are subscribing to this should find it first, and you can easily give feedback
there.
We do read it.
We do check on it.
The Greek interacts in there a bit more than I do, but I check it out as well, okay?
Yeah, hold on.
It's ocelliandthegreek.chatango.com is what you're talking about.
That's what I'm talking about.
It's a completely separate entity.
It's just like YouTube would be separate and anything else.
It's ocelliandthegreek.chatango.com.
Right, but for you as a subscriber, you could go there and give us some feedback.
If there's something that you want heard on here, you want mentioned, you want discussed,
we do read it, and reasonable requests and things that are being discussed in there do
get discussed on Rated Y.
Just wanted to let you know.
One more time, ocelliandthegreek, all spelled out, one word, .chatango, C-H-A-T-A-N-G-O.com.
That is where you can go and interact in there.
It's its own entity, yeah.
Someone else runs it.
I think I have admin privileges there.
You might too, but we don't actually own it or anything.
It's just there.
It's a free, open source kind of thing.
Just all of that out there, that's what it is, and obviously, you would have already
gone to the Patreon by now and signed up because that's the only way you got this one, okay?
So anyway, back to it, Greek, often people do give us some interesting hints about things
that do need to be revealed because although they seem to be commonplace in the world,
and people get awfully emotionally attached to things, they are wildly misunderstood.
Yeah, the bread.
Bread, we were talking about.
Yeah, money used to be ... Yeah, what I mentioned we'll get into tonight.
I had a Skype with someone who's a sub.
He's got an academic background in physics, engineering, so forth, and I brought up some
terms that I thought people kind of know, and he says, why don't you do a Sonic on finance?
By the way, it's called ... Most people call it finance, but when you have a lot of it,
you call it finance.
Oh, okay.
Excuse me.
Yeah, right.
I never have a lot of it, so I don't know.
I'll tell you something else.
I was thinking bread.
It's kind of funny.
You and I are old enough to remember when that was very commonplace.
You go to get your bread.
Later on, it might have been knots, or stacks, or paper, or whatever, a lot of street parlance
for what is it?
Money, supposedly, right?
But you're talking about finance, and to me, money and finance are different things, although
they are involved with one another, but then again, I'm not saying I fully understand it.
Well, everyone thinks we're in capitalism.
You could go back and forth with various systems, but the Soviet Union and most communist countries
as known historically never really used Marx's principles as he suggested they should be,
or Engel, right?
Because those principles are actually not even anti ... Actually, they're very capitalistic
to a degree.
Well, that's the weird thing.
The history ...
Yeah.
That's the weird thing, like China right now, right?
Everybody goes, well, it's the communist, and yes, indeed it is.
The communist party, right?
The CCP, or whatever.
In name only.
They only use what they think people think communism is against, as a ... Right.
Yeah, but oddly enough, they do behave quite a bit like capitalists do.
They do have private entities.
They have a middle class that's actually rising a lot quicker than the rest.
Yeah.
Statistically, which country has the most billionaires?
China.
Do they?
Yeah.
Which country has the most millionaires?
China.
Oh, I thought we had the most millionaires.
No?
Well, 30 years ago.
Yeah.
In the we, of course, we.
Yeah, right.
Anyway, the United States, I thought had the most, but ...
All right.
Let me just give you a quick example.
Here we have the University of Arizona in Tucson, and the better Chinese restaurants,
the students that are over here from China go and eat there, right?
Because it reminds them of home.
Well, they have quarter of a million dollar cars.
They're 18 year old students, 19 year old, right?
And they're driving $150,000, $200,000 cars.
Talking about-
So, do the math, you know?
I mean, their pops is a millionaire, right?
Or their moms?
Has to be.
You're not driving a $250,000 ... You're not driving a car which is worth more than some
people's houses.
Yeah, it's the first.
Well, the average house price in Arizona used to be around $250,000, now it's $450,000.
Same house.
Over a period of two years, so it's kind of artificial.
We'll get into why these things happen.
No problem.
It's the same.
They're driving half a house then.
Even so, it's still pretty hefty.
Yeah.
Without sounding pedantic, you know, like, what does this have to do?
Like, so, oh, we just set everybody up.
Oh, I don't want to really hear this, you know?
He's gone over this so many times before in piecemeal and something.
We've done it back in O and G, sort of in piecemeal.
What I want to do is first just put out something that is currently affecting anyone and everyone,
and this is commonly done.
When it comes to, let's just say, power utilities, utility bills, you know, electric, gas, water,
whatever, most people are complaining that the bills are going up.
Like, here in Tucson, they just came out and said, okay, from now on, your bill's going
to be 30% more.
All right.
Why?
Why are they doing that?
Because the cost of the production of the utility, all the cost doesn't call for such
an increase.
So, what are they doing?
Why is this happening?
You know, like, with the COVID, it's like all the municipalities, all the state governments,
all the federal governments in lockstep did it all together, right?
No opposition, like, you know, exposed that everyone, right, is in step with each other.
There's no opposition, right?
Okay.
Why are all the utility companies doing it?
Because they were lobbied for a while now to pledge the next 10 or 20 years of all their
billings into a private derivatives funds and hedge funds, right?
They're called CTOs, right?
And it's managed by them.
And they sell derivatives and shares in that and for a return.
So, using financial algorithms, you know, every year, you should get more, a small percentage.
So, they want to cover everything.
So the utility company comes back and says, your utilities are going up.
It has nothing to do with the production of utilities.
Now, what the hell is the Greek talking about?
Yes, what they're doing is selling the future billings, 5, 10, 20 years.
Usually, it doesn't go more than 10 years, but up to 20 years for a big stable city.
Like, if you pick a city that's not going to experience a lot of growth, you know, like
it's already built up, they can do 20 years, right?
Okay.
Because you have a pretty good idea.
It's not like you go to a small town or a growing city, right?
Like, let's say Las Vegas 20 years ago, you couldn't really estimate what it's going
to be like in 20 years because you could just keep expanding and expanding and expanding,
right?
Phoenix and places like that, right?
Oh, yes.
Because you could continuously build on pieces of land.
However, if you go to, like, say Manhattan, you got an island there, it's pretty much
Yeah, you could sell 50 years ahead because there ain't nobody building anything.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, they might build a tower and add another 500, but out of the million, 500 is not a
big jump, right?
Right.
Where something like Las Vegas can go from 1 million to 2 million people in 5 years,
right?
Right.
It's a double, yeah, yeah.
So this is I'm giving a little detail on this.
This is important because you can do something about this, right?
But it has to be organized.
So what they do is they say this is what we're going to be billing here for the next 5, 10,
20 years.
And this is the money we have coming in.
We want to put it in a fund, a derivative fund.
And you guys have people invest in it to get interest and play around, see what happens,
right?
Kind of like, you know, someone gives you money to go to Las Vegas, right?
Okay.
So it's a futures market, kind of like what they do with commodities, right?
Yeah.
And they're called CTOs.
Birth certificates are also CTOs.
And, you know, like it's really hard to find out what's going on with the birth certificate,
right?
Why?
Because it's a CTO.
All right, what is a CTO?
It's a confidential treatment order.
In other words, it's a deal that's done in secret, right?
And they didn't really have a name for it until the SEC a while back decided to classify
a series of investments under CTOs.
And they're totally illegal.
Well, first of all, the whole system is unlawful.
But these are really illegal.
But they still keep doing it, right?
So, I mean, just like, you know, anything else.
So what you do, really, if the bills go up, you get enough people organized on the Internet
because you can also organize physically, you know, in meetings and places, pubs, whatever.
I don't recommend you do that.
But you can do it on the Internet.
Even then you'll be surveyed.
And you just find out which, when they're flipping these securities, you know, whether
they're flipping them on an 80, I mean, a 90 or 180 day cycle or even a 30 day cycle.
And right when they're ready to flip it, you have a majority of people in that city not
pay the bill.
So the earnings go to zero and then they're ready to flip it.
They're like, oh, shit.
You know, flip it means you're going to sell it to someone else.
You're like, oh, I don't want to buy that.
Nobody's paying the bills.
And then then when they can't sell it, they go bankrupt.
Right.
Because why do they go bankrupt?
Because they have nothing in the till, but they have to pay out to the dividends that
they promised.
So all you got to do is not pay your bill for one month.
Everybody.
But see, if one person does it, they usually defer it because you go a couple of months
and not pay the bill.
They just keep adding it up.
Right.
And then everybody has to do it in mass.
So the so the grand total goes down way low.
Well, what percentage would be like the tipping point on that?
Because, I mean, look, you're never going to get 100 percent.
Twenty percent.
Twenty percent is all you would need.
OK.
Yeah.
Because you think they're they're only giving when they promise points on these things on
a 30 or 90 day basis.
It's just like one points, two points.
So if you drop it 20 percent, that one or two percent that they're promising gets really
small.
They can't fast.
OK.
I know.
I guess.
Yeah.
All right.
No, no.
So they're promising half and it drops 20 percent.
You still got a lot of, you know, a big, big deal.
Right.
OK.
So coming.
So.
Yeah.
So go three months.
But everyone has to do it.
Right.
It's not.
It's not a matter.
See, right away, the rational mind goes, hey, if I don't pay the bill, they're going to
shut off my utilities.
Right.
No, no, no.
They don't.
They usually defer it for a while.
But the point is, it has nothing to do with shutting utilities off.
The whole thing is to bankrupt that particular derivative, the financial house that's doing
it.
So it's usually a bunch of scumbags, retired attorneys or attorneys or whatever.
Yes.
Attorney equals scumbag, by the way, equal sign.
But anyway.
Right.
So.
So you go down the whole thing and you figure out a way to organize as many people as possible.
You pull the switch.
Watch what happens.
Right.
But you've got to do it in mass.
So it's it'd be harder to do in a really big city, but a medium city, even even Tucson might
be too big.
Right.
Because there's almost a million people here now, three quarter of a million on average.
A city that's a quarter of a million, if you can organize 50,000, 60,000 people, you could
really start taking control of the, quote unquote, billing.
And by the way, all that stuff is bullshit anyway.
It's all public utilities.
They're already paid for by another CTO, which is known as the bonds people in prison, babies
being born.
Wow.
What is he talking about?
Right.
Well, I was asked to talk about this a little more because I brought up some terms like this
and the person was like, do a sonic on it, because I don't know.
I haven't heard you talk about that.
Right.
So.
So maybe the easiest way to do it is to go back, let's say, using the U.S. because everything's
kind of pinned to the U.S.
The bankers are using the U.S. as the policemen of the world, the military, which, by the
way, the military here sucks or it's a pretty crappy military, military everywhere does.
But it's pretty shitty in the U.S.
It's one of the worst militaries, believe it or not.
But it's because they're so mechanized equipment, you know, they've got more bullets than anyone
else.
They've got more tanks than anyone else.
Right.
They have more planes than anyone else.
They're so powerful.
But the actual training and the staff, you know, the ethics and morality is very low.
It's like one of the worst in the world rated.
Right.
What people say, well, it goes against the prop what we've been practically propagandized
to believe.
Just ask anybody who knows anyone that's in the military or someone that, you know, that's
rational that came out of the military.
What they have to say about it.
Right.
It's a shithole.
So because they're very heavily mechanized, it's a mechanized right.
A hundred years ago, they knew warfare would be mechanized.
Right.
It's not going to be like everybody stands in a row and someone says fire and then they
fire those mechanized warfare.
It started World War One.
Right.
So you have the military is also part of this.
All of this is attached.
I think I just derailed my thought here.
But going back to the history of the finance is really the U.S. because everything's pinned
to the U.S.
You know, a lot of currencies pinned to the dollar.
You hear that.
Right.
What does that mean?
They talk about the petro dollar like you're only supposed to buy.
Well, that's that's fake.
The petro dollar is just that's like saying Muslim terrorists.
It's fake.
It's not.
There is no petro dollar.
It doesn't work.
That's it.
It's a distraction.
It's a distraction or a petro dollar is like saying, oh, yeah, the World Trade Center was
an inside job.
They use space weapons.
You know, they'll put that out themselves because they don't want you digging in the
direction.
Right.
That you might find some real stuff.
So.
Yeah.
No, there's no petro dollar.
That's that's no.
No.
Yeah.
The petro dollar is this.
If you say a petro dollar and you got to say the grain wheat dollar, then you got to say
your derivatives trading dollar.
Everything is great.
Well, the idea there that they that they push is that you can only make oil purchases with
U.S. dollars.
But to me, it's silly because it is silly because you can only make 90 percent of the
purchases that they do international with the dollar anyway.
So it's kind of redundant to say petro dollar.
Well, and the other thing is that with the computers, the way it is, it doesn't matter
what the name of the currency is.
Well, it works.
You know what it means that it's going to go through Goldman Sachs, JP Morgan.
And right.
That's all it means.
It's got to go through those banks first.
They get a cut.
Yeah.
It's Rico.
It's Rico's.
What it is.
You know, Rico is racketeering influence, corrupt organization.
Right.
And that just means Rico's real simple.
Anybody can use it all.
You know, if you don't like what someone's doing, just send them.
I'm going to do a Rico charge against you.
And they flip out.
Why?
Because Rico's really simple.
It's like if you want to do business with me, you have to do business with him first.
That's Rico.
OK.
Very simple.
Right.
I mean, most banks do Rico.
The most municipal, most governments do Rico telling you you have to have an attorney is
Rico is a Rico action, right, telling you you have to have insurance to drive is a Rico
action.
I mean, anything is applicable to this.
That's what's great.
If you know how to use it, you can really use it to your advantage.
Demanding a Social Security number is Rico action.
Right.
Because you're I'm coming to you to work at the place and you're asking me to get a number
from someone, another place to work with this place.
That's Rico, dude.
Yeah.
That's why any place you go that requires a Social Security number, it's give it to me
in writing and they never will because they have evidence of a Rico lawsuit.
Right.
And Rico's always trouble damages.
Means three times.
So like in the octave trouble, you know, just the trouble.
That's the third octave and up.
All right.
So let's just do the basic history and without even getting, you know, you know, people that
have listened to various sundry discussions of money that I've done basically define it
as portable land.
Right.
Because if you look at things that are precious, they come from the land.
You know, gold, silver, all the basic monetary materials or were extracted from the land.
Right.
Yeah.
So it's portable land.
And it doesn't have to be that it could be other things that haven't been discovered,
like the osmium, platinum, where they come from the land.
Right.
So, OK.
Really, really simple.
When when the people were accumulating precious metals and jewels and out of convenience or
out of security, they went to a place called a bank and they gave them the valuables.
And then the bank either took interest or gave interest for holding it, whatever.
They found out that when people went and gave deposited things into the bank, only one out
of 10 would come and frequently do a transaction to withdraw some.
So they said, hmm.
So basically everything that we're basically hoarding here in our vaults, only 10 percent
is called on.
So they developed this 10 to 1 ratio, which was basically we can lend out nine times more
than we have because if people come and call it, call us on it, they won't.
We're only going to only want to write only 10 percent.
So we're never going to say we don't have it.
Right.
So.
So they did a 10 to 1.
It's called fractional banking.
So if the bank had.
Yeah.
OK.
So if the bank had a million dollars in its vaults, they said they had nine million.
Right.
Because only 10 percent of the people come and take the money in and out.
So it fluctuates a little still.
Right.
So it's still unlawful to do this.
But the people allowed it.
By the way, it also coincided with the coincidence that most of the bankers were Jewish.
And in the Torah, there is a 10 percent, the tie that keeps coming up.
You know, you get 10 percent to the temple.
Right.
And and that.
So.
But and by the way, the Jews religiously and collectively and communities in countries
were usually chosen or rose into the position of becoming the local and almost national
bankers as well.
Why?
Two reasons.
One is because it's in their culture to be educated.
Right.
Second of all, they didn't really have racial admonishments.
So when you had a country, let's say, like Italy, which wasn't a country is a bunch of
states back then.
Right.
City states.
You had a lot of feuding.
So when people moved around and you went through this part of what's known as modern Italy,
you couldn't do any banking because they found out what your name was like, oh, we're not
going to give you any money, right.
Or deal with your money.
You're no good.
Right.
So there was a lot of this either.
It was based on either your family name, where you were from.
You know, there were very there's a lot of animosity between the Jews didn't care.
They were like, doesn't matter who you are, whatever.
And it, you know, whatever.
And even that the national banks or the people that were the national bankers, meaning the
people of the same ethnicity, didn't like lending money to people who were poor.
Right.
But the Jews did.
And and that allowed people who were poor to actually if they had a sound opportunity that
if they got a loan, let's say they can use it and get out of that poverty.
But the Jews weren't stupid on this.
They said figure.
They figured, well, this guy's poor.
He has a sound opportunity, but because no one else is going to lend it to him, we're
going to lend it to him at a much higher interest rate, kind of like these no credit, bad credit
doesn't matter.
A car.
Right.
And it's 32 percent interest.
Drive it off the lot.
No money down.
Right.
But at least you get a car.
So now you get a better job, let's say, and you pay it back.
And then everybody's happy.
Right.
But if they lose, if they lose on you, they got so many of these out, they're going to
get so much return anyway that it's it's it's almost covered.
Right.
It's like hedged.
So if you've got if you've got 32 percent, it's really simple.
You get three people out of four to cover it.
You can lose every fourth one and you're fine because that one is covered by the other three.
Oh, yeah.
Quite a bit.
Yeah.
Especially with compound interest.
So so I just want to give a little bit of that because, you know, the Jewish banker,
you know, is a big deal.
I just wanted to throw that out there because it's never really discussed.
Right.
So what they did was the Jewish banker ethic helped a lot of people get out of poverty
because of the higher interest rates, because they were at the point where and I'll talk
about what the unions are, they went after the unions, very similar to Jews, but would
crash the the power of the unions very similar.
The people that were really desperate and wanted to stay out of desperation actually
paid the interest and were quite thankful and happy because that opportunity would have
been gone if they didn't get that loan.
So anyway.
Well, they wouldn't have the ability to capitalize on anything because they'd never assemble
the money.
So here's the thing.
They're just grateful, even though it's a harsh, you know, again, it's it's got they
got out of poverty, which was a chronic condition for them.
It could have.
In other words, if they didn't if they didn't pay the 32 interest points and didn't get
the loan, that means maybe another two generations before an opportunity.
Right.
Well, a lot of people, they could never even build their credit.
They go and they get one of these crappy credit cards and they sit there and, you know, charge
this is different.
This is different.
Don't the credit card is completely different.
That's the exemption.
I'll get into that.
OK, but it's the same principle is all I'm saying is that they turn similar, but it's
really.
But hold on.
Once you find out how the credit card works, it's no, it's not the same principle.
It's complete.
It's similar in principle.
Similar.
Not the same.
OK.
Sorry.
Yeah.
It's because the conditions have changed so much.
Right.
It's conditions.
It's kind of like saying a sinking ship or a sinking airplane.
Two different things.
One is, can you swim?
The other one is, can you survive a fall of 30,000 feet?
Right.
Big difference.
They're both you know, you're both traveling.
Right.
OK.
And then you have to swim afterwards if you survive the fall.
Survive.
Yeah.
Chances.
So that's what I'm saying.
So they're they're similar.
You're in a vessel traveling.
Right.
Both vessels.
Yeah.
But very different because the conditions have changed so much.
OK.
So.
Got you.
This banking thing, fractional 10 to 1.
All right.
So basically the bank has a million in the vaults.
They lend out nine million and because they know only one out of 10 people are going to
come and withdraw.
Right.
So they could still.
OK.
So you get into what fractionalization is.
I just need to bring that up.
It's a main point here to show you really what's going on and how crazy finances or finance
either one.
And it's all scumbaggery.
It's all unlawful and illegal.
But because the people want it.
Right.
You see, just like earlier, I mentioned, if you do a big strike and everyone doesn't pay
their bill, what are they going to turn everyone's water off?
Good.
Let's see you try to do that.
Right.
That'll lead to the next thing.
You know, you have a small thing that leads to another thing, leads to another that, you
know, they're going to.
OK.
All right.
So you have this fractional banking system goes on.
So then you have all the machinations from the 19th century about privatizing the central
bank or the bank.
Instead of the national bank making it a private bank, they don't call it private.
They call it central bank.
When you hear the word central, it means private.
Right.
Just like the word nice means dumb.
It doesn't matter how you think what you think it means.
It's what it usually is, how it's being really used.
So they wanted the national bank to go private, turn it into a central bank.
And you hear of all the machinations back and forth.
And finally, you know, they did the Titanic, which was not sunk by an iceberg, which is
funny because I keep explaining to people a ship can hit a thousand icebergs and maybe
it'll scratch a little bit of the paint, maybe, maybe, you know, like you could take a two
foot by two foot block of an iceberg and I could hit you over the head with a chuck and
you'll laugh because it's like lighter than snow, lighter than styrofoam.
You could see there was a fail video I saw recently, two people trying to grapple up
on a big iceberg and they flipped the thing upside down.
That's how lightweight it is.
The iceberg was like 500 feet long and there's two people on one end and they flipped the
whole thing.
It's like one of the light.
It's almost on the category of aerogel.
If you don't know what that is, look up aerogel, A-E-R-O-G-E-L.
So the lightest substances in the world, it's the lightest natural substance.
Well, I like the idea of styrofoam because that's real relatable.
People can, you know, it's lighter than styrofoam, way lighter than styrofoam.
You know, I could pick up a big old thing of styrofoam that's probably, you know, half
the size of my house, not a problem, and just toss it if I wanted to.
Sure.
The size is irrelevant.
It's actually even lighter than that.
Yeah.
So that's a joke.
It's kind of like, you know, the 19 Arabs with hijackers, with box cutters vaporized
the World Trade Center.
It's the same.
All right.
So what that did, it got rid of opposition, but anyway.
So from one thing led to another, you know how governments pass stupid laws.
They passed the Federal Reserve Act and the Federal Reserve Act basically for all practical
purposes for the people was that now a private company is handling the money system.
So this is how it went.
The U.S. monetary system was substance backed gold.
So basically the Federal Reserve said, I'm really oversimplifying it here, but it's still
true.
Federal Reserve said, OK, you give us your gold and we'll print notes for it.
Gold and silver.
And we'll print notes.
And the cost for us to do it is six percent.
All right.
So they kept giving them all the gold, giving them all the gold.
There's lots of newspaper articles you can see between 1914 all the way to the 1920s
on how they just shipped out 70 million dollars worth of gold to France.
Oh, another 50 million dollars worth.
This is back then.
Right.
So that's like saying a billion now actually could be more accurate, 500 million now, maybe
more, more like 900 million.
So you see these, they had to take control of the newspapers because the newspapers were
printing every so often.
Federal Reserve just shipped another 60 million of gold to France, another 60 million to Germany.
And so people are like, wait a second, why am I reading that they're shipping all this
gold out?
Right.
So the Federal Reserve is like, we don't want to have that kind of rap.
You know, people hate us.
So let's just buy the newspapers to get them as they stop printing that stuff.
Right.
OK.
What happened was the gold being limited in stock by the late 1920s, they had the U.S.
had given all of the Treasury had given all of the gold to the Federal Reserve.
Right.
So they wanted to print more money and there's all you need more gold like we gave you all
the gold.
And they're like, by the way, you gave us all the gold for money, but you still owe us
six percent.
Yeah, of course.
So but we gave you everything we have.
Yeah.
But you still owe us six percent of the past 20 years.
All right.
And here's the problem.
If you try and get back all the paper that they printed and say, OK, now I want my gold
back.
It's not worth anything.
It's well.
Yeah.
So you couldn't do that anyway, because then you say the society is start.
Then you go into Star Trek.
Yeah.
Right.
There's no money in Star Trek.
Yeah.
You could do that.
That's fine.
That's how you get rid of them.
OK.
So what happened?
Well, here's the thing, because the U.S. was turned into a corporation in 1871.
Between 1871 and 1889, it was various stages of corporatizing it.
It was handled like a corporation.
It went into bankruptcy March the 9th, 1933.
There's a document on that doesn't use the word bankruptcy.
But if you understand what they're saying, it's pretty much what it is.
I went into receivership.
Now, the difference when you have a bankruptcy, usually there's a trustee of the creditor,
the person you owe the money to, send someone over to liquidate, and so they can get paid
back what is owed.
Or the other option is to put the business into what's called receivership, meaning it's
like it's not good to liquidate it because the community needs that business.
So we leave it be.
We put new management and we take over.
That's basically what happened to the whole U.S.
That's why whenever there's an election, there is no change in, quote unquote, monetary policy.
Same thing continues.
So it's all the only reason you have elections is it's a formality.
It's just like the 4th of July or Halloween or New Year's.
There's no effect at all, right?
This is this should be known.
This is right.
OK.
So and they're trying to tell you by when they when election is stolen, right?
It's like they've tried to make it more in your face how obvious it was because it's
like, come on, people, you know, anyway.
So what happened then was, well, what are we going to print money on?
Well, we need something of value.
So FDR made a couple of speeches.
They called him fireside chats back in the 30s on the radio.
Very important for people to look those up and listen to him, because if you translate
what he's saying, he basically says, well, we're in a banking situation, financial situation,
but we're a strong country.
We need everybody to pitch in.
Everybody has to volunteer what they have.
Get it?
Just like the speech that Wendell was a house made.
H.O.
U.S.C. is the guy's name.
Anyway, Mendel House, he said that soon everyone will be registering their biological property.
Right.
OK.
So what they had is basically new agreements in a CTO kind of form, confidential, but you
can find them, by the way, that all mortgages, the Federal Reserve notes that will be printed
will represent a lien, a presumptive lien on all property in the U.S., including people,
basically.
So birth certificates were already they knew they were going to go into this, just like
a lot of the stuff that you see that was put in place after 9-11 was not immediately put.
If you look at the history of it, it was started way before, like Homeland Security, most people
think, came into fruition in 2002 or late 2001.
That was already set up in the 90s, right?
And all that.
So that was under Continuity of Government because, yeah, what's weird is they came out
with the public cabinet post and all that for Homeland Security after September 11th.
But they didn't call it Homeland Security back then, but it's the same, it's the same
charter.
No, it was again, it was part of the Continuity of Government program.
That's really what it was.
The COG.
Yeah.
And it was actually written by someone who was in the 90s, who was actually behind all
of the, what were the terrorist acts in Italy?
The P2 Lodge.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
It was written by a P2 Lodge member.
And after they made it, they arrested the guy who wrote it and threw him away.
Yeah.
Giorgio Hugo Ballestieri.
The ones that didn't magically hang themselves under bridges.
Yeah.
That's funny.
And it's a little long, but you know, anyway, it goes on and on and on.
This is, this is the same stuff you, this is treachery that you read about.
If you study ancient Rome, the same treachery, if you studied ancient Babylon, same treachery,
if you study the Mayans, the same treachery, if you study the ancient Greeks or the Chinese,
you know, when a new Chinese emperor comes in, what does he do?
Not usually, but if he wants to be a strong armor, what does he do?
He goes and burns all the records and all the history, right?
That's typical for them, right?
So, okay, so now we're in that situation where, remember the 10 to 1, if they have a million
in the bank, they could lend out 9 million, 10 to 1, right?
Fractional reserve banking.
Anything above that is considered excessive, but go ahead, right?
If you look in the social security 1935 in the act, now someone says they found it.
Other people years ago said they can't find it.
And it's just true because they're changing things online, what you can access and what's
there and what's not.
And sometimes you might find it.
Sometimes you may not.
Right?
So one of the things that's mentioned in the social security act, 1935, because there's
several of them.
There was one in 1932 also that didn't call it social security, but anyway, you'll see
there that the births that are done in each state get a price of 6 million bucks, right?
This is back in the thirties, which in today's money would be a hundred million roughly with
inflation, right?
Maybe more.
Okay.
So what does that mean?
Now let's go back.
All these machinations with, you know, the U S going bankrupt and this and that, and the
birth certificates, you know, being secretly traded or used as an asset, all the land is
used as an asset for printing money and all that, that was done without the people's
consent and without any notice.
In other words, there are plenty of documentation to show that all this is in place.
Start at March the 9th, 1933, even Google brags about it.
They give you the document right there.
It's short.
It's just two paragraphs, three paragraphs.
They do mention, uh, you know, basically the same verbiage that you see in title 12, four,
11 U S code title, 12, four, 11, each country, every country in the world has a, something
like that.
It's called a rigid restrictor or conditional endorsement.
Right?
What does he tell?
What the hell is a Greek talking about?
Okay.
Let's go back.
So the, did the government give you prior notice and get your consent to go through
all these machinations with these private scumbags?
Answer is no.
No.
So because you weren't, you have to get some kind of a waiver, right?
Some kind of a waiver, right?
And what that was was what everyone calls their social security number.
What it was really called back then.
Sometimes when I tell people to read the old access, it doesn't say social security number,
I know, but you'll see the word exemption.
That's what it is.
So you get an exemption number.
Why?
Because if the shit got started getting worse and worse and worse, everyone signs up and
gets an exemption number, quote unquote, social security number.
So what you do is when you want to get some milk or some bread or pay a bill or whatever,
you use that number and it's good.
Why?
It's good.
It's a form of credit, like a credit card.
Why is it good?
Well, because the government got into a deal that screwed everything up and it really messed
up your life.
Cause now, you know, you live in a society, it's not Star Trek that you need some kind
of means of exchange.
So we'll use this number and that's what the credit card basically is doing.
Okay.
Right.
Um, so essentially that's where you are with the money.
It's very, very simple, but you remember the gold 10 to one, when someone made a deposit
for let's say a hundred dollars, the bank counted it as 900 on their own private books that
they could write.
And in other words, if someone brings in a hundred dollars, they say they have $900 as
in, in right.
Actually 800 because you can come and pull that hundred, right?
So anyway, that's going on right now.
So when you sign a credit card statement, right, it doesn't say anything about, it says
you agree to, if you read the little verbiage, every time you sign it on the electronic thing
now, right.
It says you agree to perform according to the original agreement, it's always agreements
and contracts.
Well, your prior agreement.
Okay.
Well, let's say it's a hundred dollar thing.
It's Sears, right?
Or which no longer exists.
I think, or whatever, Ace Hardware moment you sign that, that credit card company sends
all the information to the banker that's carrying that credit card.
So in many, many of these credit card bank, you never even heard of the usually insurance
companies, not always, but anyway, you know, there's the American express and all the ones
you heard of.
Right.
So anyway, when you sign that purchase for a hundred dollars, you just created 900, right?
They give a hundred to the merchant.
The bank now is 800.
I mean, that sounds, it's like, that's why for how long they've been saying, Oh, use
your credit card or debit card and you get what?
Cash back up to 5%.
Yeah.
They give you one, two, five percent.
Oh my gosh.
You're doing 800% and you're giving me 5% pittance.
That's why when you buy something on a credit card and you have a hard time with the merchant,
call the credit card company.
Well, and it's not a real 5% anyway.
They give you 5%.
Oh yeah.
It's irrelevant.
Even if they gave you a hundred percent, you're still being shorted.
Yeah.
You'd be shorted because-
You're still being shorted.
Yeah.
So let's say it was a hundred dollars and they gave you a hundred percent cash back.
That means that they give you a hundred.
They've still got, as you said, they created-
600 now.
They've got 600 now.
Yeah.
So, so the bills at the end of the month go somewhere else.
They're usually attorneys.
They go by zip code, but, okay, so this is what's going on.
So the thing is you start using this system and you're destroying the economy because
every time they create more money, the value, the value on paper, paper on paper, on a ledger
says, we've got so much of that.
That's why you start hearing about Congress got together and just gave $400 million to
Nigeria and also they gave a billion dollars to Ukraine and they're giving 800 million
a year to Israel.
Why?
Because they have this surplus.
They have to get rid of surplus.
You know, surplus is a bad thing in finance, by the way.
Well, it's actually a bad thing.
If you were running a 7-Eleven, a surplus would be a bad thing.
Hey, Chuck, I got 10,000 hot dog buns.
Well, how long are hot dog buns good for?
Yeah.
You're not supposed to.
You gotta, you gotta keep.
That's really bad.
Look, and here's, here's the thing.
Just, I need to slow you down just for a second because everybody else in the world has basically
been given to understand that if you're doing banking, uh, you can only write a check for
the amount that you have in your account, right?
So you
hold on a second.
Do you remember, do you recall loosely my whole check scenario?
What happens when you write a check?
Yes, I do.
Okay, good.
I hope others do as well because we might want to cover that again.
Yeah.
No, I think we're going to have to because here's the thing.
Everybody else would be listening to this if they didn't hear that would be saying, well,
here's the thing.
And it never makes sense.
They say, oh no, we're just adding to the debt and we have this massive debt and we're
worried about this debt.
Now it's strange that they keep calling it a debt.
It's not.
Let's stop right there.
When was the last time you've ever heard a politician in any parlance in any condition
in any place talk about the national debt?
Never.
Ever.
They never talk about it.
No, no.
But they are talking about the debt and the deficit now in Congress actually.
And the reason for this.
Well, no, not to the public though.
Not to the public.
Well, yeah, they have been recently.
They only really.
Okay.
So it's a new dish.
All right.
So they'll distract him again with this for a little bit, but never.
In other words, you'll never see it.
But here's what makes no real sense is that, okay, I can keep writing checks on an account
that, you know, they basically say is in debt.
You try that with your own bank account, right?
You know, the little one you have there with your little name on it, you go to whatever,
your credit union and so on and so forth.
Okay.
Hold on.
Hold on before you get it.
Let me give you something juicy.
Sure.
You know how, what happens if you write it, you have zero in the bank and you write a
check at a chase hour of 50 bucks.
Let's say you just wrote a bad check.
The attorney general comes after you.
This is no bad check.
Writers will be prosecuted by the attorney general.
Right.
Okay.
Well, it, if you look at title 1295 a 95 B it says there's nothing you can, anyone can
write basically one of the citizens or people that could, they could be held against them.
So you can get a napkin and write a hundred dollars on it and they could cash it and then
they'll say, Oh, that's no good.
But yes, it is.
So you see the bar association now steps in and says, we can't let the people know about
this because no one's going to go to work.
They're going to say, Hey, fuck you.
I got an exemption number.
I get whatever I want.
I'll leave the lights on door open.
The heat are going in the water running all day long.
Right.
Cause here's my signature.
And that's it.
Now you have the money.
They go away.
Yep.
They're like, because they're too savage.
John, they see it.
Would you say the start of the Federation in Star Trek, by the way, Federation and federal
are completely different, by the way, but anyway, in the Federation, let's say the communities
with under the Federation and Star Trek, would you call them savage?
I doubt it.
Maybe some of the planets that they go to are, but the Federation itself is highly organized.
You don't see any, anybody, you don't see anyone wearing work boots with no shoelaces
and their pants dropping down below their butt.
Right.
You know, I'm talking about the hip hop culture.
You don't see that.
Absolutely not.
Here's the thing about that is that basically it's the replicator, right?
Because here's the deal.
You can get anything you need.
That's all.
Everything's in place.
Yeah.
You can get everything you need.
It's there.
There's no need for any exchange.
You don't need to bother with it because of the replicator.
And that's true.
They have greenhouses too.
But what I mean is we already have the replicator going in our bodies.
All we have to do is mimic that.
Right.
But we can't just like the medical community cannot let the people know that how the body
really works because then you could replicate it and have anything you want whenever you
want it.
The same reason the financial community or finance and the Bar Association, the attorneys
do not want the people to know that that what that is social security, that exemption number
really can do and does.
Right.
Because now we will.
It'll just put them into irrelevance.
That's the biggest problem right now.
These techno companies like Amazon, Facebook, Twitter, Elon Musk and all that stuff poses
a big problem to finance because people are ready to use those platforms, those digital
cloud platforms to do finance.
Right.
And they do.
But they're not the be all end all.
The financial community, the bank, central bank does not want to give that up.
And they're fighting with a digital currency of their own.
You see, because once they give up power, it'll be like when the original power was
given up around the time of the Renaissance from the kings and the monarchs to the financiers
because the financiers were the merchants.
They were dirty.
They weren't even allowed in the palace.
So but now it's the opposite.
Now the financiers can put any king they want in.
Right.
So they don't the financiers know what they did and they don't want the tech giants to
do it to them.
So that's why you're having all these machinations going on.
And that's when when they pulled the covid stuff, they said, look, you people think you
control everything, but we're going to show you what we can do by sending everyone checks
and flooding.
Right.
OK, so that's why I told people if you get a stimulus check for a thousand dollars, you're
going to pay.
That's going to cost you over ten thousand in the next five years because of inflation.
Well, the second you sign that thing, you just created.
That's right.
Ten thousand anyway.
Right.
Yeah.
When you sign it, you create ten thousand.
Right.
They give you a thousand.
Then they divide the rest into three.
The bank gets one third.
The central bank gets another third and the feds get another third.
That's why the feds are swimming in money right now.
Don't believe all that.
The what they call the national debt is just the national ledger, because people are so
irrational that if you are minus 30 trillion in a bank account, can you write a check for
a dollar?
No, no.
And if someone gave you 30 trillion, can you write a check for a dollar?
Still no, because now you're at zero and people say, oh, this government check is good.
No, it's not.
It's only good because they have the guns to enforce it.
Right.
So let's call it quits right here.
I just had a cup of coffee and all that.
I said, let's make it just one coffee long, because this kind of conversation has a lot
of gravity to it and gravitas and it could drive people downward.
So let's keep it upbeat and continue maybe on the next one.
Yeah, no, definitely.
The mind blower to me, though, and the thing that I take away from this is, again, if people
understood this, it would make so many things irrelevant, because if all you had to do
was give your signature and therefore you had everything replicated for you.
Yeah.
But you can still, by the way, if you make a restricted endorsement, they are not supposed
to fractionalize it.
And we'll get into restrictive endorsements in the future.