Tape is running Sonic Event 59, Uccelli in the Greek rated Y.
So we'll just continue where we were last we spoke, I suppose.
But before we get there, real quick, I do have one little thing I want to throw in.
You know, I'm thinking a lot more about cosmic censorship in the past couple of days,
wondering if it is cosmic or if it is self-imposed, the very oversimplified viewpoints
that I see people deciding to line up with, with their virtue signaling,
etc, etc. I'm wondering about that. And I wanted to start off with that question, if you don't mind.
Well, you need I need more information because it's you kind of forwarded it in a way that
I don't really deliver it, meaning like, like, it's only applicable when you want it to be.
I mean, you know, it sounded like it's optional. And I'm saying,
the way you presented it, what I'm saying, it's not optional.
Well, there you go. That's what I'm trying to direct you until you directly address it. And
then there's the ritual, the spiritual algorithm of once you acknowledge something
and speak it to someone else, it starts to be examined. And then upon examination,
it can be measured, quantified, qualified and adjusted. And that happens with everything.
OK, well, what I see is relating to what we discussed last time, which was the incident
in Israel. What is going on? And it does seem to be escalating a bit, but I don't know if this is
I'll get into that. Yeah. You know, but but the virtue signaling that I see here,
you see automatically there are people attaching themselves to the cause one way or another.
Yeah. But hold on. Let me let me just get into it real quick. Yeah. I don't watch CNN or Fox
News or even click on their stuff on YouTube or anything like that. I don't I don't watch
television or cable or anything. Occasionally we I have a Roku, which is a stream device.
And I put on YouTube's when we're eating dinner just to travel the world and see what's going on.
You have a lot of control with YouTube. Right. You know, and you could put a fireplace on.
Right. And it's a nice it's a really high definition, 44 inch flat screen off to the
side. And it's entertainment. You know, the wife and I have been together 21 years now.
So having a TV on in that capacity is not having the TV on. It's just, you know,
video. Right. Of whatever we want. So other than that, if the subject is brought up the way it has
been or of certain things that pop up, I don't know what's going on. I don't watch anything at
all. You know what I mean? Oh, yeah. Yeah. So meaning I don't know how they're pushing it in
the mainstream. Believe it or not, I didn't even know how they were pushing the covid
in the mainstream. I didn't watch any of it. But I don't care about how they're pushing
it in the mainstream. What I'm saying is that people jumped even before they really got rolling
on the mainstream. People instantaneously jumped and went to their social media and went to make
statements and sent messages to me directly to other people directly about it. You know, as soon
as they got the first reports, there was like an almost reflexive action to join one way or another.
And I see it as you know, there are there are some people that
reactionary you don't want to be reactionary. Right. Right. Yeah. Even if they were ready to
nuke your town, you don't want to be reactionary. You say it's going to get real hot and pop in here
in a minute. So let's go over here. Yeah. Yeah. Or just get on the roof and take it all. Yeah.
Don't be reactionary. No, I responded to people. Look, even if you know, even if you are worried
about, you know, the world's going to end now because of this, I say, well, you know,
what doesn't work that way? Well, it doesn't work that way. But, you know, don't believe me about
that. OK, well, you know who had the right to say the world was ending was a lot of the
cities and towns in Japan and Europe during World War Two and they were being firebombed.
Yeah, right. That that would definitely look like the world was ending and you would have a lot of
right to say so. Well, if you were there. Yeah. And in retrospect, we haven't gotten a lot of
reports that people were saying it was the end of the world that actually they did. I know
several people from the 80s that were boots on the ground and in London and in Hungary,
where they were dropping rockets and bombs and they broke out the zoo. So the people came out
of the shelter in the morning and their elephants and lions in the street. Right. In Budapest,
stuff like that. Fire bombings. Yeah. Yeah. So they could say it's the end of the world and
in retrospect, we don't get a lot of them. No, it's not the end of the world. The world is man's
society. The earth is basically what it is. You still can't figure out what shape it is overall.
And you can't, by the way. I think I've gone over that. Yes. Yeah. But this is what I'm looking at
here. This is the first thing that jumped out at me at a quick Occam's razor. This is not a
Freemasonic signaling. You mentioned signaling. I don't see any five ones or one fives or fives or
thirty threes popping up. Right. Or 17s. Those are Masonic numbers. Nineteens. I don't see any
of that at all. No, three threes. No. OK, so that's because, by the way, you saw a lot of that with the
the coronavirus because of the medical industry is basically very much steep in Masonic.
If you look at the the V-neck that the doctors wear, it's you know, you have different colors
for different levels. Right. Right. That's the 90 degree. That's the Masonic. The same as
graduation and all that. That's very, very, very Masonic. You can see it in their symbol,
the the what do they call it, the square, which is laid down on the over the over the video.
The same they do with the universities. That's why a lot of hospitals are also university medical
centers, so to speak. So all that stuff is tied in. None of that. I don't see any Masonic signaling
to themselves at all. Basically, this is a purely intelligence operation. What makes it that is when
you see the word terrorist being used that instantaneously. And also when they start
saying, oh, again, a failure of intelligence, all of those signals. That's exactly what it is.
And that's the funny part, because to me, OK, look, it's not organic. This is not an organic
occurrence in my mind. This is orchestrated. There was a lot of tells before it happened.
So, yeah. Also, I have a friend who went to Israel. He's from Israel. He spent a month there
and he basically came back saying, thanks for your procrastination. All the stuff you've been
talking about is happening right now. And this was two months ago. Right. So. Right. Well, and
that's the thing I was asking you about a couple of months ago where I said, look, you know,
there's things that they're reporting on. And you said, look, forget about what they're reporting on,
because that's always wrong. But something is happening because.
Hold on. This is being proper. It's being shown more than what it is. Now, unless you start seeing
tens of thousands of people, like, for example, they talk about the nuclear atomic bombs on Japan
that didn't kill one third or one quarter or maybe conservatively a fifth of the people that died
during the fire bombings of Tokyo, right, which was over a quarter of a million, supposedly,
if we go by their numbers, or even Dresden, or, you know, those firebombing talks about those were
savage, savage bombing. So yeah, quarter of a million, almost three quarters of a million in
Japan died from American bombings, which is nothing compared to the atomic bombs to get
all the play. Okay, so what does that mean with this? Yeah, the they're doing the body count thing
they're showing stock footage, by the way, old stock footage. Some of the stock footage is so
bad. It's from the 80s, by the way. Oh, I know. So that stuff I proved recently, by the way. I
mean, you got people in the wrong uniforms, you got technology that's all over in use in the films.
I mean, everything. It's a horrible. It's not even a good attempt to do it. Right. I mean,
really, no, they don't have to because the people are so whatever, at this point, but
they've always been that way. But But here's the thing. What makes this the intelligence op is this.
The Freemasonic signaling is not there. Now people talk about the elite, the intelligence, okay.
World War One, on the surface was to get rid of the monarchies and bring in these fake republics
and all that, right. Okay, so there's an international consent League of Nations,
supposedly, which didn't work. There are international bodies before the League of
Nations that's still around, by the way, you could look them up is one or two. Anyway,
um, what it did was it put the intelligence, it knocked out all of those smaller intelligence
agencies, and of all the nations, and it's set up for a grand worldwide intelligence agency,
one of which was actually propagated during World War Two. And World War Two was they had to show
that the Americans won, which they didn't at all, because they were going to use the Americans as
the police force as the central military force, right for the world. Right. And that's all these
two wars really did. And there's a lot more finer details, you know, but that's generally it. So
basically, when we people talk about the elite, the banking leader, they're not running the show,
it's the intelligence agencies are because I've given what I've borne us a very strong witness
to someone whose job it was to call up people like Jeff bozos. After they checked their bank
account, their bank account went to zero to reconsider what they were saying in public,
right? Prince tried to break away. Right? And, you know, the former well known as Prince,
right, the musician, right. And they're like, Wait a second, what do you think you're doing buying
all this travel gear and an island? No, we're gonna make a bank count zero, you got to come
back and do a show and be normal. Like you like you're supposed to be right meaning as as a normal
Prince and he did. So who does that? It's the intelligence agencies that control all the
banking, right, not the Rothschilds in the right. So they control the government, right? The you
know, the presidents are transients, the prime ministers are transients, right? So these
intelligence agencies are not getting the play. When they say CIA or all the or Masada, whatever,
that's like a very surface. It doesn't really convey what's going on, right? People, you know,
like I know people who worked for those agencies. That's a bureaucratic end of it. Really?
It's Yeah, that's not it. Yeah, that's like the foot soldiers. They're so you know, low on the
totem pole, still basically a little closer away from the surface and a little closer to the
reality is something like the five eyes concept where you have right, the international group
together working together. And yeah, some of us on the books, but they all here, let me give you an
example. When they say their enemies, their friends, like, you know, the supernotes, for
example, the notes in the United States are printed in North Korea. Yeah, bio weapons are used and
tested there by by administrations for the Americans. Iran and Israel are enemies. I doubt
it. Anyone that knows the underworld in Japan will tell you it's the Yakuza were knocked out
of the powers been taken away, kind of like the New York mob was right. And who's in power of
the underworld there. It's the Israeli underworld and the Iranian Persian underworld. They're like
hand and glove. They work together very, very, very close. So Iran and Israel in the underworld,
which is the under under unregulated, unseen, but well known, are very, very, very close.
As a matter of fact, you can plot things that are going to happen back and forth
and see how very closely Israel and Iran work together. There are the two powers. As a matter
of fact, there is a very people don't know you could I don't know how much you could look this
up. But the oldest, quote unquote, Jewish money in the world is in Iran. They basically as a
failsafe, if Israel were to be wiped out, the quote unquote Jewish site or the Zionist world
will be run out of Iran. Well, here's a funny here's a little fun fact that I just happen to
know, and I'm not going to explain how I know it, but they communicate through a language,
which is a combination of Arabic and what it is they allegedly speak in Israel. It's not
a pure language like you see written out anywhere else, by the way.
There's this combined language that they use, which throw everything by the by that person
wouldn't that would be Farsi. Yeah, not Arabic. Yeah. So it would be like the same language
spoken in Afghanistan. There is a big contention between Arabs and Israelis. Yes, but not the
Persians at all. What? Yeah, funny thing that they speak Farsi in Afghanistan, because that's,
you know, still a plenty good source of, you know, heroin. So, you know, you got to be able
to communicate with your farmers if you're going to get directly from the source, don't you?
So sure, but that's all screwed up the the opium trade because it was given to the Americans by
the British so they would not invade Canada. Yeah, but then they stuck it over, but they stuck
a whole bunch of it over in what I call Oceania over down by Australia now and nobody pays attention,
by the way. So yeah, sure, sure. But the black market is the underworld. And all right, who's
okay, just a little tangent, the most notorious countries for the black market, there's three of
them. And if you live in the US, it's that one of the number one would be that very dangerous
country to the north of the US, which is known as Canada. The second one would be South Africa.
And the third one is Brazil. So what do these three have in common? If you need black market
nukes? Guess who purveys them? You're going to get it through a Canadian, a Brazilian,
or South Africa. That's where they're purveyed through the 21 p seven granite 700 granite
missiles that went missing on the Kursk submarine that was one was fired into the Pentagon on 911
is handled by one of those three countries, middlemen, or, you know, or based out of
operations. Canada is extremely dirty. That's why you never hear about them. You hear North Korea,
Iran, Somalia, you know, whatever. So Brazil is also not listed, but it is a nuclear power,
more atomic power, right? They have atomic weapons. And of course, everyone knows that all
the trigger mechanisms and all the stuff is goes through South Africa. By the way, when someone
sells you a nuclear weapon, it never comes with the trigger. You get the body, you get all that.
But when you want to use that want to use it, they ask you for the US for the trigger and say,
well, where do you want to use it? Then if it's approved, they give you the trigger mechanism,
it would be like the key to a car, you know, or the starter, you know, about starters,
they took the starter out of your car, right, or something. So all these things are very logically
induced, if you watch what's going on. By the way, also, when you hear about the US giving weapons
to other countries, weapons aid, they can't use any of the weapons, unless they get approval.
Right. So let's say the US gives weapons to France, or let's say they're very industrial.
Well, let's say some country in that country now has the weapons and they want to use them,
they cannot use them unless they get permission. So when you hear about some country got foreign
aid, and they use it against another country, well, they had to get the permission from who
they got the weapons from to do it. And this is an ongoing thing. It's it's comes with conditions,
right? So these things, these, everything that I'm telling you is not hard to find out,
I don't know how hard it would be on the internet. But if you're active in researching and,
and know people in various aspects of life, and you accumulate, you know, four decades of,
you have a good memory, put it all together, right? So that's where I'm, that's why I'm saying
what I'm saying. And you can take it to the bank. And what you could really take to the bank is,
if you see Iran being drawn into this, it's definitely, you know, an inside, you know,
kind of deal, very, very heavy deal between Israel sacrificing a whole bunch of people,
and on and on and on. Because if Iran is dragged into this is going to be a big dispersal of,
you know, dynamics, right, throughout the whole world. I don't think if you really want to know
what's going on, see how this affects the underworld, the black markets, it's it will,
what is going to affect is the open markets, you know, like I did some articles, I posted on Skype
to some people, one of them, I'll bring them up real quick, is how several alternative papers
are questioning how could it be an intelligence failure? It's not possible, right? Because they
have a very strong intelligence network, right? The other thing I brought up is 30 billion shekels
were put on the market because the shekels fell. Right? Now, in international law,
when a country loses a campaign, it's it's currency is usually devalued, or goes to zero,
like the Iraq war. Remember, they got right after the Iraq was taken over by the coalition,
and whether the DNR Iraqi DNR went to zero, and they created a new DNR, right? All that hype
behind that. Okay. Yeah. So if they're preempting telling you that the Israeli currency is failing,
that's like signaling to people who know what I just said that Israel is going to capitulate or
be the loser in this. By the way, I did mention this a while back, right? Unlike other campaigns,
which they've had, you know, from the Six Day War, the wars that they had in the 60s, 70s,
and the early 2000s, they did have a little skirmish with the North. You know, it lasted
about two weeks. And they said, we're at war. I think it was with Lebanon. Remember, in the early
2000s, 2003 2004, something like that was a short one week, something like that. And yeah, yeah. So
this one, they're going to compete, they're going to lose pretty much not lose, but take a negative
stance on the outcome. How's that? Okay. And they're signaling that by telling you that they're,
they're doing it backwards. They're telling you the end at the beginning. Right? Which is, you
know, the currency going down. So that's interesting. But other than that, it's the typical
media shit show circus. You know, how many people in body bags and the body counts and all that.
What's funny, I haven't even seen Masonic numbers in the body counts.
They're odd numbers. Yeah. So the Masons are out of this. I think there's a little bit of a power
struggle here, because the Masons are everywhere. He's a bar association, right? Mason's doctors,
all those upper level professionals of the banking, they're all Masonic, they use Masonic
signaling, but I don't see Masonic signaling here. So when you said it's not organic, it's beyond
being non organic. It's, it's something new, which I've talked about also, you're going to see things
that are you haven't seen before. So with that said, it's really hard to get an objective point
of view of what's going on other than boots on the ground, which I do have, by the way,
and I have not had any contact with them, because I see what's going on. I think boots on the ground
matter the most when it before any event happens, right. And then during if the what they're showing
you seems to be majorly contradicting, but I've read a lot of fake photographs, which actually,
if you look closely at that photograph, you could find it it's stock footage. Some of the
current wreckage, you know, like, you know, 1000s of buildings being hit with missiles,
you know, on both on Gaza and all that, those seem to be fairly current. But otherwise,
yeah, this is what happens, by the way, when you, as a human, stop developing at nine years old,
and you spend the rest of your life basically as an idiot. And, like, someone left a message,
should we buy silver and gold and said, Why? And so the dollar loses its value, whatever I said,
dollar doesn't have any value at all. The only value it has is the people accepted as tender for
things that you think have value to think the money currency that you're using has value is
foolish. Anyone in banking higher up will tell you that it's based on faith. Right? So what kind of
people would have faith in a system like this? There's no help for them? What kind of people
would have faith in a medical system that tells you what they do, which is everything? What kind
of people would have? Right? Look at the religion, look at everything they do. I mean, it's like,
oh, my gosh. So when these things happen, are they bad things? Or are they just an outcome of just a
really bad society? Right? You know, a lot of people say, Well, you speak against the Vatican,
so Catholics bad. And I'll say, No, they're not bad. But I'll tell you for sure. They're not good.
Right? So you can be not bad and definitely not be good. They're very, very little good is being
done by going along with it. There's an ancient well, there's a maxim that if you go along with
something, you're complicit with it, you bear some of the guilt also, right? So here's the other
part about the intelligence operation, you'll never hear anywhere else. These people, Hamas,
which is the resistance movement, right, that was put in place, of course, intelligence operation.
When they got into make things better for the quote, unquote, Palestinians, they say that
we have to get away from this corrupt judicial system with the bar attorneys, do we have to get
away from this fiat money? Did they say anything about the Pope's work schedule Hamas? Right? Did
they say anything about this bullshit medical stuff they're getting? No, no, that's how you know,
it's a that's how you know, it's an intelligence operation. And then someone will might come up
and say, Well, Greek, they're all no one talks about that. I'll say, Well, thank you. They're
all intelligence operations, you see. So, so this is their own fighting. So if you participate,
and in that, and here's the thing, things go south. Like, for example, here's a small
analogy, Portland, I think is one of these cities that during, you know, they did all that racial
stuff. And then they did the LGBTQ didn't they like close off some streets and like, like San Francisco,
the crime rates gone up high, a lot of businesses are closed, right? All this stuff, right?
You hear all that stuff. And actually, people have gone there. It's going down, right? Chicago
for the longest time, right? Right, right. Lizzie, whatever running it. Okay, all this is by design.
So when you start seeing stuff, this really shit quality, ethic and morality that you have in
society prevalent everywhere, pretty much. When you see it affecting your physicality,
it doesn't happen all of a sudden. When you see it affecting your physicality, your food,
clothing, shelter, quality, you have plenty of time to move, right? Your point or, you know,
or buck up and take it, right? In other words, it shouldn't be a surprise. So,
so when San Francisco going down in Portland, Oregon going down in other places like Chicago,
it was a slow, it might be two, three years, but that's plenty of time to make a decision where,
you know, I got to leave here because it's getting really bad, right? Okay, so the same
thing has been going on in in Palestine for a long time, but people put up with it. The problem
that they have is they're putting up with the leadership that's put over them, right? So here's
my here's what I always end up saying. Even if you live in a dictatorship, the worst dictatorship
you could imagine, it still demands a certain amount of population, the people in the populace
to participate in the activities in government, right? So, you know, especially in the American
government, it's shameful, how little participation there is. And with that participation,
you can actually create a voice and, you know, find out really what's going on. So
by trying to create a voice, you know, and then reporting back, what do I mean by this? Let's say
you want to any society participate in the affairs of the government, be public about it. So when
they shut you down or infiltrate you or call you a terrorist or whatever, you have a record that
you're, and you could show that it's an artificial state of leadership, right? Just like what I
mentioned, like Hamas, did they tell the Palestinian people they're being enslaved by a fiat system and
a poor medical system and a poor judicial? None of that. So they're part of that, right?
Right. Yeah. So this is there. But it doesn't really matter where you are. But in this case,
things happen very quickly. Right? Well, sort of, I'm sure that, look, I've been telling people,
even with you, Chuck, on the Sonics, how many times have you heard me say if you live near
Gaza or a Palestinian, especially the West Bank, you should consider moving as we go more and more
into the future. You've heard me say this many times. Sure. Especially the West Bank up north
there. That's that will be completely gone. I don't know about this time around. Right. And
I've also talked about the repeat of judges. You know, it's the 14th prime minister that's going to
do it. And that's all muddy muddled up with Netanyahu being in again, but not really. It's
still around 1213 on the count. So, yeah, what I would beckon to anyone to pay attention that
there's going to be a governmental change in Israel. In other words, this the current system
with all the all the houses of labor and parliamentary style and prime minister style,
they do have a president, by the way, any country that has a credit system, which is all have a
president. You may not see them as the forward political whatever states person, but they have
to have a president, someone to sign off right on the bonds and the bills. So the current system
they have in Israel is going to change. I would venture to say they're going to revive some form
of monarchy. Right. So this might be the impetus for that, not the other things that I've said,
but the impetus for that also, I said, was someone that would do something on the Israeli side that
would be like Samson. Right. Against the Palestinians that would have the upper hand.
So this may not be the one that I've always been talking about that will change the face of the
Middle East, but it sure does look like it's stirring up the pot enough that it would lead to
it. Right. So I'm looking at it from a perspective of the news that was written thousands of years
ago, not the news that's been written last year or this week. Right. Right. Well, I guess that's
you know, and then that still stands as far as I know, you know, the what's that stands the
prediction, you know, the way this is supposed to go. Yeah, well, it's complex. But the simple
thing is this. As long as Israel has prime ministers, they will never be considered to be
righteous on the world scene. So when they end that government and they bring in a new form of
government, then there'll be a new view on the state, quote unquote, state of Israel. Right.
The other thing that's going to happen is a massive around the 14th prime minister,
massive conflict between the Palestinians, modern day Philistines and Israel, which will lead to
heavy losses on both sides, which would be the impetus of the change of that government, most
likely. But either way, whether one happens after the other, the how this will end up is that the
Palestinians and the Israelis were going to be allies. I know it sounds crazy. Israel will give
a lot of land, even their capital. Really? Yeah, it sounds entirely crazy, because I mean, the way
it appears at the moment is almost like they're going to try and wipe them off of the planet
what's left of them. And they don't have a lot of territory at the moment for sure. Well,
that was also said by the Arabs in the 60s. Remember, I said Israel, we're going to wipe
it off. That was the slogan back in the 60s. They were going to push them into the ocean,
I think was the. Yeah. Yeah. But yeah. Right. Obliteration. Either way. Yeah. Same kind.
That's the opposite. Yeah. What I what I see is things are not as they appear today. Like,
in other words, when you look at these news stories that run for a few days or a few
weeks, even though it's never as it appears in the long run. So I'm giving a longer forecast. But
my advice to anyone who does live there is to move, especially if you're on the if you're
Palestinian, you know, in those areas, right? Certainly. Yeah. But if you're Palestinian,
and let's say Central Israel, you'll probably be fine. And that doesn't mean for this campaign.
Right. So there was a someone I spoke to in California a while back. She's a jeweler,
Palestinian in Beverly Hills, well off. And she has family in in the West Bank,
I think, and she gave them the advice and they took it from from the report that I got.
Very smart. But yeah, this was many years ago. So many years ago, about a decade. Right. So
fair enough. Yeah. So that's pretty much it. I wouldn't say watch all these events. If you
watch the news, you know, people say watch the news closely, we'll watch it closely.
There's nothing to watch closely. Right? It's all garbage, the way it's presented, right? It's like,
go to McDonald's by 20 Big Macs and eat them all in one sitting. That's right. That's gonna get
sick if you do that. Exactly. That's the thing I was trying to, you know, get at earlier with
somebody else is that like, look, don't don't keep staring at this because it's, you know,
basically, it's trauma porn. You know, people used to call it rubbernecking when we were younger.
And what was that? Rubbernecking was it meant that basically traffic was going to slow down
because people are going to stop to look at the carnage from the accident. And that's all it is.
It's that except it's on a massive scale. You're not slowing down traffic. Now what you are doing
is slowing down progress because you're just sticking yourself to this continuous reruns of
how horrible this is, how terrible this is. Well, it's shocking. It's shocking because
being traumatized by concussive forces, high speed chemistry, in other words,
bombs. Yeah, it's very shocking. But of course, I assure you that no matter how many people die
on either side, any country in the world, except for I'm going to qualify here,
you will never have as many people in recent history dying as many as the medical community
kills. And the only difference with the medical community is when they kill your loved one,
whatever the surviving family thanks the doctors for everything they did.
Right. That's the main difference, right? Well, I think the other main difference is that they've
actually killed more people than all the wars combined, actually. Yeah, exactly. In a short
amount of time. Yeah. So no matter if you if you're just concerned, some people say, well,
people are dying. Well, if it's just about people dying, you should go after the medical people
then because they've killed more than, like you said, all wars combined. So why if it's just about
killing people, right? If it's just about the killing? Yeah, go after the doc. You know,
they're not even doctors because the doctor doesn't even mean what they're their medical
technicians. And they're doing, you know, the bidding of, you know, calling the population.
Again, if a million Americans died in this war, it wouldn't be it would be nothing a drop in the
bucket compared to how many Americans have died under medical care. Right? Absolutely. So again,
no matter how you in every country, except for places that don't have these systems,
and they're doing just fine. So that's that don't never want to hear about people dying.
You know, if you start have a movement coming around says it's bad that people are being
killed by the medical institutions. Well, then, yeah, then I'll back you up. I'll say, yeah,
definitely. Let's let's talk about that more. And let's form something together.
But if you start telling me that how many people were killed in this conflict, that is absolutely
minuscule compared, right? So it's not about people dying.
So the medical slaughterhouse is more efficient than the military industrial complex any day.
Absolutely. And if you talk about human trafficking, and all that other stuff,
it's the legal association, the legal groups that do more human trafficking than anything
that anyone has ever done, then any organized crime group or anything else that they tell you,
whether it's prisons and fines and all that. Yeah. So So tell by human trafficking, what a
crock of crap, you know, there's a over six or 7 million people being trafficked in America right
now openly by the Bar Association. You know, there's no I must say this, I've said, I assure
you, there is no one in prison that is there lawfully or even legally, no one at all, at all.
Now, if some people might say, well, this person's a murderer, you think you should be? No, I didn't
say this should be whatever, out in the street. I'm just saying that no one in any prison in
America is there lawfully or even legally, because in order to be in there illegally,
there's certain procedures that have to be fulfilled. And none of those are anymore at all.
So yeah, that's how bad it is. So what is it? It's human trafficking, you know,
it goes through the Federal Reserve, bonding, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah. So
I don't want to hear about human trafficking either, unless you bring up, you know,
the Bar Association. So this is the reality that people, you know, will never figure out
in this particular ever that they have.