Okay, so rated Y, I think it's 228,
but I don't know.
Who knows?
Maybe I'm losing count.
Anyway, here we are.
And how are you tonight, Greg?
Yeah, how are you is a good question,
isn't it?
Everyone always asks that.
No one really whatever wants the answer, do
they?
Well, nobody takes that into account.
And I got to tell you, one of
the weird questions I got this week, which
I don't fully understand, actually begins on a
how are you sort of question.
Because look, emo work, you've discussed it in
earlier Sonics, right?
And that is definitely one of those things
that everybody uses to judge how they are
when you say how are you?
Well, I'm happy.
I'm sad is usually part of that question
if they bother to say anything.
Right?
So anyway, yeah, what that's, that's really a
big how are you is, is, I don't
think that could ever really be answered, right?
But that that's okay.
It's, it's, it's what they call a nicety.
Right?
And they're in, by the way, in Japan
and Bushido, they don't ask that at all.
In Japanese called traditional probably probably do.
Now you know how I say what, if
you want to know the country's been like
USA, you Sonian?
Yeah.
Frank Lloyd Wright, the architect, he wanted to
create you Sonia, which is USA.
And then you know, another country within it.
Okay, culture.
And if the country has Levi's years ago,
I used to ask, do they have leave?
Can you buy Levi jeans in Japan?
They're like, yeah, okay, then it's becoming Americanized,
right?
But anyway, back to the email.
Yeah, email, big stuff, man.
I've been working on it, doing some new
findings with it, especially with weather work and
the water work.
Yeah, remember, you know, that you can never
find anything new on that.
Because remember, in the 70s, they had this
thing called a mood ring.
Oh, yes.
Right.
It was just a heat sensitive film.
And it was it was relevant.
It was relevant.
And you know, it turned red and orange,
and it turned blue and green, right?
So yeah, I was always one of those.
Yeah, I was always one of those kids
where the mood ring didn't change.
A lot of times when I put it
on everybody else.
Oh, look, I make it green.
I make it blue.
And I would put it on and be
like, yeah, it's just stayed the same.
A lot of times.
It's temperate temperature.
Yeah.
Anyway, temperature sensor.
So So back to the thing.
Anyway, that's sorry, that reminds me that this
has been looked at forever.
Yeah, the email thing, but it's just never
openly discussed like we are.
So anyway, right.
Well, somebody is working with it.
Okay, I'm just gonna give you that context
for the long part until they get to
the question.
And they've been working with it.
And they were curious, is there a particular
best default or starting time of day, comma
state of mind?
Or is this kind of work a fully
loaded, energetic, or fully unloaded energetic best activity?
So we're going all over the place with
this question, but I think you understand none
of that.
Okay, none of that scratch all that.
No, it's none of that.
Well, I was going to go back to
the early discussions.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, I was thinking it's like asking quick.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Yeah, it's a bodily foot.
That's fine.
The echoes coming back and went away.
I got used to it not being there.
Yeah, whenever I'm on this stupid rectangle, the
known as the iPhone, an earlier iPhone, it
gets an echo.
So no, the, the the purpose of discussing
the emo is because it's an attribute that
we have.
It's a sense.
So it's more than a sense.
It's what would you call an ability that
we have just like walking, and all these
other things that we do.
And it's never been acknowledged.
It won't be by the system.
The current system is a system of control.
Don't want you to know anything.
You might back me up on this.
Maybe I don't I know I wasn't hallucinating.
But more than once, I've seen a quote,
an ex director of the CIA says that
you are our job is done when everything
the American public believes is a lie, right?
Am I close or off?
No, absolutely true.
William Colby is most often attributed with that
quote, but others have been given a similar
quote.
And it's exactly the same.
Here's the funny thing about this emo thing,
though, to me, is as you describe it
as one of those abilities, then one could
kind of conversely ask themselves, when is the
best time to walk then?
Right?
It is all situational.
So it appears to me as though, you
know, their question, they should be able to
answer it, they're going to find that things
are situational as to when it's best to
do certain things, right?
It's not always a good idea to run.
It's not always a good idea to walk.
But in certain situations, that's the only thing.
Yeah, good.
So well, here's the thing, the most effective
use of emo is when you don't know
you're effectively using it.
A very strong desire to help someone afar,
right?
People say send healing energy, you will actually
feel that hug, just like when you gesture
a hug or get a hug, there's an
emotional feel a body feel that you have,
right?
An emotional, physical feeling you have.
And you'll notice that if you really desperately
just cry out to whatever, it'll be similar
to that.
Right?
So just like the guarding, when you guard
yourself, just desperately cry, you're trying to guard
yourself, it will come out, it'll be very
similar to when you're accused of something that
you didn't do, or it's even stronger if
you're accused of something that you did do
and deny.
Denial is very powerful, very powerful, by the
way.
Yes.
So you're gonna most people are using this
is nothing.
I'm just saying take control.
It's kind of like with the contracts, right?
You know, I see banks don't lend money,
you know, they just take your instrument, get
it cashed, and then turn it into a
loan.
Oh, my gosh, you know, do a read
your contract says it very plainly.
And let's see.
The most very plain.
Yeah, let's see if it's very, very plain.
Yes, please.
Let's see if I've learned something here, then
let me try and help this question real
fast.
Last thing, and then we'll move on.
Anybody could think about this and say they've
already experienced the use of emo, with people
not realizing it, you walk into a room,
and there is somebody who does have an
aura about them that they actually just put
out.
And it does change the room, right?
Yeah, everybody's been in an experience where somebody
comes in, they change the dynamic of the
room, simply by who they are, what they're
projecting the emo that they're actually carrying with
them, knowingly or otherwise.
And that's just the way it is.
And you notice when you're in the presence
of people without them doing a thing without
them saying a thing.
They are projecting already because of exactly this
thing.
And all you're saying is that you can
be conscious of it and take control of
it.
Am I right or wrong?
Right?
Okay, exactly.
And you could test it, you can test
it just like with the weather work, just
don't go out and start swinging devices around
and see if there's a change engineer it
say like, well, we're gonna do this this
way, because it'll make rain and look, there's
no rain in the forecast, right?
Or we're gonna do this and stop the
rain, because there is rain in the forecast.
So it's engineering, like recently, I was out,
and there were these two women, and it
was the typical American woman dialogue where one
is speaking, and the other one's looking at
the other one saying, when is she going
to shut up so I can speak?
Right, right.
And, and then the other one speaks on
the ones like, when is this bitch gonna
shut up so I can speak right?
And I was like, Oh, I'm gonna make
this this one go to the bathroom real
bad in a panic.
So the first thing I did was, regardless
if it's a pool, a beach, a bathtub,
when you know, when you first immerse yourself
in warm water, there's an emotional reaction because
the water is electrically charged, you know, it
grounds you.
And even take an extreme example of the
power of water, what happens if you're in
water in a blow dryer or toaster falls
in it, right?
So without a GFI, right protection, so you
get electrocuted.
So the all water that you jump in
will have an electrical reaction.
So what I did was I combined the
emotional feeling of going into a warm bath
with an electrical shock around the bladder.
And she was like, I waited and said,
Oh, it didn't do anything.
I waited about 30 seconds.
It didn't do anything.
Yeah, I'm gonna try it again.
As soon as I said, let me run
through that cycle again.
So is there a bathroom here?
I got to use the bathroom.
And I said, God, let's put this bitch
in a panic.
She goes, Where's the bathroom?
You know, I don't believe they don't have
any signs here.
Where are the signs for the bathroom?
Fine.
I need some help.
Where's the bathroom?
Oh, wow.
Wow.
Is it Greek?
You're a jerk.
Greek, you are such a jerk.
So the weak minded, right?
Just like in Star Wars.
These are not the drones you're looking for.
You're free to go.
We're free.
You know, whatever is true is that's the
best.
That's the best thing I had a movie
that ever showed.
You can do it, especially with the quote
unquote, weak spirited.
You know, that was very weak spirited.
That always kind of pissed me off about
the whole Jedi mind trick thing.
It only really seems to work on the
weak minded with the Jedis.
You notice that like it never works on
the bad guys.
It's like those guys are always very determined,
very clear minded.
Exactly.
So that means it'll work on 99 percent
of your family, 99 percent of your friends,
99 percent of your coworkers, 99 percent, 99
.9 percent of people around you.
Yeah, you stole my.
So that's that's pretty good.
I got you.
That's some pretty good odds, though.
No, in real life, that's pretty good odds.
It's good odds in real life.
But you're killing me because you stole my
punchline.
But that's OK.
Let's move on to some other.
That's fine.
It's OK.
Let's move on to some weird random stuff,
which is has the Greek ever heard of
German new medicine?
I don't even know what that is, frankly,
but German new medicine.
Is that a particular thing?
Yeah.
But if you if you hear anything coming
out of German or Japan, pay attention because,
you know, the whole system is based on
stupidity and control.
I just I was shocked.
I was sitting down having some beef tacos
that I made.
I did a bunch of New York strip
steaks yesterday and stovetop potatoes.
You know how I just put tears with
carrots and onions and cooked enough, like five
pounds of everything just so I don't have
to cook for the next few days.
And it's really good.
Leftovers are eaten cold or are great also.
So I made some beef tacos and I
sat down, put on a YouTube beef street
tacos, Mexico, OK?
And these ads come on.
And I told Linda, I said, are these
ads getting addressing like, in other words, the
vocabulary, the demeanor, the the way that the
message is delivered is dumber and dumber and
dumber.
Like not only are they speaking to immature
children, but like dumb children.
Right.
I'm like, whoa, this is really bad.
And then another ad comes on different products
and it's all really, really dumb.
Are we being dumbed down?
And the control structure requires, in other words,
what's coming requires such a juvenile mindset and
dumb mindset that's even worse than it's ever
been.
Wow.
Yeah.
Right.
So, yeah, that's what's coming.
So anyway, I do derail the question there.
What was the question?
Oh, yeah.
German new medicine.
Is that a you know, where has the
have you ever heard of it?
Was there.
Yeah, that's that's where that's that's where I
was like, if you hear anything coming out
of Japan or Germany, pay attention.
But I hope they're not.
Oh, my gosh.
The thing that really breaks my heart.
I know Americans are dumb.
Most people who Southern Europeans are dumb.
But when you talk about I feel my
heart's broken.
I hear they're dumbing down the Germans and
the Japanese.
Right.
But anyway, because those for those people, those
two groups, by the way, are for the
past two centuries are the ones that really
provided a lot of the technological, let's say,
not the actual technology invention and devices, but
the wherewithal to have them built in a
fine in a way that, you know, the
product lasts, let's say.
Right.
And a good engineering.
Because most of the inventions are American, let's
say, or non Japanese or German.
But they're produced by Japanese and German and
refined.
Right.
So I hate my heart.
I just my heart goes out to those
people because that means we're really screwed now.
And when made it right.
So gotcha.
Anyway, it used to be made in made
in junk.
And then it went to like, wow, made
in Japan now is excellent.
Right.
And and whatever.
Anyway.
Yeah.
It just I never heard of it.
But I'm just saying it's if put it
this way, from my point of view, my
book, if it's German medicine, you should look
into it.
Yeah.
OK.
Excellent.
I don't know it.
I never heard of it.
Never heard of it.
Fair enough.
But but indeed, I mean, that would be
something new, though, for sure, because, you know,
as you said, there hasn't been any changes
in things like medicine in, you know, 200
years, pretty much.
So, you know, because, well, the teens, 120,
they dumbed it down, because if you listen
carefully, I say people learn how to read
with comprehension, listen with comprehension.
What I mean by that is you want
to treat something.
All they do is treat something, treat the
symptoms, treat the symptoms, treat the symptoms.
It's never about fixing you or being unsecure.
It means you're going to stay sick.
You're just not going to feel or look
sick.
Right.
So, yeah, Flexner, Flexner reports.
That's why I tell people there's no more
medical research because the Flexner report was was
adopted as medical standard and said that only
current medical standards will be applied when that
was 1912, 13, 14, 15, whatever.
So everything else is retarded, which which I
do know people in the medical field that
try to get patents.
And it's like, oh, my gosh, try to
get a medical patent.
I'm talking about not pharmaceuticals because they wrapped
up with the inner sanctum of the patent
office and all that.
I'm talking about just some guy practicing what
he has a device.
And I know someone like, for example, most
ER cases, people that come into emergency room
have a displaced hip.
Right.
The femur comes out of the the socket
out of the hip bone.
Oh, yeah.
And they have to pop that back in.
It's one of these unusual things like like
half the people that go to ER, especially
at night, have that.
And he and usually it takes an orderly
and two people, three people to set it
back in.
And he developed a device that one doctor
can do it.
One medic can do it.
So and it's been like 15 years and
they won't issue him a patent.
And it works really.
But anyway, that would be useful to speed
up that process, because otherwise you've got to
direct multiple people to do it right.
And and I've done that, you know, with
somebody before I've had my own shoulder.
My shoulder redone is even a pain in
the neck.
Well, this is this is hip and femur.
I had also.
Yeah.
What they do is they had me stand
outside and you could see something's wrong because
you look at your reflection yourself and you're
two inches lower on the side.
They came out and you're like, oh, that
looks weird and I can't move it.
And it's numb.
And the orderlies come says before you see
the doctor, we're just going to pull your
arm on three and they go one and
two and they pull it on to.
Right.
So.
Yeah.
So anyway.
Well, that's that's actually an effective way to
do it, though.
Anyway, would appreciate insight into the difference of
using a translator.
Now, look, in parentheses, they put no water
versus a water gun, whether assuming the devices
are the same exact material and dimensions.
I recall there is a tunneling effect when
using a water powered device.
That's their whole question, by the way.
I need more information on what it means
by tunnel effect, because when I did the
weather seminar I spoke on, I'm paraphrasing, I
might have used these exact terms that water
gun is a disintegrating ray put on any
sci fi cartoon or Star Trek disintegrating ray.
Right.
Whatever you point the water gun to, it's
a disintegrating ray.
It goes away.
Right.
It's like an eraser.
There was an old Looney Tunes cartoon where
they show the guy with an eraser right
on the cartoon character.
So that's what it does.
The water, the translator, the dry translator is
not that you want the translator to be
built in a way where it represents a
lower ethereal potential than its environment.
So it feeds the environment.
Right.
Because low to high.
So I don't know what the tunneling effect
is, but someone recently asked me about the
health benefits and whatever on the water gun.
And I do have testimonials on this.
A strong water gun or well grounded with
good water flow can be used as a
temporary pain reducer.
Like if you have a bad toothache.
Right.
And it's two in the morning or, you
know, soreness or whatever.
Yeah.
I used to go out, you know, maybe
I could save the tooth and it hurts
real bad, you know, just now it's just
extracted.
But then it was like a turn on
the water gun, put my face about six
inches from it in 10 seconds.
The pain is gone.
Right.
And it stays gone for a while.
So, well, yeah, that's interesting.
I mean, I've seen a native person do
the thing with the stone, which is which
is interesting as well.
I think that's a magnetic consideration and it
does actually alleviate the pain temporarily as well.
Well, you have the if it concentrates the
ether.
Yeah.
It will result in a lower potential feeding
the ether.
If it disperses the ether, it results in
a higher potential.
It'll make a hole.
Right.
That's what the water does.
So, yeah.
Yeah.
I really don't know.
I just know if I how many times
I push this member, push this button, this
happens.
That's all I know.
Right.
It's not that bad.
But we do know we do know it
requires grounding water and layering.
Right.
So so just specifically message to that listener,
Joe, a little more information, maybe.
And we'll definitely readdress this question.
Thank you.
Specifically on tunneling.
I've heard your turn term is used often
and I don't know how he wants to
use it here.
OK, the tunneling term.
Fair enough.
So I've only got one more piece here
and it is could the Greek explain why
a 15 minute nap can recharge us when
dead tired?
Now, that could be an interesting question of
itself.
But what is it about this 15?
Because it's not like, you know, we're set
on a clock here.
Exactly.
But what about the short nap and the
fact because it seems to me like a
lot of what's done in sleep.
Yes, it's great to get, you know, a
good amount of sleep.
But a lot of that time may be
wasted because the process is all that's required
as opposed to the rest to reset certain
things.
That's my answer to that.
But you might have a better one as
far as why is he made?
Two reasons.
It's not as physical as it is mental.
Like if you really take a bonafide nap,
which means you're out like a light, you're
not conscious.
You might even go into a dream state.
Your consciousness pops in somewhere else.
It's being used somewhere else.
And what happens there and when you come
back is whether or not you are refreshed
or not.
Like, for example, lately, when I take a
15 minute nap, I come back and I'm
totally drained.
And the first thing that goes in my
mind, where the hell did they take me?
Right, right.
So for example, if you take a 15
minute nap and you go to another world
where you're getting a massage and you have
a semi athletic Latin call girl rubbing your
feet or whatever, you might come back refreshed,
right?
But if they send you in another world
where they give you a lightsaber and you
have to fight Darth Vader or whatever, you
come back and you're like, shit, now I
have sleep inertia.
I need two more hours, right?
Oh, yeah.
So the physical, the physical part.
Yeah, you know, if you don't sleep, what
is it about seven days, you can die.
It's even less than that more like four
or five.
Actually, I was on a meth trip once
for three days, I remember.
And anyway, I didn't even know what it
was.
I was at a party.
And these two guys, these guys, anyway, they
market NASCAR stuff.
I didn't know that it's like $13 billion
a year.
You know, a long time ago, it's amazing
how much money is in some things that
people don't think of much, you know, it's
like, well, that can't possibly make a lot
of money.
And there is a lot of money and
things like I'm amazed sometimes that exactly my
gosh, but I've seen that I've seen the
hats and the jackets, they're very expensive.
But anyway, so he they bought these two
mansions next to each other and combine them
and made one big complex and the strippers
here, everything closes at 2 a.m. So
they would go and hire everything closes at
2 a.m. I don't know where you
are.
They're like 2 a.m., 1 a.m.,
something like that.
Also, not like New York.
Yeah, no, anything other than like New York.
New York's a whole other experience.
But everywhere else in the country, two o
'clock in the morning is usually your dead
limit, no matter where you are.
Maybe Vegas.
Yeah, it was a deadline.
So so they would ferry these these sorry,
Vegas isn't.
Well, I'm sure there's lots of places, you
know, but not not I can even imagine.
Well, you know, in northern Europe, Stockholm and
Netherlands, you know, Germany.
But yeah, they have this thing.
So anyway, they put this.
Yes, I show up and I see these
half naked women walking everywhere and like, oh,
these are strippers we bring up here or
whatever.
So this guy comes through the door and
he opens his brown paper bag and he
starts handing stuff out.
Everybody's looking at it.
A little baggies is all.
Let's try it right now.
So he walks up to the bathroom vanity.
We're in one of the bedrooms.
You know, those big globe lights that they
have on bathroom vanities.
Oh, yeah.
You know, the big, like cosmetic lamp.
It's a light bulb.
It's just a big glass bulb with a
little filament, like twenty five watts or whatever.
It looks like a big round one, like
the big round balls they used to get
all the way around a mirror, like for
makeup mirrors and backstage, old, old backstage mirrors.
Yeah, exactly.
But a non non frosty one.
She unscrews a bulb.
I say, what the hell?
And he breaks off the stem, dumps the
stuff out, puts this pinkish colored powder in
there and lights it with a lighter.
And everybody's passing around inhaling it.
And I'm like, take some.
Like, what the hell is it?
Just take some.
Oh, yeah.
Right.
And I'm like, what the hell is this?
So it's like burnt plastic.
Right.
And I'm like, you guys are just out
of control, man.
You guys are.
This is, you know, whatever goes in.
And just people just kept coming over.
And I'm not going to mention.
Actually, no, I'm not going to mention who
was there.
And I usually do mention them.
Right.
Let's just say local politicians, children.
Boy.
Yeah.
Like senators, like senators, children.
So that's why I want to.
I think, by the way, this is getting
off years ago, back in twenty fifteen or
so.
I think when we stopped, Ocelli in the
Greek says, how are you doing?
This is I'm working with this woman.
She's a Korean businesswoman.
And she just left Hunter by the vice
president's house in Florida.
Hunter Biden.
He's a real nut job.
Yeah.
Twenty fifteen, twenty sixteen.
I do remember that.
And I remember thinking of you every time
the laptop was brought up, like I was
wondering, are you in any of those pictures?
Because you could have been there just around.
No, I was there.
But she she she went to go visit
to do some business stuff because you go
with water, believe it or not.
And he says, I don't care about this.
Come on, take your clothes off and do
this and do that.
And she came back shocked.
She's no, I don't bother with the vice
president.
So there's a total free.
I think I reason I'm bringing this up
on the side, because I remember discussing or
bringing it up to you.
Yeah.
The vice president's son.
And then later on, we see a 10.
What is it?
Ten years later or nine, eight, eight, nine
years later.
And I'm like, oh, I knew about that.
Yeah.
First, not first and second hand.
Yeah, it was like eight years.
That's why I cracked up when I first
started hearing about the laptop, because not every
picture in the laptop is him with a
crack pipe dressed in, you know, women's clothing.
There are some regular pictures of just people
coming in and out of his place and
stuff like that.
I mean, I'm not talking about the laptop
or whatever.
That's normal because people take pictures all the
time with these digital devices.
If it wasn't a laptop, it would have
been a scrapbook film for digital devices.
People used absolutely developed film and put it
in a scrapbook or that.
No, actually, they didn't even do that.
Sorry if they were smart.
Kind of content.
Yeah, they were right.
Yeah.
It's all full rights.
Because you don't want photo viewing what you're
shooting.
Right.
The thing was that it was a total
degenerate.
And I was trying to bring that across
that because I've seen it also the level
of degeneracy and the people are supposedly authorities
because they're not really authorities.
They're only authorities because they took advantage of
the credit system.
And yeah, it's really bad.
It's really bad.
You and I like a private communication started
talking about how the sons and daughters of
a lot of these people are like really
out there as like, you know, like tornadoes
of debauchery.
I think that was what I said, because
it's always been that way.
It's always been that way.
But we talked about, you know, you ever
see the drug problem.
Right.
You hear about drug problem recently or whatever.
And then you go back in the 60s.
Oh, they had a drug problem there.
Right.
Yeah.
In the 50s, they had a drug problem.
LSD was legal, by the way, when it
first when it was first put out, when
it passed the initial testing, it was legal
and prescribed right forms of LSD, lysergic acid
to housewife preferred to treat depression for a
short time.
I don't even think it was a year.
Well, everything goes.
Everything is until the government demands.
So it's everything is legal until the government
demands are cut.
I mean, cocaine and heroin were available for
sale right out in the open until what?
Sometime around the same time that they made
what alcohol legal.
Right.
I mean, it was almost the same time
period.
It's mixed mixed bag.
Remember that reefer madness propaganda movies, just like
they do propaganda movies that Arabs are terrorists
and all this other stuff.
But I'm talking cocaine was legal in 1901.
Cocaine was something you could buy.
Oh, in part.
Well, yeah, of course it was.
Well, it was Coca-Cola was famous.
It had it for a short time.
And people died from the issue of Coca
-Cola because, you know, it's a hell of
a drug, right?
Can't get enough of it.
Yeah, you really can't.
And the it was included in a pocket
theory, really.
There was a very big you could look
this up on morphine addiction in the eighteen
hundreds, the entire eighteen hundreds, especially after the
what you call the American Civil War, the
when all the insane asylums were built, were
built.
Oh, yeah.
The sanitarium, you know, massive sanitariums.
Yeah.
But here's the massive morphine addiction.
But it was so commonly sold.
And I brought this up to you many
times.
It was so commonly sold that products for
women were basically, you know, booze and morphine
in a bottle.
And it was there for what their period
cramps.
I mean, let's be blunt.
And that's what it was sold to them
as like this.
This is mama's little helper to make you
not feel so angry once a month.
I mean, yeah, everything before.
And before that, it was the opium.
Right.
You can go look at the opium wars
and all that other stuff.
And the opium goes all the way back
to Roman times because they had massive trade
with Asia and China.
Oh, yes.
And it's not really China.
It's Afghanistan.
And I think it could be grown in
Turkey.
It has to be a certain altitude and
a certain temperature.
Right.
That's why, you know, like, for example, the
coca plant has to be grown at high
altitude.
And when they were showing videos of the
war on drugs, burning the cocaine fields down
in Columbia on sea level, I was like,
that's all fake because you can only grow
the cocoa plant at three thousand or five
thousand feet and higher.
Right.
Just like when the covid stuff came out,
they were showing full hospitals.
And that was from some ferry boat accident
in Italy 15 years ago.
Right.
People on ventilators.
So, yeah, it's insane.
No one can make sense of anything.
If they keep people confused and afraid, they'll
never be able to use proper logic.
Right.
And I think that's I think it's getting
worse, sadly.
And opium was well beyond, oh, it's an
addictive problem.
And it got into it was actually weaponized
and brought to those populations in order to
decimate them, where they just kind of dumped
it in there.
It was really cheap.
And it is really your friends, you know,
from Great Britain that utilized it as a
weapon for, I don't know, five hundred years
easily.
It was just like it was just like
the health care here is now you had
to buy it when you're in Asia.
You had to buy it.
You had to buy a certain amount of
opium or you were taxed to pay the
taxes like now you either get the health
care or you pay five hundred dollars eight.
Right.
Which is eight.
Oh, my gosh.
I should it should be eight thousand if
you're that stupid to not know how to
get out of that.
But that's OK.
I mean, and look, I was never as
well as, you know, in the Bible says,
don't say that because you were like that,
too.
I was never, ever, ever fell for all
that authoritarian tax regulation stuff.
I always knew it was a what do
you call a ruse and a prank to
the ignorant and those that are easily fear
fearful because at a very young age, I've
had several older people say you better read
the U.S. Constitution because most of the
stuff that you discover as you get older
is unconstitutional.
Of course.
And all I had to hear was the
tax is unconstitutional.
And I always knew if I ever had
to get involved with those guys to bring
up the Constitution, they'll tell you that doesn't
apply here.
Well, then you don't apply here.
Right.
That's what do they call it when you
when you go against the government or the
authorities?
It's called it's there's a term for it.
I can't recall it right now.
Sedition, sedition.
Yeah.
But ultimately, when you start looking at how
they do it, it's because it's all trust
law.
Right.
But I didn't know it was eight hundred,
but it doesn't matter.
I actually I hope it goes up to
like ten thousand and really punish those that
believe in it, because that's how the Catholic
Church does the same same stuff.
Right.
They like the Catholic Church sells indulgences right
to go to heaven.
These credit people are.
Oh, my gosh, it's so ridiculous.
It's it's really bad.
You really got to think twice.
When I see people involved with like income
tax and all this other stuff and health
care and whatever, it makes me think twice.
It's like, are you that weak that going
along with it is easier?
I'm not saying fighting and getting out of
it.
Is it that are you that weak of
an individual, you know, or whatever you want
to call yourself to fall for that system?
And the answer is yes.
Most people, even today, I bet most of
our subs are subject to it and they
don't do anything about getting out of it.
Maybe we should do what depends on how
much response we get.
I'll just post the codes.
There's a few very simple codes.
All you got to do is state that
if you it's solely voluntary.
It's one of the CFRs.
Actually, I should bring it up and read
it.
It tells you that if you're an employee
having withholding and you don't want withholding anymore,
it's just simply make a sworn a statement
that has to be sworn.
It has to be without the United States.
I could show you that code, too.
There's statements with the United States and without
the United States.
And it's funny with the United States.
So you swear the penalty of perjury, but
without the United States is you swear under
penalty perjury according to the laws of the
United States of America.
That's without the United States.
Very interesting.
But all you got to do is make
a statement and give it to the employer.
And that's it.
And you give them about a week and
they have to stop pulling taxes out.
And of course, watch the sparks fly.
Right.
And well, ultimately, what happens if you do
it right, you just send a copy of
the IRS and the IRS will call the
employer and say, don't take any more taxes.
He did all the proper stuff.
It's funny when the accountants at the company
say, I never heard of that.
You have everybody has to pay taxes and
then they get a from the IRS telling
them to stop.
It's like what a wake up call.
Right.
Yeah.
It's really sad.
The condition that people are in just in
general, you know.
You know what?
I did have one more little thing.
And I wasn't sure if we've already gone
over this because it sounds familiar.
We may have covered this already, but let's
just double check.
A question for Chuck and Greek.
If humans have a line of credit, their
signature in parentheses that apply.
OK, OK.
It's prepaid upon birth, they're saying.
And would there be a financial incentive to
slaughter the actual person since governments get paid
in full up front and are looking to
do with that?
OK, I'm just has nothing to do.
I see.
But go ahead.
Go ahead and finish.
You know, I just want to give you
the whole thing.
Would there be a financial incentive to slaughter
children since governments get paid in full up
front and are looking to minimize expenditures by
removing them from existence?
Now, my first reaction to this is that
as you continue to, you know, gather so
-called expenses as you're going through, you're still
generating just by living.
You're generating more and more of this.
It doesn't work that way at all.
OK, my mother doesn't work that way in
slaughtering children or whatever.
The worst thing that I've seen happen.
Let me just put it this way out
of war.
The worst thing I've seen happen openly with
the credit system other than the financial crashes
like tarp and covid was that doge thing
with Elon Musk.
He just went in there and got all
the private QCIP numbers attached to Social Security
numbers to fund his campaign that he's working
on.
Right.
So that's that was like amazing because no
one knows how this system works.
And those that do or don't have platforms
to discuss or like us have 10 subs,
you know, whatever.
So no one's getting any information.
And and the people that are out there
talking about this, you know, the one guy
says one thing, the other one says another.
Yeah, the credit system works this way very
simply.
It's actually based on the Constitution.
The government was set up with certain tasks
besides military protection and and whatever is to
print print and coin money.
True.
Now, to put this in perspective, you can
objectify anything political, anything social by making a
list of how you are going to objectify
qualitatively and quantitatively.
I could say this surely, which by the
way, the coin was the worst president.
You're coining and minting money, by the way.
Guess what?
They don't actually do that.
They have the Federal Reserve to do that.
So quite honestly, they're not doing one of
the things they're supposed to do.
Reserve does.
Well, no, there's a print in minting office
that does it.
The Federal Reserve puts the control over it.
No, the government still prints everything and does
everything.
The Treasury checks.
The Federal Reserve is just the trustee.
Yeah, that's the worst president the United States
has ever had without a worst president.
The United States has ever had by a
long shot.
I mean, so clear it is FDR.  Why?
There's never been a parliamentary government monarchy dictator
in the history of mankind that has ever
told its population to surrender its gold.
You could find the worst government that ever
existed.
Even they never did anything as drastic as
that.
And the American people went for it.
Right.
That's how they set them up to do
that.
Right.
Does it matter?
That's why it's land of the slave freedom.
But even back then, we're better off now
than we were back then, by the way,
believe it or not.
Yeah, kind of by a long shot.
It's kind of amazing.
There's a is the worst.
Yeah, there's a there's a former college professor
just really quickly right now who, you know,
got himself retired from his prestigious position.
I'm not going to name him, but because
he started writing about and trying to explain
to people exactly point by point how FDR
was basically an American dictator who was at
war with the Constitution and the people of
the country completely all the way around with
the historical data they've collected.
And it's amazing that he's like a liberal
icon.
He started writing about this.
And all of a sudden, you know, he
no longer had a position in academia.
They even pulled his books, all kinds of
stuff.
But he's still writing it now.
He's still doing it.
But it's kind of amazing.
He's one of those guys who went, wait
a minute, I've been sort of lied to
here.
The only one that could have possibly overshadowed
him would have been Reagan by pushing the
button and launched a full on strike on
the Soviet Union with a full on retaliation
that would be possibly a runner up to
that.
You don't think Wilson was pretty bad?
Woodrow Wilson?
No, not at.
Well, no, not as bad as FDR. No,
not as bad as FDR, as bad as
FDR. He didn't ask.
He put the Federal Reserve in.
But here I'm not here.
I'm not against the Federal Reserve at all.
I'll explain.
OK, because.
OK, so the emergencies have now gone away.
They're never going to go back to substance
back money.
And so everything is in a trust.
That's why I in one of the Sonics,
a hundred Sonics ago, I said, go look
at that guy with the toupee, the congressman,
what he said on the floor in 1992.
What's his name?
Doesn't come to mind right now.
He's a funny congressman to pay.
But anyway, he talked about the United States
as the largest bankruptcy in world history.
Right.
So everything is done by trust.
Everything is done by trust.
Like, for example, if you go look at
the critical satire cartoons of the eighteen hundreds,
they have these big fat guys as railroad
trust, mining trust, oil trust, petroleum trust.
Everything is in a trust.
You call corporations whatever you want.
There always is always a trust and a
trustee relationship.
If you have one of those God forsaken
things known as a college diploma hanging on
the wall, go read it.
What does it say here by the trustees
of the university declare that this person has
enough credits to get a bachelor's degree or
whatever?
Everything is done by trust.
So this person bringing up whatever you know,
slaughtering children or whatever, that's nothing compared to
the overall thing about the trust.
Sixteenth Section 16 of the Federal Reserve Act
states that actually the Federal Reserve Bank in
general, it's more than one place, I believe,
using Federal Reserve notes, which is anything basically
checks, credit cards, low, whatever, whatever you want
to call it, cash money.
They're all constitute Federal Reserve notes is a
mortgage, a first lien mortgage on all persons
and property in the United States.
Right.
America.
That's everyone agrees to that.
No one's ever gone after that.
So but here's the here's the thing about
the credit thing, because they took your ability
to pay away.
They have to pay for everything for you.
But they can't let you know that because
it'll collapse the labor market.
Right.
No one will want to go to work
because everything's paid for.
So they have to do that.
Now, let me just give the positive side.
The Federal Reserve Act plainly states that if
anyone is applying for Federal Reserve notes like
member banks and associations, financial institutions, you guessed
it right.
If you have a license to go to
their window.
Right.
They they have to bring collateral and the
application is the collateral.
Whatever number is on the application, we're talking
about the application.
Right.
That produces the funds.
So give me an example.
Let's say you're going to go buy a
car for, let's say, 50 K.
You apply for it.
They go get the 50 K from the
application and then you do what's called a
purchase and sale agreement.
Right.
And then they go get another 50 K
and then you do maybe a buyer seller
agreement and they go get another 50 K.
So you've created one hundred and fifty thousand
dollars.
And then they task you is they give
you the car and say you have to
pay it all back plus interest.
So now another 50 K.
Right.
So this is how they get super.
That's why when you look at any bank
statement, like look at a new bank, they
start out with like 40 million in assets.
The next year, it's like almost a billion.
How?
Because all they have to do is deny
people.
Right.
So when you apply, let's say, Chuck, you
and I get an office and we're a
bank and we tell people, why don't you
come in and apply for a hundred thousand
dollar loan?
And we get 10 people come in to
apply and we tell them because of your
credit report, we're denying you.
They believe that we get the 10 people's
hundred thousand.
We get a million dollars a day.
We get to keep it.
We get to keep the million dollars.
No people walk away.
They don't give us a fight because they've
been trained that the credit report means something,
which is a bunch of mom and pop
businesses that were started in the 70s to
do that.
There's no legal bearing on it.
It's actually slander because everything on a credit
report is is paid for, by the way.
It's just they tell you that it's not
you didn't you didn't perform as agreed, meaning
to pay it again, repay it.
Right.
So anyway, all these applications are adding up
and they're not being put on the market.
They're being held as to leverage other things,
fortunately, because if the applications that everyone's been
denied for, I think right now, 48 percent
of all mortgage applications are being denied.
So go look and go look at Wells.
This is just Wells Fargo.
Yeah.
So go look at Wells Fargo balance sheet
when they started denying the applications and where
they are now.
You can see huge earnings and no one's.
This is all very much.
This is like, what would you say?
Eighth grade math.
So the simple multiplication is what?
Eighth grade or sixth grade?
Probably sixth grade math.
Sixth grade multiplication.
It's lower than that.
I remember math.
No.
Yeah.
I was taught my multiplication table, say, in
the second or third grade.
And I wasn't even second or third grade.
I wasn't even in a good school.
So, yeah, go ahead.
So when I yes, fourth grade for me
is probably college level now anyway, but or
high school.
But let's say that kind of math.
That's how stupid the population is across the
board.
They can't go see.
You can actually do historic thing.
One charts of denials.
When did the denials for wealth to pick
one bank?
So let's say it's March of 2023.
They start denying most people.
Go look at what the bank had in
reserves or in an account in 2023 and
watch it grow as they're denying applications.
Yeah.
OK, so this is how the credit system
works.
It's all your.
So, by the way, it's all yours, but
it's abandoned.
You're abandoning it.
So what I mean by that is if
you went all those applications that were denied
and they're used as an asset to leverage
for Wells Fargo, if you look at their
paperwork, it's your name that's on there.
It's your name.
It's your property.
It's kind of like if you drop something
that has your name engraved on it and
someone finds it and you say, well, that's
my my name's on it.
You show that it's your name.
It is no question.
Oh, we're going to give it to somebody
else anyway.
You know, kind of a scam that would
be.
So no one is looking at this.
The biggest scam, the biggest scam going on
still because it's an oxymoron is university or
college.
When you apply to the college, the college
gets full tuition from your application.
And then they say, are you going to
get a loan or are you going to
buy?
You're going to pay for your tuition.
So they get paid again, again.
So the biggest scam for whatever people think
it is, you didn't learn anything.
Anyone who's gone to college and is honest
with themselves knows they didn't learn anything.
They're really worthwhile at all.
You couldn't get like, who was it?
Goodwill, Walker, whatever.
A couple of late fees at the library.
Right.
So you're being scammed on a level right
now still.
And by the way, since my early, early
days on Revolution Radio in 2009, 2010 with
Seth Michael and these three, four hour conversations
I would have through the middle of the
night on the weekend, I kept telling, they
kept talking about finance, this finance.
Have you ever filled that?
So do you know that all that funds
are first produced through your application?
And they're like, huh?
And I've been saying this for so long.
It's so tiring.
And then finally, recently, more people have been
speaking on it.
And I'm like, oh my gosh, it took
like 20 years to get people to just
start doing not because of me, but I'm
like, I just gave up.
I was like, what are you discussing credit
reports for?
Your application paid for everything.
So the credit thing is is the Federal
Reserve, believe it or not, is the friendliest
thing that has ever happened.
Even even it's on the level with the
Constitution, by the way, like the Ninth Amendment.
Everyone talks about First Amendment, Second Amendment, Fifth
Amendment.
The Ninth Amendment is the best one, because
that basically states paraphrasing here that no right
shall be a bridge that anyone has right
now, no matter what it is, like no
matter what you're doing that you consider a
right, it can be you should defend it.
It's defendable.
You should be left.
Right.
It's not specific.
It's it's not like the second is arms
or safe.
There's incrimination.
And that's like anything that you're doing right
now that you think is a right you're
able to do.
Oh, my gosh.
The Ninth Amendment is the one you should.
Everyone should be looking at and using.
And the second thing is the Federal Reserve
Act, which says when an institution or a
bank comes to get Federal Reserve notes, which
is basically money on account, because that's how
you know when you have Federal Reserve notes,
it could be it's credit on your account.
Right.
You can withdraw from it, write checks off
of it, whatever.
OK, they the Federal Reserve needs collateral and
the application serves as collateral.
Right.
And if you read it at the bottom,
it even says that if you need more,
you could come more and add more to
that application.
Now, when do you think companies show up
in town's job fair and they get what's
going on, for example, with these job fairs?
You know, these businesses, these young idiots to
apply, they don't hire anyone.
They walk away with applications.
And for the full salaries the company keeps,
that's how they fund the company, that's how
Raytheon funds itself, not through government contracts and
all that stuff or whatever.
And then the Federal Reserve Act allows that
a year later, they could come back with
that on that same application and pull another
million or two million out for you.
And the whole time it's under your name
and you have people walking around wondering how
the credit system works.
No, the two best things that ever happened
in American jurisprudence are the Ninth Amendment and
the Federal Reserve Act, Section 16, without a
doubt.