The sonic event 117, 117, yep, that's where we're at.
Greek, how are you feeling this evening?
Okay, I got about 20 minutes or so.
Let's see if the voice holds up.
Excellent.
Well, I sure hope it does.
Look, a lot of things need to be repeated, okay, because we're in a world of repetition,
which by the way, I want to ask you about that.
Anybody will tell you that, you know, in order to retrain people, in order to educate somebody,
in order to teach somebody something, there's always a certain amount of repetition.
I've noted that there are people who do see things, hear things once and can retain them
perfectly, but that's not the majority.
What are your thoughts on that?
I have a lot of thoughts on that, but not just that.
It's not just that.
It ties into a lot of other things, like, you know, we've gone through previous discussions,
not everyone that looks human is human in a standard way, right?
Humans are very non-standard.
There is no human type.
You can say this is human.
There's a lot of downgrading, major downgrading.
It's been going on, let's say, for the past 1,500 years, and then you have the genetic
pools.
Recently, I saw a woman that looks, Asian woman.
She has some very old genetics that you won't see.
You'll only see on 300-year-old wood print blocks from Japan.
Very stark, right?
So you'll see these genetics.
I've been around Illuminati-type parties, I know a wealthy, very wealthy guy, a trustafarian.
For three generations of living off the same industrial money, and he introduced me to
some people on the Upper East Side.
These were very unusual, and he was very scared if anybody, don't talk to them, you know, or
if I did start a conversation, or they had a conversation with me, the person who introduced
me, I was very nervous.
What did he say?
Did he say anything, you know, whatever?
And they had, like, perfect genetics, perfectly symmetrical faces, perfect skin, they had
a mannerism about them.
So what I'm trying to say is when you, by the way, I'm not young and beautiful anymore,
but back then, I think her name was Angelica or something, she was a daughter of a baroness.
These are the kind of people that, anyway, she says, we like you because you're smart
and good-looking.
It turns out, like, you know, they invite people that are good-looking to entertain
the party, and these models, you know, I don't know if you ever talk to any models, not too
much upstairs, not because, you know, models, it's like blonde jokes, right?
Then you got the smart, geeky types that don't look good.
So when you have a combination of looks and smarts, you're very entertaining to them,
like a good circus pet, a well-groomed circus bear, I always give the circus bear analogy,
right?
Yeah, I got you.
Okay, so when you ask about memory, who has memory, and you can't just say some people
do and others don't, because I've been around superior human, you know, in other words,
where their gene pools are maintained at a superior level, you know, like, what do you
call it when you have, when you don't just breed with anybody, you control the breed,
the stock, right?
You come from this stock and you breed, you know, it's like racehorses or whatever, right?
Well, it's animal husbandry, I think they call that, don't they?
Yeah, yeah, they practice that, and, you know, if you've heard of the problems before where
they intermarry a little too much, they get really bad feet, and they sometimes are born
with Down syndrome and things like that.
Down syndrome is more of a chemical thing, alcohol, but, you know, they get severe foot
problems and other things.
But you start twisting the branches of the family tree a little too closely together,
and sometimes you got some bad results.
No, that's true.
And I gotta say, there is a difference in beauty, right?
Back when I was, you know, there was a time, Greek, believe it or not, I was younger, and
mine wasn't maybe beautiful, but I was a lot better looking.
And I dated one of the cheerleaders for one of the professional football teams, now that's
a grade level above the average local beauty, right?
Usually, yeah.
Yeah, usually.
But it's not necessarily the professional.
But now it could be a guy, who knows, right?
Yeah, now you don't know what the hell you're getting.
They gotta let guys on there, don't they?
Okay, or, wait a minute, excuse me, let's be correct.
We have to let people or humans on there, and we don't get to ask about what their gender
is.
Oh, no fags and no lesbians, oh my gosh.
No dykes and no fags, oh shit.
Remember those days?
Well, at least dykes and fags.
If someone looked at you the wrong way, he's a fag, right, or whatever, or she's a dyke.
But anyway, yeah, no, this is all, look, the same people that make the conservative movement
make this stuff too, right?
It's a pig farm.
Let me just interject.
Sure.
When I say, I call people little piggies when I'm out in public, and I say, is this what
all the little piggies are into now?
You're like from out of store and something's fashionable, you know?
Right.
Now, the thing is, if you're listening, most likely you're not one of these little piggies.
But to presume that you're not on a pig farm is a big mistake.
You are on a pig farm.
But you could be a wild pig, right?
You could be a more feral sort of, you know, a pig in more of its natural environment.
Right, and they, by the way, pigs have their reputation in captivity, and I think I've
mentioned this before.
They're fairly clean.
Actually, they're pretty clean when they're in the wild because they're constantly moving,
just like sharks, you know, and tuna.
Right.
They're constantly moving.
So they piss and shit on the go, and that's why they're always pretty clean.
They get a reputation of being as they are when they're in captivity.
So humans in captivity probably suffer similar traits.
Well, that's what I was just about to bring up, is that, you know, if you realize that,
you know, maybe we are all little piggies in one way or another, those of us-
Speak for yourself.
I like to avoid this swine category.
Well, but those of- I know you do, because you're not what you eat, or maybe you are,
but you know, and therefore there's no fork on your fork, so you couldn't be pork.
Well, you'd be what you ate, yeah.
You'd be what you ate.
But the thing is, it-
Oh, speaking of which, you sent me a thing about the category of calories in food recently,
a link, right?
Was it-
I wanted to give you-
Ooh, Smith Peters or whatever?
Yeah, I wanted to give you a laugh as we hear from- Is that Ivan in the background, by the
way?
No, no, it's another one.
Oh, okay.
Callie.
She's a calico.
Calico.
Callie.
She's casual.
We have a colony of- It's called Colony 9.
We have 10 cats.
But they're not indoor.
We tell people, you know, it's like the crazy person starter kit, crazy cat person starter
kit.
That's the professional kit, right?
The 10?
Yeah.
But they're outdoor, you know?
But they're free to come in and out.
We have a doggy door that they use, and when the weather is pleasant, you don't see them
around at all, just for feeding.
Even feeding times, they come in one by one.
But yeah, cats are people, too, and I tell people, be wary of cats, because I've noticed
several things about them on a mental level that there's a good chance that they're here
to monitor us, by the way.
Anyway, that's another discussion.
Well, I wondered that about dogs, but then again, I'm more of a dog person, so I didn't
No, dogs are too pathetic.
Dogs can be very pathetic at times.
But I love them.
No, no, no, but cats never are pathetic.
But dogs get pathetic, and I mean, I love dogs as well, but no, it's on a different
level.
So I'd say, yeah, back just to sum up things, yeah, let's not even get into the calories.
We've talked about that.
My answer to you was, yeah, it's all the Greek-speak stuff pans out somewhere, right?
You'll find what I'm saying is, this time.
I sent that to you to hope that you would get a lap out of it, actually, because I wanted
to show you where they were giving this big credit to somebody creating the idea of calories
and making it so much better for everyone's health back in 1918.
No, it's invalid, because unless you're pooping charcoal.
Yeah, no, absolutely, and we've gone over this.
It's invalid.
It doesn't even approximate what's going on with health.
I just thought it was comical, that Smithsonian, that institution.
It's all quackery.
You know, I think I've mentioned, I have a plot of all the doctor's offices and hospitals,
and I have earplugs, because if I don't put the earplugs in while I'm driving by, the
quacking is so loud, my ears ring for about a week.
Well, I used to love when you told me, you'd ask doctors, can I purchase one of these machines
somewhere?
I'm going to start a museum.
Oh, one of the pharmacies, yeah.
I'd ask them, where do I get one of these blood pressure machines?
You know, like, I don't know where you rent them, and I said, why?
They always ask me why I want one, because I'm opening a museum of medical fakery and
quackery, and this is going to be one of the prime exhibits.
Right.
And none of them says, yeah, get out of here, you're crazy.
They're all like, wow.
Sometimes when you get them at the end of their shift, if you're at the top of the hour,
sometimes they change shifts, and they followed me, and they're like, why did you say that?
I'm like, oh my gosh, I'll tell you the whole thing right now if you've got time.
Well, you've got to do that and display drills where they would drill holes in people's heads.
By the way, have you ever read the contract?
You know, people get chemotherapy, they put you on a schedule, you go every two weeks
or whatever.
Yeah, I've seen that.
Right?
You know, it's like every time you go, you have to sign this thing, it's like 15 pages
long.
You ever read that?
No, I haven't personally, no.
Oh my gosh.
It tells you basically that it's all experimental, we could inject you with toilet water from
Chernobyl, and you're doing this all on your own behest, even though there's no proof that
it works.
You remember?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh my gosh.
So it's similar to the forms they made me sign when they were experimenting on my eyes
when I was a kid then, because that did happen.
Yeah, it's all quackery.
Because there's a whole thing about, look, we don't know if this will work, if it does.
We agree to give you this stuff even, if you like, I mean, because I was a test subject.
Okay, look, it's not like the people I was talking about before, they completely despise
the public.
And you know what?
I do too in many ways.
And they would love to just eliminate any medical care, but what would happen if they
made any medical care illegal, well, it would sound too unreasonable because other places
would not.
And it would sound too unreasonable, and also it would foster a black market or people doing
it on their own.
That's true.
Yeah, and that would not make it inferior.
That would actually make it far superior.
And they don't want that.
So I said, let's maintain control of the medical.
Which is, by the way, the same reasoning by which big pharma exists in order to supply
people with drugs, because here's the problem.
If we did not have a drug industry to do that, guess what?
We'd have pharmaceuticals that really work.
Yeah.
People would figure out the real way and get the good drugs.
That's right.
So it's all a distraction.
And, you know, and but they do have, you know, they still have procedures like micro surgeries.
Right.
You know, years ago, I remember when I was young, that technology was just coming around
that if your finger was lopped off or you lost an appendage, you put it in a brown paper
bagging it to the hospital.
Chances are they could sew it back on.
That was going on when I was a child.
Right.
Yes.
Where before the people older than me, when I was a child, they didn't have such a recommendation
or a possibility.
Well, when I was four years old, I severed my pinky down to just about the skin being
the only thing it was hanging from.
And in the past, before the 70s, that would have just been a dead, dead finger.
They would have just.
Well, sorry, that's gone.
But they say.
So they do offer.
So it's a mixed bag.
It's a really mixed bag of offering some things that are fairly valuable, more in the trauma
situation.
But even then, I've been in several trauma situations and they just have people sit there
where if they just applied an immediate within the first 15 minutes, something they would
recover much quicker.
I've gone into ICU intensive care unit and did therapy.
They let me do therapy on someone and they went home the next day.
They went home from ICU, which is unheard of.
And the head of the medical there was like, I need you here.
And I said, are you kidding?
And he's a famous here in Tucson.
Easy.
Remember when the congresswoman and the judge got shot and oh, yeah, Obama came to Tucson
and did the speech.
Well, the surgeon, the chief surgeon also did a speech.
He was hanging out with Obama.
That guy says, I need you here in the trauma center.
And I said, I'm not a doctor.
He says, oh, don't worry about that.
So, you know, you could take it two ways.
One is the guy would pull strings and have me, you know, give me a fake degree, but they're
all in a way or he'd get a little deeper and says, let's get rid of this guy because we
got one of these guys.
Right.
So the whole thing, I want nothing to do.
You know, I've said before, if everybody wants together and make paradise on earth to let
them have it, I want nothing to do with it.
If they want to get together and start killing each other, let them have it.
I want nothing to do with it either.
So you just got to do.
That's why I said the last time on Greek speak, you know, what got you here to Greek speak
ain't going to get you there.
In other words, if you're hearing stuff, whatever, you got to do it.
This is a very, how do you say, pragmatic DIY is you got to do it.
You know, just like the fellow recently, I think I mentioned he asked for pictures.
You know, he said, you know, I find I heard you a while back talk about use black shoe
polish on the car.
And he sent me pictures.
I was like, God damn, that car is bright.
I mean, it was black, but like deep black.
I was like, yeah, that's that's shoe polish.
You should get that.
Well, only with shoe polish sounds ghetto.
But yeah.
So yeah, what got you here ain't going to get you there with Greek speak.
In other words, you got to do it.
That's why if I had my druthers, if you're not like a tinkerer or an inventor or, you
know, into doing and making stuff, you don't really don't belong in a Greek speak thing.
You know, you got to get unless, hey, unless I'm a good circus bear and entertain you,
because I've got so much stuff that you can make your life better with.
But you got to do it.
Like, you know, 99 percent of the stuff I talk about, you can't go down to the store
and get it.
Right.
But you can go down to the store and buy the stuff to make it.
Well, very much like, you know, the the the silver.
Right.
Oh, my goodness.
What is that?
Aqueous Argentum.
I believe.
Because it's not colloidal silver.
You know, there's no silver in the solution.
And it works better than when you do have silver because of the reasons we've discussed.
So because of water, because of the water.
So which, by the way, that was one of the most innovative things about when they saved
my finger that I remember again.
I was four years old.
Right.
That is.
Well, no, not the silver.
I see.
I don't I didn't get that detail, but their use of fluids and very minimal.
But people would think, oh, there must have been all sorts of extensive stitching.
And no, that's exactly how you just pull something together.
That's not a medical story.
It is a very recent thing.
Yeah.
So but no, they're going away from that, by the way, more and more.
And matter of fact, if you take a look, it's more like people are using glue and indeed
you're better off sometimes using crazy glue than you are going through the issue of stitching.
Yeah.
The acryl cyanide stuff.
There's a variety.
There's an organic acryl cyanide that you can get.
Oh, no, there's better things.
But what I'm saying, what's easily readily available in a pinch is definitely, you know,
your various varieties.
Yeah.
One of the things about Greek speak is, you know, it's about the biological vacuum, right?
So when you get a cut, the body knows it's the body and the brain.
It's like, oh, I'm cut.
It says we're losing vacuum full.
Right.
So you've got to create the environment.
And prevent the things that usually happen when you don't.
But again, we got a message a while back where someone had a sore and that, you know,
sore that developed for the body to expel something.
Yeah.
By the way, I want to bring this up because I do recommend using ginger compresses when
the body wants to expel something.
Ginger.
Yeah.
Warm ginger.
What you do is you slice or grate the ginger and put it in very hot water or in a pot.
But don't let it even just barely come to a simmer or bring the water to a simmer slight
and then turn it off and then put the ginger in.
So in other words, 140 degree water.
OK.
And you wrap a cloth like you do a compress.
Or you could put the slight ginger slices over the area.
Now, it'll pull something to the surf.
Something wants to come to the surface.
It'll make it come to the surface 10 times faster.
Now, if you put ginger, it could also be dangerous.
If you put ginger.
Let's say you've got a sore on your arm or a sore on your leg.
Left arm, left leg, whichever.
And you think that something wants to come out of your body.
An abscess, a boil, something.
Yeah.
A rash.
If you apply the ginger compress or the thin ginger slices and wrap it.
And within 15 minutes, you see the location of where the sore is or the area that you're addressing.
Towards your heart.
That area will start swelling and hurting.
Remove the ginger and apply cold water.
Don't do it again.
OK, let's say you have a sore on your on your shin, on your left leg, midpoint from your ankle to your knee.
Give a visual.
And if you put ginger on it and you start seeing the part of the skin, the shin between the sore and your knee swell up and going higher because it's towards your heart.
Right.
It's going toward your heart.
Yeah.
That means that your body's rejecting it.
And it's like, no fool, that's that's not what we need.
But we're not sensitive enough to understand when or what you know, when to apply the ginger or not.
The only thing I would say is, you know, it will draw things to the surface.
But if you do see that swelling within the first five, 10, 15 minutes, that means that ginger is not a viable remedy for that condition.
Now, if you do have a sore, a boil, whatever, and you want to draw it to the surface and you apply it and that condition does not happen, a very dark, you know, very red swelling area.
And it's funny how it always moves towards the heart.
Right.
It is a viable solution if you don't get that swelling.
Now, the reason I'm saying this, there are people that read about ginger compresses and things and they do get that red swelling and whatever.
And they're like, oh, that's just detoxing.
Right.
They keep doing it and they end up with a pretty bad infection, which is not the body just trying to release something.
But now it's creating an infection, which means, you know, more systems are breaking down.
So I just want to give that warning also because there's a whole you know, here's the thing.
If I get myself together enough, I could sit down and do eight hours worth of sonics on remedies and applications.
But we'd have to go categorically.
This is what you do for liver.
This is what you do for eyes.
This is what you do for skin.
This is what you do for this condition.
You know, it's really hard to bring up, you know, what I've discovered since the early 80s and been working on in just casual sonics that we do, unless we do one specifically on remedies.
Right.
Which kind of talked about it before, but it's such a broad topic.
It's like Greek do a sonic on remedies.
Remedies for what?
So many parts of the body and so many conditions to address.
I mean, it's like eight hours just to outline.
Well, right.
But aside from that eight hours, I was trying to think if there was a way that you could condense it into like, you know, here is a Greek speak first aid kit, real first aid kit of sorts.
You know, yeah, we've done it in little pieces.
But the thing we have done down is really, you know, like you said, you are what you eat.
You are what you ate.
Yes.
I did give the natural approach, which is whole grains and greens.
And the greens would be the cabbage, lettuce, broccoli variety.
Those are all cabbage, by the way.
Broccoli is a variety of cabbage.
And then you have the chards and other things.
When you get to spinach and mustard, those get kind of intense and they could actually throw you off balance.
Whole grains would be any whole grain.
You pick it.
It's fine.
But each one has a different quality, like barley as a wet quality.
Oats have a wet quality.
And buckwheat and millet are drying and rice is in the middle.
Well, and at all times, you should try to get stuff that is grown locally to you because.
Yeah, you could.
But let me just say this.
When I say, let's say barley and oats have a wet quality.
What do I mean by that?
Well, yeah, they actually when you cook them, they require quite a bit of water.
They hold quite a bit of water.
You ever heard of people get a condition called bloating when they eat certain things?
They look fat.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
OK, so if you have a bloat, if your tendency to bloat, put on weight real fast, you eat oats and barley.
Boy, oh, boy, are you going to blow up?
Now, let's say you're of a tendency to bloat and you want to slim down, do buckwheat or brown rice or millet.
And that will contract you.
Right.
So they're very drying.
You see.
So you have that aspect as well.
But you have to understand the category also.
Let's say you run into a grain that you've never that's not categorized something new that you have to know how to.
See what kind of a grain it is.
You know, so if you look at buckwheat and millet, it's very small.
Where oats and barley is very large, more yin.
Right.
You see, for me, I'm not familiar with millet, to be honest with you.
Very, very small.
Oh, by the way, here's something that worked.
People have decided someone just had a baby.
You know, when someone tells me they're going to have a baby, I'm like, what do you think?
You're breeding the next Messiah.
How dare you make more children?
That's you know, here's the thing.
The way you change the system is everybody gets.
We're not having any more babies.
It's like the pigs on the pig farm saying we're not going to breed anymore.
What do you think?
Pig farmers get really nervous.
Right.
So because you're being commoditized, you are the commodity.
So if you say publicly we're doing a baby boycott, they'll say, what do you want?
What do you want?
You know, I'm serious.
This is very simple.
But basically with the babies and all that, they get earaches because most parents don't know how to feed their children.
Right.
They give them a variety of what they're eating.
So they get these terrible earaches, ear infections.
Right.
A really good remedy for an ear infection in most cases, which typically happens when the weather is getting cold.
Figure that is you roast some millet in a pan.
And while while you're roasting it, it gets hot to the point where you could smell the millet oil, that grainy, you know, like the fresh popcorn popping.
Right.
Yeah.
Smell and immediately you funnel it into a cotton sock or blend.
It's really hard to get cotton socks and to tie it off and put that hot millet roasted millet that's in a sock or a towel over the ear, you know, and lay down at least 20 minutes or so and repeat that a few times.
And then your infection goes away.
Something about the millet, the hot roasted millet oil, that seems to be a fantastic remedy for those kind of sinus canal.
When I said ear infection, you know, that's all sinus, right?
Well, this would also work for a sinus type situation.
Absolutely true. But, you know, I want to caution people about something, and that is that too often it became so commonplace to say ear infection.
There's an earache with babies because they couldn't speak exactly.
They could communicate, but they are not speaking.
It's misdiagnosed, you're saying.
Yeah, it's quite often misdiagnosed.
I discovered that.
Yeah, sinuses most likely. It's because the body's losing vacuum again due to the intake.
Yeah.
Or conditions.
You just balance a few things out. Now, I don't know about millet. I never knew about that.
Yeah, I think we talked about it a few years back with, what's the little guy?
You got there, you had something like that. I suggested the millet.
Yeah, well, the thing is.
Frankie, right. I got a hold of a couple of things.
But the thing is, again, you must first evaluate the situation properly, okay?
And with babies.
Well, here's the thing.
Yeah.
You don't just evaluate the victim or the patient. You have to evaluate the entire environment.
So that's what I never liked about child's not feeling well, and they take the child to the doctor, right?
Because there's a doctor at the office.
Yeah.
You have to look at the environment also.
Which, by the way, you know you're dealing with a quack right away if they don't ask what the kid has been eating,
where the kid is staying, what the condition of the room is.
He's a state license.
Thank you. You represent the best education government has to offer, right?
Yep. You're wonderful, and you're all great, and bye.
Speaking of which, I still interact with medical people.
Recently, I spoke to someone. She wants a scalerator.
I'm not shy about it.
I'm not offering any of my services to people in the legal field or medical field just as a personal boycott.
But that'll hurt me not then.
But if I get a million people to do it, then we get something to do.
But what I was talking about quackery, and she had no bones about that it is quackery,
and we talked about blood tests are quackery.
She goes, oh, yeah, blood tests are absolute quackery, and they require that, by the way.
Now, you go, we're going to do a blood test.
And I said, yeah, there's so many ways that it's quackery.
She just says, you know, when they go in in the morning at the lab,
they have to calibrate those blood test machines.
You know how they do it?
I'm like, no, I never heard of that.
She goes that the technicians use their own blood to calibrate each machine.
Okay, so here you got this, like, you know, fat, pimply, 23-year-old girl on birth control pills.
Her blood.
And then you got this other guy.
He's 42 years old, smokes a pack a day.
They use his blood on that machine.
Right?
I'm talking about, you know, I gave these discrepancies.
They don't sound very good.
Just to show you, there's a huge discrepancy in blood quality.
And they could be in the same medical park, by the way.
And they calibrate the machines randomly around.
It's such a fraud.
And it's amazing.
I like bringing this up.
You know, some people, oh, bring it, there might be a friend they work with.
I'm doing it to actually get them to confess.
And no one has been.
Once or twice, I run into someone that defends the system,
like a Freemason would defend the Brotherhood or whatever, the fraternity.
Not often, but they usually give up quite a bunch of stuff
that you would only know that if you were there.
And I appreciate that.
And of course, you know,
if we're doing Sonics,
I'm going to jump on here and mention it.
Absolutely.