Sonic event 70 or 70 as they say anyway rated why and here we are why because we love you
we've been doing this yeah we've been doing it that many times it's not how long it's
that many times you notice yeah it's like the counting it's like 70 times Wow okay
that's fine yeah all right we've almost eclipsed the amount of times that we got together to
do the other O and G incarnations I think that was less about 60 or 50 maybe oh about
two hours I know there's 40 hours of that yeah exactly 40.00 but yeah no it's it's we're
still going and people are still interested which is interesting the thing that I find
most interesting is you know well if you pull back and listen to what we talk about it's
not being talked about anywhere else in that in that scheme it's I don't know what's going
on by the way I mean I do know what's going on I'm dealing more and more with the public
and not like retail like a convenience store or shoe store or selling cars but with the
other things and I think people are going insane like when someone opens the door and
I meet them for the first time it's like this person is insane in other words what I mean
by that is the way you would cast an insane person looking like in a film right right
it's like look at those eyes look at that facial expression look at the way they speak
look at the way they walk look at their body gesture it's like this is not good you know
so I just wanted to put that out because I've been feeling that sentiment now for a few days
maybe a few weeks even and in other words when I meet people they look just like you
would cast someone that was insane how would you have them look right how would pick a
director right any director how would the director ask makeup set and crew says this
character is written in the script to be a nut job how would you have them look how would
you have them answer a door how would you have them greet you right anybody except Stanley
Kubrick leave him out of the equation okay that gets more intense yeah it does here's
the fun part about this is that I feel like you have now finally experienced what I've
been trying to tell you for the past few years which is funny because I keep saying it like
this nobody knows how to communicate I listen to conversations but that to me that to me
is representative of insanity where it's like look yeah I want to I want to I want to get
into that it's also hold that go ahead but I could just right here in the midst of this I can
just go Greek you know I like waffles with with cheese that's not what I'm talking about I'm
talking about how you would cast the way they look yeah but gesture but I'm saying I hear this in a
sonic way I'm hearing this insanity where it's like somebody goes well waffles and cheese well
that's okay because I've dunked my hand in a pot of gold no I'm saying a little different if you
were to read let's say the screenplay of what they say it seems very normal and very appropriate
but the way they say it the way they look in the way they gesture is definitely a crazy so you're
hearing sane dialogue but I'm hearing dialogue but yeah it's presented in a package that just
ain't right okay okay well at all and I'm talking about the majority of the people that are it's
not like crazy for you okay the other difference between okay when you're poor you're crazy when
you're rich you're eccentric right now the difference screen you know crazy it's what
it's how much how much money you got this is just not well spiritually psychology at all and this is
going more and more and more I'm seeing it and it's like whoa and you know it's good you know
it's good to voice these things so when anyone else picks up on this they have a little more
confirmation not that it's something that should be confirmed because you always want to be open
you know here's the thing judgment when doing observations though it is a sound bit of
reasoning to find confirmation which is not directly connected to something that's influenced
by you if you're making an observation though yes or no yes but it is more on a same sober
judgment okay judgment when people hear that word they think of it's like people that are
hypocritical maybe narcissistic or it's a spiritual religious thing right but the first
judgment that one must exercise is the mechanical judgment because you're in the material world
right no matter what you believe it is it hurts if you get cut or broken up or you know you're in the
material world you get hungry you get tired okay so the all judgments initial judges must be
mechanical material based that's why it's very important when people are scrutinized that you
always keep your clothes clean and pressed you have a clean car clean house so right you see I
mean keep the material stuff looking right so it's always I'm speaking from a material standpoint
okay now I said hold the thought on the communication because this is a I want to
give a few analogs about communication because one could bring up the subject there is no
communication and then pass over it but let me let's just do a little Greek speak analysis on
this because this is going to be helpful okay well please because the difficulty is always in
finding that which is empirical as opposed to that which is a subjective judgment you know
ephemeral but here let's let's just let's okay let's go down this road with communication sure
okay all right so you know this is the concept of a two-way street you know the concept of right
back foot forward on the same vein let's say okay so one way to judge communication there's
two ways you can figure out if someone communicates two ways from the positive and from the negative
without being antagonistic what I mean by this is let's say you just meet someone you barely have a
conversation and you bring up a concept that is well structured and simple but they don't understand
it and let's say we go a little further let's say you bring up something mathematical or technical
they don't understand it right they they don't get it okay it's a two-way street the reason why
people don't get it is because they can't communicate so you could actually find out
if someone is a good communicator by them getting and grasping ideas because if you can communicate
well which means structure mechanical meaning the sounds and the thoughts and you know how the
information relates to another being you will also the antithesis the opposite is true you will
also be able to comprehend more so people communicate have a hard time grasping also
it's a two-way street receiving okay right staying on that though that that's where I was
gonna go next is that here's the thing that you sort of jumped past and I want you to address it
is that look it doesn't matter you could have the greatest information and you could communicate it
perfectly but you must also have a receptor okay so here's the thing a radio so let me let me just
jump in real quick if there is it's receiving equally as broadcasting so if the people are
not receiving it right guess what they can't communicate so the better the communicate the
better communication skills the person has the better receptive skills learning skills acquiring
new knowledge is because it's the same thing it's along the same vein it's antagonistic yes
meaning when someone's trying to explain something and they're not a good communicator and they don't
really have a firm grip on what they want to explain it ain't gonna come out right no one's
gonna understand what they're saying right okay that person that is not a good communicator just
have difficulty communicating also has a problem receiving and typically leaving us it we call them
stupid or dumb or slow or whatever whatever and it's not it's not because we all have the same
abilities we all have it's just like you know the computer warehouse analogy I gave if you go
to a computer it's got one terabyte of hard disk and this amount of ram and all the same guess what
guess what's wrong computer quote unquote is smarter none of them they're all equal so what
I'm trying to say is that we all have the same hardware we all you know everyone can memorize
all the books ever written believe it or not we have no mental limit right so what's going on
is the communication faculty so here's the thing if you blur up the communication factor faculty
the broadcasting without even it's very efficient in other words what I'm trying to say if you could
mess up someone's ability to communicate thoughts ideas expressions information knowledge whatever
you also diminish their ability to receive all of that in one shot you don't have to mess up their
ability to express and then mess up their ability to receive you just mess up one or the other
and they both go down the tube well does that make sense yeah because it's a two-way street it's like
imagine one pipe that sends and receives if you put a dent or a kink in that pipe guess what it's
going to impair impede the ability to send and receive well what I'm hearing is this if you are
all on the same frequency right and we have you know the old no no no sorry sorry no it's not
frequency no frequency is later no frequency's not keep it keep it mechanical okay I am keeping
it mechanical I was going to something here if we're all on radios okay we have radios to receive
information somebody is broadcasting like they did on CB radios in the old days or you could
with a security that's okay hold on that's over that's over simplifying no because no this wasn't
there yet but okay okay but go ahead I don't want to drift off too mechanical because when I say
mechanical it's what you hear see touch smell and feel right not what you think about well this is
what I'm getting to though is that okay if you've got a broadcaster who is getting putting out
pertinent information that's useful absolutely clear and broadcast perfectly and someone gets
into that very same frequency turns around and opens a mic and puts it next to their car engine
or whatever else now you have an interference that is drowning the original signal well no no
it's not interference I think it's operational ability I'll give you an idea okay okay
you know the analogy you know if you hear jazz coming out of a radio you think you're
gonna open the radio on this little jazz band no the thoughts and all these things are the same it's
they're not in your head they're external so when you say frequencies when someone thinks about
saying something that's already out every anyone can receive it ergo telepathic person would hear
it right like one famous thing to do if you're in a big city like San Fran or New York or Tokyo
when you're walking down the sidewalk right constantly think about if there are any ETs
on the sidewalk in this crowded street I want to say hello and then if you do this for a few days
somebody will keep thinking that someone will stare at you and you'll say you must be an ET
because you heard you heard this and they'll nod and they'll keep walking right it's kind of crazy
right so it sounds crazy sounds very sci-fi but try it if you're in a big city you know you got
to be persistent with it okay so what I'm trying to say is that it's always put out it's not like
you're putting out a frequency to let's say someone else and they're not picking it up you're
putting it out to everyone is what I'm trying to say it's out in the ether always you see so when
you're communicating to one person you're just not communicating to one person you're putting it out
on the ether let's go back to the analogy you use well I like the radio for that reason yeah yeah
let's say you have a cb do you think uh you want to call me on a cb handle and I'm the only one
that could hear it no anyone that gets on you know 400.2 will hear it right for whatever frequency
we're using right you see so uh so that's exactly what's going on but the thing that I'm trying to
say is there's a tweak an alteration a bug something in the hardware in between the hardware
and the software of the mind that when the person's when you notice someone who can't communicate
right you can and you just met them you don't know them well or even if you know them or if
they can't communicate well guess what they won't be able to grasp ideas either because it's a
two-way street so if you meet someone that you don't know well they can't grasp ideas well guess
what when they start telling you a story you won't know what the hell they're talking about they can't
communicate you see it's a two-way street so it's very important so what this what the significance
of this is is this we typically call one or the other label socially people as being dumb or
they're stupid and I'm telling you they're not I've since early greek speak days I've always said we
all have the same you remember external input we all have the same capabilities everything there's
a tweaking but we begin with basically the same hardware and processing processing and it's it's
just like tuning you go to a guitar shop 100 guitars on the wall take them all down uh pull
the you know whatever you want to pluck none of them are going to sound the same right never now
you can tune them so they get close right that's fine right we don't expect them no two loaves of
bread are baked alike no two people are the same you can do people watching and you'll never see two
people with exactly the same features even lookalikes do not have exactly the same features
you know you've seen like the obama lookalike right oh yeah okay you look at him and his ears
are just a little too big compared to obama but everything else is fits to a t so you're never
going to find okay so what i'm trying to say here is that the important part is this is mastering
let's say the field of psychology the field of human relations or human self-improvement
is that this is just another way to assess those around you and yourself if you find yourself not
communicating well guess what you're actually not receiving no matter what you think you do
you're not receiving either well either so if you can receive well you can project well and this is
this is not the ultimate you know let's say this is always true because there what if you can
receive well but you can't communicate because of again a mechanic mechanical impediment right
so there's there's exceptions to this but i've noticed this now from observing people for about
six decades that those that can't communicate well don't receive well and it's not an aptitude
problem it's it's something between the mechanical and the process right and this is not being
addressed by the way and actually it was at some point i remember as a young student in the crazy
school system it might have been around what's called the eighth grade that's when i stopped
paying attention they did something called speech class i don't know if you remember that
it's not because yeah you get up and you just uh speak to an audience how to do public speaking
right right right matter of fact that's what they called it where i was public speaking yeah yeah
public speaking and i don't think that's well i don't know somebody can check me but i doubt that's
even being done anymore uh as it was back then so that also if you did well with public speaking
and you were struggling let's say quote unquote learning you would find yourself from taking that
public speaking class and learning how to structure your communication skills you will
find that your learning skills would also go up right yeah so if you were struggling with math
now you may not be struggling with math as much or whatever this is an interesting point because
it's not an aptitude problem right now it's a matter of orientation because they they they
would teach you to order things in a particular way to say yeah yeah well yeah it's just like
look you know tying your shoelaces you know everyone learns how to tie their shoelaces
quote-unquote everyone uh but they all learn they remember it differently and then after a while
it's rote you don't even have to remember how you remembered it you just do it right right
so this is this is the the level that i'm speaking of but it's not don't separate it
imagine just one pipe where liquid flows in both directions or air flows in both directions if you
stuff up that pipe you can't just say well now we're not going to get receive air you can't give
air either because the what you receive and what you give is going through the same conduit you see
right it's not one or the other you'll you won't find someone who is a good communicator that
doesn't grasp ideas well or knowledge well that doesn't that's not true but if you find someone
who's not a good communicator i'll bet you for sure they can't also grasp new ideas well either
so it's very interesting so there's either an obstruction or there's not that's really what
the difference it's a tuning issue yeah it's a tuning issue but this again just to say this again
this issue let's call it an issue right okay is misunderstood as people being dumb or stupid and
they're not it's a skill problem so in other words instead of trying to increase people's
aptitude and learning skill why don't you just work on the communication skills on one side
and the other side the learning skills pick up also and vice versa you see it's very interesting
and i've been and i've put this together very recently uh because it just kind of hit me here
here's the thing you know i talk about yin and yang right right and you know when you know it's
not about polarity people try to make positive negative hard software it's about antagonism so
something becomes one thing the the antagonistic quality uh seems to go well with it right so um
so yeah so it's one thing or another so in other words when you're wondering let me give you an
idea of yin and yang and how the universe works by antagonism not polarity um when you're wondering
about something right uh what it is or whatever and the more you wonder and think about it without
an answer your brain becomes mean it spreads out it becomes soft it becomes on the issue right and
then the only way you could receive the information is like a bolt of lightning it just hits you in a
second right so if you start you know the opposite is true if you start thinking on something very
strongly on focusing on one very narrow issue the more you do that you're going to find yourself
getting really wishy-washy about everything else right very soft and you'll fall apart that way
right so it's it works also with the thinking process when someone communicates and they're
very wishy-washy you're not getting the point right um they will see receiving knowledge as
a bolt of lightning that they can't handle and vice versa if someone is yeah is this akin to
okay you ever get yourself a bit flustered because you can't remember where something is
it's misplaced you're certain you knew where it was not too long ago yeah my brain you turn okay
fine yeah you you turn around let's just say it's a we'll use a common item keys right people lose
track of their keys all the time uh and you don't know where they are you don't know where they are
you're looking around you're digging around if you back off and just ease up a bit right and sort
of relax for a moment it hits you right away a lot of times just boom it comes to you just like
exactly and it but it and if you're focusing on the keys too much though right right if you if you
focus too much it'll be a very wishy-washy feeling yeah it's uh yeah it's interesting the antagonism
so in other words a harsh communicator will take in information very wishy very spread out and
unaccumulated right so it works also that antagonistic aspect works back and forth
i found it to be very interesting as a revelation to myself lately and i've been testing it
you know with people that around me uh those that i know and those that i don't know and just taking
mental notes and seeing you know how the antagonistic part works too so what i mean is
like when someone's not a good communicator very wishy-washy not getting the point when you present
a new piece of information to them you actually almost physically see them jolt as if they put
their finger in an electric socket it's kind of interesting and then people who are very forceful
with their communications when you give them a new piece of information they kind of calm down and
like they're in a they're in a bath of water the opposite right so i just wanted to see if well
this is one other thing i want to express the whole concept of the yin and yang and all that
right oh my gosh it is i occasionally look up to see because people go online they're not very few
well even if you i'm saying go to the library you look stuff up it's like a joke now right because
you know all the good stuff didn't removed anyway of course after 9-11 especially so
but after covid even more so um look up there's nothing really online that i could recommend
maybe some books uh from the macrobiotic point of view uh which by the way macrobiotics is not
just a modified type japanese diet it's not a way of eating but it's a way of thinking just the whole
idea of it leaning on food is because you know food is converted into energy and food is converted
into your body literally you are you know they say you are what you eat no you are what you ate
yesterday you know what i mean that's true yeah correct uh uh correct tense on that would be uh
you can only be what you've already eaten not what you yeah you're not what you eat you are
what you ate you are already eaten in the past yes yeah so when you hear someone talking nonsense
what did you eat for dinner last night what does that have to do with it you know well guess what
it does affect you so so from that point but it is understanding antagonism it is understanding
things it's helped me quite a bit with the transmutation work and other things like that so
what i might be talking about in the future if i can work it out more just like you know i worked
out the water thing and a bunch of people started building them and got similar if not same results
the other things i'm working on and which was with induction biological induction material
induction very much on the vein of homeopathic but not on the vein of homeopathic where they
have a very fine dilution we're talking about no dilution no contact right and still getting it
across them still working on that and it'll be quite interesting because the results are not
consistent enough to say build this and this will happen right uh if i if i build this and it happens
one out of ten times they i could maybe have a discussion group to help me on it but i'm not
going to come out and say build this and this will happen even one out of ten times because it's not
you know it needs to be worked out right you might you might stop at this question but i have this
question i've had this question in my mind a few times and i haven't brought it up because it
wasn't appropriate but now you've given me the the the uh open lane here's the thing if i understand
that a whole lot of things okay a whole lot of realities a whole lot of
natural and even unseemingly unnatural although it is all natural processes
occur via induction right energy matter indeed all this stuff seems to occur by induction
why is it that we are not able to do you know what what people would describe in like sci-fi circles
is like how about telepathic communication simply give the idea to someone else by induction without
any sort of standardized communication how is it that we are not able i disagree before you go it
is happening but it's not happening the way you expect it to happen yes i know that part of it
but someone might say that if we could learn to be more willful with this
right exactly well that's the what we have do we're dual-minded you know that term dual-minded
okay well we there's one aspect of being dual-minded that you cannot avoid and that
is the body has a mind of its own we went over this several sonics ago quick recap
absolutely there's someone's regular spiritual mind is so depressed they want to kill themselves
so they drown they try to drown and while they're drowning their body's mind which has a separate
mind what that keeps all the involuntary actions going right circulation nervous heartbeat and all
that he's like wait a second what are you doing to me i don't want to die i want to live that's
my whole purpose that's why i keep the heart pumping that's why you're breathing that's what
right so they have this dual-minded so so not only is the person thinking they have to kill themselves
but while they're trying to do it they're going to discover that there's another one of themselves
that is running their body right so that part that's that's the other part of yourself i'm
you brought this up because this is part of the whole work it's a there's a mental connection to
what i'm talking about well again that's your body is doing and you know how i mentioned the
body's is the body's mind is keeping the heart rate and the all the involuntary actions going
right well guess what well the induction that's happening from nutrition and elimination because
remember induction also happens on elimination side and rebuilding of cells and all the minerals
and things that are created and elements that are created that's already happening it's in your
body so now the the idea is can you reflect that or have that go beyond the body or do things that
are beyond the body to affect the body right through that mind so yeah we already know how
to do it but not with the mind that we normally use the the the mind that the body has in other
words let's extend it further that is the soul it is the metabolism it has its own intelligence
but it's innate and it's interchangeable right that's why well there's a lot of sci-fi which is
quite accurate when someone dies they transfer their consciousness to a computer so they keep
living or a clone right well that consciousness transfer there's a the part that was their body
that soul dies right so that you know so there is a distinction between two but there is no conversation
uh if there was a direct conversation between the body's mind and the spiritual mind you wouldn't
have cancer existing well even unless it's sudden unless it's a sudden thing because even if there
was an ability to directly communicate one body's mind sort of to another body's mind there might
be ways of repairing things for instance your body's mind is not really sure how to deal with
something it's working through the process maybe my body's mind has the answer already
gives it that information or even gives it the correct energy look i see what your problem is
here it is you know my body's mind does this not my mind per se does this hey look here's your
solution what you need to do is uh take this in and remove this from the equation you'll be fine
sure what you just described is that one of the core things that uh is about reiki but people
that practice reiki can't say that they don't know how to explain it either so i mean you just
you just explained it the healing by touch and hands and all that yes you don't have to think
about it because the body already knows what to do but the thing is can you mimic it can you not
even mimic can you duplicate the reactions and it's a reactionless reaction by the way you can't
show you know how chemists chemical reactions are written out and because of valences these things
combine or these things break up or at certain rates or give off heat or whatever yeah there's
the observable we can't do that based on yeah this is this is in between that it's kind of like you
could say when an atom is looked at very very closely however they want to look at it several
ways they notice that even the densest materials they just notice there's just dielectric space
there so that means that anything that's material is actually phenomenal even we are action even
induction in and of itself right there's a certain part of the process where you or i as far as i
know maybe you do but i don't have a way to even communicate what happens at a certain point i can
say okay here's energy the energy is now being induced from one place to another but you see that
part of the process i don't have okay well here's for that i could give you one right now very
simple you've seen the time-lapse photography where they show a flower wither or a spree a sprout
or a seed go to full plant or say a sunrise you see it happen in a course of like you know 10
seconds it goes across the sky whatever yeah let's let's stick more like with that uh the
plants and living things okay have you ever watched in slow motion a wound heal and and when
and there's two ways to do this one is to use the technical aspect of it where you use a slow motion
camera leave it on for three days and someone you know is not moving around too much and you play it
a minute right or you can actually watch it yourself in real time and then take all that
real time and explain it as if it's happening in fast motion i'm sorry slow motion fast motion
however you want to say it right when we record three days and show it in one minute that's fast
motion photography this is where somebody takes you know the the a tree over the course of an
entire year and you can actually watch the tree move because the whole thing actually moves at a
uh but but you all right so two minutes over but it was a year so this is how the induction works
so you have a membrane whether it's the skin on the outside of your body or the skin on the inside
of your body or your intestines on the inside of the intestines or the intestines on the outside
of the intestine your lungs on the inside of your lungs or the outside of your lungs it doesn't matter
either side of any skin or membranes you pick any organ you pick any blood vessel you pick any
whatever okay so what happens you have material on one side and it receives a command but it's
not a command like we think commands are it's a conditional command in other words
it's not do this and the person has to do the conditions have to be right to for it to receive
the command and the conditions are many so the membrane whatever it is organ membrane skin
whatever bone doesn't matter our material on the right gives the command in the material is able to
resonate with the commands and it goes from let's say solid it goes to liquid goes to gas and then
it goes to energy which is that energy that holds an atom together it's a dielectric wouldn't the
energy come first before yeah well well we're we're speeding this is all mechanical judgment now
okay so so so let's just say let's just make it a little easier i'm just trying to put the process
in order yeah sure let's do it like this very simple the inside of the intestines called the
lumina right the whole you know the tubes okay so food is in there okay and um the intestines are
working a certain way they're they're different they work different than any other organ because
their command to that food is going to be whatever it is uh bologna and margarine on white bread
is going to say hey you are now going to uh a liquid and then a gas and then to energy a
dielectric energy and soon as you become a dielectric energy energy you you permeate the
you get absorbed permeate uh go into the actual intestinal wall itself right now on the other side
of the intestinal wall is where the rest of your body is guess what happens that energy now is either
stored in the intestinal wall in the blood or immediately goes from what energy to gas okay to
liquid to solid again but not like it not like that's what cancer is by the way one one mechanism
of cancer when the body reproduces what you ate on the inside and if anyone's worked in cancer
biopsies when they look at tumors they'll find plant tissue in their animal tissue teeth hair
things develop that shouldn't be inside the body right because you have this this mess up
kind of like in star trek one of the movies where the the um the transporter wasn't working well
they tried to beam someone up and they arrived as a massive pile of flesh they died right because
the transporter is screwed up okay right that's one mechanism of cancer but so when this happens
on the inside of the body it has a correlation it coalesce and very discreetly process all that
information and and into uh into energies and materials that are totally different an example
that would be on a dairy farm and and what comes out of dairy farms you get different cheeses
different milk products all from the same cow they say right so this is exactly right so what happens
is one's inside the intestine it's whatever you're eating and as it goes through the wall
there's an intelligence there that when it appears inside the body it might appear as a blood cell
different types of blood cells it might appear as plasma might appear as you know a lymph fluid
it might appear as other type of energy to oversimplify the cow produces milk but it started
by eating grass let's say so the thing is that that's sure sure well let's let's let so that's
the induction process so here's the thing the body can also hold that energy from the bologna
margarine sandwich and let's say some bone needs to be rebuilt down by your ankle and it will not
manifest until it gets to the ankle here's one thing i've mentioned before like i like mentioning
this again when they look at blood who's they anyone uh with western education no uh they see
a bunch of blood cells in the group those are red blood cells these are white blood cells whatever
whatever right well you know what they don't see that when you look at the red blood cells
this blood cells for the big toe this one's for your ear this one's for your eye they can't see
that right imagine they all have serial numbers they all have messages on where to go it's not
this random lump they like to tell people that everything's random right you know it's nothing
as random each cell has a designation point once you once that is understood to read now
right if someone needs a new foot you can designate cells to go into the body and rebuild the foot
directly right and by the way this technology's existence since the 30s well isn't it but isn't
it because they oversimplified the grouping of things together where they turn around they say
well that's just plasma that's not just plasma that's hundreds of different things going on
right well if you want to go to the core of the education financing is involved and the
financers don't want it right okay and they have like for example if you look at the medical field
that's a paramilitary group of paramilitary is a fancy way of saying police so when the banksters
took over any country they would love to set up another army and get rid of the existing army but
that would put the country in total chaos and the people would never accept it so instead of creating
another military force they create a police force that enforces people certain people that are
allowed to practice medicine certain ways and others are no one else is allowed otherwise you
send this paramilitary group to arrest you right so they control this education all this stuff so
that's the problem policy enforcers is all they are the policy enforcers so they develop a policy
and then you well no no they're actually a paramilitary group they're a power see let me
just go over it again when the bankers take over a country they they would the way they say we now
we have our own military your country your military is gone and you have to do what we say
you know what the people will do they won't take it that country will will go into a massive massive
real civil war revolution and it will never settle down until they get rid of the banksters
so what they do is they convince them that police are okay which police are just paramilitary
and to prove this you look at things like waco whatever let's say someone has a hostage situation
in a suburbs country city and the police show up and the people take the the hostage takers shoot
all the police dead and all that well police say well they killed us all right so now we got to send
armored police and then they blow up all the armored police guess who they're calling next
the nearest military base to send tanks and helicopters right you get it of course yeah
waco or whatever else ruby ridge whatever you want to say okay this is so that's where the veil
of what i'm saying falls apart you could see it very clearly um that's why there is no information
that's why the information is always held in a non-public scheme or non-public place it doesn't
i mean everything we do is behind a paywall let's say for a reason also because if you have open
audio let's say we do we start getting into more of this stuff even stuff we've gone into and it's
on rumble or anybody could go to the website and click on it and get it no no you'd have some
serious problems you know what i mean right because it's public right uh this is not public
right so uh and it's all you know the the um the uh they do these things this is for education
purposes only not advice or whatever bullshit this is more than education purposes and it is advice
well just like just like you said with the terrorism when they say this is terrorism
no it's not it's a drill when they say it's a drill it's actually terrorism sure yeah speaking
of which uh i want to just tell people you know you can learn anything about everything and
everything about anything right you have an unlimited capability storage capability it's
how you grew up and the people that you respected when you you were young how they behave you you
take on these traits i've seen this many times i've seen it even with my being around as a young
man like we go camping or somewhere by the way i don't you know i don't like that but and and there's
alpha male and after the camping trip we all start using the terms and the mannerisms that
the alpha male did right we all copy women do the same and all this other stuff so as a
so as a child if you grew up around people that were respected by your parents it might be your
parents also might do this older brothers or neighbors that were respected if they say oh
i don't know anything about that and the p and everyone patted them on the back so you're still
a good guy well now you say what was what did he say he didn't know anything about math oh and
everybody still loves it okay so i can go if i don't want to work on math at all all i have to
say is i'm not good at math everybody pats me on the back says oh good boy oh good girl it's
it's acceptable and that's not acceptable because anyone can learn everything about everything
or everything about something or something about everything in other words you have unlimited
capability right so when you take all of this and you put it together where i was going with this
recently someone sent me there was an explosion of a house okay in arlington virginia and they
asked me what did this because the police said it was a flare and i looked at it and like
before the video even as it started i was like on three seconds i see exactly what happened here
was an oxygen tank that's bolted some down somewhere in the basement and it was blown by
a primary some kind of primary explosion not a spark um and it was in the basement if you look
at the thing the explosion how first of all how do i say it's oxygen because it was a bright yellow
and then bright orange immediately and any debris that was close by already caught fire because
that's how a calorimeter works when you try to figure out calories you use oxygen because it
has the ability to set everything on fire and we know the color the spread the spectrum of oxygen
right so and it wasn't just like a spark starting it doesn't work it was this was a primary ignition
like a smaller ignition setting it off like a small explosive a small flare gun could have said
you know tremendous amount right so how did i know this well because through the years
when i saw oxygen being burned the first time maybe at 12 years old someone
turning on a torch when they turned the oxygen on i remembered the color of the flame
right right when i heard when i heard oxygen pop i remembered how fast it was so all when i see that
when i saw that building the way it went off in the news in the youtube video that was sent to me
what i did immediately is recalled anything every experience that i've ever recalled since i've
been on this planet and filtered it all out say what is this and it all was very obvious to me
so why do we know it was in the basement because if you play it in slow motion you see all the
first floor windows blow out horizontally first before it rises right so it was below the first
floor not on the first floor right right so and i gave a detailed explanation how much oxygen it
was the tank had to be bolted down because it wasn't bolted down the it wouldn't have it you
know the it would have propelled itself away and spread it out it wouldn't have been so concentrated
right so so this is like very very simple this is a simple you can make any process that you see
recognizable and describable if you focus on everything that you're doing that's why
years ago when i was around the people in the new age movement they always say you're not present
you're not present be here now right that kind of thing that means to be present yeah right
you know um how many times have you seen people describe a car accident right and then you
question them and you and um you say well that accident was there a lot of broken glass in the
prison see yeah half the people will say there was broken glass even though there was no broken glass
right they'll start confabulating because everybody knows it could be broken glass so if i say there's
broken glass it's okay i wasn't paying that much attention right so one of the things that i do
also is learning you know how i say everyone's got a photographic memory is just that most people are
out of film right or out of now it would be disk space or your card is whatever right you get it
right okay so what you do is uh you know let's say you're a passenger or whatever or you're walking
it's something fast moving a bus a train a car you see a billboard with a phone number and you pass
it right you may might be in view for a second or two or three take a picture of that billboard
while and then read the number when you've already passed it and can you read the number as if it's
still in front of you as if you took a picture of it can you do that with your mind yeah and i train
people to do this and it first of all i'll never there's a whole bunch of people by the way when
i'll never be able to do that pat him on the back say good boy good girl go get some ice cream okay
who's interested in doing this as opposed to saying right away right you know what i mean
self-defeatist and i train people how to do this and i do it all the time and people test me it's
it's like um i gotta pull over and uh did you get that i'm like yeah i'll get that and actually i
you know we just passed it and it's like uh 30 seconds later and i'm still giving him the phone
number and all everything that pretty much everything on the billboard right like holy
shit well i said it's not that i remember it what i remembered was that as an image and now
that image fades by the way because it's not that important and i'm reading it
to them as if it's still in front of me right and this is a skill and it's very simple by the way
all you do is whatever it takes emo to be a camera it's kind of like the idea of not being
like a camera there's a big difference between being like a camera and being a camera
think of the emo right being like a camera we can't do it but we can create a cartoon effect
that you're in a cartoon scene and you're actually a camera in the cartoon right yeah whatever it
takes like a camera leaves a lot of open space to be other things that are not okay and and you
probably won't have the abilities of a camera if you're like a camera right because you can make a
lump of clay look like a camera you could look like a camera and have no functionality as exactly
so you want that you want to be a camera right right yeah what is it sorry so now you're getting
into that so like we said earlier everything is the same if you look at the atoms inside
a camera and the atoms in your body there's it's all space it's all energy
so that's that's another perspective so anyway keep learning because it's unlimited but the thing