The Sonic entity known as S.H.O.N.I.C.K. is here to bring you the news.
over here and continue the conversation.
But yeah, that's a good thing to do over there.
And just want to get that piece of housekeeping
out of the way before we get to the main thing.
So, Greek, you want to talk to me
about a prototype you're working on?
There's so many things that were changed on it
that now I'm making a production on,
like I'm measuring the prototype and building one,
you know, I'm trying to make a blueprint
so I can build many of them like that, right?
And it's very critical because just when you think
what happens when you get used to things,
you allow changes, you give it loose tolerances,
and you drift.
So what I'm saying is I'm trying to do
a standardized version of something that's been prototyped.
And it's so critical because you catch yourself saying,
well, I know I want to copy this, right?
So how about, but this time, you know,
instead of this being in this position,
maybe we'll move it over a little bit over here.
Maybe it's a little better.
Ah, ah, ah, don't do that, don't do that
because now you're not making a copy of the prototype.
Now you're still prototyping, right?
You're still evolving the design.
Yeah, so it's not going to be a standardized version
of the prototype.
So it's really difficult to do that.
It's very, it's almost easier to have someone else do it
where you give them the prototype and say,
all you need is a caliper, you know, to measure.
And just build, just copy this, make a print.
So if someone wants to build it, you give them the print.
But it's so difficult because I keep catching myself
measuring and transferring measurements
because I'm doing it on paper and in real,
you know, on real material, right?
That's ready to be cut and formed.
And I'm like, oh man, you know, so what am I,
I spent two hours like, oh yeah, I'm going to go,
I'm going to make it look a little different.
Like, no, no, no, because if I make it look
a little different and it doesn't sound
like the prototype, I'm going to blame the prototype, right?
Because I didn't make an exact copy.
You see, this is very difficult to do.
What I'm trying to say is I have too much instilled bias
in me still that I can't just separate myself
from some things and say, well, what's the scope?
Just make a copy and do the copy.
I don't know.
It's very, I found it more difficult to make the copy
of the prototype, in other words, duplicate it.
And why I'm doing the duplication is because the prototype,
as I moved things around, I had to cut a new hole
and fill the old hole, so it's all patches.
Like, you ever see a piece of, or an old jeans
where there's more patches
than there are original jeans, right?
Or, you know, clothing like back,
it actually became fashionable.
We have so many patches and repairs on it
that there's more repair than there is of the original.
And that's what the prototype is.
And now I'm thinking, why is it so difficult
to just make a copy of it and stop just, you know,
trying to move things and thinking of making them better?
So what I'm trying to say is there's an instilled bias
that I feel like another person or another me
would go ahead and make these slight changes again, right?
And now you're not doing what you set out
to do yesterday, let's say, right?
So it's important.
But maybe you're working toward the proper prototype
because some part of you is telling you
this is not perfect yet.
Is that a possibility?
It's not perfect, but look, perfect is,
well, here's the thing.
They are very, very, very good.
As a matter of fact, I had someone
who is a trained pianist listen to these.
And he was like, are you kidding?
These little speakers here sound like that?
This is just YouTube with a laptop, no special processing.
No, no, it's got a Yima A07 max amp.
Get it on Amazon for 70 bucks.
Sounds like a class A amp and just a Lenovo laptop,
nothing special.
And he's like, I can't believe the sound
that's coming out of this.
I'm like, I know, it's credible, isn't it?
And it's got a standard sound card on it.
I mean, there's nothing enhanced about it.
No, there's nothing, there's nothing audio,
tweak, nothing at all.
So when you hook these up to something that is special,
which I have, they sound even better.
So, and it just behooves, like if you turn off the lights,
you don't know where the sound is coming from.
And it sounds, it doesn't quite have the weight
of a full piano.
It's very hard to do that, which I'm going to be doing
the next prototype to a small that does,
but it does have the full weight of a snare
as the full weight of chorus singers.
Anyway, very small and they sound just outstanding realism,
transient response.
Like when you're listening to Orange Colored Sky,
Nat King Cole is singing in the chorus of five people jumps,
you know, in at the chorus time,
it sounds like five people yelling in your ear, right?
And it's like, whoa, where'd that come from?
Right, so anyway, I'm trying to make a copy of this.
And why is it so freaking hard?
Because I've already invested myself emotionally
and all these other things in making the prototype.
So now I have to divest myself and act like a robot
because you could actually, there are computers now
with scanners that you could, they could scan something,
make a blueprint and actually send it over
to the 3D printer and make it exactly like what they scanned.
And that's what I'm set out to do, right?
But I can't do it.
It's so difficult.
It's really, really difficult to do.
And it's even more difficult
than actually making something from scratch.
Well, it's surprising the hell out of me.
Well, you're seeing it as a difficulty,
but I'm thinking to myself, it's just your natural urge
that you just have to improve it, you know?
Because I've so invested in it
and I'm thinking what I'm doing now is a carry over.
It's not, I have to cut it off.
It's kind of like, you know what this is like?
The young boy who gets hit by a car on his bicycle
and they bring him to the, he's in critical condition
in the emergency room.
And the ER trauma surgeon is his mother, right?
Should she operate or should she have it, right?
You see what I mean?
This is a common story, right?
They're better, yeah.
And it's almost always like, look,
you're better off handing that to somebody else
because they will dispassionately pay attention to things.
They won't get swayed by their emotion
and they'll just do the job.
That's right.
So that's what I'm going through right now.
And it's very, and you can, it's easy to, here's the thing.
A lot of the things that I've spoken of, I've gone through.
And this is a new thing because I, from what,
well, the sclerator is like that also,
but the sclerator is very, it's a different animal
because it's so simple.
But this is really hard to do, to actually make it.
The best analogy would be the surgeon mom
operating on her son.
It's really difficult to do.
So I had to bring that up.
But anyway, I just wanted to throw that in there
because I'm kind of wrecked mentally and emotionally
and because I'm trying to make a copy
and I can't find myself to just make a freaking copy.
So anyway.
Maybe it's good you're taking the breather to record this.
Because you get away from it for a minute.
Yeah, what I'm saying, it's just like
the woman operating on her son.
Maybe she shouldn't be doing it.
Right.
Oh, and look, what do they always tell you though?
Take a step back and think for a moment, you know?
No, no, no, because that's what I was doing.
Remember, thinking requires all the other functions
that we've spoken about on Greek speak stuff.
All right, let's go back to the question.
I just wanted to throw that in.
No, no problem at all.
Okay, so we got either a really ugly question in my mind
or we got the question that I know we've covered before.
That's fine, either one.
Okay, well, we'll bring out the one
that we've covered before.
They were asking about inspiration.
What inspires somebody to do something?
And where does that come from
and how does that tie to this thing
they call your will, right?
You know, like how are you inspired to do things
that are not necessarily immediately adjacent
to what it is you're doing?
Because I passed the question.
It's beyond, that's beyond it.
That's like what they usually call first principle stuff.
Where do ideas come from?
That's trying to objectify the ether.
We're trying to objectify something
that is in the substrate of this reality.
Once you do that, by the way,
that has been done with what's called nuclear technology.
It has nothing to do with splitting atoms.
It's shorting out the ether, shorting out the substrate.
Like just like the old,
I don't know if you remember the TV screens,
they had these metal grids in them,
the ones that they made early computers with
because they thought the little metal grid
would help with the radiations.
If you short out that grid
or let's say you short out the board
that carries the pixels,
you short out all the other pixels.
That's what nuclear is.
So to find out where it comes from and all that
is gonna be shorting out, not the purpose of being,
because there is no purpose here.
It's just passing time.
Well, according to you,
the purpose here is to waste other people's time.
Well, I'll tell you why.
Because if you, well, here's the thing.
Everyone's wasting each other's time and things do also.
And that doesn't have to be people that waste your time.
What I mean by that is, you know,
the reincarnation cycle,
you know, everyone's got their own soul trap
or it gets worse or it gets better or it's non-linear.
Like if you die, you know,
I'm one of the few people that said this.
If there is reincarnation,
you could actually die now
and be reincarnated in ancient Rome.
It's not linear.
You're not always reincarnated in the future, right?
Well, and I've always tried to say
that the other side of that
is you could already be reincarnated right now
as a five-year-old somewhere
and you don't know it just yet.
Well, part of it is, yeah,
and there's certain cultures
that don't consider you being a spirit.
We know that you don't have the spirit
you're supposed to have until you're 12.
But here's the thing.
If the reincarnation cycle does go a certain way,
we are in an afterlife right now
because right, you were alive before.
Now you're in a different reincarnation
and you're in a different incarnation.
So that means you're actually in an afterlife right now.
So that kind of kills the whole afterlife thing too.
But it goes either way.
So these are like primary things
that we're not supposed to get an answer to right now
because we're, it doesn't,
I shouldn't say help us right now
because how do you help someone waste your time, right?
Because whatever you do to help someone waste someone's time
is gonna be another waste of time.
It's not really helping the waste of time directly.
Right, and that's the other counter question
I've always got for people on stuff like this
where it's like, what good will this do you?
Let's just imagine for a moment
that I have the absolute answer.
What good is that gonna do you?
Is it going to help you in some way to know
if I know exactly where?
No, no, no, it does.
No, it does.
It does, okay.
Yeah, of course, of course it does.
Okay.
All that stuff does,
but then you won't be wasting time anymore
and you don't have to be here.
Ah.
Right, there's certain things
that if you really knew the truth,
you would just go poof and you disappear.
Have you ever, there was something Rick and Morty,
the Meseeks, right?
Oh yeah, right.
The Meseeks.
People think it's ridiculously stupid,
but I kind of enjoy it.
The Meseeks, yeah, I need something to do,
you know, and right, I'll get it done.
Don't give me something I can't be done.
You know, it's like a day is an eternity for a Meseeks,
right?
Right.
So it's like we're Meseeks, yeah.
Now, once you find out certain primary things,
the formative things like that,
you just disappear, just like a delete, you know, right?
But then what happens?
Then what happens?
Is it another, you see?
So all these things tie in together,
but I know that inspiration comes first,
then ideas, then thought, right?
And then the rest is, you know, physical, right?
Then you take action or you don't, right?
Yeah, right.
So the thing is there,
I've pondered these things
and there's two answers I could give.
It's not time to know yet personally for me,
or maybe someone else does
and they poofed out of here, right?
And, but what I do know for sure
is we're here to waste time
and waste other people's time
and have other people waste your time.
It's all a waste of time.
It's sort of like being at a threshold.
You're neither inside nor you're outside, right?
Standing at the threshold.
Are you in the house or out of the house?
It's a very, very strange thing.
And boy, I hope the rest of the reality is not like this.
So, yeah.
But I can't invest any more into thinking about that
because I've benefited so much from inspiration.
I'll just, some people call them downloads or ideas,
whatever, you know,
but the inspiration is the core thing.
You know, the inspiration is pure emo.
Like if you get inspiration to do something,
when you have enough formulated to do that thing,
it's no longer inspiration.
It's an idea and a thought now, right?
So the inspiration is a flicker.
It's so undefinable.
And yeah, it's from that primary.
It's like the ether.
It's like, yeah,
something that if you start understanding that
and can dabble with that source,
you're out of here.
You're done.
You're a big threat, you know?
Right.
I mean, the only thing I can think of
is that it must be a very natural process
because anything that is natural like that
does evolve and grow, right?
I don't think anything is natural.
But you don't think anything is natural?
Okay.
No, because if there's a creator,
he's an artificer and everything's artificial.
Really?
If there's a creator, he's an artificer.
Yeah, there's no such,
nature is a machine, there's archetypes.
Yeah, nothing is, okay, natural,
okay, when you say natural,
it's attributed to not man-made, usually.
It's like when you say anarchy,
that attributes to, oh,
there's gonna be a big mess and chaos, right?
No, actually, it doesn't mean that at all.
No, it just means I'm without a leader, but.
Yeah, you're right.
And it's castle doctrine, each man, right?
So when you say natural,
I think of, you know, there's random,
there's a time,
there's things that have been put in order.
Yes, those things exist, you know,
things are put in order
that keep cycling and processing,
but if there's a creator behind it,
he's an artificer, an artist,
and everything is artificial, right,
of his creation or her creation, their creation.
Even when some.
It's never a single person,
or a single entity.
Right, but even when there is a creator,
there are other things that occur along with the creation
that are not necessarily part of the creator's plan, right,
but just sort of occur, right?
If he's bound or she,
if the creator's bound to that as an environmental,
quote, unquote, steady state,
then that would be the real nature,
and that platonic philosophy discussed that, right?
Okay.
Platonists discussed that.
Okay, well, I'm just thinking to myself,
look, you know, the creator could create all the vegetables,
but not necessarily create every vegetable ever grown.
You know what I'm saying?
The order of things is put into place.
Because we're too confined to understand, you see?
Okay.
It's too confined of a, yeah.
There are things that pop in and out of this reality,
you know, that you could,
has anyone found a fossil or a really old giraffe skeleton?
Never.
Those are like, those things appeared recently, right?
Giraffes, you know what?
I cannot think of an old giraffe.
There are certain things that just did not exist
a short while ago that just keep popping in and out.
Yeah, so anyway, all right, what I can't,
that's something like the book of Daniel.
It's so weird to wrap your mind around it, you know?
You ever read the book of Daniel?
Like everyone says these things happen here,
and then you read it, and it's like,
no, it's not gonna happen that way.
But then if you try to find an explanation,
you're like, wait a second, this thing is so convoluted,
it takes you right back to where you started.
And you're like, oh boy,
maybe I'll just put this down till the time is right.
Inspiration, if you have it, and you do,
if you're a doer, like Greek speak
is for people that are doers, right?
And let me just put it this way.
If you're a keyboard, whatever, you're not a doer.
But I know some keyboard people that code
and work with all this other stuff,
and they build stuff, they make stuff,
they, you know, whatever.
Yeah, okay, good, but Greek speak is people
who do things, make things, right?
And I mean that in a simple sense, right?
Like third grade craft class.
You know, when you take craft in third grade,
they give you glue and popsicle sticks.
That kind of doing, like start from there, right?
You work with your hands and your mind,
and you build stuff, and people rely on you
for your expertise in doing things, right?
Fixing things, making things, helping out with things.
See, in the context of inspiration though, right?
If we are created by the creator
and then we create something,
is that not a secondary creation of the creator, right?
So, you know, like when people say,
oh, that was, you know, inspired, you know,
the old, that was inspired by God.
Well, isn't everything in a way, right?
Because if you created it and you were a creation,
doesn't it follow that?
Well, there's also cosmic censorship the other way,
where you, the inspirations are held back.
Right.
Right, it goes both ways.
I mean, it's very frustrating when you try to think
about these core principles.
You just have to go along with it.
It becomes difficult because, you know,
the absence of evidence, right?
Doesn't necessarily mean the thing doesn't exist.
You just haven't found it yet.
No, well, you try to define,
well, here's the thing, like the ether
is one of these primary things
because you cannot objectify it
because you're made of it.
Like the image on TV, if it was sentient,
it doesn't really know that it's made up of pixels
because once it starts getting into that,
then it could really screw up the scene, right?
So, well, there's an old cartoon,
which I really enjoyed where the cartoon characters
show them on the board.
He grabs an eraser and it's in reality, right?
And he starts erasing parts of the things
in the cartoon, right?
Oh yeah, I remember that.
We're kind of stuck.
It was like a Looney Tunes thing.
He turns around and starts erasing the other character
and knocks him down and just-
Yeah, and it's a realism.
It's an eraser.
They kind of use special effects.
It's a real pencil that he reaches out
and grabs kind of like Roger Rabbit, right?
Yeah, well, sort of like-
They mix the cartoon with the, yeah.
With the physical world, right.
And the photographic with the animated.
Yeah, but before the computer though, way before that,
which is interesting.
Well, yeah, when you watch stuff before this,
especially before the 60s,
and I tell people when they're watching a movie,
all this was done without CGI.
All this was painted by hand.
All this was made by hand, right?
Yeah, and then they came up with different ways
to photograph stuff.
If we cut this down and we use the light a certain way
or this simple idea of smudging Vaseline on a lens,
you know, whatever.
They came up with practical ways.
There's always a lot of fakery in the beginning.
If you go back to when there was medium format,
large format, film negative in the 19th century,
in the early 1800s, mid 1800s, early 1900s,
most of the photographs,
even though they're originals, they've been faked.
In other words, someone sat there with a razor knife,
started cutting negatives,
because they weren't small negatives.
Medium format's large, right?
Large format negatives.
You know, like the old cameras,
boom, the flashbulb goes.
Then you see that box camera.
Well, the negative's that big, right?
It's pretty large.
So it was very easy to manipulate.
You see a lot of these old photographs on there.
Like, wait a second.
Look at this city in the background.
It's kind of like the pictures they show you
of NASA when they were on the moon, the Apollo.
You could see, like, they're on this gray sand,
and in the background, you could see
it's all been cut in and put in later, right?
If you have a knack for how photography works.
But yeah, a lot of the early photographs that you see,
the historical reference ones, are fake.
So in other words, they've been doctored.
You know, someone sat there.
They're very meticulously done.
But yeah, it's very rare to find an actual photograph,
an old, old photograph that's in, you know,
considered part of the historical record.
Most of them have been faked.
It's interesting.
And that was the beginning of photography.
And so right now, we're in the beginning
of all this other technology.
And guess what?
You got deep fake, blah, blah, blah, AI fakes this,
they fake that, because it's a newer technology
for the public.
It seems like when a newer technology comes out,
there's a lot of fakery.
Like, you know, in China, when cell phones
started becoming popular in the late 90s and early 2000s,
they sold a billion fake vanity phones, cell phones.
Still, I think in the early 2000s,
you could find them in the dollar store.
It just looked like a cell phone, right,
with the antenna sticking out.
It was a vanity phone.
So if you couldn't afford one,
you just looked like you had one, right?
So just fakery on many, many levels.
But anyway, what's the other question?
Yeah, well, the other question was about what entity drives.
They started out with this by saying,
that seems like the Greek is a cat person
and you're a dog person.
That's what they said to me.
I said, yeah, that's true.
But the thing that they asked about is animal cruelty.
Is there a particular part of what's going on
with animal cruelty currently?
Is there something to that?
Is there an entity in charge of it?
They had a bunch of questions like that.
And I'm going, well, yeah.
And then they talked about how they felt
as though this is a lower,
this is definitely like a lower spiritual level.
Like this is even worse than people who are cruel to people.
And they wanted me to ask you about it.
So go ahead.
It's more helpless.
Well, the thing is, it's never a single thing.
And also the lower the entities are,
the more identity stricken they are,
the more they identify with a specific name,
the more they identify with a specific grimoire or whatever.
But by the way, all these sigils
and ways that you summon an entity and all that,
they don't need any of that.
They like to make humans believe that they need that, right?
They're always watching.
And the ones that do get the specific grimoires
and names and the way to direct, then they appear
because that's like a pact they have on their side.
But the people have to be, okay,
the people that do that kind of animal cruelty
usually have to be brought to that situation, right?
You know, like if you hear,
even though it's in popular culture,
a lot of these serial killers,
oh yeah, he killed the family dog.
And even before that, when he was young,
he was spending most of his time outside
in the day burning ants with a magnifying glass.
You know how they build that up, right?
Yeah, that kind of thing.
You've heard that.
Yeah, yeah.
So that kind of stuff is true to an extent,
but most of it is from that military system.
Because the school system from a young age
is military based.
You know, it's that Prussian kind of like,
you know, you're gonna be a worker or a soldier,
you know, kind of thing, right?
And there's a lot of cruelty.
Cruelty is allowed in school, you know,
because they expect you, you know,
to be also have that potential as you get older,
because it could be used by the state, right?
But there's a lot of sick stuff going on.
And it's hard to tell who is and who isn't,
but there are entities behind everything.
And it's never one.
Right.
Even for example, when you read scripture,
let's say you say Yahweh.
Well, he's part of a group.
It's very clear.
It's an entire group.
And there are others that come down.
Let's say if you read scripture,
now we're not talking about the veracity of the scripture.
We're talking about what scripture actually says.
Right.
Right, you know?
So veracity in terms of is it,
should it be viewed as really came from God?
Or is it who wrote it?
None of that stuff.
That's going on with archaics right now.
I just don't watch it because very often
when you see that kind of stuff,
they don't even know what's in the scripture.
And then they talk about it in another way.
But if you just read the scripture,
there's cases where he says,
I'm going to send someone that's just like me, right?
Down into your camp, for example, in Exodus, right?
And the only difference between him and me
is he's not forgiving, right?
So don't, you know, whatever.
So you have these dupes,
these doppelganger spirits that occur.
That's very prevalent.
So to say that there's one, there isn't.
There could be an animal cruelty spirit for,
you know, let's say for the 5 billion
or actually 2 billion people,
let's say that they're on the earth, right?
There could be that many and they're just waiting there.
But I would say that we have enough.
If you take control of your thoughts
and you get the little voice in your head,
I've been doing another level of practice with that.
The voice in your head, I let it drift
and I acknowledge it and I'm like,
what the hell are you talking about?
And it stops, right?
And then it goes away for a while
and then you forget and it comes back, right?
So you always have to be in control of that.
And when you can control that voice in your head,
or just let, you know, you're going to hear it.
But when you acknowledge that it's, you know, a voice,
unknown like inspiration, where's it coming from, right?
When you acknowledge these things,
it becomes much more clear
what an influence is about to come on you.
Like most people think like, I've heard someone say,
oh yeah, most people are possessed, demonically possessed.
And the other person agrees.
I'm like, no, I wouldn't say that.
Because there's different levels of it.
Like there's the influence,
most people I would say are influenced.
And then you have the next level is oppression,
whether oppressed, you know,
where their health goes down and always whatever.
And then you have possession.
Possession is actually very, very rare.
That would be like in what they did to a little poor girl
in the movie, The Exorcist, that would be possession.
If you ask who you are,
I wouldn't say a little girl's name at all, right?
So the influence of people to be cruel to animals
is they're very broad, very broad.
And what I mean by that is like,
well, I don't know anyone who's cruel to animals.
Yeah, but you know, when you hear of a,
there's another 800 dogs were brought to the animal shelter
and they're gonna start euthanizing them, whatever.
Well, how do you, oh, that's just a news article to you,
isn't it?
Do you really feel what's happening there?
Are you gonna make a campaign to go save some dogs?
No, right?
Because you're influenced that that's okay, right?
To accept it, right?
And then there's, of course, the people that work there.
And one criticism I have on that is,
and I've spoken to people throughout,
actually since the 80s about this,
animal testing in the pharmaceutical industry.
It's completely unnecessary.
They have these cruel motherfuckers
that enjoy putting strong acid in animals' eyes.
You know that it's gonna,
look, if you drop that acid on the table
that has a paper on it, the paper will dissolve.
Why are you putting it in the rabbit's eyes, right?
Because they get a thrill from that.
They're sick fucks, you know,
people who do medical research, majority of them.
And I'm not saying this,
I'm saying this from people that did it in the inside.
I couldn't take it.
They're like, oh, what do you do?
I did medical research.
Not anymore, I don't do it anymore.
I said, what happened?
Oh, I was there three months.
These people are sick.
And I'm like, okay.
And then like a few years later,
I run into someone else.
Oh, I did medical research.
I couldn't do it anymore
because these people are crazy.
I'm like, so I'm starting to hear,
you know, the people, you know,
that used to work in that.
And I'm like, this is really fucked up.
Yeah, it is, big time.
See, so it's done on a professional level also.
Well, it seems like almost every profession
has a level where, you know what,
you can be on the outside,
but once they start bringing you
into how things actually work,
you learn that, you know,
the morality is shot.
I mean.
Yeah, it is.
Every field is like that, yeah.
Look at sports.
You can go as far as sports.
All the, you know, all the games are fixed, right?
All the major games, every sport.
Pretty much.
They're all fixed, pretty much, yeah.
And so, for example,
when you watch a baseball game
and you see the ball, you know,
a fly ball or it goes to left field
or right field or down the middle,
those guys are professional baseball players, right?
Yes, they are.
Well, they could hit that ball
exactly within a few yards
of where you want it every time.
Why are they hitting it here and there
and the game is proceeding, right?
How many of them retired from the sport?
1,000, maybe, right?
Since one of these,
let's say past 100 some odd years
of playing baseball,
how many have come forward and said this game,
all the games are fixed
or most of the major games are fixed,
you say?
None.
I've not seen any, yeah.
Pete Rose, they busted him for betting.
That's about it, right?
Judges, how many?
Actually, there have been a few federal judges
that have come forward
and said the whole system's fucked, right?
There have been maybe very few attorneys,
there's a bunch of doctors
that have come out and said
this whole system is screwed up,
but not enough when you take in consideration.
The same thing goes for the animal cruelty
and the human cruelty and whatever, you know?
Yeah, it's pretty, it's a pretty,
yeah, it's not good.
No, I've always found it extremely disturbing.
It's just, you know,
this weird principle that I got very young in life,
I think is a true and fine principle,
which is you don't prey upon anything
that's weaker than you.
You know, this is not something you're supposed to do.
That's the US military's thing.
They'll never fight anyone
that's as strong as they are stronger.
They only prey on civilian populations.
Do I sound like I'm anti-military?
No, but anyway.
Well, I'm saying the opposite thing.
I'm saying exactly the opposite thing,
which is that, you know, as an individual,
I don't want any part of preying upon
something that is weaker than me, you know?
It's just that-
Well, I mean, it happens on many levels.
It'll be with people, societies, animals, insects.
For example, okay, insects.
Okay, wasps, so let's just be specific.
Wasps are very psychic.
Like, there could be, bees are also.
If you go there with the intent of like,
you know, you're fine with them, just don't bite me.
They're okay, cool, right?
Kind of like dogs, you know?
Someone who's afraid of dogs.
Yeah, I've given the analogy many times, right?
Someone's a dog lover and someone's afraid of dogs.
Walk up to a dog they've never seen before,
the dog suddenly gets barking
at the person who's afraid of dogs, right?
In their mind, they pick up on that.
Well, with wasps, Linda said,
well, you know, there's some wasps for that.
Somebody asked, fine.
Well, I went into the shed and it's ventilated.
And I said, ooh, that's one hell of a wasp's nest.
It's a big one.
I let them go.
And I'm like, okay, guys, I think you're,
to the point where you smell the muskiness,
because if you have a lot of insects in the area,
they give off a smell like a pheromone.
It's very strong, actually.
You kind of smell that
when you go to a roach-infested apartment.
You can tell the roach is in there, right?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Typical smell, it's like a metallic kind of wet smell.
But so I go up in the shed.
I'm like, oh, it's really musky in here.
Oh, wow, look at that wasp's nest, right?
It's a lot of wasps in there.
And I'm like, listen, guys,
you're kind of like over when you're welcome.
I could usually burn you out of here.
It would be actually quite a technical thing to stop them,
but I don't wanna do that.
So go ahead and make your wasps,
go out into the desert and have fun,
and deal with it that way.
Because I personally have an affinity
for certain bugs that are psychic like that, right?
You know about the little,
the young girl always happens,
she's walking around like there's butterflies
and they land on the one particular person, right?
And they don't land on everyone.
Now, animals like insects, but they're not insect spiders,
they have no psychic quality about them at all.
They are like psychically invisible.
In other words, you could be somewhere
and you have no sense that there's a spider around.
And even if it's crawling on you,
they don't give off any kind of a psychic vibe,
which makes them a very pretty good predator, right?
Right.
In that reality.
So there's that reality of it,
what kind of connection people have.
The people that I've even depicted in film,
let's just say that they're cruel to animals, right?
They get a high off of that, they get a thrill.
It's a very short thrill,
kind of like smoking crack, right?
Right.
And they keep doing it until, you know,
what was really heinous in the beginning isn't so bad now,
and they go to bigger and bigger things.
Ultimately, the people, you know.
And the U.S. military is an analogy of that, by the way.
So, because it's designed,
the U.S. military is designed to be a world, a police force.
And it's been dubbed that for many years now,
since the Vietnam War.
Yeah, they did talk about that,
the global police force or whatever they were calling it.
And what they do is they always go after the weak
or they never confront something like head on,
like you would see in a dualistic sense,
you know, like bad guy versus good guy,
or this guy, you know, black and white, orange and green.
It's always, let's prey on the weak.
So that seems to be a shitty thing about humans,
and they put up with it.
But, you know, we'll see how much time is left
to put up with that kind of stuff.
Right.
So ultimately, what are you gonna do
about this prototype issue that you started out
talking about at the beginning?
Oh, it's very, I'm actually challenging myself
to discipline and go ahead and measure off
what I wanna build and just ignore
how I would wanna move this over a quarter of an inch.
Right, and just go ahead and build it
and see if it could be replicated.
That's the purpose, because it's worth replicating.
I mean, to quite a degree.
So.