You got it. What did I do here? Here it is. Okay.
71 is the number for this Sonic episode, but it's not an episode. It's an event. Anyway,
Sonic event. Well, I did say Sonic episode at first. That's what I screwed up.
So yeah, it's got to be Sonic event shows are for dogs and ponies. And yeah, you get shows all the
time anywhere else. This is not a show like this. Yeah, indeed. It's not episodic by nature anyway,
because it absolutely does not flow that way. We sometimes continue conversations.
It is. I've watched. You think this is episodic? Really? Of course. Yeah,
I've been watching a bunch of $6 million man from the 70s. And then they don't really one
doesn't flow into the oh, it's so poorly done. But if you watch those B movie,
stuff from the 70s, that's how I see the world here right now. So that is so B movie that it's
actually a refresher to show almost like a punctuation. You know what I mean? Not an
annoyance. Well, what's hilarious to me is the only thing I can think of, like, as soon as you
mentioned that is that that sound effect whenever they were going to show that he was
that's that whoever did that they had a pretty good handle on that. Yeah, they know what affects
the mind, right? It's like for now, commercials on television are designed to be more effective
on the mind if the people tune in and tune them out visually and audibly, whether it was walk away
from the TV, they're actually more effective than if you sat there and watched it. It's the way
it's structured now. And it's really not expensive to do. I mean, they're still using that silly
commercial on everything now. Because it was originally a broadcast television commercial.
But the ringing bells, we wish you a Merry Christmas was was a thing for what Hershey
kisses and they would do the thing where the Hershey kisses ring, but they've been playing
that. No, they got you. I've never heard. I didn't. Yeah, I'm not aware of it. I've never
know how to pick up. I'm good at tuning stuff out. Well, they stick that on my YouTube. Now
they stick that on if I go to anything pretty much. Yeah, I got commercial commercial everywhere
now. I don't get it at all. Oh, wow. I've been I've been married 21 years. I know how to tune
people out. Trust me. Yeah, I know. So yeah, it's called survival. Yeah. My survival instinct is to
flee as opposed to adapt, I guess. Yeah, that's that's probably so. And speaking of which,
it's the quote unquote season. And before we got on, it's like, do you think I'm actually
going to believe in a text that's held up by a bunch of Catholic pedophiles and a bunch of Jews
that run the publishing industry and all the media? What I mean by that is the cat the Vatican,
okay, you got all these forms of Christianity, it doesn't matter which form, it doesn't matter
what poop you stepped on, you stepped on poop, if you're right. Yeah, all of them. None of them
look, the caress guy in Waco that you know why they killed him? Because he was trying to start
another sect of Christianity that just was not approved by the Vatican. That's all they do to
you. Yeah, it's a branch. The branch Davidian was a literal branch off of another. And this is what
the problem is, if you try and see, you can go into business if you have a license, but you have
to have their license, their approval. Otherwise, if you try and put out your own shingle and just
declare yourself to be the arbiter of whatever, it doesn't matter if it's a religion or candle
making. If you do it without their permission, they're going to come they're going to come for
you. You got to you got to pay your taxes, right? Yeah. So okay. Anyway, well, they don't have to
pay taxes if they don't approve of you being in business. But right. So it doesn't matter if you're
one of those born again, you know, or, you know, they got, you know, the Chick-fil-a, I call it
chicken sandwiches, right? Oh, yeah. And because they're right. So it doesn't matter. You stepped
in it. Sorry. It's all right. Now the other thing, when I say Jews, I spell it with a j o o z. Okay,
so don't tell me I'm anti semitic, because I'm actually, quote, unquote, more Jewish
than they are, believe it or not, because you actually follow their laws.
And what's funny about that, you know, what cracks me up most is that I was reading a story this
week, and I want to throw this at you, because I'm sure you didn't see it. But you won't be
surprised at all. You've heard of Pornhub, right? I've seen it around. Yeah. Okay. Well,
I saw it once on a statistic. It's it's like, number like 20. And the if you think go look at
the top 100 websites in the world, I think it's up there. It has to be always right. It has been
like that, like pretty much since its launch. It was like the it has worked out in that industry.
This thing is a long lasting entity. Okay. Funny thing, I just read that the person who purchased
it recently, is a rabbi. Yeah, of course. And you know, and some people are going,
well, that doesn't make sense. And I'm going, I think it does. Anyway, you know,
one of its reverse psychology, the way you create population control and decrease the birth rate is
proliferation of sexual, not devious, but sexuality in society. So if you use an example,
if you go to very conservative societies, Islam, Mennonite, whatever, whatever, they don't have any
girly magazines or porn at all, openly. But guess if you go to knock on the door, how many kids you
got living here? I got seven. I got nine people that are into the sexualized societies. How many
children have you had one? We're going to we're going to skip that. Or we've been trying to have
a baby for five years. We gave up. How many children have you got to write? You go to the
ultra conservative countries. No. Oh, 12 children. You have nine children, minimum five. Right.
So you see at least five. Yeah, that's your evidence. Yeah. After four is when you get
started. So three is where you get started. Four is you actually have. And so so actually,
if you want to decrease the population or lower the birth rate, you increase sexualization
of the society and you have fewer children. Now, one of the reasons this works so well
is because people don't see it that way at all. Let's say if I have access to girly magazines
and porn and sex toys and all that and we have more to know, it's the ultra conservative societies
that have none of that that have the high. OK, enough with that. Common sense, though, because
look, if you have. OK, let's just assume comes factory. And so I disagree. It's not it's not
common. It's not common. Well, hold on, because you what I'm going to say is you can't assume that
it comes with this structure as a as as a human, whatever the shape is. It comes with it. Your
sexual stuff comes along with that. Right. Your urges. You need to do this. Your need to reproduce
comes with it now. No, no. But what I'm saying here, Chuck, I'm going to step on you for a
second. It's not common because it's the opposite. In other words, it's kind of like saying this
society has all this food and they're starving. And actually, that's true. Also, U.S. U.S. are
the most malnourished people in the world. But that's a fact, by the way. And they have the
most growing capability and caring capability to supply food. Right. So what I'm trying to say,
right. The richest people are actually the poorest people because it's right because
their credit. Right. If that if the credit notes represent a negative rate, a million in the bank
is minus a million. So it's all backwards. And that's what's uncommon about it. And yeah, but
it's not recent. It's like it's occurring always here. Right. You see. OK, so this is the way it's
always been. Is that. Yeah. And a very religious society doesn't mean that what people think it
means at all. It just means highly controlled, highly controlled, but not repressed, really,
because repression is different than control. Yes. I'm asking. No. OK.
We have to define that further, but I like defining something like,
oh, I don't know, the most common stuff. I don't think repression is common because remember,
let's take that further. The harshest dictator in the world is also government by the people,
for the people. Right. Just like the bullshit they tell you in the US government by the people,
for the people, by whatever. All governments are like that, no matter what it is,
because the people support them. If it doesn't matter which government it is,
if the people don't support it, it topples. It doesn't matter who it is in history. Right.
That's why the propaganda is really with you. But here's the thing. Well, actually,
without getting into saying here's the thing, politics aside there, one of the things we were
saying is, why did I bring this up? Do you think I'm actually going to believe believe in the in
the preserved texts? What's in there as such? You got to be crazy. It's going back to the Catholics
and the Jewish Judean community. It's put forward as the Bible. Right. OK. But I do get law from it.
And just like if you read a bullshit thing like the 9-11 Commission or the Warren Commission,
there's more being said by what's not being said than what is being said sometimes. And what is
being said actually is very highly inclusive if you know how to pick it out. Right. So I still
adhere to the biblical text as received as a communication. Right. If that makes a point.
But the biblical text itself, no, it's I don't believe anything in there as it's presented.
Even the books are out of order. Right. That's easy to that's easy to look up. You know,
they put books out of order. I mean, what your book does for three hundred years,
but it comes back. So it should be chronological. So no. So you have to be extremely discerning.
So we're going into this thing is some people are new. It's called the holiday season.
One of the things when it's brought up, the Christmas thing was brought up.
It's almost 50 percent of the time preface that it's not really the birth date of J.E.S.U.S.
and or no one really knows bullshit. You actually know it to the hour, to the day, to the week,
to the month and to the year by astronomical signal. And that would be found in Red Book
Revelation. And that day, let's do it backwards. It's around six o'clock at night on September,
on the day of 11, 3 B.C. Right. So that's why they had that big celebration on September 11th
in New York for him. So anyway, how do we. Yeah, this has been and I was one of the first people
other than Martin, Ernest Martin and someone else in the 1920s figured this out. I forgot his name.
It was one of these biblical scholars. I know this Christmas thing is bogus. We know exactly
according to the text. Now, it doesn't matter if you believe just like according to the text,
Pontius Pilate was the final authority in the say so. And Pontius Pilate refused it
by even directly refused. But he says, use your law, which is mosaic law, which is death by stoning.
Right. So. Right. So all this stuff now has nothing to do with belief. Do you know? Do you
know how to follow instructions? Now, any communication is a form of instruction. Right.
So it is. OK, when you some people think instructions, it means they have to physically
get into. Yeah, you will eventually. Something like the Bible demands or suggests physical action,
not just literary stuff. Like if you're reading Emerson, Moby Dick, there's not much physicality
you can do. Right. If you're reading something that tells you how to speak, how to think,
how to eat, how to keep time and all this other stuff. Yeah, it's going to it's going to be
an instruction book. Most books are most stuff worth reading is instruction. Oh, instructional.
So and people, by the way, hate that. They don't like they. Right.
Bring out a new device, make up a new device and put an instruction book in there and hand it out
to 100 people. And I don't think more than three or four people will actually look at the
instructions and follow them to get the device done. Only a very tiny percentage. So it's the
correlate again. Yeah. But that's what we kind of got into before we started recording. But what
I wanted to get into was what's in the chat. Got a couple of people with medical jargon or medical
background talking about doing certain things. I don't know if you recall reading the recent
chats, December 6th. Right. Well, I was just looking at them just before we went to air,
actually. And we're not on air, but you know what I mean? Just before we went to record.
And yeah, it's it's interesting what's what's coming up here. Like I said, we went from knife
sharpening over to this whole other thing. So it's it's fascinating. Let's see. The whole other
things. Yeah. Whole other things. But what was interesting is someone asked anybody applying
to the ether stuff or Greek speak stuff. Trevor James Constable stuff. I'm paraphrasing here,
Wilhelm Reich and such. And there was no real answer. But I asked, What do you mean? It's crazy,
like it's crazy results. So you can get I'd say I get into an asonic, I probably won't get into
it too much here, because it deserves its own introduction. Fair enough. But the whole thing
was basically another someone else chimed in in the chat, actually, recent comment about rapping
and all that what that's all about. Very simple. We can get probably another sonic, maybe the next
one, we'll get into the details of what was brought up in the chat. But the wrapping is very
simple thing. It's, it's in line with how things are made. Like, you know, Newton's watching the
apple fall, but he's looking up at the tree, he should have looked up a little higher and higher
looked at the sky, because what's really happening is the energies that are way above us are coming
in towards the direction of the earth and compressing things. And when compressing itself
first, and then itself becomes a thing, and then more things are compressed around it, everything's
basically hydrogen, compressed in certain energy is, you know, they're looking at the quantity,
you know, how could this element be three hydrogen, how could lithium be three hydrogens? It is,
it is actually, but the way it would put them together, it makes it it's the quality,
it's not just the numerics, the quantum, it's the quality. So everything is being compressed. So
when you compress it, and when you create enough material out of the ether by ether, in winding,
compressing towards itself, then those materials become a factor to create more materials, just
like when you make chocolate chip cookies, you grow the wheat, you make the flour, right, you grow the
sugar, the cane, you make the sugar or whatever, you grow the chocolate plant, you make the chocolate,
right. So and then with these products that are made by making these other things can come together
and make a new thing. And that's what a lot of these elements are, like, for example, platinum
might be considered as the finality of all metals and anything past platinum, gold and all that
other stuff is, is when it goes into a half life and decay. Okay, oh, I just gave a secret away
people are more than three sharpened pencils in their pocket, and sitting on a hot plate,
we'll figure it out. But we'll get into that to transmutation sometime. So everything is compression.
So how do you break up things you uncompressed and centrifugal pull them apart.
Right. So living body is under a state of compression in in winding, we say compressing,
it sounds uncomfortable. So in inward energy, when the body soul leaves and the body dies,
the centrifugal force, the outward force takes over the body starts to swell, and you get chemical
decomposition, right? Okay, so it's very simple. Now, on another level, on the same vein,
the body is completely contained and sealed. There's an opening a tunnel, like a tunnel through
the mountain. From the mouth to the anus, there is some certain ducts that go into all that direction,
you know, you see a duct and you have some brain that's in the roof of your mouth.
And then you have a cul-de-sac known as the lungs and basically the plumbing that leads
to a lot of the organs like the bladder and other things like that in the eye are basically ducts,
so cul-de-sacs again, right? So basically, something communicates the surface through a
duct. So the expansion that we see with a body once the spirit leaves, is not because of the
expansion of the internal pieces, like there's gas that we know the energy, it's purely no,
it's the quality of the energy. So it's like energetic reaction. Okay. Yeah, what is the
difference? You can take, you know, a flashlight battery is not included, right? Right? You put the
battery in and the battery is another item, but it's how things are set up. And it's the energy
of the battery, not the battery itself, because you can have a battery that looks perfectly good.
And guess what? It's dead, right? Yeah, right. Gotcha. Okay. So you put it on a scale, it weighs
exactly the same. You measure it, it weighs exactly the same. Okay, feels the same, smells the same.
So what's the difference? The energy's gone. Right. Okay. Okay. So, but about this, okay,
the reason why you're bringing this up is because in the chat, they were talking about wounds and
how to deal with them, and you apply compression in one way or another. Yeah, let's give a little,
let's give a little more tidbit, and then that'll be, then we'll get, then I'll structure it so we
can get a little more into addressing, you'll be able to study it, maybe partake a little better
in the, in some of the questions that could arise from the comments that were made. Sure. Something,
one of the things made was ozonating some ferromagnetic material, which is basically
ferromagnetic is like steel wool or wire mesh or magnetite, whatever. Okay. A magnet would stick to
normally, by the way, everything is magnetic, it just doesn't display the reaction that iron does,
right? Because if, if something is really not magnetic, guess what doesn't exist in a physical
form, even a gas. So, so one thing that was brought up there, you know, I guess the ferromagnetic
material ozonated and all that is to induce stimulation and all that. Now, let's just do a
snippet out of Wilhelm Reich. He had this discovery in some of his writings, he included, it's called
bionds. And what that meant was when he took material like quartz, stone, granite, and he's
sterilized it, triple sterilized and added some water and some sterile mixtures of like a starch,
sterile starch. He noticed that there were small little round blue corpsical cell looking things
that formed around the stone and broke off and became living things off of the sterile material.
And he called those bionds and it's usually giving off of a slight blue hue. Now, when you have a
general, let's say you have a general condition that you know, you're going to do some Greek
speak compression, wrapping and all that. And you're going to incorporate bandages or other,
you know, let's say bandages, right? Because typically that's what you'd be doing and pads.
What I suggest you do is after the immediate care, get yourself a pot of boiling water. And
I'm presuming that the bandages are not synthetic material. Most synthetic materials can handle it
and get the water to a simmer. You could have a little baking soda in it or not
and dip your bandages in there. Then ring them out in the boiling water just for a minute or two.
And then dry the ring them out when they cool off and then put them in a plastic bag in the freezer.
So they freeze solid. And when they're frozen solid, let them fall out and put them back in
boiling water. Repeat that process two or three times. So the material that goes from a boiling
water, the bandage to a freezer, back to boiling water, back to a freezer, back to boiling water,
dried off and then wrapped. You could do all that in three hours, by the way, right? Because
a thin bandage will freeze very quickly. Even in a poor rental apartment, freezer will work.
You don't need a medical freezer or something that's highly efficient like what I'm using.
So what I would suggest is this will allow the material, even though it's slightly different
from the experiments that showed granite relieving this, all material will relieve it. So the actual
bandage itself, once it's formed to the area that you're trying to treat, will start releasing these
bionds after it's been stimulated back and forth several times. And those bionds induce growth.
Tremendously. Okay. Yeah. So, uh, I wasn't aware of this. Okay. This is new to me.
Well, yeah. Yeah. Well, good. Uh, that's, that's the purpose of doing this. So,
so that's a very simple thing. And all this can be qualified by the way, and quantified. If you've
got a good enough microscope, you can see these little things. Of course, if you're looking for
a faint blue light, you shouldn't have the lights turned on all the way, right? You turn the lights
off, right? And once you're lighting the slide, you use a very indirect lighting. Use a mirror.
Don't put a bulb. I find a lot of people still, they, they, they light these devices with a
direct lamp. You want to use indirect lighting, like a mirror, right? Just like the moon mirrors,
the sunlight changes the quality of the light. And we put filters on the mirror. So yeah,
it gets a little more fine tuning, but that's why we do a Greek speak.
Okay. And you'll see this blue hue if you do this, because it'll be from the bionds actually
forming. Coming off the material that you're viewing. Yes. And it's very subtle. Depends
on the magnification. I find that anything over 400 magnification is not required, but anything
between 150 and 400 is fine. All right. All right. Well, this is very interesting. And these
encourage growth. So what you're telling me is if you have like, say some damaged skin,
this could assist in the natural repair that occurs. Yeah. Yeah. But look, if you have
breaking your skin and you throw a paper towel on there or something you find under your car
seat from a napkin from McDonald's from three years ago and some electrical tape real tight.
Yeah. That'll work really well to anything. Just you got to tighten it up. Look, let's just finish
this one off. Just on this note, the purpose of the bodies are layer and layers is to allow pressure
mediation between the external environment and the inside of the body. What else does that?
A bicycle tire, a car tire, airplane tire, right? Sure. That is also designed to do the same thing.
The environment, the pressure and conditions inside of a tire when it's inflated is quite different
and then the external environment. And also one of the tires jobs is to keep that pressure
contained and maintained. The body's job is to do that as well. Right now, the body also gets
affected by external temperature like the tire does, though, right? Because, yeah, of course,
temperature, humidity, pressure, elevation, magnetism, all that.
And everything that exists contained now, that's an interesting statement there. Everything,
if it doesn't have magnetism, it doesn't exist, which basically means that what you're telling
me is the often ignored characteristic in all things is its magnetic properties one way or
another. It may not be the obvious magnetic properties that we're accustomed to thinking
of as magnetism, where you see attraction between the metal and the magnet, you know,
this kind of thing. Iron, iron, metal, ferrous. We've just been limited to ferrous. Yeah,
ferrous first, which is iron. So yeah, but everything is magnetic. Actually,
even within the stupid academia, they do break it down to paramagnetic, ferromagnetic,
and then diamagnetic, which would be resistant. In order to resist it, you have to provide an
antagonistic energy, which is in the opposite direction, but literally are the same.