Rated Y, 135.
So here we are, Greek.
And how are you doing today?
You're yawning a bit before we started recording.
Yeah, I had dinner and just fell out.
I've got a cat on my shoulder.
I'm walking around.
I'm going to go outside and have a smoke and we'll continue this discussion with a cat
on my shoulder.
He just has to be on my shoulder.
Well, that's cool.
I mean, was he looking to relax?
Were you looking to relax?
Is there forced relaxation here?
What's going on?
Yeah.
All of it.
That's how animals die.
You know, a lot of things that people mistake, well, I shouldn't say mistake completely,
association with animals.
You know, the animal's so friendly, likes me.
It's actually domination, domination tactics, you know, a lot of times when cats rubbing
up against you, it's, it's dumb, it's, it's marking you, right?
Right.
So yeah.
Yeah.
We've got some stuff going.
Didn't you bring up a super moon?
Yeah.
I'm going to bring that up in a second.
But just since you bring up the animals real fast, I mean, cats and dogs seem different
in this way.
Right.
Because cats, I believe in, you know, as soon as you say domination, I go, yeah, and you're
right about, oh, he's so friendly.
No, he doesn't love you.
He's just making sure that you're his, but nobody does.
Well, no.
No, they do love you.
Actually, I felt more affection from cats and dogs.
Really?
Well, they do.
They both have a tremendous affection, I should say, that they just show it differently.
And I'm more into pussy than into dogs.
So anyway, well, maybe I'm more doggy style.
What can I say?
But the thing is, they just seem to be more of the affectionate type to me.
I don't know if that's just a personal thing or I mean, are they more submissive than cats?
Generally speaking, you think?
No.
Well, I also view dogs.
I was I learned from a young age, if you have an unemployed dog, it's not going to be a
happy dog.
Any dog.
They always need a job.
They have to have something to do.
So I'm not for the dogs in the New York City apartment kind of thing, you know, you got
to have some property and it's not just a friend that you got to they have to have
a job.
Otherwise, they get whatever, you know, not always, you know, not always, but typically
well, my little dogs, they have to warn us when people come near the property or on the
property.
Right.
Yeah.
That's part of their job.
And, you know, but but I don't know, Buster is super affectionate, though.
He likes to you think he's just marking me when he wants to, like, get up on my leg and
stuff.
Of course.
OK.
I was just curious.
Anyway.
No, you did mention the super moon.
And because I mentioned it to you before we started recording.
And the thing is, and people talk about this, oh, it's a super moon.
There's a special moon coming.
It's extra.
But it's so funny.
You said something to me right before we recorded.
I'd love for you to repeat because, I mean, people are so stupid that, you know, the word
month.
What does it sound like?
It sounds like.
Yeah.
Well, anything they have to say, they meaning the conventional society is foolish.
They even have a ridiculous thing where the blue moon, you have two moons, two full moons
in one month.
What?
Yeah.
But that doesn't make any sense.
You have to move on.
Your month starts.
You have two months and one month.
Great.
Right.
Oh, my gosh.
It's so ridiculous.
You know, this leads into a lot of things.
I think I want to bring up someone mentioned in chat.
So the moon thing's pretty short because there there's no comparison or you can contrast.
But you can't compare what the norm is.
The regular people have in their societies of many modern culture.
It's all Western culture, even the Chinese.
Right.
And Asian.
And what's interesting about the Asian culture, it's all about vanity.
People don't understand that, you know, I can't stand people from Asia because of the
vanity.
I mean, I love Asian culture.
I love you.
Do enjoy.
I love the food.
I love the traditional ways.
But the current like modern people remember, I'm going to be my 60th year next month.
And I still when I was when I was young, some old wise man told me, you know, you're getting
old when you walk into a room and everybody in the room is younger than you.
And a lot of people, you know, start you hear about them dying.
Right.
Anyway.
So the average age is around 30 years old.
Right.
And it's very immature because they were captured.
Their mentality was captured, you know, 30 years ago or 20 years ago.
Very, very bad.
So the vanity of the Asian people, I just can't stand.
And it's not them.
It's not them, meaning the 30 somethings or the 20 somethings or whatever.
Even before I give you I lived with an Asian family, they were Indonesian Chinese for about
two weeks when I was 17 years old.
And the man cooks, the dad cooks, everyone waits for the dad.
He comes in, breaks out the wok, makes a dish, a vegetable stir fry.
Everybody gets rice.
And by the way, they eat with tablespoons, not chopsticks, because you could scoop a
lot better.
So the chopsticks are for scooping.
Tablespoon is a much more efficient they spoon the rice in their mouth.
They still have chopsticks.
And everyone picks the entree from the center.
You don't get like your entree, your side and all that in the same plate.
You just have a bowl of rice.
OK, make a long story short.
This was a two bedroom apartment with like nine people in me.
And and right when it came to bedtime, everyone knew their place.
It was an L couch or three people slept along the L couch to two people slept in the bed.
Two people slept on the floor near the bed.
The two people slept in the back foyer.
Everyone found a place to sleep.
Right.
You just didn't want to block the bathroom.
OK.
And that's how everybody lived.
It was, you know, now the aunt that lived there worked in a sweatshop at minimum wage.
And one day when I happened to be there, she comes home and she's so excited that she bought
a Gucci handbag.
A Gucci handbag.
OK.
Now, I don't know.
What is a Gucci handbag?
Oh, thousands now.
But then it was at least nine hundred or a thousand.
Yes.
There you are.
Five hundred dollars.
That's like a week's pay at a decent job kind of bag, at least.
And some people.
Three months.
Yeah.
Probably a month.
More than a month's pay.
So she could walk around.
She's poor.
Off the boat.
Are you right?
And it's what most important thing for her was not to get her and her daughter on a place.
It may be a better paying job, but to get a Gucci bag.
And at that point, I started paying more attention to this culture.
And I was like, oh, the vanity is unbelievable.
Right.
Because you're going to go.
Yeah.
Because you're willing to invest money that you could spend on a whole month's rent into
a bag.
We don't have to explain it.
Just think about it.
Just think about what I just said.
It's no different than in the ghetto.
The ghetto.
Right.
You buy a two thousand dollar car, you touch it up with spray paint from the or a thousand
dollar car or you inherit a car.
You touch it up with spray paint.
That's close enough for me.
It's hardware.
But you go out and spend four thousand dollars on spinning rims.
Those days are up.
Do you need to explain anything there?
It's vanity.
It's pure.
So in other words, the vanity has outdone.
And there's a there's a lesson here for the current vanity, because the current vanity
is that we're technologically advanced.
Why are we having these problems yet?
They're dumb or they're doornails.
Right.
It's also it's also akin to the you know, in any neighborhood anywhere, actually, not
just the ghetto with the spinning rims, but any neighborhood anywhere.
You got five hundred dollar car with a two thousand dollar stereo.
Right.
You don't have to explain it.
Wherever you tell this is happening to you should be able to see it's vanity.
I've kind of spelled it out.
But the same with the moons, the same with what everyone is talking about out in the world
here.
There's one or two more items I want to cover.
Let's cover the dentistry real quick.
Someone brought up dentistry.
I saw it in the chat.
It's funny because I rebuilt an upper and lower partial just the other day.
And my advice to people doing dentistry is learn how to communicate in it, because you're
going to need the tools of the trade and the language of the trade.
Right.
So there's actually enough classes and courses online you can zoom through and have a better
better part of an undergraduate degree in dentistry.
You can do it on your own.
And dentistry is amazing in that it is one of those things that, you know, how you talk
about everything was already done 150 years ago, it is one of those things that literally
the tools haven't changed even there is, you know, the same tools that, say, Doc Holliday
used when he was a gunfighter.
He was a dentist.
The same tools he used are virtually the same things they use today.
Yes, they have a few motors and whatever.
But aside from that, it's about distraction.
OK, it's one other thing, because I had a medical doctor, recent conversation being
out in the wild.
And the medicine that you have right now, it's very clear what's going on.
If it was up to the elite, the people control the world, they would have no medical offered
to you at all, at all, die in the street.
If that were the case, people would get together and form their own groups and actually do
research and actually figure out how things work, much like we discuss here and actually
have incredible medicine, incredible, you know, the stuff where you can regrow parts
of the body and rapid healing and all that.
So instead, what they do is they have this medical show, all fiction, universities very
well endowed, billions and billions in hospitals.
And the state, the administrative state, basically has laws.
Oh, you can't do it.
They only they can do it.
OK, that means that they're restricting it and they're closing it down, just like education,
academia.
Right.
Any all the school, any school that gets federal funding has to give all the bullshit.
Right. Which is all of them.
There are schools that are not federally funded.
But unfortunately, the people that try to operate those, just like people who homeschool.
Right. Where did they get their education?
Most likely from a federal school.
So when they homeschool or do a non-federally funded school, guess what?
They're going to teach the same shit that's being taught in the right.
Yeah. Unfortunately, I don't school.
So it doesn't make much of a difference.
Again, again.
Right. And I have done the homeschooling, by the way, and I try to change it up a bit.
But honestly, a lot of the stuff I wind up teaching is, in fact, the stuff that I learned
from. Yeah, I know.
Which doesn't work.
Yeah. You can teach it and you can show it, but tell them it's not part of the teaching.
Right. There's a difference.
Like really, math is one of those things that I don't mind using because it's you know, if
it makes sense, it makes sense.
The math works. Even the math is screwed up because they're not putting the emphasis on how
the math is practical.
They're putting the emphasis on a syllabus.
Well, see, that's the thing.
I'm trying to say, look, you can use this to do this with it.
You know what I mean? When I do math with my with Frankie, I do it so that it's like,
look, this is this and you can actually apply it with this.
You know what I mean? You can measure this.
This is this long and this is why it makes sense.
You got to fit this into this.
You know, I try to apply some practical use to it, not just here's a number.
Here's a sheet. Here's the order you do it.
You know, hopefully if I were to do homeschooling or non-fairly funded school, I would
present what's being taught to everyone else as a presentation, but not as the teaching.
There's a difference. And however, that's couch back to dentistry.
The thing I would advise on dentistry is you have the the hardest part of the body, you
know, that's on the out, you know, in the mouth, the tooth near the softest part of the
body, which is the soft tissue of the the lingual, you know, the cheek, you know, all
that. Right. Just all everything going on in the mouth.
Tongue, teeth, soft.
OK. Yes. Very, very, very soft.
And for surface area, it's the softest surface area.
It's exposed next to the hardest.
So so what my point here, why are you saying that?
Because one of the most basic things and fundamental things in dentistry is an
extraction. When a tooth, it's very rare that a tooth should be reconstructed or
rehabilitated. It's better to have them just pulled out.
Because there's enough plastic so you can do partials now if you have a grouping.
But and the partials, if they're done right, which they're never done right, I'm
probably make the best partials in the world.
Partials like a denture.
You know, if you like, you lose your front teeth.
I can make one and it looks like your natural teeth.
As a matter of fact, I have I have front I have upper and lower partials right now.
I only have eight teeth left in my mouth, but I have a full set of teeth in my mouth.
Right. But only eight of them are left that are mine.
And all the other 24 are ones that I've made and put in and gotten and modified.
And it's funny when I see my dentist friend, he takes the partials and he shows
them to everyone in the lab or whoever's around.
And they're like, wow, those are pretty good.
OK, so what's the deal?
He says, well, he made these.
And they're like, well, you know, you have to be you have to understand that it's a
form of artistry. Right.
And I do notice that good dentists are also like good sculptors, you know, meaning like
sculptors, the people who carve shit out of wood and marble and stone.
Right. Right. Because you have to form something that looks good and works well.
But my advice to that, again, is you have the hardest part of the tooth and the
softest part of the mouth.
And an extraction is usually the way to go with with most cases, especially if you
have what's called mobility, a loose tooth.
You know, we're talking about your adult teeth now.
We got loose. You have to extract that.
And then cleaning out the PDL, PDL, the periodontal ligament doesn't always have to be
cleaned out in the socket, depending on the mobility.
If you have three or four millimeter mobility in the tooth, the PDL is probably gone.
But if it's a loose tooth, it's very painful.
You're going to have to clean the socket out.
I've gone over this before.
Now, my point, my advice again is that when you get into that soft area known as the
mouth, all around, up, down, inside, back, front, very soft.
And you have something called a hard tooth.
When you're going to do an extraction requires a good amount of energy and strength to
get that out. You have to wiggle back and forth, just like remember when you were a
child and you wiggled the tooth before you pulled it out.
You know, your baby teeth, I call them, right?
Right. Well, same thing with an adult.
But you don't want to be wiggling back and forth all day.
You got to go one, two, three out.
And it's really tough.
You got to have. It's kind of like those when you get to take a shvitz, you know, a
bath, a steam shower and you get a massage.
If you walked in there and a Russian bathhouse and it's time to get rubbed down and
you see some skinny, scrawny 90 pounder, that's not going to be a good massage.
You want someone that's two and a quarter, at least six foot, right, to give you a rub
down. Right. You know what I mean?
So you're going to have to find that energy.
If you're going to be doing extractions, you can't baby pussyfoot around.
It's one, two, three out.
And it's a lot. It's hard.
It's hard. It's like imagine pulling out a kernel of corn off the cob with your finger,
right? Not biting into it.
You know, are you strong enough to do that?
Or yeah, it's it's pretty tough.
It's pretty tough. And the reason I'm saying this is because you want to you want to
inflict as little pain.
It's called torture, as little pain as possible on who you're working on.
And the best thing is just one, two, boom out.
The hardest thing to learn in dentistry, if even if you're artistic or not, is doing an
extraction well.
Right. And that's it.
Other than that, it's fine, because once you get the teeth out of the mouth, there's
plenty of easy ways.
There are enough kits sold on Amazon that you can have a professional, semi-professional
dentist office set up at home for less than five hundred bucks right now.
Now, I'm at an unfair advantage because I know someone who's a dentist.
Very so often, his wife will say, oh, you know, I'm not going to mention names.
He left these tools for you.
You know, he's not using them anymore.
Come over. Maybe you could use some of these, you know, as a kind of relationship.
You know what I mean? It's not fair.
And yeah, I could roll with any dentist.
It's no big deal.
So yeah, and also there's plenty of topical antiseptics, not antiseptics,
anesthetics, anesthetics right now that they're horrible tasting.
But they get they get pretty deep into the tissue that if you didn't, instead of going
with a hypo into the into the under under to get to the nerve directly, a lot of the
topical ones in most cases will it'll feel like your nerve is numbed out.
So in other words, what I'm trying to say, get into dentistry because it's been
because we have tap water and sewer water separated.
And dentistry is why people are living longer, not because of any other reason.
So, yeah, I chose that because you can literally say you can extend someone's
life. If you're living with rotten teeth in your mouth, you're not going to live as
long as if you had them not in your mouth.
And no one has to be walking around toothless because you can you can make your
own dentures, your own parcels.
Right. I call them parcels even when it's a full because you need anyway, it's
another we can do it. I should do a dental seminar, shouldn't I?
That would be great. Yeah.
If you did one solid one.
Yeah, that would be good.
And just to show the do's and don'ts.
But you still have time before everything collapses, it seems.
Maybe, maybe not.
But, you know, something like when they did the COVID debacle, a lot of dentists
weren't seeing people. So you might have wanted to be able to do some dentistry.
Right. On a lockdown.
Right. And it's going to be one of those things where if you've got a big, major
problem, it's going to be an essential, you know, last thought of, but definitely
essential service to keeping people alive.
Yeah. The other thing I want to mention, I got messages from someone I consider a
friend and his one of his children had sprained an ankle
and he was messaging me.
I didn't get the message for four hours or so about wrapping it.
And they put cold on it.
And he was very unsure about he knows about the Greek speaking, the compression.
So my suggestion on that is when you hear me make up something, not
make up, but bring up something like compression on an injury.
And it's so radically different of an approach than what you see out there.
You have to meditate on that. So when the opportunity comes up to do it, you're ready
to go. And, you know, if you meditate on something that you've heard,
you can be you can for the first time, it'll be 90 percent if you've thought about
it. But if you haven't thought about, oh, you heard this or whatever, everybody runs
for an ice pack and you're like, well, rapid type, but I'm not sure I really think
about it. It's not going to work.
So. Right. So you have to really meditate and think that that I can't do for you.
I presented several things on great specifics and they're so simple.
I just keep being redundant, basically wrapped towards the heart.
Now, it was an ankle.
So in this case, what I messaged back was start wrapping from the middle of the foot
or wrap towards the heart, you know, back up towards the ankle.
But don't double back.
You ever see someone's ankle being wrapped?
They start at the middle of the foot, they wrap up to the ankle and they cross over
the ankle and they double back down and finish at the bottom of the foot.
Right. Usually. Right.
Don't do that, because when you wrap double back and go down towards the foot, what
are you doing? You're going against the heart, away from the heart and the energy
flow. You just change the whole thing.
So what do you do there?
You have two bandages or, you know, what you do is you wrap from the middle of the
foot towards the heart, which is up towards the ankle, up to be up towards the
calf. You stop there, tie it off, cut the bandage or get another bandage and start
again. Your second layer starts again at the middle of the foot.
That's one thing. When you go towards the heart, you cannot double back the same
with the wrist or the hand.
You're tempted. You ever see how a hand is wrapped?
They go back over the wrist and they double back again.
But when you double back, you're going away from the heart.
It's very critical that it's all motion and intent is towards the heart.
Big difference. Yeah.
So, yeah. And you have to do it immediately.
Very, very fast because you're living in a society of morons and you have a choice
to do what everybody else does or do something a little better.
Right. So that's what you have to think of, you know.
And but if you haven't meditated on it, practice means gone over it.
It's like rumination, right? Chewing the cut.
What I mean by meditate is when you hear something go over in your mind over and
over and over, even if you have to go back and replay the past minute a hundred
times, do it and think about it a hundred different ways or think about it for a
few days. Make notes on it.
That's meditation. The same thing.
It doesn't have to be constant new, new, new feed or stream of information.
Just go over the same thing because you'll see it differently over time, just like
it's. So let's say I did a sonic when it had one and a half minutes on wrapping
something tight, go back and replay that 10, 20, 30, 40, 50 times and think about it
for a few days. What will happen is by the second day, it'll be like, you know, when
you watch a movie the second time, you're like, I don't remember seeing this.
Right. Right. So it'll settle.
And that's what meditation is.
Well, I did that when I asked you about my hand, actually, because I had the same
thought, too. And when I did it immediately and I said, wait a minute, this is wrong
because I'm going back the other way.
Yeah. Don't back. That's that's what makes it so strange.
Yeah. And I took the bandage away and I said, you know what?
Let me think about this. And I did exactly what you said is I went back over in my
mind and said, no, it's supposed to go in that one direction.
If I go this way, I'm going in the opposite direction.
So that's why I do that. You don't do that.
You don't do that, does it?
Yeah. Yeah. With my hand, because you told me to start with the fingertips and then to
go toward. Yeah, right.
Towards the heart, towards the heart.
So it could be any part of the body.
Now, why does I think of let's just let's create some justification real quick.
So whether you're in real life, you see someone yourself or in the movies or on TV,
someone gets their nose punched or slammed and they what do they do?
They put their hands over it.
What do they cover? They press on.
They're not really pressing it, but they're covering it.
Right. Which is right.
More and more pressure than it would have been if they did.
Someone bumps an elbow.
Ouch. What do they do?
They reach over with their opposite arm and hand.
And what do they do?
Naturally, you hold it.
Yeah. You're always holding something.
That's the body's intelligence telling you, squeeze it, push, put pressure on it, even
if just touching it is more compression than not touching it.
So your body is telling you to do that.
But when you get that, you understand that it's a natural reflex because that's what you
should do. How do we advance that?
And that's what the Greek speak compression stuff on wounds is.
I've had I had an injury a week ago for a left forefinger and wrist.
And I was like, oh, this is really messed up.
This is going to hurt. It's going to be sore.
And as I'm saying this to myself, I'm walking around looking for some electrical tape and
paper towels. And I wrapped the paper towel first on the electrical tape, super tight
and paper towel you do.
So, you know, it doesn't the you want a bond breaker so that the adhesive doesn't stick to
your skin. Yeah, right.
Yeah. And it was 15 minutes.
My finger turned blue and my hand was numb.
Perfect. Unwrapped it and immediately wrapped it again.
Not as tight, not as tight.
After three hours, the third after the third time, which was very loose.
But that night I just, you know, barely felt a soreness.
And the next day it was healed, where if I had not, I would still be feeling it if I had
not done that. You know, most people say, well, it's not bad.
It'll get it'll get better.
No, do go ahead and practice the compression on the small stuff and watch stuff that you
expected a scratch or a cut.
I got cut by a sharp piece of metal on my forearm.
I was like, ah, it's not deep.
It's it's a cut.
Well, it's all right.
And I'm like, no, wrap that shit.
And I wrapped it and the next day it was healed almost completely.
Right. And that was the other thing about the compression is that I didn't do it right
away. I told you I had this problem for a little while.
So now I'm thinking to myself, remember, you had said and I remember you saying, look,
since you let it sit for a while, it's going to take now a while to pull it back.
If I had gotten on it right away, then I could have answered it right away and pulled back
the problem right away for this numbers.
Right. Right. Make a big deal of doing it when it's really minor.
So you could see how miraculous it is.
So when something major, you're confident.
And I've done really bad injuries that way.
A third degree.
What do you call when the bone comes through the tibia?
Yeah. And it was a laceration and a broken tibia.
But I'm saying compound fracture.
Yeah. But if you walked around with this problem now for a while and you didn't address
it, now it's going to take longer to address.
Oh, you couldn't walk around with a compound.
So I'm not a compound fracture.
I'm saying the thing that I had is that I realized also there's a time issue here where
if you get to it right away, then you can get it back right away.
But if you don't, it's going to take more time.
Yeah. That was something. Yeah.
In other words, you don't need to call the the body has its internal paramedics, ambulance
and emergency room. You don't want to activate that.
Right. Because that'll get swelling and it'll create a whole other.
Then what it'll do is say, oh, it's injured.
We need to separate from the rest of the body.
So go ahead and create some edema, send some plot, a lot of plasma there, get it to
swell up so it doesn't mess up any other part of the body.
You don't want that at all.
You want to tell yourself that nothing, everything's fine, you know, and you're on your
way. But yeah, yeah, it works really, really well.
And things that are inside the body.
Also, I've gotten messages.
Some person had some skin manifestations.
And the first thing is like, great, I'm glad it's on your skin, because if it was on the
internal organs, it would be much more difficult.
Right. So in society, we have stigmas of people that have skin manifestations.
But it's actually a blessing in a way that you're getting all that manifestation on the
surface and not in your liver or in your kidneys.
Right. Or in your brain.
Right. I mean, that's that's a little more harder.
It's much slower to recover from.
So when on the skin, you can actually do more topical things and you can monitor it.
You know, you could in other words, you can have what they call abnormal tissue growing
all over your liver and you don't know it.
You just feel slight discomfort and you never know it sometimes.
But if you have abnormal tissue on your skin, you're going to see it right away and do
something about it. Right.
Right. So it's actually a positive thing.
And then you can address it that way.
Yeah, there's so much to do.
I need to do a medical seminar somehow.
And actually, I think it's something that needs to be done in manual form, because
meditating on it with the audio is good.
But it may be having something on in text also.
That's where I need a publicist or someone because I'm like, there's so many things
that I'm working on that for me to sit down and write, you know, I guess I could do
an hour a day, you know, before I retire, let's say for the day, make sure I just
spend an hour, I guess.
I don't know. I'm not making excuses.
It can be done. But you should have something in writing like a bullet points at
least. And then combined with the audio, there might be.
I'm not going to. I'm not supposed to say this, but I'm going to say it.
There might be somebody working on a compilation of Greek speak stuff, which is
around twelve thousand thirteen thousand pages.
I went to an author's club one day, by the way, here in town on a meet up group
because authors clubs are not a book reading, but all were authors meet.
Right. Because it's all different subjects.
There was a retired psychiatrist, retired fireman, retired engineers, people from all
walks of writing books about whatever bullshit.
Right. Yeah. And they were like, oh, how do I get my manuscript down from one
hundred fifty thousand words?
I'm like, oh, yeah, OK.
How many pages is that? Four hundred pages or something, you know, three hundred
pages. I said, what are you?
All right. Well, who are you and what are you doing?
I said, well, I got what have you got written?
I said, I've got eleven thousand eight hundred something pages.
They thought I said words. I said, oh, that's easy.
I said pages. And they're like, what?
Who the hell's got eleven thousand twelve thousand pages of transcripts?
Right. Nobody that I know of.
I mean, I'm sure I'm sure they're out there, but, you know, to to publish.
But doing and this is the part that I'm not supposed to talk about is the possibility
of having all that accessed via an A.I.
search. So you say, you know, compression healing in the A.I.
searches is twelve thousand pages and brings up everything I've said about that
subject. Right. Is it the same guy who's working on the master manuscripts?
A master. Yeah, sort of, sort of.
It may never happen. I'm not supposed to talk about it, really.
But I kind of did because I'm seeing the necessity of it, because I think majority
of this kind of the salient Greek topics are you won't find anywhere else, which is
kind of pathetic because it's so basic.
Well, the thing that'll make it a great tool is a searchable index, which is exactly,
you know, right. But a very good of, you know, one that's very pertinent, not general,
because, you know, you search it and you got thirty six pages.
No, I mean, like spot on.
That's where. Yeah, no, I don't know.
A very something like that.
Yeah. Very specific.
Well, look, there's a difference between an index and a well done index, too.
So, I mean, an index that's really searchable and easy, you know, very accessible
and very specific when you search for specific things.
So that that's the that's the key of it.
Transcripts are nothing anymore.
They they're automated at this point.
You know, that's what I mean.
Yeah. Yeah. But if you're a good speaker, it should read well.
Oh, no, definitely.
But it doesn't mean that you can't make it even better with the search based on the
indexing, like I said. So I keep using that word.
Why? OK, anyways.
So anything else you want to cover here?
So I think we're good. OK, excellent.