Hey, hey, Rated Y, and 208, anyway, Sonic
Event, and here it is, Greek, you know,
only feedback I got this week was about
dog food and organs and stuff, but, and
they wanted to talk about that, sometimes you
can get it for free at certain grocery
stores, other places they sell it to you,
good quality, etc.
But very important, that organ meat, why?
Because it makes the system work for that
kind of animal, and which kind of animal
are we talking about?
Generally, people have dogs and cats, and am
I wrong on any of this yet?
What's going on?
Well, they typically eat the organ meat first,
the muscle, just muscle meat is toxic.
Let me give you an example, when we
enjoy steak and stuff, you know, people, generally
enjoy steak.
People don't, let's say I'm going to get
beef or pork or chicken or lamb, they
don't understand that that's just muscle.
People don't think of it that way, right?
The organ meat is really where it's at,
all along.
That's another discussion, really, it's a big discussion,
why, but typically when zoos were first started
and they fed the animals muscle meat, they
got sick, and they needed the organ meat.
Also, if you study them in the wild,
you'll see how the pack of lions or
whatever always howls out the carcass first, right,
before they eat the legs and arms, right,
you notice?
So yeah, so yeah, I wanted to get
into the human body because it's very important,
and also I want to see if I
could eke out some support on it, because
it's very important.
In other words, the more I study, let's
just say the more I've been studying, I've
been studying the human body since the 1980s,
early 80s, so it might sound cocky, but
I know a lot more than any doctor
I've ever met, a lot more, it's scary,
it's just like I know a lot more
than any attorney I've ever met, a lot
more, not just a little, and it scares
me to the point where these industries, medical
and legal industries, let's just say medical and
legal, are thriving, and they're so busy, right?
The police, wait a minute, wait a minute,
the police state is thriving behind you, I'm
sorry.
Yeah, you hear it?
But anyway, I'm going to go on the
other side, there's a fire, but I can
smell it, there's a fire somewhere, you know
what I mean?
Oh, it's a fire, okay, no, no, no,
it's just because it was so loud, it
was drowning you out, right, I needed to
interrupt you.
Oh, it should have been, okay, but this
is what I was saying, the people are
going there, and what are they going for?
What are they getting?
Sorry.
It's unbelievable, no, it's fine, no, it's fine,
yeah, I'm sheltered right now.
Yeah, now it's way better.
You know that smell when a house is
burning, it's kind of like paint, have you
ever stripped paint or smelled burning paint?
Oh, absolutely.
That's the most, and a roofing material, when
you, yeah, I can always tell what's burning,
whether it's a car, or a house, or,
you know.
There's certain kinds of plastics that I find
absolutely suffocating when people are burning them, you
know, like they throw them in one of
their fire pits or whatever, and it's like,
oh my God, what did you just throw
in there?
Yeah, well, they have a distinctive smell, it's
just like spectrography, you know, when they burn
things in a laboratory, the spectrum of light
that it gives off is an ID for
the element.
So anyway, these industries are busy, and people
are going to them and thanking them for
their profession, and they don't know anything at
all.
And they're functioning, the society's functioning like this,
it's kind of like, what a planet of
dumbasses, right?
It's just dumb-ass-ville all the way,
all the way, all the way.
So what it is possible to do is
form an elitist group that teaches a more
elite human, like better, elitist meaning elite, just
what the word means, to go and give
hints and bring it down to the DIY
level.
I've been, like, I was looking at surgery
procedures, thorax, stuff like that, for the past
month, and I'm like, you know, you only
need like 10 days of training to do
that, to become a surgeon.
There's not much to know, right?
You have to understand, you know, the dermis,
you have to understand, like, you know, you
got to get through the skin, let's just
be practical.
You got to go through, you got to
enter the body somehow, orthoscopy's great, you know,
you make a hole and you send a
probe in there, and then tools that are
accompanied the size of the probes, you don't
have to cut someone open, right?
But even in trauma, trauma's completely different, but
the surgery, I mean, I can teach someone,
train someone to do surgery in less than
a week.
The hardest part about the surgery is you
have to have lightning-fast reflexes, right, because
everyone's different, right?
You know, in other words, you can open
someone up and there's not a drop of
blood, and the same exact procedure, it's just
like gobs and gobs everywhere, right?
It's just like they're bleeding to death, right?
Oh, yeah, no, even the smallest tiny incision,
I've actually experienced it where I figure the
same type of incision, I would get that,
you know, okay, it's going to be a
simple leak, no problem, I should be able
to dab it real quick and get it
out of there, and they spring like a
freaking garden sprinkler on me.
Yeah, that's a release of yin, and what
I'm saying is, okay, everything has to be
combined.
So you know how they do prep before
surgery?
They give you a sheet of paper, don't
eat, don't drink, don't, right?
Yeah.
Well, we're going to have a list of
things to eat and condiments.
Mm-hmm.
We'll get into it.
I'm just going to bounce around a little
bit over here, okay?
So you know how the body, the food
goes through the intestinal, the GI tract, and
nothing gets absorbed?
It has to be broken down into the
right condition for the body to convert it
to energy, and then on the inside of
the body, it converts to gas, liquid, and
solids, right, carried by the cells.
Some of the energy is carried by the
cells and then converts it when it gets
to its destination.
Another example would be when you see blood
cells under a microscope.
There's a whole variety of stuff, and also
fungus.
You see every kind of living organism sometimes,
amoeba, you know, all that stuff in blood
samples.
What these people don't realize that I even
spoke to someone who has a live blood
test equipment.
I'm like, what good is that if you
don't know what you're looking at?
Yeah, but you don't.
No one does.
Very few people do.
Now here's where I have a question, right?
When it comes to induction, wouldn't it be
better to sort of label the general way
that induction occurs to give people an idea
of the process?
Because look, it doesn't just simply, okay, on
one side of the wall, it's this.
Next side of the wall, it's that.
Yeah, that's right.
It does, but there's a zone, an intermediary
zone where it's turned into biological energy.
But it's biological.
It's like a pseudo matter.
It's not really material, but the best, I
would try to explain it that it's like
that ectoplasm stuff, but it's transparent goo.
It's like a, not quite like mucus, but
it has less density than water.
And that's what's carried.
They call it plasma.
The plasma is not plasma.
There is plasma, yes, in the body, but
it's like a form of plasma that materializes
material.
Yeah, and that's the thing, is when it's
in that plasma state, it's energy, but it
has some of the characteristics.
No, no, I mean material plasma, not the
woo-woo plasma that they're calling electrical plasma.
When I say plasma, I mean like the
blood plasma, but it's in that category.
If you were to discern the material, the
nutritive energy as it goes into, as it
forms in the blood vessels around the intestine,
because if you look at a cross-section
of the intestine, especially the large intestine, either
one, inside of the, you know, look at
the lumen of the opening and then the
walls, it's completely saturated, just like the eyeball
is saturated with blood vessels, right, even more
so.
Right.
And it's completely sealed.
There's no absorption.
I assure you, nothing goes through.
If you study the older texts about absorption,
they know what I'm talking about.
They call it absorption.
They have all these other terms.
There's three categories of how the nutrition passes,
how you gain nutrition from food, and it
becomes cellular matter and all these other things,
right?
But it's confounding to really think about how
it works, because we're taught in such a
base physical reality that we tend to ignore
or exclude these things that we would consider
to be phenomenal now, right?
Right.
It's a phenomenon.
But one of the prerequisites is the quality
of the biological vacuum.
But let me just, I just want to
go back to, the body's made up of
solid, liquid, and gas, and what happens is
the quality of the energy being transferred from
the intestine, digestion also happens in the mouth,
right?
So we're talking all the way from the
mouth to the anus.
The entire process is taking effect.
But when the body requires gas, liquid, and
solid from the nutrition, it'll draw what it
needs.
But there's also a dictate that if the
food that you're eating is very active or
overly nutritious, it will send more, right?
And you'll get an overreaction, right, in the
body.
So what you're saying is the body's entirely
made of solid, liquid, and gas, but there's
also an energetic component, which is separate from
those things.
Well, that would be the biological vacuum, and
then the energetic component that converts what's in
the intestine or in the lungs, the air
in the lungs, let's say, into what the
body needs.
That's the second component.
The energetic components would be the biological vacuum.
What's inducing?
What's creating the vacuum?
Like think of it in a base mechanical
sense.
I need to draw a vacuum on something.
Well, you bring out this vacuum pump, and
it pulls a vacuum, right?
Okay, yeah.
Okay, so what's creating the vacuum?
What's inducing?
What is making the body make the vacuum?
That's the big confounding mystery.
But it's directly related to the body's ability
to draw nutrition through the intestinal wall.
Right.
You know, energetically.
Now, that's the other component that I've been
looking at.
Okay, because if you're creating an artificial vacuum,
right, it's based on conditions that are applied
to the container, which creates the vacuum inside
of it.
Now, but that's not the case with this
biological vacuum.
No, it's not artificial.
It actually, let's just, well, artificial means it's
made by design, and nature is made by
design.
So it's all artificial, or it's all natural,
right?
Yeah, but I'm saying if you were inducing
a vacuum in a container.
Synthesized would be a better choice of words,
right?
Synthesized, okay, fine, fine.
So if I was synthesizing a vacuum, it
would be based on conditions applied to the
container from an external force.
But in this case, this exists.
In all living things, plants have it.
Yeah.
All animals, cells, single cell, anything alive has
it.
And the way you kill something is by
arresting that biological vacuum.
Now, they don't say that when they want
to poison in toxicology or when something is
burned to death or whatever.
Or, you know, a human is killed many
different ways.
Why does the biological vacuum cease, right, when
there's a mass trauma, right, or mass toxicity,
right?
So these things need to be studied.
It's a very grim subject.
Maybe if we can learn more about the
biological vacuum and what it takes to turn
it off, right?
And it seems to be a switch, like
shock, for example.
Well, most people up until the 19th century
died of shock or infections of the mouth,
teeth.
Right.
Or poisoning because they, you know, is the
food, especially white people, is this food that
didn't season their food properly.
How is this food, Mary?
Oh, it's fine.
You know, I think this horse has turned.
You know, eat it anyway.
And then the next day they're all, you
know, a couple of days they're dead, right?
Right.
From food poisoning.
These were common ways of dying.
So these are things that stopped the biological
vacuum.
Toxicity and trauma.
Shock.
When, you know, shock is purely mental, right?
If you're, like, the best soldiers are, you
know, even in World War II were doped
up with meth and synthetic cocaine and things
like that, right?
You want to be, if you're going to
go fight in a battle to, you're willing
to give up your life.
Yeah.
Shit, man.
You want to take a serious, serious stimulants,
right?
Right.
This is very normal.
They gave them some.
It's not talked about.
Yeah.
Because they're illegal now.
A painkiller and a stimulant.
OK.
So that you've got plenty of excess energy.
You can, you know, fight.
You could psych yourself up.
But I'm telling you, the chemicals, the cocaine
is a hell of a drug.
But here's the thing.
Someone like that going to their battle and
have their arms shot off and keep going.
Right.
Blown off completely and keep going.
Where someone in a car accident, you know,
a guy works in a joint car and
sees his arm off, came off.
He goes into shock and dies in two
minutes from suffocation, basically.
Right.
You see what I mean?
So it's psychological.
So there's a psychological component that triggers shock.
They stopped using mask trousers, which was something
that prevented shock.
Or when someone was in shock, kept sustain
them.
So there's the trauma, toxicity and the mental
side that can arrest the biological vacuum.
So if we study, we don't know what
it is.
But if we study what things affect it,
maybe we can learn more about it.
It's kind of like we've heard of this
mythical creature known as a bear.
Right.
No one's really seen one, you know, like
Bigfoot.
But let's just say it's a bear.
But we've had glimpses of them going through
your garbage can if you live adjacent to
a forest.
So let's set up a lab.
Right.
With some garbage cans with varieties of food
and wait to see these bears come.
And then we'll photograph them, maybe capture one.
Right.
You see what I mean?
That's what I want to do with the
biological vacuum.
How do we induce it?
Because the whole thing is inducing it.
But again, remember, there's no free ride.
Just because you know how to create the
biological vacuum doesn't mean you'll live forever or
heal everything.
Right.
Either.
But we don't know enough about it.
But through my studies yet so far, I
know what stops it.
The toxicity, mental effect, mental trauma and physical
trauma stops it.
Bloodletting, tremendous bloodletting and all that.
So what induces it?
Well, what happens if you look at conception
or germination of a seed or conception in
animals?
The cells that are in that condition already
have a biological vacuum.
It's very important.
There are some seeds that the husk is
broken.
That's OK.
It's important.
If the seed is damaged, it won't germinate.
It's in a closed shell.
Some seeds do, though.
And if you look at the ovum and
the sperm for conception, they're already in a
biological vacuum.
They're living cells.
So how do we see where it starts?
You see, that's very, very difficult.
Also, how do we capture it from its
inception?
So I'm putting these things out.
And I'm not naive.
The chances of someone joining.
This might sound really.
Well, I don't care what people think.
The chances of someone emerging from a conversation
like this or a proposal or things that
I'm putting like this to work with me
on it is like I could go.
I better play the lottery on the Powerball
and win the Powerball before someone comes forward.
Right.
I mean, I'm not naive, but I'm putting
it out anyway.
Just like I say, go, you know, if
I had too many beers, go play the
Powerball.
OK, I play the Powerball.
Then I find out a month later because
I'm not going to look at the ticket
that I won.
That's possible.
Right.
Isn't it possible?
Yeah.
So same here.
I'm putting this out because there might be
someone out there listening or someone listening that
brings this up.
I hope they can communicate because you can't
communicate.
We will bring up anything I'm saying.
If you could have halfway decent communication skills
and bring it up to someone who brings
it up to someone who brings it up
to someone who knows someone who might be
interested would probably be more of the reality
of it.
Right.
All right.
So I'm being sarcastic because I'm not that
stupid.
I mean, I'm not that smart, but I'm
not that stupid.
And I'm not naive.
But if you can try to be naive.
Yeah.
But if you can multiply the number of
tickets bought, you do increase your chances.
That's right.
So the more I talk about it, the
chances do increase.
Now, what's important here is because like I
was stating earlier, these medical community and legal
community, let's say the medical community, they're morons.
Period.
That's just if you were to classify them
by law of averages, they're definitely morons.
Are there exceptions?
Yes.
The successes that they have with surgeries and
stuff like that, who I can train in
any type of surgery in less than a
week, anyone, is because they've gotten that from
the military development.
All of that surgery was developed by the
military.
Why?
Anyone that takes basic military, military, let's say
from an academic point of view, it's better
to injure an army than kill them because
an injured soldier takes two soldiers to maintain.
So when you literally injure even a small
portion of an army, you've basically disabled most
of the army.
Right.
To support them.
So the so the thing was because when
they're dead, you know, they're not going to
develop surgeries for the dead.
They're going to use the dead for practice,
which is wrong, by the way.
You're not going to learn much other than
basic anatomy.
And the anatomy does change when you die,
by the way, rapidly.
They wanted to minimize the field hospitals and
the wounded.
Right.
In reality, the bookkeepers, if you're wounded, they
just put a bullet in your head.
That would be the best reality.
And keep moving.
Right.
So if you're injured, you take a suicide
pill.
So being injured is the same as a
fatality.
You get it.
Then you would have one hell of a
dominant army, just like with Alexander the Great
and other invasions.
What they did, they wanted to show that
they meant to take over a city or
a town.
So when they landed with their ships, they
set their own ships on fire.
Right.
So that means they you know, there's no
way back.
You know, so every man.
Well, like if I were to design a
military, if you're injured, you take a suicide
pill.
Well, see, that's why if you observe the
stuff like Alexander.
Yeah, if you observe Alexander and one of
those movements.
Yeah, if that was known, then we wouldn't
have 90% of the medical procedures that
exist today.
Right.
But I'm just saying, I'm giving that as
a hypothetical.
Okay.
Right.
That would be a perfect army.
Or you move to a robotic army.
Right.
Then there's none of this, oh, I lost
my brother or my father or my sister
or whatever.
None of that.
Go to pure robots.
Right.
So and drones, which is that seems to
be the case since the 80s, by the
way.
You remember the early robots in the 80s?
Military ones.
Matter of fact.
Yeah.
In the 80s, 40 years ago.
So anyway.
They had little they had little tank tracks
on their for feet.
Yeah.
Tracks to attract rent or skid steering.
So.
So the thing to do now is to
come up with an elitist way of treating
the human body for any kind of ill
or whatever injury, trauma, toxicity, but not bringing
it to the professional class, bringing it to
the DIY class.
You know, in other words, the people like
what I've always been saying, you go to
a neighborhood.
Hey, I just moved here.
Let's say it's friendly.
You know, let's just say, you know, one
out of 100 chance you live, you live
in a neighborhood where people want to know
each other.
Right.
That's not good, by the way.
By the way, that's for me.
I don't know any of the neighbors around
me.
I mean, I've used to I've been here
20 some odd years, same place.
But now I don't want to know who
they are.
You know, I just wave hello and it's
like, yeah, whatever.
You tell me their name and I'm like,
anyway.
Then it's like a minute later, what's their
name?
I don't know.
I don't even bother recording it.
So but here's the thing.
Let's say you have a friendly neighborhood.
Oh, yeah.
That guy, Jimmy, three houses down.
He's really good with cars.
You know, I've been through this before.
And Amy up the street here, she makes
the best bread.
And any baked goods are really good.
This guy right here, he knows the guy
across the street.
He's an electrician.
He's good at general construction.
This guy here, he's a plumber.
He's he's a lawyer down the street.
You know, if you need anything, go to
him.
Right.
But you notice that they never say this
guy is a really good medic.
And if you need anything, go to him
for you.
You ever hear that?
Never, ever, ever.
Not even historically.
Historically, you would be called a doctor, a
physician, not a medical doctor, which, as the
name implies, physical, physicality, physiology, physician.
Right.
Not medical doctor.
Doctor doesn't mean anything.
Anyway, doctor just means teacher, a doctor of
what medicine, pharmaceuticals.
Right.
So, by the way, many people I've heard
I've been logging this now for 40 years.
When they go to these idiots and they
have an ailment and he just he's the
doctor is booked all day.
So he's not going to really do any
homework or study to find out how to
help you.
You know what they do?
They say here are painkillers or antibiotics.
Look, you probably have some unknown virus.
That's what they tell everyone.
You have an unknown virus.
I can't help you.
I can give you a painkiller.
You know, they give you this, whatever the
fashionable one is or this fashion.
By the way, the new antibiotics will kill
you.
Do not take any new.
If you believe you might need some antibiotics,
stick with the penicillin or amoxicillin.
Do not take any of the other stuff.
They almost they almost even are trying to
message and signal this to you by how
bright and like a toxic turquoise blue.
The pills come in.
They come in these toxic colors, you know,
like those are you ready?
Like those day glow colors almost.
Yeah.
But talk to pink looking stuff and all
that.
Yeah.
Because sometimes the medicines I do experiment with.
Let me take a little bit of that.
This is for this.
Let me just take it.
Oh, my gosh.
It doesn't do anything.
It'll kill you.
It'll just completely destroy your insides.
Right.
Yellow stuff like that.
Yeah.
But yeah, they're signaling, you know, because like
in the jungle.
Right.
We can't help it.
We live in a natural environment, no matter
how much we synthesize or make artificial.
What's interesting is, you know, we still follow
the rules of the jungle.
If you go into the jungle and you
see an extremely bright, colorful frog.
What is that signaling?
I'm poison.
Yeah.
So this is what they're doing.
They're following.
They can't avoid it.
Like the poison arrow frogs that a friend
of mine had for a while.
They had this bright orange like the cones
on the street color on their back.
With small black spots also, I think.
Exactly.
Yeah.
So this is where it's at.
And then make a little handbook on basic
surgery.
The problem with surgery is it's just squeamish.
But just go get a pig, a big
piece of pork or something.
Other animals don't.
The closest you're going to get to human
is pork, right?
Right.
Pig.
Yes.
Get everything.
Muscle tissue.
Cut everything down to.
It'll be bled out, though.
The pig when you get it.
If you get one that's not bled out,
you'll have pretty accurate depiction of what human
is like.
You don't need to do that, though.
I think on the DIY level, you could
even do orthoscopic.
Here's the other thing also.
With the archaic stuff and the timing with
the Phoenix and all that, I believe they're
going to cut back public services and the
grid way before 2040.
Right.
And you know how fast time goes.
I mean, we did the original O&G
in 2015, and that's ridiculously.
It seems ridiculously like recently.
Right.
But it's 10 years.
So 10 years is ridiculously short period of
time for me.
Very much so.
Right.
Yeah.
For other people, if you're really young, it
seems like.
Because when you're really young, you don't want
to be young.
You want to become older.
And when you're older, you keep wondering what's
next, what's next, what's next.
And before you know it, you look at
your watch.
Five years just went by.
Right.
That's a Pink Floyd song about that.
Every older person I ever talked to would
always tell me that.
You don't realize it, but time is going
to fly by real quick.
And when you're 15 or 20, you're going,
no, it's not.
It's slow.
It's exactly the opposite.
You get older, and then it starts flying
by.
It's like, oh, gee, that was already 20
years ago.
Yeah.
You start doing stuff like that.
Well, I have extremely well and good, fond
memories with high retention of spending time in
the New York Public Library on 42nd and
5th, back in 1984, 85, and reading.
It was like a year ago, right?
And that's, what, 40 years ago?
Man, get out of here.
Yeah.
Really?
And I do the same thing when it
comes to the 90s, because I'm like 10
years younger than you.
So exactly.
There you go.
So I reach the same age.
So I'm like, yeah.
I mean, I remember it like it was
maybe a year or two ago, and it's
40 years, right?
So holy crap.
Yeah.
Okay.
Maybe I have attributes that allow me to
do that, because I know people that, you
know, a goldfish, right?
Mm-hmm.
Don't know what happened yesterday.
And I could get that way, too.
But certain things that are important, you remember.
Now, enough about those statements that I made.
I'm not going to continue more on the
human body in general, but I got an
email from someone regarding the thyroid.
Okay.
And I get a lot of questions like
that regarding parts of the body in certain
conditions.
And the first thing I want to just
tell people, why don't we just, because we're
all going to follow this standard operating procedure,
right?
Because we have, because, all right, if you
ask any organ of the body, oh, that
is a medical question or a biological.
No one says a biological question.
Everyone says medical, right, always.
Well, why?
Don't call it medical.
It's a biological question, right?
And if it's biological, then why do we
have to always lean to this clinical way
of looking at it, academic way?
Stop it.
Right?
So let's do this.
The anatomy can be trusted, because like I
said, these morons through the decades, I didn't
notice, we've been looking at the human body
for thousands of years, but we only have
information from the past 75 to 100, best,
right?
Mm-hmm.
Why?
But anyway, I want to interject something.
You know, the Greeks, the ancient Greeks knew
the heart was not a pump.
They said that the blood moved like a
wave throughout the body.
Mm-hmm.
Think about it.
So if the heart is a brake, right,
anyway, okay, they were correct.
All right, so let's go back to this.
So we bring up something like the thyroid.
I said I'm going to discuss this on
a sonic.
Okay.
We can trust the anatomy, because these guys
are good ditch diggers, these medical academic people.
They're good at digging ditches.
Like if someone digs a really good ditch,
you build a foundation, you can't just say,
hey, look at this dummy.
All you could do is dig ditches.
Man, you dig a good ditch, you're important,
right?
It's important that you do that well, right?
No, it's very useful.
It's very useful to have properly measured and
directed ditches.
It absolutely is.
Yeah, or grunts.
These are all grunts.
So the grunt work is necessary.
So let's call them grunts.
And these grunts now, they've been able to
amass, unfortunately, most of the stuff depicts a
cadaver type anatomy, right?
Right.
So let's look at the thyroid.
When you look at the thyroid anatomy, you
notice how it wraps around the throat section,
the windpipe and all that area, you know,
voice box and all that, right?
Okay.
Now, it's slightly different when you're alive.
When you're dead, what happens is it expands.
So it's always going to seem, everything's going
to seem more conflated when you look at
their anatomy books.
You always have to keep that in mind.
That's from a cadaver, not a living being,
right?
So, and there's rapid change that takes place
within minutes.
Not extremely, like there's not a big difference,
but there is a difference.
So just keep that in mind.
First thing, remember, when you look at what
these grunts have put together in anatomy, it's
always a cadaver.
So this is what it looks like when
you're dead, but I'm not dead, right?
So we have to kind of go back
and say, okay, I'm not dead, but that's
what it looks like when you're dead, close
enough, but that's not it, right?
Okay.
So then we look at the location of
the thyroid.
It looks like you had built this system,
you know, that connects the head.
You know, you have the structure, the spine,
the muscles, you know, the spinal erectors, all
the neck muscles that come up from the
clavicle, you know, the collarbone, all that stuff.
You have a windpipe, you have glands, you
have lymphatics, you have blood vessels, you have
all covered in skin.
Then you have this thing, like a spongy
material that wraps around your throat, literally.
It almost looks like an alien.
You know in the alien movies when the
thing came out and stuck to your face?
Yeah, it kind of looks like something went
into your body and stuck to that part
of your body, right?
It doesn't look like it was grown there
naturally, right?
All the other elements that I described look
like they were naturally emerging, just like when
a tree grows, right?
You have the various, you know, the sinew,
all of the structure that you see between
like the upper thorax, the upper part of
your center body, everything in your neck.
It looks very naturally combined.
Then you have this thing, sorry, it just
wraps around like an alien creature.
What the hell?
Almost like it's a sensor.
You know, when you have like, imagine an
elaborate plumbing technology where you have all these
pipes and the plumber wants to know what's
going on, so he straps this sensor thing
around your pipe, right?
And it has an x-ray built into
it, sonic, like sonogram, it has temperature gate,
you know, you strap it around the pipe
and it gives you all this data, right?
Imagine something like that, like an alien creature
came and strapped around your neck.
Think of it like that.
Then you start to see clearly what's going
on with the thyroid.
First of all, what kind of activity happens
in the neck area there?
In the neck area, what you're going to
have is extreme, you have an interchangeability of
mobility.
In other words, your body could be facing
one way and your head could go another
way and it's a very robust structure, right?
Very robust.
And you have all the connectivity.
What's above your neck?
Some people that I've met, they actually have
something called a brain up there, right?
And that has connectivity.
So massive connectivity has to go through that
area.
What else is happening in that area?
It's one of the most critical junction points
to connect the regulation of the intake of
air to the lungs, the organs that process
it, right?
It would be much more efficient to have
gills on your chest, wouldn't it?
Think about it.
It would, but all these key things come
together at the head, though, because you have
your ears, your eyes, all of these sensory
inputs.
Sure, all the venting.
Yeah, but let's just stick with the neck.
So with the breathing, when you design an
engine, there's something called runner length.
It's critical when you do airplanes, combustion engine
airplanes.
Runner length is, if you have a combustion
engine airplane and you screw up the length
of the exhaust pipe, you may not have
enough power at certain altitudes.
So runner length is the amount of distance
that the air, either going into the engine
or coming out of the engine, must maintain
for the engine to be optimum, right?
So the neck represents a runner length that's
necessary.
So there's a lot of things put together
by design, engineering.
It's very good engineering.
The worst engineering, obviously, is the groin.
Why do you have something like this next
to something like that, you know?
The sewer next to the, right?
You have the sewer and the reproduction at
the same.
And that one I'll never understand.
I'll just say that and leave it as
that.
I'll never understand why you have the reproductive
area and the sewer so close together.
Yeah, reproduction, a giant bundle of nerves, and
also your waste disposal vent.
Yeah, right there.
It's like, oh my gosh, is that a
joke or what?
You know?
I mean, that's why I was, you know,
I'm all in favor for a detachable penis
or a detachable vagina.
I think you can get vaginas now.
You don't even, anyway, need the rest of
the body.
But anyway.
Yeah, so anyway.
They have flesh lights, too.
That's another.
Yeah, so I don't mean to be serious,
but that's something that I just chalk up
as being like, don't, so let's not go
there.
But we just did.
We did.
Okay, so the thyroid, when you look at
it, the main thing, you have all this
circulation of lymphatic fluid.
Remember, you have more lymphatic fluid than you
do blood in your body running up and
down, right?
You have all this stuff draining and going,
passing directions.
You have the nerves, all of the nerves
generally that connect to the body pass there.
You also have the air passing through there.
You also have what else is going on.
You have all those things that I mentioned
are dynamic functions, but they're like in a
passive location.
They have to go through there.
One thing that is the most dynamic and
doesn't have to be used is what?
Your speech, your voice box is there also.
You've heard of the monks that have an
oath of silence for like a month or
40 days or whatever, right?
I believe that has something to do with
the thyroid.
It's not just you'll be better off not
speaking, right?
And you notice when certain people are in
certain emotional conditions, I'm not speaking to you.
That ties in with the thyroid.
So let's take it a little further.
If you speak too much, you can damage
the thyroid, right?
Over-stimulate, not damage.
Over-stimulation, which leads to irritation.
Lack of recovery then leads to persistent damage.
That's the proper way to think of it,
right?
Yeah, that sounds right.
Right?
You have overuse, irritation, lack of recovery, then
damage.
Because you can overuse and if you recover,
hey, you recovered, right?
Right.
Now, not speaking will under-stimulate.
Under-stimulate.
And under-stimulation has to be recovered also.
Think about someone who's in bed for a
month.
Under-stimulation, can they get up and walk
whenever they want?
Very rarely.
Right.
What they always call atrophy because things are
not being used.
Under-stimulation.
The old use it or lose it kind
of thing.
Yeah.
So let's take these extreme points and then
bring it to the Midland where most people
are, right?
Because most people are not always speaking all
the time unless you're the Greek or whatever.
And then you have most people that are
not always silent all the time.
Unless the husband and wife are locked in
a room and they ate each other.
So these are extreme situations.
So most likely you're going to have a
moderate amount of speaking.
So if you have, here's the simple, this
is like the cheapest way to go about
it.
If you have thyroid issues, other than the
passive dynamic set up of the structure that
I mentioned by looking at it, the only
thing that is not mandatory and not happening,
let's say involuntarily, that affects the thyroid directly
is speech.
All the other things you do, they're all
involuntary, right?
The structure of the spine, the nerves, the
fluids running, all involuntary.
But the only thing involuntary is speech.
Right.
Okay.
So mind what you're doing.
Are you the type of person that speaks
too much, doesn't speak enough, let's say, underspoken,
overspoken, right?
And I would try both.
Maybe not speaking for a little while, speaking
less, or maybe speaking more.
See how that affects the thyroid health.
Also, there's this whole thing about hormone production,
right?
And we brought up the thyroid before this
email even came in regarding radiation.
I think it was with you, wasn't it?
Yeah.
So there wouldn't be much concern about taking
iodine unless you have irradiated particles in your
body.
If you get irradiated, right, by x-rays
or anything like that, taking iodine doesn't help
because it's done.
Right.
But when you intake particles that are now
irradiating you from the inside out, yes, the
iodine will damp that out somewhat.
Because remember, it's a halide.
So anyway, the other thing with it is
we're looking at the structure of the thyroid.
It looks very spongy.
It's not, actually.
I mean, it's pretty robust, but, you know,
it's a soft tissue.
It's robust enough to hold the structure.
What level of biological vacuum does it have
to retain?
What level of nutrition?
You know, each organ takes on its different
nutrition.
You ever hear, like, this food's good for
your kidneys, this food's good for your liver,
this, right?
Like, for example, what food is really good
for your kidneys?
Beans.
Oh, my gosh.
How'd you figure that out?
Because they're shaped like a kidney.
Exactly like a bean, yeah.
But it is possible to overdo it, right?
So all these other things are similar.
Like, for example, it's an unclean food, but
the little, what do they call it, baby
rock, rock little clams?
I forgot what they're called.
Rock, you get it, right?
Being in Jersey Shore, you should know your
clams.
Come on, man.
Yeah, yeah, well, there's the Chesapeake Bay type,
and then there's the- The little rock,
the ones with the rock in the name,
what is it?
Anyway, those look exactly like your liver.
Eating those can help rebuild your liver, by
the way.
Right, the internal part of a clam does
look a lot like a liver if you
look at the part.
Exactly, and there's a Japanese medicine based on
that, not based on it, but actually issues
that people have damage to their liver.
So anyway, lungs, lotus root.
Look up lotus root and take a cross
-section of lotus root and then look at
the cross-section of the lungs.
It's identical, right?
There's a study of, this is not the
fix for the organs, but it's a corresponding
archetype that exists in nature.
What would be corresponding to the thyroid, right?
A sea urchin, sea urchin material?
Is that what it is?
I don't know, I haven't looked at it.
It would be sea urchin probably, and that
needs to be studied.
So this is all I'm going to put
out for now.
I need to look into it a little
bit, meditate on it a little bit more,
but I wanted to put this out because
this is a primer and a way to
approach any part of the body.
It's biology we're looking at.
What is its function?
What's involuntary?
What's voluntary, right?
What form of intake can we immediately adjust
our diet to benefit that, right?
Yeah, those questions.
Now, by the way, from any perspective, and
I know a lot of, there's been, I
think most of the people listening to me
have not fallen for the paleo diet or
the, what's the other one where you eat
the keto?
Ketosis.
Yeah, oh my gosh, what's next?
You know, these people that do the keto
and the paleo, I have a better diet
for them.
Hold your breath diet.
Hold your breath for like a day.
How about that?
We'll put that together with the suicide pill
for the military.
Anyway.
Sounds good.
By the way, a thyroid to me looks
like two things, one, an old lady's bra,
and two, kind of like a butterfly almost.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
There's symmetry.
So study that, and we'll revisit this again.
I'll dig in.
Unfortunately, the internet is, you know, what's it
called?
The dead internet theory that most of the
stuff is.
Yeah.
Not real.
Okay.
It's fabricated by machines.
Right.
All right.
Yeah, or something.
Yeah.
So I'll see what's been archived.
I might have some things to access thyroid
study, but not from a medical clinical, because
they don't know, those morons.
The most you're going to get from the
medical community is what they call chemical biopsies
and anatomy.
And remember, it's all from dead people.
Right.
They don't know how to perceive the organ
while it's still alive.
Right.
I'm sure they have done studies like that,
you know, where they tear people up, you
know, in death camps or prisons.
Yeah.
Or, you know, they just abduct people.
Right.
One does wonder why a see-through skin
kind of study hasn't been done.
You know what I mean?
Where there must be a way to do
that.
Right.
Yeah.
There's many ways, but the best way to
do it is to project intuitively.
I'll give you an example.
Like right now, what's interesting is I was
like, oh, man, you know, I've been studying
water for more than 20 years intensely and
developing water technologies intensely.
And now that we've got the lab funded
and any resources we want, I realized what
a joke.
Didn't need the lab at all.
I create everything in my head.
Everything gets done in my head.
I don't need the lab at all.
The purpose of the lab is after I
bring it up and bring it forward or
manifest it down to the finest detail in
my mind, then I can build it in
the lab and blow it up or test
it or whatever.
Right.
But most of the time when I manifest
the idea, it works.
So we can go right to production with
it.
Right.
Because the principle is so strong.
So that was a pretty good joke to
be run on me.
Right.
I think I've mentioned it.
Some things have been brought to me that
according to devices that I was using or
brought up like the scalarator, all small form
factor, and now they needed something very large.
And we can't make a scalarator that large.
And in 15 minutes, I came up with
a solution.
And now there's another thing, and I came
up with a solution for that based on
the same principles.
This is freaking amazing.
It's great.
And lab, I mean, they're still looking to
set it up or whatever.
When you have the funding, you know what
they say.
If you don't use it, you lose it.
Right.
Absolutely.
So, yeah.
So the same thing is there's an intuitive
aspect to this.
And, you know, these moronic medical people, academics,
whatever, they say, oh, you can't do it.
They'll tell you stuff like that.
Right.
It's kind of like they'll make fun of
you for saying that.
It's kind of like Max Planck when there
was some convention in Paris back in the
20s or 30s before the war broke out
in Europe.
And they asked him about his scientific studies.
There was someone who was interviewing him for
a newspaper.
And he says, what about your studies with
science and nature?
And he says, oh, science has nothing to
do with nature.
This is Max Planck saying this.
Right.
You know, he's like one of the great
atomic theorists.
Right.
Supposedly.
Moron.
Yeah.
So, yeah.
I think we're on a good foot with
understanding the basics.
And, by the way, did I mention that
I went to chat GPT and asked them,
is there a biological vacuum that holds all
living things together?
It says no.
Yeah.
You mentioned it last time.
Very emphatically.
No.
Very emphatically, too.
So why are they saying that when obviously
there is?
Right.
Why?
There's a big agenda here that we've hit
into.
But it also does that with, you know,
it says show me the laws that state
all debts belong to the United States.
And it shows you, like, anywhere between three
to 15 different places in all the codes
and laws.
Then if you ask it do all debts
belong in the United States, it says no.
Right.
Even though it just showed you the laws.
Well, you just ask.
You don't ask it.
You ask it show me which the verbiage
in laws.
Yeah.
And it brings up the UCC here, the
U.S. Code here, the Code of Federal
Regulations here are laws that state all debts
belong, you know, anyway.
Yeah.
So it's kind of I think I commented
on the tritango that what all it is
is, you know, the flight AI, all it
is is, you know, flight simulator software.
Yes.
They took that logic train and converted it
to looking up files and putting it together
in a way that issues a human like
response.
That's all it is.
There you go.
It's flight simulator software.
So, you know, you know how complicated flight
simulated software can be in order to make
conditions.
But if they simplify it, then even, you
know, a seven year old can fly a
drone.
So.
Right.
Yeah.
And it looks very realistic.
Subtle movements translate to subtle.
Right.
You program, you program wind speeds in the
thing reacts like, you know, I was on
one a long time ago and you put
in a certain lateral wind speed.
And no matter what you did, you couldn't
fight it.
And then someone who was a pilot is,
yeah, it's exactly what it's like, you know,
you couldn't get back on the runway, you
know, no matter what you did.
So it was pretty accurate.
So, yeah, that's what they're doing.
Don't be impressed by all this stupid shit.
And one thing, you know, Trump and Musk,
I think I should have said something about
it when Trump, this is just total segue.
When Musk was running everywhere with doge, you
know, infiltrating, you know, and all that.
So I said, this isn't going to last
too long.
I have a feeling they're going to have
a falling out.
I should have said something, but now it's
too late.
Let's see.
Let's just not say, but I was saying,
I think I did tell someone these two
are going to have a falling out.
This is what be everyone's being set up
for publicity stunt here.
And what happened?
Yeah, but it's, you know, it's fake anyway.
Oh, that's right.
It's a public.
In other words.
Yeah.
What Musk was doing was a publicity stunt.
And the only way to accentuate it, you
know, and as it's all distraction, by the
way, this is all right.
All of this belongs to the United States.
And, you know, it's every government and major
corporate employee is funding their own salaries, right?
Everyone.
And every single thing is meant to keep
you distracted from getting to anything real.
That's just the bottom line.
Exactly.
But, you know, it's funny to look at
the play and all this is just going
to go away because there's going to be
something coming up in the news and the
next, how long were they playing the dog
thing?
Doge thing thing for about a month, maybe
a month.
They were leaving in and out of stuff.
And then I call it a move.
Yeah.
So this will play for another month and
then watch what happens in about a month
or before the fall.
We're going to have some kind of quote
unquote event, you know, because remember you don't
have any events in the summer, unless they're
military events.
Like the, when did the, the USS Liberty
get shot up by the Israeli fighters that
was in the summer.
Wasn't it?
I think that was in the summer and
actually right now they're actually having these weird
clashes in the streets in LA over the,
you know, people are allegedly attacking federal agents
who are doing ice.
Yeah.
That started, that was, I saw that popped
up today.
Right.
Yeah.
Something like that.
So that's yeah.
Whatever.
Yeah.
And it'll justify the next thing as per
usual.
So there you go.
Yeah.
It's just a show because the people have
to have it that way.
Yeah.