Hey, Rated Y, 235, that's what it appears
to be.
And how are you today, Creek?
Yeah, you, are you, yeah, all that and
above.
That's how are you with a capital O.
You know, soon, soon, I never knew, I
never know how to answer that.
I never, I never figured out the proper
way to answer that in English, other than
the nice city.
I'm fine.
How are you?
And then you say, well, I'm fine.
That's all right.
You never give a complete or honest answer
about that when asked, I mean, to be
straight, right?
I mean, isn't that correct?
I'm pretty, I'm pretty honest.
We, we know we're going to meet and
do a sonic and, um, yeah.
And I, so what I do is I
usually drop everything that I'm doing sometimes literally
and, uh, run to the computer and, you
know, I'm usually on time and, uh, or
the phone, but I'm not, I'm getting another
phone now.
Someone's getting me a phone and, um, that'll,
that'll work.
So I can walk around and do other
stuff, but yeah, it's just, everything's cool, man.
Yeah.
Excellent.
All right.
Well, you sound pretty mellow tonight, so I
guess we'll just get, cause I'm tired.
Yeah.
I've been doing a 3 a.m. to
midnight for a long time.
So, uh, well look, and eventually, uh, you
will have to rest a bit more.
I mean, again, appropriate to age and what
your condition is and what it is you're
doing.
That's how you have to adjust your health,
but maybe we'll get to that a little
later.
Let's just go at the questions.
Okay.
Follow up question about teeth, because there was
a bit of a few questions about teeth
recently.
I'm trying to understand if, if the Greek
put dental implants in after losing his teeth
and what's his view on them, I had
two teeth removed and I'd been thinking what
to do.
Never said implant.
Basically it was a fixture or temporary.
It's a flipper.
It's a small partial is what I called.
Uh, it's, it's called a partial, it's called
a temporary, a flipper in dental parlance.
Uh, and, uh, it's technically a denture, a
denture could be one tooth, you know, I
know if you know anyone who's a professional
hockey player, they all have that in the
front, right?
Uh, you want to be able to remove
it for the game, right?
Or a boxer or whatever.
Uh, I think Leon Spinks too, um, he
had a great set of teeth until he
took them out for a fight, right?
So you know, uh, it's a partial, what
it is, it's a, it's actually an acrylic,
a high mineral contact acrylic that's molded to
your palate for the upper and, and for
the mandible or the jaw for the lower,
it's a little more technical because you have
saliva glands in that area.
Uh, they typically are made way too thick.
Uh, they have to be, I contour them
and reinforce them.
Uh, yeah, it's a denture actually.
No, no implants.
Okay.
Now implant, they're literally putting a fence post
into, into your bone, whether it's your jaw
or your skull, right?
They're going to actually, you've seen how fence
posts are put in literally, it's the same
exact principle.
And it's, it's called an abutment for something
to connect to the, and it's, it could
be threaded or bonded.
Uh, they put a false tooth on that
post that goes into the, into the, uh,
body.
And I'm, I'm, I'm against those for several
reasons, uh, depending on the tooth condition.
Like for example, if, uh, if you have
bone decay, right, where teeth go loose and
break or fall out, uh, the, the posts
usually don't take because it's too soft.
And you're actually creating, uh, an area that
it's going to irritate the bone even more.
I highly recommend temporary a flipper.
Just if you talk to the dentist, say
I want a flipper or temporary, I want
to try it out and get yourself a
Dremel with some, with some, um, burrs, diamond
burrs and whittle it down.
Uh, get yourself some carbon paper and you
bite on the carbon paper and guess what
that does.
It leaves a trace where you need to
whittle it down right for the bite and,
uh, just to look up.
I don't know how many good YouTube videos
are on doing sculpture or wood carving, actually
carving with a, with a rotary tool and
then polish it out.
And you've got yourself, um, a removable, whatever.
I think the why in this now, maybe
I'm wrong, but you know, check my thinking.
The why in this, why you would suggest
the partial as opposed to say, getting the
implant is a little deeper because, yeah, as
opposed to the implant, the partial or the
denture is better.
That's what I was saying.
Uh, but the thing is that it's not
just about the fact that you lost your
tooth.
It is the condition.
Your gum didn't want to hold onto the
tooth.
I mean, it might not want to hold
onto the unnatural posts.
So you know, I'm just thinking logically, the
bone, not the gum.
It would be the bone.
Yeah.
The bone.
But either way, yeah.
The condition of your mouth.
No, seriously.
Okay.
Well, also look, when you have a tooth,
when you have a tooth in the socket,
whether it's the upper or lower, there's something
called a PDL periodontal ligament.
It's literally a shock absorber.
So the tooth, which is very hard, doesn't
go into a hard substructure or structure like
the bone.
You have a periodontal ligaments called the PDL.
Very often when a extraction is done, they
don't address it.
And when the socket heals over, the periodontal
ligaments in there, which sends a signal to
the body that the tooth is still there,
sends blood to the area, and you could
have a problem later on.
Yeah.
Hilda Clark addresses that, and it's funny because
when I tell people if they're getting an
extraction, I ask if they're going to clean
out the PDL and use like a number
eight or number 10 burr to clean it
out.
You know, it means, you know, you're going
to clean it out really well, make sure
it's all gone.
And they're like, wow, I haven't, the dentist's
typical remark is I haven't heard of that
since I was in college.
You know, how many extractions have you done
in the past 20 years that go improperly,
right?
Right.
So, um, and, and I've been a victim
of a sloppy, I've been a victim of
a sloppy one or two of those because
I don't know if I ever told you,
but occasionally I get phantom pains where it's
like the tooth is still there, it feels
like it's still the bad tooth every once
in a while.
And I'm like, oh, that's exactly what you're
talking about.
PDL mostly, it's probably the PDL periodontal ligament
and look it up.
It's very, and the other thing is when
you have an extraction, we're almost all dentists
don't tell you that the opposite tooth on
the bite will start erupting, start growing into
that gap.
So let's say you have an extraction on
the upper, uh, the lower tooth where that
gap is, we'll start growing into it.
So now instead of having an even, uh,
bottom row right under where the gap is
on the top, that tooth wants to fill
in the gap and it just keeps growing
up and growing up.
The tooth itself does not elongate, but you'll
see it almost, you can almost see the
roots sometimes.
It just wants to reach and close that
gap.
Right.
So I tell people, I said, did you
know, did the dentist tell you you have
this thing called eruption and the tooth be
prepared for that?
Right.
So, um, yeah, yeah.
And I was like, no, I didn't say
anything.
And I went back and he was surprised
that I said it.
So yeah, these, these guys are morons.
The member, they have a, you really want
to hear the joke.
It's the joke and the punchline.
They are state certified, state licensed, right?
That's all you got to say.
Yeah.
So, uh, but it don't underestimate the importance
of a dentist though, a dentist and a
barber, right?
And let's cut your own hair, but a
barber is also a surgeon.
I think that should come back, but, um,
no, I'm not into the, uh, there's a
big fad.
The reason why they want to do, uh,
implants is cause they're expensive.
Um, they're, they can justify, uh, the costs,
right?
So I play with a lot of, um,
energy systems and the last thing I want
is a metal post in my skull or
jaw.
Right.
So use your own discretion.
I'm not saying no, but you know, you
want a metal post in there, you know,
that it's actually threaded in there.
Yeah.
Uh, depends.
I, I, um, a good implants probably better
than a bad temporary flipper denture, but a
good denture is better than a bad post.
And the chances that you're going to get
a good post are slim.
So go for the denture is another way.
Another like mathematical way to look at it,
right?
Another common sense.
Another common sense element is it's a lot
easier for you to take that out of
your mouth and work on it yourself than
it is if you got something that's kind
of, you know, anchored in there.
So, you know, especially if they don't do
it, right.
Yeah.
What are they going to do?
They get one chance to do it, you
know?
Right.
And then you got to drill a hole
and yeah, and then you got to deal
with it.
Yeah.
And I've heard a lot of negative comments,
uh, here, here's the quandary with it.
The best people in any sort of the
ones that dropped out of school by the
eighth grade are on, are on the FBI
most wanted list, right?
Most likely.
And those people will not be state certified.
You won't be able to get state certification
if you qualify.
Right.
So now you're going to have to put
up with morons that finished school, paid for
college about two, three times, right?
They got jixed by the call.
They got jerked by their own school, uh,
because you know, the application for the school
pays for the tuition by the way.
And uh, you actually have to go sign
all this stuff to get state certification.
You are, you gotta be like a normie
that's off the rock off there, like a
normie that fell out, fell off their bar
stool to do that, whether, you know, to
be a medical or a whatever.
So you gotta balance that out.
I mean, put it this way.
If you stayed in school enough to go
to college and get a state degree, a
state license, you're a freaking moron.
You mean, or in other words, you don't
read, you just, you're just, you're just, um,
norm normally a very good person, right?
It's just for society and you just go
along your life doing what you're told to
do on TV and, uh, peers who are
morons in themselves.
So yeah, so that's, that's the quandaries part.
So it's just, this is kind of like
the relationship.
Just find a dentist that doesn't, uh, you
don't find to be, what did we say,
uh, when you was something that someone can't
change that you don't like repugnant to you,
right?
Or whatever.
Uh, yeah.
Just find someone that's sort of agreeable and
then train them.
And if they're not trainable, then go find
another one.
A dental school will probably be the best
in big cities.
I don't think small towns have dental schools,
you know, cause if you're in a small
town and you want it, you're probably going
to have to go to a bigger college
in a bigger city.
Right.
So yeah, depending on, uh, I know that
there's a lot of that stuff in the
Midwest, like Kansas and all that, because you
know, they were going to fortify in the
early 20th century, they were going to fortify
the middle of the country, uh, because basically
FDR wanted to go to war with the
entire world and he wanted to put most
of the important infrastructure right smack in the
center, like Kansas and all Oklahoma, you know,
all that central area.
So they, if you have a landing of
army, they have to march a long way
to get to the key infrastructure.
But there was so much sabotage you don't
hear about, you know, what is it?
A million and a half Americans, 2 million
Americans died during world war II here on
the mainland, but due to sabotage and you,
yeah, you don't hear about it.
I mean, 5,001 night, I mean, uh,
yeah, fires, bombings, all that stuff.
You don't hear any of that.
They call it the great generation.
Yeah.
My ass.
So there was a good reason why I
was just going to say, there's a very
good logical reason why they went to lucky
Luciano to protect the ports in New York,
you know, uh, because they needed somebody who
could actually get the job done and moving
it to the middle of the country.
Also provided them with a little bit more,
you know, of a buffer for air aerial
attacks as well, as well as what you
were talking about, the marches.
Yeah.
So they got a, they got a 5
,000 miles in inland and believe it or
not, it wouldn't be that hard to do
anyway, based on the competency of the military
anyway, well, but that's yet another issue.
Yeah.
Okay.
So how about this?
Issues everywhere.
Exactly.
Well, we'll move along for now.
You know, there might be more dental questions
later, but not today.
Okay.
Uh, whatever happened to possible debate with DAC
Hillman, uh, would like to hear about the
Greeks opinion, uh, you know, uh, number one,
geez, being a pederast.
Okay.
Now look, there's that.
And then there's a followup to this irrelevant,
irrelevant on the overall challenge to the public
perception of the overall subject.
Once you start correcting it, right, it's kind
of like nine 11, right?
Mm.
Uh, the most, what most people think of
nine 11 is, uh, 19 Arab hijackers vaporized
the world trade center with box cutters.
And it's funny people say that's ridiculous.
So we'll tell me the official story if
that's not ridiculous.
So the official, uh, yeah, uh, it's all
presumed, but they're missing the salient points.
They're missing the stuff.
Uh, it wasn't even a debate.
I'm not challenging.
I just want to bring forward, uh, here's
the thing.
Let's say there was a debate, me versus
whatever.
I don't care about that.
I'll grant them the wind, right?
And so you can't do that.
Right.
But anyway, I want to get to the
audience.
I want to see who in the audience
will come out of their trance.
The trance is when you accept all the
normalcy, how things have been normalized, right?
So, uh, I have nothing against Solomon or
anyone, uh, regarding which, whatever way they go.
I do have a hard on for the,
for the Vatican though.
Okay.
However you want to take that.
I was going to say, that's a bit
of a multipurpose statement, but you know what's,
look, what's, what's interesting to me here.
And, and there was a followup about this
debate question that I want to read to
you as well, because it shows me that
people just say there's no debate F sorry,
after the archaics interview, someone reached out to
me that we wanted to get Breshears, uh,
Jason, uh, myself, Hillman and one other person.
And he basically said, well, you're, you're honorable,
you know, you've answered both of my emails.
And I'm like, your buddy, Jason, you know,
he was ignoring him and I'm like, he's
not my buddy and no one's my buddy,
but yeah.
Okay.
You know, if I get an email answer,
like I said, if I get a 10
page email, which I do sometimes, uh, I'll,
I'll say, listen, uh, thank you for the
email.
Uh, I'll have to come back to it
and read it another time, you know, in
a couple of weeks later.
Right.
So that's how I view everything.
Just, I always tell people, if you want
to know what I'm thinking, just listen to
what I'm saying.
Right.
So I don't mind the debate.
There's no challenge, but it's the audience that
I'm, that, that I want to serve.
Right.
That's why I said, oh, great.
If he wants to debate me on one
thing, fine.
I'll grant you the win.
Go ahead.
I'll make it.
I'll fix it.
So you win.
How's that?
But I want your audience, other new people
to hear what I have to say, because
here's the thing.
I think a lot of people fail to
recognize when they use the word debate, they're
looking for you to have a competition where
there's a winner and a loser.
That is not the entirety nor the primary
reason for debating.
And another person responded, debating is only ever
done by people of extremely poor character, cowardly
halfwits seeking approval and dominance.
Discussion is for adults.
Debate is for freetards, fretards, fretards, anyways, yeah,
he used an F at the beginning there.
It's more like a.
Go ahead.
No, I get you.
I get you.
And whoever was that, the same person put
that question.
It also, their follow up comment.
No, no, it was a different person responding
to it.
OK, OK.
I thought it was because that would be
like answering your own question.
But no, it's more of a potluck than
a than a boxing match.
Right.
So what are you going to bring?
And that's what I you know, I don't
mind.
Here's the thing.
I don't really find anyone that has opposing
views because I really if you really listen
to what I'm saying, I have no viewpoint.
All I do is bringing forward stuff that
you can say challenges the normal narrative on
anything But that what kind of a challenge
is it when you see that the normal
narrative is based on nothing Right, and what
I'm bringing forward is what you could look
at based on you know What's what could
be called that benchmark reference material memorialized data?
I'll go back on and on so you
know it's not you know I'm very that's
why I'm very confident because I don't have
to create anything.
It's already been done all I'm doing is
serving it right I'm like the butler or
the waiter.
I'm not in the kitchen right it seems
like Hillman's in the kitchen again, but that's
not right But see again people are like
debate because I want to see a winner
And it's again not the purpose and also
not what you do you can't debate with
people that refuse to even accept a premise
That's another problem So you know and and
if they're going to latch on to something
that is completely false, and we know it's
false How do you argue with somebody who
goes look I've seen Santa Claus on TV
I know he exists and therefore now prove
me wrong.
He's real What are you supposed to do
with somebody like that?
I wouldn't even I won't even say it's
false though because It's based on nothing right
so it could be true It could be
false and most people presume that it's true
if you have let's say a narrative or
structure of a story With characters and events
based on nothing right is it true or
false?
There's there's nothing to grab on to right,
so it's even worse than being false But
that's my point.
I'm not accepting the premise see I don't
know how to word these things as well
as you do sometimes But I I get
your point and but that's the thing it's
there's no debate to be had and even
if there was you're not asking For a
debate you're asking for a competition to prove
who's right and that's not up to us
to do in this way So you know
you present information, and you can take it
or not It's just that simple yeah It's
it's who in the who is listening regardless
of what stance they feel that they're leaning
towards or you know That wants to break
out of the trance that they've been in
their entire life right that's that's what I'm
interested in it Does it matter exactly so
subject matter is irrelevant and whoever it is
is irrelevant there you go precisely all right
So there's a follow-up to the cheese
question which I think you requested in response
to the question back from the Greek I
am sensitive to eggs Though less so from
my neighbors very fresh ones two of those
go down fine See I have the same
experience as this person by the way Just
just to say so I'd love to hear
this okay real quick, and I have avoided
poultry No if the eggs say that they're
not a rate here's this here's you're ready
for this This is a drop in a
big one here Okay, if you go to
carton of eggs, and it says it doesn't
say specifically that it hasn't been irradiated.
It's been irradiated Even if they're organic free
-range Chickens that never been fucked in the
ass or all that stuff does it matter
this well now We just broke now.
We just breached the family hour now.
We're not a family show anymore, but anyway
It's it's pretty scary.
It's pretty scary because you think you're going
out and getting The best you know these
are organic free-range vegetarian bed, but they're
irradiated unless they say they're not irradiated just
means a high dose of x-ray for
whatever yeah, and That so that's why when
you get the ones that are not irradiated
Okay, think about it an egg is very
young on the outside extremely in on the
inside It's already balanced when you irradiate it.
It's extremely mean.
It's the most eating energy you can get
It makes the young it makes everything it
breaks up stuff on a very small level
torques the molecule Right so instead of the
molecule looking let's say like it should It
almost looks it's bent in half Your body
sees some of that energy or most of
energy is foreign And it's going to have
an opposite effect on you Then it should
so or it might you know again it
depends on If you're used to it or
not you know I mean So but anyway
to just I don't think I answered the
question, but the the question here is the
statement that whole food that hasn't been Transported
and tainted is better than the ones right
yeah, that's right Yeah, well and the other
thing is toxic right point.
Yeah, yeah Well, I was just gonna add
here because he has more that he was
answering to you about to give you more
context And I be this sort of fits
exactly with what you just said, but and
I have avoided poultry for almost 30 years
I find it disgusting especially if it slips
into a dish I ordered Fish is delicious
appreciate the response and the New York slice
analogy It was in NYC and specifically pizza
that I started having cheese issues in my
30s Around the time the average slice went
above 250 Okay, so interesting to me because
chicken has been one of those things that
I'm just saying it's David It says it's
chicken, but it doesn't say it's real chicken.
Okay.
You know kind of like you say it
says it's history It doesn't say it's real
history Okay, so They're bred to be for
their meat.
Yeah, right Not a real chicken all right
if you get a real chicken, and you
eat it that Might is a different experience
from what they say is chicken.
That's all I'm getting at I'm using your
history Thing about poultry is it's extremely dependent
on the feed just like a beef connoisseur,
right?
You know the Wagyu beef is because it
gets fed chocolate and beer let's say massaged
and premium Grass and whatever right that's what
makes the Wagyu the Wagyu right and also
they you know a breed of cow that
they select and most of the cheap Beef
is raised on garbage stock.
Hopefully they won't give it protein that comes
from cows, and then they do They finish
it off.
Maybe with grass or fatten it up But
yeah, but poultry it birds are especially sensitive
to their feed So yeah It's not gonna
taste good when I get a chicken.
I try to get an organic free-range
ends up being around 20 bucks for a
three-pounder or whatever and I Soak it
in salt water and ginger for two hours
three hours hour and a half depending on
the How I want to how long I
want to dry it for And I enjoy
a roasted chicken.
It ends up anyone who's seen photos of
what I've done.
It looks just like Chinatown, you know the
ducks that are hanging in the window.
Mm-hmm Yeah roasted that way so I
can go I can do without it.
I can do straight up veg.
I Just have let's say moments of weakness
But the food here has been tainted for
more than 50 years if I see 70s,
that's 50 years easily, right so Half a
century so you're gonna have to be careful.
Now.
Here's one way to fix it if you
can't get good food Guess what eat less?
You're not gonna wither away and die.
You'll get plenty of quote-unquote calories for
though, you know Hopefully anybody here knows it's
irrelevant, right?
Because what do they say need at least
1,500 or 2,000 calories of what
you know, so Yeah, so you just start
eating less.
So this is one thing that I suggest
Overall to people is start eating less Also
your food.
Well, it's kind of hard when you have
children and teenagers, especially right?
But for yourself if you can manage that
like for example If you go get a
slice and you're with someone split it tell
them to cut it in half again I
know it might just tamp up your appetite
You might be hungrier than you then you
before you started eating it, but wait Eat
very little wait 10 or 15 minutes and
see what happens Right.
So eat less if you have no choice
I learned this from traveling when I was
traveling with doing the mining and stuff It
was just truck stops and I was like,
no, no No, I wish these guys fill
up on these microwave pizzas and burritos.
I was like, no No, I'm just gonna
get a tiny amount of food and see
how well I do on it Yeah, I
did lose a little bit of weight looked
a little drawn after a month of that,
but I wasn't Feeling crappy as crappy as
it would have a fight more of it.
So yeah food is an issue I've been
anyone has been listening to Sonics from from
how even 20 years ago when I was
speaking to people I'm always bringing up food
is an issue here in the US, you
know in America It's crazy because we can
supply the entire we could supply 5 billion
people wherever there I don't think there's maybe
a billion people not even But we could
supply the entire planet with all their food
and still have plenty left over by the
way Yes, but unfortunately what is being supplied
for the most part is is making people,
you know fat so to speak But it's
not feeding them.
Well, so that's where we're at malnourished.
They're malnourished and yet they're in the yeah
It's the crisis gene.
Yeah, it has nothing to do with sugar
or corn, you know, it's funny listening to
see Sometimes I'll clear the computer and it'll
be on YouTube in the background autoplay and
some guy some doctor Some idiot came on
talking about it's the corn syrup, you know,
I'm like, oh my gosh, you know Yeah,
there's no single thing And the reason why
the medical system is as bad as it
is in the quote-unquote health care system
is Because the elites that run the world
or whatever you want to call them.
They would rather you have none of it
No health care.
No doctors nothing like that But they know
if they did if they did that and
banned it That people would get together and
they'd actually figure out really what's good for
you to do it And now they're gonna
have a problem, right?
It'll be underground, right?
So so what they do is they they
put on the facade that you're getting care
and you're getting knowledge and Whatever and food
or whatever, but they're actually destroying you little
by little so right you make them Oh,
you make them a bad offer so they
don't seek to discover something.
That is good.
That's all that is That's it.
Well, no you give them a good offer
Wait, where the substance and the actual material
and the knowledge is bad Yeah, it's actually
they're making good offers all the time, I'm
sorry It would be like they market it
as if it's a necessity and it's beneficial,
right?
Let's just say it that way instead of
an offer.
Yeah Yeah, and but people take it as
an offer all marketing is an offer, right?
Take it, you know, take this You'll get
whiter teeth, right?
That's an offer, right?
Even though it's we call it marketing.
So Although I did find it remarkable.
Somebody brought up the old 80s commercial where
the guy just literally puts a battery on
his shoulder And that's like the whole ad
Weird thing like the sub subliminal about that.
Yeah.
Yeah, you know, it was like go ahead
knock that off It was a chip on
my shoulder kind of thing, right?
Yeah, I got bodybuilder type athletic guy, right?
Something I think I remember that TV in
the background Yeah, TV was all you had
in the 80s and movies right and then
the end of ECR, right?
That's why it was worth it to still
travel to the ridiculous movie theater because at
least you got something different Anyways, or you
thought you did Interestingly, that's when they started
break.
Yeah.
Yeah dividing them up into plex Multiplexes.
Yeah, then the small theaters because they figured
instead of having one big theater will make
small for small ones We can run for
movies.
Yeah.
Yeah Anyways, interesting interesting the connection between the
Quran and the laws of Moses Correct me
if I'm wrong, but the most prominent philosophers
and scientists from the Persian Empire were actually
Jewish, right?
and also Jewish people really thrived in Spain
while it was under the Arabs people like
Ibn Ezra Ibn Ezra, sorry Mm-hmm.
Yeah, so that was just a commentary No,
that's fine.
But the Persians are not Muslim no matter
how you slice it They're still not Muslim
the Muslim the Islam pushed on Persia is
a CIA thing 100% 150% and
I know this because I know Persians and
Anyone who knows Persian or Persians or they're
not Muslim now, they play it as if
they are and of course, they're gonna transplant
that Right and push it because they do
have you know religious police in Iran, right?
Yeah, there is a such a thing as
religious police.
It's so Yeah No, it's a horrible situation.
The P the Persians have got it pretty
bad But Islam remember was just trying to
unify just like the Christianity was unified with
Catholicism like it or not Don't believe for
a second Protestantism and all that other stuff
was to protest the Vatican.
It was a charade It's it's all the
same stuff Don't believe for a second was
taken over co-opted and then kept you
know to see who right?
Don't don't believe any of that.
There hasn't been any real Sorting out of
anything over 500 years It's all these things
were settled 500 years ago, except I feel
bad for Iran Persians because they're not Muslim.
Hmm.
So so anyway, we got yet another Message
about the immune system and it seems as
though that is starting to you know, make
sense Yeah, if it's a system within the
body, where is it exactly located?
That's so interesting.
But hey, that's a huge business Just like
cancer.
Oh, yeah and take this or that supplement
to boost your immune system Okay, we know
about this and they're just saying you know
what?
This is great I'm glad you you kind
of gave me this idea and it just
makes perfect sense I wonder if you kept
up with the news recently though because I
got a question about that And I'll just
link it to this and it'll be the
last thing I ask you about tonight You
know Tylenol I got mixed feelings about this
whole, you know Tylenol is bad for pregnant
women now and maybe that's what caused autism
and I find that to be a very
weird Circumstance because Tylenol is almost useless as
a medication anyway, but yet it has been
heavily marketed Yeah, but hold on pregnant women
are bad for pregnant women what the hell
they do and getting pregnant They're gonna have
the next Messiah, you know, you know people
this is the two most common things I
get a message.
My wife is pregnant.
And at first, you know, what my first
response is it wasn't me and the other
response and the other response is You think
you're having a child because you think you're
gonna have the next Messiah in other words
If you don't think you're making the next
Messiah or world Savior, why bother what's wrong
with you?
right, so So most of the people being
pregnant, they're just breeders, you know for more
normies It's kind of like guppies You ever
you know, you know, this is a guppies
and rabbits, right?
you don't believe it or not cats never
made it to that category, but Cat can
can in like three years three or four
years Hundred cats if you look at you
know, not many lips Sorry, you're getting a
little bit of electronic disturbance there.
It sounds like you're walking between zones Yeah,
okay so cats, I'm sorry Your cat point
was Good.
Oh The cat yeah, well they guppies and
cats guppies and rabbits are known for being
big breeders But cats are also are very
big breeders And they never made the list
Anyway aside from the breeding thing in the
Tylenol 80s I remember they tainted the Tylenol
and some people died right because they wanted
to promote the safety seal thing Yeah, and
one of the jokes back then was when
someone pissed you off you told him go
take a Tylenol Yeah, no twice that's basically
tell them to go kill themselves, right yeah
there was two it was almost like the
anthrax scares There was like two of those
Two waves of it and the funny thing
is if you think about it people go
Oh, they always solve the crimes and those
crimes as yet still remain pretty much unsolved
You know, I find that fascinating because it's
like was it done at the factory.
Did somebody do it at the store?
Maybe somebody tainted it, you know personally and
it's a mess anyway Yeah, I usually write
it, you know, it was the s e
e hyphen e y e a y e
E-y-e and a y-e CIA,
right?
I mean their whole thing is to terrorize,
you know, or You gotta understand.
I Think the the CIA is more of
a European ex-nazi Influence and for sure
the FBI is created by the Jewish Mafia.
That's goes on undoubtedly, you know Intuitively, right
So so between those two organizations Another organization
that's like that is the poverty for media
is the Poverty Law Center.
What's it called?
Oh, it's the southern if you're anti-semitism
Right, yeah, that's like a spinoff of intelligence
agencies and then you have the then you
have the main media ones Put it this
way Zuckerberg Organization and Musk's organization can pull
off operations like Traditionally that were left for
the FBI and the CIA right and they
would never get their finger pointed at them
now They would have to be more Anyway
more implicated and they're not so But anyway,
we got away.
So Tylenol is it it's acetomyophen ibuprofen mix,
isn't it?
No, it's just the acetaminophen basically Which Trump
had trouble pronouncing but I found it funny
because it was like really the only thing
I've ever found Tylenol useful for is to
Reduce a fever a little bit but outside
of that.
It's not very useful I mean, it's not
even the best over-the-counter, you know
analgesic type, you know pain reducer.
It's garbage Yeah, so yeah garden variety ibuprofen.
Sometimes I take them by the fistful believe
it or not and they work You know,
yeah, but that's a different yeah ibuprofen is
different but the thing is Acetaminophen is sort
of like an additive that they continue to
sell because take a look at your Percocet
They're loaded with acetaminophen, you know compulsory everybody's
everybody's, you know Percocet prescription came with acetaminophen
and nobody asked you you know what I'm
saying?
It's just one of those things and there's
a bunch of stuff out there that has
acetaminophen mixed in it And it's just an
ingredient that they turned into a marketable, you
know capsule or whatever.
So that's all I see So now they're
throwing Tylenol into the dumpster fire, you know,
meaning what a dumpster fire the term is
used for Yeah, this is RFK jr You
know being in charge of the you know,
the Health Department and all that So but
that's their latest announcement is that it causes
autism.
I'm just telling you Yeah No, no, no,
no, it's irrelevant.
It's irrelevant.
It's the Yeah There's such a thing called
medical Darwinism if you're dumb enough to believe
their treatments and go for it.
You shouldn't be Here or you should you
shouldn't you shouldn't be procreating, you know the
whole concept of the Darwin Awards and Survival
of the fittest if you do anything that
they suggest you you're you're going down as
not To having progeny or procreating or yeah,
it's a test I think they're all laughing
their asses off behind the scenes.
Like I said, they've got a It's just
a dumpster fire.
But here's the thing if you know, like
the stuff we're talking about, you know it
So many people don't know it and create
such a hoop to do about it that
you can get don't get caught in their
wake I mean try to live the best
life you can Right do the best but
sometimes when the entire majority like with the
mask stuff, right you get caught in the
wake it's like they create this vacuum and
it could suck you in and you don't
want to be like, you know, Fighting to
get out of that vacuum being sucked in.
So you have to be very very how
would you say?
Much on the on the sidelines as much
as possible without looking like you're on the
sidelines when they're looking for people on the
sidelines Right, so right and the other thing
to keep in mind is some a friend
of mine always used to say I always
wanted to Run this by you.
I might have done it in the past
But he said that you know what there'd
be a lot less idiots around if it
wasn't for the invention of you know velcro
Attached shoes and bicycle helmets.
We might live in a world of less
idiots and He used to tell me that
all the time.
What do you think?
No, I don't think that has much to
do with it Not at all, I know
how to fix I've discussed already how to
fix it here It's not my job to
do it.
If I was given the job is it's
kind of like was it?
the poppy bush About when they asked him
if he was gonna run for president.
He says you have to be really dumb
to do that job and in if Want
to want to do that job and even
dumber to do it something like that But
no they were it's pretty easy to fix
any society, it's brutal It's going to be
brutal And when you get that brutal you
don't want to hire psychopaths