The sonic event 39 hitting the ground running best we can.
Anyway, Ocelli in the Greek, and you know what you're listening to because you're subscribed
if you're hearing it.
So that's that.
By the way, just a really quick note.
Any rumors of this show's demise, this sonic event's demise, this element's demise out
there are exaggerated, at least for the moment.
So, anyway, we are rolling, and gee, on the Pope's work schedule, we're toward the end
of the seventh month, but I know that's not the right day of the year, but kind of close,
I was going to say.
Close enough.
Yeah.
If you reckon it, yeah, if you reckon it around that time now, it'll be a day off, two days
off when the next moon comes around.
So yeah, it happens.
They cycle around, yeah.
Well, eventually, just like the broken clock, right?
It's got to come around and land that way.
Yeah, pretty much.
Yeah, okay.
What else are they hiding?
What else is wrong, right?
Well, true enough.
What else are they hiding?
Interesting stuff came up recently in a couple of emails and other contacts, let's call it,
like say I was on with Freeman recently by myself, which was clearly a different show
than what you and I would have done.
Okay.
And the same that I would have done if I was alone.
Right, right.
You do a different thing.
I mean, when we're separate, it's a different thing when we're together, it's a different
thing when we're separate.
That's the way it is.
Anyways, so let's just get to a couple of odds and ends before we roll right into whatever's
really on your mind tonight.
So no, then we wouldn't be doing the sonic, but anyway, go ahead.
Okay.
Fair enough.
It's going to be one of those kind of events, folks.
Okay.
So I got a question about induction and I'm going to boil it down for you real easy so
that you don't have to go through the whole email and I'm not going to identify the person
on the email because I don't like to do that.
But anyway, everything we, by the way, you Chuck or anyone that you send anything to,
it's always anonymous.
As a matter of fact, I don't even share it with Chuck and vice versa.
It's very, very private.
And in other words, everyone's privacy is respected in real time and in reality.
So I just want to put that out.
Yeah, no, we do absolutely respect everybody's privacy and we don't even cross pollinate with
emails or anything.
The only thing I will do is share, just like I'm about to do here verbally, hold on, especially
the one who sent me naked pictures of his girlfriend.
I'm not going to reveal that guy's identity, but anyway, go ahead where the picture is
good.
I said, I'm not going to reveal because if I anyway, well, you can say if the pictures
are good or bad.
I mean, everybody knows they got a variety of girlfriend out there and it could be a
lot of different ways.
I knew that was going to get a soft topic.
All right.
Go ahead.
What's the deal?
The email that I got.
Right.
OK.
And I did him to the Greek.
It's about induction.
Here's the thing.
They said, OK, now this is a new concept to me and they are not new to Greek speak exactly,
but they are new enough that the concept of induction is like, wow, OK, that's something
I have to consider.
They were asking about the sweating.
OK, so if you have induction and water is literally created inside the body, along
with other things, right, fluids, they actually got to are created inside the body based on
induction.
It's not a matter of it, you know, going through, seeping through the pores, filtering in.
So how about the going the other way?
They tell us that sweat comes out of our pores and comes out of the body.
Well, how does that work when it comes to the concept of induction?
If I accept absolutely that you're correct about this, which it seems like he is starting
to do, but he's examining it as he goes.
Does this make sense?
Easy.
Sweating.
Very easy.
As a matter of fact, the other night I was on a long technical water conversation.
I brought this up, the sweat glands.
They produce water as what other things, mostly other things in water.
It works the other way.
I think I'm one of the sonics recently.
I said, you know, when you jump in a pool, don't be in the pool or in a bathtub.
You want to pee.
That's not because the body senses all that water and makes new water.
Right.
Now, the concept of induction is is is a replication, just like if you have you want to dub two
cassette tapes, two magnetic tapes, you load one in one machine or, you know, the right
one side and you load the blank one on the other and it transfers the information over.
You need to start out with some of the material that is capable of transferring information.
Then you need the device, the device being every organic living organism.
Now, it does work both ways.
But that or that machine known as the skin, part of the machine, the body, the component
known as the skin.
Yes.
We'll do it more from the inside out than the outside in.
Otherwise, the patch wouldn't work.
You know, the tobacco patch and other things like that, which, by the way, just quickly
addressing someone in the chat.
If I spray myself and I get with the aqua sargentum, do I get silver in my body?
Yes and no.
Again, because the skin will resist, you know, but it is the same as putting a silver coin.
If you have to ask that, you missed the point because it has to be by silver coin is not
biologically compatible.
You always got to look at biological compatibility.
That's why most Americans are so unhealthy, because most of the food they eat is just
not biocompatible.
Example, bologna, margarine, white bread, corn syrup.
Those things are.
Yes, they are slightly biological compatible, but not like whole foods.
Well, when you have a natural gelatin that's actually created from the ground up bones
of an animal, it might work somewhat.
But it's not something that really you should be consuming.
I think the bones are not generally something to be just well, you know, they can't.
They will have an effect simply because of their arrangement, energetic arrangement.
But their energetic arrangement is, again, not optimal.
But the body will pretty much synthesize anything and can induce anything on the periodic table.
But certain combinations will block it and act like a resistor where other things will
not.
Other things, things that induce very quickly is in the category of a poison.
OK, well, now that was where I was going to just add one more question to this and let
you go back around to the sweat process.
Maybe if you just give a basic thumbnail sketch of how how it runs, that would be the best
way to answer it.
But before we go there, really quickly, you said, OK, why doesn't it work with, say, you're
holding a silver coin and you would produce silver in your body?
I get it.
But exposure to some types of metals and some people would say if you grind it up into a
silver powder.
That's through the lungs, which is more receptive than the skin.
Are you familiar with I try to look this up a few years ago, no luck other than another
subject of skin maladies, but it's a dermal luminescence.
You look that up now and they just talk about how when you have an infected area, the skin
will swell up and it's a phenomenon.
They named it after some medical guy, from what I recall.
But dermal luminescence back in the 50s and 60s and 70s was a lot of experimentations
where young children up until about the age of seven could read with the bottoms of the
feet and the palms of their hands, just as well as with their eyes.
So you could write the word cat and they read it on a card, right?
Or you put you don't show them the word and you just have them blindfolded or in a dark
room, put their hand over it and they'll read it, read with the palm of their hand or the
bottoms of their feet.
And this was a lot of studies were done on this.
So the skin is susceptible, photosensitive.
Let me just get into how the operation, the thing works.
You know, water likes to take an ovoid shape, usually like the bulb of an onion or an egg
or the chicken.
Anything that's going to hold water takes that ovoid shape.
If you look at the sweat gland, what does it look like?
There you go.
So it's optimizing itself for the water body.
Just like when you have you open a drawer, someone's kitchen utensils, you always recognize
the cookie cutters, right?
Yeah.
Because that's all, you know, the function, it just looks so much like what they should
be doing.
The way the induction works is just like any other form.
Like for example, look up how does ibuprofen work in a in a search, right?
And they're going to give you, you know, it's a basically a fat reaction, but it's a fat
and it's also a hormone and it's a pain receptor, blah, blah, blah.
And when you start reading about where this comes from and also what else it does, basically
it comes from inside the cell, an impervious cell that's produced outside of the cell.
They say the cell excretes it, but when you look at the cells, you'll see there's no opening
for it to go out, right?
So in other words, when I just gave a very sundry point, like look up how does ibuprofen
work and if you know what you're looking at, you'll see it's by induction.
Just like saying, hey, Chuck, I've got a old cassette tape, right?
You could even do this with lasers too, but I got it and I want to make a copy.
How does that work?
You can, anyone can pretty much explore what you need.
What if you have a boombox that doesn't have a record button on it?
You can't record, right?
Well, no, not necessarily true.
There is ways of transferring things without the record button because you can literally
have something like, I've done this with magnetic tapes accidentally, where if you
put them close together enough under just the right conditions, the information-
It'll ghost.
It'll ghost over, but it won't make any sense.
You'll play one song and hear the middle or wherever geometrically it worked.
That works as well.
Yeah.
Let me just go back to do a simple search and how does ibuprofen work?
How does this work?
How does that work?
It's like any drug, right?
You will see that it's usually a blocker of a receptor or a stimulator of something in
the body.
When you look at the function of what it's blocking or stimulating, it doesn't make,
there's no physical way that's happening.
It's actually being reproduced.
What they lay out is, look, here's the chemical pathway for this.
Here's the receptor for it.
This is how it works.
They tell you where the wires are.
They tell you how the plug is, but they don't explain exactly how it travels because-
Go ahead.
No.
They show you everything that it's not happening coming out of the cell, even though they say
it comes out of the cell.
Wait a second.
It's like, how does it come out of the cell?
Where is it coming out of the cell?
There's no opening in the cell wall, right?
It's lying through omission, but they're giving you-
When you lie through omission, for example, not you, but anyone, you're actually, it's
by omission.
That means that everything that you've put out is true, right?
You just left out certain things that make all those true things fit together neatly.
You see?
That's what lying by omission is.
Everything you said is the truth, but he's lying by omission.
There is a lie when they say it comes out of the cell.
They just don't tell you how.
Just like when you're dubbing the cassette tape, and I make a copy, and the copy's done.
I say, didn't this second copy, didn't this copy of that tape come out of that tape?
The first one?
But I didn't tell anyone.
No one knows how the magnetic works, and they don't care to.
This is one of the things that leads me to mental and spiritual desperation.
Everybody cover their ears.
I'm just going to tell you, Chuck, why the hell am I the only person talking about this
publicly?
That's fucking scary.
I'm using a medical term there, right?
Sorry.
That is scary, that the Greek is the only one boasting and roasting about organic and
biological induction and biological vacuum.
Yeah, Schauburger talked a little bit about biological vacuum, or water naturally does,
right?
But why am I the only one?
It can't be.
Now, here's the thing.
It only takes one person talking about it publicly, but I bet there are scores and scores of people
behind the scenes that know about this since time immemorial that are working with it.
And they're not offering it.
Yeah, frankly, it never occurred to me exactly what was happening until you said it.
And now what it's done is change the way I'm looking at a bunch of things, because I'm
saying to myself, well, if we take this concept, okay, and understand that this is a missing
piece that's always been missing, it begins to change a lot of things here, okay?
It's not about, okay, this has to be digested, and, yeah.
Hold on.
It's not missing.
It's missing cognitively.
It's only missing between years, or it's only missing in the language.
It's only missing in the communication.
It's only missing in the method and the process that people hold in their minds as how things
work.
It's not missing.
It's happening.
Because if it wasn't happening, we wouldn't be here.
Oh, no.
I get it.
I mean, that's why I love that there's a podcast I used to really enjoy called How Things Work.
And what it would do is literally lay these things out, and they would put a lot of connective
tissue together, a lot better than what everybody else was doing.
And it was like, well, see, it's all those little missing pieces in the process are what
makes ... Now, it wasn't Joe Rogan successful or anything.
I think it still exists, maybe.
Yeah.
The problem is, okay, just like the Bible, you start talking about the Bible.
If you don't say, this is going to be a discussion on the Bible, and by the way, there are no
translations in any other language before you start, right?
Because you see, and if you start using how things work, and you start using stock scientific
principles, it's not going to work.
You know why?
Because I assure you, not these guys or other guys, when they talk about how the body works,
they're going to say, what about nutrition?
It's absorbed.
How?
Show me.
Show me the ... You can't.
They use ... By the way, I've been down that road, and I've been down several roads with
people in the alternative, all fields, about, hey, listen, if you want to be more successful
in getting this out to people, and actually getting it into the hands of people who actually
use it, you're going to have to use different language.
You can't say the body is absorbing nutrition, because it's not.
Right?
You see?
This is where the catch-22 is.
Let me just divert for a moment.
Sure.
You know how you have a hole?
Something is the hole.
I mean, it's about mixing and holes, okay, and hole, W-H-O-L-E, right?
Okay.
When you have a hole, and you have a part of that hole, and you're holding that part,
you identify it as a part, because it came from something else that you consider to be
a hole.
When you hold that part in your hand that you're calling a part, guess what?
That is also a hole within itself, isn't it?
Oh, right.
That's hole in itself, right?
Yeah.
You take out your oil filter.
Yeah, you take out your oil filter out of the car.
Okay.
It is a part of the car, but it is also a hole oil filter.
Oil filter.
Right.
Exactly.
Okay.
Right?
Now, you break it down, and you just tear off a piece of the sidewall.
It's a piece of sheet metal.
It's a part of the oil filter, but it is, in itself, sheet metal, right, as a category.
You see?
It's a hole chunk of this.
It's a hole piece of that.
Right.
Hole, and again, one more time, W-H-O-L-E, the entire or complete hole.
Yes.
It's in itself its entirety, so every fragment in itself is its entirety.
So if people are trying to comprehend how the physical body works, the part where they
say absorption, right, or whatever, that is a hole in itself, meaning that part of absorption
takes over all of the other processes and methods and objects involved in how the human
body works, and now you walk away thinking you're a pressurized filter bag.
Yeah.
You see?
Well, every single process in the body, no matter what, at some point, you have to confront
this because you're in a constant state of doing this.
Yes.
The body is completely sealed, by the way.
There is nothing.
It's completely sealed, just like a thermos or a vacuum, you see?
You ever get a thermos where it doesn't keep things hot or cold anymore?
It must be leaking, right?
No, that's not the problem, but yeah, yeah, I know what you mean.
In other words, the vacuum is lost, right?
Right.
But no, look.
Very simple.
There are certain things within the apparatus of communication that if taken as a whole,
even though they're a part, it will become the whole.
So in other words, you could study the entire body and have a pretty good knowledge.
I'm not just talking about the terms.
The moment you believe you're absorbing, you are now, everything you've ever learned, you'll
be walking around thinking that things are actually permeating through tissue in the
body.
And what that does, it allows you to buy all the other stuff.
So that's how a little bit of yeast leavens the entire lump, right?
That's how that works.
Now, here's the other part.
There is an inseparable part, this is the part I said about mixing.
I'll give you a story, back in a village in Greece about 100 years ago, a man was running
a general store, happens to be a relative of mine.
And the gypsies would come through and everybody hated when the gypsies came through because
you just didn't know how they were going to get you this time.
They were really slick.
Right.
And I'm not talking about old gypsy stories where they knock when they know only the woman
is at home with the young children and they knock on the door and they're preoccupying
the one in the front door while the other ones are robbing the back, right?
Kind of thing.
Not like that.
All right.
So here's an old gypsy story.
No offense to any gypsies that might be listening, but anyway.
General store, you have bins of bulk beans and rice and flour, right?
And each one sold independently and weighed out.
So gypsy comes in, he's got a sack and he throws in two scoops of beans, same sack through
two scoops of flour, same sack, throws in two scoops of rice.
He goes to pay for it.
It's 11 drachma.
He only has two drachma.
He says, OK, if I only know if it's not enough here, take it back.
So he hands the store owner back a sack that's got flour and beans and rice mixed in together.
It's going to cost him more than the balance.
You know what I mean?
To separate that or throw it away.
He'd rather make the two drachma.
Right.
You see what I mean?
Got you.
I'll give it to you for the two drachma.
Because what am I going to do with it now?
Yeah.
I got it.
It's going to cost me more than nine drachma to clean it up.
Right.
And don't ever come here again.
That wasn't planning on anyway.
Right.
Of course.
OK.
So the same guy.
So.
So this is what's going on with them also.
Now here with people, it was so easy if you took people that were aware and you put them
on a country or an island or whatever, and then the other island, this is their stories
written about this, by the way, but more robots and other things and put the people that were
not aware on a continent, because that's what you would need and separate them.
And you have one society that's enlightened and forward moving and almost close to what
they call utopia.
By the way, the word utopia means no man's land.
Right.
But anyway, or better land.
And then the other continent would be like pretty much like it is now.
OK.
You can't have that.
Right.
You can.
You'd have to be able to defend it.
It's possible.
But that's not how it is.
Everybody's mixed in.
Right.
And even if you try to restrict communication and all that, too, there's that other concept
of the what is it, the hundredth monkey or whatever, where even if it is sitting there
permeating all by itself, somehow by induction, even without direct contact, those ideas travel.
Now, they may not travel in whole, so to speak, but somehow, you know, you teach monkeys on
one island to use tools and the other island, they start learning to use tools, even though
they've never seen the other monkeys or had communication with them.
Yeah.
That's by what?
By induction.
Induction somehow.
Right.
It just seems to be communicated without a standard communication being in place.
So there's action at a distance, just like you can copy a tape from another tape at a
distance.
Right.
It's all action at a distance, even within the body itself.
You know, the concept of fractal, you know, if you look at each cell and you study it,
it's like a small planet or a small, you know, whatever.
And by the way, there are single celled organisms that are up in the sky.
They're as large as a county.
Trevor James Constable was photographing them all the time.
They look just like amoebas, but they're about 100 miles wide.
Right.
Anyway.
OK.
So the part about the mixing.
So here's the thing.
You're all stuck in the bag.
So back to the rice, the flour and the and the beans mixed in the bag, it would be great
to come up with a recipe where you don't have to separate all that stuff and you've got
a dish that you could make out of that right up right off the cuff.
Right.
OK.
So the dish right now is this.
I tell people a lot of stuff about body nutrition, scientific stuff or whatever, and I say, work
with what you got.
What have I what have I been saying for three decades now is all of the grunt work, the
hard, heavy, digging, heavy, moving, heavy hauling has been done by mechanistic material
science.
Right.
Let's leave the denial and the censorship out right now.
So you have a base.
It's a good base if you don't want to know material to a certain point, because a lot
of the stuff they said about material, like the human body is unintuitive that you absorb.
Right.
So then you figure out how things really work and see if you can mix the two or go a couple
of sonics ago.
I said, hey, I'm getting older and I'm pushing hard sometimes.
I take a fistful of ibuprofen if I have to.
It's better than putting up with the pain.
Right.
OK.
You see.
So why?
There are other methods.
Yeah, sure.
But I find them to be convenient and they're actually pretty weak for, you know, there's
So you ever hear about people overdosing on fentanyl because it's like there I think it's
what, 20, 30, 40 times more potent than heroin.
Right.
OK.
And they overdose on it easy.
I've heard of people that that doesn't do anything for them.
Right.
Because guess what?
Well, we went over that already because they're not they can induce it.
Their body somehow cannot reproduce it.
So here's the part about everything being mixed together and the way society is right
now.
There is a level of communication.
It's all communication, by the way, that can be implemented by certain individuals that
even the most staunch mainstream closed down NPC can follow into the more ethereal or the
better way.
Right.
OK.
That communication to follow.
But each NPC will be different.
You might run into one NPC and they'll be totally cool with it.
And the other NPC will just reject it before you even open your mouth because they sense
it's going to be a drastic change to them.
Just the way a dog.
Two people approach a dog behind a fence.
One person's a dog lover, the other person's afraid of dogs.
If you let that dog out, guess who's going to bite first without either one saying anything
or doing anything.
Dog's going to bite the one who's afraid.
Yeah.
The one that's afraid.
Right.
How does he know?
He just picks up on that subtle energy.
Right.
So the subtle component with people.
Like I said, there was a table set up for vaccines and I was with someone who was an
anti-vaxxer and he started yelling at the nurses and they were laughing at him.
You're one of those whack jobs, loose nuts.
Oh, yeah.
You saw this on Facebook.
Yeah.
Or so.
Or they'll see you when he's active.
They want to get.
Don't care.
People are sick.
You're selfish.
And I go to the rest.
Are you taking into account body weight, blood type, sex and all that?
And she's like, oh, are they packed up?
They packed up.
They didn't say they couldn't look at me straight in the eye many, many times.
Why?
Same.
Now, who had the better effect?
You certainly did.
Obviously.
Now, what did I do?
Did I criticize them for what they were doing?
No, I criticized them for what?
What they weren't doing.
Well, you asked a proper question, which they did not want to answer.
So you got.
Well, here's the thing.
There was an older nurse that knew this.
The younger ones didn't know that the younger ones were ready to kick the same line that
they kicked to the other guy.
What does that tell you?
Their education has changed.
Of course.
One of the women were in their 60s.
She knew.
OK, so.
All right.
So what was put in that?
Because I'm going to have to come back to it for another email.
But go ahead.
No.
OK, so that's.
So this is around.
Look, these sonics, it's kind of hard to set them to music, right?
Yeah, for sure.
So.
So what's the other email?
Well, the other email actually had to do about an older sonic that we did regarding external
input, which fits perfectly into the conversation.
That's why I'm bringing it out.
And the thing is, they were talking about dreams and they had listened to the recent
discussion about the inner voice.
Now, if we are all at all times subject to external input, how does one source or sort?
Excuse me.
The difference between what is coming from external input in your dreams and what may
indeed be coming from your true internal voice during a dream state, because they
are kind of confused as to what is happening when they're having disturbing dreams.
So yeah, that was an interesting.
Yeah.
Easy.
The same beings are similar beings.
Let's say the ones that give you the voice that you think is your voice and the dreams
is considered the military.
Within the military, you have Navy, Army, Air Force, right?
Different branches.
Sure.
Within these beings, the waking conscious voice that you think is you because it sounds
like you.
Right.
And it both.
It's morally flexible.
So part of you says, for example, oh, I want to go get that.
But oh, that.
But the other party says that's wrong.
It controls both sides.
Right.
OK.
So the way you stop the dreams and the way you stop the external input is when you anticipate
it.
If you think that you're being overrun by voices and you say, OK, I hear your voices
and all that.
But what do you have to say now?
And the moment you tell them that you're anticipating that you're listening, they stop.
Because that's that's not how they're supposed to.
You're supposed to think that it's you.
The moment you anticipate them, you're busted.
They stop.
They can't keep talking because if they keep talking, they're just going to give up, give
up the whole thing.
Right.
OK.
The same with dreams.
If you there's two ways.
One is.
You want to people go to fantasy parks or brothels or movies or these external entertainment.
Right.
They pay.
Why not say I want to go to bed tonight and I want to go to a brothel in ancient India.
I want to dream about that.
Right.
OK.
The chances of you dreaming at all is like next to nothing the moment you say that because
you just anticipated it.
Right.
Well, I've noticed that when I wanted to return to something like let's just keep it real
general, say I, you know, gotten to some like really cool scenario and I was enjoying myself
in the dream.
The next night, I, you know, kind of say to myself, oh, I want to I used to do this a
long time ago.
I want to go back to that.
I want to go, you know, visit that place again.
That doesn't happen.
OK.
Here, here.
Let me inject something here for whatever it's worth, because you can get information
from anywhere.
And if you have enough, how would you call it, Moxie to source out the bullshit from the
good stuff?
It's still good.
It doesn't matter where it comes from.
It's information.
Right.
Years ago, when I was looking into all this stuff, I got word from someone that every paranormal
research facility ever known, whether it's Vanilla Surface or Black Project, that what
they all agree on when they research dreams, psychics, remote viewing, astral projection,
ET abduction.
OK.
What they all agreed on is this one thing that when we sleep, our consciousness is being
used somewhere else.
That's what they all agreed on.
They don't know why or how or when they each have their own program of specialty.
Right.
But what they all agreed on is that when we're sleeping, that sleep function, yes, it's tied
in biologically.
You know, if you don't sleep for a week, you die, maybe less, right?
Right.
Biology.
The biology just just kicks in, just blows a fuse and you're done.
Right.
But not blows a fuse.
The bus bar burns out.
You're done.
Most cases, sleep deprivation is a form of torture, by the way.
Right.
Sleep deprivation is recognized worldwide by every single organization possible.
That is a way of torturing somebody.
Yes.
To death possibly.
Right.
As well.
So all of these these research, quote unquote, groups, both vanilla and black, meaning above
board that you they write, you see their stuff in art, scientific magazines and the black
ops that you can surmise.
They all agree whether that we're being used.
OK, now that is a question that I cannot answer directly.
I'll give you something personal.
All right.
So when I'm in a pinch, either emotionally, spiritually or physically or whatever, and
I need a break.
Yeah.
And it's just like when I'm in a pinch, meaning like I have a heavy burden on me because let's
say I'm making something and it has to be delivered on a certain time and it ain't going
right or it's not good enough for me and I just don't have the time to make it better.
And I need to clear my mind.
And I know you walk away from a few minutes, do something different, right?
Come back to it.
It doesn't clear whether it's relationship based, work based, anything.
What I do.
This is this is I'll share this.
I imagine that there is a parallel world with me just like me might look a little different.
Like once I had a dream that I looked in the mirror and it was a short Latin guy.
OK.
Right.
I was like, wait a second.
That's not me.
Right.
I imagine that there is another parallel world running.
That's me.
My spirit's being shared there and they're not having this problem.
They're enjoying something else at the moment.
Then, boom, when I come back, it's as if I really got away from what I wanted to get
away from.
Hmm.
You know what I mean?
OK.
Yeah.
It's like Greek.
You got imaginary.
Well, that works for me.
I just wanted to share that.
That there is a parallel.
You wait.
Wait.
If our sleep is being used, we're being our consciousness is being used when we're sleeping
in there.
Mostly everyone agreed to the researchers and stuff.
How far off is what I just said?
That's an area that there is a parallel world with another one of me.
And I just go there, share their consciousness for a moment.
And then I come back here in my mind.
And I did get the clearing, the break that I needed.
Right.
Well, to some degree or another, almost anybody who attempts, you know, either self-help or,
you know, or spiritual guidance or personal guidance, life coach, all these types of people,
no matter how useless most of them appear to be, almost none of them would complain
about the idea of positive visualization.
Right.
Where if you simply take yourself mentally out of the situation, you know, by your own
will and go somewhere else and envision something positive, this is usually a helpful thing.
Right.
Yeah.
One way or another.
Like you want a Ferrari.
You know, they got Nishin, what is it, Nishin Daikonen.
What's her name?
She recently died.
Tina Turner.
She's into that.
It's a form of Shintoism where you meditate.
So there's a crane and you chant Nishin Daikonen, something like that.
And in that you envision you want a red Corvette, you want a red Corvette.
You meditate like that every day, you chant 15 minutes a day, somehow within a short time
you'll get a red Corvette.
Right.
I don't know if you know about the Nishin Daikonen, they call it.
Yeah.
No, I agree with it.
It's to manifest things.
Right.
That's part of it.
That's a very, maybe 10%, 5% of it.
Okay.
So if you know there's a parallel reality and in this reality, you want to, let's say
a Corvette, you don't have one and you can't afford, you don't know how you're going to
afford one.
Start thinking every day like, oh, I got to go pick up my red Corvette.
It's getting an oil change.
Maybe it's done now.
I know this sounds crazy.
Maybe you say, oh, don't say you just keep creating psychosis.
Right.
Yeah.
I could create a psychosis.
Right.
Uh, but if you're, if you're not in control, but in this, in essence, that is one way to
manifest, you know, that, uh, that feeling, because if you don't look, you know how the
universe gives stuff people when they're ready to get it right.
If you don't have something and you want something, but you act as if you have it, you're going
to see if you're ready for it.
The moment you start acting as if you have it, don't you, you might want something and
you never thought that you should act like you should have that thing.
And the moment you really start emailing, let's say the email gets involved.
I'm not talking about the email.
I talk about, but emotionally you feel like you have it and it scares the living daylights
out of you.
Hmm.
You might want to rethink wanting to have that.
Right.
Yeah.
Of course.
You see how well that works.
Now I wanted to get into a couple other things.
Do you want to go, go on with the messages you've got?
No, I think that's good.
I mean, there might've been a couple of things in chat you might want to address.
Um, yeah, I'm outside right now.
I'm doing this on a stupid rectangle, uh, because I think there was noise on the other
end of the house.
So this is what I wanted to bring up from memory.
I went through, uh, the earlier things that I picked up on was what the silver, a couple
of questions that, um, uh, were a little off one.
It makes me wonder if people are actually getting what I'm saying and I'm not going
to cover that part.
I'm just going to cover that.
This concept.
Well, a couple of people were excited.
I just want to note that a couple of people were excited.
But some of the questions were a little off from, from the, the, the, the mindset that
I like to communicate and the mindset is if it's not biocompatible, it's not, it doesn't
mean it's 100% not, but it's going to be materialistically, you know, like in material science, in order
to get a certain by a chemical or vitamin in the body, you have to physically, you know,
get it into the body.
Right.
And I'm saying that the body, if you were to be exposed to it, the body doesn't take
it in physically, even though it appears physically it's induced.
Right.
So it has to be biocompatible.
What biocompatible means that it's ready to be ready for induction, right?
It's like, you know, T remember the years ago, the TVs, they said cable ready on them.
Right.
Oh yeah.
Okay.
So stuff like they have to be induction ready.
So with the silver, this is the thing also, there was a question about charge.
If you spray it, does the charge go away?
I've given the analogy before.
And the one thing I want to address also, there's a lot of new people that haven't been
listening to Greek speak for years, like many have.
So we have to kind of recap.
And every time you recap, it comes out a little different and throws in a little more, you
know, detail.
Let's say we gave, I gave an example with water.
It's very interesting.
Please I don't want to get into water in it because I'm actually working on water intensely
now for the past month or so.
And there's a lot I can say about it.
And then, and you know, the old adage, the more you study or you think, you know you realize
how little, you know, yes.
I'm getting to that point where it's scary and scary and what's going on.
It's beyond anything I've ever talked about.
But let's go back to the part with when you spray and with the water.
Chuck, I'm on one end of a large swimming pool.
You're on the other end of a swimming pool.
You drop you drop a glass of water on your end and I take a glass of water on my end.
Is it the same water?
No.
Are you sure about that?
I don't think it is.
I think it is not specifically the same water.
It does change the amount if we have glasses that are the same size.
Yeah.
I mean, I mean, what the water can do.
What I'm trying to say is this.
Once the water integrates, once you drop water in somewhere, it becomes water.
Right.
OK.
So the charge that's held in the spray bubble when you atomize the liquid.
By the way, I might have to revisit that because that's a big conversation on its own.
And there's several ways you can view it.
Right.
But either way you view it, it shows you how big this this topic is.
When you spray, if you get a close up camera with some ultraviolet or infrared light and
you look at the little spray atomization bubbles, they look like like water spheres floating
in the air.
Right.
Or moving through the air.
And if you zoom in on it and you fill the picture frame with it and you ask someone,
how big is that?
I don't know how big that is.
It looks pretty big.
Right.
Yeah.
Like you ever see a close up of the ball on the end of a ballpoint pen, a good close
up.
It looks like a bowling ball.
Depends on how much you enlarge the image in the resolution.
Or an ant can look like a giant monster, depending on how you view it.
OK, fine.
Sure.
Well, what I'm telling you is the water body itself is is a water body.
That little atomized droplet is a water body, just like an Olympic sized swimming pool is
a water body.
Right.
Not an ocean or a lake.
Because those are different.
There are types of those are living.
You can classify a sea, an ocean, a lake and a river as being an independent animal, like
a wolf, a dog and a fox.
OK.
Right.
Even though they're independent.
Those are three different independent.
They're not all canine, but they're considered.
But they're not.
So this charge that's held on that once it makes its landing, it decides whether or not
it's the same material or not.
And that's where the charge prevails or not.
In other words, opposites do not attract all these same things attract.
But for example, when you put water on a freshly waxed car hood, the water beads up because
it was all as if all the water wants to join itself together.
Actually, it does.
If you you know, when the water beads on a wax surface, if you just move it left to right,
you'll see those little beads attaching to each other.
Yes.
Right.
They will.
And then they'll break off again.
OK.
If you pour hot wax on that wax thing, it would just lay down just fine.
I'll be on the hood saying, oh, I love you.
I love you.
Right.
Not not pulling away.
So like always goes with like.
And just like, for example, in classification and mining, you know, the heavies go to the
bottom.
Not some of the heavies, all of the heavies and all the light things go up to the top
liquefaction.
Right.
Not some of the light things.
All of the light things go up.
Right.
So these classifications and determinations are based on like goes with like.
If like goes with like didn't work, about 90 percent of all industrial processes would
not work.
So our natural processes also.
So when the water droplet, again, I feel like I'm doing a thesis on this, sees the skin
as a charge.
We just let's say the water droplet holds a charge.
It's not as much as a pool of water, an Olympic sized swimming pool, but it's the same.
It holds the charge exactly the same way.
Exactly the same way.
And when it meets the skin, it sees something that can induce in both directions.
But more induction on the way out than the way in for water.
Right.
OK.
So you'll sweat more than you'll pee more.
Right.
Or in other words, your body can still take in water through the skin, but not enough
to satisfy you to keep you from dying of thirst, you see.
And by the way, you will live longer if you're in fresh water in your skin and we can't drink
it.
Then if you're in salt water, because when you're in salt water, you'll die of thirst
faster because the water is going to also induce the salt.
Right.
It's very simple.
You will not separate.
You're not a reverse osmosis.
So this gets into, again, the member we just mentioned, fentanyl is killing people because
it's 20, 30, 40, 50 times, depending on the mix, stronger than heroin.
But there's people I've heard that can take it all day like gummy bears.
It doesn't do anything.
Right.
The charge effect on the body is exactly the same.
So that is a big subject.
That's why I always mentioned to people what I do is I bring up a scenario.
I bring up the aqua sargentum and then I bring up how you can use it and how you can use it,
meaning you put it in a spray bottle.
Very, very handy.
Easier than pouring.
Actually, just putting something in a spray bottle and misting it will last a lot longer
than pouring it.
Right.
Of course.
And also it holds more of a charge because each droplet, the surface area of each droplet
picks up the charge in the air.
Right.
Because you see lightning in the air.
You don't see it underwater.
Right.
It is possible, but it's unlikely.
So yeah, in other words, the field's collapsing and it'll draw more energy to itself.
So that is a big, big question.
And the thing is, that's why I suggest to people I'll bring up a scenario, let's say skin condition
that's having, you're having a hard time.
Try this.
It doesn't mean it'll work every time.
Right.
This is not square, square peg and square hole stuff.
And I'm not saying take a square peg and whittle it to round to make it fit in a round hole
either.
Right.
So these things are things that need to be brought out that I feel, believe it or not,
need to be brought up because they'll help people on the on a dime.
This is like nickel and dime stuff.
Right.
Very, very inexpensive, very easy to do and exponential increase in quality of life.
The other thing I wanted to bring up, I think Vandy asked in there about mold on the inside
of a stone building, oxygenate it.
That was the quick, you know how you use bleach to get rid of mold?
Yeah.
Sodium hypochlorite is a very strong, what, oxygenator.
Right.
Hydrogen peroxide is a oxygenator, but it's not in the form of a salt.
So it doesn't stick around as long.
The word oxygen means sharp, generating in Greek, right?
Oxis means like, you know, right.
Be careful.
That's oxis.
That's sharp.
Right.
Like usually the tip of a point or quick.
So oxygenating several ways to do it.
If you can't, if you don't have any quote unquote chemical oxygenators acids, if you
have a, let's say you want to produce oxygen, right?
With from water.
The side of the device that produces oxygen and electrolysis is always acidic.
The side that produces hydrogen is always alkaline.
So hydrogen is alkaline, oxygen is an acid.
So if you have a mildew problem and you don't have oxygenators like industrial ones like
hydrogen peroxide or sodium hypochlorite, which is just laundry bleach, right?
You guess what?
Another typical thing is vinegar.
Vinegar is acidic, isn't it?
Yeah.
Lemon juice.
Actually, I would rather be spraying vinegar than spraying bleach.
You know, yeah.
Fumes from vinegar are not going to kill you.
You know, they can hurt you.
They can hurt you.
They can make you go blind, actually.
But yeah, but you, you're more likely to injure yourself with fumes from the others.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
A long term, long term chronic condition too.
Bleach, you know, bleach in an enclosed area, not good.
You know, I mean, I'm just saying you get too high of a concentration in the lungs and
it becomes a problem.
Yeah.
And if you have ammonia around and you mix bleach, guess what you get?
Oh yeah.
Well, that's the, uh, mustard mustard gas.
Yeah.
So rudimentary.
Anyway.
Yeah.
I'm surprised they have bleach and ammonia at this in the supermarkets on the same aisle.
Somebody just running down the aisle with a big razor blade, you know, anyway.
You know, I often think of that. Why are they like right next to each other on the shelf?
Don't people think, you know, these, you don't want to mix them together.
It's like putting fireworks next to the barbecue fluid or something, or I don't know,
next to the cigarette lighters, whatever. Yeah. Not everything is for our interest, right?
Yeah. I don't know. I've always said that.
I just wanted to bring that up with mold and mildew. And by the way, they do some of the self,
the household hint books and stuff do talk about the using vinegar. Actually,
even I was at a dollar store recently. Now they're putting out cleaning vinegar
instead of, you know, all the chemicals. I haven't seen that yet. Okay.
Yeah. It's okay. It's, it's denatured. So it doesn't smell like it doesn't have that
pungent smell. It has a little bit of soap in it.
I saw club soda bottled that way, but I've never seen vinegar bottled that way.
You know, like a club soda to clean like, you know, a cloth and things.
I don't know. I've never seen that.
Yeah. They had club soda like that for a little bit, but yeah.
Yeah. So anyway, most of these things require strong oxygenation and acids do that. Anybody
drops acid on a side of muriatic acid, sulfuric acid starts foaming up, right?
Or just the same way, anything that oxygenate does. So acids oxygenate. So acids for mold and
mildew, which are anaerobic conditions, anaerobic meaning anaerobic, meaning lack of oxygen. You
get moisture, you get a water leak, right? And you pull up the carpet a week later, what do you
see? Mold, right? You don't see it right on top of the carpet. Usually you don't, or on the wall
where it's open. Usually it's behind areas that don't get air circulation.
Right. That's, that's how it is. It's denied air or it makes right. Yeah, exactly.
Yeah. So anything that has anything like that and certain types of bacterial growth, also acid
is the way to go. A lemon juice is another, you know, there's so many citric acid powder that
you can get it anywhere. They use it. Yeah. People buy it for canning. People make jams and
so any, any goods grocery store will sell citric acid powder crystals, you know, for the canners.
Actually they're, they're not encouraging canning. And they consider you a survivalist. If you say
you're canning, they make fun of you, right? Now you're a prepper, right? Yeah. Right. Right.
But you could still get it. It's usually about 10 bucks a pound in Australia, probably 30 bucks
a pound, but always have that on hand. If you don't use vinegar, by the way, or citric acid in
a washing machine regularly, because the type of acetyl and nitrile rubber that they use for all
the hoses is very susceptible and all your hoses will deteriorate. I mean, crumble. And you know
what that means with a washing machine and wash cycle. So yeah, right. They'll, they'll dry up
kind of in split. Oh, you will lose. Yeah. Yeah. Especially when you put it on max load and you
wonder where, yeah. And the second floor, you ruin the whole house. So yeah, don't use a, you
could use it once a year to clean it out and, but do a cycle right away, but don't use it when there's
rubber around, don't use it on swimming pools, things like that. Right. Eat away. Right. So be,
be smart about it. The only thing I wanted to throw out the washing machine thing, because
I'd say about a quarter of the washing machines are most three quarters of the washing machines
that people think they need to keep using vinegar or better laundry will destroy the washing machine
and their house. So I just wanted to put that out just in case people are whatever.
Well, it's like once in a while, it's good to, you know, throw, throw like a cap full of bleach
in there and run it with nothing in it, you know, kind of thing. That's good once in a while,
but not all the time. No, the best thing is to, well, I shouldn't say, but you need to start
water. Everybody's got to improve their water quality. And maybe in the near future, we'll
get more into that, make it more readily available. But right now when it's been
becoming a hell of a ride for me. So. All right. Absolutely. Look,
this has been a great piece. Now, did you have something else you wanted to grab from chat
or because I was thinking, no, it's just one more thing from memory is they got into a little
bit of some old rits about the soul being the breath and the spirit being the mind and the heart.
Okay. And these, these are hard to find because the past 500 years, they've messed up all the
definitions, right? It got actually so messed up that we actually wish each other a nice day.
Think about that. That's pretty messed up. Yeah. So, so if you go back more than 500 years,
it was commonly known, well, not common, but it was well known that the spirit is the mind
and the personality. The soul is the metabolism. What allows living things to be alive. It's
interchangeable amongst all living things. Right. And that was, and that just came up and how the
which means spirit in Chinese or close to it or heart is very close to the PSI in Greek, right?
Shen side, very not too far off. Right. Right. So I think that's, that's it for now. I can go
check out the chat and, you know, literally look at it again, but anything for you?
No. Yeah. One more thing, actually. But, but just to tack on to what you were saying,
it's very interesting. You look at the language today, there's still some of it preserved there
because psychology is what it's not about the, you know, it's the mind. Okay. But
psi is also spirit, right? It's like both things. The mind, the spirit is the mind.
Right. But both things are in the definition. So a psychologist and someone who is into the psychic
things, et cetera, et cetera, you're talking about, and I don't mean psychic, like, you know,
dial me up 1-800-whatever. It's the same, the same prefix, psychotic, psychopath,
psychiatrist, psychologist, all of these things, mind and spirit are the same.
The same, right? Because your mind is who you are and your spirit is who you are, but your pneuma,
where you get pneumatic, pneumonia, right? Right. Means the movement of air. What's the first thing
even in the movies say? Is he breathing? No, he's not breathing. I guess he's done.
Yeah. Right. That's your pneuma. They switch it. It's very easy to deflect. Just switch.
Look, if you want to keep a, if I want to give you a combination to my locker
and you know that the first two numbers are reversed, I could say, Hey, combination for my
lockers, five, three, one, Chuck. But we already, you already know the first two numbers have to
be reversed for it to work. So when you get the five, three, one, you say, oh, so the combination
is three, five, one, right? Right. See how it works. That's how it's all you got to do is put
everything out, but just make it so it's in the wrong order. Exactly. So look, the last thing I
wanted to go through, and then we'll, we'll bring this one to a close is a, is pretty simple. It
came up because of the current events actually. And, uh, just wanted to see if you had anything
to say about it, because I know you're probably not paying too much attention to any of this, but
Bobby Kennedy jr. Is out there making some statements and they sort of attacked him.
I found it interesting, not because of the political element of it or any of that,
but, uh, he was talking about who was susceptible to certain things. And, uh, and he said that,
you know, uh, certain people are not as susceptible to, uh, the, the, you know, the virus,
whatever. Okay. Now look, forget, forget the premise. All right. Uh, here's the thing about
it that I found interesting is that they started calling him racist and all this other stuff. Um,
and I said to myself, but this is idiocy due to the fact that, uh, ethnicity, uh, has something
to do with what you're susceptible to or not. There is, you know, and I'm not saying that
people should be treated differently, medical racism, medical racism. Yeah. Which is weird
because I'm sorry. There's scientific fact. That's true. That's certain. Look the most basic
low hanging fruit really quick. And then I want you to attack it is this, um, the sickle cell
anemia, right? Okay. Uh, look, not everybody is susceptible to sickle cell anemia. Okay. Only
that is black or no, I'm sorry. Black Cooley's anemia is for black people. Sickle cell anemia
is a certain European group. No, no, no. Other way around. Other way around. Okay. Sickle cell is,
is, uh, you, you have to have African blood. You have to be, uh, you know, yeah. It's when the
cell inverts itself and it does, it clumps or it doesn't quite get right now. Cooley's anemia,
quite frankly, is, uh, Italians get it. And why? Because they actually share some ethnic heritage
with Africa. This is the reason why. And it is almost the same thing. It's much more severe
than that, but go ahead. Well, I'm just saying in a general sense though, right? If you're Irish,
say, or if you're a Lithuanian, the likelihood of you getting sickle cell anemia is very low. Now,
all I'm saying is or non-existent or non-existent. Yeah. Very, very low non-existent. However you
want to go. The point is that based on ethnicity, there is just a truth that some things are,
you know, present themselves more often and not you brought up one time. And this is where I'm
going to link it all together and hand it to you brought up. And, uh, you know, it's apparently
true. They don't sell certain drugs in Asia. Why? Because it is completely destructive
to their physiology. Prozac to be exact. There you go. Okay. But that's a scientific reality.
That is not about racism. That's not saying treat Asians differently. You know what I'm saying?
Like if you said we should treat Asians differently than we should treat, you know,
white people under the law. Yeah. I think you should treat different ethnicities different
because that preserves their culture. Well, yes. But, but, but equal, but equal protection
under the law, equal rights under the law. Well, that happens anyway, unless the law is competency
in order for the law to be competent, to be applied to someone, whether it's backwards,
the person has to be competent. Okay. If you stood good, if you're going to trial, uh,
tomorrow to court, uh, let's say, uh, about, uh, you stealing a horse and on your way to
court the next morning, you steal another horse and get caught. That that trial is for the horse
that you were accused of stealing prior, not the one you just stole, but it's pretty damn convincing
that you're a horse thief. You know what I mean? You see what I mean? Let's just put it this way.
You go into court because you were caught stealing a car and on your way to court,
you steal another car and get caught. Uh, it's going to be kind of hard. They shouldn't,
they can't use that. You just stole a car as evidence that you stole the other one,
but the character, uh, shows speaks for itself, right? Okay. You should be found guilty for
stealing cars or horses at that point, because that's your character, right? Yeah. Give me an
example. Every culture and race should be treated differently. If you want to preserve that culture
and race, an example, I'll give a loose example. When I'm watching, uh, what they call a movie or
something, even recently, there's watching some piece of a movie, a trailer from an old movie
where Nicholas Cage is in a bathrobe laying down in bed. And the camera comes from the end, uh,
his bedroom, uh, and the camera comes from the end and it's almost passes like a big giant,
like almost not a zoom, but his, his, the bottoms of his feet are in most of the frame and then
goes up the robe and shows his face on a telephone. Okay. Okay. If that film is going to be shown in
the middle East, that entire scene has to be edited out because in the middle East,
if you show the bottoms of your feet, that's like in a Western culture,
showing the middle finger. Okay. You see that? So, so I keep pointing that out. Oh, you see that
showing the bottoms of the feet here? That's that would be edited out. If it was shown in Yemen,
Saudi Arabia, UAE, Iraq, it would be edited out. I assure you for sure that would be edited out
the whole scene. So, or it'd be adjusted. You could tell some, you're a watch a film that's
made for another country. It looks certain scenes look really grainy because they have to zoom in
only in the part that's appropriate to show. And when they zoom in on it, they lose resolution.
Right. So, okay. So you have to adjust based on the culture and because that is slightly
different race that you can say, right. Race has culture as well. We'll see. But adjusting actions
based on culture is one thing to say that recognizing that there is a difference because
of cultural realities and ethnic realities is yet another. Okay. Let me, let me get more specific
on the stuff that I've been repeating for a long time. Sure. I'm an anesthesiologist. I paid two
and a half million dollars a year in insurance. Yes. Anesthesiologists, as I think there may
premiums might be higher than that. Okay. Right. Okay. I have two, I have to put two people down
down, but you anesthetize them. I have two people coming to me for an apodectomy. One is the girl
in Wendy's. She's a 90 pounds, redhead with freckles. And the other one is Shaquille O'Neal,
300 pound black guy. Okay. Okay. The amount of anesthesia that I have to administer to the Wendy's
daughter, the red 90 pound redhead girl with freckles will kill Shaquille O'Neal. That doesn't
make any sense because she's 90 pounds. He's 300 pounds. It means he takes three times plus,
right? The amount that I would have to give the little tiny 90 pound white girl with red hair
and freckles. I keep emphasizing red hair and freckles. Right. Right. We'll kill Shaquille
O'Neal. Right. Right. So that's not because he's Shaquille O'Neal. And the other one is her dad
has a hamburger company. No, it has to do with, with race big time. Also the reason why so many
people in Korea, Japan and parts of China and Taiwan died with the Prozac and all these other
tests. Now they might have Prozac now in Asia, but it's not the same chemical to administer to
the Westerners. They call it Prozac or whatever. Right. Because all these names, if they look at
the chemical name, they try to shorten it to see if it'll work in the pub. You know what I mean?
Right. Right. So, uh, yeah, this goes, this is on, on and on and on and on, but it's disregarded
again when they give, if anytime they have a one size fits all, it's a scam. And it's pretty
obvious with the recent injection scheme that they had. But fortunately, I keep saying this,
no humans got the shot. Fortunately. Anyway, what does he mean by that? What are the 50 million
people in the U S got? Uh, well, I'm still sticking to it. They weren't, they weren't
really people, but anyway. All right. Let's just call them Guinea pigs for now. Fair enough.
Uh, no, I get it. It's just, I just found it remarkable that nobody bothered to take a moment
and say, you know what, there might be a difference based on, uh, not, not just ethnicity, but
cultural exposure to certain things. You know, if nobody in a culture eats a particular food,
they might not ever get toxicity from said food. You know what I'm saying? If, if there are people
that are, here's the thing right now is to anyone that comes from Asia, Europe, or the continent
of Africa, people say Africa, like it's a country, right? Anyway, uh, when they come here to the
States, the first thing they notice is, uh, well, the first comment they'll make,
especially if they're sensitive, uh, you ask them about the food, they'll say,
it tastes like everything has was poisoned. Right. Right. Think about it. Oh, I know that's
a Testament. Hey, that's a Testament to the robustness of the human condition, the human
body where we could take a, well, I'll leave you off with this Betty white comment. Uh, she's Greek
too, by the way, was what a dummy man. She was telling her to get a vaccine. She got hers. She
dies the next day. Right. Anyway, maybe a non-human Greek. So she says, everybody says, you know,
balls are tough, but vaginas, man. Oh, they could take a pounding anyway. Fair enough. But I just,
I just find it remarkable that there's always things that can be learned by observing the
silliness of others when they, uh, when they get into it, it's racist to say that about, and I'm
like, how is that in a way that it should be done? A racist is not a bad word, by the way,
it just become a bad word, like anarchists and all this other stuff. It doesn't say anything.
When you say you're racist, you know, the real races are man and woman, you know? So all men
of any race, quote unquote, will be more similar than any women of any race within the race. Right.
So if you separate, if you had a group of people, some people don't like calling people black or
Negro or what a dark skin or African-American, whatever. Um, uh, they don't like that. And so
just use the term that's accepted. If you take a white males, black males, Asian males, uh,
native American ESCO, put them in one side, they'll get, and he'd take the same in women,
black women, white women, Inuit, Asian women, put them on the other side. They will get along
those two separate one mixed race, female group, one mixed race, male group. Those groups will get
along better than if you had them all mixed together, male and female. That's a Carlos
Castaneda thing I've picked up by. It's one thing that I, I liked where he says the rate,
the real races are man and woman, male and female. That's the real race in two races
and the most evident by the way. So there you go.