Sonic Advent 230 and here we are and
Greek how you today again I ask I'm
doing yeah much better on a laptop I
hope the audio is a little better the
old iPhone that I have is just not
hacking the this type of transmission so yeah
I want to go to the chat real
quick you have some stuff Vandy posted some
Michio Kushi stuff and nice there's really not
much to go anywhere on macrobiotics or that
kind of philosophy other than people's like what
do they call them when you do a
website to talk about your personal experiences kind
of thing Oh like a blog yeah yeah
yeah right and you could look up some
of his books but one thing I met
Michio Kushi I don't know him very well
but I did not know him very well
I when I was at the New York
City Macrobiotic Center they they had an honorary
dinner for him and Shizuko asked me to
bake to make the dessert mind you I
was only there for a few months and
but anyway I baked this carrot cake macrobiotic
sort of vegan yeah mm-hmm and it's
always good to make the cake a day
before like if you know anyone who has
like a cake business especially for high and
you know wedding cakes would cost 5,000
bucks right and yeah or more and so
you always make the actually wedding cakes you
freeze them when you freeze the sponge the
cake and thaw it out it gets moist
but supposedly hmm okay I was sort of
aware so anyway I made the entire cake
the day before next day of I opened
the fridge I had a frosting on it
was made with some spices agar-agar kuzu
silken soy milk a bunch of other stuff
like you know vegetable stuff really nice frosting
or icing icing okay there's a difference in
frosting and icing I think what's supposed to
be thicker than the other but anyway okay
I opened the fridge the next day and
all the icing frosting is gone it got
absorbed into the cake so now I had
a cake with no I just look like
a plain cake the two-layer cake I
panicked so I made it again and put
it on this time it stayed so ended
up turning like a rum cake see because
when you put those frostings you know when
you whip you creams and things you make
butter right or hydrogen it's very durable where
if you whip certain vegetable stuff and it's
not hydrogenated it doesn't support itself very long
kind of like a cappuccino imagine a cappuccino
in the fridge overnight it's no longer a
cappuccino right so yeah so anyway I anyway
make a long story short I met him
there once and I met him again but
we're looking reading his books very dogmatic very
very dogmatic he's almost like really angry about
Americans he's happy about being here some weird
story but it's very dogmatic in the end
of his life he started speaking more on
how you should just eat traditional right so
if you're in Saudi Arabia don't keep donkey
milk is fine right okay or cat I'm
sorry can't camel milk is fine camel milk
all right camel milk but from someone that
knows him sick meet you you know they
said they died of cancer he would secretly
have a rice cooker for regular white rice
and salted salmon and when no one was
around or when he wanted to be alone
he told people not to come over he
would prepare regular white rice and salted salmon
for himself on a regular basis and a
couple of people that I knew personally found
him in the closet with some young intern
ladies he was married so he's not perfect
and he's very dogmatic he brings forward some
good information I personally would not recommend him
to beginners or overall unless you know the
warning I just gave you very dogmatic so
but most of the information that is neutral
without his opinion let's say on it is
pretty good because he's just referring bringing forward
what was around for thousands of years anyway
so I like to mix experimental you know
the province of the mind has no limits
and it's to be experienced experimentation right right
that's John C.
Lilly not just you hear people talk about
just experience well most people are just too
dead from the neck up to for any
experience to matter first of all but when
you say experience through experimentation if you're learned
about the real scientific method or the scientific
method it gives you protocols for experimentation right
right you got your theory hypothesis experiment conclusion
and other things so you have to be
a good observer you have to have controls
be able to take measurement be able to
communicate what you're doing and the results you
have to be honest in terms of objective
if you do exclusions mention them that's how
I live my life and I always have
people when we had circles of social people
when they met someone they would always come
to me and say hey do you know
so-and-so I'm thinking of dating or
what do you think and they knew that
whatever I said held water you know what
I mean okay why because my experience with
that person was experimental that's X sounds kind
of weird though right there because when you
say what did you experiment with yeah nothing
like that but you know it meaning I
observed them that try to based on certain
whatever benchmark so I'm glad that he put
that video up and I know more and
more people are watching it that kind of
stuff and that's a very good foundation but
there's really no way to simplify outside of
microbiotics what Michio is doing and that's what
I try to do that's why I don't
even want to call it yin and yang
at all but I call it expansive contractive
balance of universal principles so I just want
to bring that up because it's good it's
very rare that someone puts up a Michio
video but also Vandy asked about some guy
having his head almost severed and put on
ice now you got to give me information
Vandy where you got that source of that
because we have this thing in America I
think you call it Chinese whispers here it's
called telephone right where you start when one
story goes from one place to another could
have been the guy lost his wallet and
he saw you know a severed head and
ended up being by time he gets the
story that his head was severed and you
put in an ice barrel you know I
don't know so if it's a lot otherwise
I'm not going to invest money much in
it and the guy regular one two three
four five six put up a video for
a tick tock video about aliens talking about
how screwed or rugged humans are for having
a monetary system as they do which I
keep talking about so right and I posted
an old interview I didn't this is where
Chuck and I I was asked to fill
in for Vinny Eastwood I said no and
then you filled in for it I went
back to see who filled in for it
that's how got introduced to you right and
I had done one prior way prior to
that for Vinny and I had Trevor James
Constable as the guest and that's what that's
posted on the chat recently and I think
there's other stuff we can address but I
posted some public enemy stuff and super sperm
I don't know if you guys know Captain
Sky you remember that song super sperm I
you know you mentioned this to me before
and it's still not ringing a bell I
don't remember even going to look it up
all right well it's on the chat you
could you could public enemy my 88 Delta
88 by Oldsmobile 88 mm-hmm that song
in the they use the samples from that
oh they sample then I put up the
samples from super sperm and in public enemy
public enemies the album mm-hmm I guess
from 1984 85 think about it most some
actually I would say I don't know but
venture to say half or most or some
of our subs were not even born yet
believe it or not yeah that is a
weird thought so yeah yeah well sometimes when
you and I go back into like the
70s and 80s I mean to them that
that might as well be what you know
the 1800s because it's just outside of their
experiences and so I always find that interesting
anyway you know somebody sent me one of
the longest messages ever like it's an email
length serious message right and he tells me
I've gotten a 24 by the way I've
gotten a 24 page PDF email right well
24 so when you say long and it's
a page or two okay deal with it
no hey look nobody related to what we
do here has sent me a message like
that in email they do that for JFK
stuff they send me you know a thousand
page treatise on something and go what is
your thought you know and they want it
in five minutes just read the conclusion yeah
I know I go back to the conclusion
should wrap it up right I go backwards
and I skim and then I can usually
get it done in 15 but you can't
get it in five okay you know anyway
is that this is pretty interesting though and
I want to read the whole thing and
pause and let you address each piece of
it okay I would really appreciate the law
information I have paid thousands of dollars for
different teachers and it's still very confusing to
me some people say I need to rescind
all my documents others say that's not necessary
so I stopped right go ahead okay I
would rescind what is what is not necessary
like lice any license any corporation is a
rescission but it's not they don't have an
offer for a rescission is different rescission is
for a contract you could rescind what you
do is you cancel them right you would
cancel them or annul them and that most
of these things do have forms for that
what you can't cancel is a social security
number and the straw man just don't use
it I had I had spent a year
trying to get high up people in the
Social Security Administration finally did in the US
Treasury and it's their creation so you you
know you you had no part in it
there's a baby act about that something called
the baby act look it up that you're
not responsible for anything that was done for
you by others right whether it was official
unofficial or whatever when you were a younger
than 18 have you heard of the baby
act it's pretty powerful if you know how
to use it yeah it begins when they
say your mother reports on your birth your
mother reports your birth and it begins there
right yeah yeah right it begins there it
also begins on prenatal care before you were
born if they determine you or whatever okay
he's called a retard back then down syndrome
now it's not politically correct to say that
right mm-hmm so I mean like I
grew up in a very whatever white neighborhood
and when a black people were niggers right
you say it like that you know and
they knew what you were talking about if
you said someone was black they stopped for
a minute and thinking like what does that
mean oh you mean a nigger I said
yeah okay that's how I grew up and
and when you were just dysfunctional retard and
they had you know the down syndrome all
that stuff these are things that were put
on you before you were born including the
n-word by the way it's all that
shit you can so the baby act doesn't
make you responsible and you do that by
injunction but driver's license and corporations and stuff
like that yeah get rid of all that
stuff if you can because that ties you
into something that you know nothing about unless
you do know it all goes back to
the Queen and the Vatican all of it
now there used to be a very comprehensive
website about the Vatican building in the vat
in Vatican City and it's not the Vatican
St. Pilar's Basilica they tell you we are
a red building behind that all of the
State Departments of the world that subscribe to
us we create their policy and they cannot
appeal it and that was a first line
of the thing real arrogant now you can't
find it anymore it used to be an
HTML if anyone wants to look it up
the Vatican red building or something I forgot
what they call it just it was just
called the Vatican all the State Department subscribed
to so State Department is actually ecclesiastic and
then you have the Queen of England which
is the money system but through the Bar
Association and the Attorney General's position as trustee
and blah blah blah blah blah right there's
another Attorney General called a private Attorney General
that anyone can take that position but it
should what case-by-case basis right so
you can't say you're a private Attorney General
you would only be for one case at
a time and when you're not running the
case you're not a private Attorney General so
like for example we're going to be trafficking
the water devices way we do that is
the sole proprietorship known as the straw man
the all-caps letter fills out a DBA
doing business as and we don't say DBA
we're just I could actually read the doc
it's very simple it's two sentences that you
you know everything is materially factual and you
are going to be doing business in the
county city states and worldwide is this other
name and I just want to make public
record and then you put it in the
newspaper and once you get the record back
from the county you get a raised seal
on it you can go open a bank
account with it using the Social Security number
right which is actually a trust number it's
in the state trust and the name is
what's in the trust which is a sole
proprietorship and then you do business that way
and when you do banking you open the
bank account at the signature card you write
demand for lawful money per 12 USC 411
sign your name comma agent or you could
sign your name semicolon last name first name
last you could also do last name first
but the best is agent because in the
UCC you know on checks it says authorized
signature right the UCC states that if you
sign any document instrument it's called and the
name of the that's on the instrument is
the same as the person that's signing you
are not responsible for the name on the
instrument so let's say you're Chuck Ocelli on
your checkbook you know it's all capital letters
Chuck Ocelli whatever Charles Ocelli right right and
on the signature line when you're issuing the
check on the front that's micro print on
the line and it says authorized signature authorized
signature repeat I think you know about that
right and well you're signing for that entity
known as Charles Ocelli which is a sole
proprietorship with the trust to state identification number
it's not an ID number but it says
trust the state ID means you have a
share of the United States from the receivership
okay so you could actually write a bad
check or a blank or check a check
from a closed account or these blank checks
you can get from whatever you can buy
them at Office Depot no bank account or
anything and it's good if you go and
use it they'll tell you the check bounced
or it's that's why I use the one
that doesn't have any bank information and they'll
tell you it's no good well give it
back to me and then you're not going
to give it back to you because they're
going to give you a legal copy and
this back shows that the bank stamped received
on it received does it mean like when
you receive something receive is a contractual term
right because it has to be without defect
for a legal entity like a bank to
receive it so when you have a received
stamp from a bank it means it's without
defect and the purpose of the instrument can
be fulfilled and is fulfilled what is the
purpose of an instrument like a check it's
very good Chuck to order funds to order
funds either for cash or credit on account
right right if the bank couldn't do that
they would not stamp it received so there's
no such thing as a bad check so
Attorney General says you go into sources bad
check writers will be prosecuted you see out
all the time go ahead of course try
it try it and the only way they
could prosecute you is if they go back
and say you had a bank account and
you gave the bank full security interest and
you're operating on a hundred percent banking fees
that's the most they can do right so
attorneys don't know anything just because the Attorney
General doesn't mean on any law at all
that's confusing that's confusing because one would think
that receiving something is simply it was you
know put in your possession but right it's
not like that just like the word nice
doesn't mean what you think it is look
up what received means in banking it's called
a bankers acceptance a banker will not accept
anything that has defects and that's outside of
the purpose of banker when he gets something
he has to see what the purpose of
that instrument is if he can't fulfill the
purpose of that instrument it's returned with a
with a note why they usually incorporate when
you have accounts they'll return checks or whatever
and they'll give you a Xerox copy and
they'll just check off boxes why it was
no good they don't want even sits there
and writes anything anymore and you just look
at the sheet and it checked off well
it didn't have a date checked off it
didn't have a signature right whatever so yeah
okay yeah I kind of gave it slow
enough you notice I spoke at a low
tempo right yes very much so very much
so I went I just did a quick
lookup you know what is what does it
mean to receive something in banking and it
means that a payment or deposit has been
successfully sent to the recipient bank and is
in the process of being credited to the
recipients right account the exact status and availability
of the funds depend on the type of
transaction and the banks processing times says but
that's cool how they said that's a newer
definition because it says in the process so
they get some leeway right so they come
back and say it's no good so if
the bank if the check is no good
all right simply give me back the check
they can't they only give you a copy
of it I was in trial once and
need a recess I ran out that we
wanted the check back from the bank and
the banks that the judge says this is
good enough and it was just said legal
copy on a Xerox mm-hmm front and
back so I said any 10-minute recess
mm-hmm and they wouldn't give it but
finally make a long story short I did
get it I went and got a $10
bill I made a copy of it front
and back came into the courtroom and I
said just I'm going to object to what
the plaintiff has brought forward and my response
and rebuttal is your honor can I spend
this and I held up Xerox copy of
a $10 bill that wrote legal copy on
it right right so no the next next
we're not can't use that point anymore yeah
you didn't get your check yeah you don't
need the check and it just went on
and on this is like 2007 Wow what
do I know anyway I've been in this
for a long time so well 20 years
plus but anyway back to the I am
yeah I wanted to continue on with this
question though to see where else it goes
because there's supposedly a remedy yeah please do
I just want to see that we covered
the question oh yeah I believe we do
and the reason let you go back to
it the bank card should cover should say
demand for let's your only remedy and if
you want to know where this remedy is
best explained go to YouTube and it would
be YouTube called 1913 Federal Reserve Act remedy
by David Merrill it's about a half hour
long listen to that he speaks he's speaking
on like a 16th grade level you know
high school is 12th grade right college bachelor's
degree is 16th degree 16th grade so that's
how the government has you by the way
if you have a four-year degree it's
you've completed 16 grades right you've seen that
before yeah I've seen okay yeah and it
goes up to yeah so that would be
your backup what's the remedy for the Federal
Reserve it's the only remedy for the Federal
Reserve Act directly there are other remedies for
other things every time you have an instrument
before you endorse it demand for law or
lawful money only is also a demand only
means the demand lawful money only or demand
for lawful money 12 USC 411 sign the
name however you sign it comma agent or
without recourse when you get more advanced you'll
know when to use what right so you
know like when you get food you don't
automatically put salt on it like like like
television you taste it first right people I've
seen people sit down and put food and
they throw it away salt and pepper before
they taste it that's they learned how to
eat by watching television wow right so you're
not going to get any of this on
TV or alternative media or gurus right so
anyway all right so I hope I was
clear with that yeah I've never thought about
that before there are some people who salt
and pepper their stuff before they ever tasted
I don't understand that at all because they
learned how to eat by watching TV how
pathetic is that it just makes no sense
so anyway you know no TV doesn't make
any sense that's right exactly all right so
there's supposedly a remedy for everything yet people
won't tell you the remedy because quote you
need to figure it out for yourself end
quote uh honestly not really well honestly all
this law legal stuff is like reading the
bible you can read it in all sorts
of ways it depends on who is translating
it once you know the truth you can
see through the lies but until then it's
all very convoluted I like how the greek
is very straightforward but I'd like to hear
some of his information uh where he talks
for hours straight I feel like he starts
to get into something and then the sound
clip cuts off uh these are very brief
yeah they're very brief they're hints anyways um
I'm new here and so I'm trying to
start from the beginning and piece all these
together but if anyone has some direction toward
the law info that's why I joined this
patreon and yes I get that everything the
greek talks about is about the laws of
this realm there's more to this by the
way but I think I'll pause there yeah
it's not everything it's actually how can you
get her how can you sit at a
game board without right I'm not going to
give the analogy you can guess how can
you sit down and play a game without
what oh the laws the rules yeah you
need to know what the rules are otherwise
even something simple when you when you're given
uh different shape holes and different shape pegs
this one doesn't fit anybody got a sander
and a chisel no you're supposed to move
them around until they fit right find the
one that fits right this is a this
is a one it doesn't go uh the
square one doesn't go in the run you
let's chisel it down no you're supposed to
make maneuvers till you yeah cut the top
off the box throw them all in there
done uh you know just well my favorite
is I've seen people that said they're good
mechanics I had a water pump and a
timing belt change and he ended up with
extra bolts wow oh where do they go
god damn it why do you have bolts
left over such a good mechanic asshole yeah
or the word you go to surgery and
they you know they're cleaning up and it's
like we're missing some hemostats and some yeah
you've heard of surgeons leaving oh absolutely somebody
I remember the joke for a while was
somebody count the sponges because there was a
oh yeah that's a big one sponges getting
lost inside of patients constantly that's a terrible
way to go slow sepsisemia oh you turn
green oh my gosh I've seen that I've
walked down hospitals and seen you know like
hepatitis with looking yellow green skin and dark
circles under the eyes under morphine I'm like
oh they left the sponge in that one
anyway yeah it's a murder fucking factory avoid
those assholes but okay right okay so anyway
next uh but I'd really like to catch
some aha waves on the bigger picture of
how to live without the fear of government
coming after me for not saying the right
thing or signing the right document I'm tired
of living with analysis paralysis hiding from the
world because I can't figure out how this
all works all right stop right there that's
it that's the end what it's that's all
good it's all based on money everything's being
done for money that doesn't exist think how
insane that is there is no money and
everyone wants money the government all corporations all
governments are what's called legally debtors in possession
they're all debtors you are the creditor period
by doing the demand for lawful money will
clear you from the you know taxes don't
pay anything no taxes it can't they use
negotiable instruments and I've explained the miller bond
process let me just do a thing this
will help let's say uh New York wants
to build the governor como bridge cost a
billion dollars this is actually pretty close to
the truth I've researched that I was looking
at it the actual the bonds also so
they get all these they get an architect
and they get the the the project bid
out blueprints and all that to contractors and
they bid on it and when they award
the bid the contractor does what's called the
miller bond process he puts in what's called
a performance bond a bid bond a performance
bond and a surety bond and they each
have a let's say the the award is
a billion dollars it's pretty close to a
billion I think was like 700 800 million
for that bridge each one of those bonds
let's say is a billion the government the
state takes that and they deposit it through
the federal reserve and they get three billion
actually a little less than the billions federal
reserve takes five percent and then they put
it on the market for about three four
months and they start building it about a
year later sound about right they never start
right away so so the actual this is
how sick of a world you live in
whoever you is and uh billion dollar bridge
the guy who's building it funded it not
once not twice but three times and as
he's building it he's under the impression that
he has to get progress payments as he's
building it according to contract and the money's
coming from taxes that the state collected what
a crock of shit that's worse than the
world trade centers were vaporized by osama bin
laden with box cutters hmm that's how bad
this is the world you live in and
you go to these morons to tell you
how you're if you're healthy or not or
your financial advice come on you are on
your own is the first thing so the
advice that you got regarding analysis paralysis yes
very good you realize you it's not nothing's
working because it's a planet full of idiots
I don't know how else to say it
right so give me an example I recently
caught an archaic thing with this guy mark
pass you I don't know if you remember
him from back in the days of american
freedom radio he's making a lot of rounds
back 15 20 years ago I didn't think
he was still around I didn't either I
didn't either I was because I never was
into now this is not to disparage him
I don't know it's it's like it's it's
tom and dick or michael harris or whatever
it doesn't matter it's not personal it's my
god not personal what he says is ra
ra ra we gotta create human freedom and
slavery we gotta be free we gotta be
not one goddamn comment not one suggestion on
how to go about doing that not one
thing no oh my gosh that's worse than
uh than anything I've heard out there from
the mainstream just as bad so this is
what this is what you guys meaning you
guys whoever you guys are or have to
put up with until you find someone that
can tell you how it can be done
and show you the mechanics behind it a
really good car mechanic will do that by
the way or a really good surgeon will
walk you into the say this is what
we want to do and show you the
x-rays and tell you what they're going
to do and how long it's going to
heal a really good dentist will tell you
if you ever have a tooth extracted that
the opposite truth the opposing tooth will experience
something called eruption and continue growing because now
there's an empty pocket above it so be
aware of that it'll you're right anyone who's
ever said i'm going to go have a
tooth extract this let me know if the
dentist talks about eruption of the opposing tooth
on the bite no one ever does then
when the person went for a follow-through
they brought that up and the dentist was
surprised that they brought it up this is
standard stuff that needs to be discussed so
i always bring up the medical morons and
legal morons are not even worth talking about
they're like oh my gosh that's why idiocracy
already happened but another interesting thing about money
itself it has always cracked me up as
people scream about they're taking away our change
they're taking it's going to be a cashless
society and i'm you guys are a little
late cashless here's the problem this is okay
even if you go with their rules and
you go with their uh reports and everything
else the amount of money that they say
exists does not physically exist it hasn't it
doesn't it actually does not securities okay yeah
chuck let me just say this but the
amount of dollars they say there's so many
dollars here there's so many dollars there you
can't physically account for that you could never
collect up all the paper and everything else
and add it up to what they have
on the computer just a trillion just a
trillion is not enough paper to print and
it would be a stack of money to
the moon yeah it's not fathom it can't
be done so here um you've heard me
say that when regulations get strong uh the
black market gets strong when you want to
weaken the black same people by the way
run the government run the black market same
group of course uh the same and if
you want the black market to get weak
you deregulate okay so the cash is dependent
two people the two industries or groups that
are mostly dependent on cash money i'm talking
like federal reserve notes or bureaus no in
notes paper notes in australia they have plastic
notes whatever it's like a tyvek yeah all
that stuff and coin but mostly paper it's
much better to carry a hundred dollar bill
than a hundred dollars and quarters by the
way for sure and you notice i didn't
say pennies and don't even bother with the
pennies so the black market depends on that
and also the super wealthy depend on that
i'm giving you an example all right so
i got 150 million i'm going to go
put it in the bank that's a really
good business decision since the bank only insures
it for 250 000 that sounds like a
good business decision to put 150 million in
the bank when only 250 000 is going
to be insured does that sound like a
good risk no it sounds stupid that's the
funny thing that's about as dumb as dumb
can get like i've always seen those people
who win the lottery you know there's like
a billion dollar lottery that just i don't
know if they anybody wanted or whatever but
i passed they put the money in the
bank they're only insured for 250 000 yeah
that's the funny thing like i'm going to
take this check to the bank and i'm
like you're going to take a half a
billion dollar check to a bank that's only
guaranteeing you that you'll have 250 000 yeah
well let's say per account so you might
if you broke it up into 10 accounts
that's still just 2.5 yeah million right
right yeah because which was not even not
even one percent right right so uh because
one percent would be five million so okay
so the wealthy what they do is they
call the bank ahead and they want pallets
of cash okay and they have there's people
that do that and they move it and
it could be as simple as moving the
cash from one building to another across the
street it could be on a property that
they have give you an example when you're
on a compound a wealthy person's compound right
um and they have a break-in or
they have a let's say a security issue
they don't call the the local sheriff or
the police they have their own security people
right right and when they catch you you
don't have any rights they don't read you
any rights they actually catch you and they've
been trained that you're not human they would
treat you like a wild dog you'll probably
never be found again for breaking into someone's
house they don't call the sheriff right or
the police hint so the money system works
the same way they don't use banks the
way that slaves these are slave banks right
so anyway i just wanted to bring up
the easiest thing is take care of the
money first um learn about i don't know
uh learn about the constitution learn how to
do injunctions go ahead and google i don't
know what comes up first driver driver's license
injunction that went popular let me do it
right now start with your injunctions jonah bay
is good at the injunctions by the way
jonah bay like the bible jonah and then
bey could go to his website it's it's
pretty cheap stuff it's like these letters and
courses are like 100 bucks but he every
holiday he runs like a 50 off sale
okay so uh that was funny because one
of the cannabis you know cannabis stores aren't
doing well because they have a 50 markup
and sometimes they have to compete with uh
buy one get one free and if you're
on a 50 markup and you do buy
one get one free how much money did
you make yeah nothing zero yeah you're giving
it away and this is what they're operating
on all right so i'm going to write
driver's license injunction well this is like a
live uh oh this is great just a
keyboard uh driver's license injunction refers to a
court order that stops to prevent someone's action
related to a driver's license no no uh
arizona can deny driver's licenses no this is
driver's license injunction done by first individual the
guy did it in the 70s and it
kind of took off well you got to
remember most search engines have an ai function
at the top now that's supposed to like
cobble together oh my gosh yeah and it's
just a mess you got to skip past
that giving you anything yeah it's good garbage
what's the guy's name he went national with
it um oh shit i i we'll bring
it up again just like i promised i
was going to bring up the code okay
write this down this is an introduction this
is kind of pop fury you know we're
like uh bananas in a monkey grove or
whatever okay uh 26 cfr section 31
.3402 part one it's called voluntary withholding agreements
so voluntary withholding agreements employer uh employer employee
agreement employee and his employer may enter an
agreement upon section 3402 to provide withholding of
income tax payments of amounts described in paragraph
b made after december 1970 an agreement may
be entered under this section with respect to
the amounts of gross income and then it
says an employee wants to enter blah blah
blah if you read down this is about
where you can cancel that okay it's about
income tax withholding right i mean this is
about canceling the withholding right well it's income
tax well here's the thing i want to
get into that too okay uh if you
read that if you want to make a
request in case the employee who desires to
enter an agreement under section blah blah with
his employer if his employee performs services the
agreement was subject monitoring of the i think
this is there's might be another part to
it so in other words you have to
do a statement that uh okay if the
employee desires the agreement terminate on a specific
date the date of termination of the agreement
a statement that the employee desires withholding a
federal income tax on a parallel state tax
income tax the chapter name address of the
employer and they're okay basically you have to
write an affidavit where you no longer want
withholding it's an affidavit form uh an agreement
under section 3402 shall be effective such employer
employee mutually agreed upon however either employer employee
may terminate the agreement prior to the end
of such period by furnishing a signed written
notice whenever you hear a signed written notice
means an affidavit and the way you do
an affidavit is without the united states i'll
give you that one too that's always evidence
right so for example let's say there's a
trial over a burned car sometimes they have
the people go out to where the burned
car is or they bring a picture or
the burned car into the courtroom you know
what even trumps that evidence is an affidavit
but it has to be done under a
proper attorneys cannot write proper affidavits i don't
know why they just can't they don't hold
water and their clients don't either okay unless
the employer employee have an agreed termination date
the notice should be effective with respect to
the first payment of the amount of respect
to the agreement is effective on made on
the first status determined date okay so every
right so you put a date the other
goes 30 days after the date okay furnishing
place so so you can terminate all that
right now i gave you the code you
go back it's 26 cfr section 31.3402
part one voluntary withholding agreements and then there's
a very important is how to write an
affidavit which is it's called this one would
go to 28 usc section 1746 unsworn declarations
under penalty of perjury so here this is
interesting you want to do it without the
united states this is the when you when
you execute without the united states this is
what the verbiage is i declare certify verify
your state under penalty of perjury under the
laws of the united states of america that
the foregoing is true and correct if executed
within the united states wink wink united states
is what washington dc right it's not part
of this country guys this is what verbiage
that it has i declare certify verify your
state under penalty of perjury that the foregoing
is true and correct that's it you see
the difference yeah but if you do it
without the united states the verbiage is this
i declare certify verify your state under penalty
of perjury under the laws of the united
states of america that the foregoing is true
and correct wow so whenever you talk about
the united states of may america you're doing
it without the united states whenever you do
stuff with the united states you're getting shafted
with a big cucumber like uh brendan joe
williams says so those are the two things
i want to give that one is 28
usc 1746 unsworn declarations under penalty of perjury
now attorneys always do with the united states
they never you'll never see attorney doing the
first verbiage and if you told them to
do it he'll show up to court with
a document and have you sign one that
is the second one for some reason they
they're going to shaft you that's funny anyone
that i've ever known i talk about how
attorneys are scumbags and they're not smart someone
says you know my sister is an attorney
and she's such an asshole i'm like thank
you i mean i don't need to hear
that from you right i mean we know
that already you know but you know it's
it's interesting how the dumb ones in the
family either and the ones that are assholes
become attorneys and doctors usually you know now
if the whole family is like that well
i no comment you may not be able
to see the difference so all right so
basically everything is around the money thing and
declarations and all that and i brought up
how the money works um the next thing
after that is obviously i don't like to
use the word morality but your law form
right if you think this world is fucked
up then why do you want to act
like you belong here be prudent be uh
conservative i don't mean conservative versus liberal right
you know uh learn how to um fix
stuff including yourself so you don't rely on
these idiots known as professionals because they're morons
and um with very few exception and uh
you know that's that's pretty much it i
mean i don't know i mean the money
thing is is not all about that but
that's a good what they always come after
so if you have a problem with a
certain agency or whatever what do they want
from you a foot massage or they want
money from you right there's money and they
want performance and that performance is monetized okay
what are taxes taxes are very simple um
if you read uh who's the guy with
the toupee the congressman who says i'm congress
uh they from idaho ohio and they killed
trafficant trafficking the u.s has been bankrupt
it's the biggest trust in world history in
terms of the bookkeeping the irs is there
to manage the bookkeeping of the trust your
all caps name and social security number which
is a security number it's not really a
license to issue securities but it's a license
to create them that's it because if you
look at the it's not even a license
it just ties you into the treasury the
social security cannot be used as identification it's
right on the card read the back of
it that's true right not to be used
for identification if it's lost return it back
to the office okay so that's in the
trust your sole prop meaning your all caps
name and this and the number associated with
it is in the trust and it's a
very big asset it's a let's say there's
300 million people in the u.s of
a you get a 103 a three one
out of 300 millionth share of the country
but it's not even those are not even
the conditions because when it says the definition
of united states debt it says any any
check any bond any stock any whatever anything
that resembles money paper or not is owed
to owed by the united states and they
will handle it right so it's title it's
uh title uh i think it's title 18
section 8 12 is it 18 usc 8
uh this laptop i got a nice screen
here let's see uh 18 usc 8 let
me see how good the memory works yeah
okay 18 usc 8 obligation or other security
of the united states defined the term obligation
or other security of the united states includes
all bonds certificates of indebtedness national bank currency
federal reserve notes federal reserve bank notes coupons
united states notes treasury notes gold certificates silver
certificates fractional notes certificate of deposit bills should
i say bills again let me say one
more time bills checks or drafts for money
drawn upon or authorized officers of the united
states stamps and represent that's why people say
stamps are backed by gold no they're not
and other representatives of representatives of value of
whatever denomination issued under any act of congress
and canceled united states stamps so cancel united
states stamps so out of value i used
to play around with those but uh a
canceled two cent stamp without a zip code
you send the envelope they get it take
the stamp off because it's canceled as long
as you don't use the zip code you
can keep using the two cent stamp until
it's totally worn out so uh yeah yeah
sometimes they don't they don't know that but
you can so don't that doesn't care it
doesn't matter what letter what they're charging for
anyway these are i know it says upon
authorized officers of the united states it's not
an authorized officer the term united states territorial
sense includes all places and waters country okay
they're not explaining what an officer is here
an officer does stuff that's official now an
officer since you're a part of a trust
anyone in a trust can be an officer
of a you hold an office not you
the all caps name right and this is
drawn by or upon authorized officers of the
united states stamps right okay so it does
not exclude it doesn't say it includes all
the citizens all the non-citizens resident aliens
non-resident aliens but it doesn't exclude them
because it's all by presumption but it basically
gave you a long list so what happens
when you get an electric bill it's already
paid by the united states not the bill
itself by the application right and that bill
is actually an interest payment to you from
that huge chunk they took out when you
applied that's why if anyone has a car
in a trust and you want to get
insurance for it's registered with the trust name
the issue the insurance will will fight you
tooth and nail and they say we cannot
insure the trust it has to be as
someone with a social security number because when
you get an insurance they run to the
treasury and pull i don't know eight nine
hundred thousand a million depending on what the
policy is ten times usually so let's say
you get basic coverage and it's forty thousand
dollars right coverage basic coverage they pull a
minimum four hundred thousand plus their fees and
it's sitting there you don't know that and
then when you have a claim they go
take that claim and monetize it again you
could it's not hard to prove this by
the way so i just wanted to bring
these things up but the money issue okay
so back to taxes what taxes are is
the franchise board collects the the fees the
irs collects the fees the state franchise tax
collects the fees for the trustees who are
running the trust that your name is in
and your property's name is in that's all
it is it's if you are a trustee
you have a right to charge for your
services there are professional trustee services they're usually
accountants and they start at 250 an hour
good ones are 700 an hour okay right
so that's why you you are doing you're
using that name that all caps name and
the irs withholding which is voluntary is the
truck is the fee you're met the irs
is managing the trust and no who works
for free right very good right no one
so they have a scale of what their
fees are just like when you go rent
the tool they have a chart you know
whatever income bracket whatever and you have to
do reporting that's all trust stuff i've been
saying this for a long time and jonah
bay recently said it's all trust stuff that's
like the hundredth monkey thing right yeah so
the taxes are actually fees for the trustees
to operate the trust when you do the
12 usc 411 demand for lawful money what
you're doing is say i can handle my
own affairs i'm not looking to get trust
funds right okay so leave me alone now
the thing with for example property tax every
every every property tax jurisdiction says that if
you are a non-profit you're not subject
to property property tax and some people bring
this up if you do a proper statement
they'll say well where's your 501c3 or 508
blah blah blah like where does it say
in the law i have to have an
irs certificate nowhere and just think about it
when people hear non-profit say oh 501c3
blah blah blah right yes 505 whatever right
no no no non-profit so let me
ask you where you eat sleep shit fuck
uh whatever else you do are you doing
any of that for profit no and the
answer is no so why are you paying
property tax if you have a house right
make a statement take them to court you
know it's funny when you go to the
county see where do you get the authority
to tax the property they say from the
state you go to the state and you
ask them where do you get the authority
to tax it to the county says no
we don't the county does it because there's
no it's all bullshit it's all if you
cannot remember i read a thing you will
be treated as a minor even though you're
of legal age can you be does that
mean if i'm 65 can i be treated
as a minor that's according to that statement
that's what it says yeah yeah it didn't
give conditions up until you're 25 and then
you're not no no no so yeah that's
why early on on the sonics what i
say people start developing 9 or 12 years
old you might see your grandpa your uncle
your mom and your dad 60 70 50
i'm telling you that's a nine-year-old
in there they've never grown up right you've
heard me say this early on the sonics
yes you know yeah they're minors so this
is not a matter of learning what to
do from guru it's a matter of growing
up look i don't still don't know what
i'm going to do when i grow up
right so i don't even know what that
means you actually grow down by the way
you don't grow up when your body grows
yeah eventually right your arms your arms no
no no as your arms get longer and
you get taller let's say you're really small
four years old and by the time you're
eight nine ten but from let's say an
infant to adult your arms are getting longer
and your legs are getting longer that's not
growing up that's growing down your legs are
growing down towards the ground and your arms
are growing like out from the body right
your legs grow down and your arms grow
down a human the the legs and the
arms project downwards not upwards right remember we're
upside down plants plants grow up we grow
down so got into a conversation today what
fruit really is that would be an interesting
one for another time what else you got
on this uh hope i hope this has
been helpful i've been pouring this out this
is what the financial seminar was like what
i would get into the and this is
not philosophy if you're i'm always good i'm
not mark pastor oops did i say that
i'm gonna if i'm gonna speak for five
minutes uh i hope four minutes of it
is exactly what to do and how to
do it your choice sometimes i wouldn't do
what i would do right you know what
i mean do you remember evil knievel back
in the day and a lot of people
try to imitate his stuff and really got
screwed up remember the evil knievel oh that's
a real flashback for people yeah i remember
you never heard of him yeah i remember
how many how many people were trying to
do what he's you're a broken neck but
even himself he broke his back like three
times right broke every bone in his body
right yeah broke many bones all the time
yeah when you watch just because you watch
and listen to evil cameo doesn't mean you
should do what he does i i think
it was