Hey, Sonic Event 121 and there's a bit of noise happening because I guess you might
sound strange.
Greek pizza.
That's right.
Yeah, I said it.
Greek pizza.
But is it Greek pizza?
No, it's the Greek making pizza.
All right.
Well, you know, Greek, I actually used to eat pizza from a stop in Connecticut when
I lived there.
And it was it was like Alpha Pizza, I think they called it or something like that.
Well, you know, Greek letters on it.
And it was literally Greeks running a pizza shop.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
I just sent you a picture, by the way, if you want to describe it, we see what I'm doing
with Sonic on a phone.
So these are not polyton style pizzas and a polyton style oven, you know, outdoors mesquite
wood.
They take about 90 seconds to make.
That's the oven right now in Fahrenheit, seven hundred and seventy degrees because I keep
opening the door.
OK, see, but right there, you just made the mistake, though, that you complain about with
the TV chefs.
You're saying it takes 90 seconds to make a pizza.
It doesn't take 90 seconds to make a pizza.
It takes a lot to make it, to cook it, to cook it.
Right.
I mean.
But but you you didn't show.
Hey, if you're telling me it's 90 seconds to make a pizza, you're definitely not showing
me any of the prep work, any of the selection or no, no.
That's right.
You just did the thing.
Well, people.
Yeah.
People would have been around for the phonics.
This is the no need.
No, it's OK.
If it's really wet in the end, you just handle it like you handle anything.
Let's really wet.
Right.
So anyway.
Yeah.
You handle it in a way that you're careful.
But just because the dough has high moisture content doesn't mean that it's not it's going
to lack tension when you have to work it.
Right.
Anybody that you know.
And we're talking Napolitano style, small pies.
These are like 12, 13 inches.
Just sauce and cheese.
Look at this one.
Yeah.
So I just made two pies and do the sonic and then I'm going to enjoy them.
They actually do taste better when they cool down just above room temperature.
I don't like biting into a really hot, you know, burn your mouth kind of stuff.
No, no, no.
A warm pizza is best if you can't enjoy the pizza when it's just warm.
It's a problem.
It's not good.
Yeah.
Well, that's the thing about really good food.
You could have it at any temperature where crappy.
You imagine having any fast food cold.
So that's horrible.
Yeah.
I mean, a cold, cold French fries is the absolute worst.
If you get your McDonald's and you can't you can't reheat them or anything.
OK.
Nothing.
But if you make them yourself, they're.
Yeah, they're.
Yeah, exactly.
Right.
You wanted to ask.
I wanted to get into this tonight about law.
Somebody sent you a message about why I chose.
Go ahead.
The biblical law.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I want to refer to a few other few other things.
Yeah.
If you don't mind that.
Because this question comes up a lot.
And I love this.
By the way, guys, all the noises and stuff.
I'm not going to filter none of this out.
It's going to be exactly as I'm making pizza.
Yeah.
While he's making pizza and he's moving around, which causes that other noise.
It's actually not bad, though, because you're actually are you outside right now?
Yeah.
Now I'm inside.
But the back the kitchens at the back of the house, I go through the back door to the pizza
oven outside and then I come back inside.
All right.
So right now I'm going to take a slight break from that because I've made two pies already.
And let's just kick it.
Yeah.
No, we're going to do that.
But which is really fast.
He's inside.
He's outside.
So all the different noises.
I'm going to leave it in there exactly as is.
Oh, yeah.
So.
So you guys have a definite rough, you know, this is just the way it was recorded.
That's it.
OK, so.
Well, yeah.
This question, like I said, you kept asking, what's that noise?
I said, I told you, you're making pizza, making pizza.
Yeah.
But there's many noises happening here.
So all these noises all are coming from the inside, the outside, the oven, everything.
OK.
And the reason why I'm not pausing and we don't need to reschedule recording is because
once you get that oven hot.
Yeah.
Right.
You got to go for it.
Because, you know, a thousand degree, you know, between seven and a thousand seven hundred
Fahrenheit, you're going to six hundred Celsius.
Right.
To do it.
You know, if your oven's not that hot, the type of dough that it is takes much longer
to cook and it gets tough.
So it's really soft.
It's crisp.
It's like we have a really good plate of pasta.
There's only one way to make it right.
Good pasta.
Yeah.
Right.
Not soggy.
Not too well done.
You're just right.
You're same thing with pizzas.
So.
Yeah.
So anyway, the question that comes up often.
Right now.
So I wanted to explain this real fast.
All right.
So I get this question every so often and over the years, even I've gotten this question
in one form or another.
But this is somebody who is sort of newer to listening to the Sonics, has come to them
recently and is catching up on the old ones, but is going off of the most recent mention
that you made of why you decide to use the biblical text in any way, shape or form.
Not because you necessarily believe in it, you said, to paraphrase, but because it does
provide you your law and the listener asks you basically why and not just why, but why
is this any better or worse than any other set of regulations, rules out there that somebody
else could adapt his law?
Other people have certainly done it one way or another.
And some people have picked up something else and decided to rewrite it.
I mean, we could get into the work of John Smith and the Mormon church.
Again, we don't have to be that broad.
It's a broad question, but let's jump on something specific.
I mentioned last week this new guy has been studying law for about two years.
It's Brandon Joe Williams or something.
Joe Brandon Williams.
Yeah.
And he's an ex-marketing guy, young guy, funny looking dude.
And he's spending all this on marketing because he wants people to learn the law.
Kind of like what I've been saying, but that's the thing, like I'm moderating between him
and Archaic.
Archaic and this guy, Brandon Joe Williams, are probably the two best stuff you can research
online right now.
And I'll tell you what they're lacking, you know, in terms of if you understand this point,
then you put it together, what they're saying, and then you got a pretty complete breakfast.
Right.
Okay.
So what you're telling me is that somewhere between the chronology and this other guy discussing
law.
Well, these are two subjects.
I want us to go to Joe Brand.
If you watch him, he basically shows you how all the definitions are circuitous.
Like for example, the United States, to give you an example, I've been saying this all,
but he kind of underscored this.
When you look at the law of, before you become a citizen of the United States, you have to
identify the United States and it's in the district of Columbia, but it doesn't specify
where it is.
It doesn't specify.
It doesn't say the district of Columbia is United States, somewhere in the district of
Columbia.
But there's, if you keep reading the statute, I believe it's title eight, title five, title
50, which is war.
It says that if you want to live in the United States, dig this.
You need permission from the board members.
Okay.
Whoa.
So we cannot define the United States citizen if we got to find the United States what you're
a citizen of.
So what I'm trying to say, like, for example, IRS, you're a taxpayer.
Well, if you look at the definition, they call everyone a taxpayer, a taxpayer, it's
someone who's subject to the tax.
Oh my gosh, how do I, right?
So what you, when you look at all of these laws, right, they're all circuitous.
They really, they define themselves as, as air smoke.
They're not really there.
It's all in your mind.
It's all illusion.
Right?
So now a lot of people follow these laws.
Like they'll say, you know, it's the law.
You can't carry a firearm.
Right.
Okay.
And people think that a handgun is a firearm, which it's not by definition.
Right.
And all these things.
So they live by it.
Okay.
So there's nothing there.
But let's go now.
I'm giving this as a preface.
Yeah.
And do I endorse Brandon, Joe Williams or Belinda Williams, Joe Brandon or whatever?
No, I don't endorse him.
Are you going to get like hours of fun?
You know, I remember they used to advertise games.
It's hours of fun in the seventies, right?
Hours of fun and good education.
Yes, you will.
Right.
And he doesn't know about the endorsement clause.
So he can get nailed by the IRS.
They'll just ignore the other stuff that he does because he, you don't have to be a citizen
to endorse a check and have a tax liability.
You just have to show each individual time, uh, you know, 12 USC for 11.
It's unbelievable when I speak to people in private, how terrified they are of that.
But on another sonic, I'll talk about how to experiment with it harmlessly.
OK, so you have all these laws that are hard to define and people follow.
Right. But there's if you look at the meat and bones, there's nothing there.
Now, let's jump to the biblical stuff again.
Right. OK, so if you say you follow the Old Testament right away, people think you're
Jewish. Right.
And then I've had this done many times.
And when the Jewish holiday of Passover comes around on their Pope's works, you know, on
their schedule, they wish me a happy Passover.
I said that was a month ago.
That was two weeks ago or that was, you know, no, I don't know what you're talking about.
So that confuses them.
Right. So here's two quick questions, then.
Is it incorrect to think that people who are identified as Jewish are supposed to be
following the Old Testament one and two?
How is it or what what measurement of time?
They don't use the Pope's works.
It's like getting to the subject matter, just the subject matter, not the subject itself.
So what I'm trying to say is so when these U.S.
citizens, that's where the U.S.
citizens cannot define what U.S.
citizenship is. Actually, it's defined very loosely.
And they think the United States is what they've been told.
And it's not legally right.
So the Jewish people think they're following the Old Testament.
They don't have a clue.
Right. Like, for example, they, you know, in very Orthodox, they have what's called dare.
Remember to go to especially New Jersey deal would be a very Jewish neighborhood, a summer
resort town. Right.
Very well known as not too far from maybe where you were.
Yeah. And I was discussing deal recently.
Yeah. Good. Yeah.
OK, well, they have what's called a dairy restaurant.
The reason why they have a dairy restaurant is because if you serve meat, you can't serve
any dairy if it's kosher.
And if you serve dairy, you can't serve any meat because of the 10th Commandment.
Do not serve. By the way, the 10th Commandment written on stones is do not see a goat
in its mother's milk or boil, cook meat, you know, of a goat or right.
But they don't know which way to interpret.
It means you've not cooked the meat with the milk or do you not?
If if the goat or the lamb is still suckling, you should not slaughter it to eat.
You have to wait for it right to be weaned away.
Right. So they just go right.
And how this gets applied, because, look, I also lived in Lakewood, right, which has
quite an Orthodox Jewish enclave and has a shul there.
And a few other things. Right.
And they have a dairy restaurant, probably.
So, no, they had a sandwich shop.
Now, the sandwich shop.
No cheese. Yeah. Well, here's the thing.
Under the supervision of the rabbis there, they had to separate that.
So if you had you could make cheese sandwiches, you could make meat sandwiches.
No problem. Different, different fridge, different slicers, different counters.
Everything separated tremendously, whether it's the knife point.
Let's not get into the subject.
What I'm just explaining that quickly, that that's one of those things that they
absolutely separated, like you couldn't even put the meat on the same counter as the
cheese if you did.
And the story, it's no longer proper based on that.
But the commandment, the commandment basically says to not cook it in its mother's
milk. So you can probably if you have milk from not its mother, you can cook it in its
milk. Right. Like fricassee is basically cream sauce.
Right. Or if it's on its mother's milk, meaning
it's still suckling, you shouldn't eat it.
Right. So either one is not being followed.
The letter of the law and the definitions provided are not being followed.
They just separate everything.
So anyway, it's not very difficult to see that if you're Jewish, you really are not
following the Old Testament because they're on a completely different calendar.
OK, so so what I'm doing when I say biblical law, I do biblical law, but I'm not
Jewish. Like when I go to a restaurant and I see a lot of pork on the menu, I say, do
you have anything without any swine?
And they're like, are you Jewish?
I'm like, no. Are you Muslim?
No. Right.
So so when people ask that question, I'm going to take that question as if they are
competent and what I'm saying and their question is competent can be answered
competently. Right.
So I've made this long roundabout that I'm not Jewish and I don't follow any
religion. So what I'm trying to caution and you're clearly not you're clearly not a
Muslim either who is concerned about Haram, not a Muslim.
Hello. But it's the same.
But, you know, the Koran indirectly tells you to go read the law in the Bible.
Right. Well, basically, they say directly.
Yeah. I mean, basically, my understanding is as far as it comes, you know, when the
food thing is concerned, they basically say, look, just go look at the Jewish idea and
it's about the same thing. Well, no.
It says basically in several places, several areas, starting on 28th, it states that
Allah gave the law to Moses.
That's all. Now, where is Moses?
Where do we find out about? You know, I mean, everybody and they and they call it Torah.
You know, they call it they did follow the Torah.
Right. Back then. I mean, and they the old they stopped about 50, about 100 years ago
when the when they were restructured.
Right. But you can still do the Torah.
They even have holidays that are based on some of the same characters like they have
Ishmael's day, which is a big deal among the Muslims, because he's the.
Yeah, good. Sorry. But the competent.
Whenever I get a question, I try to answer it where the competency yields and that
doesn't yield, but can go through.
So what I'm trying to say is that anyone asking that, why do I follow biblical law
must be aware of biblical law in the sense that it has nothing to do with anything
that's out in the world, really.
And when I say nothing to do, I mean, cannot be administered with anything that's
followed in the world. So someone might say, I've seen this more than once back 15
years ago when I decided to take on this law form.
Right. Right. Because we all have law forms like I'm going, you know, what Bougainvillea
is, are there like desert plants?
Say they grow like weeds, like vines.
They're huge. They have thorns.
They grow like six feet a year.
They have these beautiful red flowers, but they're not they're full of red.
People hate them because the whole neighborhood gets full of these red petals.
Right. OK. And but they're not really flowers that leaves that turn red.
Bougainvillea. Right.
OK. Don't ask me how to spell it.
B-O-U-G-I-N-V-I-L-I-A-H, some Bougainvillea, it's a desert plant.
So first time I'm planting these things and growing them and, you know, it's a plant.
So you water it, leave it alone.
Right. No, I want these things to thrive.
So guess what? I need to go and find the law of Bougainvillea.
I need to find. And it turns out there are some specific things that do's and don'ts
with these things. Right.
You can most people that buy the Bougainvillea pot and kill them because, you know, they
grow a very sensitive root ball.
So if you buy it in a pot and you take it out of the pot, you've seen how you turn a
plant upside down, take the pot off, cut the pot off, plant it.
Any motion to the root ball will kill the plant.
So what you should do is take the pot and cut the sides open.
It doesn't have a tap root.
It always maintains this ball.
If you disturb that ball in the slightest, it's like a prima donna.
It'll just die. So.
So I discovered this before, thankfully, because I was planning on taking them out of the
pots. I would have had four plants that were dead, 40, 50 bucks for plants.
So. So what I did was I followed the laws of Bougainvillea and they're thriving like
crazy. I mean, they froze a bad freeze this year.
I cut them down to the ground and they're already four feet tall.
So and I'm looking for I'm using them as shade cover.
Right. OK, so my example here is very, very clear.
Another example, which should be very clear, is do you remember Mitsubishi motor cars?
You don't see them that much here anymore.
Not so much. But yeah, in the 90s, they decided to put out next to Rolls-Royce
is a fact the most precision manufactured engine in the world, you know, that you can
buy. Right. In other words, the tolerances of the manufacturing of the rings, the seals
of that was super high precision.
Right. Very, very, very, very tight.
Anyone can afford something as the quality of a Rolls-Royce engine, a Porsche, a
Mercedes or actually higher tolerances of Mercedes, Porsche.
So. But the kick was in the early 90s that you had to use a special synthetic oil or
you could use a zero 20 oil has to be synthetic, though.
Right. In order for it to work.
So all these people that bought Mitsubishi's right.
Three thousand miles, six, five.
Got to change the oil, honey.
What do they do? What do they do?
They go to name an oil change place.
Right. Yeah. Discount.
Nineteen. And what do you think they did?
What do you think? Do you think they went and got the right oil or do you think they
just put in the cheapest shit?
Right. OK. Yeah.
Your average Jiffy Lube monkey doesn't even look at the the standards.
They just how many ports do I have to put in?
And that's that. Right.
Yeah. The cheapest oil.
So what happened? The oil was 10 times thicker than it should be.
And now now, wait a second.
About two years after Mitsubishi released the highest precision factory motor, you
can buy an engine, you can buy.
They got a bad reputation because, oh, don't buy the Mitsubishi because it's going to
start smoking on you.
The engine will start smoking.
It's only a couple of years old.
They got a bad reputation and they nobody bought it.
Right. And if you remember back in the 90s, if you had a red light, light turns green
if it was chances are nine out of 10, if there was a Mitsubishi car, new Mitsubishi
car around you, they hit the gas and watch a big puff of smoke out of the car.
Right. So so what did they try to do?
They try to do something good. What happened?
Something bad. They lost their reputation by trying to do that.
Right. So you got to understand why.
Because they didn't follow the directions, the laws of that engine.
It's very, very simple.
Let me just go back.
What before I decided to follow biblical law, I did my research on it.
Right. I started finding out that I'm not for circumcision, but I'll just say it like
this. Circumcision happens in eight days.
Well, it turns out it's been clinically proven that at eight days old, the human male
has the highest coagulative properties.
How did they know that? And it wasn't nine or 10 days or a month.
All these other things.
For example, pork has if you eat, you get what's called trichinella, one trichinosis.
It's a roundworm. Right.
Right. Now, what's interesting, it tells you to eat.
It gives you discernment. If you're going to eat anything with four legs, it should chew the
cut and have a cloven hoof.
And it gives the example of a pig as a cloven hoof.
Right. You've seen pigs feed at the deli at the deli.
Right. Delicacy in many places.
Yeah. And but it doesn't chew the cut.
Now, rabbit chews the cut, but he has a paw.
You've seen a rabbit's paw. It's like a cat's paw or something.
Right. Right. OK.
All right. So but you know what's interesting, interesting here.
Is not only can you get trichinosis from eating pork, you get trichinosis from eating
bugs, bunny, rabbit hair also wasn't aware how the hell they put this stuff together.
Right. It's really interesting.
So I started looking at a lot of these, quote unquote, laws were in concert with the
natural environment.
Now, let's go back to man's law.
Oh, you can't smoke cannabis.
It's illegal. Now, how is that in line with the natural environment?
It's a fucking plant. Right.
So you see what happens?
Yeah. So, you know, and you know, the story behind making cannabis illegal had nothing to
do with getting high. Of course, it was about the paper manufacturers didn't want it.
And that's right. The fiber industry, the fiber industry wanted synthetic fiber.
Right. Right. And by the way, the hemp is still superior here, by the way, unless you go
to these nanofiber, you know, aramid, which is Kevlar and all of it.
That's not practical. You know, aramid, the Kevlar, bulletproof vests, all that stuff.
If you expose it to UV for more than 18 hours, it loses 40 percent of its strength.
No, I wasn't aware of that.
Well, it's crap.
Yeah, it's total crap.
So. So anyway.
So here's what the ultimate why is from what I'm gathering here, from what you're
saying. And I hate to cut to the chase, but let's do it.
It sounds to me like what you're saying is this is something that makes just behaviors
more conducive with a higher level of function.
In other words, it's a practical thing.
It's a benefit.
It's a benefit. Like like you're sitting there telling me, OK, look, I need to know
about the laws of the plant because I want the plant to thrive and survive.
And the same principle applied here is that this is a better way to thrive and survive
in the environment.
And based on the organism, OK, because you're an organism, a plant's an organism.
I think that's a fair characterization.
So you got to know what goes into the organism, what's best for it, what the, you
know, for example, when somebody's working too hard and they can't think straight, what
do you say? You need to take a break, break.
Yeah. So if you have a scheduled break, let's say the seventh day.
Right. It doesn't say don't work.
Right. Specifically, it's you need to take it's basically taking a break from work.
Right. And also making others work.
Right. So the word was like, I always heard directly.
It tells you she'll do no work on the Sabbath.
It's it's kind of like it means like don't be industrious in a way that you do not like
the fires of your shop.
So. Right.
And, you know, the day starts at noon.
Right. So with these idiots that are still, you know, archaics, by the way, no, I'm
surprised no one's retired. He doesn't know that the day starts at noon.
He thinks it's sundown. You can't measure that.
Right. But I'm not going to reach out to me.
And I think Sam sent him like a dozen emails.
He didn't answer one. So I would
suggest that when you cannot
approach there, OK, there are certain things.
It's jurisdictional also in the Bible that ninety nine percent of the people here.
And this is something if you don't know how to keep biblical time, you're not going to be
able to do these things properly because the seventh day off, by the way, if you're in
an agricultural society, I've said this many, many times before, it's worth saying it
yet. The Jews, right.
They they do Sabbath at night, sundown to sundown.
Now, you're agricultural society.
Yes or no. Yes.
Right. You have animals you got to feed and water.
Right. And so Sabbath comes Friday night.
You know, they whatever Pope's work schedule Sabbath starts the end of the day.
Right now, the next all night.
And that's the whole next day.
Your animals don't get watered.
They don't get fed the whole next day.
And you got to wait till sundown.
Got to wait till sundown.
But now the Sabbath's over.
So we're all going to. So Sabbath's over Saturday night sundown.
Now we go to the farm in the middle of the night and feed water the animals.
That makes no sense. No, because you're not going to make that all in the dark.
Yeah, of course. Right.
That's right. So pretty much you're going to show up the next person.
That's 36 hours later.
And the animals are distressed.
Right. This is all about distress.
Now, if you know biblical timekeeping and you start your Sabbath at noon, it goes from
noon to noon.
You show up at the farm in the morning and you get all your stuff done by noon.
So the animals are usually going to feed them and water them in the morning.
Right. They might miss a late afternoon meal or watering at night because you left at
noon. Right. And the next day in the morning, instead of getting the early feed and the
early whatever, they're like, where is he?
We show up at noon.
Right. And you catch up for the race.
I have the other half of the day to catch a minor delay.
So what you know, major stress.
If you do this, there might be some stress.
So major stress. So if you do this properly, right, you get everything done in the
morning all the way up to noon and that begins the new day.
So therefore, now your Sabbath day occurs starting at noontime.
You go back around. It goes to noon.
And the next noon here is an easier way to say it.
Bear with me on this one more.
So the Greek says he does the Sabbath, but I saw him show up every day.
I don't know how he's doing the Sabbath.
Yeah, but he left early and one day and the next day he came in late.
But to them, it looks like I'm showing up every day because their day starts.
Well, that's why I was just explaining that, because it look, if you get everything done
before noon, OK, that's one day.
The next day, you get everything done immediately after noon.
It seems like, well, you didn't take a day off, but you actually did.
That's right. To noon.
That's right. Because even now, my day goes from noon to noon.
As a matter of fact, there's a major cultural movement still.
Not so much, but up until the 80s, it was still very strong in Europe.
They did siesta right around noon, around 11 o'clock.
Everyone home at a big meal, slept till two o'clock.
Right. Spain, Italy, Greece, everywhere.
And all over the world.
It was typical because it was ingrained.
That was the end of the day.
When you fast for a day, you break your fast.
And right before the day ends, which is it.
Right. Yeah. That's why you break fast.
Break fast breakfast. Right.
So these things are critical.
So these questions about biblical law and not only law, do you have to do?
OK, so if you want to follow the laws of the United States, first of all,
it's all voluntary.
All the laws in the U.S. are because you say it's the law.
Each individual person has to agree to it.
No one can enforce them as such unless they coerce you.
And you're ignorant. You don't know. Right.
So it's I like what Brandon Joe Williams is doing.
I think that's how you say his name, because he basically shows like this,
you know, is getting citizenship and nationalities by declaration.
He doesn't know about the passport, by the way.
He used to use a passport.
What I would just want to add here is I don't have a passport
and I could still travel anywhere because I think it's State Department code
1865. I think it's 1865 or 1867 or 1896.
They have their own codes.
It's called an affidavit in lieu of passport.
LIEU in lieu of instead of you put an affidavit
in lieu of passport in a Google search and images.
You'll see after World War Two, a lot of these countries,
their government building and administrations were blown up.
People still wanted to travel for years.
You know, they didn't patch up Europe until like the early 50s.
Right. Late 40s.
So people had affidavits in lieu of passport.
And basically, you write, you swear who you are.
You say who you are, what your nationality is.
And they stamp the letter just like a passport.
So you see these letters, affidavits, little passport.
And you see all these stamps just like a passport, the picture on it and everything.
So if you understand that, like I use, but this is how I do it.
If I'm going to go fly, I fax a copy to the airport
before like four hours or the day before.
I let them know I'm coming to fly the next day. OK.
And you show up at the airport, show up at the airport.
And I go to the guy said he talks to head of security.
And he goes, oh, really? Why?
I said, because I fax.
And before I even finish saying I faxes, I know who you are. Come with me.
It's like they're all briefed.
All the security outside is briefed on who I am and what I look like
because I have a picture. Right.
And they sit me down. I got away for half an hour.
And then they walk me right to the plane.
No security check. Nothing, nothing.
None of that TSA stuff, whatever. OK.
Right. Let's just make a long story short.
So people think it's a disadvantage.
I find it as a high advantage.
Now, you can be pulled over and they could delay your flight sometimes.
And they delay you from taking, missing your flight.
And they'll say, oh, why do you do this?
You hate the United States.
I just don't know how to answer your question.
It goes both ways that you always if they give you a hard time,
they always apologize in the end. Right.
So make a long story short about all the travails and things
that I personally take on because I still don't do banking.
You know, someone sent me a PayPal still sitting there.
I'm looking at I just read the whole legal thing of PayPal.
I'm like, you got to be kidding.
You have to be insane to use this unless you're going to
you're willing to put something else forward.
You can't just go inside, you know.
But, you know, the definition of that nasty term, conspiracy theory
is a dirty term that they give to people who are not insane.
Right. You get it.
So so someone calls you a conspiracy theorist.
It's like they're just calling you sane because, you know,
you have to be insane to believe what you've been told all around.
But back again about law, it should prove out.
You should know it. You should know how to administrate.
So if someone is Jewish, I'd say about 75 percent of what they told is the law.
They'll tell you, by the way, if you corner a rabbi says, no, this is Jewish
tradition we're doing.
We're not trying to do the one in the Old Testament.
They'll tell you. They'll tell you right away. Right.
And again, with the U.S. codes and the U.S.
laws, doesn't matter if they're local, federal, state.
When you speak to someone higher up, forget about all the rights
and all the stuff they tell you.
They say you have to do what everybody else does,
even when you show them the law, that they're wrong.
They'll just tell you, just do what everybody else does.
They don't have no. That's called scoff law.
When you scoff at the law, it's called a scoff law.
People don't even use that term anymore.
You've heard of it, I'm sure.
It is a it is a scoff.
They're used to get tickets for scoff laws.
Remember jaywalking?
Yeah, right. Right.
But it's hardly ever, ever used anymore.
Some of the highlights that I like about Brandon Williams,
he brings up about law or two, two of them.
One of them is a lot of the black people lean on civil rights,
freedom and getting the rights.
Well, you have to remember that law comes first.
Then human rights came with various conventions.
And the last thing that came along, I think it was Johnson
that finalized most of them with civil rights.
So each one descends.
So when you ask for civil rights, it's actually less than human rights.
And the system understands that.
That's why the police and paramilitary target black people,
because they're under civil rights, which means they don't have human rights.
Anyway, that's a point that he brought up, which is absolutely valid.
He brought up some other points that were pretty valid.
None really come to mind.
But I just want to and if you're, by the way, black or other than white,
don't call yourself a minority because it has nothing to do
with how many of you there are that look like you or say you are who you are.
It has to do with being competent or not.
When you say you're a minority means you're not competent to go into contract
or to have the law competently applied to you as any minor.
As any minor would be incompetent to be under contract.
You need a guardian or your award award of the state.
You need to be you need an attorney.
Has nothing to do with being represented in court, which is an interesting
chronological question here based on something you just brought up is, look,
if you have the human rights to begin with,
then why is there even a necessity to have the civil rights applied?
Because they were they were created by convention.
Yes. But a lot of individuals are not included in the human rights equation.
You see, that was the whole.
No, but that's what I'm just saying.
There is a descending order.
So let's say they come up with a new set of rights,
which is they're doing with the LGBTQ, RSTUV, FUCK stuff.
Yeah. Right.
That is even worse because now you're a binary.
You're not binary because law only applies to men and women.
So now you're an object.
And when you get the vaccine, you have a patented substance in your body.
And you your control of your body goes under the patent laws.
Now, just like when GMO crops are neither an organic farm
and they take seed in the organic farm, they come and claim the farm
because you're growing the right, the wind blew it over.
I still feel like this is a legitimate question, though.
If you already had the human rights, though, and you had access
to all of the activities and facilities, et cetera.
No, hold on. You don't have the rights.
You have what you say you have.
Yes. But if that were the case, then there wouldn't have been a need.
It is the case.
No, it's not the case in case law, but it is the reality in the law.
You say who you are like.
They have these long processes for becoming a U.S.
citizen, which is criminal.
You could just do it with a piece of paper in five minutes.
And if the State Department doesn't accept it, you litigate against them.
And they won't take it to litigation because the law is there.
And one thing that Brandon does say that I do is, is no one knows anything
that's going on. No one.
No one in the State Department.
He's been through various offices all the way up.
No one knows anything at all.
They'll just when you bring up the lessons, you know, I've been doing this
for twenty five years and it doesn't matter how you do it.
You know, they don't know what it sounds exactly.
No one knows. Everything is completely wide open.
So the thing about all the U.S.
laws and codes, including the Constitution, if you understand the Ninth
Amendment, Ninth Amendment in the Bill of Rights basically says that as long
as you do, you can make up your own rights as long as it doesn't interfere
with any of these other rights and hurt anyone.
Right. So, you know, so if you say it's in the Bill of Rights, well, no, it's
not, you know, whatever, you know.
So the Second Amendment thing with the guns and the First Amendment, this
should always be paired with the Ninth Amendment.
Because they'll say, well, what you're doing isn't defined by that.
Well, then go to Ninth Amendment.
That's like a catch all. No one's being hurt and I'm not violating the other.
So anyway, he's doing a pretty good public service, but I wish you would find
out about doing the Senate because he's still doing he's doing conditional
endorsements, but he's not showing a demand.
So the IRS might might cook his bird because I've seen it.
You know, for example, taxation has nothing to do with citizenship because I
know someone who has a YouTube account in England and they do YouTube does
IRS withdrawal, even though he's getting paid in pounds.
How is he a U.S. citizen?
Right. How? How does he fall into that?
So there's a lot of stuff.
You know, I've already been over the holes in the archaic stuff that he talks
about just to correct, not to knock the archaics or not to knock Brandon.
But if you want if you study what they're putting out, which is generally
good and supplement it with these things that I put forth, you've got a pretty
good basis.
OK, right. So I'm filling in what they either forgot or incorrect.
Now, chances of them coming back and doing it with me is zero to none because
you only have like 50 subscribers and like five listeners.
Right. So it's not going to happen.
So but I would I would I would love to have dialogue with either one of them.
Right. So I'm not I'm too right now.
I'm at the point where emails I get to the email every three days.
That's the fastest I can get to it.
Right. So and you notice when we do the record the sonics, I'm always doing
something else. I'm multitasking.
Right. So with that said, I'm going to multitask and eat some pizza.
Well, there you have it.