Sonic Event 45, Ocelli and the Greek, and here we go.
I'll tell you this, looks like you got a few things in the chat and maybe some other communications
to sort out, so I don't know if I'll have a lot to say here and this might be one of those
quick ones.
So, here we go.
Where do we begin, Greek?
How are you tonight?
I'm alright.
We're coming up on the 8th month here pretty soon it looks like, the year's going by fast.
I want to get into basically energy perception so you can manage it.
I worked for someone a long time ago for about a week and he said if you can't, it was science
stuff, if you can't, a loudspeaker design, and then, well anyway, we're not kidding.
When you're 18, 19 and working with stuff that people usually go to engineering degrees
and you can mix right in with them and do what they do, it's kind of strange to them,
but they accept you.
I was in a very good situation.
One of the things I left with was, they were saying if you can't measure it, you can't
manage it, right?
So, you know, it's like, what's that smell?
You know, if you don't know where it's coming from, you're going to have to put up with it,
right?
It's kind of, what's that sound?
Or if you don't know, you know, where it's coming from first and what's making it, you
know, you're going to have to put up with it.
So what's going on is, how do we measure and look at energies?
You know, back to the chat, I want to go back to just Yin and Yang, and whoever is familiar
with the chat.
Wouldn't identifying it be the first step, though, because you got to, like you're saying,
what is it?
You got to know what it is first, and then you can measure it, because...
Yeah, and measurement is a way to make it more tangible, because there are things that
we can't measure that we could still use based on their effects, like the ether.
Well, like Yin and Yang, like, okay, so that's what we're going to get into.
Well, yeah, but first, why not identify exactly what it is you're looking for?
Like, how is it you're going to pick up on that to begin with?
I mean...
No, no, it's about direction.
It's about direction.
Energy.
Energy is all about direction.
If you have something that's not, let's say, in a common way, whether it's correct or incorrect,
when you call something giving off energy or whatever, the first thing that we say about
it is based on its direction, right?
We notice the directional movement.
Something is, something dynamic, some kind of action in some direction, even if it's
going in all directions, like a light bulb, for example, versus a laser, which is focused.
So let's get started on this.
This is a thing, people that have been almost doing shout-outs to archaics, even though
I don't endorse him.
You know?
Like, if he invited me to go and speak, I wouldn't.
It's just too much, you know what I mean?
And vice versa.
But he puts out some good stuff, and the good stuff here is, you'll see if you're familiar
with archaics material.
Okay.
As you said previously, you should always listen because you can take something from
a situation, even if there's not a lot of useful things there, there might be something
and you can almost always learn something if you just listen.
Yeah, there's some gratitude I have because of the chronology.
This is not from him, but it allowed me to tie this in.
The yin and yang, when you start saying that stuff, yin-yang, right, or whatever, that's
almost a putan, and back you see your yin-yang or whatever, everyone takes it as being Eastern.
It's actually not.
It comes back from a prehistorical time where we can go back and say, well, most sources
might agree.
Emperor Yao, the first emperor, was the one that put the culture living in that part of
the world in Asia on notice of yin and yang and the energies and what are named many
other things like qi, prana, whatever.
Emperor Yao was about six foot eight, red-haired, blue eyes.
All right, so very Asian-looking, right?
Okay.
Yeah.
Not at all.
He's the one that put the culture on back then.
This is right around flood days, right?
Asia, what planet, you know?
China, yeah.
And this was known amongst others.
In other words, he came from a milieu or a collective that this was known, that went
all over the world and ruled basic pockets of humanity.
Same people.
If you look even down to the Scythians, they were six foot seven, six foot eight, seven
foot tall, red-haired, blue eyes.
Is this the same guy who's credited with unifying China eventually from the fiefdoms?
Okay.
I'm just checking.
No, there was no China.
It was just nomadic people before that.
So anyway, I just wanted, this is not, look, you know, I have a lot of problems with macrobiotics
because there's nowhere to send people.
The concept is very sound, but it's really, what you'll find is a modified Japanese diet.
And then you'll have the personalities of Michio Kushi and others who were actually slightly
just, we call them disturbed individuals.
They couldn't fit into their society and they really didn't fit in here, you know?
So when I say disturbed, they were disturbing because they were very rigid.
But a lot of the stuff you see in the videos, so I met Michio Kushi several times and I was
asked to make a dessert for a dinner that was held for him back in 1988.
Anyway, they're very, very rigid.
And they put out their information as if they're not.
So you have to be very careful.
So everyone links it to being Japanese or, well, all these Asian cats, right?
All these Asian guys, right, and gals.
So there's a way to get away from it and the basic core there is.
And that's why I brought up Emperia.
I was not Asian.
So this core fundamental reasoning came from a pre, you might even say pre-Adamic society,
right?
Which is pretty much, you know, we're the descendants of anyway, not we, who's we?
So here's the idea, that the universe is always in balance and flux no matter what.
It always will try to make balance and when you're watching something change or grow, that's
what you're actually watching.
And once the balance is achieved, just like scales, if you have some very simple balance
scales, there's a lot of motion while you're loading and unloading them, but once the balance
is achieved, you look at the system and it's static, right?
No movement, right?
So basically, let's just take some of the pine needle ideas that were going up.
There was a, I keep posting images of the brown rice number eight, it's number eight
because I put the Imabashi plum in there, but I call it brown rice seven or brown rice
eight, just to inspire and just show what finished product may look like, right?
Especially what I was going to do, I should have, was do all the pre-cut items and everything
before it's combined and cooked, just to see the cut and all that.
So you didn't communicate well with the picture here, referring back to last Sonic, right?
What's the finished product?
What I wanted to do was do another posting that shows the pre-cut, before everything
is combined, what the cuts are like.
Well, that's what I'm saying.
You didn't communicate the process.
No, I didn't communicate that because there are people who are already jumped in making
it.
So I wanted to see if the final product was similar.
See what they would come up with on their own without it, and then go backwards.
But you can still see the cut in there, the vegetable.
You could still see the cut.
Oh, yeah.
You can see how it was cut.
Even if you look at a soup, you can tell, okay, this was diced.
This was, you know.
Well, we're looking at the rice, you could see the various cuts and it's basically a bias
cut.
Everything is, except for the onion, which is cut longitudinally, always cut across the
root and the top.
All right.
So the reason I had gotten several messages, I want to add this to it.
And it's like, no, no, no, no.
This is not about taste or flavor, right?
It's about energy balance.
And the finished plates that I showed on plating, I added a picante sauce and a parsley pesto,
which is just finely chopped parsley with a mubashi plum vinegar and olive oil.
But the energy in itself is, this has nothing to do with taste and flavor.
And I think most of the people get that, right?
Because I think someone posted that's amazing.
When you make this and eat it, it tastes good and it gives you the energy of a steak or
a good burger, right?
That's the idea.
But what it is, it's a very balanced, it has a very roundabout gathering of energies.
That's what we're going to get into.
So let's just use the yin and yang vernacular because it's easy to communicate.
But if anyone gets on you because it's Asian, that means we have to work even more to de-Asian,
decentralize it from that notion of being Asian alone, right?
That's what I try to do when I brought up Emperor Yao.
So let's just start, for example.
So cold is considered a very yin energy, yin being expansive and all that.
Now, when I say yin and yang, if you were to look up yin and yang, they have like less
than third grader definitions of it on the internet, no matter where you look.
It'll be a chart, right?
Yin on one side, yang on the other.
And you just read what's on the chart.
That's like not even third grade.
That's like second or first grade, right?
So let's refer to those for now.
That's fine for now.
But this we're going to run through is the measurement process and the functionality
and how things go into balance, and then ultimately how this affects you and how you can actually
be quote unquote a healer by recommending remedies and how you can come up with remedies,
even if you were put into an environment where you're completely unfamiliar, just based on
the way things look, grow, smell, color, touch, feel, all that stuff, right?
Using the senses.
And which I, by the way, I've been doing for almost 30 plus years with people, right?
Just coming up with remedies on things that were in the environment.
And most of the time it works, if you understand what we're going to be talking about tonight.
So culturally, culturally, it's rather Mediterranean anyway, to use food in order to solve things.
Seems like, you know, I hate to use the phrase food as medicine, but there it is.
It is.
Well, the ancient Egyptians believed that if you were sick, it was because of your diet.
The ancient Greeks and modern Greeks even still believe if you're sick, it's because
of your diet.
They've been brainwashed by the pharmaceutical companies now also.
I know for sure the Italians believe that also.
When I was growing up, up until the 70s, if you were sick, it was because of your diet.
And that can go on and on and on and pretty much name most cultures nationalities, right?
Yeah, you need to either eat something or stop eating something one or the other quite
often.
So let's get started on this.
So cold is considered a yin energy, very, very yin.
So we have a body of water, which let's not consider if the water is yin or yang.
OK, let's just say we have a body of water and this yin energy known as a lot of cold
comes to it, which is very, very yin.
And it keeps affecting this body of water.
Now the water in its current state is a fluid and it has density and all that.
It's not compressible.
Water is not a good example for this to see because water doesn't have any molecules.
By the way, I just want to interject this.
If anybody tells you they saw that they draw a molecule of water, even the Ken Wheeler guy
talks about this.
It's all bullshit.
No one has ever seen a molecule of water.
There is no hex bonding.
It's impossible for water to have a molecule because it's not compressible.
If it was made up of molecules, the interstitial space of the molecule would allow for compression
to take place.
And water is known to be incompressible at 39 degrees, of course.
It's the only material that will do that.
So if you had a column, a six foot column in a water and a six foot column of the hardest
steel known to man, you can compress the steel and see it move, but you cannot compress the
water.
You see?
So there's no molecules in water.
That's why I always gave the examples that I do.
So that's another, that's more advanced and I'm beginning to discover that and be able
to back that up with devices here in the near future.
All right.
So you have this water.
It's in a state and you keep hitting it with this yin energy, which is cold, right?
And yin remember is expansive, soft, dark, right?
But the energy is yin.
So it keeps hitting this substance called water.
What does the water do when you keep hitting it with more and more cold?
It gets what?
Hard.
It becomes yang.
Right?
Even regardless if the water is yin and yang itself, it starts to exhibit yang properties.
Becomes hard, right?
Ice.
Okay.
So we then mistake a mature, an immature person would say, Oh, the water, if yin and yang became
hard, that means that it's hard because of the cold is yang.
No, it's easy to say a lot of beginners make this, this premise that cold is yang.
No, it's yangifying because it's so yin.
So what happens is when the substance known as water, which is fluid, it can consider
yin compared to other things, but it's, again, it's not a good example because it's incompressible.
So in reality, water is more yang than the hardest material, harder than diamond.
But anyway, that's another, but I'm using this as a stark example, right?
Another example would be, have you ever seen, they have a vat of liquid nitrogen and they
dip a banana in it and freeze it and then they use it to drive a nail.
There's a lot of videos on that.
And if you take the hammer and dip it in the liquid nitrogen, you try to drive a nail.
What happens?
The hammer shatters like glass.
Yeah.
Okay.
Same principle.
If you understand what I just mentioned, what happens here, right now, because the energies
that subject the material, the material always exhibits the opposite.
Okay.
Let's give another example.
Anything that goes down into the ground is young.
The roots of a tree and anything that goes up into the sky is yin, right?
But wait a second.
When something is pointy and going up and moving a sharp edge, like the, you know, the edge
of a plant, the front end of a plant that would be young.
Yes.
Because the plant is growing into the yin environment known as the atmosphere, in order
to balance, it starts to develop sharp, hard edges, right?
Okay.
So basically if you apply a yin circumstance to something or a yin energy, you will get
the opposite.
I'll get a young outcome.
And the other way you put a young on it, you'll get a yin outcome.
That's right.
Okay.
So, so let's say you have something like a banana and you have a steel mallet, a wooden
mallet.
Now, which one is more young?
The mallet, the steel mallet is more young or even a wooden mallet than a banana.
It's harder, right?
In it's beginning way, the mallet is way harder.
The banana will get smashed if you try to drive a nail with it, the mallet will smash
the nail.
Okay.
Right.
So, well, but in this case, it's the hard mallet hitting the banana is very, very young,
but it makes the banana even more yin, right?
More yin, it gets splatters everywhere, it's more expanded, right?
Right.
So, so in other words, materials exhibit these energies anyway, they're broadcasting it.
Okay.
So let's move forward.
When you look at the water that was affected by a tremendous amount of yin energy, it is
now hard.
So it is broadcasting a young energy to balance the yin energy and itself, the substance has
become young.
So let's go back to the pine needle analogy.
Someone mentioned maybe they'll use pine needles and I made a comment that I'm not sure about
it.
It doesn't seem like a bad idea if it's, if it's within the climate and geography, the
latitude wise, right?
But pine needles alone, I think they need to be balanced with more things because what
will happen, this is, this is the Testament to the rice.
If you look at the number seven or number eight rice, the reason why I did that is because
it's got all of these things that work together and each one covers a certain base.
Think of it like a baseball diamond.
You have a people in the outfield, left field, right field, and someone's playing each base,
right?
Right.
It wouldn't be really baseball if you had one man or two men out in the field, right?
It would be kind of ridiculous because I'll hit the ball where they're not right and watch
them chase it and they'll run out of energy and the game would look really dumb.
It'll just look like a training game, but because there's so many players in the field
and covering different parts of the field with different purposes and skill, it makes
it very interesting, you see?
So when you have a very narrow single thing, let's say that a pine needle, whether, however
you do it, is it tincture or tea or whatever, what will happen is you will get an effect
for it.
See, the pine is going towards the yin energy as it goes up, but it's going up into the
yin which itself is manifesting yang.
But it's yang only because of all of the yin that it's going into, right?
So what happens when you have that pine needle, it has this very distinct quality because
also the more easily identifiable something is, the more distinct its quality also, right?
So when you look at a pine needle, it's unmistakable what it is, right?
So also its energy will be very narrow and unmistakable.
It'll be very narrow, right?
You know, this doesn't always hold true because someone gives you some white powder and says,
snort it.
It's not necessarily what you might think it is.
It could be any white.
There's so many white powders, right?
Titanium dioxide.
I just made a pizza tonight.
It could be flour.
It could be soap.
It could be, right?
Right.
Anything from powdered sugar on.
Sure.
Why not?
Yeah.
Sure.
Powdered sugar.
But this is also the, actually, there was a funny thing with John Belushi.
You're predicting, remember eating the powdered sugar donut in the end, you would think he
was doing something else.
So we're talking about things that are not processed now.
That's why I brought up that example.
So what happens if you do the pine needle thing, you will have an immediate effect that
is very, let's say, narrow banded.
And of course it helps, you know, if that's what you're looking for and then comprehend
it, right?
So what you would perhaps do in this case is look at the energies that the pine needle
is exhibiting.
They're young, right?
It's narrow, hard, right?
It can take a lot of coal and all that.
But it's only because of that, because the foundation of its purpose of manifesting was
the yin in a colder place of yin environment growing up upwards, right?
You see, into the atmosphere.
So the purpose and impetus of its manifestation was yin, the resultant is yang, and you, by
consuming it and how you prepare it, is the effect that you're going to get is going to
be somewhere in the middle.
Always in the middle.
Give me an example.
If you are in a lot of yin energy, very cold, and you take water that has been subjected
to that, you wouldn't be taking liquid water, you'd be taking a piece of ice.
When you subject yourself to that ice, because of your body temperature, a part of it will
start to thaw out immediately, if it's not like super cold, right?
So you'll start to get the balance of the thawed out ice as liquid also.
You won't just have ice, right?
So you're somewhere in the middle, when you throw yourself into the situation.
This is the part that I always want to bring up, and this is maybe people with at least
a few sharpened pencils in their pocket can start putting together what we're saying in
this sonic.
It's never yin or never just yang.
It's how this thing came to be, let's say yang, because it was penetrating the yin environment
and affected by the yin environment, and when you put a human in there, in the mix, when
that substance, whether it's the energy or the product of that energy, the plant usually,
they're going to get a little bit of both, and you're going to be in between, you see?
So what's so fascinating, if this was a simple principle that was, let's say, quote unquote,
in air quotes and brackets, mastered by the Asians, why do they still have practitioners
and doctors they have to go to?
Because everyone would get it, right?
Everyone, you wouldn't need a doctor, a practitioner to figure it out, or a quote unquote, you know,
medicine person.
So what's going on with these people that are practitioners in this field, especially with
medicines and remedies, and this science is also, in ancient times, if you wanted to be
a weapons builder, come up with a new weapon, you had to understand yin and yang, right?
Or anything, like Da Vinci, people think, you know, Da Vinci, we would know about him
if he did not advertise himself as a weapons designer, right?
That's how he got his funding.
That was one of the main things, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
And that's where the money is, right?
So let's say, so in those days, they had money.
Okay, so the specialty in this is the contemplation and the study.
So when you look at something for its quality, you have to also consider who is going to
be who's the recipient, their quality, right, what they're trying to do with it.
And typically, what I would suggest, most people look at these remedies is like, okay,
this is good for this ailment, this is good for that ailment, this is good for this condition
for that, stop doing that, when you're going to learn this.
Never think about in the beginning, do not start thinking about ailments and remedies.
You see, imagine if you were going to affect a perfectly balanced, healthy person with
various different types of intake, right?
And then watch what happens.
You see, meaning yourself, if you want to explain if you, for example, if you're not
in really good shape, physically, health wise, and all that, you shouldn't be messing with
what I'm talking about.
Only people who are in good shape, physical health, and all that should take on what I'm
saying as a task of contemplation, as a task of study, you see, right?
And then when they understand it, and they can see the balance to and fro, and the dynamics,
when then they take on a study and a case study with someone who has this condition,
you will be able to see it very clearly.
But if you yourself, for example, are suffering some ailment or condition, and are trying
to figure out what to do based on this yin and yang principle and using the naturopathy
and all this other stuff, it's going to be extremely difficult.
You got too many things working against you, because the physical condition also works
against the mind, right?
Okay.
For example, the intestines and the brain look very much the same, right?
They're in different positions.
So the intestines or your gut, you know, the gut feeling you can't describe, but it's a
very base feeling, and the brain feeling is more, you can describe more intellectual,
but they're basically the same.
When the body is folded over in the embryo, they come from the same thing.
You know, the first thing that forms when the egg starts to divide, the first feature
before even a zygote is the anus.
So we're one big anus first.
That's why when you call people an asshole, anyway.
Yeah, we were all just assholes.
We were all assholes to begin with.
We were all asshole all in the beginning.
Everyone was all asshole.
So anyway, crazy, right?
Going forward, when you have someone that has intestinal problems, they can't think clearly
and vice versa.
If someone doesn't think clearly, eventually they have stomach problems.
Oh, you ever wonder why so many Americans have stomach problems?
How could they think clearly with their education and what they watch on TV and take in a church
or a radio, right?
Well, stomach and back is what I always hear.
Stomach and back.
Stomach and back is complicated because there's so many functions there.
There's actually things that can develop in the body, forms of fungus that are so powerful,
they will form a ring around the vertebrae and crush the vertebrae.
So that's another thing.
I don't know if you guys ever...
Anyway, medical study is incredible, by the way, because anything can happen based on
the conditions changing.
Like, for example, before being subject...
Right now, it's pretty easy to be subject to radioactive high doses of radiation.
Very easy for that to happen.
We're not just talking about people who are targeted to be taken out that way.
But if you went back into the past, it was a very rare occurrence.
Right?
I mean, now you could rig a microwave door open and perhaps put it near someone and they'll
get...
They don't know what happened.
They go to the medical and they'll say, you have all the things of radiation, microwave
poisoning, right?
All that, right?
That's very rare.
If you went back to 300 years, that was unheard of.
Right.
You see?
So that's what I mean.
The human body is constantly changing.
And the stuff that you're seeing what people are going through now are 100% based on their
environment.
All these cancers, all these diseases, diabetes, high blood pressure.
Actually, the ones I mentioned do not exist.
There's just a form of communication.
By the way, you know what?
No one has ever gotten ill from diabetes.
Only the people that receive treatment for it, right?
I think you understand that too, right?
Yeah.
Most people don't understand that.
Most people get tested and they have low blood sugar and they keep sending you letters and
phone calls.
You know, you were diagnosed...
Not you have anything.
You were diagnosed with a possible serious condition.
You should consider treatment.
Of course, there's nothing wrong with you, right?
They need business, right?
So it's kind of like the guys here with window tint.
Oh, you don't have tint on your windows in Arizona.
You need to get some window tint to make it sound real important.
You don't have windshield insurance.
You know how many rocks and grout, right?
You know, people are like, oh my gosh.
Yeah.
You know, it sounds right.
It sounds pretty convincing.
So the same with AIDS and all this other stuff.
Cancer is the same.
The problem is that some people, you know, you'll hear a lot of stories.
Well, they didn't get diagnosed early enough and they died of cancer.
Well, yeah.
Well, you know, because they just kept ignoring.
You know, it's a certain lifestyle, right?
That brought it on, right?
So again, I didn't focus much on too many examples, but I don't think too many examples
are necessary.
You can go through the third or first or second grade level chart of yin and yang.
And those energies will always manifest the opposite in material form.
And you are always somewhere in the middle.