Sonic Event 65, Ocelli and the Greek rated Y, and you know, I keep getting hit with lots
and lots of commercials.
And oh, by the way, I've been going over some old footage of the Kennedy assassination because
I'm going to be doing a conference soon and all that.
But going over that stuff and taking a look at the new coverage, you might want to look
back at some of the Sonics where the Greek was talking about what it is they show you
versus what's actually happening.
It's really fascinating when you look at the archival footage from 1963.
But anyway, another day we'll talk about that because a lot of things going on.
So you know, Greek, I'm getting hit with tons of commercials about just for your signature
nowadays, weirdly enough, you can end up with because you're entitled to these subsidies
and they'll send you a nice plastic card that allows you to pay for groceries and rent and
all kinds of things because you're just entitled to it.
Weird that that's going on, but maybe not.
No, that's the exemption.
It's called a social security number.
I think it's called social security in almost every country, right?
Something like it.
If it's not social security, it's a social, you know, a social number or what is the other
thing they call it?
In England, it's called something else.
A lot of them in England will call it like council this or that because it's issued by
the local councils that are supposed to govern an area.
So it's a council payment or a council tax.
Well, not always.
Not tax accounts.
Yeah.
What what they didn't tell you was they went into a bad deal.
They didn't illegal and unlawful stuff without your consent and notice.
So since it's already done, they're giving you an exemption.
You're exempt from it, right?
So just like when there's an accident, they redirect traffic.
You don't really stop you from going down that road.
They do.
It's called a banking holiday when they do stop it.
But they read.
Right.
So but the Bar Association attorneys are scumbags, by the way.
And I'm talking about the one percent of the attorneys that actually know what's going
on.
Ninety nine percent of the attorneys are just incompetent because they think they it's very
important when they go to school.
It's just like the CIA people.
Right.
I think I told you when they go through the initial phase of recruitment at CIA, they
say, OK, we've been here for a couple of weeks for initial whatever indoctrination, let's
go out in the parking lot.
Why?
You'll see.
So they'll go out in the parking lot and they start raising the American flag and they have
a camera about knee height and whoever's knees are shaking the most when the flag is going
up are the ones that they recruit, right, because they want you to be really patriotic.
Right.
And then they tell you that everything you're doing is to protect the republic, the constitution.
Then they start switching it to obeying orders and then it's all about obeying orders and
then they switch it to.
Right.
OK.
So the same thing with the attorneys.
What happens is people that want to go to law school, the ones that are smart drop out
because the reason why is they're like, you know, it's so complicated.
They're not talking about any law at all.
I'm out of here.
Right.
Same with medical school.
You know, I want to go to become a doctor to help people.
They're not talking about anything about healing or how the body really works.
I'm out of here.
So they give the impression, the society, that if you dropped out of law school or medical
school, you're done.
It's actually the opposite.
Right.
So they want the dummies in there.
And then they do the same thing in law school where it's they start bringing they don't
teach law.
By the way, you can go to like a little community college like Harvard Law School and look up
their curriculum.
Right.
You know, saying that sarcastically.
You're not going to get any more that.
Yeah.
So you look at the curriculum.
They don't teach any law.
You'll see stuff like how to start a law clinic later on.
Well, I know a guy years ago.
Let me ask you this real fast, because I know a guy years ago who dropped out of both medical
and law school and, you know, he had dropped out of one and then went to the other and
dropped out of that one.
And he said, you know, the common thing that I found with both of these places is that
it's not about the law and it's not about the medicine.
It's actually about signing up for stuff.
They tell you how to sign up for things so you can become part of this and that.
And the third thing he said, that's the universal idea between the two things.
That's the real secret that they teach you.
That's what you're paying the money for.
So you know how to get in on this and that racket.
That's literally it is.
Right.
Is a racket.
Yeah.
Well, essentially.
All right.
The law, the law is very much tied in.
OK.
Two years ago, when I had cable more than a few years ago, I turned it on real late
at night and it was C-SPAN and it was the head of the Bar Association and he's making
a nice initiating speech.
It was his first speech to the Bar Association.
You know, the first thing he said is everyone knows that in order to have a strong economy,
a strong legal system.
And what that means is when they charge, when people are charged with crimes, you know what
they call criminal law, you can't charge a human being.
And what they're doing is they're charging, right.
The exemption.
Right.
And they have a there's a it's not public, but there's a code for every crime and misdemeanor.
There's a commercial charge.
Actually, if you look at civil law and federal codes, it tells you that all crimes are commercial
crimes.
So essentially what they're doing is they're running a serious racket.
It's really horrific what they're doing.
And I've actually met here in town in Tucson, one of the former district attorneys, and she
came from a prominent family.
I'm not going to mention her name.
Just by saying those two things, you could find out who she is.
She says she was in the legal system for a couple of years and she quit because she found
out what they were doing.
Right.
So she didn't want to discuss it because that's how horrific it is.
But we can discuss horrific things.
They are horrific.
Most attorneys, by the way, don't have a clue, just like most doctors don't have a clue what's
going on there.
They're following along, you know.
So both things show are a testament to the robustness of the human condition.
In other words, you could live in a society that has no law and no medicine, really, and
still be OK because you're really tough.
Humans are built tough.
Right.
So, yeah.
So that's basically the thing.
What I wanted to jump to.
You know, that is the primary excuse, by the way, that people use for why it is they don't
challenge anything, is that, look, you know, what am I supposed to do?
I'm supposed to live in a society that doesn't have this, that doesn't have that.
And you don't have it.
Well, that's the funny part.
You don't actually have it.
But they you know, but the fact that it's supposed to be there, right.
There's supposed to be a country.
There's supposed to be an army that is protecting all the people that are in this one place.
There's supposed to be laws that protect, you know, people that are not breaking the
laws.
Right.
Isn't that the key thing?
It's so funny, too.
You bring up everything's a commercial crime.
I don't know how many times I've tried to explain to people that whether you got caught
with, you know, eight tons of cannabis or you got caught with heroin, it's really about
the fact that you violated commercial codes.
Oh, well, here's the thing.
You can look up the the the drug laws.
I think it's Title 21 have been repealed, by the way.
What they did is they first repealed parole and then they repealed the rest of it.
But they're not telling anyone.
Right.
I was looking at Title 12 the other day to see if I could find anything juicy.
And if you go to the code online, every other section is it says omitted, omitted, omitted.
It doesn't mean it's not in effect.
It's just that they're not publicly showing you what it is anymore.
I think more and more people are starting to look at it.
Right.
But what I wanted to bring up is a few things is a heavy philosophical aspect to this, where
the lady, you know, if you've ever heard Greek speak, especially vintage Greek speak or Greek
speak better.
You've heard me say several times over and over that everything that could have been
known was known by the late eighteen hundreds.
Right. And this 20th century is like the stalled century.
It's like it when it's like the heart that put the brakes on the whole body.
And yeah, you could just look at the history of 20th century and the end of the 19th
century. What was going on in the the end of the 19th century was there was a
philosophic aspect that got quashed.
And if you want to know what got quashed is go study Walter Russell's work, because
he's an offshoot of this philosophy that was growing that never really made it to the
20th century in print.
One of the reasons why is you hear of all these philanthropists at the late eighteen
hundreds, Carnegie, the Carnegie Mellon Foundation's Rockefeller.
They were building all these libraries supposedly to be philanthropists.
No, they were not. They were getting involved because they were removing the libraries
and putting in new ones.
Right. OK, so let's go.
What happened then was what if you study, let's say, the universal one, I think, Walter
Russell, he he kind of gets into it.
This is the point, like everything.
And I was a P.D.
Ospinski gets into this in the first few books or the book, Churcham or get them.
If you get into it, basically our perception makes our reality.
So when when you talk about banking, you talk about how it really works is an attorney, a
judge, a bank will stop you.
Yeah, but you got your car.
You want it, didn't you?
You went to the store and got milk, didn't you?
Right. You got your house, didn't you?
It's like a distraction, right?
Right. Because the whole thing is based on perception, like force is based is defined
as with matter.
So force is defined on something that moves matter and matter is defined as something
that stops a force.
But what if we're thinking and more than in relative terms, but in actual terms, working
with, quote unquote, forces that have no material counterpart, like ether and electricity
and things like that, then how do you define them?
And you can't the fourth dimension.
You see, you talk about three dimensions.
You've got length, width and height.
Right. It's all projection within our reality outward.
So they're looking for this fourth dimension, right, which is another projection beyond
length, width or height.
But what if the fourth dimension is the other way?
It's it's before length, it's before width and before height, you see, and it's
projecting that way now.
Now, right.
That's very spooky when you look at it.
You're giving example. I had a hard time this week because, you know, I build the water
devices. It's aqueous, aqueous borealis.
And the device is called the Mark One Scalarator.
Right. So the guy who's getting is out in the country in Jersey.
And it was just like turbid well water that stinks.
Turbid, meaning like it's yellowish tan.
Right. Comes out of the tap.
No, there are parts of well water in Jersey that come out and it just smells like rotten
eggs because of the.
Yeah, this one was more like smell like an S.O.S.
pad. Oh, OK.
That's even worse. Oh, yeah.
And the water was not clear.
I was like, this may not be the right thing.
Well, Plummer puts it in and guess what?
Photograph before photograph after the water is crystal clear and tasted.
Smells good. Holy crap.
How is that possible?
Well, I know how it's possible.
I've invested the past six months of my life putting it together.
And I think this is my life's work in terms of making a tool or something like years
ago. I had a discussion, this guy, John, in Phoenix.
He invented he's an inventor.
About 30 years ago, he invented, you know, electricians.
They have this tool that strips the wire and cuts it at the same time.
It's like a pliers. Oh, yeah, yeah.
When you squeeze the pliers, it has a gear that pulls a plate that pulls the insulation
off and then cuts it. No, I used to.
It's a perfect trip. It's the perfect stripping tool.
I used to use that in the studio all the time because I had to make wires bare to make
my own. John, so we're talking about all these things.
You know, it's really cool to come up with stuff, you know, like that gizmos, gadgets,
inventions. But this is crazy.
I mean, think about something you bury in the ground or put them hang on the wall and
your plumbing, whoever your plumbing comes in the house.
And you got dirty water coming in and goes through this loop, the spool and a magnetic
reactor because it's starting to engineer.
Is it so using magnets?
I'm like, no, yeah, it's a magnet.
We're not using any magnetism.
And he's like, so what? So are you using magnetism or not?
No, it's a magnetic reactor.
There's a magnet present, but it's not.
But it's not using magnetism.
Well, if you want to stop the device from working, go ahead and apply the magnetism to
the flow and you'll see everything stops.
It's kind of like you want to get the word reactor.
It's like nuclear reactors.
You only have time to hear it now.
They use nuclear reactors to heat water, to drive turbines.
Now, the purpose of that is just to give to the reactor nuclear reactor to produce heat,
not to put radiation in the water.
Same principle. The magnetic reactor is there to unleash the potential of the water's
ability to clean itself.
And yes, water does clean itself.
The way you can witness that is when you have I don't want to make this a talk about
water, but just if anyone says, how does water clean itself?
Go look at either Google Earth, which is a still photo or live photos.
If you can't find them, video of when the confluence of rivers flowing into the ocean
or sea. What happens is right before the river water falls into the sea or the ocean,
it starts foaming on its banks.
You can see it on Google Earth.
Yeah, of course. Yeah.
The foam is there because the river is like being apologetic.
It's like, you know, I've got all this stuff in here and I don't want to dump it into
you. So let's remove as much as we can right now.
So it starts to foam and it dumps all the dirt off the banks and then it delivers the
cleanest water it can do in that short time to the sea or the tributary or wherever it
goes. Very interesting phenomenon.
So then if you study, for example, I wouldn't say Moto because he did a lot of
exclusions. You know, he's the guy that shows the water positive energy and negative
energy, you know, pretty and ugly.
Right. He did all exclusion.
So his experiments, people can't repeat them because he took 2000 pictures and he only
shows you two. And you think he just took two pictures.
He omitted all the ones that didn't show anything.
Right. And he didn't tell you he took 2000 pictures to get those two either.
So everybody's like, oh, well, I'll try it doesn't work.
You know, so whatever. So that's exclusions that he does.
The medical industry is like that, too.
But history is like that.
But the whole Veda Austin hydroglyphs, Veda Austin, you could look her up.
I always make a comment. She's so bedroomy.
Every time she shows up in a video, she she's like bedroomy.
She puts on like like she looks like she just got disheveled in the bedroom.
You know, she's very bedroomy, like when a woman's going to go to the bedroom.
OK, gotcha. Yeah, that's her.
That's her. That's how she sees herself.
Kind of like when I was growing up, you notice how women, as they get older,
they always stick with a style that they that resembles
when they thought they were the prettiest.
But what I mean by that is like when I was growing up in the 60s, 70s and 80s,
I noticed even in the 80s, like my friend's mom,
who thought she was the prettiest, probably in the 50s, still had the 50s hairdo.
Right. Right. Because that's what she was happiest with.
You know, anyway, that's a that's a whole other discussion.
Anyway, we like you, Veda.
But all right. So, yeah, interesting stuff.
Interesting, very interesting stuff.
So so by the way, on a personal note, because of this water device,
my reality is is like I'm dreaming, you know, it's like wherever this thing goes,
it's you expect one X or two X and it does 10 X.
And it's like, oh, my gosh, oh, my gosh, this is pretty incredible stuff.
And by the way, I put out for, you know, stuff on how to build.
We've gone much further than that.
There's a lot of treatments, you know, to build this thing and slight transmutations.
Yeah. So anyway, well, that's anyone interested in that?
Yeah, that's the key word I was waiting for is transmutation,
because I was thinking to myself that, you know, indeed, even the quality of your air.
I've seen people change the quality of air by by putting out things
that if somebody looks at it from a pure engineering standpoint,
it makes no sense, but somehow you have less debris in the air
if you place these things around and they're of particular colors
and they're made of particular components.
And it just simply changes the quality of the air in an area. Right.
I'm thinking it's a similar principle to what's happening with the water.
Yeah. Here's a way to start the way to do that.
Believe it or not, piezoelectrics, you know, when you piezoelectrics
in essence is if you put electricity in a crystal,
it vibrates or if you vibrate a crystal, it gives off electricity. Right.
Yeah. Like I have a cigarette lighter that you when you click, it makes a loud click
because it's a little hammer that hits a crystal that gives off a spark. Right.
So, yeah, that's when you hear some ovens and you hear click, click, click, click.
Right. So all that the pilotless starters and all that piezoelectrics.
All right. So what you do is you find yourself a big honking crystal,
big meaning like more than three or four inches and get a C clamp.
Like the kind of carpenters use, you get them, seen them at the dollar store. Sure.
And go ahead and start clamping on that crystal.
Make it nice and tight, but don't break it.
Right. Go as tight as you can without breaking it. Right.
So and you'll know how much pressure is on that because, you know,
if you put a C clamp on your finger and you start turning it,
you could really feel it. Right. Yeah.
So so get a sense to do it on your finger first.
So you know how much of a turn does how much of a squeeze, believe it or not,
get get an organic gauge going. Right. Put it on your big toe.
Don't put it on anything else.
But, yeah, get a feeling when you when you start pinching with that clamp
and part of your body, how fast it gets tight.
Right. Before you do it on the crystal. Right.
So then do it on the crystal. Keep it tight.
Put the crystal in the corner of the room. Leave the room.
Come back a half hour later.
Talk about air quality change big time.
Right. Yeah. These are these are small things.
I'm going to be getting more into this in the future about induction
and a little little tricks and tips like this.
And we're going to put some things together.
And, yeah, listeners of Greek speak will be on a whole other level.
Practical devices that are pretty incredible.
So well, that's why these people were encasing these crystals.
And I don't know if you remember this.
This was kind of fashionable about 10 years ago.
They were encasing them in this like plastic type substance.
So organize stuff.
This is different because you can't.
Yeah, those things do compress a little bit.
But you have no control over the compression.
Each crystal should get a little different compression.
Well, that's the problem is that you can create a result with this.
But it does vary. It's not the same.
It's not. Yeah, it's not the same thing.
But I'm just saying, yeah.
And certain crystals don't like being near other materials.
Like, for example, if you have aluminum powder and copper powder
and you put it in that plastic matrix, you know, the aluminum and by the way,
powder, aluminum and copper don't like each other. Right.
But aluminum powder and copper powder hate each other.
I hate you. Get away from me.
But you force them in a in a in a plastic matrix, epoxy or crystals.
And now you got this natural thing.
So and I hate you. I hate you, too.
I hate you. I hate you, too.
All day and all night.
Yeah. And these people think it's good.
You know, I wouldn't do that.
Yeah. So the simplest thing. Right.
Like your basic course that you could find, you know, on the ground
almost anywhere, that stuff gets along with everybody, you know.
Yes. So speaking of getting along in the chat, someone put on about property
ownership when you get a house or something like that.
Well, oh, yes.
The philosophical part of this still holds.
In other words, you're not going to get lawful money.
Silver and gold don't work no more.
It's just like saying cars are polluting.
So let's bring back horse and carriage.
Ain't going to happen. Right.
And here's the thing.
If you try to make it happen, you're going to be like,
yeah, when I had a car, I didn't use it for a week.
It just sat there.
But if I have a horse and I don't use it for a week, you got to feed it.
You got to water it every day.
You got to let it walk around some, too.
You can't leave it sitting there a long time because it doesn't work around.
So you got to check with the Amish on this to see how that works.
You know what I mean?
Yeah. So it's not going to work.
The lawful money, what they did, what they did is basically the twelve
USC for 11 USC.
That would be how would you say that, Uncle Sam?
Cat or Uncle Sam?
Cradle USC, United States Code
12 for 11. Right.
I think Charlie used to be the way they would do the Charlie.
Yeah, there you go.
OK, yeah.
So United States Code Title 12 Section 411 is the remedy.
And it's also in the original Federal Reserve Act.
And and they've right.
So basically all it's like in a form of exemption.
You just make a demand for lawful money.
All you have to do is make a demand for lawful money.
But you have to maintain good records to show that you've made your demand
and dated. Right.
And what that does, it sort of keeps you free from all those shenanigans.
It's kind of like when the mob goes into a club
and tells everyone the low level mob put their wallets on the table
and you don't put your wallet on the table and you say,
well, because I'm a Gambino.
Right. Why did you put your wallet on your table?
Because I'm a Gambino.
Were they going to say, oh, yeah, OK, that's right.
Next one. Right. Right.
They're going to take it from the Schwartz and they're going to take it
from the Pollyanna guy. Right.
So you kind of exempt.
So it's about record keeping.
So if you do have a piece of property or something, whoever you got it from,
send them something back saying that the deal was done in lawful money.
And also while you're doing the deal, the payments or whatever,
you make a note in the memo.
Anytime you have a check or whatever, there's a memo line.
Put lawful money, 12 USC, 411.
So you have something to to stand on. Right.
It's all about record keeping.
They switched over.
You see, the Bolsheviks went into Russia and they did what they did.
They did the same thing here, but differently.
In other words, a takeover.
The takeover here was done financially, taking control of the money
because even then, Americans just had too many guns. Right.
And they were too spread out.
So, yeah, sorry to be the bearer of bad news and good news.
See all bad news.
See, if bad news is helpful to know, it's really not all that bad, is it?
This is this has a good aspect to it also. Right. Right.
Well, you can learn from look, it sucks that people had to suffer or whatever.
But now we know what not to do.
You know, right. That's why ever since you've known me in private,
I said, did you do it in a conditional endorsement?
You know, you do conditional endorsement.
It's just got to keep. Oh, the other thing.
So in other words, I don't have much more to say on no one owns anything.
No one owns anything because they can't.
They don't exist. Right.
They only if their premise of any government or administration
is they exist on the power of the people.
If they're screwing the people, you can't go to them and say,
why are you screwing us?
Because they've stopped existing before they started screwing you
in order to screw you.
OK, OK. So. All right.
Go, go think of that a little bit.
I'm not going to repeat that. I don't know if I can't.
No, I'm just wrapping my mind around it or trying to hear.
Yeah, it's you got it. You got to first.
Look, if they don't exist, you can't go back on the power of the people
and for the people, by the people.
And you see that they're screwing you.
You can't go to them anymore because it's not the same government.
And it's right because they had to not be the same government
in order to screw you, of course, because if they were the same government,
they were screwing you.
They are their options. They'd have to answer for it.
Right. But now because they don't care,
it's obviously not the same one.
It's kind of like
men in black.
It starts off with the roach takes over the guy's body.
He's in a suit.
The wife is like sitting there with the lemonade.
I don't know if you remember the first men in black movie.
Yeah, he was in an Edgar suit.
Edgar. Yeah. OK, so the government is like in an Edgar suit.
It's not don't go there.
That's a it's a big bug, right?
They don't exist anymore.
And I keep telling you, they don't exist.
I mean, they tell you they don't exist.
It's around the Civil War.
They shut down Congress.
They call it close a Latin term for meaning no more day.
And so they just show up as a formality. Right.
Yeah. So it's like having a birthday party for someone who's no longer alive.
That's been done, too. You know what I mean?
Yeah. So it's all it's all just formalities.
That's why these things are on their end are getting worse and worse and worse.
So speaking of formality, somebody did mention in chat this idea
about possibly being able to use a signature with PayPal or something.
I don't know. Yes, that's what I would.
George, thank you very much. Yes, I'm going from memory.
He did bring up this is what they did.
I have not looked at it yet for reasons I may have mentioned earlier
what's going on with the water stuff right now.
So I really you know, I'm so excited that sitting down on the Internet
to even look at the chat for three minutes is a big takeaway from what I'm doing.
So, you know, so.
I will look at that, but I did see that.
In other words, I didn't look at the video that he put in.
So I would suggest that that's what Lawful Money Trust is doing.
You can go and, you know, reach out to those guys.
They're very confidential, let's say
they do have a saving to suitors for them.
OK, go look at the successes and all that around there.
And that would be I don't endorse them fully,
but that's the way to go on the 12 USC for 11.
There's a lot of people in jail, by the way.
And there's no one in jail for tax evasion ever.
If you look at the court document that was called the charging instrument,
you know that that has to when they when they put them in jail or prison,
they the prison has to get a charging instrument.
You know, in other words, a formal record of why they should be.
And you look at the charging instrument says false information,
a government official, not tax evasion.
Right. Martha Stewart's the same thing.
Everyone thinks, oh, is insider trading.
Well, no, she gave she did an interview and they said,
oh, you gave false information here.
The lollipop was blue, not green. So here you go.
So if you listen carefully to a lot of news stories,
you'll find that that's exactly what goes on.
It's lying to the FBI. It's lying to a federal agent.
It's just starting to tell you.
And by the way, what they do, these
all the all the any agency in the alphabet agency is not government, by the way.
They're all put in.
They're not government, as you're taught in civil civics
when they used to teach it.
What they are is they're franchises of the Federal Reserve
of the central banking system.
Right. Like the FBI was started by the Jewish mafia, by the way.
You know, before that, it was they had another group.
It was the oh, some they used to Pinkerton's.
Right. Right.
And the Pinkerton's were like they were they had
those armored, armored trucks and armored wagons. Right.
And the FBI came out when they when they were Pinkerton's were too corrupt.
They said, we need something else.
So the the American Jews in New York said, we got an answer for that.
We'll fund that.
And they structured it all.
And that's what the FBI is.
Anybody who was a veteran in the FBI knows what I'm telling you.
By the way, that's where I got it from.
What that went into is two things actually went into the Bureau of Investigation,
which was not yet the Federal Bureau of Investigation.
And then it also went into the Secret Service
because the Secret Service at that time was mainly charged with.
And if you notice, Pinkerton's did security in quotes. Right.
Right. They ended up saying that name exists in security somehow.
I think it still is.
You know, Pinkerton still exists, but it doesn't have the same,
you know, responsibility.
Yeah. Just like the. Yeah.
But so here's what's going on through the years.
It's like, why are they busting all the guineas, the Italians, the lops?
We got to bust the Jew here and there to make it seem OK.
So so what's going on with people of every every
decade or two?
They have to bust someone in the public eye for tax evasion to scare all the people
like the first one was Max Schliemann, who was a boxer
in the 50s. And then they did.
Who's the. Oh, Schmeling.
Schmeling, you mean, right?
Schmeling. Yeah, yeah. Schleiman or Schmeling.
Schmeling. Schmeling was Schleiman.
But OK, either way, Schmeling.
Schmeling was a heavyweight champion.
And that's right. And he got they made him fight again to pay the bill.
And he got beat up by a young guy.
So it goes on and on.
And then it was the woman, the real tacky woman that owned Park Avenue
South, Leona, Park Avenue, Leona.
Yeah. And then it was Willie Nelson.
And then the black guy. What's his name?
The actor, Wesley Snipes.
See, I know all these guys.
Yeah, there you go. Yeah.
So they so they put these famous people.
So I was like, oh, my gosh, I better.
Right. So that's how much power they have.
Why? Because you endorse it.
You endorse it. Everybody's endorsing it.
And, you know, you want to go along with it.
You know, and that's that's the whole thing.
You cannot change this because the majority of the people want it that way.
So what you do is you have your own reality within the reality
and your reality within the reality is how do you make your reality
better within this reality?
That's the DNA of Greek speak.
The DNA of Greek speak is figure out what's going on,
what's really going on, demand definitions.
Right. Right. Demand histories, what things really are.
So you can make a better decision.
I'm not telling you to do anything ever.
The DNA of Greek speak is definition.
Define, define, define.
And when you're done with that, define some more
and try to be objective as possible, because you really can't be objective
because your senses are always lying to you anyway. So.
You know, like recently, I was teaching someone how to do watch flicker rate.
You know, these LED lights, you know, they have flicker rate of 60 cycle per second.
If you look away from the light, have the light behind you
and try to look at your peripheral vision, you'll see the flicker.
But if you turn around, look at it straight ahead.
You don't see the flicker only from your peripheral vision.
Right. And I'm not talking about where they show a video of a brand new car.
And it looks like the headlights are blinking
because that's the flicker rate conflicting with the camera.
Yeah, that's because of the frame rate. Right.
That's the frame rate versus flicker rate of the pulsing of the P
pulse with modulation in the amplifier, the driver of the light.
So. Right.
So what happens when you look at the wheels of a car with your peripheral?
Yeah, I was just saying, same thing happens if you look at the wheels of a car
and you notice a lot of times they look like they're going backwards.
It's because the film rate is conflicting with the flicker rate of the light on it.
Is it really conflicting?
No, because it really looks like it's really going backwards.
You can you could swear that those wheels look like they're going backwards
and you wouldn't be wrong.
You wouldn't be right.
But you won't be wrong either, because anyone visually see,
that's exactly where the perception lies.
You see, we are only as good as our perception.
But if you get speed, though, you can actually see him roll forward
if you adjust the speed properly.
Sure, sure. But but it's the whole thing like they lie and you swear to it.
Right. Like 500 people cut a woman in half.
500 people in the audience watching a magician
cut a woman in half and put her back together.
If you don't know how that trick is done.
Five hundred people.
Can you sign right here that you swear that you saw a woman cut in half?
Yes, I will sign that. I will swear.
So basically they lie and you swear to their lies.
And it ain't going to change going back to that.
It ain't going to change.
Well, after all, you did see the guy pull a pigeon out of the lady's ear
who was sitting in the front row.
I mean, you saw it, didn't you?
By the way, do you know how the sawing in half trick works?
Well, I mean, there's a bunch of different ways that it can work,
but I know what that's like.
Well, the way the way to do it and pull it off.
It's difficult because you need to magicians when they always around a big city,
international city, because they need people with special skills. Right.
This is how it's done.
The box is never just big enough to hold one person.
It has to be big enough to hold two people. Right.
So what happens is where the woman standing before she gets in the box
is already another woman in the box who's all contorted is in the bottom half.
Yeah. And as the woman is getting in the box,
they have to time it just right that she's ready to slide her legs through the box.
It's the other woman that slides the legs through the box.
Yeah. But you got to make sure her legs go down away from the saw.
Yeah. You got to make sure they're wearing the same shoes.
Otherwise it looks crazy.
You know, you can't go in there like the hard part is the timing.
You make it look like the legs look the same.
Well, you got to make sure the shoes are the same.
You can't have a woman walk on stage.
That's right. That would be out the bottom.
That would suck. I mean, you know, just saying.
Good. Yeah, that would be worse than finding a passport
on the roof of a building from a burning airplane.
Right. Yeah. Something that melted a building, but couldn't get a passport.
It's really weird. Right.
So, you know, don't don't stick sneakers out when the woman walked on stage with pumps.
That's all I'm saying. Yeah.
And they do get let's say you do have a magician doing the ledger domain or press
the digitization.
But most people have heard of press the digitization.
But just about everyone ever brought up ledger domain has never heard of it.
Ledger domain, L.A.G.R. domain anyway, is a magic tricks.
Food, tomfoolery or whatever that.
So if you go to a place where banks are doing their business and you start saying,
you know, do a forensic audit where he's got money to give you, he's got no money.
He's monetizing your signature.
They get very nervous, just like a magician when he's ready to perform the act.
And you're sitting in the back yelling out.
He's already got another woman in the box.
You know, they have people that throw you out.
Right. There's a lot of money there. Right.
Yeah. Same thing.
So I've spoken to bankers about fractionalization.
One guy's brains. Yeah. Ten to one. We do ten to one.
Yeah. We do. We take your signature.
We get ten to one out of that. Yeah.
What? You got a problem with that? They don't.
They got everything they want that way.
So do we. So fuck off.
Right. Oh, my God.
You came in to get the hundred dollars.
You got your hundred dollars and we made a thousand out of it.
What do you care?
Yeah. Well, nine hundred. Yeah.
Well, actually, eight hundred because they turned it into nine hundred.
Gave you the hundred. Right.
They have the eight hundred left over.
They do have to pay taxes on that, by the way, unless they're a member
bank of the Federal Reserve.
Most banks are not member.
By the way, banks are not corporations and they're not their national associations.
That's why we look at Wells Fargo and a right national national associations
like the Sierra Club, the Boy Scouts, the Girl Scouts.
It's a vague Smithsonian Institute's National Association.
It's like these in between things. Right.
So anyway. Yeah.
Those are the two things I wanted to cover that were in the chat was
there's no ownership.
Just you just want to get them out of your hair.
Just show keep records that you've made demand for lawful money
every step of the way.
And the property tax, I kind of got into a little bit.
There's a guy that I would endorse is Steve property tax.
Steve, Steve of Florida.
I don't know if he maybe got rid of his stuff,
but basically his whole thing is you just stick with one thing.
People are not mentioned under tax laws.
It says persons.
It says corporations, trusts, organizations, this and that.
People are not in there. So you're out.
The other thing is property taxes, which says nonprofits don't do property tax.
Doesn't say 501 C three.
It can't. They can't use any.
They say, do you obey the codes of the IRS?
There's 60 million, 60,000 pages.
Which one don't you know has nothing to do with the IRS?
So again, where you live, if you don't have a profit
doing anything for profit where you live, and by the way,
you cannot profit in a credit based economy here.
I'll throw another thing at you.
One of the things that they omitted in Title 12
when I was looking at was it says that banks, member banks
and bank associations cannot lend credit and they cannot lend
credit credit that's on deposit or deposits of accounts.
So what are they lending you?
Right. They're not allowed to be lending at all.
It's really wild.
And this was one of this.
I think it was under 95 or 95 B.
And it says omitted.
So they're starting to move, you know, on this.
It's kind of like, you know,
it was quite well known in the engineering community before 9-11
that there were nukes underneath the U.N.
building, underneath the Dag Hammarskjld building,
underneath the World Trade Center.
The janitor knew it, right?
It was spoken.
It was it was even an article in The New York Times
where the janitor was interviewed.
Yeah, this nuclear
device under the building for an emergency, you know.
But after 9-11, oh, no, no, we got to omit all that.
Right. So, yeah, same thing with the banking.
I think what's happening is because it's going critical on what they're doing.
And by the way, when they do the subsidy thing, if you sign and get money,
you know, they produce not ten to one.
And now you're going to you know, I was telling people,
if you're going to sign that stimulus check that you're getting in the mail,
whatever is a thousand, three thousand, whatever,
you're going to pay for it ten times through inflation over the next few years.
And what I said is actually pretty accurate.
The average cost has gone up 80 percent on average on many things.
Right. 80 percent.
Right. Almost double. So, yeah.
Right. Just take a look at a used car.
You could have got one for a thousand dollars not too long ago.
Guess what? They're about five thousand now,
you know, for the same thing that you could have bought.
Basically, you know, comparably same amount of years old.
You know, it's like five to one, four to one.
It's still not as bad as the late 70s, by the way.
No, the inflation in the late 70s was worse.
But it's it's it's going in the in other words, the state to the state.
Yeah. Well, this thing is almost the same.
It's you know, right.
It's like if you get shot with four bullets or six bullets.
Yeah. You know, you still a lot of bullets to get hit with.
Right. No, exactly. Exactly. Yeah. So, yeah.
I don't know if there's anything else we can get into a bit.
I just want to maybe keep this kind of short and then finally
to put a cap on the financial thing that I talked about.
But basically anything
anything you do, you have to show that you made a demand.
So electronic stuff is out unless you could show it electronically.
So if you get this direct deposit. Right. Right.
Get rid of a demand to check. Right.
And if they say we don't do that, we do is if the direct deposit
into an account, we do is just close the account.
And then when they send the direct deposit, it's going to bounce back
and they're going to know.
And then you go to the office a week, I say, yeah, I didn't get anything.
Yeah, because it bounced back.
Well, you write me a check.
And when you get the check on the back of the check, you do the demand
for lawful money per 12 per 12 USC for 11.
At the end of the year, you make a copy of that for you,
deposit it or cash it and you keep all that.
And when you give an IRS paperwork, you just fill it out like you're supposed to.
But at the bottom, your total is zero.
And you say, why?
Because I redeemed it all for lawful money.
And they're like, OK, well, have you got any checks that you didn't sign that way?
We could tax those, you know.
So, you know, they're very they're very cordial about it.
But the problem is with the IRS or the police or whatever, they don't know anything.
So you're going to have to go to a higher, you know, higher up the ladder.
Yeah. So.