The sonic event 29, I think, one of them apparently disappeared off my website already, and I'm
not sure exactly why it did that.
But I think that's the one where I call the intelligence agencies panty sniffers.
That's all I said like 15 times in the past three minutes.
Yes, I think I'm and I watch them wrong.
Watch. It's 26.
No, no, you're about right.
Fifteen is about right.
As to how many times you've just repeated that to me when I keep saying different things about it.
Yeah, I said that's the one where I call.
Remember, these people have nothing.
Doctors, lawyers, intelligence agencies, politicians, the it's all of it is social rank.
They like to come over to you and say, I'm a doctor.
And, oh, yes, sir.
You know, or the FBI comes to your door and you start talking about is what do you mean government?
I am the government, you know, all this stuff.
These people have nothing, zero.
And the only thing they have is social rank.
Right. Actually, there is a code in the military disrespecting someone's rank.
Right. Well, it's very broad.
There must be an illusion of authority must be projected by a title.
That's something, whether it's military or it's the hierarchy, it's all this stuff, though,
because if you don't call a king or queen by their proper name, they might have your head beaten.
Right. I mean, same thing, you know, used to be that would take your head off.
But nowadays, you know, probably just somebody beats you up in a funny hat.
Right. I mean, isn't that about the way that works or they still do it?
What they do is they'll clone you and take your consciousness when you're sleeping and then take your head off over and over and over.
Wonderful. Yeah.
So, you know, they made a Black Mirror episode about that, this guy that kept executing his consciousness in this weird thing.
So you could go into this, you know, like one of those amusement parks and you could virtually like keep executing the guy and his consciousness coming.
Did you ever see that? No, no.
It's all. No, but it's all telling you the same.
You know, cosmically, it doesn't matter if you label it fact or fiction.
Well, Black Mirror did a lot of that stuff, by the way.
Black Mirror did a lot of weird stuff like that.
You'd be amazed at consciousness.
So in other words, are you saying Black Mirror put that out there?
Yeah, they did a bunch of stuff, weird things about the implants and your memory being messed with and you recording your memory and being able to play it back and having it held against you.
The social credit system trapping people's consciousness.
Like there's this one where this guy, his wife dies and he wants to retain his wife's consciousness.
So they put it in his head and then he carries her around for a while.
And then after a while, you can't stand it anymore.
Yeah, well, dude, I don't want I don't want any woman I've ever been with in my head.
Are you kidding me? But the thing is, he keeps her around for a little while and then he's worried his daughter will miss her.
So he sticks her in a teddy bear.
It's messed up.
If you ever want to entertain yourself with the darker end of like how this could torture human beings, that's Black Mirror.
And of course, the Black Mirror is the stupid rectangle, the black screen, right?
Because it reflects back at you.
And that's the point of it.
Well, they give you all these little toys.
Yeah, go ahead. Sorry.
No, no. The tablet, the screen, the stupid rectangle, regardless if it's a tube, you know, the cathode ray tube or flat, it does the same purpose.
And the people that got behind manifesting that in earnest, in other words, to really make it buildable, practically buildable were occultists.
And they if you ask them why they were developing these things, they said to get into other worlds, to bring other worlds here.
So and the weird thing is that that's actually changed over time because you had the different alpha waves that were being attacked by the television and the flicker rates.
Now there's no flicker rate because of the different replacement that comes in.
This creates a different wave in the mind, right?
Or a different sort of mindset is set now by the screen.
Nobody talks about it.
But you remember the flicker rate thing with TV and all that.
It's still it's still there.
If you ever see a car, a video of a car with the headlights on, the headlights are blinking or a video, a lot of videos that I was watching a video of electronics show and they had LED lights on.
I saw the flicker rate with the new camera.
So I don't know. It goes back and forth.
I think a progressive scanning, right?
Progressive scanning. Yes.
You know, that's a little different, though.
It creates a different sort of a subtle thing that your mind gets set to.
That's a weird reactive like I don't understand all of that, but I do understand that just like with the tones and music and things that they can be constructed in such a way to encourage certain things, right?
The different semitones and stuff.
I don't know if you remember all the lawsuits and everything over the heavy metal and the rock music and stuff.
And there were some people tried to bring in scientific evidence about the the semitones and like Ozzy Osbourne's music and things like that.
You remember that stuff?
Yeah. Well, yeah, that was the whole age.
Talk about the 90s.
Yeah, well, the 80s and 90s.
But yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
I think the music is really benign.
It's really that they get you more in the in the stuff that you use, like, you know, the logos on packages, I think are far more powerful because not everyone's going to buy.
I never heard a rock and roll musician selling seven billion albums.
Right. But, you know, you see the structure is nefarious.
But it's very, very subtle.
All right. Yeah.
Like the oddity of the X's and the different geometric signals that are sent through these.
What did you call them again?
That the different symbols.
I mean, they're they're geometric in nature.
Scalar antennas, I call scalar antennas.
That's it. And they definitely do receive and and they send and receive.
Right. It seems like it's a broadcast through changing kind of like when you put Spice on
something, it does.
It's just giving off what it has.
What I mean by scalar, it doesn't matter if it's out in the open or you put it away in a cupboard, whether you see it or not or know where it is.
It's still pumping. That's what scalar is.
That's why these new age people talk about scalar waves that there's no scalar.
It doesn't make waves. Scalar is the part that doesn't have a waveform.
Right. So anyway, why does that work, though, when you block it out with a marker than in that case?
Because otherwise, I mean, if I put it behind a wall, I can't see it, but it's still broadcasting.
Right. There's a that's where the research comes in.
There's a depth. If you look at that photograph or of the logo, the printing, it looks 2D flat.
But if you put it under a microscope, the ink looks like little mountain, mountain ranges on the paper.
Right. So, you know, it's 3D, you know, if you look at a bright, shiny ball bearing chrome metal under a microscope, it looks like the Grand Canyon.
Right. Well, it's not that smooth.
Yeah. Actually, depending on the scale, again, because even with photographs, right, because I used to study black and white photographs a lot.
You know why? It was really interesting to me that, you know, in the digital age, you don't have these gradients where, you know, there's the different levels of, you know, of the print in there.
And there's a lot of information, actually, in black and white photograph.
Like why people are so struck by them is because they're very they're very third dimension.
Basically, you have a third dimension in a black and white photograph.
It's very subtle. It's that's where just to get back to how it's scalar and what it does, if you don't see it and block it out, it's it's both 2D and 3D.
And then it also goes in the 1D, which is the spiritual realm, let's say 1D, 2D, 3D is just measurement systems.
Right. But which is say on on the subtlety of perceive of a perception.
It's the intent.
And the panty snippers, the panty snippers don't know this stuff.
They're just using it, though.
Right. Yeah.
Yeah. No, they're just killer.
Oh, by the way, the reason why you there are so many, quote unquote, government employees.
Yes.
You don't rebel against someone or an organization that you rely to get your pay for, let's say, a roof over your head and feed your children.
It's no one ever rebels against anyone that gets a paycheck from.
Well, nobody's going to set fire to the food stamp office is what you're telling me.
Yeah, that's right. That's why I mean, when you look at the rebellion, when let's say the French Revolution, she said, let them eat their children.
They changed it to let them eat cake because I was too much of an expose.
The reason that people rebelled is because the king was taking and the people couldn't take.
Right. But excuse me.
The irony of it is there is no money.
All substances and things that are being produced and created are done by credit to people's ignorance on how it works.
You know how you open a bank. It's real easy.
The Federal Reserve tells you it takes a couple of years.
But if you have contacts, you get a number, which is a privileged number to the Fed window.
You get a little office space.
You put a sign outside and a desk and a computer and you put out that you give loans.
So people walk in, you put them through a little rigmarole like it, you know, and the moment they sign the promissory note, you go to the terminal, you put a transaction number, which goes to the Federal Reserve, whatever.
And it shows the amount that they signed for.
And then you switch that amount to an account to get access or write them a check.
You have no money. There's no it works.
You see. So this is how the system works and the people don't care and they want it.
Well, there you go. So it sounds like you cut off there for a second.
I don't know what happened. Oh, look at that.
OK, so a little loss in Internet there on your end.
So go ahead.
By the way, the last thing people would have heard there is you said the people want it and then boom, you were gone.
Well, then the screen went black and says no Internet connection and just checked up on it.
So I'm on the stupid rectangle, which has data.
Nice. Yeah.
So we're on. That's how the people want it.
Wicked and whatever.
But, yeah, the the logos, I think, is on the packaging and the scalar aspect intent.
It goes very deep and it goes all around.
It's good to keep it light.
And I've always said, look, if you're on Earth, you somehow cosmically you stepped in shit.
It's the same thing. Right.
So, you know, when you go to a place and you stepped in shit, you know, and everybody else knows it.
So go clean that off. Right.
Oh, yeah. So if you've said you've come to Earth, they're like, did you clean up?
You know, what do you mean you're on Earth?
That's pretty screwy.
So, yeah.
By the way, even if you let's go back to scripture, there is nothing, absolutely nothing, zero.
The Christ said there was any anything positive about being here.
Not a one thing.
Ever. It's in scripture.
So but that's OK.
You don't have that much time anyway.
70, 80, 90, 100 years, whatever.
That's like minimal.
In terms of even you forget about years, you want to look at it in terms of heartbeats, you know.
So. Right.
Let's let's go back to it.
I want what I want to get into some light stuff.
I like to give a lot of practical stuff just to bounce around.
I want to get into the emo.
Two things I haven't gotten into.
Well, I have gotten into the practical stuff.
Yes. Like, for example, if someone asked me in a household way, most practical thing is all of your
soaps, not not laundry detergents, but dilute them and put them in a sprayed bottle.
All right. Like you're cleaning soaps and also have some hydrogen peroxide in a spray bottle, which is easy.
They already come in a dark hydrogen peroxide should be kept out of the light, by the way.
It's funny how that that is a requirement.
Hydrogen peroxide, but they don't transfer over to regular water.
Right. It will lose its efficacy.
It's acidic. But, you know, using hydrogen peroxide as a strong cleaner, it's an oxidizer.
You know, if you have pets and you clean up after a pet on the floor, wipe it with hydrogen peroxide.
Give you a quick story about cleaners.
And, you know, I mentioned supermarkets early earlier.
I went to an Albertsons, which is a regular supermarket.
I went to the back to the hot counter.
I didn't feel like cooking. Got some fried chicken.
I didn't need it. I fed it to the cats.
Wasn't up to par because I can taste the feed.
If the meat is not good, it doesn't matter if it's beef or lamb or usually a lamb is pretty good.
But beef or chicken, I can smell what they were feeding the animal.
If they were giving them vegetarian feed or animal, you know, science say, oh, our animals need more protein.
So they buy protein, which is derived from animals to give to animals that shouldn't be eating that.
Right. Right. So I brought the fried chicken home.
And I said, this really smells like the feed they were feeding the chicken, you know.
And here's an example.
If you've ever had grass fed beef, it tastes like grass fed beef where corn fed beef tastes like corn fed beef.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
So let me ask you something about chicken, actually.
Really quick is that I've noted in the past, say, three, four years especially, that a lot of times I'll cook chicken and now parts of the chicken turn black.
This is blood. That's blood.
Yeah, but this is hasn't been drained.
Well, but but I haven't.
I didn't used to see that a lot.
You know, yeah. Most of my life has been drained.
Well, OK. I was just curious.
In other words, you're cutting short.
Yeah. Well, here's the thing.
You live in a this is a capitalist world now.
One of the rules about capitalism is if you're done using something or you can't use it, you ruin it.
So no one else can.
Right. So that's a rule of capitalism.
So that's why if you look at the US, every time they go into a country, they ruin it.
Right. Except for Japan, because they didn't win the war.
They lost the war in Japan.
Right. But the winner writes the history.
So the Japanese said, no, no, you're going to say you won because two reasons.
One, if you say you lost all the money we have in Swiss bank accounts and dollars will be will be devalued to zero because that's international law, by the way.
Right. When a country loses a war, they their currency is devalued.
And so we're going to lose the wealth that we've got.
The other thing is we want to boost ourselves industrially.
We're going to take over your industry, which they did.
So cars, electronics industry, World Trade Center, all the steel was not good enough from the US.
It had to come from Japan.
Right. All of it.
All the main skyscrapers, the steel comes from Japan.
You can look this up. So where was I back to the chicken, the chicken?
Yes. So they have these deli cases now where you pick up the front glass to clean the inside and the backside.
So this little snotball manager, you could tell he was like a 25 year old guy.
You know, they get like a hundred grand manager in a supermarket, right?
Because the supermarket does a million dollars a day on a weekend.
Right. It's a little slimy, you know, white boy, whatever.
And I say white boy, it's not racial.
It's just like if you got to know him, everything that comes out of his mouth and you learned on television or college, not much in college.
College was about drinking, getting laid.
So, I mean, one of these people that are just like, well, think about the Spanish word for for white, you know, blanco.
And that's about how it translates, you know, basically just exuded that, you know, like you just want to punch him and you don't know why.
Right. But anyway, and he had his Polo Oxford shirt on or whatever.
And he's given the guys in the back behind the deli counter who were really busy, a hard time about the deli case glass being dirty.
So he goes and grabs a thing, a Windex glass cleaner, the blue stuff.
And he lifts up the glass and he's ready to spray.
And I'm 20 feet over to the right.
And I look over, I said, don't spray that.
Don't spray that.
Spray it on the paper first.
And he heard me. He stopped, but he never looked over to me.
He always just looked forward and down like he didn't acknowledge me.
But then he stopped pulling the trigger and he did spray it on the paper and said, you should be using distilled water or hydrogen peroxide for that.
Not on the food. And he's looking forward and he's starting to turn pink and red.
Right. And, you know, and that's that's how I do it.
That's how people look. Most people would think that know what I'm telling you would think that.
But I always say, if you want to know what I'm thinking, listen to what I'm saying.
I have no inner monologue.
I project everything that I'm thinking through my mouth.
Right. Because the stuff that I use internally has no voice.
It's totally silent. It's based on feeling.
Right. But not the feeling that most people think.
So anyway, I didn't get kicked out of the store and that little white boy should have got a little white boy.
He was like six foot five, 200 pound, muscular, clear, strong jaw line, very clean cut.
You know what I mean?
Right. Whatever is not this, you know, whatever.
So I sense these I sense people like, for example, I give the thing you got a junkyard dog or a dog that's supposed to protect the industrial building behind a fence.
Two people approach the fence.
Both don't say anything or gesture anything.
One of those two people are afraid of dogs.
The other one is a dog lover.
Who do you think immediately the dog is going to start barking at?
The guy who is afraid of dogs.
Do you see how this this correlates?
Right. So most people would look at the manager doing that.
Really. First of all, most people wouldn't even realize he's about to toxify the entire deli case.
And he's really stupid.
Most people wouldn't even think that.
And the small percentage that would see that wouldn't say anything.
Right. Well, is it really that bad, the Windex?
Because Windex is only like a little bit of blue coloring, really, and a touch of ammonia and water, supposedly.
I mean, that's the total contents of it.
That's the chemical.
But the energy is different.
Remember, it's an energy thing.
So I want to get into the practicality.
Outdoor lights.
I think I posted this in the chat.
I got back patio, front patio.
You got a nightlight, right?
It could be a globe fixture.
Usually it's a sconce mounted on the wall.
I have track lights mounted under the deck, but you don't see them unless you're really under them.
Bugs.
Summertime.
Little moths.
Little can't see them.
All kinds of stuff likes to gravitate towards the light.
And they fly around the light, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Right. Okay.
And then they stick on the light.
Right. They get dirty.
Makes the lights dirty.
Or they come inside when you open the door.
Or they fly around you.
It's a, you know, right.
Bugs. Moth goes to the flame.
Right. The bugs go to the light.
I'm like, you know, I've been wanting to do this for a long time.
And I have.
I said, I got to do this here.
This is the Taoist perspective.
Now, how would people treat that?
Oh, we got to get a bug zapper.
Oh, we got to get this.
Oh, turn on.
Or blah, blah, blah.
They make a special bulb, right?
Whatever.
Okay. Well, the Taoist perspective is the bug is really small and hard.
It makes him young.
He's a young creature, relatively.
Right.
And he also goes upward very easily compared to other animals, which makes him young.
Upward is young.
Downward is yin.
So from almost every measure, the bug is classified as a young creature.
From every measure, the light that's coming out of this, whether it's an LED bulb or mercury
or incandescent fluorescent, is very yin.
Starts off from one spot and it spreads out, right?
Not only is the light by nature yin, but it's actually flickering, which makes it even more yin.
And all these other yin qualities.
It gets warm, which is the yang quality.
But generally, the light is yin.
So you have very young going to very yin.
Oh, of course, right?
Yin and yang.
That's because they're opposites.
When I say yin and yang, a lot of people say, oh, opposites attract.
No, opposites do not attract.
This is not opposites.
It's easy to categorize them as such.
So what I need to do is to make, if that light were yangified, they would want to not go to it.
So let's pick blue.
Let's just put a little bit of blue within the vicinity of the light,
like an eighth-inch paintbrush, eighth-inch stripe of blue around the base of the bulb.
Or a piece of blue tape, if you have one of those globes, take the globe off,
put a rim of blue either on top of the globe, just a little bit, and some behind the bulb.
Put it all back together.
You say, oh, honey, do the lights look blue to me?
Blue to you?
She's like, no, they look just like they did before.
Okay, guess what?
No bugs.
Bugs stay away from the light.
Right?
That's interesting.
Where'd you read that?
No, it's all yin and yang.
You see the Taoist perspective, right?
So if you start going up in Taoism, it attaches itself to man know thyself, right?
And how can you know yourself if you know nothing about your environment?
Or how about if you know a lot about your environment, how can you not know about yourself?
You see the Taoist perspective?
Right, because you're just something within that environment anyway, so you should.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, you're a part of that environment.
Like, you don't believe it?
Suck the air out of the environment.
How do you feel?
There you go.
Right, so again, back to feeling.
So I just wanted to give that as practicality.
And I just mentioned earlier, I never gave any driving tips, you know?
I don't like the word driving.
Driving is a commercial term, but let's just say.
I understand, right.
Okay, and you know, I used to give a joke.
Stevie Wonder, give them, Stevie, why don't you take the wheel, you know?
And this is not a bad joke.
Chuck, why don't you take the wheel while I'm talking about this, right?
Kind of thing.
So driving really depends on your sight, you know?
Absolutely.
You know what, though?
I give credit to Eddie Murphy on that one.
That's where I first heard it, you know?
Yeah, that's right.
That was Eddie Murphy.
Yeah, so it is a visual thing.
But you also have to be very careful.
Some of the things that I'm going to say, you have to be very keen on that.
Keen on what you perceive with your sight.
Two things I want to talk about.
Driving.
I used to give driving lessons over Skype.
It was about an hour long, and everyone on there came back and said,
I'm a better driver because of that.
It's like, what the hell, honey?
Because, you know, driving, you got to be, you know, you got to see pictures.
You got to be behind the wheel while you're learning all that bullshit.
It's all between the ears, right?
And you start with the ears to go in between the ears.
So for those of you that do operate an engine-driven wagon and not an automobile,
if it was an automobile, we would never think about gas prices
because you wouldn't need gas because it's automobile, right?
So anyway, all right, two things on the driving.
One is parking, the damn thing.
And the other one is when you're going on curvy roads, right?
That's, those are two things where most people get the most hiccups
and the most comments if they have, quote unquote, passengers, right?
Passengers is a commercial term, by the way.
I never had passengers because no one ever paid me to drive them around.
And I was never driving.
And if that ever happened, it would be a private contract.
So it's out of the commercial thing.
You see, this is one way to think about it.
But if you keep that, the intent in there, it's better than falling into the collective language.
So those are two key things that are problems.
Look, I don't have a lot of experience driving.
Parking and curvy roads are where you're going to get the most comments, yeah.
Okay, okay.
Right? You with me on that?
Sure, I got you. All right.
Okay, so most parking, you have parallel parking.
And we're not going to get into that because most parking that you see in most parts of the country
is where you just drive, you go down a parking lane and you make a left or a right into a spot.
Right?
And then you pull out.
And we're talking about driving here, nothing else.
Right, guys?
Pulling out.
Anyway.
Yeah, I got you.
So when we do that, very often, that's like a one, it should be, okay, let's do the parking.
So you go into one of these supermarket places like I was yesterday and you got a big parking lot
and you have an arrow painted, you know, this way down this lane and the parking spots are slightly
angled towards the direction that you're going down, right, to just go right in.
And sometimes if you go where the arrow is pointing against you, you're like, oh, it's really,
I can't get in here because all the angle is against my steering, right?
Okay, so you got to go down the lane where, how it's marked.
So let's say you see a spot on the right and spot on the left, pick a side.
Okay, so you pick the left.
So what you do is you spot up ahead, let's see, a few car links or a few spots.
You're going to turn a left into this spot, right?
Okay.
And you're going to turn in there.
It should be a one-shot maneuver and it usually is, but sometimes it's not.
People are not centered or whatever.
They have to pull back and center too close to one side or whatever.
So what you do is you start approaching, you're going to go into the left spot.
You try to right yourself as much as possible to increase your radius.
So when you go in there, your radius is larger, so you're not going on a sharp angle.
And as you're going into the spot, as you start getting, let's say, the front quarter part of the
car within the spot, start aiming towards the right, which would be the left driver's side
wheel of the car parked to the right.
Oh, my gosh.
Was that confusing?
So instead of going into the spot.
I didn't quite follow that.
Yeah, go ahead.
Okay, so as you're making a left into that spot, most people look at the center of the
spot that they're going into and they're going to end up too close to the left side.
Okay.
Too close to, in other words, they try to open the door to get out on the left-hand driver.
Not going to have enough space between them and the car next to them.
Right.
Okay.
Or you're going to have too much of an angle.
So the best thing to do here is you aim at the car at the right, the car that's on the right
side, your passenger's side.
Remember, I'm presuming everyone here is left-hand drive.
Right.
You're aiming at the front of the other car, like the front driver's side wheel, as if you're
going to almost on an angle hit that car, right?
Okay.
But don't hit it.
And just at the last moment, if you know the distance of your car, when you're less than a
foot away or about a foot away, abruptly steer towards the left.
And what'll happen there is you will see yourself perfectly centered and balanced in the center
of that spot in one maneuver.
And the joy of this is when you have these really tight spots.
Like California, like in Arizona, everything's 10 feet, the distances between the white lines
and lanes.
Okay.
And in California, everything's just a little bit over eight.
By the way, if you want to give the perception that someone is going faster, you make the
lanes narrower, right?
So that's how you get people to slow down.
You make the lanes narrower, but that's another discussion on highway and road design.
Because perceptually, it feels like you're going faster.
So basically, if you're going to make a right-hand turn into a spot, as you're turning the arc,
as you start getting into the zone where the spot is, aim towards the left-hand side, the
passenger side of the car on the left wheel, as if you're going to hit the car.
Right?
Don't cut the wheel so much to the right.
And then right the wheel at the last second, and you'll see the car is totally straight.
It kind of doesn't make sense.
Because you think that once you're getting into the spot within the radius that you started,
you're going to just smoothly get in there.
But you know, you end up continuing that radius, and you're usually cockeyed.
But as you start getting into the spot, and you aim opposite in the direction that you
want to go, the car will straighten itself out.
It's a form of counter-steering at speed.
But this is counter-steering at low parking position.
And the last second, turn the wheel to the right, and the car rights itself and ends
up straight every time.
I do this at speed.
Very often, I have people in a car, and it's, let's get that parking spot right there.
And I barely slow down.
I mean, I don't go in like a saturated turn or something.
But I go in really fast compared to, and I do that technique.
And they're like, oh, you know, I thought you were going to hit the other car.
I was like, no, no, watch.
This is a technique that I always use.
And they get out, and they're like, it's perfect.
It's the same, just, you know, every time.
So there's the idea.
This is the employment, the slow counter.
Do you know what counter-steering is?
Have you heard that?
I've heard it.
I'm not quite certain what that means exactly.
Okay, it's the principle of counter-steering, which is very much applied to anyone that's
in performance driving, two-wheel, four-wheel, whatever.
It doesn't work that well when you have a trailer.
Actually, it's the opposite with a trailer.
But counter-steering is when you're going to turn to the right, it creates a, the car
wants to go to the left because it sees turning to the right as a braking action, just like
a rowboat, right?
So what you do is before you turn to the right, you quickly turn the steering mechanism to
the left, and you snap it back to the right.
And it fools the car to lean towards the right, where the direction you want to go.
That's what I see people do.
And again, I don't steer much, but the idea that they kind of lean left a little bit before
they turn right, or the other way, I just thought it was just give yourself a little
more clearance, a little more of a radius.
It's to relieve that braking force that happens in the direction that you're turning.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Right?
So you can get, if you're going to turn to the left, the car wants to go to the right
because it sees going to the left as a braking mechanism, friction, it wants to go where
there's less friction.
So you quickly snap it to the right.
So the car now relieves that, right?
So that's called counter-steering.
So this is like a parking counter-steering method.
And it's funny when I do this with people I don't know me, and they're into driving,
they're like, oh, you're a really good driver.
You came with, I mean, it's like, how the hell did you get into this spot so perfectly?
It's easier when it's a very tight spot.
Okay, right.
So counter-steering perspective.
If you're interested, maybe the first time I brought up how to do it in parking was the
best, and it didn't sound the best, but it is.
So you could go back to that.
Okay.
We didn't time-mark it.
But the next thing I want to get into is a curvy road.
You go uphill or across, you know, where you can't see around the bend, and here comes
another bend, and everyone's going, oh, to the left.
You're swinging to the right.
And the cars, you feel the car rocking back and forth, left and right, as you're going
around these short bends, right?
At speed.
Well, especially, it gets really more nervous when it's downhill, right?
Uphill, this holds true uphill as well, but you have, you know, a negative force keeping
you, like, an inertia holding you back.
Climbing is not that much.
But when you're descending on a curvy road or flat at speed, a curvy road, you kind of
feel the car, you know, oh, to the left, oh, to the right, you know.
So when you're turning to the left, the car wants to go to the right.
And everybody's rocking back and forth.
Everybody starts looking up, paying attention, and wants something to hold on to, right?
Well, I see that when, during that, or I see it during when, you know, when people come
off exit ramps, and it's kind of a corkscrew, where you're coming down, you're descending,
and you go in one direction for a while, but it really, you know, turns you around.
Sure.
This works well also on a long cloverleaf type exit like that, yeah, like one of those
almost 360 or 270 turns.
Right.
Okay.
So what you do here, this combines EMO.
This shows you how you are variable X.
In other words, the driver, you don't have to see the drivers, any road feel, you become
part of the machine and all that.
This is where the machine becomes part of you.
This has to do with stabilizing the car.
And the way you do that is also by having a proper seating position.
A proper seating position is have the backrest as upright as possible, right?
Believe it or not, if you look at race cars, they don't, the backrests don't lean back
at all.
It's like straight up and down, right?
Yeah, that is a weird phenomenon I've noticed in the past few years too, is that there are
people that I swear to God, it's like they want to lay back in the car.
Well, yeah, that started with the gangster stuff in the 70s, you know, with the Conair
hairbrushes and the Cadillac Eldorado and all that, right?
I mean, really ridiculous.
Yeah.
I don't understand that at all.
So the way you sit down is basically you want a slight bend in the legs for the pedals on
the floor and you want a slight bend in the elbow to the steering wheel.
Now, if you're taller than 5'6", it's kind of hard to do that unless you're in a big
car.
In other words, you're going to find you're moving the seat back.
It's really easy for a small person, believe it or not, even though the cars look big or
whatever, they're really designed for people between 5'6 and 5'8".
Once you're above 5'8", it's really hard to get into this position, you know, the seat
all the way back, depending on the car again.
I got into a Volkswagen once, I think a Passat, where I set it up and I was like, whoa, you
could be seven foot tall and fit and set it up right, you know?
So there's some exceptions, but you want a slight bend in your elbow.
So when you're sitting in the position, the back is as upright as possible, being comfortable.
Now, for some people, an upright back feels like you're leaning forward, like you're going
to get dumped forward, right?
So don't do that. Maybe five, ten degrees back is fine.
Also, headrests are useless.
You're trying to lean your head back on a headrest.
You're staring at the ceiling of the car, you know, the headliner, you know.
But anyway, and you want a slight bend in your elbow.
In other words, your arms, lock out your arms and then put about a five or ten degree bend,
which would be two or three inches in.
And your legs should be mostly extended with a slight bend.
Not, you know, you shouldn't lock your knees out if you're touching the pedals, the brake
pedal all the way down or accelerator all the way down.
Should have a slight bend.
Don't be bunched up.
OK, so once you have that position and you reset yourself, or if you already have it
good on you, what you're doing is when you start getting into the curved road situation,
whether it's flat or uphill at speed, what I want you to do is slightly pull on the
steering wheel with both hands evenly towards you as if you want to pull the steering
wheel out of the rack, out of the off of its axle where it's attached from the car,
right? Just pull on it.
The reason I'm saying this, because most people will either grip the steering wheel or
rest their hands on it or be conscious of the force moving up and down, you know, to
turn the wheel. What I'd like for you to do is be conscious of pulling on the steering
wheel slightly, right, as if you want to pull it off of the slot or the bearing that it's
mounted it off of its mount.
Well, this occurs to me, does the pitch, you know, because a lot of steering wheels are
adjustable, does the pitch of the wheel matter?
OK, it is parallel to your chest as possible.
But if you do that, sometimes it feels like it's pointing towards your navel.
OK, so whatever is comfortable, but it should be vertical as possible.
OK. All right. Well, 12, I found 12 to 15 degrees up, you know, is good, you know, so.
But the tilt with the upper part slightly away at 12 degrees.
Yeah. You want to make it look if you really want to see race cars are high performance.
You always want to be high performance when you're in a car, right?
Unless you're, you know, driving around in a boat or, you know, a lot of people like these
cars you mentioned sit back. That's how boats are set up.
Right. Yeah. Very relaxed.
You know, look at a speedboat.
Everything's upright. Right.
Race cars. Everything is upright.
So what I'm saying here is when you put a slight tug on the steering wheel, not much.
We're talking about a light force while you're turning left and right and negotiating the
bends, you're going to notice, hey, the car isn't swaying anymore.
It's really stable and actually have better traction.
Now, wait a second. What the hell does slightly pulling on the steering wheel in a good
seating posture have to do with the wheels increasing traction and the suspension
tightening up? How is that physically possible?
It's not physically.
If you start thinking about how someone say, well, you're stabilizing the wheel.
No, what happens is the car feels like a completely different car.
It feels like you just went and upgraded your suspension to the best Kony suspension
available. But all you've done is change your orientation, which gives you a better feel
for what's going on. Right.
Right. It feels like you have a new car and it feels like you just got put on, you know,
Michelin tires or something that grip the road really well.
That's the thing, by the way, Michelin, I'm not endorsed by them, but I do endorse them
for this. When you get Michelin tires for whatever, not the truck LTX, but if you have a
car, I've tried this with several cars.
There's no difference if it's wet out or dry.
I've in the middle of a thunderstorm going on a curvy road.
Now, like, let me just try to, like, you know, grab the brakes and see if the car
slides up. And it behaved just like as if it was dry.
It's the only car tires I've ever seen do that.
So like the commercial says, a lot's riding on your tires.
Even the wife who got a car and had new tires, brand new tires, you know, with the
little things that stick out right from the casting.
Oh, yeah. The next day I said we got to get Michelin's and she's she's the kind of
person that needs to test drive cars.
So, you know, test drive, just roll it 10 feet in the parking lot.
I could tell you everything the car is doing there, except for, you know, shifting into
the high gear. So anyway, she gets the new tires to get in.
She's in the bay. They let her get in and pull the car out.
She looks at me as I could feel the difference.
And I just pulled out 10 feet.
Right. That's how radical Michelin's are.
So anyway, if I approach Michelin for a spot endorsement, they wouldn't they would see
what I'm talking about and wouldn't want anything to do with me anyway.
But I'm thinking that there is that there is definitely some engineering that goes into
exactly how they cut the grooves in the tire.
Well, it's it's the casing, believe it or not.
What makes the tire is the casing, the stuff the rubber is cast on.
It's I from dealing with high end bikes like a few for bicycles, a decent tire is 50 to
75 bucks.
And if you get something like a Continental Olympic, it's 300 bucks for a bicycle tire.
The difference is the casing TPI threads per inch, how it's woven and what type of weave.
And then, of course, the rubber, because that's the contact patch.
Right. But mainly it's the casing that gives you the feel.
Because think about if you take the casing away from the tire, just a balloon.
I mean, like a party balloon, a really thick party balloon doesn't you can't ride on that.
It's really all about the casing and you can't ride on the casing because it has no
traction. Well, right.
I remember in the early 80s, the guys that started using the red tires and the BMX,
because for some reason they were making them red and the compound.
No carbon is gripped better against metal surfaces.
That's what it was. Yeah.
So. All right.
So pulling slightly on the steering wheel, but you notice I stress the body position
first, because if you've got the wheel pointing this way and your seat's going that
away and this is going like did that, this is going like did that.
You're not going to get the right force.
You have to be in a position that yields or leans
towards what is considered performance, quote unquote, posture.
Right. And this is all about you feeling things as you're steering.
So I don't know what it's about.
It's actually, you know, it is nothing.
All you're feeling is your intent is to negotiate the road as you normally would, you
know, around the bends.
All you're really feeling and focusing on is a slight pull on the steering wheel,
slightly pulling on the steering wheel just slightly.
I have so many. Actually, if I've told this to a thousand people, a thousand people
came back to me. They made sure they wanted to get in contact me to thank them for
this little thing just for this.
I can't believe how it works. Even people that are into cars, people that build race
engines and all this stuff like, dude, I kind of did it.
I think I did it intuitively, but I never thought of doing it.
And it's like it's just there.
These are people who build race engines.
They know about all the mechanics and what different suspensions.
It was like putting in a new suspension.
It was right. It's like it's like putting in high end tires.
Right. So this I was I wanted to talk about the Emo
tonight, but I wanted to give these two practical examples.
And we did a little bit before on how certain things
that right away when you discuss like this little trick or this practical thing
must have a mechanical counterpart to explain it.
And I'm telling you, it doesn't.
How the hell can slightly pulling on the steering wheel in a good
posture stop the car from rocking?
You're going down the same road at the same speed.
Well, the only practical explanation I have for that is that you as the driver
are part of the situation and what you're doing by doing that is adjusting yourself.
Right. But how does that affect the suspension and the tire traction?
Doesn't make any sense, but it doesn't actually affect it.
It just affects your ability to utilize it, maybe.
Yeah, but it actually is a measurable effect.
In other words, if you it would be like someone having a mediocre stock car
and then hopping it up with a twenty thousand dollar suspension with the best
Michelin tires, drive it the same way.
Oh, yeah. Drive totally different.
This does almost the same thing by just slightly pulling on the steering wheel.
Well, you know, much like gripping a baseball bat when you swing it, different
grips will create different results.
Okay. The bat didn't change.
The ball didn't change.
But you did. And the bat didn't change.
Right. But you did. But how does it.
But the bat is very direct.
Yeah. Here it's you're sitting in a car and a steering wheel, which has a shaft that
goes to a rack and pinion or electric whatever moves the steering wheel, which
goes to the body struts on the wheels, which has a suspension system.
Then you have independent traction ratios.
And you know how much friction the tire rolling resistance.
How does all that change by slightly pulling on the steering wheel again?
I'm thinking that the adjustment of you because you are.
But there's no physical explanation.
And I've had people look at this for many years.
I've been saying this for decades.
But you don't think I mean, again, I'm not trying to argue.
I'm just trying to say it just seems to me as though.
And again, not with a lot of experience.
If you change you in that equation, then you react a little bit different.
Sure. And therefore slight movements.
Yeah. But don't look for a mechanical explanation because the change in the
mechanics is so radical.
In other words, that only one would expect such a radical change by actually
replacing or upgrading the mechanical parts.
That's amazing how that works.
Right. It's kind of like, you know, you got an old Ford Pinto, you know, zero zero
60 and 35 seconds, you know, you can't even get out of its own way.
You know, sure. And you think you think about something and then you go race a
Ferrari and keep up with it.
Right. Same car, same car, same car.
Nothing changed now that you can do that.
Now, mechanically, someone would say, well, you could race Ferrari and a Pinto will
pull the engine out, put another engine in.
We have to do the suspension.
We put some nitro burner in there, a couple of turbos, maybe a supercharger also.
No, no, no. I'm talking about exactly the same stuff.
And you have such a radical.
Now, I'm not saying that could be done, but I'm saying.
From the hand, Lisa, when high performance cars, the three things that matter, most
people that don't know about high performance cars, I think, how fast can it go?
No, that means you don't know high performance cars.
The first thing that high performance cars think about, yes, how fast can it go?
That is such a minimal side note that's only considered for one point five
seconds. Where the hours of thought goes into is how does the suspension react and
how well does the brakes react?
And that's where the hours, days and weeks go into.
Right. You could put a rocket, you can go down to the Air Force base if you have a
cousin that works at the Air Force base and get some surplus C-130 hydrogen peroxide
rockets, 30, 33 percent ones.
They look like three inch tubes, five feet long.
Strap it underneath the car, fire it off and you'll go from zero to one hundred and
two seconds. Right.
So that doesn't mean anything.
Right. I mean, how do you stop?
Right. How do you go around the turn?
Yeah, that's why the that's why I say the best value for a car dollar for dollar money
is a Bugatti Veyron, which is two and a half million dollars.
I said value, not price.
Why? Because it's the only car that could go from zero to 60 back to zero in less than
five seconds. People, people don't hear what I just said.
They'll say zero to sixty and five.
So that's kind of fast.
But no, no, it actually goes zero to 60 in less than two seconds.
It goes from zero to 60 back to zero in less than five seconds.
Think about it. Can't do it, right?
Imagine. No. So I've never seen a car personally do that.
No. There's a couple of YouTube's on that.
You put in zero to 60 back to zero in five seconds.
There's a bunch of people that did the testing of the machine and it does it safely.
And you feel like when it does it, you could have, you know, basically a Starbucks with a
lid next to you and it wouldn't spill.
Right. Now, I didn't say no lid.
That would be stupid. Right.
Not much will come out of that little sippy hole.
That's what they call it, a sippy hole.
I have some children. Yeah.
Okay. So what I wanted to bring up tonight again, essentially, is just pulling on the
steering wheel on a curvy situation.
Not much. Not when I said pull it as if you want to pull the steering wheel out of the
shaft, off the shaft.
Not that hard, but in that direction, in line with the shaft, the pole, both hands even
as you're turning. And what I assure you, and I have had people that are car people
look into this and they come back, say it doesn't make any sense because the amount of
change that happens, mechanical difference only happens when you start replacing
components. Right.
It's amazing. So I just want to bring that up for those of you that are interested.
And for those who are not interested, we just burned up about 20 minutes on some Greek
speak. Right.
So emo. What do you think we should go on the emo?
That's that is so wide open.
The reason why I've been getting I say this often, if I hear two or three people, I
don't know of each other, almost ask or say or comment on the same thing.
I've said this for many years.
I bring it up because to me it's like a synchronous coincidence kind of thing.
Right. So so I've had several people with rated Y and outside bring up the emo
recently. And I said, I'll talk about it.
So what do you think we should go with it?
Chuck. Well, obviously, something that is practical, what what is a problem that could
be addressed with this? What is a circumstance that people would like to affect
most commonly that they could use to affect?
You know, that they would want to affect with it.
How about that? What do you think?
Well, that's the way I would ponder that and say what I ponder is this.
If you are focusing on food, clothing, shelter.
Remember, we got into the other things as well, which is water, energy and silver.
And you are, let's say, a happy camper to a degree.
The next thing would be affect others around you, because it's really the others
around you that control your happiness to a degree.
Right. Well, they're going to.
Yes, they can.
Right. They can. They can control your happiness.
So well, can you just generally have an effect on anywhere you go?
Is there a default that you can have that is?
Yes. OK, so why don't we describe that?
Well, you know, the description where two people approach a dog, one is definitely
afraid of dogs. The other one loves dogs.
Which one is the dog want to bite?
Well, the one that's afraid, of course.
Yeah. And well, how does the dog figure that out?
It's emo, right? The animals have this perception that they're stationary here.
This is like the flat Earth thing in the globe Earth.
But, you know, the Earth is a little flat and a little round.
And it's also very round and very flat.
Right. OK, anyway, the perception on this is which one does it want to bite?
The the the animals see that they're stationary and everything is moving around them
because the body that they're in overrules their actions.
OK, what I mean by that, our body, for example, if someone is going to slap you,
you're going to flinch, try to move out of the way without thinking about it.
Right. That's not you doing it.
That's the human body.
That's a built in feature on the human body doing that kind of like the automatic
windshield wipers. You turn it one knob and they go a little bit and then you turn
another right and they go the net another little bit.
Right. That's built into the wiper.
You know, the first click, second click, third click.
So we have these clicks that are built into us that when we're going to fall and
slip and fall, we put our hands out like it or not.
Right. All these things.
That's the human body.
When you see a cat jump a certain way, like they're spring loaded.
Right. That's the cat body doing that.
Right. That they have that they don't have to think about doing that.
Right. The dog will do a certain thing sometimes.
That's the dog body. A fish has a fish body reaction.
Swing its tail. It'll make its body bend like a C, letter C, if you look at it from
the top down. All these bodies have little built in reactions, reflexes, you can call
them or whatever.
So when the dog picks up the person who is in fear of dogs, the person doesn't even
have to be recollecting at the moment they're afraid of dogs.
It could just be stored in the back file.
The dog will pick up on it because it's there.
Right. And it's the dog body reacting on that.
So the animals do not see themselves moving through any situation.
They see situations moving around them.
That's why they're so well, in a way, in martial arts, you know how they have different
styles that are named after animals.
Right. You almost copy.
Yeah, because the animals have seemed like masters at certain styles and movements.
That's because their perception is very different.
Now, we can perceive that also in a way where to a certain degree, see, we are vertical
creatures. Our spine goes perpendicular to the flowing energy field on the earth, but
it goes parallel to the ether.
The animals go parallel with the flows, fields on the earth and perpendicular to the
ether. So they're being charged more by the fields on the earth or in flow with the
fields because they're parallel to them.
They offer no resistance, but they they're contrary and less attached to the etherical
fields. We are in line with the etherical fields, which are rays that go vertically up
and down. And we are contrary to the earth fields that go horizontal.
Right. So the earth fields go left and right, front and back.
Right. Our spine is vertical.
So these lines on the earth cut are through our spine, different vertebrae at different
levels. Right. You see, I brought this up several times.
There's a couple of people, only one or two, why is the spine on the animal horizontal
and vertical? That's a long explanation.
And I just gave a basic introduction on it.
Now, plants are very interesting, too.
And if you study the creepy crawly plants, the ones that are horizontal versus the
vertical ones, they follow a very similar suit in terms of the way they grow and the
way they react. And just to recap, you know, plants have a consciousness, but they're
always in dreamland. And I've said this many times, because this is a preface to a
much longer discussion on the on how the physical, the ethereal archetypes
affect us physically. Right.
So if plants have a consciousness, why do we eat them?
But they're always in dreamtime.
So when you go up to a bush or a vegetable plant to cut off some of it to eat,
it would be as if you are having a dream and in your dream someone cuts your arm off.
You're like, oh, fuck it. I'm in a dream, right?
It's no big deal. You don't go into shock, do you?
Some plants can go into shock depending on the weather and the conditions.
Right. And they die.
Right. So and by the way, where do psychedelics and dreamlike chemicals usually come
from? Right.
I'm not talking about licking frogs as an exception, but they come from plants 99
percent of the time. The dead plants.
Right. So going back to the emo, there is the body of the human, the
autonomous reaction, because we sense that we are moving through the world constantly.
Right. Get up from the chair, go get a beer, get up from here, do this.
Right. The Internet gets shut down.
I get up, find this stupid rectangle.
Right. So I'm moving through the world.
Right. OK. Yeah.
The animals don't sense that.
So once you get into a certain emo thing, how about flipping it a little bit where
you're not moving? You're completely stationary.
Everything is moving around you.
Hmm. And I you know where I got a really good jolt of that, you know, back in the
eighteen hundreds, early 19 is that moving sidewalks in cities?
They tried that second conveyor belt.
So instead of walking down the let's say Fifth Avenue, you just stand on the sidewalk
and it's a conveyor just moves you down.
You stand right. Have you seen those?
I've never seen them.
I've heard something about it, but I never saw them.
Yeah, they're quite popular.
They had them at train stations all over the place.
Yeah. There's a video called I think I posted in the chat a week ago.
This is what you've missed.
Showed all the technology in the eighteen hundreds that you don't have now.
Right. Electric electric cars is one thing, by the way.
Yeah. Eighty percent of the cars in 1920 were electric and they had greater range in
the car than the Teslas do now.
Think about it. And batteries didn't go dead in four years.
Like anyway. So think about these things.
You're stationary and everything's moving around you.
Why? That's the emo aspect.
Right. The emo grabs the environment that way.
Once you have a stationary perspective and everything is moving.
Well, Greek, that's really hard for me to do if I'm jogging, you know, right.
Going for a run. Actually, that's the best time to notice it.
See, I don't think it's that hard to do nowadays because we have, again, like I brought
up last time you brought this up, video games.
This is exactly what happens during a video game.
Your character stays within a particular area.
The VR goggles, you mean, right?
Well, yeah. The screen.
Either one or either one works because you are going and just you're on the screen.
The world is coming to you.
Really? Yep. What do you think they're doing?
They're creating. They're redefining, redefining the reality that you're in.
I've seen videos, idiots, videos sometimes where the guy's got the VR goggles on playing
golf and he walks up and he swings and he knocks the TV down.
Everybody's like, oh, no.
Right. Or grandma falls over because she's on a roller coaster standing up.
Right. Right. VR.
Yeah. So what they're doing is redefining reality by bringing this to you.
And I kind of brought up why and how.
And from the ethereal end, kind of like a Steiner-ish, Rudolf Steiner-ish kind of
perspective of how the emo, let's say, using the emo as a base.
So when you go places, let's say you're invited to a party and it's a group of people
and by the way, I would get to a party group.
By the way, when you go into a situation, you rated why people are interested.
If you go into a situation and you're not in control, guess what?
That situation is out of control.
Now, if I tell this to your average Westerner, especially academic, they're going to
class out the Greek. Don't listen to him, man.
He's a passive aggressive control freak.
Right. He's saying that you've got to go take control of every situation.
Blah, blah, blah. Right. That's the way people take it.
When you first say it that way. Right.
Well, see, and I wouldn't even start with the party thing.
I would go with, you know, look, more commonly, people walk into a store, you're not
in control of it. I mean, there's certain expectations you have of what you're going to
encounter when you go inside.
You know, there's going to be a place where there is something to be picked up, goods,
whatever. There's a place to pay, blah, blah.
You have expectations, but you go in there, you're not in control of that situation, are
you? But you know, the thing is not to ultimately be in control, but to have the
perception that when you enter into a situation, nothing, it's out of control.
In other words, there are controlling mechanisms there that are set by default.
But any shit can be set off at any time.
You know, think about someone in a prison yard, right?
You don't want to get to, even though it's for rec time, it's not you don't want to get
to when they see you're really comfy.
That's when they come and jig you with a sharpened toothbrush.
Right. When they pick up like a dog, they'll pick up when your guard is down.
I'm not saying have your guard up, but when you go into a situation, most people are
thinking very passively that they walked into this situation.
And I'm telling you from an emo perspective, that situation came to you.
You haven't left from an ethereal, emotional, emo point of view.
You never went anywhere in your whole life.
Everything is coming towards you.
That doesn't make any sense.
Right. From a mechanic, just like pulling on the steering wheel slightly as if you just
upgraded, you know, 10,000 bucks worth of suspension and tires.
How can that be? You know, how can this old jalopy drive like a higher performance car
just by slightly pulling on the steering wheel?
It doesn't make any sense in the mechanical world.
So this is more advanced, but I thought I'd drop it out there because there are people
thinking about it and using it.
It takes a little bit to think about it.
But, you know, if people ever listen to me speak on the ether potential, you know, with
the weather work, the potential is different.
It goes from low to high.
We're always taught that all potentials go from high to low.
Right. You know, you have a battery, it's charged, high potential, and it discharges.
Right. Well, the ether is different.
What's low, it starts building up to a higher point, right, where the low feeds the
high. So in a regular situation, the way we're taught potentials work, when you have a
battery that's draining down, you have to attach it to a battery that's full, right, to
charge it. But in an ether battery, when the battery is low, the way you charge is by
attaching it to an even weaker battery and that weaker battery will discharge into that
one. Right.
So when you want to charge, let's say your glasses, you're drinking the water in your
glass, right?
The way you would increase an ethereal environment is by putting it next to a glass
that has even less water in it or taking water from a glass that has less water in it and
putting it in your glass, you see, instead of a big pitcher.
Right. I've actually seen people do that when someone's not, they drink their drink
almost all the way down and they were drinking, they poured into their glass kind of
thing or whatever.
You know, it's but that's not a really good analogy because the physical reality that we
live in is all perception.
And proof of that is with sound and with light.
You know, we only see one to five percent of the visible spectrum.
It's easy to prove with an infrared camera, with ultraviolet.
Right. You know, since the 60s, they've been looking through people's houses with
infrared cameras right through the window.
You got the shades down. It doesn't matter.
They still see you with the heat signature.
Right. Unfortunately, I have a practical experience with this because I see stuff that I'm
supposed to. And yet I miss things that I'm supposed to see.
So because I'm in a different part of the spectrum visual.
Yeah. Yeah.
Sensitive. They try to tell you it's all mechanical.
I think at all. You don't see with your eyes or hear with your ears.
You see and hear with your brain.
It's the processing. Right.
But I'm highly sensitive.
Like I see heat as other people do not see it.
I don't know why that is, but I can see heat differentials.
Yeah, I'm with you. So I know someone who can see magnetic fields.
It's a distortion. It's actually it's funny.
It's a distortion that goes around it.
Like if you try and look just just slightly around something, you can see that it
distorts. And depending on the level of heat, it can distort a lot because it's
emanating a lot of heat. I can see that before I get anywhere near it and
physically feel. Oh, oh, so just like the heat to share with the rest of what you
have in common with when we see the heat waves coming off of a hot road.
Yeah. Yeah. I can tell.
OK, so it's not a color spectrum.
It's actually it's it's a distortion or it's a diffraction, refraction thing.
Well, there's a color thing, too.
But but aside from I'm just saying that for some reason, I don't know why that I
mean, I have less pigment in my eyes.
So I'm what they call an albino.
So, yeah. So what I've been laying out some what most people might think is a
little bit of nonsense here, but just things to think about that we're not really
well here. You know, I said you don't go anywhere.
Everything comes to you. Think of the movie The Matrix.
You spend your whole life. Where are you in a pod?
The movie. Right. You're not going anywhere.
Right. Well, again, it's a video game.
Same thing. I mean, look, you go from here to here and here.
It doesn't know your character and your whatever is on that same screen all the
time anyway. Or the pod in The Matrix or the pod in The Matrix.
You're sitting there and you're sitting there not going anywhere.
Right. So this is where the emo works.
And that's how the emo works in terms of its fundamental establishment.
In other words, to establish a strong emo.
Or to establish emo as a strong tool, you must first establish that you're not
moving. You've never gone anywhere, never done anything.
All of it is coming to you like you're the center of the universe.
I know, again, if someone hears that the Greek is crazy, sounds like you're now
you're an egomaniac. Right.
But this is true for all of us.
It's the ultimate form of narcissism, the ultimate form of narcissism.
Right. Where I remember the big example was actually nothing.
Everything in the world is just a pigment of my imagination.
Sure. But this is not like this because we're looking to work the reality that we
perceive again, where the imagination, again, is perception and visualization and
creativity. People with no creativity have no imagination.
You hear that often, right?
Oh, yeah. Well, you have no imagination.
That's why, you know, whatever.
So all of these things coming towards you.
So if you are if you're not doing anything or going anywhere and everything is
coming towards you and you know that the potential goes from low to high.
Right. That means that you are the most important thing and you have the most
potential because that's the lower things are coming to the higher thing.
This is ether now. Right.
This is where the the emo is working.
It is a substance in the ethereal world.
We see it as non substance, as non material in any in any way.
And that substance is made of thought.
And that's why I started getting into that inner voice is not you.
It's something that comes into you when you're a child and it keeps changing as
you evolve. But again, for most people in the public, you know, if you know anyone
who's 70 or 80, they still have the same one that they had when they were probably
10 or 12. By the way, when I was out yesterday, these old people cover your
ears or a lot. Most of them are just old scumbags.
And I'm saying that as a as a as an accurate term.
In the past week, I've been out because I've been sourcing things and I don't I
try to see where people are at.
And these old scumbags, old scumbags, meaning over 55, bring up certain things.
And when it gets to a philosophical, I'm going to give them a little Greek speak on
how the end is near, but not in the way they're used to hearing it.
Every one of them this past two weeks says, well, I don't care because I'm going to
be dead by then.
That's and I, you know, and I say, oh, yeah, fuck the young people who cares about
them. Right. So what that tells you is that is an irresponsible scumbag.
And when I hear about them being drugged up and thrown into a nursing home with a
diaper, I have zero sympathy for them.
As a matter of fact, a lot of the Agenda 30 and a lot of the communist regime stuff
is if you're older than 55, you can't work, you get an option taking a pill.
Right. Or we put you in an area, whatever, turn you into food sludge.
I'm all I'm down for that, except for a tiny, tiny, tiny percentage that may have
some modicum of some value.
And I'm disgusted with them.
I've had it with the older people.
I remember I put a we you and I did a sonic on this with Ocelli in the Greek and
we had this dumb lady put a comment.
What do you mean? The old people's where you go to get truth and wisdom.
Wait till the Greek hits 50.
Remember that? Yeah, I'm already older than 50.
I mean, people don't understand that I'm objectifying these things.
I have no care or regard or interest in anything people do.
Just like I say, if everyone wants to turn this world into a living paradise, have at
it. Just count me out.
If you want to turn into a living hell and start killing and eating each other, have
at it. Just count me out.
No matter what they do, whether it's good or bad, I want nothing to do with it.
You see, I don't want to I don't want to participate in either one of those things,
but I do feel a responsibility to try and leave things in slightly better condition
than I found them. I don't know why that is.
I don't know where it comes from, but I have this idea that, you know, you're talking
about these older scumbags.
And look, I'm just over 51 now.
You know, I feel this just responsibility that you're supposed to leave things just a
little better. But that's you.
But the majority in the collective are just that.
They don't care. They're like, well, now I'm not saying all of them, please.
I never include anything everywhere, all except for attorneys and doctors, by the way.
I'm just joking. An intelligence agency is pretty much all of them are, except for a
small group that realize what's going on and they want to exit, but looking for an exit
strategy. But the ones that stay there, yeah, they all are.
I've never met a doctor personally that's worth a damn.
But OK. Yeah, I mean, look, the all inclusive is true.
And I always say, except for those that figured it out and are looking for an exit
strategy and that gives you a two week to two year leeway.
Usually when a doctor, an attorney, intelligence or cop or whatever agency figures out
this is all bullshit and it's actually to the detriment of society, they try to figure
out an exit strategy.
And it usually takes them two weeks to two years to exit.
Right. And by the way, fact check, an attorney that does that ends up being a
car, a car salesman.
Pick it either new or used.
It's it's amazing because I've followed a couple of them quit.
And if you want to think that I had something with them doing quitting, I'm not going to
brag about it, even though I do have bragging rights on it.
I found them ending up selling cars, which which is another thing.
What do you use car sales?
Right. It's another negative connotation.
Right. So anyway, well, because a lot of used car salesmen do cheat people.
And I mean, look, you got to take your skills somewhere.
But if you're an honest car salesman, then you're doing you know, you're doing something
that's practically serves a purpose, at least.
Sure. It can be.
It's all about. Yeah, it's all about mindset, you know.
So, again, with the I think I maybe I jumped in too deep or something like that with the
email because it still hasn't been too practical.
But I took it sort of like a little glimpse of the end of the matter.
When you start to get what makes a master, a master versus an amateur, two things.
Level of skill and confidence, because if you have the level of skill and no confidence,
you're going to shy away from most situations and you won't seem like you're a master.
Right. But if you have too much confidence and no skill, you're definitely going to show
you're not a master.
Right. So it's a it's a combination of skill and confidence.
So to get to that point, you have to comprehend that you are sort of like a plant.
Like they say, it would be like a tree, right?
That willow that bends.
But sometimes you need to be like an oak.
You have to decide when. But what I'm saying is, you know, trees, by the way, when they're
in trouble, they can't go anywhere.
Can they? Well, not very quickly.
Yeah. Right. So that is a good analogy with the email also, because you're not going
anywhere. If I tell people a couple of when I got to more of an evolved email talk that
I had some private talks, not even with the Skype groups, I said that, you know, you've
never done anything and you've never gone anywhere your whole life.
All this experience and all this is a product of your perception and your senses and the
reactions of your perceptions of your environment and those around you interacting.
But none of you have ever done anything or gone anywhere.
By the way, that sounds like a lot like what society is like.
It seems like, you know, nothing's going anywhere.
Sometimes you even hear that.
Right. You a lot of the things that we talk about in the email are cliches already in
society. Like, for example, people say or, you know, the inner voice that's not your
voice. How many times you hear people say something like, I can't believe I said that.
Right. That's what because it's not, you know, you're relying on that voice that you think
is you because it sounds like you.
Right. So, again, on the email aspect, there is the
projection into the environment by measured perception.
What that means is when you perceive something that immediately gets you excited.
Right. You can take that however you want.
I can make a couple of them.
Or you could perceive something that immediately gets you excited in a panic, in a
negative way, fight or flight.
Right. These things that we use the human body, like someone's going to throw a punch or
slap, you move out of the way without thinking about it.
Okay. That's not measured.
That's the human body reacting.
Right. So when you have a certain level of composure and you are able to measure your
movement down to the millisecond, let's say, then the email can be applied.
But if you're a reactionary person, you hear some bad news and immediately you go into
that mode that you should, right, it messes you up immediately or whatever, the email is
not going to work on you. So it's by measured composure, in other words, measured
reactions. Everything you do is measured.
It doesn't mean a long time.
It can happen in points where a lot of times when I see an example, I said I thought
about that in point three seconds.
Right. You hear me say that point three seconds is a long time, by the way.
For who? Right.
Again, depends on who.
So and also your skill, your skill level, karate kid type stuff.
Right. So when you start seeing and you're measuring everything around you and you are
these things have. How many times have you you know, I said you haven't done anything or
gone anywhere. How many times in cliche language, I can't believe you brought that upon
yourself. Right.
You've heard that. Right. They didn't say I can't believe you got into that.
Well, they say that to brought it upon yourself means you didn't go anywhere.
It came to you. But there's also.
You got into that. But I think brought upon yourself is used a little bit more.
Yeah. When people are trying to reach for something higher, that's what they often say.
Otherwise, you know, I can't believe that happened to you is the most basic.
But or you went to it.
It's more like it comes to you than you go to it in the cliche.
So watch these cliches.
In other words, it's already out there in the what we're what we're talking about on a
deep level is already out there in cliches in the collective, the ignorant collective.
But it's meant to be dismissed in the collective.
Well, however, they handle it, because, you know, where do you find people in the in the
collective? Right. You that's why I like Nepal.
OK. That's why I like Napoleonic law, Napoleonic law, you're presumed guilty.
Right. And then you have to prove innocence.
We're here. They tell you you preserve here.
There's no presumed guilt or innocence.
Just about monetizing the charge.
Right. Of course.
Yeah. That's the one thing that people will never understand.
Meaning until these people are these people that are here now will never understand this.
The new people hopefully will now.
The the collective has when you are putting out stuff like that's unrated, why it's
actually aimed at the collective, but not it's not it's towards them, but not for them.
Right. You see, like sometimes they say, hey, we should get some more subs.
We need to put it out here, put it out there.
We're putting it out to the collective, whether it's alternative media or not.
The alternative media to me is like the lie that Satan said.
The first thing Satan got people to believe is that he doesn't exist.
Well, the alternative media got people to believe that they're really alternative.
Right. Anyway, that's just take it how you want it.
I think that's pretty true.
Yeah. So.
Well, this is this is towards the collective, the stuff that's on rated Y, but it's not for
them, it's towards them, because there's going to be one out of a thousand, one out of a
hundred thousand that will hear this and say, I could use this.
Right. Or or this is super rarefied information that's super usable and super practical.
Right. So you see, that's where the emo works.
Also, you can when you're doing emo work and I think you and I have gotten over, I said
I'm going to save it for the solo sonics, but you and I have gotten over some of it or
enough of it where the emotions that you have are for a purpose and no one, even in
psychology and psychiatry, know why it's there.
It's just that it's there.
And the other example that I gave is it makes certain people that are measured character
a certain way, do things that are out of their measured character.
You know, the mild mannered guy that kills his whole family, what made him do it?
Right. Other than the voice in his head, it's the he had to be into an emotional state.
Have you ever gotten into a frenzy where the adrenaline kicks in and you stop and your
heart rates go, you know, you need to relax, get out of it.
Right. That's all emotionally ticked off.
Right. So the emo can tick off your adrenals and all the dopamines and all this other
stuff. If you've ever been in a fight that you weren't planning or expecting or
weren't skilled, when the fight ends and you pull yourself away, your whole body is
numb. If your fists are numb while you're punching the other guy, you don't feel
them. And if you got your face beaten to a pulp, you don't feel anything anyway.
No, not until the next day.
Yeah. And even like I'm saying during the fight, your body just shuts down.
So. Right.
So this is all the initial that is the the body, the human body doing that.
Not you. The emo overrides all that.
That's like. You know, the it doesn't override it to
stop it, but it overrides it either to enhance it or control it.
That's why I said earlier, when you get into a situation, if you're not in control,
the situation is out of control.
Right. It has nothing.
It's more on the emo ether perspective.
In other words, when most people walk into a room, they just as tall
tell me something about the room.
They're going to give you mostly physical descriptions
where when you're into the emo, you're going to give more of a feeling.
How does it feel? Fortunately, I was around people in the 70s and 80s that were
kind of new agey, but more practical.
They would talk a lot about energy like once they would meet.
So that person has good energy.
That person has bad energy or this room has bad energy.
This place has good energy. Right.
You've heard that, right? Of course.
Yeah. Fortunately, from a young age, I was around that.
And I wasn't really digging it too much using language from back then.
Right. And but it was stuck in the mind that it was something available.
And not until I kept asking what is the purpose of emotions and started piecing
that together into a workable form that I see that to see things in energy forms.
The other thing about the energy forms is this is something also I recently got
from listening to the Castaneda audiobooks is omens.
I heard like I was doing some masonry work and oh, the Don Juan looked free, saw
enough omens. I was like, oh, my gosh, we call that synchronicities.
And there is no level to how fine that can go.
When you're going into a situation, let's say yesterday I went to get some I
didn't feel like I can get some fried chicken from Albertson's.
It was terrible. I just fed it to the cats.
I couldn't get it past my nose.
And actually, most people cover your ears, white people, whatever people don't
know how to cook, would think it's great.
I went, it's crunchy, it's tasty, it's a little salty.
So it's preference, yes, but I'm telling you, it's not good.
On my way there, I had so many little tiny omens showing me this is not the place
to get where and I ignored them.
But I acknowledge them, but I ignored them.
In other words, I didn't let that these little signs dissuade me from making the
order, actually making the transaction and taking it home.
But on another occasion and around people, I would walk into a place and use those
omens and say, this is not right.
And then someone else that we knew would go over there.
So how is that? Sucks.
I said, OK, so now I know I'm dialed in.
Right. I ignored all of the little omens.
What those omens are lots of minutiae, minutiae.
You look as you're walking through a path, you look at the from your peripheral
vision, what are you picking up?
Is the without getting into my personal details of what I saw in the space that
won't really help. Maybe it will.
But let's say you're walking from down a supermarket aisle or an open aisle where
the vegetables are.
OK, you're kind of not really hyper focused on where you're going.
You just know you've got to go to the back of the store.
There's no one in front of you that you're going to walk into like a dummy.
Right. You just keep walking.
And your main focusing is kind of off and kind of like general glancing.
You're not focused on it, but your peripheral vision at that point gets into
high, high view, but you don't notice it.
You don't notice it. I was picking up crazy stuff in the peripheral vision, maybe
things that other people couldn't see, maybe the presence of certain energies and
things. And just how you said you can see color.
I mean, you could see heat on something.
The peripheral vision I was picking up was a lot of greens, but not the green that
you consider with fresh fruits and vegetables and plants, but a putrid kind of
green aura right in the in the place.
And then some physical things like some a piece of fruit had fallen.
It was at the bottom of the stand and it was like pushed in by someone's toes.
And it was just sitting there more than a day.
Right. When I got to the counter, it looked clear.
But as soon as I turned around, there was a morbidly obese woman in one of these
motorized wagons that looked like you could carry masonry blocks.
She was about four feet wide and she could have weighed no less than 500 pounds.
That morbidly obese.
Okay. Didn't even look human.
Kind of like a job of the hut character.
Gotcha. About four feet wide.
So she couldn't go into most shops because most shops are 36 inch or 38, 40 inch
doors. Right. She had for her.
It has to be the double door sliders.
No way she can go.
And the wheels on this thing were like very heavy, airless tires like you see on
heavy duty wheelbarrow carts that they have at railroad yards, solid tires and the
kind of carts you see at railroad yards that move heavy stuff.
Like if you go to a railroad yard and pick up a bucket of something, you try to pick
it up. Feels like it's bolted to the floor.
That's how heavy stuff is there.
Right. Nothing against morbidly, but she showed up out of nowhere.
She was not in my peripheral.
She was not in my view.
The moment I got to the counter and looked to the left, it's like Scotty Beam, you're
down there. At that point, I was already having everyone behind the counter laughing
and the jerk off manager that got out of college was ready to spray the Windex, you
see, the glass cleaner.
Everything was going wrong.
But what I asked the guy behind the counter is I said, is this chicken dry?
He says, it's OK. I said, how long has it been here?
When someone doesn't give you a quantitative or quality of answer, then you got to play
detective. All right.
How long has it been out here?
20 minutes. All right.
Now I got something I can use.
Right. Right.
Right. The next thing I said is if your mom came here and she wanted to get chicken, what
would you give her? He says, I would go in the back and I'd batter some up and fry some
fresh. And how long would it take?
She'd have to wait, what, 15 minutes?
Yeah, 15 minutes.
Mm hmm. And he looks at me and he says, I'm going to do that for you.
Right. And OK.
And that's how I talk to people.
Every time there's no one talks to them that way, they just say, I want a quarter pound
of ham sliced in and I want to.
OK, thank you.
That's all they get all day, all day.
They get no interaction.
Right. Right. So so I interact with these people like I haven't seen them since the third
grade. Right.
Right. So anyway, while this is happening and all this, I'm looking around and I say,
you know, I need to leave this place.
But I didn't. Right.
So again, I don't like to talk about personal experiences, but this is to illustrate how
the emo is being used.
Now, I didn't use the Jedi on him very often.
Give some personal stuff.
I had gone with the wife once to get some recycled paint.
OK, and it's excellent, by the way.
Take a look up. Recycled paint, one coat covers it's the people bring all their trash paint
and they mix them in general colors and they sell them to you real cheap.
It's super thick. It covers really well because the particle sizes are so mixed up that
it's going to cover what I mean by particle sizes.
You know that a half a gallon of gravel, a half a gallon of sand and a half a gallon
of rock make one gallon all fit in a one gallon container.
Most people say, how could that be?
A half a gallon plus a half a gallon plus a half a gallon.
You need a gallon and a half. No.
If you take a half a gallon of rock, a half a gallon of sand and a half a gallon of gravel
and mix them all together, they all fit neatly in one gallon.
Right. Because one fits inside the spaces of the other.
Right. OK.
Anyway, that's how the recycled paint works.
So once you get recycled paint and they were advertising fifteen dollars a bucket, I get
there, it's twenty dollars a bucket.
I say, well, how about fifteen dollars?
And the guy says, no, it's nineteen ninety nine plus tax.
You know, when they say plus tax, it's like, fuck you.
Right. So I'm like, all right.
Oh, I wasn't expecting this and I want to try this stuff.
So we look around the store. I take two buckets to the cashier and I the guy is not
busy. You know, when no one's behind the cashier, you're kind of taking a break.
All right. He wasn't thinking I caught he wasn't thinking about anything at all.
And I went into his head and I said, dude, I love you and I need this paint.
So and you're going to help me out.
Something like that. Emo without words.
So he looks at me with a dead stare and I and I say, I'd like to check out these two
buckets and I'm dead stare back.
He rings up ten dollars even just ten dollars even.
And I had that number in my mind anyway.
OK, I'm not so sure if I had that number, but I wanted to just get the paint and feel
like I just got a Christmas gift.
You know how they say, right? It was Christmas.
So I look at him. I always do this with him.
I say ten dollars for these two buckets.
Right. And he goes, yes.
My wife's like, what?
And I'm like, honey, go get the car, because I don't know how long this is going to
last on this guy. Right. Right.
Go get the car right now. Also, you get out, leave the store now, get the car now.
So when I'm done with the train, basically, you know, that means when I'm when I get
when I give by telling him the money, the car's on its way.
We get the hell out of here. Right.
And she's in the car, she goes, oh, my gosh, I don't believe we did to that poor guy.
I said, what poor guy? He was a jerk off to us.
And I've done this over and over and over and over hundreds of times in the past
decade in my life, in in commercial situations, not to get over.
Right. One time I had done something out of hardware, so I don't to get in particulars of the
story. And I walked out with time and a half the money that I walked in with, with all
the stuff I had.
And I was like, this isn't right.
So I went back in and I put the note because she gave me back my note and the change
and all the stuff.
And I said, oh, my gosh, this is a single mom with three children that lives in a trailer
park. And at the end of the day, when they add up the register and it's fifty dollars
off, she's going to lose her job.
That's not good. Right.
So I go back in and I put the note on the counter.
I said, just put this in the register.
It'll add up. It'll check out.
Well, she goes, what?
Why are you giving me this?
And then she's checking people's manager.
I need a manager to just put this in the register and everything will be fine.
And I ran out of there. Right.
Because you always have to do the right thing, you know, to an extent.
But when someone is acting like they really don't like you and it's a cash business
and you just met them and you're trying to be courteous, you could pull the email on
them and say, these are not the droids that you seek, you know, kind of thing.
That's just more of an evolved position.
But basically, it all comes from I don't like to use the word love, but I do because
love is doing the definition of the word love is to do the right thing.
Right. When someone asks you for something, people always look at all these other
conditions and whether they're going to meet that request.
Right. And when you measure the degree of that request, the person is making and you
measure the degree that you that your condition and you see that that you're much
better off. You write that you show them love.
Right. See what I mean?
So when someone like the analogy that I give with love is if someone calls you up at
three in the morning because they need to help moving, it shouldn't have taken that
long. Most people are going to say, dude, it's three in the morning.
I got to go to work in the morning.
Right. What are you doing? Call.
Right. Where's the love?
Right. And when you get there to help them, don't be begrudging.
Right. Because then you cut the love off, you showed the love by agreeing to be there
and showing up. But you have to do it joyfully.
Right. So all this has to be done with joy.
But the funniest thing is to is to get over on these techno corporate morons, both the
people that work there and the institution itself.
And the easiest way to do that, by the way, because the people that work in these
corporations don't know anything.
Like, for example, if you go to a bank, those bank tellers don't know anything.
I used to screw them up.
Well, years ago, I used to go in with a check and I said, can I get can I exchange this
for Federal Reserve notes?
Sure. Hold on a second.
Don't call the manager. No, I have to call the manager.
No, don't call the manager.
Manager comes over.
He said he wants Federal Reserve notes for this.
She doesn't even glance at the clerk.
She elbows her out of the way and she counts the notes out and gives me a dead stare.
Right. Because they're really dumb.
The same with doctors and lawyers and all that stuff.
But the really way to get back at the corporate system, in other words, the people that
work in these corporate other foot soldiers, right?
You can't talk to them.
Just pawn pieces.
And when you play chess, what's the first thing gets wiped off the board?
Right. The pawns.
The way to do it is by not in non endorsement and everything has conditions.
You do everything with conditions.
And the easiest way to do that is with your signature.
By the way, I don't know if I've ever shared this.
A lot of these patriot law types say, oh, it's your signature, right?
Your signature, right? Don't give them your signature.
Oh, a cop wanted me to sign the ticket and I didn't want to sign.
So they took me to jail. Right.
I don't know if you've ever heard this before.
Yeah. OK. Stupid.
Signature is yes, they're using it.
And someone came back to me and said, Greek, any mark you make is bullshit because it's
intent. Remember the logos marking them out?
Right. Intent is very important.
I'll sign anything all day long.
It don't matter to the Greek. Why?
Because whenever I sign anything, I sign void.
I haven't signed the Greeks government name in 15 years on anything ever.
I sign void. How do I sign void?
I don't write block letters V, O, D.
No, you sign it like a doctor writes void.
You scribble it and it kind of looks like a V.
A scribble in the middle kind of looks like a D with an I over the left part of the
scribble. So so if you look at that, it looks like a signature.
What does it say? I'm not sure.
I said it says void.
The moment I say it says void, you look at it.
Yeah, I see it now like that.
Right. Everything.
So if you don't like what you sign or what they made you sign, you just simply write
them a letter, tell them they have to settle that discharge or get rid of it because
you signed it void.
For this reason, this reason and that reason, what they're doing is unlawful.
Holy shit.
Holy shit. What just happened?