Rated Y 107, okay, so here we are, and looking back, in 71 we were talking about wrapping
wounds tightly, properly, why you do that, why you don't do that, and there is a time
to do it and a time not to, and you were going over that.
Time went by fast, so that would have been quite a few months ago, but still.
It seems like it was very recent though, doesn't it seem like we were just talking about this
as well?
Yeah, well, yeah, I think this has never come about, eventually I'm going to just switch
to doing classes, like seminars, you know, these conversations we're having are fine,
but we were going to do some solo sonics, Sam got involved, so it's like the three
of us working it now, I do all the talking and you guys provide the platform and whatever,
but my usefulness is, well, first of all, I'm very novel, new sounding, especially the
older stuff, the older the subject matter, the newer it sounds, because no one knows
shit anymore, and there's a joke about that, by the way, you don't know shit, right, but
to be more poignant and to the point is really where I'm at, because sometimes people say
you're a jack of all trades, and I'm like, no, no, I'm actually a master of quite a few
trades, quite a few things on mastership level, so someone like that, if I can separate myself
and talk about myself this way, is best by, if you indeed have mastered many things, traditionally
and culturally and whatever there is, when you attain that level and you have enough
social graces, meaning you can be in the room with two or three people, digital or not,
you should be teaching and imparting that, because the reason to impart this stuff is
to save on time, it's for the sake of efficiency, and it's not even time, some people, okay,
let's say time is graced by the distance between when you were born to when you die, I'd say
about 99% of the stuff that I've ever discussed on Sonics, most people will go that distance
from the cradle to the grave and not ever know or hear about it, ever, right, so actually
making a concerted effort to bring forward stuff that I know I'm good at, and okay, I'm
going to expand on that, because it's not what it sounds, is what I'm saying, to expand
on that for efficiency's sake, so people can hear it and catch up very quickly, of course,
if they're interested, now what I mean that I'm good at, is what I want to expand on,
is a very simple way that you don't need a lot of background, but you get everything
up front, okay, what do I mean by that, by the way, this goes into criticism also, you
should never accept criticism from someone that you normally would not ask for advice,
right, because think about what criticism is, so first of all, second of all, the form
of what advice is to advise, right, also has to fit, right, so there are a small concerted
group of people on this planet still, I believe, and it's evident by the subs, that want to
catch up with something that they don't know about, you know, right, but they know it'll
be interesting if they do, what I'm good at is, for example, when it comes to criticism,
like recently I helped out someone clean a professional space, now I'll give you the
little background, typically when you say you do cleaning work, I don't do cleaning
work, that's all I do, right, someone who does this cleaning work, they're looked down
upon, but they don't understand that in certain fields, like semiconductors, the clean, the
people that maintain the cleanliness of facilities like that, are at the paramount, at the top
of the pyramid, really, other than the engineers that, you know, so...
Well, the same thing with the old development of photographs, the people that actually kept
things clean and in order and all of that, and kept the chemicals straight...
Oh, yeah, you couldn't expose, yeah, digital is different, the pixels don't get dirty,
but...
Right, but in the days of chemical photography, like I'm saying, the people that...
Well, anything, see, well, anyway, one of the principals walked in and says, wow, I'd
like for you to do my space also, and I said, well, you know, it's expensive and it's not
what you think, I basically said to them, when you say you do cleaning work, it's looked
down on the society, but it's actually a very high attribute, and the principal response
was, yeah, you know, when I was young, my mom said, you didn't clean that, that's not
clean, and I said, is that all she said?
Pretty much, when you give criticism, and this is what I do, if I give criticism, I'm
going to produce the criticism as a gesticulation to the victim, right, because you're victimized
if you criticize, basically, that's the category, well, then I produce why it's what I criticized
it about, and then how to fix it.
If I can't do all those three things at once, I will not criticize, or those other two things,
if they can't follow, if I can't do a follow-through of why I'm criticizing it, and specifically,
and then how to remedy it, I will not form a criticism.
So it's fair to say that you're not going to bother to pick on someone or something unless
you know how to fix it, and then you'll also include that in picking on it.
What they can do about it, exactly.
I'll never call someone out on something, even derogatory, unless I can finish with
a component that will show them a way out of that, or a remedy.
Okay.
A remedy.
I always provide the remedy in the same breath, unlike the systems that you have now that
do not do that, do not provide the remedy.
So immediately.
By the way, when you hear of legal remedy or financial remedy, that means you're sick, right?
It's a sickness.
So, okay.
So what I'm thinking of is producing a seminar thing.
I did a take on it with the Scalarator, which I think I voiced on the last Sonic that anything
that I pretty much do, I've given up on doing it as a business or with an organization.
What it is, it's like I will promote myself as an artist, right?
Stelios the Greek, whatever, whatever, or however.
And this guy makes extraordinary devices.
And if you want one of his devices, you're actually buying a part, a piece of his time.
It's not something, right?
So when I worked in different fields and it always turned out the same, it always turned
out the same.
I've worked in various things and when I took one or two days off, I came back and everything
fell apart.
Now, it didn't fall apart at a critical failure.
It would have been fine for any other business, but for the level that I wanted it to operate
on, I considered it falling apart, right?
Because then we're just like everybody else.
So, right.
So what I'm planning is a long-winded explanation of what I'm thinking of in the background
is doing the prototype, the beta test of the Scalarator seminar, the way I went through
that, doing a series of those and getting into medical, legal, lawful, historical stuff.
And also, just to asterisk on the historical stuff, I'm leaning heavy on the material that
Brashear's, Jason Brashear's at Archaics is putting out, because everything historical
is based on chronological accuracy, right?
So I'm looking at what he's digging up and I'm finding some holes, but generally it holds
together.
In other words, it's a leaky boat, but it floats, if that makes any sense.
It's not airtight or watertight, right?
But it floats.
Okay.
So I'm revising a lot of the stuff that I've said in the past and thought about because
of his work, which I appreciate.
But again, nothing is flawless as far as I can tell or no one is, I should say.
So I'm thinking of, I could get some feedback from people and do it, quote unquote, democratically
by the numbers, meaning what you would like to see or hear on these seminar sonic type
things.
And it'll be by myself and I'll be doing the admin, I'll be doing the whole thing on my
own.
So I have to learn how to use the digital payment systems and all that.
I just, I'll sit down and have complete control over it.
Maybe use something like Podbean, I don't know, something that offers it all together.
And something that doesn't rape you, like I found that from speaking with Sam and other
people that it's normal to pay over 10% of whatever fees you lay out to the host.
And that's like robbery, really anything over.
And I found that the younger the people are, the less they mind it.
But yeah, being a child of the early 60s, you know, and growing up in the 70s and 80s, anything
even even to the 2000s, anyone or anything that asked for more than 5% was scrutinized
very heavily.
Right.
I'm talking about like a non partnership, you know, like basically you're not doing anything,
you're just providing.
Right.
So, yeah.
So I'm like, oh, my gosh, you know, this is I don't think, you know, so I'm going to look
at all that stuff and put it out there because they by the way, my compensation is 150 bucks
an hour.
If people want to hire me, I just put that out there because I've gotten some messages
wondering what I would charge for doing something.
So my personal time at the minimum is 150 and it goes on a scale, right, depending
on like, for example, I used to do calls with consultation calls with professional people
and a two hour call, they would send me 500 bucks.
So that's more than 150 an hour.
Right.
It's 250.
Yeah.
And that's normal, by the way.
These psychics, you know, now, you know, the tarot reader, that's 250 an hour.
You go to their website.
Actually, I was thinking about the private readings run about 200 bucks an hour.
Yeah.
Anyway.
And what do you get for that?
I mean, I'm not going to criticize that because I don't have a remedy for it.
Right.
Yeah.
Other than to avoid it.
So I just want to put that out there.
That's what I see in the future.
A little bit.
Maybe that'll be my retirement so I don't have to eat out of a garbage can.
I don't know.
I just want to share that with everyone.
But what I also wanted to share also was the the aspect of criticism and all that.
You must provide the remedy and the solution.
And that also helps you with your own character development because it kind of slows you down.
Some people say I've been very harsh with them in the past and I don't come around and
say I'm sorry.
Everything I said, I still would say maybe it's the way I delivered it that was harsh.
Right.
But I don't take the content and the syntax and all that was correct.
But the way that it was done, maybe.
Yeah.
But no.
And that's very important.
So when I give frankly, I think automatically I would feel less of a harsh feeling for somebody
who criticizes me and provides a solution, like you said, or exactly automatically, that's
better because, look, if you're just going to pick on me and tell me what I you know,
and pull me down.
Well, you know, then you suck.
So what?
You know, but yeah, the Children's Indoctrination Center is known as the public fool system.
I mean, public school system sets up people for this kind of like prison rape molestation
system.
So in other words, what when you're in what they get away with doing in the schoolyard
will land them in jail at the off at the workplace.
Right.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
And that's, you know, the attorneys, by the way.
When you hear legal or illegal, illegal means that you don't have a license to do it.
It's not unlawful.
It has nothing to do with law.
So the society in terms of legal is raised like they're, you know, if you speak to someone
like they're eight years old for their entire life and you go and speak to them again when
they're 70, they can only comprehend that eight year old the way you talk to young children.
So if you look at way attorneys speak, doctors, the politicians, television, the school, whatever,
that is a juvenile approach.
These people grow up, you know, like if you live, if you have parents that are older workers
or whatever, you know, you look at them and they're older or whatever.
But yeah, if you think and listen to what they say and how they say it, it's no different
than an eight year old.
Right.
I've gotten a lot of feedback when I said that.
It was funny.
Once we had this lady, I really knocked how old people are useless.
You know, they were supposed to be bastions of wisdom years ago.
Right.
Oh, there was a comment about eight years ago.
Wait until the Greek heats.
What do you mean?
Well, old people are full of truth or the Greek is the terrible comp criticism.
I wait till he turns 50.
I was already past 50.
Right.
Well, I remember that on the old O.N.G.'s.
Yeah, I got responses like that.
People were like, well, what?
Learned elders.
How dare you?
Because they have been through more than you ever have been through.
And, you know, OK.
They've been through more diaper changes at 50.
Shame on them.
You know, then.
Yeah.
So so what's going on, for example, going back to the legal thing, when you hear illegal
all the let me translate that in plain language.
That just means you don't have license to do that.
So but here's the follow through.
Prohibition is prohibited, prohibited, by the way.
There is no prohibition.
Like after the prohibition laws were done on alcohol, it was an amendment to the Constitution
and all that.
And it was reamended, I think.
I think it went up to the Constitution, didn't it?
Yeah, it did.
It was a constitutional amendment.
Yeah.
OK.
So that's why it was repealed.
That's why they say it was repealed, because they actually repeal the amendment.
Yeah.
Right.
Well, what they also did was they also prohibited prohibitions.
That's why you don't hear about prohibitions anymore.
So if they're telling you something is illegal without offering or telling you because due
to failure to have a maintain a license or acquire a license, they're actually not practicing
illegal, convicting you or charging you with illegality.
They're actually charging you with prohibition.
In other words, they're prohibitive.
Right.
So in other words, if someone says that's illegal, what you do is, well, I never was
aware that you were offering a license for it.
So how could it be illegal unless you offer a license for it?
See, yeah, this is pretty advanced, by the way.
The only people I could have a conversation with on this is like a fifteen hundred dollar
an hour attorney or a retired Supreme Court justice.
The regular attorneys don't know anything at all.
I mean, if I if you know an attorney, especially one that's been doing it for more than 20
years and bring up what I just did, he'll he'll flip out.
He'll laugh.
But if you press on him to research it about the same about a year, in about a year, he'll
come back, says, you know, what you're saying is actually correct.
I just never heard of it before.
This is how the I'm giving this as an example, because this is what you're this is what you're
dealing with.
Because remember, the attorneys, attorney generals, they're also operating as if they're
eight years old.
Doesn't matter if they're 70.
Well, because here's the reality about a common thing.
Drug charges.
Right.
When people get charged, you know, for for drug distribution, it's a prohibition.
They're telling you it's illegal.
It's illegal to sell because you don't have a license to do it.
That's what it basically comes down to.
Is that right?
You can get a license.
They don't finish that thought.
They don't finish that.
It's less left open.
You see?
Yeah.
But that's the reality of it is you don't have the right license.
When it comes to legal.
Yeah.
Right.
And lawful.
There is no unlawfulness with that unless you're deliberately doing harm to someone else.
There is no unlawful drug, by the way.
Right.
Not in and of itself.
It doesn't have.
No, there is.
In law, there's never been anything unlawful.
Right.
At all.
Not like like that.
Substances, foods or anything like that.
Right.
Permissible or non permissible in certain case, in certain situations.
So basically the whole legal system is based on you don't have a license to do that.
Like police have a license to kill.
Right.
And they pull that license from them.
It's very complex how they do it.
They will never charge a cop.
If you ever look at these cops, when they get charged for murder, a lot of them recently
have been going to prison for like second degree murder, right.
For shooting a perp.
Yes.
Right.
OK.
If you look at it, it doesn't work the way they show you on TV.
But if you look at how it works, how they do it, they cannot charge him unless they
relieve him of his badge number first.
That's why they're always fired first.
It's not because of the reaction from the community or any of that other stuff.
It's because they have to take that office away from them.
The badge number.
Yeah.
Not the badge.
Just a piece of metal.
They have to separate him from that number, which is a license, which indeed is not because
all police work for the city manager.
And the city manager is bankrupt, just like the city is.
And the city manager is working basically for their creditors.
But basically, I say if you run into a cop, say, hey, how's the city manager doing?
And they go back because they know that they know that it gets drummed out of them after
a while because they have these meetings with the sergeant every day, what they're supposed
to do.
Yeah.
And they don't bring it up, but they will bring up the importance of the city manager.
That was very much like in the commissioner in Batman, you know, it was basically a city
manager.
You know, it was the commissioner or whatever.
So it's all business.
There's no pulley in.
But in law, there is no police in law.
The only time police come around is when someone owns your town and they have a personal interest
in providing their own protection, just like a Wal-Mart, for example.
You'll have a Wal-Mart cop or a security guard on Wal-Mart.
He won't start walking the streets, the neighborhoods, right?
No.
Yeah.
If you if you pick another business that has the rent to cops, you know, they stay within
that area.
Right.
So it's the same thing.
Now, why does Wal-Mart hire a cop actually hiring cops now for a while?
Why do they hire the security?
Because they need the extra security.
They just to protect their property.
It's called loss prevention.
Right.
So that's what the police are there to do.
Loss prevention.
But also at the same time, because they work for the banks, they put out a lot of charges.
So this whole system or systems is based on very, very simple matter.
So I think that through the years, whenever I've gone into Greek speak subjects, I've
always provide within the first few breaths after bringing the subject, what's wrong with
it and why it's wrong, why and then how it could be fixed.
Right.
And basically, when you listen to Greek speak, the way to fix anything really is to just
be silent and non-participatory.
So if you see something heinous going on that you want to stop, don't address it because
it gives it energy because remember, they work both sides.
And we talked about last time.
Don't protest.
Yeah.
And don't protest.
But just withdraw any possible support.
They do it all the time.
They say, we're going to withdraw funding.
Are you outside or do you have an open window, by the way?
No, I'm outside in the birds.
Bird migration.
Yeah.
I was hearing birds chirping.
That's why I was wondering.
OK, sorry.
Yeah.
It's cool.
In the desert, you have bird migration.
Not so much in the back east, I remember, but you have bird migrations and they get
really chirpy, really chatty at night.
Right.
No, I was noticing that.
Yeah, I was just noticing it.
And I was like, wow, it's cool, though.
I mean, it's not distracting.
It's just this like late in the background.
Sure, it's distracting.
It's distracting.
It made you voice about it.
But OK.
The other thing I want to bring up was offensive.
Some people.
OK.
How people take offense.
Not legal offenses.
I'm done with the legal stuff.
Right.
Well, people feel offended.
You know what?
They're too dumb to be offended.
In other words, when people say they were offended, it's part of the training mechanism.
In other words, they heard somewhere like, you have a right to your religion.
And if anyone says anything, it's offensive.
Right.
And so they.
You see, people are too dumb to be genuinely offended.
Yeah.
I find most people that use that phrase that say they're offended have no idea why.
Actually.
Yeah.
It's all pre-packaged.
Because that's offensive.
That's it.
And it's like, well.
But why is it offensive?
Well, because they learned it on TV.
Like, for example, this morning I made a pancake.
Now I don't make pancakes.
I make pan cakes.
You know the difference between pancakes and pan cakes?
No, I don't.
What is it?
OK.
Pancakes are like what you need.
Stacks and all that.
And you get them.
They're not very good.
And people say my grandma makes great pancakes.
Go over to grandma's.
And he's like, oh, I wouldn't use these.
I'll use as a doorstop.
Right.
By the way.
Anyone ever tell you my mom's a good cook or grandma's a good cook?
Bullshit.
They can't cook.
But anyway.
Especially if they're white.
I know.
So, yeah, it's true.
It's just that needs to stop.
And it has stopped.
Because most of them have passed away.
But OK.
The difference between a pancake and a pan cake is the first one most people know about.
They're not that good.
Even if you like them, you know they're not that good.
Right.
But a pan cake is more like a cake.
But it's made in a pan.
But it looks like a pancake.
OK.
It's just delicious.
Why is it delicious?
Because I use almond flour and hard wheat, like a Hungarian high altitude wheat.
OK.
Right.
And other things in it.
And it's really wonderful and moist.
And it's just like a good white sponge cake.
But it looks like a pancake.
OK.
So anyway.
With that, I made.
I had some fried eggs.
And it's funny.
And when I lay the eggs down, people always watch me.
Because when you crack an egg into a pan, most people do it how?
The way they saw it where?
On TV.
And how do they do it?
They got some guy.
And boom.
He breaks the egg.
It's about anywhere between four to six inches off the pan.
Splashes the egg down.
Wrong.
That's not how you do it.
You crack the egg very carefully.
And never do it on a sharp object.
Always on a blunt object to crack it.
And you lower the egg.
Now, if you have asbestos fingers, fingers like asbestos that can take the heat, it's
even better.
You lower the egg into the, as close as you can take to the pan without touching the hot
butter or oil to burn your fingers, as low as possible.
And as slowly as possible, open the shell into the pan or the griddle.
Very slowly open it.
And as low as possible.
And let it flow out.
Right?
You have more control.
And the egg turns out much better.
Now, if you watch most people prepare breakfast, they'll open a fried egg.
They'll drop the egg at a pretty good height.
Right?
Why?
Because they saw it on TV.
And you wouldn't believe.
I've been watching people, including my wife, for a long time.
I'd say about 75 to 90% people around me, the things that they do, they got from TV.
Wow.
And that's one of my criticisms.
I say, you do that like they do it on TV, which is absolutely wrong or deficient.
And it will not give good results.
Why?
Because no matter how good it looks to drop an egg from six or eight inches or two stories
up on a griddle, guess what?
TV uses.
TV magic.
They have what's called editing.
Right.
Then they have the stunt chef in the background make the eggs that they present.
They're not going to present the eggs that you saw the guy drop.
Right?
Well, a lot of them they do right in front of you where it's like the guy's preparing.
He's moving stuff.
He's doing all that for you.
And then he goes, and by the way, it'll turn out like this.
And he grabs a pan from behind him.
Yeah.
Just like I've educated a lot of people with these fixer-up things and stuff that they build
out in the jungle.
I said, that's all done by stuntmen.
Right.
There's actually, it's very well known.
Nothing is real.
Nothing is presented.
Just like the World Trade Center.
Only the people with a TV saw airplanes go into the building.
Everyone else saw the buildings explode.
Right.
So, but how many people know about that event from television and how many people know about
that event because of the boots on the ground?
It's like a million to one.
Yeah.
Right.
So you don't stand a chance.
So again, when you watch someone frying, dropping fried eggs into a pan or a griddle, guess
where they learned that from?
So that's one of the things I want to counter with Greek speak, because one of my criticisms
has been released for the past 10 years is you learn to watch, you do that just like
they do it on TV.
And now most people don't know how to take that.
They'll say, oh, well, thanks because I'm famous.
But no, that's stupid because everyone knows TV is stupid.
Right.
So it's a known fact.
It's very well known.
So.
Again, just about everyone I met, about 70 to 90 percent of what they do, they and say
and say and offends them, they get from TV or they learn from.
Right.
There is no.
It's authentically stupid.
Put it that way.
Right.
So if I can counter that with a few last breaths, I have few, meaning how many breaths I have
left, that would be a better contribution than just having these conversations, even though
I think these conversations have aided many people.
Another thing I want to just suggest is that there's quite a few new people.
By the way, we don't have a big sub subscribership or listenership, but there are quite a few
new people, quite a few.
Right.
And most of them, like I was communicating with someone this morning, he did not know
about lawful timekeeping, barely heard of it.
But he listens to the Sonics now, you know, because he's recent.
So I think Sam has provided on the page or page free to anyone, especially if you're a
sub past events.
And I think you and I did one on how to keep time.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
So what I might do if I do the seminar thing, which I think I have to do the seminar thing
because I have I've been speaking with you and others for such a long time and there's
still a majority of stuff that I just haven't put out because it's not a subject that I
could just bring up and discuss.
It's a subject that I have to bring up.
I have to preface.
I have to inform and then discuss with time in between.
It's kind of like the weather work.
We can talk.
You and I could do three Sonics on weather work.
Right.
OK.
And how to manipulate the weather.
I'm talking about DIY, not about the all the fear mongering stuff about harp and the guy
that winning Dave Whittington talks about the chemtrails and none of that stuff.
Right.
You can't do it in three consecutive Sonics from back to back because you need to give
people that are industrious.
By the way, if you want to do weather work, what I mean by being industrious, you just
walk around your neighborhood and pick up junk that people throw out in a scrap bin.
That's what it seems to have more effect when you find the stuff in the garbage than do
you go out and buy it.
Meaning like a two piece of pipe.
Right.
OK.
Seems to work better.
But I'm only kidding.
It doesn't work better.
Just more satisfying.
Right.
It's more satisfying to find like a four foot piece of pipe in the garbage and you end up
making that a rainmaker.
Well, purchasing something that seems to have been discarded into something useful.
Yeah.
Extremely satisfying.
OK.
So I think giving people time in between weather work at least a week or two or three to practice
on their own and then you could do more of a Q&A and develop it.
Recently, I've gotten positive feedback from someone that I sent a small custom built device
that they've over a year ago now.
And they haven't had much success.
And we finally got into a more detailed discussion.
And he was it was not set up optimally.
They didn't really even though I had gone over these fine points, they didn't get it.
And they were it was not set up optimally.
It was set up.
It wasn't really working that well.
And then once I started discussing the fine points, why we set it up this way, he's been
getting results.
OK.
Right.
So you would think like a 10 degree change in angle the way you angle it would be the
difference between no results and consistent results.
Right.
Makes sense.
Yeah.
So these things are critical.
So a lot of times when I say like 50, I don't know, I don't mean 49 or 51.
I mean, 50.
Right.
If I say 108 degrees, I don't mean 107 or 109.
I mean, 108.
So once you start listening on that level, right, then you'll be more successful.
And I think that can only come through in a didactic context and climate, like a seminar
type thing.
Like I noticed when I did the Scalarator seminar, there was good participation and people were
attentive and what I was going over.
And I went over everything in great detail, step by step.
What precautions, what to expect, what could happen that you shouldn't accept.
Right.
Things like that.
Basically walk through all that and doing something like that on various other things.
Now, we started off talking about wrapping things tightly.
Now, I just wanted to bring it up.
What came up a while back with someone is that they mentioned I said I would address
it on a sonic, which I did.
They had a sore on their leg, lower leg, and they wrapped it tight was getting worse.
Well, that's because the sore was a natural occlusion.
The body wanted to get so if the body wants to exit, it's kind of like barricading the
exit door.
Right.
You don't do that.
You could barricade the entrance door to stop people from coming in.
But not right now.
That's not a good thing, because actually, when you when you wrap a wound tightly, it's
the same thing as putting a patch on a tire.
Right.
You need to prevent the vacuum loss from continuing, because if you don't wrap a wound
tightly.
The body will will clog it up and fill the hole on its own.
You get a lot of swelling, you know, long time feeling.
But if you wrap it tight, the body gets the signal that we've got the vacuum loss taken
care of.
Let's go back to normal.
Right.
OK.
And the body will heal itself because it's epithelial tissue.
Right.
So.
But when the body has a sore, that outbreak, you want to encourage that to to to to dump
out what it be.
Right.
You want it.
You don't want to wrap it tight.
And once it's done doing that, you know, it's done doing what it's supposed to be doing.
Then you could wrap it tight to finish off the healing.
And I think that was the whole thing of the the episode that we the sonic event we spoke
on in the while back.
And that's something I never really covered because I never really thought of mentioning
if you have a sore that is trying to expel something to to encourage it, you know, with
warm, wet compresses and things to have it flow, warm bathing and change of diet.
Right.
So when it's trying to go outward, when it's trying to push something outward, you want
to encourage it.
And when it's not doing that, what you want to do is restore the sealed vacuum as best
you can.
And but the body when the body releases something like that, it already minds the vacuum on
its own.
It's kind of like a balcony on a on a house versus a window that you jump out of.
OK, it's a you could step outside, but you don't right.
You don't falls.
In other words, the body will make a sore and let things step out.
But we will not compromise the vacuum while it's doing that.
Right.
Essentially.
But there still is a compromise in the vacuum.
There still is a compromise.
There's still a break in the skin.
So that has to be repaired.
And as that's being repaired, some things are going to go out.
Some things are going to go in.
The vacuum loss of the body.
What's your first sign?
Mucus, mucus, mucus development.
Right.
Whenever you see mucus development.
And by the way, one way to really send this home, do some basic anatomy.
A pregnant woman holds a baby or whatever trimester.
If you go look at the anatomy of it, of a pregnant woman, the uterus, the bottom of the
uterus, what keeps everything from falling out?
It has.
What's it called?
Mucus plug.
Exactly.
Yeah.
So whenever you develop mucus, even mucus linings, things like that, it is to prevent
vacuum.
But by the way, your colon has a mucus line.
Right.
The entire colon has a mucus lining, but it's a different type of mucus.
So that's why people who do frequent enemas get very, very ill.
These strange diseases.
And they don't know why.
Right.
Because they've cleaned out all the natural.
Yeah.
So.
The.
The aspect of knowing the signaling.
Right.
So when people to little children get sick, they get very typical for children to get
mucus.
Right.
They even it's so typical now that when you go to the pediatric part of a drugstore
or whatever, they sell these little syringes that you stick in the baby's nose, suck
the mucus out.
Right.
That's where the phrase not knows little kid because they constantly.
Yeah.
Because they're constantly eating food that deters, you know, development from, you
know, the body's developing to maintain a vacuum.
Right.
They're eating things that are non-seasonal, you know, from a non-territorial,
non-local.
Look at baby food.
You know, they the brands that put out baby food, they put out a menu and they
serve that same menu wherever you go in the US.
Right.
Yeah.
Pretty much.
Tropical food.
They even have one called tropical fruit.
Well, every time of the year.
Yeah.
There's tropical fruit, but there's plenty of bananas.
Bananas is most common constant.
Doesn't matter what time of year it is or where you are.
And it doesn't matter.
You know.
No.
Yeah.
So they're going to get.
Drink the oranges so you don't get sick in the winter.
Oh, yeah.
Sure.
So, OK, all these things now breaking them down to a point where we can start from
the beginning.
A recap.
Didn't we do a recap recently on something?
What did we do?
Did we do a recap on or not?
We've done it.
Was it the container?
The container.
We did a recap.
Yeah.
I didn't really we didn't really get technical.
I just pretty much ranted on how bad the system is.
And by the way, speaking of bad system is I'm hearing more and more people
passing away like they're totally fine.
Right.
Totally fine.
And then they go for some procedure and they're dead in two weeks.
Yep.
Very common now.
I'm saying these are people that I know.
Right.
And I tell them, oh, don't go there.
They'll die.
And then it's like funny.
You know, it's like two weeks later.
They die.
And I'm like, I told him.
It's like, what the hell?
Yeah.
Yes.
So just I bring that up.
So wherever you are in your circles, watch out for that, too.