Sonic Event 17, here on Ocelli and the Greek Rated Y, and this ought to be, as per usual,
another unusual conversation.
Why is that?
Because you don't get this information anywhere else, because, unfortunately to the Greek's
dismay, there are not others like him out there saying what he's saying.
Anyway, that's where I'll begin this one, Greek.
How are you feeling today?
Well, feeling interesting, because I'll tell you, we just said, is this 17?
And yeah, it's 17, and lawful timekeeping, it's the 17th day of the second month, right?
Interesting.
Now, 15 was done on the 15th of the Pope's work schedule, right?
Right.
So, because there's a four-day lag, or, you know, you can't really, it's really hard to
surmise, let's say, you know, go from Celsius to Fahrenheit, there's no conversion, and
what really makes it difficult is the noon-midnight day start, right?
One lawful is noontime start, the other one is midnight, so you end up not having anything
direct.
But it is, yeah, the 17th day of the second month, when this gets up, hopefully will be
soon enough, not to mess anyone up who's trying to do lawful timekeeping, it appears to be.
Yeah, the whole thing about this, we were just chatting about, you know, I don't get
into anything technical, I try to talk about stuff that's just right in front of everyone,
or easily accessible.
Lawful, you know how I keep redefining what lawful is, it means you don't have to buy
anything, right?
Right.
You don't have to subscribe to someone else's protocol for, you know, whatever.
So I would suggest it being lawful to notice what is around you is just that.
Well, and I'll say this, because you don't automatically notice some things around you,
I don't think that is something to, I don't mean you, Greg, I do mean just the general
you, it is not really your fault, I mean, it's sort of like this is not the way things
are structured for you to notice what's obvious.
So what's interesting to me is when I first started to work with you a bit, you know,
doing the Sonics, it was a little different.
And I said to myself, you know, listening to the information that you were imparting,
I said, okay, this is not what I'm used to hearing at all.
And I don't automatically dismiss things simply because I don't recognize them.
Of course, we talked about recognition in an earlier Sonic, but, you know, on the Rated
Y series here.
But I didn't dismiss it, but I didn't accept it automatically either.
I said to myself, well, let me see what I can observe.
And upon doing that and observing things, I found that I had not fully observed them
in the same way that I had previously.
It's sort of like the whole idea about, well, you've been telling me for probably eight
years personally, okay, about, well, the day begins at solar noon.
Okay, you've been telling me that all this time, it doesn't mean that I really examined
that or attempted to apply it.
Now, I did that recently.
And when I did, it created some changes.
Not just in the way that I was reckoning time, but it created other changes.
And I don't know fully how to articulate that, but it gave me a different sort of orientation
to be able to examine other things.
So it seems to me as though when you change one orientation of your perspective, you alter
everything else after that, right?
So this is, I don't know if I'm setting this up properly for you to knock it down, but
I think so.
No, no.
That's fine.
Seasonal eating is another one.
And then eating clean, Old Testament is another one.
It's a benchmark moment.
Everyone's got their own place that they like to pivot or start from.
They call it the chocolate foot in sports, the foot that you prefer to use, launch or
use first.
And I think in cycling, the one that you put onto the pedals on the cranks first is called
the chocolate foot.
But everyone's got their own way.
And then there's, of course, the time.
Some take a really long, some get it right away, some take a little longer, some never
get it.
But it doesn't matter either way, as long as it makes some change.
Because people are always wondering, when is the change going to come?
Oh boy, what change?
Speaking of which, speaking of change, I mentioned I wanted to do a little bit of a recap on
the crucifixion debacle story thing, whatever.
Right, because that keeps coming up in the chat as well.
Yeah, yeah, that's a really good example, as an example of an example, on how culture
shapes one's mind and thought regarding anything.
And the more important the thing is, the harder it is to change it once you accept it a certain
way, right?
So, one of the things that I always do is, when I discuss it, let's say, it's not whether,
this is not like flat earth, round earth, or any other argument, pro or con or denial.
A lot of people, for example, in the past have said, oh, Greek, you're denying the crucifixion.
And I'm like, well, are you saying that from a point of rational logic and reason?
And he says, yes, you are.
I said, well, in logic and reason, you cannot deny something that doesn't exist or didn't
happen.
In other words, you have to show it exists, right, before you can deny it.
That's why when people call me a Vax Denier, right, or never called me other people, well,
you can't be a Vax Denier because there is no such thing, right?
So anyway, what's interesting about it is, when I bring up and broach this topic and more
than broach the topic, let's say, get into it, I don't give specifics.
Why?
Because when you hear people sounding off reference points in the Bible, to me, it always
left such a bad taste in my mouth.
Even when I thought the Bible was written by Shakespeare, I had not read it.
I just went along.
I was comfortable with what some respectful person said, and I was just happy with that.
I didn't feel like reading it, so I just said, you know, whatever.
But then when I read it, I discovered, just like anything else, if you read any reference
material on any subject, you'll find that it's very contrasting to what you were told.
Any reference material, by the way.
So again, back to the story here.
Whenever I heard anyone citing verses from a Bible, you know what it sounded like to me?
Like that jingle, McDonald's, I think, two old beef patties, special sauce, sesame seed
bun.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
You know that tempo?
Yeah, I know the tempo.
You know, I don't have that memorized, but I recognize it when I hear it, for sure, yeah.
You recognize the tempo, right, of a jingle.
So when people mouth off these, you know, this is in the Bible, blah, blah, blah, blah,
I was like, oh my gosh, I never want to do that publicly.
I never.
Okay, so this is semi-public, not public, whatever.
I wouldn't consider it to be public.
So guess what the Greek is going to do?
I'm going to read some Bible verses.
Okay.
It's the Bible guru going to read some Bible verses.
That cracks me up, by the way.
I love that from the Skype call you referenced.
What was it, last Sonic or the Sonic before?
Yeah, the conference call.
Yeah, I would refer to the Bible guru.
I love the Bible guru.
You know, oh boy.
Okay, so.
Now, he may indeed love you, by the way.
I mean, that may be a legitimate, he actually loves you and the sound you make.
He might really, truly love that, you know?
I mean, oh my gosh, I'm sorry, guys.
Yeah, yeah, I really like keeping to myself, but, okay.
All right, so I've also mentioned, let me just preface this, it is a chronological, it's
not a chronographic, it can be considered a chronographic book, but as you go further
down into the text, it gets more and more advanced.
So let's say, you've heard that back in the, quote unquote, American colonial days, they
used the Bible as a form of education, right?
In single room, right?
Schoolhouses.
It was a math, the three R's, read and write and arithmetic.
And simple, look, simple sort of pragmatic reasoning was that it was one of the most
printed books, therefore very accessible, you could afford one, et cetera.
So of course, there were Bibles around.
Yeah, or you already had one, you didn't have to buy a textbook.
That's it, right.
Yep.
So it was very economic.
All right, so as we go further down, and I realize this actually from contrasting that
aspect of the Bible as an educational tool back in the days, with actually what's going
on in the Bible.
So I've always situated myself, and I, since the beginning, I realized that by the time
you get to what's called the New Testament, you've graduated from high school.
And the New Testament is graduate studies, basically.
And as you get further down, it gets to doctorate level graduate studies.
So I'm going to bring up some stuff on that level, which is the writings of Paul and others
around that time, Shaul.
By the way, I recently received a very beautiful hardbound Aramaic New Testament.
So thank you very much.
So I'm going to read something that's from the Book of Acts.
I didn't go through and see what kind of filtering or if the translation is correct, but I did
read it in Greek about a week ago.
And I'm looking at the English, and it's pretty close.
So we'll just, and I haven't studied it in Aramaic, but it's pretty, I looked at any
kind of major change, but it is stoning.
What did I just say?
Okay.
So if you go to the Book of Acts, Chapter 14, between the verses of 19 and 22, and this
is, I believe, a King James Version, then some Jews, which I would say Judeans, came
from Antioch and Iconium and won the crowd over.
They stoned Paul and dragged him outside the city, thinking he was dead.
Okay.
So we have a situation in the Book of Acts.
Now, a few years later, or more than a few years later, in the writings of Paul, in the
Book of Galatians, which is actually a very pivotal book, because, well, actually, I'll
just say it without, it's another can of worms here, the laws in the Bible were never done
away with, and if you read the Book of Galatians, it's very clear, right?
But if you go to Galatians, Chapter 6, Verse 17, he says, these are a lot of context, but
I'm just reading the verse, so if you want the context, you could read the chapter.
But the verses are contextual to what I'm showing here.
So Galatians, Chapter 6, Verse 17.
From henceforth let no man trouble me, for I bear on my body the marks of our Mashiach
Yahshua, says Lord Jesus.
Okay.
Okay, so let me just put these together one more time.
Acts 14, 1922, Then some Jews came from Antioch and Iconium, and won the crowd over.
They stoned Paul, and dragged him outside the city, thinking he was dead.
Paul is the author of Galatians, Chapter 6, Verse 17.
From henceforth let no man trouble me, for I bear on my body the marks of our Yahshua
Mashiach.
Okay.
Okay?
So, all right.
When stoning takes place, you want to kill someone, and it's usually, it's capital punishment,
and it's usually violent.
People get all worked up, and you have a barrage of stones coming at you, hit you in the face,
some hit you square, some don't.
They're going to leave a mark.
Certainly.
Yep.
Some people are blinded from it.
Other people, you know, you could lose a jaw, if the stone is big enough, it'll tear your
jaw right off.
Okay, so he had obviously been stoned to the point where he was unconscious, and they thought
he was dead.
So they had a clear, pretty good, clear shot of what you would visibly see on his body,
meaning hands, face, neck, head, and here he says, look how I bear the marks of Yahshua
Mashiach.
Right.
Or he says, Lord, J-E-S-U-S.
All right, so in this society, people wouldn't recognize what surviving a stoning would look
like, but back then they did.
So I just wanted to bring that up.
These are little, he doesn't say I bear the marks of stoning on my body, he just says
I bear the same marks as Yahshua Mashiach.
Right.
Right?
You see?
So it's kind of like back in the day, I remember a Vietnam vet showing a bullet wound.
It just looks like a little, you can barely, if it's clear through, it's just like a puck
mark on a scar.
A dent.
Yeah.
And the guy, I remember this really tall guy who had a glass eye, he was in a shootout
in the ghetto.
He says, look, I've got them too.
Right?
So one guy got it from Nam, the other guy got it from living in Brooklyn.
Similar marks, though.
Well, let me ask you a question about this, though, because I already hear an argument
in the back of my head that probably somebody could make, and I'm just curious.
And I'm not trying to argue with you, because I think you're correct, but here's the thing.
Bearing those marks, could that not be that he's bearing those marks because he is a follower
of the same?
So therefore, that's the marks you get from being that follower?
No?
Nope, nope.
It's not a ritualistic thing.
Okay.
Actually, they were forbidden in law.
You're not supposed to mark your body in any way.
Don't make me read it in context.
No, no, no.
It's just a matter of...
No, I'm just joking.
The full context is very slight, slightly relevant to it.
He gets into talking about bearing the stake of the Christ and circumcision and uncircumcision,
what counts in Israel and Elohim and all this other stuff, and then he's pleading with the
crowd here.
Well, actually, he's pleading.
He's trying to make...
It's a sermon, actually, is what it is, but it's very egocentric.
It's about his perspective and his accomplishments that he expects others to make.
That's why he brings up the marks on his body.
Well, see, but that's the thing.
You wouldn't voluntarily get the marks from stoning, so you bear them because they are
there.
You might show them.
No, because he survived it.
You survived them, right.
And people do that when they're scarred.
Okay.
Right.
It used to be...
Well, here, let me just...
This is the point why I brought this up.
Sure.
Because I could spend literally a very long sonic showing all of the verses that I have
found that I believe are pertinent without reading into it what I want it to mean, but
reading out of it.
It's very simple.
And there are no less than 50 verses from the Old Testament all the way through the
New Testament that refer to the Judeans handling and being responsible for the capital punishment
of the Christ and the methodology and the things that you should be aware of, all the
way to the almond tree, right, even in symbolism.
Nowhere does it say at any point, the sky is blue, like in a science book, right?
But you should surmise...
By the way, they don't.
If you ask a PhD physicist or a naturalist or anyone in university why the sky is blue,
they tell you it's because it reflects the blue from the ocean.
Anyway, yeah.
So there are so many hints towards this that are supposed to be the framework for what
happens.
And I just wanted to bring this up because this is something, as you progress towards
the graduate level study, right?
Remember, this is the Book of Galatians, so this is like master's degree, PhD thesis type
stuff, right?
On that level.
So you have to be very well grounded in all of the rest of it that is clearly in the proximity
of the Judean culture, you see, not the Roman culture.
So what's interesting about all of this is how much information can be given through
so many hints, right?
Because what I'm suggesting here is that even if you have a very firm statement, like the
crucifixion is very firm in the King James translation, all the English translations,
they make it very firm, as if they emphasize that word crucifixion, and then immediately
dangles something in front of you.
This is what it is, right?
And they show you the symbol, right?
So this is a very, very, very strong, strong propaganda effort that's been made for a very
long time.
The interesting thing also, if you understand the setting here with Paul, by that time,
meaning mid-first century, there was already a tremendous movement in messiahship, people
claiming to be the messiah, right?
And the crucifixion being confused with what happened, and crucifixions, by the way, are
torture vices, they're not capital punishment, ever.
Capital punishment, by the way, in Rome was beheading.
You could look this up.
It's just beheading.
It's the other anomaly.
If you were to be condemned to capital punishment, they just cut your head off in Rome.
They don't nail you to a crucifix.
The most popular application of the crucifixion in Roman culture was to slaves, disobedient
slaves and revolutionary slaves, like the Spartacus story, right?
Sort of like that.
So understanding that.
But here's the interesting part about the whole thing.
Everything is like this to a certain degree.
I compare what's going on with the crucifixion debacle or story that's been put on people
with 9-11 very firmly.
It's almost an identical plot narrative, right?
One, being pragmatic, 9-11 was just a textbook nuclear demolition.
There actually was a website called nucleardemolition.com, and it comes up and it goes away, it comes
up and it goes away.
So if you have a big structure and you want to take it down safely, you know, we have
all the licensing and approvals and all that.
Okay, anyway, with examples on how it's going to work.
But we're told it's something else, right?
It's so radically different, but it still sounds appealing and plausible, right?
And it seems like the people who believe the 9-11 narrative, whatever it might be or was,
are very, very relaxed and comfortable about it.
The same thing with people that are happy with Christmas and the crucifixion and Easter.
They're very, very relaxed about it.
It's like, don't shake my tree.
Here's the other thing.
There's a guy named Dr. Ernest Martin, Ernest L. Martin, and in one of his books, I think
I might have it somewhere here, I haven't read it, but if you look up Ernest L. Martin,
he talks about the Christ was not crucified, he was death by lapidation.
He doesn't like using the word stoning too much, but lapidation is the technical term.
Now, what's interesting about someone like him who is trying to make a living on selling
books to quote unquote Christians or whatever he did, he's passed now.
He was an offshoot of the Armstrong movement, whatever his name was, Wide World Church of
God and all this other stuff, the splintered group or whatever.
When that church grew very large in Pasadena, I think California, back in the 60s and 70s,
they were shut down by the Attorney General because they were telling people, if you're
a Christian, you shouldn't vote.
God chooses your leaders.
Anyway, there were many reasons.
They were just getting really, they were growing very fast.
Most of them hightailed it here to Tucson to leave California.
So when I moved here and I started getting interested in biblical studies, I ran into
one of the men that was, more than one, and that was part of that movement from the 1960s
and on.
And when I brought up, you know, even Ernest Martin, who was part of this group, states
lapidation, stoning, he says, yeah, but, you know, we can't really stress that because
if we stress that, no one will buy our books.
Ah, okay.
And when it came to lawful timekeeping, oh, what you're saying is going to divide us.
No one will listen to us.
Nothing like, oh, Greek, let's look at what you're saying, if it's true or not.
No, no, no, no.
All self-interest, you know, I understand it.
I totally understand it, right?
But that's not me, though, right?
So I just wanted to bring up the point again, just maybe to wrap up on the crucifixion stoning
thing.
If you look at those that are known to be, let's say, very academic in the field of biblical
study, especially the New Testament, well, when you say biblical study, unless you're,
excuse me, going to a Judean side, which the Judean side, if you're a biblical student,
also they do, unless it's very orthodox, let's say, will also study the New Testament.
I have yet to find any academic at all, in private, that would not agree that it was
a stoning, with the caveat to himself in the conversation, but we can't really talk about
that, or it doesn't really matter overall.
Very, very interesting.
So, yeah, and that's what I've got to say about that.
Well, there you go, I mean, I've encountered the it-doesn't-really-matter answer before.
Right.
Well, it's a series of things, it's not only that.
It's a series of properly identifying, like, let's go back to 9-11.
How many Osama bin Laden's are there?
How many times did he die?
How many times was he killed, right?
But there's only, will the real Osama bin Laden please stand up kind of thing, right?
Remember, there was a show like that, Will the Real Whatever Please Stand Up, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, so everything is just misidentification out there.
Well, there was a TV show called To Tell the Truth, which was pretty funny, where that
was the end of it, right?
There was three people would say they were the same guy, and then that would happen,
and then, of course, that's sort of a cultural trope, actually.
Yeah.
And even Eminem used it, right?
Yeah, there you go.
So the thing is, if you're going to invest something as important as, quote-unquote,
your faith to the faith, because it's not faith, it's the faith, don't you want to have
your identification correct?
I mean, if you're going to invest in something, don't you put it in a lockbox?
Don't you want to have the key or the combination to your own lockbox?
Yeah.
Right?
It's pretty interesting.
So, yeah, and by the way, you're not going to win people over talking this way, by the
way.
No, that's a guarantee.
No one's going to come rushing over.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's a guarantee.
You do not win friends with this.
No.
Or a following, by the way, because it displaces the entire center of gravity of everything
that people think and know about Christianity.
The same thing with the nuclear demolition, right?
And here's the thing that's real interesting.
How many people are silent?
You know, like 9-11, for example, there are thousands of people involved in orchestrating
that.
Thousands.
Maybe tens, I wouldn't say tens of thousands, but pretty close.
How many come out and, you know, are speaking?
None.
Right?
Very few.
The same thing with this.
Same thing with...
I always found to use 9-11 and the biblical Christ as quite the parallel.
And we've covered, you know, like, for example, in the Exodus, you know, when they crossed
the Sea of Reeds, not the Red Sea, the Sea of Reeds, they walked on it as if it was dry
land, right?
And it's not like the movie where they're walking on the bottom.
I don't know.
You ever walked on a dredged lake, right?
Well, you go knee deep in the silt and the sludge, right?
So, yeah.
So, anyway, and the book states very clearly that when the pharaoh tried to cross in the
morning, in the morning, when the sun is out, basically stated, that he fell to the bottom
like stone.
He fell to the bottom like lead.
Well, if they're walking on the bottom, how can he fall to the bottom if he's already
on the bottom?
Yeah, right.
I mean, this is another thing that will really get people, get their ire going.
They'll be like, Greek, you're nuts, man.
We saw it in the movie.
You know?
I was like, okay, yeah.
Yeah.
So, things are radically, radically different.
Speaking of radically different, one of the other things we spoke about in the recent
Sonic was hygiene.
And I didn't even mention that people should wash their bum.
I didn't even mention that, right?
No, we didn't get into the washing very much.
No, we talked about a great many other things.
You gave a great many interesting hints about how to properly clean a few things.
Yeah, sort of.
But we didn't get there.
It's perspective.
Remember, okay, by the way, wash your bum if you're, you know, if you're listening.
Yeah, it's very important, but there's an order to it.
From the top down, face, armpits, groin, feet, right?
Why am I saying this?
Camping in the desert.
If you're active, you're going to need a gallon of water a day for drinking, right?
Because of respiration and evaporation, okay?
You still want to wash.
They have these little screw bottle tops you put on a 28-millimeter bottle, you know, the basic water bottles.
Right.
With lots of little tiny holes in there.
They're like, you know, number 30 holes, really small.
32 ounces, 24 to 32-ounce bottle that you leave in the sun to get hot, by the way.
You take a nice hot shower.
It's plenty, believe it or not.
A 32-ounce shower.
I call it a bottle bath.
And just leave the bottle in the sun.
It gets really almost hot to the touch.
Put it in a bag.
Keep it warm.
You know, you want to wash before the sun goes down.
32 ounces will do it, but you got to have a very fine spray.
We're not talking about, you know, let's say dumping, decanting the bottle.
You know, you have one of these, you know, the bottle cap's got like 100 tiny holes drilled in it, right?
So it's a very fine spray when you squeeze the bottle.
Yeah, I've only been able to accomplish that by hand with a gallon, honestly.
But that's because the holes are larger.
No, no, large holes.
The holes are larger.
Use the point of something and just kind of, you know, poke holes.
Oh, gotcha.
Yeah.
Well, you could use a needle, a hot needle, and spend about 15 minutes putting as many holes as possible.
Finer the spray, the better.
And just like the shower states, it starts, you know, gravity, let's say, guides it
so you got head, face, then armpits, then groin, then feet.
The feet is kind of de facto.
If you're standing there and the water's running, even running off, you're going to get your feet clean.
But that's basically it.
There's something in the old nurse's handbook when patients were brought in,
this is from the 1800s up until the early 1900s, it was all based on hygiene.
Even the success of surgeries and childbearing and recovery, convalescence, was all based on hygiene.
What they stated was when a new patient came in and they were going to be in a bed,
that the nurses first had to examine them for lice, and some people might laugh about that,
but that still is a problem, by the way, in public schools.
You might even see in some newspaper articles there's a lice breakout, right?
Even these days.
Right, still, yes.
Yep.
So they examine for that, and if there's any question, the hair is cut to a quarter of an inch or less.
The next thing they do, or while that's happening, is fingernails are trimmed to remove any debris or matter that's under the fingernails.
Right?
Right.
So down where there's no cuticle, well, there's no overlap on the finger.
And then they're washed from the waist down thoroughly, and the toenails are also clipped and feet are washed.
I think they even say with the feet you add a small amount of iodine to the water, and this is before the iodine was colored red.
Dyed red.
The reason they dye things like that is so you don't use them internally or other things.
They say, oh, so the doctor can see where he's putting it on.
No, no, because they know it has properties that for some in the right combination would be, quote, unquote, a miracle cure kind of thing.
Right?
So they deliberately adulterate things.
So this is just like a hint that when I read that, I was like, wow, I've seen people go into a hospital,
and they don't trim their fingernails or cut their hair, and they're just sitting there with antiseptics sprayed in the air or whatever.
So hygiene gets down to that point where ultimately in old days when you acquired people as property, you basically shaved all their bodily hair off to start fresh.
Right.
So, yeah, interesting stuff from that perspective.
But I did not get into just the direct washing, and the reason why I didn't, I guess, is because it's obvious.
Right?
Maybe it's obvious enough.
It should be, yeah.
Yeah.
One of the questions that was interesting from Vandy was about being in balance.
What's interesting is I did bring up, like, for example, I think it was E. coli.
It's not the bug that hurts you.
It's what the bug eats and gives off that hurts you.
Right.
From almost a chemical aspect.
That balance is maintained, again, by induction.
If you have anything in a high population, by the way, all these bugs are found in the body already.
It's when they, what would you call when something gets out of hand, when too much of something, right?
Overwhelms.
Yeah, overpopulation of it is when you have the problem.
But the balance is upset thusly, because since I brought up the E. coli, typically E. coli you'll find it in natural form.
It grows on the surface of flesh where the dermis has been removed.
It doesn't grow on the dermis, only on the muscle tissue when it's exposed.
So let's say you get a steak, right, from beef muscle and you leave it exposed.
E. coli through induction and through, I guess you might call it biogenesis, starts to appear just like amoebas appear in grass when it's in water on the surface of the meat in very, very small amounts.
And typically the meat will be, at that point as the E. coli population starts to increase, the meat will be prepared for eating.
Maybe a salt bath, maybe it'll be baked, grilled or fried, right?
And that eliminates the E. coli on the surface then.
It keeps the balance very low.
You're not going to get too much induction from that after it's been cured.
Cured and cooked, yeah.
Cured and cooked or cured or cooked, right?
Because the curing, the salt, the brine, all this other stuff and spices will retard the growth.
Right.
Typically when you have these E. coli breakouts, it's from ground beef.
Because if you've ever seen how ground beef is done, they put all the steaks or meat cuts on a tray and there's a big grinder, meat grinder that they feed it into, right?
Little by little and get whatever mix they want or prescribe.
Now what happens if that meat is not treated well or eaten quickly or not kept at a low enough temperature, remember all the meat that was fed into the grinder already has the E. coli growing on the surface.
But now that you ground it, now it's on the inside.
Now it's mixed in the meat.
It's all over the place.
It's not just on the surface.
It's everywhere.
Right.
And not only that, when you're done grinding the meat, you have a big lump of ground meat that now you have more E. coli growing on the surface.
And you've got it growing inside.
Okay.
So you start out with some on the surface.
Now you mix that in.
So it's in.
It's out.
It's in the center.
It's on the side.
And now this new surface that has come together develops more.
Okay.
It makes perfect sense.
Yeah.
That's why typically they say you shouldn't eat ground beef out rare.
Right.
Yeah, it should be well done or whatever, unless precautions are taken.
A lot of salt is used in the area, so on and so forth.
So what I'm giving here is an example of a form of balance.
I would say the situation first where it's just on the surface and the meat is prepared either with salt or brine or thrown on the grill or fried or whatever, it's in balance with what we can handle.
Right?
Right.
It's also sort of in balance if you grind it into the meat and once it's ground in, it's kept at a low enough temperature so more won't grow or, of course, it's cooked and treated again in sausage or whatever.
But when it gets out of balance is when you don't treat the ground meat well and it keeps growing again, but now you've got a double whammy because it's mixed in.
It's not just on the surface.
Right.
So this is where your imbalance happens when you understand, let's say, the terrain or the environment, and it all happens by induction.
Because if you eat that ground beef that, let's say, is tainted and the vermin is found in the blood, for example, it's usually found in the stool is where they do a stool test.
But if it's in the blood, your body starts to create these guys in larger numbers, and it's much harder than if it just stayed in the stool.
Right.
You know what I mean?
And it wasn't inducted.
And then you're really out of whack, as they say.
Right.
And in that case, then you have to be more extreme.
Now, one thing I hearken to is macrobiotics, the Yin and Yang principle.
I don't lean on it too heavily because people think I'm pushing Asian or Oriental philosophy or science on them.
But unfortunately, it's the, quote, unquote, Oriental side of this philosophy, let's say, or process has been preserved there.
It has not been preserved very well in the Western sector of the world.
Right.
But to lean on that, understanding Yin and Yang, one day we'll probably get into it.
Maybe we'll get into it a little bit now because it does pertain, because that has to do with balance.
Now, Yin is considered soft, expansive.
Right.
And Yang is considered hard and contractive.
And this is typically when you're just looking at objects in the room or foodstuffs.
But when you start moving into the energies, the non-tangible Yin and Yang, it gets really complicated quickly.
Because when you have, for example, an energy or a condition known as cold, that is very Yin.
But when you affect something with a lot of cold, let's say a piece of meat that's soft, does it become more Yin?
Or does it become the opposite?
It becomes Yang.
Because when you start chilling meat more and more, it doesn't get softer.
No, it gets harder.
It gets harder.
Well, it gets harder.
So a very Yin force like cold will freeze things and make them harder.
Even a piece of metal is harder when the temperature goes down.
Right.
As the temperature rises, the metal gets softer.
So the Yin, let's call it a force, because it's a force in motion also.
If it stops moving, it's no longer an energy.
It has manifested.
It's arrived.
Right.
So cold, which is Yin, will turn things Yang.
Now, heat, fire, is very Yang.
But it makes things Yin.
Let's go back to, let's say, a piece of metal.
We have a really hard piece of metal.
And we're going to put a Yang energy on it, which is fire.
We keep heating it, keep heating it, keep heating it.
What happens to that metal?
Does it get harder because it's being hit with Yang energy?
No.
It goes the opposite.
It gets softer and softer until it melts.
You see how it works?
Yeah.
It leads to two really interesting questions.
And I'm not sure if this is the appropriate time to ask them.
But I'll throw them there anyway.
One thing is, look, at a certain point, yeah, things get softer.
But they also become more difficult to manage and more difficult to be contained.
Because, okay, a soft piece of metal, you can pick it up, you can bend it,
yeah, it becomes malleable, right?
Well, it depends on what level of Yin it is.
Like if you're working with copper, 80 degrees, 85 degrees is an excellent,
you know, for hammering copper, you know, shape it.
Oh, yeah, you can begin to shape it there.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah.
But if you go higher in temperature, it gets harder again.
Right.
You have to go then much higher for it to soften again.
So everything has its zone where it fights back.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's what I was going to ask about it fighting back and forth,
because there's that that goes on.
Yeah, go ahead.
They call them latent points, you know, like the water has that at 98.6.
If you look at a graph of as you add equal amounts of heat to a given amount of volume of water,
you'll notice that the temperature and the expansion of the water is pretty linear.
The graph shows at 45 degrees.
As you add more temperature, the water keeps expanding very evenly.
But once you get to about 98, 98.6, it bottoms out.
You keep adding heat, the water does not expand.
Keep adding more heat, the water's still not expanding for quite a while.
And then you add, once you get to a certain point of heat again, it starts expanding again.
Isn't that an interesting coincidence?
Mm-hmm.
Right?
No, it's interesting.
But I'm just saying there's a certain difference in resistance that's not exact to, like,
it's not like, okay, so every 10 degrees you go up, you're going to get.
It's not linear.
Everything based on its melting point will have a resonance going backwards on where
it will have a point where it's not linear.
Right.
And that gets a little more complicated.
But what I wanted to state, ultimately, when you're speaking of balance in the human body,
the yin is the life force.
So when you're eating food, you could have food that's yin and food that's yang, right?
Like meat would be yang and sweets and sugars would be considered yin, right?
But all of it, all of your intake, all of your food and water and breathing is actually
you're feeding the yin part of the body.
Yin is where the life is, the motion.
See, when you're alive, you're soft and you can move around a lot, right?
Right.
But when you're not alive, you're typically not that soft.
You dry up like a mummy, right, and you're not moving.
Right.
So yin is motion.
Okay.
You can move anywhere you want, pretty much.
So there's the yang component in the body which protects the yin.
So it would be the energetic armor, the energetic field.
Very much like a yang expression would be, let's say you're having a conversation with
someone and they're joking around and they fake a punch and you flinch and try to defend
yourself, right, without even thinking about it, right?
Right.
You pretty much do it automatically.
That's the yang being triggered in the body to protect the body, right?
Okay.
Even if you're just playing around.
Sure, sure.
So it also works all the way to death.
I've always given, maybe I'll give the example now.
When you work with people on health matters and things like that, you always get the grandma
that's really ill and she's in hospital or hospice, right?
Yes.
You always get that story.
Sure.
Or parent.
And they're in there for weeks and weeks and months and months.
They try all kinds of stuff and really the person is quite old and they've really, let's
say, not considered these things and there are protocols that the allopathic medicine
people say they should do.
So there's really no helping them.
But you get a call and they're getting worse and worse and worse.
And the call is, they're calling everyone and all the friends and relatives to come visit
grandma because she's sitting up in bed after three months in hospice.
She's sitting up in bed.
She's bright and alert.
And she's so alert and so physically well, she can get up and walk around a little bit
that they think they're going to take her home.
It's a miracle.
Well, yeah, it's a weird thing.
It's often done and they say it's a good thing to go do that because...
Yeah, but let me hear this out.
Well, they do it for the outside perspective really fast all the time because let's just
say it's your grandma, Greek.
They'd want you to come there and do that because they'd say to you, look, it's good
for you to see her like this to remember her like this.
Sure, sure.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, I got it.
From a compassion.
But I'm getting this call also.
Right.
So my question, this is Yin and Yang now.
My question is, how is her skin tone?
Does it look like you remember her or does she look really, really shiny like you rubbed
her down with Vaseline?
She goes, oh, Greek, you know, she does look really shiny like you rubbed her down with
Vaseline.
How do you know?
I said, well, she's probably going to be, whatever you're going to do, do it with her
now because she probably will pass in the next few hours or by morning.
And you're like, Greek, how dare you say that?
You asshole, bye.
Right?
Yeah.
And guess what happens?
Okay, what's going on?
As this person is laying in bed getting worse and worse and worse and worse, the Yin is
leaving the body.
The Yang is still there.
So the first thing that leaves is the Yin.
The last thing that leaves is the Yang.
Yin is spread out, soft, malleable.
Yang is hard and focused.
So this person, all their Yin is being drained out of their body for weeks and months.
And when all the Yin is just about gone, because a little bit Yin is left to perform
the exiting of the Yang, because the Yang can't do it on its own.
If it's just Yang, you're just a mummy.
You're just as stiff like a twig.
So a little bit of Yin is in reserve to allow the Yang to escape the body.
So what happens is Yang is focused, very directed, energetic, upright.
So when all the Yin is gone, the Yang says, it's my time to go also.
That part of the energy field.
And what happens?
It manifests all of its glory.
The person is, what is Yang?
Upright, firm, directed.
What does the person do?
Sits upright, firm, directed, very clear, right?
Okay, so.
What I always note at that time, because I've been called in for these kind of things as
well, is a very hard, fixed, very solid focus.
The eyes are very focused at this time.
And although people tell me I'm absolutely crazy for seeing this, I do see it.
There is a bit of light which comes from the eye.
Literally, some people notice it, but it's a subconscious thing.
They don't literally see light, but they say their eyes are lit up.
Yeah, exactly.
The body, the Yang, which is light, by the way.
The most Yang light would be a laser beam.
So it would be like a laser beam focus.
Yeah.
It's a very solid, fixed focus that comes from the eyes at that time, which would be
uncharacteristic of recent events.
Their eyes are not fixed.
They're wandering around.
People talk about eyes rolling around in their head.
They use different descriptions.
But the truth is that when you see this person sitting up, and all of a sudden, a lot of
people see it as, oh, this is a great improvement.
And I go, no, that is the indicator that...
It's the last call.
That's the last bit of strength.
And it literally, I can see light.
So I know it's, I don't know how to describe it, but I see a bit of light.
Well, that's where the oily, the Vaseline-coated skin look comes from.
And if you touch the skin, by the way, it's not oily at all.
But they look really, really shiny.
Even if grandma's got completely wrinkled up, not a smooth surface on her face, it will
look really, really shiny.
Because the skin, being the most yin organ in the body, is now completely depleted.
The body's completely depleted of yin.
And it's asking the skin, please produce, you're the most yin, give us some of your
yin.
And the skin says, no, I'm going to just produce what I do normally, all my normal
functions, which is produce all these oils and urea and all that.
But what's interesting, the intensity of the material that's produced on the skin
at this point does not feel oily to the touch or sticky, but it takes on this very
high sheen, almost as if it's, when something is shiny, it reflects a lot more
light also, you see.
So for some reason, the skin gets very shiny, in almost all cases.
So this is how life ends.
For another example, shallow breathing is very yin.
A sharp breath or an exhale is yang.
When someone passes, sometimes their last breath is a pretty strong inhale or exhale.
I've been around when someone passed and it was just shallow all the way down.
So this is not something true for every case, but it's something to be aware of.
There's a lot of factors that can come in regarding the breath.
But the nature of it and the outward appearance, I don't think is what's actually,
you're not actually observing how it's really going.
You know what I mean?
I brought this up because it's a perfect example for how the yin and yang interact
in the body in terms of balance, because the question in the chat was regarding
balance, and I gave, let's say, the quote-unquote story about how the E. coli
worked in the body, being out of balance through induction.
And then ultimately, balance is the balance of these two forces.
But what happens when something goes out of balance means that one of them is missing.
Just like in a storm, what defines a hurricane is you have two arms that are counter-rotating.
If you eliminate one of the arms, it's not a hurricane now.
It's just one arm. It's just a storm, right?
Yeah, it's a storm. It's a strong wind in one direction.
Yeah, you need both arms to make, okay, so the balance to a hurricane is extremely balanced.
That's why when I did weather work, notably, I chased hurricanes and eliminated them.
I had about 3,000 to 5,000-mile range, a very confident 75% chance of elimination of a hurricane.
And I developed a method, went back and forth with Trevor James Constable.
I said, look, he was like, aim at the eye, and I was like, no,
I'm just going to take out one of the arms because if one of the arms goes out, then it's no longer a hurricane.
He's a brilliant idea.
And that was my methodology instead of going for the eye.
But the balance, again, it's just a balancing there.
So in this case, the yin, one part of the balancing act has to go first.
Very rarely do they both go together.
They can.
This goes with every system of health, by the way.
For example, what I state, I've been using this as an analogy.
I discovered this in the 1980s.
Where you have socialized medicine that had a union-based platform for the socialism, where they were allowed to strike,
well, the doctors were socialists.
You made more as a bellhop at a Hilton hotel than you did as a surgeon, right, in some countries back in the day and probably still now.
Well, when the doctors went on strike, the morgues were empty.
People stopped dying.
And when the doctors went back to work, the morgues started filling up again.
So there was a direct correlation between an active medical community, meaning medical technicians, and a steady flow at the morgue.
Now, some people might say, just like the crucifixion, well, Greek, I want to argue that maybe where the ambulance workers and the drivers also.
Oh, so maybe the bodies were happening, but nobody was picking them up, kind of argument.
Yeah, I said, look, if the strike is more than three days, you're going to put them in a cab to take them to the morgue.
Yeah, nobody's going to, right.
Yeah, you're not going to, yeah.
If Grandma dies in the house, you might keep her until the next day, but you ain't keeping her past that.
You're going to find a way to get mobile.
Yeah, so it's amazing what I've heard through the years.
That's why it's like, I don't argue.
I say, you want to argue with me so you could win?
And they're like, yeah, of course.
Oh, you won already.
Oh, you can't do that.
You have to.
No, I just did.
Leave me alone, please.
I got better things to do, like sleep.
Yeah, so there's a direct correlation between all of these things.
You could look at, all right, what is the balance here, what the doctors are doing?
They're pretty much destroying your yin is what they're doing with all of the drugs and all that.
So the body's yang is always last to leave.
And what's interesting, when you look at with their methodologies, you ever notice or heard protocols,
when someone is dying from treatment that they give, they try to resuscitate them with adrenalines and amphetamines,
just stuff that wakes you uppers, right?
Right.
Oh, that'll bring them back, right?
So even they're using the same principle in their wackadoo system.
Right.
Because, look, they inject people for chemotherapy, they get water from the toilet at Chernobyl,
and they inject it into your body, right?
And when you pass out from that, they inject you with amphetamines or adrenaline, right, the yang.
So it's kind of hard to escape the balancing.
Because they're still working within this confine of this environment, this universe, this simulation,
the current medical system.
So if you want to just look at, let's say, natural causes or the causes through the Western medicine,
which, by the way, the Eastern world is also adopting, it's still the same.
You could see when someone is dying from their treatment, they apply yang principles in the end.
Very interesting.
So the balancing act is what it is.
But once you understand induction, you start to go more into the finer realm,
which is actually, the finer realm is what makes everything.
So once you start, I call it the formative zone, where all things are formed,
once you start delving there and knowing what's going on,
then you will develop a sensitivity and a sensibility for it, right?
Because you have to be sensitive, because it's not in your face,
it's not something you could put in a jar, close the lid.
And then you have the sensibility, right?
Like, for example, a sensibility would be like, oh yeah, there's a quote-unquote airborne virus,
let's just put on a dust mask, that'll help us, right?
That's not sensible, right?
So the sensitivity and the sensibility.
By the way, when it comes to pandemics, real ones, I think I'm just going to do a quick repeat.
If the water is cut off and the sewer lines are not working,
so what I mean by water is cut off, the taps don't work,
and you have trucks bringing, tanker trucks bringing water to people,
and they're standing out in the street with pots and pans to get water, right?
Like Flint, Michigan, but, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, kind of.
Or, and the sewers don't work, in other words, you're driving down the street,
and here's a manhole cover and all this fecal matter is coming out of the manhole cover,
all over the street, right?
Right.
Kind of like if you ever go to a rainstorm in Mexico, it's kind of like that.
Sometimes the, as it starts raining, the system gets overcharged,
and anybody flushes their toilet, well, here it comes up to the street,
through the sewer that's overflowing, you know?
So it was going on in Lake Charles also, Louisiana.
Anyway, I just told them a bunch of passcodes that you have to untie the storm sewer from the main sewer.
But anyway, when you start seeing that happening, now that's the setup for a pandemic, you see?
And it'll still take weeks and months to develop.
Okay, but once something like that is developed, like the plague,
where people's skin basically exploded in a few days, literally,
it just soars internally as well.
And if you look at what was going on with the hemorrhagic fever,
they called the Spanish flu, which is the American army flu, really,
where your lungs basically got, it's almost like a tuberculosis kind of condition,
where your big holes, Swiss cheese lungs kind of thing, immediately,
once it sets on, it only takes a few hours.
Things like that, once they set into the population,
the induction is so strong that the concept of sterilization
and those precautionary methods are sort of very difficult.
You almost have to get out of dodge.
So what do I mean by this?
With the bubonic plague, if you had something, let's say garments
or something you wanted to clean and sterilize from the bubonic plague,
you would have to boil it for no less than 15 minutes.
Not 14 minutes, 15 minutes.
That's how tenacious this inductive power is.
It's almost as if, once this sets into our program, meaning this reality,
it has like a crystalline form to it.
It's not this little virus bug thing, you know, whatever.
It almost has a crystalline nature to it, which is very, very, very tough, you see.
And what do crystals do?
They're known to be energy transfer and information transfer.
You hear about advanced societies,
well, look, even the earthy, crunchy, airy fairies,
you know, hold on to this crystal, right?
It gives you, you know, has information.
So I just wanted to throw this out there because I see some stuff like that
being resolved in this society, but not now.
You'll see it coming weeks and months before.
And here's the other thing.
If there was a real pandemic, it would be completely denied,
and the people that were shouting that it's real would be what?
Not disqualified, but what do you call it when you smear people?
Call them conspiracy theory.
What do you call that?
Well, there's a lot of disparaged.
Yes, yes, thank you.
Disparaged, I was looking for that.
Yeah, they would be disparaged until it finally sets in about a year later.
Oh, those people were right.
So hygiene in this case is also being aware of what you should get into
and what not get into and recognize the signs where, in other words,
let's just say hygiene may not take care of certain things on the extreme.
But in the meantime, in the day-to-day,
I brought up what we brought up in the last Sonic,
because I think it was in a form and in a way that people usually haven't heard it.
No, absolutely true.
And one thing to remember about the hemorrhagic fevers and those kind of things,
you know, the Ebola's and so on and so forth, is that at the end of the day,
the only way that this hasn't become a massive problem,
to my understanding, and maybe I'm wrong,
is that, you know, it moves so quickly, so aggressively,
that you don't even have time to connect with the outside world fast enough
in order to spread it quick enough.
In other words, the reverse is the only way to deal with it is to contain it.
And then it does what it does in a particular area.
Right, if it's too aggressive, it won't spread,
because it will just kill everybody and it will send off an alarm.
And if it's too benign, it won't spread again,
because if it's too benign, you'll have just pockets of people.
There are some of these, again, what they call the Spanish Flu,
the American Army Flu, and the bubonic plague.
And there are a set of other pandemics.
You know, there was a smallpox pandemic in the U.S.
that got to its peak in the colonies in 1776,
and that was a perfect time to start what they call the American Revolution.
A lot of the ships that were sent over,
they started fighting on Long Island, the Battle of Brooklyn.
A lot of the Polish and English troops did not want to disembark.
They were like, hey, why'd they send us over here?
Don't you know that there's a smallpox pandemic here?
I ain't getting off this ship, right, kind of thing, demoralizing.
Right.
So one of the things I did mention is when you do have a pandemic, there's war.
And it didn't really directly correlate with the, quote-unquote, Ukraine War,
because it's not really a war.
It's almost like what the U.S. did in Vietnam, sort of,
except they wanted to demilitarize.
But anyway, yeah.
So I guess I thought about hygiene again,
because I didn't say wash your bum, you know,
and I just wanted to throw these things in here.
Well, it is important and does seem to be the key.
You know, that is actually my argument most of the time.
It's a little incongruous, but it's the argument that people tell me quite often.
How can you possibly argue against, you know, vaccination?
And what they're talking about is, you know, how do you argue against that?
How do you argue, what's the matter with you?
Don't you realize that that, you know, it cured, it eliminated this and that,
and the third thing.
It didn't.
And I always say, and you can correct me if I'm wrong,
but I always say the only reason why any of that stuff was ever controlled
or not allowed to spread is because of hygiene, really.
It was, you know, being able to take the waste away and bring in clean water.
These were two important elements, and not leaving things to fester and grow.
And the seasonal changes will wipe it out.
Also, when you go through a series of hot and cold cycles,
that's why most of them don't last for a few years unless they're reconditioned.
And also, you know, the champion of the VAX idea is polio,
and polio had nothing to do with a virus.
It had all to do with the bug spray, what's a DDT.
And it's very simple to find, I hope, still.
If you go online and doctors, I think no less than a dozen doctors went to Congress
and spoke on the floor of Congress when they were in session about banning DDT
because of the palsy and nervous degenerative nerve.
They had all these terms for it, and based on their studies,
it was basically crippling people.
And there was a woman who wrote a book on it.
Sorry, severe nerve damage is what I was saying.
Yeah, exactly.
And it affected not everyone equally and not everyone the same
because you had all ages and all ranges of people coming down with certain maladies.
So they banned it, and the polio went away,
but they're still championing the vaccine over that.
Now, there was a few years ago, more than a few years ago, about a decade ago,
the Zika thing with the mosquitoes going on,
and they were spraying for mosquitoes, and guess what happened?
Children couldn't walk.
They were crippled again, and they called it something else,
and they developed a vaccine for that, which, of course, made it even worse.
It seems to keep on happening is what I meant to say.
I just said it twice, but yeah.
And if people are not aware of the pranking, then it's very easy to repeat, right?
So anything in the chat that's of notoriety other than the massive topic of slave speak
or slave, what is it called?
Neuro-linguistic programming was announced.
It was a book.
I think there was a book written about it.
NLP was a popular thing that people lectured on and wrote about for a little while.
Slave speak was the term I mentioned and kind of cued a couple of conversations in there,
but I think the general idea, we'd have to do a separate one on this,
but the general idea that's focused on how the language is used in order to create circumstances
that are not necessarily what people would interpret to be the circumstances that are created by the language.
Simply applying names to things is one thing, right?
But also the structure of the language.
People like to use the term weaponized speech, right?
This is a big thing nowadays.
Well, yeah, speech is at all times weaponized,
and I think the way that the common use of language, the way it's constructed,
and you talk about this all the time, but I think a focus on it would be good.
Also, a little ways back, somebody brought up a list of, oh boy, of terms for you because you had mentioned.
Yeah, that was great.
That was a breath of fresh air, yeah.
Yeah, these were the, what did you call it, metric terms, right?
Metrics.
If you use those words, you're considered just fine.
Right, and it's a great list, actually.
Of course, you had the J-E-S-U-S word in there.
I'm now going to pull to the list real fast.
Reptilian rights, justice, the Constitution, hell, Monday through Sunday, January through December,
virus, blood pressure, God, Lord, rapture.
One word missing from this, by the way.
I'll finish it, though.
Let's see.
Petrol.
Ooh, what is this?
Oh, petrol, some fossil fuels, okay.
Fossil fuels, for sure.
Love, woke, Santa Claus, Xmas, okay.
Anarchy, fallen angels, and mine and yours.
Mine and yours is there.
That's great, but I think it's also good to mention the conjunctions
because when you are identifying something as mine, it may be different.
Okay, when you're talking about my government, right,
that always gives me pause because how is it yours?
I always ask, you know.
How is it yours exactly?
Much like when people were screaming, you know, they stole my vote.
And I go, well, look, for you to claim it's yours, right, that kind of implies possession.
And why are you voting at an election?
Why are you voting at an election?
Shouldn't you be electing at an election?
You elect, okay.
You're not an elector.
They even tell you you're the voters and the electors decided that, yeah.
Just to recap real quick, it just means you're confident in the system.
That's why it's called a vote of confidence or a vote of no confidence, right?
Right, but the interesting thing is when it's yours, it's just very interesting.
They stole my vote.
I say, how do they steal something that you do not have possession of?
See, because to me the idea of theft is that you took something that didn't belong to you.
That's what it is.
It's not yours.
You took it, right?
So who owned it?
You're saying my vote, so you're describing the thing as yours.
That means that you believe you owned it, right?
Well, here's a simple thing.
If you create something, it's yours.
You can give up control to it, but in a sense, if it's in the stipulations of the control that the ownership,
now you're giving that over, then it's still not right for whoever takes it over to say it's theirs
because they didn't create it, but it's theirs for use.
You see?
So you cannot say something that you did not create is yours.
You're just basically using it, and that's one of the memes regarding the Rockefellers.
It says, own nothing, control everything, right?
Remember, this is a common meme that was put.
Well, what in the world could you truly own then?
I mean, I would argue that maybe you could control and own your children.
Control is different, though.
I mean, that could have been registered.
By the way, just to throw something out, when people have problems with the child trafficking,
it's called Child Protection Services, right?
It's very well known that internationally it's a child trafficking ring.
By the way, there's dozens of almost mainstream articles written about it that are factable, let's say, if that's a word.
Just tell them, this child does not have a birth certificate.
There is no birth certificate on this child or this offspring, and they run.
They're told.
That's one of the key words.
Also, from an attorney that I noticed, I didn't say lawyer, they do family court with child stuff.
And I said, you know, that's all based on the birth certificate.
She goes, yeah.
And I say, if the birth certificate's in question or there is no birth certificate, you have no case.
She goes, yep, absolutely.
That's right.
It's all based on the birth certificate, right?
So I kind of tested these things back and forth, and it's essentially words, paper, what's called  well, it's in law.
You can sign over something to someone, right?
I mean, that's essentially what's going on.
Okay, what's going on here is you made it.
You have  it's yours.
But you're going to sign it over to us.
And when you sign it over to us, now you have to pay a tax or a rent for using it.
How does that sound?
Right.
Right?
Now, this is what happened in Afghanistan.
The Army set up Army-protected tents in all the villages, the main villages, and told people
that's why if you look at Afghanistan, all the Toyota pickup trucks, Nissan trucks or whatever,
none of them have license plates on them, right?
No, of course not.
Right, but the American Army set up these tents and told people,
why don't you come here and give us all the vehicle information, VIN number and all that,
and you can register it with us.
And they're backwards people supposedly, but they were like, okay, so when I register it with you,
now I'm basically taking my rightful ownership of it over to you,
and then I have to pay a tax or a use fee for using my own truck, right?
Mm-hmm.
And no one showed up.
This word got around.
That's what they're  don't even bother going.
They want you to sign over your children, sign over your land, your house, your goats, your cows, your car to them,
and then you have to pay  they call it a tax, and they take it away because you didn't pay the tax.
There's no such thing.
In other words, taxes are for foreigners in ports and duties.
If you live somewhere and you're paying a tax on anything, it's because somehow you transferred over anyway,
and now you have to rent it.
So they pretty much got laughed out of the country, this aspect of the legal thing they try to put out of Afghanistan.
They laughed them all out, and there's someone that lives here, this part of town,
that talked about how they just basically  all the Afghanis laughed at them.
But I said, here they take it very seriously, and they'll sign over it.
He says, yeah, Americans will sign anything.
They sign over their children.
They sign over their cars.
They sign over everything.
It's a pretty rough place because here's the thing.
If you drive around, quote-unquote driving, operating an engine-driven wagon without a plate and all that,
they're going to go into seizure, what's called letter of mark.
It's an old thing, and they're going to pirate it.
They're going to throw you in jail or give you fines for not having signed it over to them.
So, yeah, welcome to  what is it?
Was it home of the free?
Land of the free, home of the brave.
Yeah, or land of the slave or whatever.
So, yeah, it's probably the worst it's ever been since about 75, 80 years ago.
And still  but they're not making a big deal about it anymore.
There were a lot of patriots that made a big deal about it.
Brother Ali would say, you know, welcome to the American snakes, land of the thief, home of the slave is what he would say.
There you go, yeah.
I like that one better.
This is the war brother Ali from back in the day.
But, brother, I don't know if you're familiar with the musician.
Okay, cool.
Oh, the musician, okay, because there's a Moorish from the 1920s.
Yes, yes, that's another guy.
I think that's where he got, you know, decided to pick the name from.
He's mirroring the philosophy as well.
Right, right.
You know, but most people don't know that.
They just hear him.
He's kind of like, you know, hip-hop, jazzy, rock kind of guy.
I got you, contemporary.
Contemporary, yeah.
But the concept remains the same.
Right.
And it's fascinating because you bring up this whole thing about not having the plate and not registering and all that.
Here's the problem.
You try it.
It's not worth it.
No, it's really not.
Here's the other thing.
I've had people communicate with me about Greek.
What do we do?
The system is so corrupt.
It's so saddening.
It's so vicious.
It's so whatever.
I want to leave here.
I said, no, well, you can do that.
You can live in it.
But, you know, shield yourself from it.
Or if you loosen your moral grip or heighten your moral grip where you have even better insulation, dive into it.
Right.
And you could benefit from it.
You could become very wealthy from it.
Right.
But it's a personal decision.
When I say to dive into it and use it to become wealthy from it, it's a simple analogy would be during the Depression,
the Monopoly game board was so popular it made them very wealthy.
Right.
Because it was a play on the times.
There's constant stuff going on.
But if that's your interest, just because things are bad, quote, unquote, morally and ethically,
doesn't mean you can't prosper from them.
But you're going to have to, you know, it depends again.
Well, your definition of prosperity.
Your definition of prosperity.
Right.
Sure.
Which, you know, to some people might be an accounting of how many zeros you have on your bank account.
Well, look.
They're doctors that were pecker choppers.
They cut off your pecker, right, and hollow it out, whatever.
They weren't too busy, let's say, 25, 30 years ago or even 10 years ago.
Now they're really busy.
Oh, no.
That's very true.
Yeah.
But, you know, what if, so you think he's busy because he decided to.
Right.
Or she.
So.
Or they are them.
They know what's going on.
I'm sorry.
It's a joke.
But anyhow.
No, I think this is a great point to end on.
Is there anything else, though, that we missed?
I mean, outside of wash your bum.
Yeah, well, we started off with just something I usually don't do.
Right.
And there's just a lot more if anyone wants to read it with comprehension.
I think that's something I haven't mentioned in a long time.
No, very good.
It's primary Greek speech.
Comprehension is where it's at.
Well, very good.
And I see this as very solid because the analogy, most things are analogous to one another.
There is a great deal of synchronicity.
I think it's a very interesting order to just think about the very simplistic idea of the order in which someone washes themselves and then consider that.
Because, you know, one thing that is consistent is the order of things as they are in the universe.
You know, people point out, well, there is a sequence.
And, you know, even if you look at the segments that come into your bones, into your hands and everything, there is a consistency here.
So I think that it's relevant on a much larger scale.
Yeah, one thing I want to throw in there also, I've said this many times, I'm an Old Testament kind of guy.
There's lots of stuff about washing, and it's very specific, by the way.
What's great, the computer is a great tool for study.
Of course, a lot of it is mistranslated, and you're going to have to go back to an interlinear.
And if you're serious about the subject, see if it really says what it's supposed to be saying in English or whatever corresponding language you're reading.
But you'll see that it applies to certain things.
I'll give a quick example before we go.
There are things that were deemed unclean, people in certain states, things that were just unclean.
And when a piece of pottery was touched with something unclean, it would not be ever rendered clean again.
It had to be broken, right?
So you basically cherished your pottery.
You were careful who touched it and what happened, let's say, right?
Because you would lose it.
It would be for unclean things, or you'd make it a piss pot, let's say, right?
If it became unclean.
But here's the interesting thing, that stone does not become unclean.
When I say stone, I mean not stoneware, but stone.
If you actually cut a pot out of stone, I actually have a granite pot.
It's a cooking pot.
And you put it in the fire in the oven for half an hour.
And it's about an inch thick.
It's made of granite.
And you take it out of the oven, and it holds that heat for a very long time.
So you bring it to the table, and whatever you put in there, you cook in it.
And it just keeps cooking, right?
You've seen certain things tableside.
They have a thick cast iron base, and they put the food on it,
and it's cooking while you're, right?
Oh, yeah.
I've even seen, I forget what country it came from,
but there was this circumstance in New York where they had like a slot,
a modular slot in a table where they would bring out sort of a stone oven.
I can't remember what ethnic food it was.
Sorry?
Without any coals.
It's just preheated.
No, no.
It's just a preheated piece of stone that gets placed into a, you know,
a prearranged spot in the table.
I'm sure you've seen this.
I only saw it once.
You just put strips of meat on it and things,
and it just keeps cooking for about 20 minutes.
Yeah.
So I have this.
It has a very interesting feel to it.
It's a real stone material pot.
Now, my point here is, again, for being clean.
The pottery had to be broken.
But stone was immune to that in what they call Old Testament or Torah law.
So what's interesting is certain societies like the Essenes,
when they held water instead of keeping them in terracotta pots
where if they were rendered unclean, they would have to break these big pots,
they actually took the time to make the pots out of stone,
which are immune from being unclean.
So regardless of who touched the stone or what the situation was,
the water or whatever contents were held in these stone vessels
was always rendered clean.
Very interesting.
Well, it could be rendered clean.
I mean, for instance, somehow through mishap,
you ended up with animal blood inside of your water jar.
If it was made of pottery, that's the end of that jar.
You would, well, the terracotta would have to be broken
or it would be rendered as an unclean pot, right?
You'd still use it for other things.
Well, like you said, a piss pot or whatever, yeah.
Yeah, but the stone pot, you just exchange the water.
You could clean it out.
The vessel itself remains clean.
So I was thinking about our talk about hygiene kind of getting into that,
but just to recap, again, just if you study what's in Torah,
it's very interesting.
A body of water that has an input and an output is clean,
even if something unclean is in it.
So taking a bath, that's one thing that escaped the mind.
If you're taking a bath and you want the water to be, let's say,
considered spiritually clean according to Torah,
you would have water dripping into it from a spout
and the stopper slightly open where some water leaks out at the same time
and that water then is clean versus taking a bath in a basin where no water.
See, even if the water is coming in, it has to flow out.
So if you're in a basin situation,
the water would have to flow in to the point where it overflows out.
Then it's rendered clean again.
But if you're just sitting in a water and nothing's coming in,
nothing's going out of the container, it's unclean.
It's not cleaning, I should say, according to biblical law.
So by the way, to make this even easier,
that's why most of the laundry was done where?
Down by the river, which was usually fed by a spring of some sort.
It had water coming in and water would exit through, yeah.
And it also makes basic sense.
So, yeah, following these things are quite interesting.
And they do work, by the way, for therapeutic reasons,
both psychological for the mind and the body.
I've had several people from back in the day say,
in Greek, I always just took a bath and turned all the fill water off
and had the stopper shut.
And since I heard you say that,
I let the water drip in and the stopper slightly open,
and I feel so much better.
I was like, are you sure it's not like some kind of placebo or something?
She goes, no, I could feel the difference because I would take baths
for relieving aches in my hips and my legs, and it sometimes worked.
But when I do this, every time it works.
So I was like, okay, great.
Well, there you go.
What are your thoughts on using something like Epsom salt
or whatever in those sorts of baths?
Sure, sure.
But that would be, again, an additive to the water.
No, in those kinds of baths, no, it wouldn't last very long.
No.
What you would do there is after your Epsom salt bath,
because it's the finish that counts, right?
I would finish with when you're finished sitting in the bath with the Epsom salt.
Because when you do an Epsom salt bath properly,
you need about a pound of salt easily.
It should be pretty saturated for it to work well, the magnesium.
Right.
Yeah.
But I would finish off with some water trickling out or a shower.
But actually sitting in a therapeutic bath like that,
it wouldn't be rendered clean.
I always shower afterwards.
I have no explanation for why,
but it always works better if I shower afterwards.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
The Epsom salts don't work on dry
in other words, if you have dry Epsom salt on skin,
it's just going to dry your skin.
No, yeah, yeah.
No, no, no.
I have constant back and leg pain, so that's
Since we're on the  oh, okay.
Since we're on the thing about bathing
and how many times have I mentioned induction,
check this out.
Don't pee in the pool, right?
No.
People get into a pool, swimming pool, right,
and they tell you don't pee in the pool, right?
Why?
You get into a body of water,
and via induction, water is created in the body
to replace the water that's already there,
and it goes to the bladder.
It's created again in the bladder, goes out.
Same thing if you're sitting in a bath.
Sort of explains why you have the instant feeling
like you might want to pee as soon as you go into a bath or a pool.
That's why.
Exactly.
It's induction.
That's a perfect example for induction.
Even people who are
if you're dehydrated and you're in a bath,
you will feel like you will have to pee.
It will not necessarily hydrate you
because there's a very fine balance on blood hydration.
It has to go through the mouth,
touch the roof of the mouth, the throat, and all that,
and then, of course, for it to be produced in the blood.
That's why people are severely dehydrated or unconscious.
They put them on an IV to get it into the blood,
but that only works for so long.
So I just wanted to bring up that point of peeing in the bath
or peeing in the pool.
It's induction that induces that.
It's not
I remember a medical person once said,
Greek, what about the physical pressure on the bladder?
I looked at them, and I'm like, what about induction?
He says, yeah, you're right.
I'm like, don't tell me I'm right.
Do you know this?
That's one of the things that I
when people say you're right,
it doesn't really help the overall situation.
No, it doesn't.
But peeing in the shower, not so bad
because it goes right down the drain.
You will have induction there as well,
but not as much when you're submerged
because of the soft areas.
From the outside of the body,
most induction happens in the very soft areas,
which would be between the toes, between the fingers,
the armpits, the bend in the arm,
like the opposite part of your elbow or the wrist.
No, the parts that are less exposed
to things on the outside rubbing against them.
Sure, of course.
Typically, typically, yeah.
That's where you have the most
yeah, interesting stuff.
So I think that'll be it for 17.