I'm going to address is wrapping it tight like you recommended if something in the body right let me get into it
Yeah, you know absolutely we'll just we'll start the recording and say I see those knives now though just so you know
Yeah, I didn't see that before
That's pretty nice
They you know they're pretty unassuming looking actually those are the ones that I bought at Marshall's for 30 bucks for three nights
Oh, okay, okay, so these aren't really I posted these and then the next day on Monday
We've got the box with the other knives, so whoever's there's still Japanese in other words
When I was got the knives someone had already put a knife set for me in the mail
Before it was already in the mail. I got you. Okay. Yeah, cuz I got it the next day
Yeah, then it's in the next day
so
Yeah, yeah, but these are nice knives. They have they have a poplar handles or wooden handles. I've tried them out
They're made in the traditional fashion
mm-hmm
So
Nice, okay cool
For other people that in other words to look up that brand tends to you because you've got Amazon you get a knife for 20 bucks
and it's Japanese certified steel so
Hmm cuz I got these three for 30. They were normally 80
They're not bad, then they're like passable. They're okay. No. They're good. They're good too very good to good
Yeah, and only 80 bucks top price. That's how I retail 80 bucks
I got him for 30 if you zoom in on the sticker
Okay, I
Believe you. Let's see. Oh, I can zoom in. Yeah a little bit
You can control depends on what browser you have. Yeah, you know what it is
I already have a control scroll. You already have it set for large already. So it kind of rolls scrolls
Marshall scroll and you'll go up to a thousand percent. Well, I do control plus and it moves it up
That's who yeah, that's what I was just doing but yeah, I see it now Marshall's and yeah $29.99, right?
Yeah, Amazon's got even better price for three. Well, Amazon has a better price on just about everything, doesn't it?
And at their point, all right. Yeah, it's actually anti capitalism. We can get it. Let's get started. Yeah, absolutely
Okay, so as I was saying
Electrical interference electronic interference
I've noticed stuff weird stuff's been weird lately and I said that that on that one too. I'm pretty sure
Sorry about that
Nasty nasty from the
tooth anyways, um
Yeah left down right up and this creates a circular motion and I know we talked about that
So we're talking about directionality and also what happens. Okay. Yep
Yeah, we just got any I just got an email regarding a manifestation on the left side so, okay great
So we'll talk about we'll let you lead off with the email
Well, I also also said I was going to talk about more about the what the decipher. Oh, who was it?
serum at xeromatics
About the personal injuries and applying on if you read those from a week ago. Yeah, there was a guy with his foot and all that
Yeah, no before that the one with the broken leg. Oh
Yeah, I'm not gonna get into that detail
Yeah, you said you're gonna do a solo on that one. All right, no problem
72 looks like and here we are rated Y. All right, so getting right back into it
I know you got some stuff in your email recently Greek and I know you wanted to address that first. So, uh, go ahead. Oh
Yeah, let's let's move on. It's it's interesting how it reflects things we did in episode 27
So I wanted to get into also last time we were on I said get more into detail on some of the stuff
So what obviously?
How uses enough medical jargon that one can say they're in the medical profession or well, we're well exposed to it
about healing
Doing using ether devices Greek speak stuff on the recovery of a broken bone
I think it was tibial fracture and it was more than just a tibial fracture on a distal part
which means further down so or away from the center, so
I was thinking about that, you know doing it here not necessarily a solo about how to deal with broken bones, but then
What hit me is what reality I
Walked outside went on a short walk and I ran up to three or four people
I'm not disparaging the subs or anything
But I realized no you can't get into this because someone might actually miss a point and do the wrong thing
Right. So what I would suggest this is not a disclaimer because I do give legal and medical advice, right?
Right. I don't I do because I've never been licensed to do either one
That's what the law says if you've been licensed to do either one and the license is you're no longer licensed for whatever reason
You can't do it, right, but they charge plenty of people with those crimes or alleged
Misdemeanors or whatever because they don't know the law and by the way
I've sat down with attorneys and brought up long like that's not in the law
They show I said get the books as I know everything in this book and he brings out the book
I show the law I read it. He says wait a second. It doesn't say that
I mean, that's that's the kind of moxie that they have
Even though it doesn't say even though it says that it doesn't say yeah, okay, and it's written in eighth grade level
It's not even in jargon legal jargon. It's written in plain English. So certain certain laws, but anyway
What I would say because of the human condition everyone including myself. I might you know
go if you have an injury that is
mild to severe and
It seems like it needs quote-unquote emergency care get it, you know the hospital the doctor, you know
I was at the doctor like there's one doctor right with no doctor go to a doctor or whatever first get started there
right
Do I do that? No hell no
No way, and I think I mentioned that earlier from a spiritual point of view. Here's the Greek
He goes to a hospital or a doctor and wait
He's the one talking against them and give it all these things. What kind of what is he doing or
Here's the Greek. He just passed away
And he the stuff he talked about didn't apply. So what the hell is he talking about?
So either way, you know you lose, right? Yeah
Well, I try to handle most things on my own at home for sure, but on occasion I need another pair of hands
And I figure sometimes if I do need a bone set or something like that
I'll go get it from you know, the hospital whichever one's nearby
Something like that if I need right now, by the way
They're shutting those things down because they've served their function which is financial function purely and they're opening emergency clinics
Which you'll see that if you drive by these little mall strip mall places and it says intensive care urgent care here
You know urgent care now. Mostly that's the biggest phrase. I guess. Sorry. Yeah. Yeah, go ahead and get it
So the thing that you have to do certain things even a quote-unquote medical person has to get done
This is not like being a lawyer when you sue a lawyer
He has to get another lawyer how ridiculous it is, right shows you how it's a game
You know when you have you have a game you have to use the parts that are in the game
You can't right so when a lawyer gets sued or an attorney calling them lawyers is not right their attorneys
They have to hire an attorney to represent them, right? So it tells you has nothing to do with being competent
It's a game. Yeah, so, you know, I think Maxwell talked about it's a court, right?
Whatever well you play games on a court a tennis court a basketball court, etc. It's a game
So basically the doctors now, they often need someone else because of the hands
I'm fully well-versed and competent in all forms of dentistry and
I
Need a dentist to do it and the dentist that I go to needs a dentist
It's you know, he says he has three root canals in his mouth as you doing yourself
Looks at me sideways like you know, you can't do that to yourself, right?
Well, it's rather difficult to do dentistry to oneself. I mean, let's be honest you you you it's it's a it's not impossible
But it's difficult, right? Yes, you need a community. In other words, that's why I've always said, you know
You go it. Let's say you have a semi loosely knit or a block, you know people or you know in the city in town
Or whatever, you don't know. Hey Jimmy's good with the cars
He's good at cooking when you do the barbecue bring him this guy's good at boats
This guy's good at fishing go talk to him. This guy's good at carpentry go talk to him
But you notice they never say he's really good at setting bones or this guy's really good with the health stuff in the medical stuff
You don't hear it
so eventually if you're in a loosely knit community or tightly knit community gonna have to
Find out who is good at the teeth at the body at the organs at the bones
You know all these other things and if guess what you'll probably find out that nobody is because they all say
Oh, we go to the hospital or the doctor, right?
So guess what you have to do you find out who is most who might be most proficient or is naturally inclined
Right. Yeah and get them get them some training. And by the way, I dare anyone you just randomly just try to fun
Don't pick something you want to do pick something that randomly in the medical profession just a specialty
Doesn't matter up follow me dentistry a diatribe
Whatever, whatever. Yeah, just pick something out of a hat random and then go study it online online courses for doctors or whatever everything
You get and I assure you I assure you in less than 10 days
Let's say podiatrist. You will be able to walk into any podiatrist office and have a
Conversation with the podiatrist and he'll ask you where's your residency? Where's your office because he thinks you're on his level. I'm serious
Now obviously it doesn't mean experience but neither does that it's mean a lot because when I had a tooth extraction number 19
about 10-15 years ago, I
Know that when a tooth is extracted and there isn't severe decay in the mandible or the skull or the bone area
You have something called a period on periodontal ligaments called the PDL
What basically it's a cushion that when the the tooth whether it's one root two roots three is set into the bone
It's a ligament. It's softer tissue. It acts as a shock absorber
Yeah
When the tooth is extracted if that PDL remains and the socket closes
The body gets a signal that the tooth is still there and there will be decay that could form between the PDL and the closed
Socket, right?
So what has to be done if the PDL is present or any of the PDL is present periodontal ligament is you need?
Depending on the size of the root, you know number eight number ten number eleven burr
Which is basically a small file in the shape of a ball goes the other drum. They stick it in the socket
It's kind of messy because it's bloody right, right and you have to remove the PDL by scraping it out, right?
If you don't do that, it will never heal properly Hilda Clark cure for all diseases is a book. She wrote about 30 years ago
She's alive in Mexico
I think she recently died
But she they said she died 20 years ago because in Mexico because she was putting out a lot of remedy
Anyway, Hilda Hilda Clark H ULD a Clark. I have her book
Pretty good. Hold on H ULDA. Hold up. Yeah, Clark. Yeah, I believe so. It's a cure for all diseases. It's a good read
She believes in viruses and things like that, but a lot of the practical stuff works
anyway
Where was I going with this? Oh, yeah talked about a lot of people in older age when they
You find they're in the wheelchair, they can't walk and one of the reasons was when they had teeth pulled
The socket wasn't cleaned out and they had decay forming in the bone and it eventually caused enough
Nerve debilitation where they couldn't walk in older age older age could be 65 70 80, right?
So anyway, so even at that age they would scan their mouths and find out that the sockets looked hollow
Where the bone is healed over and they would break through and clean it out and guess what after recovering from the tooth surgery within a
Few days, they're able to regain the use of their legs again. So one thing you notice so say what is what is an infected tooth?
Socket that's been closed up for 40 years have to do with you being able to walk, right? Yeah, that's all energy, right?
Yeah, so I just give this example, but by the way, I so I asked the the relationship I have with the dentist is informal
So I won't mention his name, but if I call him up and I say he says hey, what do you need done?
Well, you know, I'm number 21. I might need an extraction or whatever and he says, all right. Listen, when do you when?
Can you call me says? All right. Look up. How about we'll meet at the office at 8 o'clock after I play basketball Thursday
That's that's the relationship. I have one right we do a barter, right?
so it's funny I'll sit there and
He'll bring in assistant because it's easier that way
It's really easy to get assistance by the way, you know
You go to the colleges and they're just dying to get you know, people to sign off that they didn't so many hours, right?
Yep
so if you want someone eight o'clock at night, you call them up and
It'll be an hour or two and you say look I'm gonna sign off that you did 12 hours and oh boy
Are they happy they'll come right really right away, right? Right. So anyway, yeah the whole world
This is how the world works. You will scratch my back. I scratch yours, right?
So anyway, so I mentioned, you know what I want. I think the PDL is good
I want to get an eight. Do you have an eight bird? He goes what?
Number eight bird I said and I see so I want to clean up the PDLs. He's not the PDL
I'm like, yeah clean out the PDL. So the socket he'll solve, you know, you know completely because I haven't heard that since I was in
College, they're like how many?
Extractions have you done since you've been out of college? Oh thousands. Oh my gosh. Oh my gosh
Right, so tie this back to the pediatrists the pediatric the podiatrists by the way
Pito and pedo are two different things, right? So yes, anyway
Yeah
You will learn enough fresh out of what's let's say memorialized and I don't think that's good
They pick podiatrists because I don't think they're going to it's like pathology where they totally destroyed that field
Online and oncology which oncology is totally useless. Anyway, all right
You know, so podiatry podiatry is a very practical thing because a lot of people have trouble with their feet
I mean, it's one of those things that's constantly in use and damage occurs
It's called cheap shoes. Yeah cheap shoes, you know, right? So go ahead. I mean, it's just it's a very practical
Thing I was thinking just like dentistry. Yeah. So in other words after after 10 days to a month, let's say
You will be able to operate in that field
Believe it or not technically
practically
So what do you say?
No, I agree
I mean look I was able to in I can tell you from personal experience
It took me about a month
I would say of really reading but I did find having conversations with all sorts of people in the x-ray field x-ray technicians
No problem. It took me about a month to pull it together
To be able to have discussions so I could accurately
Yeah, and x-rays are like in code
You need someone who knows how to read them
Most doctors will stand there staring at it for hours and told the guy who knows how to read x-rays has brought it
Yeah, the doctor never reads him the doctor reads the report from the technician
Is what the doctor reads and that's what they go on usually, you know
Normally, so I wanted to know what the technicians knew. So I just grabbed their textbooks. I went through it and I went
Okay, this is what?
You know, this is what I mean. I don't recall all this off the top of my head now
Cuz this is probably about 20 years ago
And I haven't had to use it much
Since that's another thing, but I don't use something like that
You know, I don't access it as quickly and easily but I mean if I've just recently read it obviously
It's more fresh in my mind and I can utilize it a lot better
But back to the podiatry thing. I mean that's a common issue, right you get older
You might have had injuries that didn't heal properly
You know the common old complaints of corns and this and that right?
You don't take care of your feet you're gonna have issues
I mean, it's just right but once the bones form that way and they don't form back they can continue if they continue growing
They'll go back but the part that grew in the way it did will not will not change right? So with that said I
Would suggest going back to the first emergency situation in the case in the chat the person who listed the various things that they did
Seemed pretty okay
There was mentioned something about two pine boards and all that I would have something more flexible
Because if if you're tying something to the bone to keep the bone aligned it should not be as hard as bone
Wait a second. Does that make any sense? Yes, it does
because
There's an energetic value to these things as well. So you want it to be as hard as bone or
Not as hard as bone, but not harder than bone or stronger than the bone. There is a tiny amount of flexibility
That's necessary still for circulation and other things like that within the broken area, believe it or not
The other thing I wanted to bring up when you have a broken bone
Have you ever heard of people dying because they had a broken leg and it wasn't treated?
It's rare, but it happens and why does it happen? I'll give you the chemical reason why yeah, I read
I want to say I read about that more in the
1960s seemed to have occurred a bit more for some odd reason right where there were people what will happen
You know how they say blood is produced in the bone marrow it's not
Right only under severe conditions. Well, this is a severe condition. What happens is the blood that's
Produced in the bone marrow when the bone is completely broken is overloaded with potassium
And the potassium let me just without getting into much of it because I don't have direct experience
Seeing anyone go through this or the laboratory clinical experience
But what I would suggest is the flood of potassium rich extra rich
Enriched potassium blood short-circuits the heart muscle
right and
Then you have they can't start it again. Okay, once it once it's short-circuited with potassium and it's a type of organic potassium
It's extremely strong. So it's a salt basically. So enough. So what I would suggest also
with a broken bone is
Potassium is formed in the body with from sodium salts basically high quality salts and activity
You must have activity if you're sedentary all sedentary people have potassium deficiency guaranteed
Guaranteed does it by the way intake of potassium as a supplement is worthless?
It just goes right out the body body looks at it says, huh? We don't we make that we don't need it to induce that right?
So the reason you have a lot of problems with people that are sedentary is they have a high sodium or sodium intake no activity
The body produces potassium too much potassium now that it creates a potassium deficiency
Right. Okay, because the potassium is still not at the level that it should be because you need the activity
Right and you're depleting salts at the same time. So yeah, so don't be sedentary the other thing about
Having a broken bone is the problem of being sedentary
It is a certain amount of request and sleep therapy
By the way, if you do sleep therapy with broken bones you recover much faster
But there's only so much sleep therapy. You can do one popular treatment in the medical community is
to
Induce sleep therapy like some older people can't swallow and they literally can choke
So and if that gets if they get an emergency like that
They bring them into the hospital and they induce a coma for a week for them to recover and other things
Yeah, right gunshot wounds are typical
Severe traumas they induce a coma
Which is basically sleep therapy, which is not good because to get sleep therapy you must cycle in and out of sleep not a coma
Again, you'll have the potassium problem
Wow, how did we go down this road?
The I've made the decision to not get into a lot of specifics, but I will get into some specific accounts. How's that?
Okay, that sounds like a good way to go because I'll give us some examples. Yeah
Someone who's probably here it will hear this. Yeah
I'll recap this recount the story
We talked about ginger
Therapy and a few other things and just remind me about this because I'm gonna I'm gonna stop this right here
it's not a tangent and I'm gonna go to the
email
was which was someone who
Discussed he has you know, someone who has a sore on the back of their left leg back
Left leg and it's getting worse. What do you do?
They did mention that they had applied pressure. Like I said, right, okay
Okay, so I'm bringing this up at the same time that I brought up the ginger therapy
When you have an open sore that actually something that develops and then bursts through the skin comes through the skin
It's very different than having a cut
Where it's from the outside in
When something comes to the skin and wants to go out it's from the inside out it needs to do that
So you don't want to wrap it tight
Right, right. Now if you have a cut that's from the outside in like puncturing the tire you do want to wrap it tight
Well, okay
So even if you're if you're developing something like, you know
One of those little pus sacks under the skin there the obvious thing is what do you usually do you get the pus out?
Okay, let that stuff go out
Then blister breaks
Yeah, then wrap it tight. Yes, if something wants to come out facilitate that coming out
Something. All right, and then it's treated like a normal puncture which then
Right once it's once it's empty, right once it's once it's empty or yeah
Yeah, where that cycle is completed and it's got to be sometimes
Let's say you have a pus thing you you open it up and you and you believe in the end the pus comes out
You do a wrap not too tight and check it the next day if there's more pus guess what you're not done yet
Yeah, you got to let it out some more
In other words, you got to make sure that it stops producing new stuff to pack into it to push out or right?
Yeah, exactly. Once it's done ejecting then you treat it as a cut. So this is a first time
I've mentioned when not to wrap tight
Let's go back to the ginger thing when something wants to come out of the body
And it's below the skin level dermal epidermal a ginger compress will accelerate that
You grate some ginger or sliced ginger. Don't boil it simmer it hot and a clean white towel washcloth type size
Ring it out. Keep hot as hot as you can take it, which would be in the hundred and twenty two hundred twenty-five degree range
Over the area for twenty minutes at a time and cycle it how many cycles it's up to you
Right how much time you by the way people I've read it someone says I don't have any time. I have very little time
It's like oh my gosh. I
Take that it's like you don't have a lot of time for me and someone else or is that just something that you keep repeating?
Oh my gosh, it's just I think people are getting more and more insane, right? Yeah, so
So so anyway, I just want to throw that in there. Of course. So so the ginger thing
So here's a this person is listening most likely. Okay, and it's okay. I'm not gonna mention names, but it's a sheet and
I don't say this often and I don't say this lightly, but when I say I have a lot of respect for this
Human person right woman. I can't say it anymore
All right. Okay, and you'll find out why
There was a bump on the breast right breast, which means it's the energy of the going up. So the so this is very yin
Right upward energy that wants to come out if it was on the left
Mm-hmm. It would also be yin, but it's a blockage versus a coming out, right?
So bodies forming a blockage if it was on the left, but if it's on the right, it means it wants to come out
so they proceeded with the
Ginger and it came close and went to the doctor and they of course, you know the c-word, right?
They came closer and closer to the surface surface got black and blue and itchy and red and black and blue and itchy and very
Very close to the surface and the closer came the surface the harder it got wasn't something that's going to go through the skin
Okay
She lives in California and she went of a little more than walking distance to the Pacific Ocean early in the winter morning
Spent time in the water in the winter Pacific Ocean till she was completely numbed out
walked home
Put a mirror on the floor knelt down took about three swigs of tequila
Got a very sharp blade because it was on the underside of the breast
Now I'll continue cut it open and
Pushed it out
Okay, and wrapped it up and all that and they're fine
Right. Okay now
now that is
balls or
Vagina, however, you want to put it right because I think vaginas are tougher than balls know whatever it takes to yeah
Explain that this is something that takes, you know bit of strength to do good. Yeah, think about it
That's like stuff you see in film
like like
Fellini movies, you know
So I just wanted to share that people in a certain age might think back to Rambo stitching himself up in a canyon
You know during the first first blood movie, right? Yeah, and that's you don't have to actually no one cities themselves up
They wrap it tight. No, but it's the example. Yes jumping right in and doing it. Yeah
So here's something about you don't need someone else, but you do but you don't
Right, so I wanted to bring that up now
When something like that on the body
Occurs the right side is where the energy goes up on the left side is when the energy goes down and just because you have
manifestation on the right
Doesn't mean it's the opposite of a manifestation on the left
Because you have two things
That could happen on either side one is that something needs to be ejected because it is of that quality
So if it is something on the right
Manifestation happens whether it's in the organ on the skin or breast or head
It's something that has to come out
or the body is forming an abnormal tissue to block too much of the opposite energy of
Energy going down now the same is true for the left
When you have an manifestation on the left, it could be too much of the energy that goes down normally wants to come out
Or it could be in a formation of abnormal tissue to block too much of the stuff that should be on the right
That's spilling over to the left. So you have to determine that right?
So this one for example going back to the leg a sore on the back of the leg
Versus the side or the front of the leg
Right, and it would tell me that that is a young discharge
But it's because of young and mean
What would I mean about that? Let's make it simple. Yeah
Young a young discharge would be too much animal product animal fat animal proteins is
Young, but if it was on the front or the inside or the outside of the leg
It would be purely young and to I would say too much animal fat too much animal product
Most likely bovine or pork or four-legged animal
Right most likely but because it's on the back side of the leg
It doesn't mean that it's not young. Yes it is
But it's also you mean so meaning here and you'll this when I say this it'll hit home
Yes, because it's on the left on the bottom
It's too much animal product, but it's too much animal product that has chemicals in it like hormones drugs in the meat
Okay
Which are very yin
chemicals are yin, right so into this person by by the location of it and
Specific location on the back of the left is telling me there's too much animal product of low quality animal product typically
American factory farm product or right so bovine hormones growth hormones
antibiotic chemicals
Pesticides
Kovat vaccines, whatever whatever whatever so if this person ate only organic meat
It would move to the side inside of the leg or the front of the leg
It's not funny
Right if they start eating organic, but it would still be there because they're eating meat
Too much animal protein and it could be too much animal protein from years ago
That the body says I'm tired of it just like a relationship you could be in a relationship 5 10 20 30 years
And one day you wake up and you start it. That's enough
Mmm, right, okay. You have a divorce or whatever, right? Well, you've heard of that
Yeah, no, absolutely. I and then they become really good friends and then some people turn around and remarry again
It's a weird thing. But um, right in this case, it depends on the age of the person, of course
but let me just continue sure good a
Manifestation on the left leg means it's the energy going the down. Is it something?
Abnormal tissue the body is developing to block the opposite yin energy
No, it's because it wants to come out and he says it's actually starting to smell putrid
But it's on the back of the leg. So it means it's more yin. The front is young the back is yin
So that means that it's low quality meaning chemicals mixed in with the meat
Now if you're eating pork or beef or that kind of formula in America, do you think there are chemicals in it?
Of course guaranteed, right guaranteed. Yeah now what set it off?
Is the condiments now, there's a smell
The smell that's coming out is not the animal it can be and I'll get into that
Briefly, it's the condiments that are being used
With when they're eating that ketchup mustard spices Lowry's seasoning
That's a typical one. I mean whatever a steak sauce
Whatever right you condiments, right?
Mayonnaise with the meat with the meat taken with that meal is what spurred it off. So here's one example
I've experimented this if the person continues to eat what they're eating and they just removed all the condiments and spices
The smell would go away. Hmm, and it might shrink a little bit
Hmm, do you see the logic behind this the reasoning? Okay, let's go something that I don't think I brought up
I was going to bring up I went off on a tangent
Well a little something I just want to clarify real fast because it went by so quick I
Noticed okay, I get the left and right difference
But I was gonna ask about the front and back difference and then you addressed it
So could you make that a little more clear please? Because yeah, the front is young and the back is mean always
I've dubbed the bottom. Yes. Okay the bottom. Yes, because your body knows which is front which is back
Right. So for example, it's even in behavioral study
When you shoot someone when you're facing them
It's very forceful and when you shoot forward from the front of their if you shoot the front of their body
But if you shoot them in the back, it's considered very cowardly. Yeah, right, so
Cowardliness is Ying
Forcefulness aggressiveness is young
Again, even if we even with this methodology even works in behavioral studies
Okay and cultural studies, it's interesting
I'm gonna start saying mean more than mean yin whether I'm gonna drop the why
Okay, sure and just say yin because that's more proper yin and yang. So
Yang is forceful
concentrated
Focused bright yin is scattered soft
unfocused
Right. Okay now in order for food to be
Used by the body it has to become mean all food is yin and within all food you have the yin and yang
but once you take the food a
Certain amount that yin is converted to yang to protect the body because when you are taking in food
Which is always yin you need to take in yin
it nourishes the body and also and it gives you energy and the quality of energy and also a certain amount of that nourishment that
you take in is to
Protect the body replenish the skin maintain the bones give you strength. That's what I mean by protection, right?
Right. Okay replenish
The yang protects the yin
Always and when you lose the yin the last thing you can keep losing yin the yang is the last to go we talked about
that with people thinking that
Someone who's terminally ill is gonna have a speedy recovery
Because they got up and they looked like they were gonna be fine and then they died an hour later
Because all the yin was leaving while they're in bed
But the last hour when the yang leaves yang is very bright and focused the person looks very bright and focused
They'd get ready to come home, but then they die. Yeah, cuz they've actually let go of the heavier energy. Anyway, they've let go
Yes, yeah
Let go all the nourishment and all the life force. The last thing is the protection just like when you buy something a bubblegum
Eat all the soft yin stuff and the last thing you throw away is the wrapper, which is hard and thin, right?
Right the wrapper is the last thing right that's considered it's tossed so
When you're whatever eating on the go, let's say so
Yeah
So the you buy a hamburger wrapped in paper. The paper is the young part. The hamburger is the yin
But within the hamburger, there's even young and within the wrapper. There's even young right, right, right
So the protective aspect of the wrapper is young, but once you spread it out, you'll see how far it spreads out
That's very yin
It's amazing how it's just it has nothing to do with polarity by the way a lot of people mistake this is polarity
It's not polarity. It's antagonism
But not antagonism in a social behavioral way, but antagonistic in an energetic way
When something is too hot like an end you need a coolant system
When something gets too cold, you need a heating system to maintain a certain degree of life
This is the level of antagonism that I'm talking about. Okay, so
To go back to when I give another example someone has a brain tumor and it's in the middle of the head
So it's both left and right
And that means it's extremely yin because the top of the head is the most young part of the body, right?
It's the most focused. It's the highest part right the hardest part, right?
Noggin, right top of the noggin all the way at the top of the skull in the center by Camrille fissure area
It was more on the right side of it, but still
You know, anyway a lot of yin energy chemicals severe severe radiation will cause that to
That severe radiation internal ionization
Let where you get other things, but yeah exposure to frequent radiation and severe yin chemicals more than any sugar
See if you have a lot of sugar in your diet, which is yin
It'll decay the spine before it goes and builds a tumor in the head
But when you have a tumor in the head like that
It can go away if you have a just basically a grain based diet with some legumes and sea vegetable
But if you wanted to address
That because you have a brain tumor its energy too much yin ran up to the most young part of this
So the yin energy will run to the most young part of the body to make balance
The young energy too much young energy will run to the most yin part of the body to make balance, which is the feet
That's why you see very common
A lot of Americans over 50 if you see them in the summer like for their calves are dark red
They have sores on the lower part of their legs very common. There's swollen ankles and things like that, right?
Okay, all of those people eat excessive animal all of them
you'll never see anyone who's vegetarian eat that eat except for now the
The problem with the everyone going vegan is they don't understand the energy. They just think as long as it's not animal
I'll eat it and they eat the strangest combinations of stuff and then also remind me that dry skin too, right?
The dry skin comes along with that too
Okay, and dry skin is too much oil. Yeah, it could be too much vegetable or protein if it's just dry skin
It's too much oil and it could be vegetable oil too. But if it's dry skin and it flakes like eczema then it's animal protein
Right like dandruff is animal protein, right
So but it's an animal protein again processed animal so
Like processed would be you like eating Mexican food and the tacos are always cooked with lard
So you're not eating the pork, but you're eating the lard, right? So that would be dandruff. Yeah, okay
Okay
so
the brain tumor
have formed because too much yin extreme yin ran to the most extreme young part of the body with most yin part of the
Body is the bottom of the feet. The most young is the top of the head
So if you want to address that with a sledgehammer right away
we need to give something that is a
Biologically occurring substance or animal or plant that is very young and then make it even more young and administer it
So well, how what would we be now? We know that for example the most yin energy
That we know of is radiation gamma x-ray all that stuff, right
So what animal can take the most radiation is a joke about this since the 80s remember with the Russian was supposed to go
Reagan was gonna have his finger on the button, right?
And everybody was talking about this joke that the only thing that'll be alive after nuclear the roaches right cockroaches
Yeah, take they could take a lot of radiation, right? Yeah, are they technically an animal though?
I mean, I've always had that weird thing about insects insects or animals. This isn't it. This is extreme cases
I'm not saying you should do this, but this is the thinking behind it. Okay
So you have extreme mean so you have to balance it with extreme young. So that you take cockroaches now, they're not young enough
Because we want it we can they're young. They're gonna plenty young. Sorry
But can we make them even more young?
Yes, we take them and we carbonize them. We put them on a cookie sheet at 500 degree oven until they turn black
And then we grind them up and put them in a capsule and the person takes three capsules in the morning three capsules in the
afternoon and three capsules at night
Or actually three capsules in the morning through capsules in the afternoon even just don't do the ones at night
Okay, and within two weeks that brain tumor is almost diminished to nothing
Really?
Yeah, now you the thing is to borrow you notice
I didn't say find what chemical is young because chemicals are processed and removed from their original condition
The thing about applying what I'm saying is finding things that are naturally occurring
Yes, there you could find chemical substances made in the laboratory industrial byproducts that are more young than that
But it's not naturally. It doesn't have all the energy
Of a living thing living thing meaning plant animal right plant or animal, right?
Well, that was my argument with the iodine people were getting into, you know
Making sure they had plenty of iodine around and I'm going no that's not the way to do it with the extracted iodine
What you got to do is find something that has it in it
You know, well that the idea behind that is replacement therapy that if you load up on the iodine, you won't take the radioactive
But that's not true. It doesn't work that way either right, right?
It's it apparently works that way enough
But if you look at the full experiment, it doesn't really work either because they remember they practice exclusions. They will tell you
We tested this and it worked like that in this experiment
But they won't tell you they tried it on a thousand people only 20 of them that worked right? Yeah, they'll exclude the other right
They only tell you what were it right? So it's big exclusions 20 successes
Yeah, that's a lot. Yeah. All right. Well, you tried it on nine a thousand nine hundred eighty didn't work
It didn't do any inconclusive usually it's inconclusive. That's how we either they could go either way like with the sugar pills
Alright, so what do I mean by that?
So what do we let's go back to the person with the sore on their leg on the back, right?
Well, first of all
I'm a type of person that would always tell someone let's just go this way. Let me just preface this
If someone is eating McDonald's, well, that's all they eat. By the way. I have run into people like that back in the days in New York
Right. I'm gonna
You want to get them on a healthful diet?
Good what no I met a guy recently and I was a little surprised
It's like that's all he eats is stuff like that like out of a bag out of a drive-thru constantly and I'm like wow
I don't even know. Yeah, you're still here. Okay, the condiments will get him first
I mean, well, it will tip them over is the condiments by the way
You know, it's like the let you win a glass when something flows over the top
What you notice flowing over the top is what was already the last thing that was up there, right?
So when people get these bodily
Discharges it's the thing that pushed it over the top that comes out first
Mm-hmm
So when someone has a sore and it's not it'll probably end up smelling like a condiment that they're one of their favorite condiments ketchup
mustard mayo
Blowery seasoning something like that very much
So, you know, I'll get into why and I think I have if you understand the difference between chlorophyll and hemoglobin
You'll see what I'm talking about
There's only one thing that's different between chlorophyll and hemoglobin and that's another question
Okay
And the body turns chlorophyll and directly into hemoglobin simply by inside of the chlorophyll is a magnesium atom
And the identical molecule is hemoglobin, but the only difference is that magnesium is not there. It's an iron atom instead
so the body turns chlorophyll into hemoglobin by transmuting the magnesium in the chlorophyll into iron and
I will get we'll get into how that's done by the way because you can do it at home. I mean on a science experiment
Biological and the one lot of diseases are when the hemoglobin in the body turns back to chlorophyll in the bloodstream
Which is very toxic by the way
Well, it forms tumors and lymphomas and things like that
And it is possible in an instant for iron to go back to magnesium if the conditions are correct
This sounds crazy, right because it's not taught
So anyway, let's go back. So what do we do?
So let's say someone eats McDonald's all the time and you want to get them on a grain diet organic food
Okay, most most cases. Oh, what's wrong with you eating that bag food? You gotta stop that and eat. Well
Always right now what I would say is go ahead you McDonald's we're gonna try something
But this is how I'd like for you to try it
In your in-between time
I want you to get a pressure cooker make some brown rice and get some
Veggies and stuff like that when you come home tonight with your bag dinner or a bag lunch
Do me a favor and just put a little side plate of that rice and vegetable and have it with your McDonald's
Have some of it. Make sure you eat some of it
Right. So how's it been going there for a week? Yeah, I've been eating some of it
Yeah, and then you know, okay good. So what do you get?
All right, don't get the french fries eat your you know
Cut back right and then eat more of the rice, right keep eating the McDonald's two weeks later
Keep eating don't get the triple burger get the double burger and eat more rice and you see transition
Gradual changing. Yeah. Okay. Yeah, keep doing what you're doing, but just introduce because most people want to change it. Oh
Austerity I'm gonna lose it. No, just keep doing what you're doing
Just introduce the new thing in addition to and then you start decreasing one
Increasing the other right is you don't get the withdrawal that way you don't get that right very smooth transition
Okay phase it out kind of like what they tell you to do it and people do that with coffee
I don't know why they do it with coffee, but they do it with coffee where they phase the coffee out, you know
Yeah, dude
so you if it's the caffeine that's bothering you get the regular coffee and get the decaf and then
Instead of just three cups of coffee
Do two cups of coffee one cup of decaf right and then the next day or next week or next month do
One cup of coffee two cups of decaf and then another month
You're just on the decaf and now you can pretty much switch over to tea or right
Red bull. Yeah, whatever. It's not a shock. Yeah, but it's not a shock. Yeah. Yeah
Seven and seven at seven in the morning. Anyway
Anyway
Transition so okay back to the leg with the left. Yeah and the sore on the bottom on the back
Go ahead do what you're doing. I would diagnose that very simply
Conditionally without knowing this person as animal that is bought from a regular supermarket that is tainted with hormones
chemicals
pesticides by the way
when I say pesticides you'll find a lot of
Pesticides in meat not because they're spraying the cows with pesticides because the food that the cows are eating is loaded with pesticides, right?
right the growth, okay, so
What I would suggest is immediately start introducing these three things mint tea with golden seal and echinacea
If you can go to an herbal shop where they sell these things in bulk you walk in it smells really good
It's kind of earthy crunchy
Earthy place and they have jars and the jars have labels and it's in bulk and you take it out and weigh it
That's the best
We have a place here called aqua Vita that has just rows and rows of stuff that when I was in LA
I couldn't find the stuff that was here in Tucson. I was like fuck LA, you know
They don't have anything there. So anyway
You'll find them in Manhattan you'll find it in places like, New Mexico
the town, you know a lot of like Santa Fe or
Dallas
Silver City places in Colorado
Places we got a lot of these earthy crunchy types, you know what? I mean the earthy type the you know
Some places they might combine it with a vitamin shop to where they got the vitamins
But then they got a yeah in a little section, but then they have all the natural jars
Barefoot women with unshaved legs with hemp skirts and rope bracelets and anklets
Right with hairy armpits that that kind of place
Hempskirt and a rope necklace a necklace
Yes, exactly, right. Those are the ones yeah, you got okay
Okay that you see them run flying around and walking around just probably one of these shops nearby
There you go, right? Otherwise, you could find a golden seal echinacea mint
Maybe someone already put this together. Why?
right, those are
Antiseptic and they're mid-growth, but they're very yin. So what I would recommend for the left
Back is a yin treatment, but with a quality yang
the quality yang
would be
something like umeboshi plum
if you can get it make a
a
Kuzu K uzu which is a root starch. It's like cornstarch
But it's much better than cornstarch
You thicken that what's in some hot water and you put some plum in there and drink it
another if you don't want it if you don't have access to that a
Quality yin would be a parsley tea
Get yourself a bunch of parsley, you know when I say bunch they sell them in bunches for 57 cents at Walmart. They're fine
And and throw it in a pot boil to bring the water to a boil with a pinch of salt turn the water off
Throw the parsley in there put the lid on the next day
You open the lid for an eight hours and it's kind of gelled like jello
This aspect pot parsley has that ability, right? So it's very binding
And it's also grief growth
Another thing I would suggest for nutrition if this person wanted to stop
Eating and do a little I would recommend that
slow down on the intake, especially the animal a
nutritious meal in the glass
Would be yes, it's not seasonal, but you can try it is
Soy milk peanut butter and a banana in a blender
so you put the soy milk in the blender then put the peanut butter first and
Then the banana last and always by the way when you peel a banana
Always peel it from the blossom end first. It tastes different
It's amazing how it works, you know
You have the blossom end which is the bottom of the banana and then the stem end where all the bananas are tied together at
The top naturally, right?
Most people break off the stem and start peeling from the stem. No, no, no
Always peel it from the blossom end where the flower is on the bottom first and a sure you could do a double blind test
500 people and they'll all say the banana tastes better when you peel it from the blossom end first
Just to show you. Yeah. Now. This is not seasonal, but it can be a replacement for a short time if the person is hardy
It's very important. See when people are not hardy
They can't take the cold or the heat not eating seasonally is devastating
If someone is not hardy and they're frail or like a sensitive person they eat seasonally
They're in balance right but if someone is hardy
I've met some hardy people where it'd be, you know, really cold outside and they're out in the t-shirt doesn't bother them too much, right?
Or whatever, you know so you can do non-seasonal
Why did I suggest this because the peanuts are underground?
The soybeans are about waist high and the bananas are much higher and they're all very lean
At the same time. Okay, right to balance out the young that's happening as a nutrition
Right now I've been experimenting with soy milk since the 80s. I'm not a soy boy
Remember, there's so many varieties of soys and for the American market. They've been pushing animal grade soybeans
That's why when you look at the silk and all these soy milks are out there
They're so full of other things because they're not using quality. So I the only way a place you get quality soy milk is Asian
Traditional Asian and the best one is called West soy and it's usually organic even though it doesn't say it
On the label if you look at the ingredients usually it means it says organic soybeans naturally
But I've been experimenting with and believe it or not the Walmart brand great value organic soy milk is as good as the West soy
Believe it or not. And so is the organic Walmart peanut butter?
the great value
Yeah, Walmart also sells organic bananas. Oh, I want to mention this also
If you don't eat organic bananas, you're not eating bananas
You're eating some decorative thing that looks like a banana and I've mentioned this to Linda my wife many years ago
I said get the organic. Yeah, why is it when I buy bananas?
They taste good and when you buy them, they don't you know
Why because when they always buy bananas and make sure that they're organic and she's really yeah
There's a big difference between the flavor and the organic banana and the non-organic big difference
Huge same with apples, you know, if you but you don't buy an organic apple looks pretty but it doesn't taste like anything, right?
Now, by the way organic is a scam
When when they want to certify a batch of goods organic it has to be 60% of it has to be free of chemicals
And then it's a legally organic
That's the legal aspect right
Now you're a passing grade in school. They're 60% but yeah
Yeah, yeah exactly it doesn't mean that it was not it's not even how it's growing right let's sometimes the manufacturer put a label
It's organically growing blah blah blah, but the the legal American organic is it has to be 60% free of chemicals or whatever?
Yeah, right. Okay. So yeah. Yeah, so but anyway
Walmart, I did my research which is available to most people. They have organic bananas. They're only about three or four or five cents more
For the non-organic they have the organic peanut butter
Which is cheaper than skippy right and they have the organic great value soy milk you get the vanilla or the regular
I've tested them. I've tested soy milks for years now
West soy is the best
Yale's is very high quality. Also. Yale's why e o
apostrophe s
Which is named after the first?
acknowledged Chinese Emperor
is
It the soy milk is so rich and it's such a variety of soybean that it tastes like white corn sweet white corn
You ever have like sweet white corn how delicious just raw just bite into it, right?
That's what it tastes like when you drink that it's it's very yeah, it's pretty neat
But you can't find that here other than the can
So what what I would suggest is get the Walmart
Organic peanut butter organic bananas and the organic soy milk. It's in a half gallon thing. It's real cheap, too
Something
if you can't find the West soy either one because in other words
West soy is so good that if you want to get someone who drinks a lot of coffee off the dairy or children that are
into dairy in their cereal
Substitute it with West soy or the great value organic soy milk and they won't know it's like 2% milk
Okay, you know it doesn't look you know, like a lot of these milk substance. They taste terrible
Yeah, right
but if you have a child that is used to 2% or not whole milk or even whole milk and you use the
West so I were this great value organic
They won't tell the difference
So anyone who wants but listen if you drink too much so much you will have the same
Manifestations if you have too much dairy except you'll be a little smarter because too much dairy makes you dumb
Okay, or and and depressed by the way, you know
Do you ever notice how the they did the big dairy campaign got milk?
Yeah, and then at the same time there was the big depression campaign. Are you depressed?
Right because it causes depression in humans
It's amazing how when you you make the correlation and you see how it's actually manifesting
So anyway, we kind of went into a few things of jumping around a banana grove here. And yes, no, I
Not gonna say eat cockroaches. I gave that as an example, and I'm not gonna say it winter in the US have
Bananas, but winter bananas are harvested in the winter by the way
Right, just like oranges are harvested in the winter where they grow where they grow, right?
So I'm in Tucson and we have a lot of citrus here. Well, guess what? It's not till January
Well, so it's winter. It's cold here. But if the citrus is in balance, but if you take it up to New York
Oh, you're gonna lose vacuum. How do we know you lose the body's losing vacuum what develops in the body?
mucus
Yeah
Body when the body is losing vacuum where it wants to create a plug because it's losing vacuum
Just like you plug a tire when it's losing pressure
It develops mucus by the way for those that are new or maybe not
So I want you to go look up anatomy of a woman who is pregnant
What keeps the baby and all the other stuff from falling out? Oh, yeah in the cervix. It's what's it called
Is it anatomical point to it? It's called what the mucus mucus plug? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Perfect and all these things are all these signs and code. We're here to read the codes, right? Yeah
Definitely