Okay, Sonic Event 199, Rated Y, here we
are.
Greek, a little confusion because we did lose
Skype, RIP Skype, the other day, but anyway,
how are you doing?
Yeah, I'm all right.
I'm on the laptop, the old setup.
It's fine.
I think we're going to go to Jitsi,
practice that, I have to get another phone
because it doesn't support this or that.
It's crazy.
I just want to mention it's crazy.
Today I got confirmation I could draw funds
on the lab and all that, and as
soon as I got that message, the washing
machine breaks, the car computer burned out, yeah,
this happens all the time.
I think I went over this, the frustration
when I was building the Scalarator.
By the way, it's the one year anniversary
for the Scalarator.
Where are the chances of getting funding for
a lab for the Scalarator exactly, I'm sorry,
and the two year anniversary exactly on the
day, right?
Even so, getting funding for something like that
within two years is one of those wet
dreams usually for somebody.
It is.
Yeah, and that's just because it works really
well.
The Scalarator is a wet dream, by the
way, in its own right.
There you go.
Well, that was the double entendre there.
Yeah, that's right.
Anyway, let's get into questions, but everything, yeah,
it's like someone who was running this whatever,
is always like kind of, and I sound
like whatever, they're putting the thumb on me.
It's like, nah, we don't want you moving
too fast, so we're going to burn out
your car computer and break your washing machine
while you're doing a load, and we're going
to prevent you from getting on the audio
because you have a DAC, a high end
DAC plugged in, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
I'm like, you know, screw you.
Well, it wouldn't be memorable unless they were
screwing with you a little bit, and you
know, the funny thing is I tested this
with three different people yesterday, Jitsi, just to
make sure that it was an easy connect
audio wise, so I connected with three different
people that are just, you know, subscribers, and
I ended up talking to them, and it
was very easy.
It was very simple.
They were on video.
I didn't even need the video.
We're talking this and that, and they wind
up talking to me quite a while, and
I'm like, oh, this is no problem.
All I got to do is send a
link to the Greek and done, and it
was my fault.
Yeah, I had a homemade DAC plugged in
that takes control of the sound card, so
no matter what adjustments you make in the
settings, it doesn't override it until you unplug
the damn thing, and I had to do
one of those Terminator scans on it, like,
what the hell is preventing this?
It's got to be that, and yeah, okay,
so let's get into some questions.
Yeah, meanwhile, on my end, I'm just saying,
I was sitting here trying to scan everything
and going, what the hell did I do
wrong, and I couldn't find anything, and I'm
going.
Yeah, because it's always your fault anyway, right?
Well, I assume that, to be honest with
you, not just with you.
I just always assume it's my fault.
Anyway, it doesn't matter.
Let's not get into that.
Who cares what I think?
Here we go.
Can Greek comment on if antagonist relationships in
the realm of nine-star key work, okay,
this I didn't quite understand, but I guess,
can you comment on antagonist relationships in the
realm of nine-star key work, which is
a reference to an earlier Sonic where you
talked about that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, definitely.
I've been in them, and it feeds, what
it does, antagonism would be like metal and
earth because metal cuts earth, right, so, or
wood and fire, right, imagine wood and fire,
right?
So who's the winner in that one?
Guess.
The fire.
Fire consumes wood.
So, you know, the metal consumes the soil,
the fire consumes, so that's how that would
go.
Well, unless you have ridiculous proportions, obviously, if
you dump, you know, eight million pounds of
wood on top of a campfire, yeah, you
know, fire loses it.
Because they're in a relationship one-on-one,
it would be a parity on the allotted,
you know, amount, right, it would be how
much one can do, so, and of course,
if your water and someone else's soil, you're
going to make mud, right, and now it's
not always like that because I'm giving the
Western perspective on these things, you know, like,
for example, when we want to show something
alarming, we use red in the West, and
something sickly, we use green, you know, in,
or whatever, it's the opposite in the East,
right, like red is good luck, or here,
it's warning, right?
Yeah, let me add a question from a
different listener, which followed up to the original
question, which will fit with what you're talking
about right now, can Greek also explain why
nine-star key astrology would be a better
system for looking into someone's life than Western
astrology, Vedic astrology, and other systems?
Sure, sure, it would be like asking Spock
that question, not because I'm Spock, but asking
a Vulcan that question, because nine-star key
did not come about through just like geomancy
and, you know, reading tea leaves, for about
two or three thousand years, there were people
by imperial order assigned multi-generation to go
and scour the cities and the countryside and
keep records and statistics, and at the end
of the year, like a census, they would
compile all this information they gathered when people
were born, when they were born and all
that, and see what the tendencies were, these
are not presumed, this is all gathered like
statistical data, believe it or not, it's not
like reading tea leaves and someone said some
psychic, well this is it, you know, no,
no, this stuff is based on what you
would call science today, what science should be,
gathering information, collating it, making a report.
Well, because logic is a much more sensible
system is how Spock would respond, yeah, okay.
It's not presumptive, in other words, it's by
using averages, you know, people that have a
mole on their left cheek, what is their
life like, when were they born, you know,
like people who have a mole on their
left cheek, they can't be very difficult to
manage other people, they're usually introverted, they might
be good artists, you know, but if you
make them like a manager of a Starbucks,
the business will go down, it's just a
damn mole on your cheek, right, stuff like
that, that they looked at, and because the
nine star key stuff that we get, like
in these little, someone very graciously sent me
a little paperback book, and I'm very gracious
by looking through it, but I'm like, oh,
this is just like a basic of the
basic, imagine the cliff notes of the cliff
notes, right, like if you had a book
that was 2,000 pages thick, can you
make a 15 or 80 page cliff notes,
it wouldn't do it justice, right, you would
need at least a 400 page book to
tell you what's going on in a very
information jam-packed 2,000 page book, so,
but with nine star key, we get the
most basic of the most basic, but it
doesn't mean we're lost, we have an outline,
and then you can keep digging and researching
further, unfortunately we don't have good libraries to
go to anymore that house this information, and
the internet's becoming a wasteland, so all I
can say is do the best you can,
right?
I'm actually going to make a bit of
a trip to the local library soon here
in Macon, Georgia, I want to see what
condition it's in, and see what they're doing
there, because I've heard stories, so I want
to go check it out for myself, and
see, because I haven't been to a library
in many years, ever since I moved from
the northeast, anyway, I was just letting you
know that, so I'll report on that when
I come back, and maybe we'll have more
to discuss, so here's Let me tell you,
I spent a lot of time at the
main library in New York, and the one
that was built in 1902 on 42nd and
5th, which is a great place, even for
architectural students, even if you're not going to
read a book, just go look at the
architecture, but where I sat, I was like,
I used to tell guys, you know, you
want to go meet girls at bars, man,
go to the library, they have the cutest
librarians, but anyway, I was 20 years old,
21, 22, so about 27, but not all
of them, you know, some of them forget
to shave, but anyway, what I mean is,
when I got used to that experience, and
there's a big major library in Brooklyn, which
is also very good, not as good, it's
right there at the Grand Army Plaza area,
Park Slope, the major one there, which is
very, they have an excellent Egyptian display, all
this other stuff, and that was, they have
the books that no one wants, you know,
and one of the books I took out
once from the Brooklyn one was the Ten
Worst Popes of All Time, that's when I
started really realizing how everything is backwards, but
what I want to say is, when I
came to Tucson in 98, I said, like
you said, let me go check out the
library here, right?
So I walked through, it was like, nobody
there, and I was looking at what they
had, and it's basically like school textbooks, right?
And I'll tell you in a minute what
I think of that.
And suddenly a librarian comes out and says,
oh yeah, I told her, you know, I'm
from New York, moved to Tucson, and I
was, she goes, oh, okay, everything on this
side is fiction, everything here is non-fiction.
I looked at her, I said, darling, based
on what I've seen so far, everything you
have is fiction, you know, because remember, because
the books that they were showing and the
non-fiction were like college textbooks, which are
fiction, right?
Bullshit, right?
And I was like, darling, everything you have
is fiction, and I walked out, never been
back, there's no reason to.
You know, I can recognize a college textbook,
you know, from a mile away, I could
smell it, you know, it's all propaganda, right?
So anyway, that's what I think.
I hope you don't find that at MAKE,
and I hope you find some old stuff.
No, I hope so too, because that, the
chances are, you might, here in the South,
you know, it depends.
It could be high quality or low quality.
Very high, very good chances of finding it.
So anyway, another comment here is, the stuff
from Walter Russell I read was mind-blowing.
Funny how they describe him on the Wikipedia
page as an, quote, American artist.
It looks like very little credit was given
to him for his work as a scientist.
Well, because who gets more money?
Okay, remember years ago, people asked me about
CERN?
You know what CERN is?
It's like, remember that show Pimp My Ride?
Oh yeah.
Yeah, it's kind of, what do you remember
about, if you were to explain it in
less than 10 seconds, it's kind of gaudy
or bodacious, overdone.
You put crazy things in a car, where
they were putting televisions and fish tanks and
jacuzzis in a car.
Yeah.
Right.
So what CERN is telling you is, ha
ha, we have access to the credit system
and you don't, which is unlimited money, right?
That's all there, right?
So do the artists say that?
Do the artists say, ha ha, we have
unlimited access to the credit system?
No.
They keep them what?
What are they, what do, how are artists
described?
Starving artists.
There you go.
Right.
So, so when they put him in the
category as an artist, right away, you're like,
eh, I'm not impressed because what impresses people?
What was the whole purpose of Pimp My
Ride?
Oh yeah, just to show your wealth, to
be impressive.
Exactly.
You had the unique.
Yeah.
And what's the whole purpose of CERN?
Same thing.
I've told people over the years, and if
you ask me to prove it, I can,
but I won't.
Now I'm too much in another direction.
I can do what CERN is doing on
a desktop, like a benchtop, like in my
kitchen, you can do the same thing they're
doing.
You don't need that scale.
Right.
Um, very simple if you understand the principle
of what they're doing.
So, um, like for example, and I'll just
end it right here.
Everyone talks about the speed of light.
Okay.
But no one talks about the speed of
magnetism.
Don't touch it.
It's a hell of a lot faster than
the speed of light.
And what are they using to drive CERN?
Magnetism.
To do what?
Right.
You can figure out the rest of your,
you can do that irrespective of scale.
So anyway, just like Pimp My Ride, do
you really need your car to be done
by Pimp My Ride to have a good
car functioning?
No, not even.
Absolutely not.
Yeah.
So actually there was a YouTube channel that
would follow the Pimp My Ride cars years
later and like half of them are in
junkyards.
Literally.
Mostly.
Yeah.
Right.
You've seen that.
So, uh, yeah.
All right.
What else?
Okay.
So here's the last one.
Uh, does the Greek have thoughts on the
concept of controlling one's own environment by strategically
and intelligently selecting colors and color schemes on
walls, clothing, et cetera, to create circumstances and
encourage things to be much like they used
to do in institutions when they wanted to,
uh, impress upon the inmates, calm and stuff
like that.
Is there a way to sort of adapt
a color scheme or a color wheel to
create certain results automatically or to encourage them
in one's own environment?
That's the question.
Yeah.
I would research Abraham with an I, Kareem,
biogeometry, synesthesia, dowsing, radionics, uh, like back to
the prisoner thing.
I mean, you know that it's a fact,
uh, well, I haven't done it.
I haven't looked into it much, but I
keep, keeps popping up that if you surround
someone with the color pink, you typically, um,
they become 10 to 20, 20% weaker
muscularly if they're surrounded.
That's why one of the football teams, they
painted the visitors, a locker room pink.
They thought it was should be demoralizing.
It was more than that.
Now, what you learn from Abraham Kareem is
with biogeometry, there is each, a lot of
people mistake this with the feng shui or
what they call feng shui, uh, that the
wall should be different colors like black for
the North whatever for water and wealth and
red.
And, um, you don't have to do the
entire wall.
So if you determine through your own geomancy,
which is literally means the study of the
earth and that type of, let's say, we
might call in quotes, divination or dowsing.
If a room needs red, for example, you
can make a small two by two inch
square red square and put it underneath a
picture.
It doesn't have to be visible.
Just the presence of that red in that
direction is fine.
Just to give you an example, the same
thing works.
This is like not a segue, but it's
the same subject.
Smart meters affect some people, right?
Like they get this acute tinnitus.
Some people get nauseous.
Some people come down with physical.
It's not everyone right now, just like for
example, cell phones seem to be harmless.
But once I was on a cell phone
for nine hours and I did get the
side of my head did feel like it
was cooked.
Yeah.
Right.
So what I tell people for smart meters
is if it's on the wall of the
house, which it usually is, what you do
is you put a mirror behind between you
and the as close as possible to the
smart meter.
So if the smart meter, let's say, is
on the wall of the back room of
your house and you find out where that
is on the inside, you just put a
mirror up on that area where the smart
meter is.
But the mirror is facing the smart mirror,
the smart meter, not the inside.
So inside the room, all you see is
the back of the mirror.
Ugly.
Right.
So you just cover that with another picture.
You know, years ago, that works reflecting the
energy back out.
Right.
Years ago, you brought this up on an
on a Sonic and Ocelli in the Greek,
and I passed that along to a handful
of people and they reported back to me
that it worked actually.
Yeah, they felt the difference.
Yeah.
They felt the difference like immediately within a
day, the problems they were having sort of
started to go away and they play strategically
placed mirrors for a couple of different reasons
facing outward.
Like basically it's up against the wall.
And like you said, just put a picture
on the back of the mirror and boom.
Now it's a decoration and it serves a
purpose.
It's it's hidden.
Yeah.
And it's hidden or buried.
If a new new construction, put it in
the wall.
If it's a new if you know the
meter is going there, I mean, new construction,
it's framed out.
Right.
Go ahead and put it inside the wall.
Yeah.
But that would be that would be the
most hidden way nobody would ever see the
thing.
Exactly.
Or if it's mounted like we have a
gas meter like that and it comes out
of the ground, it's two inches from the
wall because it's connected to the ground.
You just go outside and put the mirror
between the outside of the house and the
meter.
I actually have a bunch of old mirrors.
I used to save them.
You know, when my wife first met me,
I was living alone and she thought I
was narcissistic or whatever, because all the mirrors
I had and I said, those mirrors are
strategically placed, one opposite the front door, one
here, one there.
You know, she's like, oh, really?
You know, I thought you just like looking
at yourself.
I'm like, yeah, that that's another story, though.
But no, the mirrors are there strategically, you
know, again, like the nine star key and
the colors in the room change energy.
The simplest way is, you know, the the
idea in Feng Shui or Feng Shui in
Chinese, which means water, wind or water, earth,
water, wind, typically a mirror of any size.
It could be a mirror, an eighth inch
in diameter, which wouldn't be qualified as a
mirror because some of these office pens have
a shiny tip, right?
That is an eighth of an inch in
diameter, right?
Just opposite the entrance door.
What the story behind that, that they told
the base people back then is that if
a demon wants to come into your abode,
the purpose of the mirror is the demon
is so ugly, he'll see the mirror, get
scared, right?
And then run out again.
That's what they told the simple people, right?
He'll be scared of his own image.
So that's how I tell people, you know,
basically, but it has a lot to do.
Remember, I said the gods are humans or
humans, people or like people, but they just
have higher tech.
They get away with saying they're gods because
whatever, right, you know, so the tech of
the mirror, like what we consider harmful from
smart meters, has always been around and always
used for people or against people or certain
groups against other groups or for benefit of
some, all this technology we have has always
been around.
And I've told people in the past, you
can't show me any time in history, if
you really study any society that did not
know about electricity, everybody knew about it.
It was just not used.
Like, for example, I don't want to get
into a whole thing here.
But cell phones, cell phones were invented in
the 1930s.
And anyone with a truck that ran along
highways that had the lines had what looked
like a regular phone receiver in a box.
And they were trucking and they would pick
up the phone.
And as long as they're on that highway,
there were telephone radio lines along the highway
and they can make a phone call to
their dispatcher.
Where do you want me?
This is where I am.
This is where the package is good.
It was very common.
And actually, there are YouTube videos, cell phones
in the 1940s, films in the 1930s and
40s.
About that you see a trucker on the
phone, but it looks just like the hand
receiver that you and I grew up with,
right?
Landline, right?
Yeah.
And then what happened in the 70s that
they had too much control over the truckers.
They said, screw this stuff.
Let's get CB radios.
We're independent.
Now we can communicate wherever we go.
Remember the CB craze in the 70s, right?
They even did a movie called Convoy or
whatever based on it.
It was about the CB radio was a
representation or an expression of a form of
rebellion.
The Citizen's Band, which some people got bases
and they could communicate with people over long
distances.
There was all kinds of stuff going on.
But what happened in the 70s, you see,
it was a rebellion.
If you look at the films that were
done around it, it was like they were
rebels.
Why?
Because then they can get off the main
cell lines.
I told this to people years ago.
I had a client.
They had these twins and they said, these
twins are special.
They're really smart.
They were raised by nannies and all that.
And I asked them, OK, if they're so
smart, they're like five years old boy and
girl fraternal.
I said, they're always watching TV.
And the parents said, we don't want your
services anymore because I told them, don't let
the TV raise your children.
Right.
They didn't like that.
But someone's got to tell them.
Right.
Well, I asked the little children, do you
know when you're considered geniuses?
Yeah, we're considered geniuses.
I said, when was it?
How long has the TV been around?
It's always been around.
Right.
They didn't know the TV was invented.
The electric TV was invented by Farnsworth in
the 30s.
They didn't know that.
They thought it went back to the dinosaurs.
Yeah, of course.
Yeah.
Because they don't know the history of it.
Much like these young people now think that
there was always cameras everywhere you went.
So, you know, because that's the way it's
always been.
Yeah.
It's funny when you see there's actually videos
I noticed even not recently, but even 10
years ago, some young people, they gave them
a regular rotary phone.
They picked up the receiver part, but they
were like, what do we do now?
You know, you remember the rotary dial, right?
I was like, man, that's worse than watching
a monkey trying to fuck a football.
But anyway, yeah, true enough.
Okay, well, look, fair enough.
I think this is all very interesting.
Is there anything else that you want to
add for today or, you know, a bunch
of stuff, but I think we're going to
make this one super short.
We'll make it up on the next one.
How's that?
Look, that sounds good.
I want to let you know, that whole
color thing, though, was inspired by an earlier
sonic where you mentioned the color blue for
repelling bugs in the yard.
Oh, yeah.
That was from a year.
That works.
Just blue, any blue around light bulbs and
the bugs go away because it's the yin
yang principle.
You can apply universal principle.
You can apply principles that are like, how
would you call it when something's already thought
out for you?
It's like eating out of a can, right?
Microwave dinner, you know, there's a lot of
pre-packaged stuff.
Yeah.
Do this and do this and you get
that.
That's fine.
But I like using universal principles.
By the way, I've gotten a lot of
feedback you know, bugs around the light.
What do you have a light at night
outside the house, usually by the door?
And all the bugs are there.
What happens when you open the door?
All the bugs come in, yeah.
Well, if you put some blue tape or
some blue color, electric blue works best, like
the most vibrant blue you can get, cobalt
blue, they stay away.
Most of them do.
And I've gotten a lot of feedback on
that.
And it works.
That's based on universal principle, yin and yang.