Sonic Event 23, Ocelli in the Greek.
So I do that at the beginning, I'm not sure if I really need to, but I guess I should
mark the occasion.
Anyway, I'm here with the Greek as per usual, because otherwise it wouldn't be Ocelli in
the Greek.
Simple things to be pointed out, right?
Occasionally.
You know, I want to start with the chat, but I don't know if I should.
I saw something mentioned about water and things like that, I don't know if that's what's
on your mind.
Yeah, so I said, let's just start recording, we'll call this shoot the shit.
Shoot the shit, number 23.
Yeah, so in the chat, yeah, it's pretty responsive.
Sometimes I'll get on there, it'll just be one.
Sometimes I'll get on there, it'll be nine.
So it's getting some activity, it's a good place to...
It's like the suggestion box, you know?
Right, and if you're listening to this and you haven't been there, by the way, all you
got to do is scroll down and toward the bottom of the page where I put the playlist all together,
you'll see that there is a chat box there, and it's a Chatango box.
You don't need to sign up if you don't want to.
You can go in there anonymously if you like, but yeah, people are communicating right there
about these sonics specifically.
So there you go.
Yeah, yeah.
Wasn't the one that you...
Bring up some, let's see what you got.
What caught your eye, so to speak?
Well, what caught my attention was somebody was talking about the water and magnets, and
they had gotten, I don't know, magnets out of a speaker.
You had brought that up on a previous sonic.
So I don't know if...
That was my first thought, actually, is that's usually where I find magnets around the house,
just laying around.
You know, what about the magnets that are in speakers?
Did you communicate with that guy about that?
Yeah, Vandy, I did drop a message back.
He's using eight small magnets.
I guess they're stacked.
I don't know.
See, if they're stacked, it's not going to work too well.
If they're each separate, it'll work much better.
So he didn't say if he stacked them or had them in series.
But the key with the magnetic water is it's not really even magnetic water.
I think we went over it on a sonic before.
The monkey human is easily fooled.
So you get a magnet, and I'll just do a quick recap here.
And boom, this side sticks to the fridge real strong, or metal, and the other side does
too.
But when we put these two magnets together, they repel, and then when we turn them around,
they stick together.
Wow, that's really a strong magnet.
That's a weak magnet.
Oh, look at what magnets can do, right?
That's the typical...
That's about...
This attitude that I just mentioned, this perception, is you'll get all the way up to
university and research labs, too, everything I just told you.
So they say, oh, we can magnetically treat water.
So they take...
Oh, where's the magnet that's so strong?
Get the strong magnet, Jack.
Get the strong one.
Not the weak one.
Okay, here, it's really strong.
Boom, sticks, pulls it off a piece of metal.
And the side that's sticking to the metal, let's say, he's putting it on the water pipe.
Wrong.
Yeah, but see, there's nothing beyond the...
When you're about nine years old, right, and you're in grade school, you're in about the
third grade or so, you play with magnets like this, and that's about as far as it goes, to
be honest.
Well, they get fooled.
They get fooled.
Yeah, what sticks to it?
What doesn't?
What's strong?
What's not?
And that's about it.
I mean, you've never really experienced.
There's that lady, she went to live with the gorillas, and they were always hiding out,
and she took her...
Jane Goodall was her name, I think.
I think so.
Yeah.
She took a silver bracelet that she had, or a watch, really shiny, and she hung it from
a tree branch in an opening, and the gorillas were like, oh, look at that, right?
That's what people are doing with magnets.
So what we've discovered, the corporate we, collective we, is that between the two poles,
by the way, magnets do not attract or repel.
That is a vortex, like a screw going through the magnet, right?
So if you spin a globe looking from the top down, it looks counterclockwise, but same
spin direction.
If you look from underneath, it looks clockwise.
It depends on which angle you're viewing that screwing action, right?
It's a vortex that goes right through the magnet.
And by the way, magnets don't...
The poles, opposite poles do not attract, because if that were true, if you're holding
a bar magnet, let's say, or a round magnet in your hand, and the poles are attracting
to each other, they would do it already on the magnet, and there would be no magnetism
ever, right?
They would just come together internally.
Why do they need another magnet, you see?
So all this basic stuff, if you want to hear about someone who's more sarcastic, is a lot
fatter than me, and has got tattoos, not like me, I have no tattoos, Ken Wheeler.
Ken Wheeler on YouTube.
I don't endorse everything he says, but I endorse his magnetic stuff mostly.
I've always been saying similar things, but his experimentation and point of view, if
he can handle it, is worth a while.
But there's something between the poles where nothing...
If you put it against the fridge, it doesn't want to go there, right?
Right.
It doesn't stick.
That's called the block wall.
Where it doesn't attract or repel, that's where you want the water to pass.
But what's interesting is now we've developed another way to do it, if you don't have a
round magnet, using any shape magnet in a star configuration.
It's like a daisy chain, and what you basically do is you lay all the magnets out so they're
all attracting to each other, and then you spread them out, so nothing really...
If you put it on a refrigerator, nothing will stick to it, and the water pipe goes right
through that.
It's just basically daisy chaining, shorting out the magnetic field.
I know the best way to do this is with pictures.
I found that no matter how descriptive I get, people still need pictures to a certain
degree.
I do, but when you look at a piece of land, they have the blueprint or the plot on a drawing,
but they also have what's called the legal description.
Oh, how boring.
You ever read one of those legal descriptions, starting from the west-east corner of here,
going to the north-south corner there, and it's so boring.
It tells you about the orientation, the actual pitch, here's the angle from this and that.
Yeah, but if you read all that, a paragraph of describing the land's location on the
earth, it's boring as hell, but if you set your mind to it, you can put those words into
action.
That's why, for example, I tell people, people like studying the Bible, I say, look, you
go on the internet.
There's not one image of what the seven-branch lampstand or the Ark of the Covenant on the
internet images that is accurate.
Not a one.
Not one.
I tell people the way you do that is you get an eight-year-old with a pencil, and you read
the part where it tells you what the lampstand should look like or the Ark of the Covenant
should look like.
I said an eight-year-old because that's all you require in terms of education level, which
would be third grade or such.
While you're reading how these things should be made and what they should look like, start
sketching it out.
When you're done with your sketch, and by the way, if whoever is sketching the description
that you're reading for the Ark of the Covenant or the seven-branch lampstand, whoever's
sketching it, anywhere in the world, you get a hundred people, as long as they can sketch
and do what it says in terms of description, and you've finished, all the sketches will
look very similar, by the way, but nothing like what the images they show you in religions.
Not at all.
This is a major problem here with descriptions and attitudes.
What I mean by attitude is, you see the magnet's really strong this way, so that's where we
should put the water, right?
No.
That's not how it works.
I'm not sure, again, going back to the chat, the orientation, it's got eight 20-millimeter
magnets.
Are they stacked?
Are they separate?
I don't know.
We'll leave that at best.
I wrote the, if you stack them, I'm presuming they're stacked, what happens when you start
stacking magnets, they get a little stronger, but that block wall, instead of it being an
inertial plane through the middle, starts to spiral and get away from the center and
spread out.
You don't want to stack them more than two or three, three or five.
By the way, when you're doing magnets, odd numbers, please.
Odd numbers, okay.
Don't stack two, stack three magnets, five magnets, seven magnets, why?
Because whenever you do an odd number stack, you're always going to have a center one.
Let's say you do seven magnets, right?
You're going to have a center magnet, the fourth one, and you're going to have three
on the left, three on the right, or three up, three down, right?
Or if it's five, you have two on the left, two on the right, or, yeah, gotcha, okay.
So on and so forth, so you're always going to get a better energetic symmetry using odd
numbers whenever you're doing stuff, also with capacitors and inductors if you're doing
circuitry.
Anyway, yeah, so the magnetic water is quite, it's not magnetic water because if you're
eluding, meaning avoiding what they call a magnetic field, is it really magnetic water?
And actually, it's not.
What we're doing is taking advantage of the inertial plane, which is the main part of
the dielectric, has to do with potential.
We're using the maximum potential.
Potential is, it's taught, by the way, in rudimentary school, the physics, they do have
a proper description of it.
Potential is something's potential.
Shouldn't I use that word again to describe it, to define it?
No, it's what it could possibly exhibit, but it hasn't done it yet.
So when you're holding, let's say, a grenade, that's its maximum potential, but when you
explode the grenade or the fireworks, it has no potential, but most people will think that
explosion or the grenade exploding is the potential.
No, no, no.
The potential is when it's sitting on your desk with the ring in it still, you know what
I mean?
Well, because it has the potential to do something else.
That's right.
Once it's been exploded, it's, yeah, prior, it's putting it in order.
So once it's done what it's done, then it's already done it, there's no potential left.
That's that.
Right.
It's like what's in stock.
You know, if you open a store and you've got, you know, the fridge is all full of beer,
you've got great potential.
But if you sold all the beer, now you've got no potential, right?
But you'd rather sell all the beer.
You saw people focus on the outcome more than the potential.
So what we're doing is chasing the potential energy and leaving it there.
And some real incredible stuff going on with it.
What, okay, before we get on to the next one, what happens is the actual total dissolved
solids goes down and the alkalinity starts to fluctuate.
Yeah.
Maybe we'll talk a little bit about transmutation and what's going on with certain things.
What else, what else caught you there on the chat?
Well, on the chat, there was also this discussion about two Adams.
Now, I mean, look, anybody who's, again, at that third grade level is probably familiar
with the story of Adam.
I mean, that's supposed to be the first man in quotes, right?
Well, sort of, sort of, it's, it's, it goes back and forth.
It's really a group of people called Adam.
You know, like, I don't know.
It's done.
If you're in England, you know, it's like, I feel like an Indian because Indian food
is their main thing because, you know, white people can't cook.
Oops.
Did I say that?
You did.
Oh, no.
Okay.
So they, they adopted a lot of these Northern countries.
Their main dishes are from the, where they colonized and brought over delicious food
and culture.
Yeah.
So, say, if I feel in India, let's say you want Indian food in England, they say, oh,
I could really feel like an Indian.
I could just murder one.
Well, so it's used in that sense, you know?
Well, in America, practically none of the cuisine in quotes is actually American in
its origin.
I mean, think about the most commonly consumed things.
They mess it up.
Like, pizza in America is not like pizza originally, but yeah.
But it was popularized here.
Yeah.
That's the thing, though.
It becomes popularized here, but it's not, it's not its point of origin, you know?
Right.
And the thing is, the thing is when you, when you imitate, you should do it better, not
degrade it.
That would be the best way to go.
Yeah.
I mean.
Yeah, because imitation is flattery.
They're not, it's not flatter.
American pizza is not, well, actually a lot of, if you go to Italy, a lot of people don't,
if you're raised on New York pizza, by the way, you're not going to like the pizza there
because they sell it in a bakery cold, you know, unless you go to a Napoli, which is a
different thing.
And I, by the way, I want to not talk about food, but I've perfected the Napoli pie.
And you don't have to use the special flour and all the special stuff.
It's a no need.
And you leave it alone and you just do it.
And it's just, yeah.
Best pizza.
I used to say, oh man, I want to go back east and get some pizza.
You know what?
I make the best pizza right here, right now, here in Tucson, not, I don't have to go to
New York for a slice.
I think I sent you some pictures of pies that I made here.
Yeah, they look great.
I mean, but I'm always thinking about, I want to go back to New York or New Jersey to get
some pizza because God, it's awful here.
If you buy something, somebody eats here.
But here's the thing.
I was like that up until about a year ago.
And I finally perfected the Napoli style, which is, it's very, very pillowy, soft with
a slight crunch.
When, if you remember the pizza in New York and Jersey, it's a little tough sometimes.
You got to pull on it, you know, and it has this high tension.
This is different.
This is the Napoli style and it's very different, but I've got a way to do it that is just killer.
And anyway, let's not get into the tangent on the food.
Well, yeah.
So what were we on?
We weren't on pizza.
We were on Adam, but that's okay.
We could, we could go.
That's what I thought.
Why not?
Right.
Well, here's the thing.
There's a real, real problem and I don't have a filter for this.
I used to.
I used to have a filter for it.
Anything that comes from churchianity or Christianity, I have, I take out a big hammer, you know,
the BFH, big fucking hammer.
Boom.
Right.
Or in the cartoons, they have the four fingered Mickey Mouse hand.
I want to put one of those big hands on a stick and you see people left and right.
You know what I mean?
So the Christianity and the churchianity stuff is like the medical stuff, you know, you got
high blood pressure and your blood sugar is off.
Both are fiction, but people rely, I mean, how many people you got on high blood pressure
and diabetes?
50 million in the country, at least like that.
Yeah.
It's, it's all complete fiction, you know, AIDS and all that.
It's, it's, it's, you know, it's made up for, uh, it's kind of like the, um, the printers
and the cell phones, you know, once they've been on a certain amount of copies or calls
that they stopped working, you know, so you could buy another one.
It's the same exact, um, which was a topic I might want to touch on how it goes back
to the emo and all that.
But yeah, that's, um, the Adam is, is if you read it very carefully, there's, there's two
sets.
We've gone over this.
You've got, um, men and women that are made together and blessed and then there's a Sabbath
and then they make this guy out of the dust of the earth and he's alone, right.
And, um, in, in the garden, uh, and they say, it's not good to be alone.
Right.
Uh, he is alone.
It's not good to be alone.
And we, Oh, by the way, we've got, we've got a great, we could make, make a great partner
for you.
Adam.
Excellent partner.
Best ever.
Adam says, what's it going to cost me?
This is going to cost you a leg.
Adam says, what do you got for a rib anyway?
Uh, okay.
So, so he gets out of his rib, right.
Uh, they, they make the woman and then they get kicked out and do they get a blessing?
No, it's like actually the earth is cursed.
So we have two completely different stories, two Adams and they're about 2000 years apart.
So if you, anyone digests that, you know, you have, I call it six day man and eight
day man, right?
Cause the seven, you have the six day Adam, then you have the Sabbath, the seventh day
and then the eighth day, right?
Cause they didn't make him during the Sabbath.
It was after the Sabbath.
Now I'm not saying that I, you should believe in any of this.
I'm just saying, are you getting the descriptions right?
You see what I mean?
This goes back to exactly what I was saying, that if you go online and put in the seven
branch lamp stand or the arc of the covenant, there's not one image that's accurate, not
even close, right?
But if you actually read the description in the text and had someone next to you pencil
it out while you're reading it, you'll compare it to what's out in the world and it's not
the same at all, right?
This is the same thing that's going on with Adam and all this other stuff.
Then I noticed there was something else about sin.
Um, yeah, that too.
Hey, I just want to break, look, look, I want to let you guys know, I don't sin.
I avoid it.
And this is how you avoid sin.
If you don't say you're going to do something and you know you can't do it because the
word sin means to fall short.
So let's say you're throwing darts and you say, I got three darts in my hand.
I'm going to get three bullseyes and you don't, you just send, right?
Cause, because did you make, did you make the mark?
Did you do what you said?
No, right?
So, uh, it's missing the mark.
So if you say, I'm going to do this, this and that, and you don't, or you try to do
it and you fail or don't succeed, you, you, that's a sin.
You missed the mark, right?
Well, that's all it is.
So sin, no one's doing anything about sin.
Uh, if you actually look on a higher spiritual level, the thing about sin in the Bible is
that we are imperfect.
In other words, what do they say when you've got more desire than ability and you get yourself
in trouble?
There are a lot of cliché terms for that, isn't there?
Yeah, of course.
Stuff with writing checks, stuff with, you know, my eyes are hungrier than whatever, you
know, right?
Yeah.
So, in other words, man's desires and thoughtful abilities and perspectives on what he can
do overrides his ability and he ends up flat on his face.
So, that's what sin is.
Does that mean that it's a sin if you make an attempt, an honest attempt to do something
and you fail?
I mean, that seems a little strange to me.
It is a sin, yeah, because no one sets out to build a tower that can't succeed.
In other words, you measure twice, cut once.
Or what man does is, listen, I cut this board twice and it's still too short.
Anyway.
Okay.
Cut it a third time, it's still too short.
It's still going to be too short, yeah.
So, it's like, wait a second, wait a second, you got your perspective is all screwed up.
So, even with the Christ, with the woman being stoned, he says, go and sin no more.
Right?
So, in other words, that could mean several things on a high spiritual level.
It means don't do adultery, or if you do adultery, don't get caught, because when you do adultery,
you're not supposed to get caught, right?
Do you see the two levels, the two-edged sword?
How I get away from, unless there is a, here's the thing.
Why, just like with the magnets, why is it that everything in the world has to be between
five and eight-year-old mentality?
Right?
Even spirituality, right?
Like, people convert to other religions because they don't like this one, but they don't pay
any attention to what's going on with the one they're converting to, right?
You know what I mean?
Okay.
Or whatever.
So, what I mean is, when you're reading something like the biblical text, which is on a high
spiritual level, if he tells the woman, Christ tells the woman, go and sin no more, that
has two meanings.
It has two meanings to it.
You see?
Because if you're doing adultery and get caught, you sin, didn't you?
Well, what?
If you do adultery, you don't?
On a human level.
And you don't get caught?
Because you're not supposed to get caught.
Yeah, but if you don't get caught, then there's no sin?
I mean, a cop didn't see it, I didn't do it?
Yeah.
No, according to the people, no, because no one knows you're doing it.
Well, but you do.
There would be no stoning there.
But you do.
You know you did it.
No?
You know you're doing it, but if you have a responsibility to a higher authority or
another authority that within that responsibility is not to do it, then you're sinning there.
Let me give you an example.
Okay.
Someone who's, let's say, a pagan or a Mormon, I don't know, whatever, you know, multi-polygamy
is okay?
Okay.
Are they sinning?
No.
Right?
Actually, in the Bible, is polygamy okay?
Yes or no?
Well, it appears to be okay because it's in a whole lot of stories among men that are
supposed to be men of God.
I mean, unless I missed something.
So, it's a very touchy subject because it's, here's the thing that people forget.
Okay, we say, they say, G-O-D the Father, right?
And he loves everybody.
Then why does he kill 185,000 here, 50,000 here, 100,000 here, millions and billions
here?
Why does he allow suffering to continue if he loves so much?
Why do people have to suffer then?
Well, because there's a higher level to it.
Because love means to do the right thing.
So, if something is so wicked and bad that the only right thing left to do is to, you
see how this works?
But when you go on the internet or listen to people, oh, how could he be a loving God
when he killed all those people?
Because there is thinking between a five-year-old and an eight-year-old.
Again, the magnet's so strong here against the bridge.
Let's put the water where it's strong.
Right?
Words sin.
Oh, we're sinners.
No, you're not.
Look, if you have no desires and you do very little, there's no way you can sin.
Right?
These are very, very, by the way, these are what the rabbis and the sages used to do
and other people used to sit around and contemplate these things.
But when they go to present them to the public and they're like,
they're like, oh my gosh, we can't bring this subject to them.
We got to wait for them to get their diapers off.
Wait a second.
They're 30 years old, still wearing diapers.
No, we're going to just hide it.
There's a natural system, a cycle.
What is it?
You've seen the wheel of government.
You go from oppression to slavery to dictatorship to revolution to democracy to oppression to slavery to revolution to democracy.
You've seen that cycle, right?
Yeah.
How the societies go.
Okay.
You have a society that becomes spiritual.
It develops a priesthood that studies these things.
And then what does it become?
Completely unspiritual.
And then back again.
Why?
Because when these things are contemplated, when a development of the mind and quote-unquote law and morality is done,
there's always going to be, everyone's got to do what they have to do to survive.
You're a baker.
You're a radio show host.
You fix cars.
You're a bookkeeper or whatever.
You do your job, right?
But you want to know about spirituality.
You don't have eight hours a day for 20 years to study this.
But you know what?
There's a group of people over here that do.
And when you go to them to see what they're studying and to share it with you,
they don't have like an open door.
What is it?
The free software.
What is it called?
Open source.
They don't open source their stuff.
They look at you and say, who are you?
And they do a little query.
Oh, my God.
And if you go there and you're like...
They're not going to give you anything.
They're going to say, go over here.
We have a temple over here that deals with people.
And they're going to tell you you're a sinner.
But no, you can't get any of this stuff, man.
What are you talking about?
You see what I mean?
Okay.
All right.
So what happens is the people that contemplate these things,
these high spiritual notions,
they keep it to themselves.
And if the books get lost or they die, what happens?
You end up with a group of people that know nothing about it.
If you don't share the knowledge, then it's not out there.
Right.
But before they share, they don't open source it.
They look at the individuals and they say,
these are like highfalutin ideas, man.
They ain't going to get it.
This is a lot of finning and reckoning we've been doing,
and we're going to just hand it over to these guys here?
No.
So you get this elitist secreted information.
By the way, if you're a contemplative individual, let's say,
you can figure these things out on your own
as long as you parse it out within your time.
You could be a mechanic working eight hours a day,
but you know how you have different tabs open on a computer?
You have to be able to multitask,
take in a certain amount of study and contemplate on it,
chew it in the background while you're doing your work.
Can you do that and still focus on doing what you do well?
Well, people can't do the multitasking like that.
True.
But there are some that have.
Years ago, they used to have newsletters.
Now they have websites and blogs, right,
where people are whatever vocation,
but they have an interest in something else.
And believe it or not,
that's where you're going to get your best information.
Like, for example, when you look at –
I always – not threaten.
I challenge people.
Threaten.
Yeah.
Well, it's a threat to them when I bring this up.
Name something that was invented out of a university
or one of these big academic institutions.
Name an invention that they put out.
And you can't.
I can't think of one, no.
Yeah.
Right?
The Wright Brothers.
Were they in university?
No.
Nope.
Bike mechanics.
Right?
Hewlett-Packard.
They started beating up stuff in a garage, right?
The only thing I can think of that came out of a university
is maybe LSD.
But outside of that, I can't think of anything.
I don't even think –
Well, that started back in the –
That came out of the 30s.
Well, that's because of Project Paperclip and stuff like that.
Yeah.
They were prescribing –
Well, LSD was supposed to be a truth serum in the 1930s.
Lysergic acid type stuff.
Okay.
Yeah.
What came –
What was it?
Steve Jobs was a college dropout, if I'm not correct.
Right?
Yeah.
Another guy working in a garage.
So I can't think of anything that was –
Okay.
So this is still going on.
It's always been going on that way.
So what these institutions, churches, universities are putting out
is to reframe from what is higher knowledge to fool the collective
to think this is the way to think about something, right?
So that's where the sin thing comes from.
Yeah.
So I think I've said enough without –
You can't attack that directly.
It does deserve to be attacked, by the way,
the sin aspect in people's minds.
You can't go at it directly because then they turn it on you.
Well, then you're just defending sin.
You're defending blah, blah, blah.
No, you're not.
You see, you have to go around it, circle the wagons around it
and around and around and then drive away.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
It just means missing the mark.
So if you're a very well-measured, I would say humble and well-measured,
meaning you think about things before you do them,
you're not going to be sinning.
And also what responsibilities do you have to this reality and to who?
And if you follow those and you achieve,
you were within the scope of those things without missing anything,
you're not sinning either.
And that's really the definition of it.
That's why it's so strange to people when you talk about these things
because the word love just means to do the right thing.
Hey, if wiping out billions of people in the flood is the right thing,
that's love, yeah.
Right?
It's not like, well, the apple is red and the car is red.
That means the apple is a car.
No.
If you define love as doing the right thing, even if it inconveniences you,
yeah, it is.
You do that.
You do eliminate the entire population out of love.
Yes.
You see?
But because we've taken the word love to mean someone in a Skype message,
I put a photo of some food and they said there was one fork there, how romantic.
And I'm like, because I said it was a plate for two.
And I said, romantic?
What's that?
I've got to look that word up.
It must be something they use for the collective.
I don't know what that word means.
Now, that's double-sided.
Now, one person will say, oh, man, the Greek must be cold.
He's not romantic.
But on the other side, it's like, oh, man, the Greek doesn't fall for that,
get me flowers on Valentine's Day
and rub my feet and tell me sweet nothings just to get something.
You see what I mean?
Mm-hmm.
Right?
Okay.
You know what I mean?
No, I'm getting the point.
Yeah, I got you.
I understand.
It's totally, yeah, it's very different.
If I say I'm not romantic, most people in the general will say, oh, my gosh,
what is he, a robot?
What is he, you know?
Right?
Yeah, it's terrible.
What are you, lack of emotions?
Because if you're romantic, where do people learn how to be romantic?
Television, movies, novels, their friends?
Mostly, yeah.
What kind of quality is that?
What kind of reality is that?
No, but if you're doing the right thing by somebody,
then that's a lot higher a calling than romance, right?
I mean…
Well, understanding the reason for it.
Yeah, and that word is not even being used probably because it comes from
Romania, Rome, right, and the romantic languages, supposedly.
Are you guys familiar, I think, familiar with,
I think it's Winston Churchill, I'm going to paraphrase,
heaven and hell in Europe.
Do you remember that?
Vaguely, vaguely, yeah.
Yeah, heaven in Europe is when the Germans are the mechanics,
the British are the police, the French are the chefs,
the Italians are the lovers, and the Swiss are the bankers, right?
Something like that.
Hell in Europe would be when the Germans are the police,
the British are the cooks, the French are the mechanics,
the Italians are the bankers, and the Swiss are the lovers.
That would be hell in Europe.
There you go.
So, anyway.
Well, that actually leads to another,
one of the last things in the chat I was going to bring up,
which is kind of funny, because it leads perfectly in my mind,
because I always have a mindset like that,
and I get there are many jokes in what you just said,
related to what Churchill, I think, said at one point.
And it makes perfect sense, you know,
once you get to know the culture and you take a look at, look,
some cultures are just geared towards certain things.
It's the way it is.
But something you brought up on a previous Sonic was mentioned in the chat
about the, there's only a handful of like spiritual genotypes, you call them.
And, you know, we talked about how people just seem to resemble others,
you know, after a while.
It's like there's only so many variations.
Well, let me rephrase that real quick.
Not a handful of spiritual genotypes,
but in the spirit realm it's divided into various genotypes.
I think it's between, let's say, the high 40s to the low 70s.
And you'll see that reflected in the personage,
and it has nothing to do with race.
Like I think I gave the example where, you know what Snoop Dogg looks like?
I know a white guy that looks exactly like Snoop Dogg, but he's a white guy.
Sounds like him, acts like him, same mannerisms.
How is that possible?
But go ahead.
Well, no, but that was the thing.
You brought that up in the previous Sonic, and I remember that,
and I was just wondering if you want to comment on that further,
because I think they asked specifically.
I did comment.
Race has nothing to do with it.
There was a study.
Yeah, no, not about race.
Forget race.
What I'm saying is.
Oh, the genotype.
Yeah, I can, but I don't have enough to substantiate it.
But you will see similarities in people types, and that is formed.
You know, you can affect how the embryo and the fetus is being formed, right,
by external input, right?
You know, like what's it called when a mother is an alcoholic, right, when the baby?
That will malform.
Fetal malform.
You see, there's thalidomide.
Yeah, right.
And there's thalidomide where you're born with no arms.
You know, I suppose in the 50s and 60s,
they were giving mothers to not have morning sickness,
and the babies were born with the fingers coming out of the elbow, all this.
So you can affect it.
So what I'm saying is when the spirit, each genotype,
it's a genotype not because it's genetic in the sense that it comes from the genes,
but it affects the genes.
When the spirit comes in, it has a certain effect.
You'll see that in personages in cartoon styles that way.
You know how cartoons are drawn, you know.
Isn't another way to look at this, though, that, you know, like, look,
if it is nurtured spiritually in a certain way,
you have a very substantial and healthy person in general,
and that's just the way maybe they'll be their entire life
because that is the infusion that was kind of happening there to the physical.
Like, I'm not wording this correctly.
No, no, but hold on.
Hold on.
There was a study done in Russia.
I'm going to bring up the one in China and Russia real quick,
where when the woman conceived, for nine months,
she was reading to the baby, to the child she's carrying.
Right.
And guess what?
Those children, the majority of them, between two and four years old,
by four years old they had a high school comprehension just by reading to them.
And technical stuff, not fun with Dick and Jane and blah, blah, blah, you know,
Barney and stuff like that.
Right.
I mean, everything that you would do is if you came to Earth
and you needed a download on what's going on here.
Technical stuff.
The other thing I want to bring up is in China they said,
well, the Chinese people speak Chinese because they're Chinese,
so they took a mixed race of, let's say, black, white, northern, southern, European, whatever children,
and they had them born and raised in China.
And they went through the regular schooling, nothing special.
And guess what?
Regardless of your whatever race or what part of the world you came from,
you spoke Chinese just as well as the Chinese children.
Right.
So it has nothing to do with you speak Chinese well because you're Chinese.
They have an epithelial flap on your eye or whatever.
No, it doesn't work that way.
The majority of what I answered in the comment was you have this influx of a spirit that comes in
that does shape and mold you to a certain degree,
but how you perform and behave is all about if you have open, free mind and proper training.
Mm-hmm.
Right?
This is very well known.
This was developed, and if you want to touch on this very closely,
MKUltra was about that.
If you're going to raise an assassin, you better start one there, too.
Oh, right.
I mean, look, and the other way around, too.
You take a full-blooded Chinese person, you bring them here to the United States,
you raise them from birth here.
Look, what do they do?
They speak just like if they're in the south, they've got a southern drawl.
It's just the way it is.
If they're in the north, they might sound a bit like me in the northeast, you know.
There is a shape to the vocal cords that's different.
Like on the phone, I could tell that seeing someone, if they're black, white, or Asian,
even if they're born here, by the way, there is a very subtle shape.
Yeah, there is a subtle, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
I remember doing Skype calls for someone a long time,
and a very intelligent-sounding guy, and everybody thought he was a white guy.
I said, oh, Sam, come here.
He's black, man.
What are you talking about?
He's like, he's black?
It doesn't sound like black.
I said, what do you mean?
Can't you hear it in his voice?
Right?
Well, they're looking for a particular.
But I can.
Other people can.
I can hear if someone is Asian, even if they're born and raised here.
It's a very, very, very subtle.
So this is something that is now we're getting into the extreme subtleties that,
unfortunately, can be taught, right?
Here is something that's even more important, by the way.
Okay.
Well, what's important, it's all behavior.
It's what's done with the personal culture.
You know, you have the overall culture, and then you have the personal culture,
how the individual is raised, right?
If you raise a child, you know, the Olympic swimmers in Russia,
underwater birth, right?
Okay.
That's what they did.
So if you want to raise a James Bond, you better start at two, right?
If you want to raise a worker, you could put him in front of Sesame Street
and send him through government schools and high school,
and they're done because they develop their –
they'll spend the rest of their life with a high school mentality, right?
I've seen people in their 60s, 70s, and older that have a high school mentality still.
Right.
That's what they latched on.
That's what they were trained for.
They were trained to be – this is very much like Aldous Huxley, Brave New World,
you know, the alphas, the betas, the gammas, the delta morons, right?
Right.
Very much that way.
So it's all that.
But the higher level to it is the nurturing when you're in the formative years.
But, you know, I think I missed something.
I don't think I went on too much of a tangent there.
No, not too much.
Yeah, not too much.
But there was something important I wanted to bring up, but maybe I missed it.
It has to do with, again, all of this.
It's how the person is raised, but there is a very strong, not genetic component,
but a component while the child is being formed in the womb.
Let's just leave it at that.
Okay.
So when you see a woman who is pregnant,
you can follow her around and get a slice of how she acts for those first nine months
and then the next five years.
And you could pretty much draw up a quick dossier on the child,
what the child will be like or very close for the rest of its life,
depending on schooling and all that.
It doesn't mean all is lost.
You can have even someone go through, what do they call them, a complete normie,
go through even high school and whatever and then they wake up.
How many times do you hear people say on blogs,
I woke up in 2014 and I found out, right, and they changed their lives, right?
Right.
Yeah.
But imagine that starting at conception, you see.
So, yeah, it's important.
That's why, I don't know, I think, look,
either the two kinds of people, the kinds that are self-centered,
just think about themselves and what they can get
and then there's the other kind of person that likes to help other people.
Yeah, sort of narcissistic versus altruistic, sure.
Yeah, okay.
So, well, you don't want to be altruistic because we're not in an altruistic universe.
It doesn't work that way.
Yeah, the wolf will eat.
As long as you have bugs eating, big fish eating smaller fish, if you know what I mean,
you're not in the right universe for altruism.
But it can be, let's say, padded as, let's say, altruistic, you know, but it's not.
It's a pretty sad place.
Not just the planet, the whole thing, until it changes in any way.
But, yeah, what I wanted to say is, you know,
you have to get special permissions if you don't have a license for something.
I don't like to use that term because really what it means is something different.
But what I suggest is that if I were to be emperor of the world,
everyone would stop having babies
and those that wanted to have babies would have to go through very special,
they would have to see it as a privilege.
You know what I mean?
They'd have to be screened, you know, your education level, not school, your spiritual level.
Can you see or are you a dummy?
And then if you pass a certain amount of basic human requirements, go ahead and have children.
Yeah, look, it's very easy to take the earth to the next level.
And people, you know, when they say, Greek, what's the right thing?
Who makes the law?
I say, you do, you do.
You make it.
But if you don't want to sit there and reinvent it, it's already been done.
You know, like the thing about government being corrupt.
It's not your government.
It's not a government.
It's a corporation.
None of them are doing anything that's in the books that they're supposed to be following.
No one is.
All you got to do with anything is just go back to what's been memorialized.
You know, medical industry, screw up.
No, well, it's not really medical.
It's business.
If you just go into the medical books and look at what's been memorialized and how things work, you'll be fine.
If you go in the legal books and look how it's supposed to be applied, you'd be fine.
If you go to the, you know, financial side, look how it's supposed to be applied, you'd be fine.
Nothing is being done the way it's been written to be done, if that makes any sense.
You see?
No one's following any rules at all.
It's just the appearance of it.
And here's the thing, though.
Once you have a society that, let's say, gets rid of a monarchy where, you know, you have no freedom or whatever, which is bullshit,
the best government is a benevolent dictator.
Dictator means you just dictate, right?
A benevolent one, right, would be the best government because, you know, you have a central point.
There's no bureaucracy, really.
Well, you could say there is because how are you going to get to the king?
You've got to go through all these hoops and all these layers, right?
Well, you need to have administrators.
I mean, you can't possibly handle every single aspect of everything, so you've got to delegate.
You've got to have the book stops here somewhere.
So when you have this system where they tell you you have a free government, it's open government,
what happens is the people that want to usurp it will be the ones that will get in there, right?
I was thinking this today based on a conversation recently out in public,
is there's no public participation in government.
Don't say voting.
No, don't say that.
I'm talking about active public participation in government.
There is none, zero, anywhere.
It's all government employees and agencies.
You ever notice?
So we're not talking about someone volunteering night watch or picking up litter.
So there is no active public.
So it's all closed off because when they did open it up,
all the people that were supposedly doing other things like attorneys of certain corrupt institutions,
find a politician in the U.S. who's not an attorney.
Good luck.
What does that tell you right away?
I mean, come on.
So all you have to do is go back to what's been written and do it.
If you go in the medical books and it says that there's induction of disease, induction, induction,
what does that mean?
If you look at the medical diagrams on anatomy
and you see that there's three hydrophobic layers and nothing goes through,
well, how is the nutrition getting into the body?
There's no absorption.
Well, just follow what's been laid out.
If you look at the legal stuff, all those millions of codes and everyone says,
oh, the cops are code enforcers.
No, they're not code enforcers.
They work for the banks.
If you go look at the definitions, you know,
in a court case or wherever they're charging someone with crimes and all this stuff
and they list the codes and all that, that's fine.
Let's go back to the definitions.
This is supposed to be applying to corporations, trusts, persons, and residents, right?
Where do you fit in there?
You know, we're charging you, you know, Title 18, whatever, stealing rocks from the moon.
Oh, my gosh.
It has nothing to do with you.
Right?
But the people don't know and they buy it.
You know, it's all around, everything, everything.
How many times do you hear someone, oh, I got high blood pressure and my blood sugar is off?
Both are fictional.
Both are completely fictional.
But, Greek, I get sick if I don't, no, you get sick after you start taking treatment, right?
Yeah.
But without the treatment, I'd die.
Like, okay, that person is finished.
They just, you know what I mean?
If they never got treatment, they would, right, never been sick.
So we have this incredible situation here where things look like they're in control,
but they're out of control because the control mechanisms that were set up,
the way we're supposed to do things, whether it's legal, medical, or whatever,
or even religious, is not being followed.
So you've got to see, again, you know how we started off with the magnet.
Well, this is the strong part of the magnet, so we should put the water on this, right?
See?
It's the same exact ideology.
All right.
That was a tangential rant.
But it's all about, again, genetics and hereditary.
No, it's very subtle, very, very subtle.
It's from when the sperm meets the egg and before.