Rated Y, Sonic Event 1.1.0, and here it is, how are you doing, Greg?
Hey, I'm doing, yeah, I figured we'd get personal or less personal.
Everything's working on the Sonic side now, it seems like.
Yeah, I just want to say I got some good feedback about speaking on the money system again,
and again and again and again, and did I say again?
You did.
I'm kind of naive thinking that I can just say things once or twice and people kind of get it,
but it doesn't really work that way, and one of the things I brought up,
even people that I know very well, I watch them and sometimes I say,
this can't really be happening, right?
This isn't real, and kind of puts that whole simulation thing that we're not in a real world,
more and more real, right, no pun intended.
By the way, there's a guy out there, Golan, I think his last name is,
and talks about on a good DMT trip, people with a laser, if you can diffract the laser,
in that diffraction pattern, you start seeing code, and it's objective.
In other words, multiple people see the same thing, so it's not personal, right?
Right.
And DMT is very different than LSD, by the way.
In other words, when you get high, drunk, or whatever, or even LSD,
which is most people, it's been overdone, but LSD, by the way, it's very speedy, right?
It's like drinking and getting high on pot, and speed is a very close analogy to what LSD is like,
but then it becomes psychotropic big time.
What those kinds of psychotropics do is it changes your perception.
What's interesting about DMT is it doesn't change your perception.
You're still pretty sober, but your environment changes.
Everything around you starts to change.
That's the trippy thing about DMT, which is synthesized stuff that's in mushrooms.
But anyway, he says that basically if you do this experiment, set this up a certain way,
you will see code like in the screens in the movie The Matrix running through the diffraction.
Okay, the reason I got into this just now, and actually I looked up some of his work,
I don't really trust the guy's stuff.
I definitely don't endorse him.
But anyway, it's because it can be objective that we're not in a real –
it's very difficult to be in a movie and say you're in a movie to those watching the movie, right?
They've tried it many times where cartoon characters jump out of the anime into the studio, right?
It's kind of cute.
I believe that the state that nothing is real is maybe a little bit of an overstatement.
It's a Beatles lyric after all.
Nothing is real, right?
Yeah, but most of the things that I see and experience through people should not be happening by any measure, by any measure.
Okay.
So that's where you have to kick back.
Like I said earlier, no one can make you happy.
No one can make you sad.
It's how you process what you see and feel and all that, right?
Which is what you see in different cultures, right?
So something that's acceptable in one culture will seem draconian, limited or dictatorial
and not accepted in another culture.
It's what culture you're raised in.
But this goes beyond culture.
This is more personal, personal when you're discussing things with people.
But anyway, I'm naive thinking that you do something called Greek speak and just share what you have found out as facts.
By the way, as I'm getting more mature, I'm starting to discern the difference between facts and the truth.
I would like to limit the truth to being your personal experience, right?
Okay.
And the fact being something that can literally be checked on.
Like fact checkers only came around when more truth started getting out, right?
You get it?
There's a certain level to that.
Here's a little term.
I kind of modified it.
Conspiracy theorists are negative.
Let me slow you down for a second because this is an important point and I want to ask a question here.
What you're saying is, though, that you could have an experience and you're certain of said experience, right?
But that's not a fact.
That would be the truth.
That is the truth.
And a fact if it's applicable to who you're communicating.
If you can view structure of good communication, if you're bringing up something new in communication, you should always preface, inform, and then discuss.
You can't go right into a discussion on something that is not – someone is not aware of.
So if I describe to you an experience which is incredible, nearly unbelievable, right?
But I swear to you, look, I experienced this thing that is unbelievable.
Okay.
Now hold on.
This is where you get into the jurisprudence of it.
Okay.
If you are the only one, then it might be considered as testimony, subjective, maybe hearsay or taken as your testimony.
But if you have witnesses that can collaborate the same thing, now it becomes more of a fact.
That's why I brought up the judicial side of it.
Okay.
So with corroboration, my –
It's a fact.
Incredible experience becomes more credible because I have corroboration.
Right.
Here's an example.
Someone came selling solar to me the other day and he said, you're not one of these end-of-the-worlders.
I said, no, no, no.
He talked about nukes.
I said nukes don't work.
Otherwise, they would have used them.
I brought up 9-11.
It was airplanes, right?
So I said, well, it was airplanes for those people who watched it on TV.
But if you were on the ground, you saw the sides of the buildings explode.
So is it true that there were airplanes?
No.
And how is that backed up?
Because a lot of times you have authorities that back up what is the truth and tell people what is the truth or not.
And I mentioned this and I brought up facts and truth with him.
This is important because this is cultural again.
What's the authority, right?
It could be religious, political, whatever, right?
Okay.
All right.
So I said I dare you to find any government document, official document in any agency that says there were airplanes that crashed into the buildings on 9-11.
You won't.
What you will see written in government documents on that day, on September, the terrorist events of September 11th, 2001.
You'll never say you would never.
So you'll never find anything that's memorialized in any government official paper.
It says there were airplanes in the buildings.
Never.
They will mention the terrorist events on that fateful day, blah, blah, blah, right?
On and on and on.
I'm telling you, try this out.
You won't find it because.
Right.
So now the authority holds no mention of airplanes.
The only place the airplanes were shown is on television.
The only place.
Right.
So and by the way, I have a direct witness, a guy named I'll give his name.
He's in the Carpenters Union.
His name is William Gonzalez.
And he was walking across the Brooklyn Bridge.
And when you get Brooklyn Bridges on a diagonal, when you get past the middle tower, the second tower, you get a clear shot of the World Trade Center.
And he saw a C-130 really low.
He says, wow, C-130 on the East River so low flying.
And suddenly he says, just I'm going to look at the buildings.
This is when the first one hit.
And he just saw the side of the building explode.
No airplane.
Nothing.
Right.
And he hung around and watched it.
And then he saw the other the other building explode.
No airplane.
Nothing.
Right.
So when I heard this, I kind of, you know, whatever.
And then I started piecing it all together.
OK, so here's the thing.
9-11 is always a good example.
Is it true that airplanes hit the building?
The only source we have for that is the television.
For that.
Then we have the people on the ground where their source is collaborating testimony.
Everyone says except the ones that were hired to say otherwise.
Right.
So this gets very sticky and messy so that neither one is a truth and neither one is a fact.
Because now we have this thing called a television.
Right.
So now the television creates a whole world.
Where you can have facts and truths that only apply to television.
How many times have you heard you speak recently as seen on TV people?
Right.
Now, what do you make of the two brothers who were filming the documentary on the latter company?
That, you know, we're doing the documentary and captured easy what they claim to be the first plane.
That's easy.
That wasn't OK.
That was not a live stream.
That was a film that they had in a can and then played back.
Well, it was it was what they said they recorded that morning.
But it was recorded.
Right.
But it wasn't live stream.
It was not being broadcast.
Right.
Because the broadcast live streams did not show airplanes.
There were several stations, especially one in a helicopter that has the background of New Jersey in the background.
Right.
Where the ones that show the airplane, there is no background in New Jersey.
It's been whited out.
That's been proven several times already.
And also there's three missing frames when they switch from the Jersey background into the New Jersey background.
In between that switch is three black frames, which would each be about a 16th of a second.
Right.
And then they switch to no Jersey background, white haze.
And then you see the airplane come in on the TV.
OK.
Are you familiar with that?
It's been analyzed.
I have not have not looked at that in that.
Oh, yeah.
That's cool.
And the three black frames are typical on a poor edit.
Not a good edit.
OK.
On a poor editing software.
You know.
All right.
I have.
Yeah.
So what I'm saying is, is there's another.
OK.
Let me give you an example.
Like if you live in the country with off the grid, let's say.
Right.
Just to be more specific.
And you live in a city.
Your realities are way different.
If you want milk, you ask the children that's raised in the city.
Where do you get milk?
Where do they say from the store?
That's where you get milk.
Right.
Of course.
As someone who was raised in the country.
Where do you.
You know, where do you get milk?
They're going to say, well, what do you mean?
Goat milk, sheep milk, cow milk.
Right.
From the cow animal.
So the.
So are they both right?
They are both right.
And years and years ago in the suburbs, somebody might have said the milkman brings it.
OK.
Now, piece this all together.
Tell me this is a real world.
It's not.
Just like I said earlier, no one can make you feel good or.
Well, that's not true.
I've met some chicks that made me feel real good back in the day.
But anyway, there's plenty of ways people have talents to make you feel good.
Yeah.
One wet lady.
But anyway, if you go back and look at things that upset you, things that made you happy,
it's you, not them that did that.
You've allowed.
Because, for example, you could look at someone standing in a drill line and in boot camp
and the sergeant comes right up to their face and yells at them, whatever.
Some pretty harsh stuff.
Right.
They just stand there as stoic as possible because they know that's what they have to
do.
And they pass pass it over.
Now, if you go up to someone in the street that, you know, is unfamiliar and is a little
edgy and you do that, you probably get punched in the face.
Probably.
Yeah.
So it's how you process what's happening, that either you end up leaving the situation
or actively experiencing situation as a good situation or a bad situation.
Right.
So a good portion of this is expectation.
What you expect to have come at you.
Sometimes.
But even expectations, it's how you process it in real time as it's happening.
More than that.
OK.
Right.
For example, I've seen people I've been in situations where there's a trauma.
Someone gets injured and everyone standing around is looking.
And I'm like, you grab this.
You did that.
You pick up his leg.
You hold that.
I'm like.
And one time there was a trauma situation.
And I said, I'm going to be like everybody else.
And everyone just stood around and just commented.
I said, what a bunch of fucking assholes.
Well, that's why we have this phenomenon today where people are filming stuff instead of doing
something.
Right.
But I'm talking about before they were.
I'm talking about the 90s and early 2000s.
I've been witnessing this.
And why is it I'm the one that has to step in and direct people?
Well, you know, because here's the thing, you know, that a lot of new agers say you chose
this.
You came here to have this type of experience.
Right.
Well, I better make a note to self.
Don't ever pick anything like that.
That was a really bad decision.
OK.
No, I'm like I said many times, if I meet who sent me here, they're going to get kicked
in the nuts or they're going to have one swollen labia.
No, I've said the same thing to these people where they go, well, you chose that.
I go, well, really?
Well, you know, yeah.
Prove it.
Right.
Is that the truth or is that a fact?
Yeah.
Please.
You know, that's look, I've made bad decisions before, but this is a really bad decision
to come here.
And note to self.
I'm not coming back here.
Yeah.
No, just absolutely not.
And if it's, you know, whatever.
So anyway, let's go back to the moment at hand that we started with.
I got some good feedback from some people who were very excited that they went back and
listened to what we talked about, the money system twice.
Right.
And with that said, I'm going to have I sent you a link to YouTube.
It's one minute, 42 seconds.
And it's some guy that he's supposedly the head economic advisor for the current administration.
And there's an interview.
Or would you play that?
It's one minute and 42 seconds.
And I'll just do some brief comments and the significance of this.
You got it.
So you'll comment at the end.
Yeah.
The US government can't go bankrupt because we can print our own money.
It obviously begs the question, why exactly are we borrowing in a currency that we print
ourselves?
I'm waiting for someone to stand up and say, why don't we borrow our own currency in the
first place?
Like you said, they print the dollar.
So why?
Why does the government even borrow?
Well, the so the I mean, again, some of this stuff gets some of the language that the some
of the language and concepts are just confusing.
I mean, the government definitely prints money and it definitely lends that money, which
is why the government definitely prints money.
And then it lends that money by by selling bonds.
Is that what they do?
They they they yeah, they they they sell bonds.
Yeah, they sell bonds.
Right.
Since they sell bonds and people buy the bonds and lend them the money.
Yeah.
So a lot of times, a lot of times, at least to my ear with with MMT, the language and
the concepts can be kind of unnecessarily confusing.
But there is no question that the government prints money and then it uses that money to
So, yeah, I guess I'm just I don't I can't really talk.
I don't I don't get it.
I don't know what they're talking about, like because it's like the government clearly prints
money.
It does it all the time and it clearly borrows.
Otherwise you wouldn't be having this debt and deficit conversation.
So I don't think there's anything confusing there.
OK.
That's the.
All right.
OK.
Yeah.
Good.
OK.
That's Jared Bernstein.
Bernstein or Bernstein, however, it's J.A.R.E.D Bernstein, B.E.R.N.S.T.E.I.N.
Anyway, he's the chair of the Council of Economic Advisers.
Now, first of all, the woman that was there, the female voice is as dumb as can as they
come because she says, why can't we borrow our own money?
Right.
There's a maximum law that you cannot lend money and borrow money to yourself.
It's impossible.
Right.
So I have a dollar in my left pocket.
I'm going to lend it to myself by putting it in my right pocket.
It's not possible.
Right.
So the woman is an idiot.
Category certification.
I'll write the certification that she's a moron.
Now this guy is very interesting.
What he said.
Now he's an idiot as well.
Now, I'm not disparaging either one of them because they're the majority of the people
you'll ever run into or even the people that you're in the room right now with most likely
are.
Here's the interesting.
I'm not disparaging me.
It's just a technical term that I'm using.
Yeah.
Moronic or whatever.
Now, here's the interesting part.
There's two sides to this.
One thing where he says, sure, the government prints money and all this.
First of all, none of that is true.
But if you take it as truth, it's even more profound.
Because what he's telling you there, if the government prints money all the time, that
means that the original government, the lawful government is gone.
How many times have I said that has disappeared, has been completely dissolved.
And what is the current government is, in fact, the Federal Reserve System shareholders.
Right. So right.
Because they're the ones that print the money.
Now, you can say the Office of Printing and Engraving does it and all that.
But so what's interesting, someone who does a rudimentary study on how the system works,
how the government has a subcontractor, a private contractor, do the money there.
It's a quasi relation, quasi legal relationship.
OK. Right.
And so what he's telling you is what I've said.
It's bullshit on the surface because the government doesn't print money.
It's the Federal Reserve. Right.
But but what he's telling you, if you're going to take it as truth, it confirms what I've
said, that there is no more government's completely dissolved.
And it's really run by the, you know, the legal society and the shareholders of the
Federal Reserve. Because if you go to the Federal Reserve and ask them, which I have
and ask them, you guys are running, they're like, no, how can you just say no?
He says, you're just not asking me the right question.
Well, because then I. OK, plainly, let me get to this plainly.
If you accept that the government is printing the money, then that means that this agency
that we are told is not part of the government is the government, is the actual
government, which means exactly.
Yeah. So what exactly?
Thank you. Because if you take on face value what he's saying, it's even more profound
than it sounds, because most patriots will listen and say he's wrong.
It's the Federal Reserve. So you need to go one step deeper, because I believe, yes, these
people are morons. I'll even write the certificates that they are.
Yeah, sure. And that is the declarations.
But but that's at the same time, if they were told to say this, the chances that they were
told to say this was scripted is very high, by the way, is to basically send a message.
Right. Because you can have Bozo the Clown or Ronald McDonald give a government issue
statement. Right. That's official.
That goes into the records.
But most people will discount it because it was said by this Bozo or Ronald McDonald,
let's say. Right. So is that listening to the message or the messenger?
So I believe this was interesting.
It was crafted to do both things.
One is to put out pure bullshit because that's what people are used to.
The other one is to get people arguing that he's wrong.
And the other one is that he's actually speaking facts and truth, meaning that what we call
the government, you know, is is this group.
Right. So I just found that to be interesting.
What's the name of the video? What's the title of the video?
So people would look it up.
YouTube title. Let's see.
I don't understand. In quotes, Jared Bernstein, chair of the Council of Economic Advisors.
What's the channel? The channel is Raw Booty.
B-O-O-T-Y. Yes.
OK, good. So anybody could look it up.
Maybe if it's it'll be fun.
Yeah. So this is the kind of stuff that's going on.
Like we mentioned, 9-11 planes or no planes.
Well, it's if you give a simple answer, it doesn't make sense.
Right. With most most things like who killed JFK.
If you give a simple answer, it doesn't make sense.
Right. Well, here's something I want to ask you, then.
What you're telling me is that, you know, because KRS-One used to say this and it always
stuck with me for multiple reasons.
And maybe this is why, you know, when he says you go there, you're dissatisfied with your
hamburger. You ask to speak to who's in charge.
They send you the manager.
The manager doesn't own anything.
The manager just works there.
So anybody that seems to be in charge and is making these arrangements is handling the
food, is handling the business, appears to be the manager.
But he doesn't own anything.
And that's what we're looking at here, is that when the government that they say is our
government right now are the managers, they're not the owners.
Is that right? They're actually worse than that because the manager can still push buttons
that will make big changes.
Right. Yeah.
The manager can turn the lights out and lock up the doors.
No, I think they're just puppets that are there with a message.
But ultimately, that manager doesn't look.
If the owner wants to close the store, the manager can't stop him.
If the owner wants to have the store do nothing, the manager can't stop him.
But the point the point I wanted to bring up here is if these two people in this video
are exemplary in their explanation of what they tried to explain.
Can you imagine someone that you might be in the room with you or a co-worker or an
associate or a family member?
Yeah. When you're looking at it, forget it.
Discussing how the money system works, it's it's alien, literally alien.
And I mean, is staring, stammering around and reaching for an answer and not really
being able to get too much. I mean, he must have spent a good 30, 40 seconds of that
minute, 40 something seconds stammering around.
Yeah, exactly. But imagine these are people set up here, the interviewer that are
supposed to put forward a message that have some, quote unquote, expertise on the
subject. Right. This is a chair is literally the head of the Council of Economic
Advisors. Right. So this is a guy who basically should know about how this works or
how to be a little more eloquent.
Now, here's the other thing. I've been in the presence of Federal Reserve chairman
and there's like 30 of them or there's there's 12 banks and each one has like vice
presidents, not chairman, vice presidents, vice presidents.
Right. Has several of them, just like when you meet someone who's vice president of
insurance company, they have like 50 vice presidents.
Right. Right. But it's it's considered a high position.
And basically the discussion I basically mentioned, yes, he did confirm the birth
certificate is what creates the value of the money.
In other words, a country that has a lot of babies, their money will be worth less.
China. Right. And so why the EU at the time it was the the euro came out as to the
euro is higher because the Europeans are having fewer babies than the Americans.
They're like, absolutely. That's right.
But the whole thing is they they they are a personal discussion.
If you do speak with them, just like the when I mentioned the Federal Reserve pretty
much runs everything and owns everything.
And he's like, no, you didn't ask it.
You didn't ask me the right question.
And basically shuffling around.
I said it's their shareholders.
And that's right. It's the shareholders.
So in other words, Federal Reserve is a front.
Right. So they put forward.
So it's yet another layer of management.
In other words, it's not the store manager.
Now you're telling me the Federal Reserve is the district.
You have the managers that manage the managers that you find out about.
Right. So that's the district manager as opposed to the store manager.
And we still haven't hit upon the owners is what you know.
Exactly. That's why, for example, when you go to the court system, I found that this
was very interesting because when I spoke to a former district attorney, assistant
district attorney who quit because she said she found out what was going on.
She lives here in Tucson.
And she didn't want to talk about it.
But basically, later on, I found out what was going on.
The all the judges have handlers since the early 90s and who these handlers are.
And to say that's fine to shake it off, whatever.
But once you find out really who they are and give specifics, it scares them because
I have brought this up with the specifics.
And this is what it is. The handlers come from the underwriting agencies where the
insurance companies, in other words, those courts are insured.
If the judge makes a bad decision or whatever, they can get sued.
The city can. So they have full staff, depending on how big the courthouse is.
These observers, the insurance company has observers and they tell the judges basically
what to say, what not to say, when to to get up and leave the courtrooms and end the
court date, you know, ended for now or whatever.
And typically, like here in Tucson, there's about one for each floor.
So you have a three or four floor court building.
You have one of these inspectors on each one.
And they're usually well-dressed. And the way you find out who they are is very simple.
You dress up a certain way and you spend the whole day at the courtroom.
Most courtrooms you can walk in and out of, especially the ones for traffic tickets and
stuff. Right. They're big public audience type things.
You can sit in the galley and you can observe.
I've done this. Yeah, exactly.
So have I. And I've spent days and days, maybe a hundred hours.
So this is the interesting part.
You start doing that and you just do a quick observation, facial recognition, who's in
there. Then you go to another courtroom and do facial recognition.
By the end of the day, if you keep switching around, you see everyone has their time in
court and leaves. But you'll find someone that is hanging around like you are all day.
Right. With a notepad or a mic or a recorder, dictaphone type thing, a personal
recorder. And those are the guys from the insurance companies.
And you find out where they leave.
They go through.
They go. This is how they exit the courtroom.
They go to an empty courtroom, let courtroom be on floor number three.
Yeah. And they'll go into an empty courtroom and walk all the way through the
courtroom and go out into the judge's chambers where the judge exits as a separate
door. And they go out, they exit through there, not where you would exit being.
If you try to exit through there, they'll show you go the other way.
Right. So these people I found out later when I brought this up to a senior person
who's worked there a long time, who was shamelessly fine about time.
He says those he says those are insurance people.
They're from the insurance companies.
So those are the handlers.
Right. Just like I've said earlier, I've met an attorney and he was from England.
He worked in the U.S. and said, you know, I never asked you what, you know, your
attorney. But what kind of what do you do?
What kind of work do you do? He says, oh, I edit medical books.
So do you have medical study?
No, I don't read it. Oh, my gosh.
So when medical textbooks are written, he goes through them and edits out what you
know, what it takes out.
And does he know anything about medicine?
No, he just knows when it has a certain language or whatever.
Right. So that was a big wake up call.
So in other words, like we started early, this reality is not real.
We do not. It cannot be real.
Right. There's got to be some kind of a guiding system, everything.
So you wake up at three in the morning and stub your toe on the kitchen chair going to
get some water or something.
And, you know, that was that planned, even though you think it's accidental.
I'm starting to question that.
And I've said before, everything is predetermined.
Because remember, when you're watching a fiction, a theater or a movie or something,
that's all preplanned. Very rarely, even live stuff, stuff that used to be live is
still scripted to a certain degree.
So how much of this because it can't be real, quote unquote, naturally.
Then, of course, I said, how can anything really be natural if it has a creator?
Right. So, yeah, it's very, very disturbing to one level.
But one message I'd like to give is people can consider no one can make you happy
or no one can make you sad or angry or upset unless you let them.
Right. So then it goes back to that aspect where it's
objectively subjective.
Well, even if things are not absolutely scripted point by point, because some people
might find that entirely impossible to believe that every single little nuance, every
single incident is absolutely scripted.
You could say that there's choreography involved, right?
Enough of it. There's a general idea that this is going to happen.
This is going to happen. Now, some other stuff might happen during this.
But generally speaking, you have to hit each of these marks.
So this must occur.
This must occur. I mean, whether you take five or six steps in between the two trees, it
doesn't matter. Almost like a twilight zone.
That's why years ago, before the Matrix, the twilight zone was a reference.
People used for strange things that happened.
Right. Right. Absolutely.
Yeah. It's like you have a book reader.
You find out a library burned down a hundred years ago.
You wake up, you go a hundred years back and you're the one that ends up starting the fire
because you accidentally kick the lamp over.
Right. So how much of it is absolute?
Well, I've also given the analogy.
Everyone's on a cruise ship. It's going from London to New York.
While you're on the cruise ship, you have certain freedoms and things you can take up your
time with for the trip. But for sure, everyone is going.
From London to New York.
Right now, the guy who's walking with a limp, he goes back in time, he sees himself and
scares himself as a small child out of the tree, falls down and breaks his leg.
And that's why he walks with the limp.
But he's the guy who scared himself out of the tree.
Yeah. So are we in a closed loop paradox?
By the way, the paradoxes are all paradoxes can be viewed a certain way, whether or not
paradoxes. Right. But yeah, is it is it a closed thing like that?
I don't I don't think that if you really have time traveled, you end up going exactly to
the same place.
Right. It's things are slightly different.
There are some interesting stories recounting that where you'd go back and instead of
having this color painted on your kitchen wall now, it's a different color.
But it's essentially, you know, for all intents and purposes, it's the same kitchen,
right? You have little minor changes, right?
Because I don't think anything ever duplicates exactly.
Even if it's overlaid, it cannot be exact, but it's good enough.
Right.