Rated Y, Sonic, let's see now, 89, because it was 88 last time, right?
I think so, I'm losing track on occasion.
Anyway, it doesn't matter, Otelli in the Greek Rated Y, here we are, and how are you doing
tonight, Greek?
Oh, napping as usual, yeah, falling asleep on the job.
That's okay, hey, whatever job you're on, sometimes it's good to fall asleep.
I hear that little bit of nasally that leads me to believe that you were probably just
breathing deeply a short time ago.
Actually, I was welding today, and if you're not used to it, you're not used to it, right?
But when you weld, you're creating plasma and you're evaporating metal, so you're literally
breathing metal gas, not gases, but the actual plasma itself, so it's fine.
It was stick welding, you know, the basic stuff, but I didn't have enough ventilation,
so.
Yeah, so you said you wanted to start off with, maybe you've got a question or something.
Yeah, definitely.
Well, there's been a bunch of suggestions and generalized questions recently in chats
and private messages, one sent on Skype, one sent through Facebook, let's see, emails,
you know, all that, kind of coming together, generally asking about something, so I figured
let's just step back on something and talk about it in a slightly different way.
Parables, in and of themselves, right?
Generally speaking, storytelling, moral lesson, doesn't matter if you believe that it's a
work of fiction or not.
Like, I enjoy Star Trek and I've been, you know, checking out some of those things a
little more lately.
When it is I want to, you know, do something that is not necessarily productive and I want
to relax, I like Star Trek.
But anyway, always there's a moral lesson in there of some kind, and it's not always
necessarily a moral lesson.
It might be about society.
It's some sort of exposition meant to give you an idea through a parable.
And I would say that no matter what it is you think of the biblical text or the various
versions of it or the translations, on and on and on, one thing that I think is always
supposed to be retained and is retained in it is the parables.
There is a constant.
I don't get into them that much because they're so clear, even though they're parables.
That's the irony of it.
And the stuff that people think is clear is not.
Parables are great because you could find them in every culture, right?
Well, and you can you get more than one thing out of the parable, too.
You know, like different versions of it.
Well, they operate on multiple levels, you could say.
Okay.
That's what I was reaching for, though, because you or I could hear it or, you know, read
it and take it one way or a couple of ways, and then we could hand it to someone else
and they might derive a completely different lesson.
They might draw a completely different inference.
Most people won't get anything out of it, believe it or not.
Otherwise, they would be more venerated, right?
Well, I don't know how that works, because honestly, I'm always looking for the other
message, you know, the subtext.
Some people would say I'm always looking for the subtext, you know, the stuff that's
not being told to me directly, necessarily.
But forget about me.
In general, I think people, whether they're aware of it or not, should be picking up on
some other lesson, even if it's the wrong lesson.
They're picking up something from it.
Well, in short, it's like calling it the philosophy that you find in the biblical text,
because a lot of it is not.
It's pretty much telling certain people what to do, like what you call law.
So there's a philosophy side of it, right?
And there's usually a pun in a lesson, right?
And there's usually a follow through.
Like, you know, a good comedian, by the way, he spends the difference between a good comedian
and a bad comedian is a good comedian will draw out a joke much longer than a not so
good comedian will do short jokes.
Right.
They'll draw out the punch line really, really far.
So in other words, if you're good at holding an audience, you can stretch something out
and they'll still appreciate it.
Right.
And still keep their interest.
Like, I love Chappelle because he'll turn around, he'll begin with a premise and go
through a bunch of other things that aren't exactly dead on, clearly connected to one
another, come back around and hit that punch line a half hour later.
Right.
After he's already and repeatedly, you could use the same theme on multiple jokes.
But the reason I'm bringing up comedy is because you're addressing a group of people that are
hearing stuff for the first time usually.
Right.
Because, you know, most comedians, when they go on a circuit, they do they repeat their
show.
Right.
Slight variation, basically the whole whether you see Chappelle in Vegas or New York or
Chicago, he's pretty much doing the same skit.
Right.
Majority of stand up operate that way.
Yes.
Yeah.
So there's something parallel to the biblical because the rest of it would be very strict
law to those that are in covenant.
So the parables would be for both.
You see, it's more inclusive.
OK.
See, what I find interesting about this, though, is that it's it's a direct relation
to because where do people often get their best lessons out of these things, even in
the organized church, which I find almost no use for whatsoever?
It does have, you know, a bit of relevance in a community sometimes where they.
Yeah.
But I'm going to stop you there because people don't learn.
They follow their culture.
In other words, whatever culture you live in and whatever is accepted or not accepted up
until adolescence is what you've learned.
The rest of it is just, you know, frilled.
They don't look.
So it's more positive because about being blunt and to the point, how many people actually
use what's in the parables?
They cite it as cliche, but I don't know anyone who really uses it.
Hardly anybody.
But yeah, so it's an entertainment gimmick for them.
Well, entertainment, but even entertainment in and of itself is is reinforcement of a
cultural idea one way or another.
Right.
Well, the culture, again, is independent because it's geographic and it's familial or
tribal, right?
You could have a big tribe, right?
Like Sunnis and Shias, right?
Or whatever.
Yeah, it's interesting to see what's in the parables from many points of view.
And that's how I always viewed it, because a lot of it you'll find in other languages,
in other cultures that are not biblical, which shows that there was a worldwide economy
at the time, right?
Just like the, you know, the the imperial inch in the yard is right is pretty much.
And there was another measurement, not mile.
It's it's longer than a mile.
Hectors and all these things.
These things were universal economic.
You know, when I say economics, the word economics means the laws of the house.
Right.
Nomics means law and echo means house.
And when you get ecosystem, you're literally saying a house system.
You're a boat, right?
So economic, what I mean by that is a set of standards that people use.
If you really want to find some interesting parables, it's really hard to find them online
now.
But I was looking at this subject more than a more than 15 years ago, say the early 2000s
is a lot of the Persian ones.
And I remember some of them, you know, brought some up maybe in private calls or other calls
about or other sonics about the poison water and the warnings of all kinds of things.
But if you look at the parables, you could say they're fairly cynical, by the way.
Right.
Most of them are in a negative attribute in a cynical attribute.
The majority of them are certainly cautionary, and it doesn't matter if you're talking about
the biblical texts or Aesop's fables, right?
Yeah, but cautionary could be pretty harsh also.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I mean, you think about the one where the whatever it is gives a ride to the scorpion,
you know, help me get across the water and the scorpion stings him anyway, the scorpion
and the fox or whatever.
Yeah.
You know, it's pretty harsh because the animal dies that you're, you know, engaged in in
the story.
Yeah.
The biblical parables don't lean on that that much.
They do a little bit like, you know, the dead don't worship the Lord.
You know, if you read the King James and things like that.
Oh, you think about a lot getting away from, you know, Sodom and Gomorrah and.
That's not a that's not that would be more of the Genesis, the beginning of the tribe,
let's say.
But, yeah, the parables, I would say that it's the wisdom writings.
It's kind of hard when you say parables.
Really, you're leaning more on the New Testament.
That's where you'll find the parables.
The rest of it, you'll find statements that lean on something.
But the wisdom writings of Solomon and then the parables are the ones that Christ use,
which are allegories.
But but they're very much broad.
Here's the thing.
The reason why the biblical biblical text is not known is because it's being used by
certain groups of people to run the majority of the groups of people.
And I got into it because early on.
Well, in the 2002, someone was talking about all law comes from the Bible, Western cultures.
Right.
You know, even if it's not, you know, banking, whatever.
Yeah.
The common statement is that everything in the Western world, the 72 hour writer refused
all that stuff.
And I was like, oh, how could that be?
I never heard of that.
So I went and studied it just based on the laws.
Right.
So you'd find that in Exodus, Leviticus mostly.
Some numbers in Deuteronomy.
Side note law.
And I was studying that.
How come no one ever talks about these things?
Right.
And then when you went out talking about them, you found out why.
Because it is they are.
You could see that they're the underpinning of the Western jurisprudence.
But they want to hide that from people.
Right.
So the people, all they have left because they're told to stay away from that is to
go look at parables.
That's mostly in the New Testament with the parables of the Christ, let's say.
And then there's the wisdom writings which have parables in them.
But I would say that if you don't have the footing that the biblical text is to lay down
civil jurisprudence.
Right.
OK.
Because Islam also, right, the you're going to you're not going to get much out of it
because there's a famous thing about the woman being ready to be stoned.
And the Christ says he without whoever is without sin.
Right.
Yeah.
Everyone takes that wrong because they don't know the specifics of the law.
Just to restate it, it's if you have outstanding.
OK, if you have outstanding parking tickets or a warrant or whatever, you can't be a witness.
Right.
I think the same thing is here.
Well, not really.
But so so how can they say they're going to stoner if they don't have a witness?
Right.
A viable witness.
So what I'm trying to say is biblical law is very harsh.
People just think, oh, we don't do that anymore.
But actually, it's much easier because if everyone who witnessed a particular crime
has outstanding parking tickets or warrants, they are not a viable witness.
So you actually walk.
So even even if you murdered someone in front of 20 people and those 20 people were going
to perform the positions, the social position of a witness for that case, and they were
they have to be examined prior.
And if they have, again, outstanding parking tickets or warrants, their testimony doesn't
count.
Yeah.
But that almost sounds like all I got to do is get a room full of shoplifters and I can
murder a family in front of them.
And yeah, pretty much.
That's how that's that's so no matter how harsh biblical law looks, those things need
to be met now.
So you will not suffer that.
Right.
So this is the whole thing.
So most people who don't know the law will say, oh, he's saying that out of the goodness
of his heart.
So forgiving.
No, no.
Because the whole thing is about his whole thing was reiterating do you know, doing the
law of Moses.
Right.
So that's what, you know, referred to in common colloquial, the law of Moses.
Well, don't they also have to be competent to be a witness?
Like, right.
They have.
Well, yes.
Well, the way the word competent doesn't necessarily mean it means many things.
Right.
So in this case, they would not be competent.
No, no.
In this case, they wouldn't be.
What I'm saying is, though, to get a legitimate witness, isn't there some measure of competency
to where?
Yes.
Yeah, it would be if you have outstanding.
In other words, competency, meaning do you qualify from a qualitative point of view,
not a quantity.
So if you had a thousand people witness, you murder someone and all of them have outstanding
parking tickets or warrants and warrants or warrants.
None of them are competent.
The competent now means something different means like mental competent, but competent
also means you can't you don't have standing.
Right.
It's not just mental ability.
That's how we're using it now.
Because if you read, for example, old constitutional law, the the for example, the common law can
only be applied where it was competent to do so.
So if you waive common law because you have some private contract and they're coming after
you because the common law says you have a right to private contract without interference.
So if there is someone that you have a private contract with is coming after you after some
bizarre performance issue that you didn't upkeep, the common law is not competent in
that case.
Right.
So when I say competent, meaning they cannot withstand as as a witness.
So most people here, that's you could take that as a parable, take that as a fiction
or whatever.
But if you don't have an understanding of the law, you will never see what's going on
there.
Now, I wasn't there.
And it doesn't say that he said whoever is without sin throw the first stone because
of the law.
He didn't say so.
Someone could take a strict interpretation of the other way, saying, well, he said that
because he's benevolent.
Right.
OK, so you be the judge.
In other words, again, it's open, but I'm telling you, it's not open because it's
reiterated over and over and over about doing the law of Moses.
Right.
And when he says, like, sin no more and all this other stuff also is with the law of Moses.
Because the payment is high and also the writing on the dirt.
You know, if someone is accused without a witness of adultery, the law is written and
dust from the temple flaws put into a cup and water and she drinks it.
And if she loses, it's like magic.
If she loses the use of her leg or legs, she's guilty.
If she can walk freely after she drinks that potion, she's not guilty.
So you see, so he's writing on the dust.
So if you understand the law, but when someone jumps, OK, let's be frank.
If you just jump around and saying, I like this or like that about the Bible or want
to know about this or about that, and you start making it fractional, you're never
going to you can see it in multiple different ways, which it's not even a diamond that has
many facets.
It's still a holistic piece.
Right.
It's a diamond.
OK, so the what makes what gives the the hardness to the Bible is that it is a law book.
All right.
First, and it shows you history.
It shows you law of those that agree to follow those laws and then temporal things.
And of course, the parables.
But for people that are interested in the parables, I think they without law, they would
get just as much out of philosophy.
And if I see that most of the stuff written in the Bible to those that are not in the
covenant, it's very cynical towards them.
Right.
So if you going to be towards cynicism, I would go and read Diogenes.
You'll get more out of that.
Actually, if you lean towards Greece, Greek speak, there's plenty of YouTube's you could
put in Diogenes, Greek philosopher.
And if you like Greek speak, you'll like Diogenes, you know, like Alexander the Great
went to Diogenes.
Diogenes was he was a cynic, but it goes it goes a long way.
OK, Alexander the Great came to him, as it goes, I'm paraphrasing and says, you know,
I'm Alexander the Great.
We came to Diogenes while Diogenes was signing near a tree in the afternoon.
And Diogenes, as Alexander said to Diogenes, you know, I'm Alexander.
I could grant you anything you wish.
So what would you wish?
And Diogenes says, yeah, just move over a little bit.
You're blocking the sun.
Right.
And then another time he came to Diogenes and he says, well, do you fear me?
And he says, well, men, well, it depends if you're good or evil.
If you're good, I have no reason to fear you.
Right.
He would stand outside of a whorehouse and yell while it was busy.
Prostitutes are like poison and honey.
Prostitutes are like poison and honey and disturb everyone in there.
So they would throw money at him to go away because he was known to be a beggar.
So when he collected enough coins, he went in and he joined.
He had enough money now to go inside the brothel himself, you see.
OK.
Right.
So he was quite interesting.
I like him.
One of his quotes is poverty is the only thing money can't buy.
OK.
I see.
So we have a level of irony here.
A comedian of his day, sort of.
Well, he was a cynic.
I mean, he did some foul things and he lived in a large ceramic cask.
Imagine a hundred gallon wine flask, you know, wine vessel.
OK.
You know, it'd be three feet wide, four feet tall.
He lived in one of those.
He would go into the town, into the Agora, which is the main market
at noon with a lantern fully lit at noon and shine at people's face.
And he says, what are you doing?
And he says, I'm looking for an honest man.
Yeah, he's pretty.
So if you're if you're down with Greek speak, check out Diogenes.
Some of the stuff is really harsh.
I wouldn't approve of defecating or masturbating in public.
Right.
Just to show people whatever.
And people call him, they call him a dog that spit in his face and all that.
Right.
Because he was a cynic.
But he says, what are you calling me a dog?
You think it's bad, but a dog is a good thing.
A dog, when he wants something, he barks at you.
And when and when you give him something, he, you know, wags his tail and licks you.
And he also bites the scoundrels.
So dog calling is actually dog has actually good qualities.
Yeah.
Dog will bite the people that are there to hurt you.
That's, you know, so anyway.
Yeah.
I would suggest the cynicism going along with the Greek speak, because very often I get into
a subject and to add levity to, you know, the three F's when you promote something or say
something.
Three F's are first one should have facts.
It should have feeling.
It should have fun.
So when I give some facts, I try to get the feeling of the person.
Let's talk about the money system.
I try to say something with fun, but so usually very cynic.
It's like, have you been on this planet for more than a week?
You should know this.
And someone heard me say this to someone new and they were like, oh, he says that to everyone
because, you know, the person was cautious that I might offend someone.
I said, no, I don't.
Person's person's not offended at all.
They just most of them laugh.
But in a nervous laugh when you, you know, if someone's showing you something that should
be well known, but it's not well known and they ask you, have you been on this planet
more than a week?
First of all, nobody says stuff like that.
I've never heard anyone say that.
And the other thing is, would you feel threatened?
Do you feel insulted?
Occasionally out of context, I'll say, what are you new here?
You know, in a situation which is kind of the same thing in a different way, but I can
use that in different situations, you know, not necessarily something.
But, you know, so there's many levels to it, but I've never some some people do get
insulted with the religious stuff.
I'm like, you know, basically, if I meet a Catholic, I mean, you're basically into
down with Satanism.
I'm not into they saw you just insulted me.
Right.
So, yeah, by the way, it is 100 percent.
That's, you know, anyway, you know, the politics signal each other by going to that
they're Catholic has nothing to do with being Catholic.
It's a signal, you know, public signal like in the men in black, you know, Catholicism
is satanic, among other things.
It's a huge composite.
It's adversarial.
Ton of things.
So, yeah, sure, sure.
But as somebody who is, you know, sort of the goes to church every Sunday, make sure
to put something in the plate.
And, you know, we'll quote that stuff any time there's any sort of controversy ever.
That guy gets offended at it because how dare you?
You know.
Yeah.
Well, that's why I say the atheists are the real nonprofits.
You'll never see an atheist megachurch.
And there's multiple meanings there, too.
They're nonprofits and they can't possibly be prophets because they don't believe in
prophecy.
So that's right.
So either way, there's secularists.
But they've always been atheists, by the way, always.
So, all right.
So so back to how we started on this, I I don't.
Hmm.
Let's just be forthright.
I the interests that I put forward, say, to be specific regarding what they call Scripture,
the Bible, whatever, are my own.
And the only reason I put my own interests out is because I find that when you strip
everything down about anything, especially the Bible, you can ask, what's its purpose?
What what's written in it?
And do we know it when we when we when we say we should?
And the answer to that is, no, no one seems to know what's in it.
Right.
Even the worst ones are the ones that go to church or seminary or whatever.
So, yeah.
So just like a lawyer, lawyers don't know anything about law.
They don't.
They know a little bit.
This is go look at a small community college teaches law like Harvard or Yale, right?
A minor college and look at their curriculum.
It's online.
You could put someone to go to the law school and they have the curriculum.
First year, second year, third year, four all the way down.
And where do they teach any law?
You won't find it at all.
It's all about how to start a legal clinic, Supreme Court opinions, constitutional
arguments, corporate trading, blah, blah, blah.
How to start a clinic again.
Level two.
Well, nothing.
What what law really is, where it comes from, where it should be, what the purpose, because
they're not because the way people behave, like we use that term earlier with way everything
is, they're not competent.
The law is not competent to them, because you can be competent or something else can
be incompetent.
Usually when you use the term competency, it refers to someone's mental aptitude, degree
and mental health.
Right, right.
But but when you're talking about law or rules, when it doesn't apply because you waived right
to it or you waived application, then that is not competent to the situation.
So something that is inanimate, like a law also may not be competent.
Right.
You see, it's it's this is old talk.
Like, for example, someone asked me at the scale or how many of these have you saw?
So I never sold one.
But I thought you said you got to, you know, a whole bunch of them out there.
I said, yeah, but they're not for sale.
They're for lease.
And right there for lease and is for 90 years.
And it's a one time settlement on the lease.
Right.
But the lease doesn't even say lease on it.
Oh, my gosh.
So what does it say?
I mean, you see, because I'm what I'm trying to do is create a situation where the law is
competent.
Right now, the law, if you read the lease agreement that I wrote up, you've never heard
anything, I guarantee you in your life before.
No, this is I paraphrasing.
If you're familiar with 19th century horse trader language, you know, like now you have
used car salesman.
But back in the 19th century, it was horse traders.
OK, you familiar with that language?
I'm familiar with the type of language.
Yeah, I get it.
I mean, yeah, you can be.
You will be in a minute.
I lived in a town called Ocean Grove in New Jersey.
Right.
And it's a funny thing.
You can own a house, but not the land.
The house is here.
I'll show you what competence is in the law.
The law being competent.
All right.
I'll tell you about it later.
OK, so this is only this is only OK.
I'll just pull it up just to get that out of the way so we don't go on a tangent.
Tell me about it.
Yeah.
But let's just do this is only this is about 55 words.
Ready?
All right.
So it starts off.
It's half a page.
Letting and leaving agreement doesn't say least just letting and leaving agreement for
an object affectionately known as the scalarator or and the Mark one, a decorative device to
be installed, held and used in good manner by blank, including their heirs in the signs
provided by its creator, Stelios, the Greek blank on blank and with mutual understanding
until a time of 90 years, known as the year 2114, to promise and to hold and use without
tamper and without malice.
And from time to time, its creator may improve, replace, upgrade, wilting use and holding
in good manner.
And here we come to fulfill our agreement for the sum of blank redeemed in lawful money
in accordance with 12 U.S.C.
411, quote, demand for lawful money, quote, clause.
And once fulfilled as a one time settlement of obligation with no further demand.
And further evidence of agreement, both have produced their appellations and marks to endorse
and seal this agreement.
That's it.
Does it say lease anywhere?
Doesn't say anything about water or doesn't say anything.
So someone comes back and says, well, that thing doesn't do anything for the water.
And he gives this to an attorney.
He says, well, it doesn't say anything about water here.
It's a matter of fact, it says it's for an object that affectionately known as the
mark one, a decorative device to be installed and held in good use.
Good use.
So you're going to say your lampshade is not cleaning the water?
No, but it's good.
You got no recourse, right?
It's good use, which could mean nearly anything.
You know, if I use it specifically to what they're complaining about.
So this is not the I've given this to quite a few people with doctorate degrees.
Even they're like, this is fine.
I've never heard of it called a letting elite.
But I said, if you I want you to read this and if you don't understand it, could you
show it to you and to an attorney?
And they're like, oh, no, I understand.
And I'm like, oh, my gosh, you know, they didn't really.
This is not a scam.
This is not a setup, because, by the way, it's a lease, right?
So, yeah, well, it's mine.
It's mine the whole time.
So but this is the reason why I'm doing this, because if the men in black come to me and
say, if this works, you're a dead man.
How many have you sold?
I can legally lawfully say zero.
I've never sold one.
Right.
Never sold any.
And here's the thing.
The word let you're letting at the beginning, letting and leaving.
OK, so letting and leaving.
Well, here's the thing.
I understand that word letting to be like a lease anyway, because what do you do when
you were released as legal?
Letting and leaving is in law.
So so in other words, if you have a lease agreement, the law is not competent there.
Yeah, that's legalese.
Right.
What I was going to say is when you have an apartment, right, and somewhere and you sub
let it.
Right.
That basically means that you have got under your agreement, whatever that is, you have
let it to someone else.
So subletting means that it was, you know, let to you and now you have let to someone
else.
It's the second going on a second tier now, which is the sub tier.
Yeah.
So this is direct because there's no sub to it.
So it is letting just the same kind of thing and leaving.
Yeah.
But here's the point.
Doesn't imply ownership.
Number one, number two, most people, even those lease agreements, you know, by the way, I
remember in New York, whenever I get one, I just put a diagonal line through the top
and sign the bottom and I put the date of the first month's rent and that's it.
In other words, I would sign it and put my I would after signing it, I'd write till the
first month's rent.
So in other words, if I don't like it after a month, I don't like it here.
I'm out of here.
Right.
You get it.
OK, well, yeah, and most of the time they looked at it like, why did you do that?
They wouldn't say.
Was there something in here you don't like?
So why did you do that?
Right.
Like, for example, I've seen people go to court and they have these long like quashing
a warrant or whatever.
If you ever read a quashing a warrant agreement, you know, quash a warrant.
You missed a truck.
You can't if you get it can't be federal.
You can't get you can't even get a ticket or anything for 30 days or 60 days because
they have a bond on you.
Right.
You can't whatever, whatever, whatever.
It's like, how would you sign the thing?
Oh, my gosh, the thing is so harsh.
Right.
Just put a line through it.
And most people don't understand that when you do stuff legally, it's not for your
benefit ever.
It's the one who is unilateral.
It's the one that's producing the legal document who's benefiting every time.
You see what I mean?
That's what I was going to point out about this thing as you read it to me.
Right.
Is that OK?
So you let it to someone.
It means that you never had a transfer of ownership.
No, that's for a different reason, because first of all, this is a prototype.
And I still don't if you ask me scientifically, tell me how it works.
I really can't tell you because I don't have the language.
Yeah.
All I know is that every time you hook it up, it does what I say it does.
Right.
Yeah, that's fine.
But that's the functionality which I can get to in a minute.
But first thing is you're not transferring ownership because you let it.
So you can't you can't transfer ownership because then
then you go into a different form of commerce.
This is we're not doing commerce here.
This is not commercial.
Yeah, that's but that's the point I'm trying to make here is that if you're letting it to
someone, you're not transferring ownership.
Right.
Normally, if you sell something, this is another reason why this is not a sale.
If you sell it, it means that you granted ownership to them.
You transferred your ownership to them in this document.
You're not transferring ownership.
Well, you know, you want to get even deeper.
The reason another reason not to do it is because you're transferring your interest
because there's no ownership, because there's no money.
Right.
Well, right.
But you can't in a more private setting.
You can do it.
But I'm trying to be prudent here.
Like if someone wants, quote unquote, their money back, which, you know, they get it back.
It's no big deal because it's a matter of
doing it for them, you know, because in other words, I have one already.
Right.
The device to clean my water.
So what do I care about anybody else?
Right.
And I'm not doing it to create a company or a business.
So then so that means that I'm doing it to extend this courtesy to others.
So, of course, if they're not happy with it, I take it back.
But it's also kind of like poking fun at society, just like
Diogenes.
Right.
So I got you.
But the thing that's interesting to me that is different from, you know, your normal
legal paperwork here is that all of the different elements that come together in a piece of
paperwork that are supposed to make things work a certain way are completely absent from
this thing, with the exception of a transfer of legal money or lawful money, lawful, excuse
me, lawful money.
I'm sorry.
I'm mixing up my terms because I'm trying to get it in there.
But anyway, that's fine.
When you start using the redemption, then you feel it.
This is what I tell people.
You can listen to Greek speak all you want, but until you start doing it, you won't really
feel it.
And if you don't, it's not real.
See, you can experience something in your mind or whatever.
But when you experience it in actual practice, you develop the emo for it because you cannot
develop an emo for something that you have not physically, not physically done, but are
experienced.
You see, so.
No, that's a constant.
That's a constant lesson in life that I really wish more people would learn.
You know, whatever they imagine something to be, it never is.
And no matter what we're talking about until they do it, they don't really know it.
Right.
Yeah.
Well, that develops the emo and everything is based on emo anyway, because how else?
Otherwise, you're going to you're doomed to listen to the voices in your head.
By the way, are the voices in my head bothering you today?
Not not me.
No, no.
OK.
All right.
I don't know if they bother anybody else.
No, I'm just because they're there anyway.
So, of course, it's kind of like a sideline cynic thing to say.
But the reason I bring this up is because the issue of competency, just like the issue of
minority is an issue of competency.
Like, for example, when I meet black or Latino people and they say I'm a minority, I said,
are you competent, mentally competent or are you underage?
And they're like, no, I'm not underage and I am mentally accomplished.
So why would you call yourself a minority?
So this is what they're pulling on the legal system.
So let's say 90 percent of the U.S. was black or Latino.
They would still call themselves minorities, even though they're the majority in number.
It has nothing to do with number.
A minority is someone who's under 18.
Right.
Can't get into me.
A minority just means you're not you can't go into contract.
You're a ward of the state.
You have to have a guardian or someone represent you.
Oh, my gosh.
This sounds like every, quote unquote, American U.S. citizen.
They are the minority.
Right.
So in other words, the law, when someone says they're a they're part of a minority,
the law is not competent for them.
In other words, they have to go to whatever agreement, their guardian or their attorney.
They need to have to have an attorney, not a lawyer, an attorney specifically
represent them because they're incompetent.
They're a minority.
And you have the I'll show you how strong the programming is.
You have how many black and Latinos, Native American, whatever, whoever else is under
I think Asian people are also considered minority.
Right.
If it was ninety nine point nine percent black, Latino and Asian, they would still
call themselves minority and they still haven't woken up.
That has nothing to do with a headcount, but it has to do with competency.
And now let's go back to the biblical.
They will take the curses upon themselves.
Right.
So if you're an adult and you're trying to operate in a society, whether it's legal or
lawful, you call yourself a minority.
It's like going out and say, hey, I'm crazy and competent.
I don't know what I'm doing.
It's the same thing.
It's also a question of geography as well.
Right.
Because the first time I ever questioned this in my life, I got into a weird argument
with somebody where they said, no, we're a minority.
And I said, OK, in in America, you're calling yourself a minority.
But, you know, if I was standing here having this conversation with you and I think Zaire
was the place that I called out.
I said, if we're having this conversation in Zaire, am I the minority?
Because I think I would be in within the borders of that place.
You're not minority because you're competent in the law.
In other words, when you call yourself this is not going to come about this.
If you call yourself a minority in legal parlance, that means you're incompetent and you need
a guardian or someone to represent you just like you were as if you were four years old.
Like, for example, you know, there's plenty of children in public schools that get injured
and they sue the school system and they get awarded a sum of cash.
But that child can't use that until they're 18 or 21.
Yeah.
Right.
OK, because they're a minority.
So if you still consider yourself a minority at 18 or 21 to go collect that, why do they
give it to you?
So it's duality.
They're practicing duality here.
Right.
So so all this vagueness, that's the law is not competent in that.
You cannot go into law if you practice that kind of stuff, either the administrative side
or the receiving side.
So let's say you have a Latino.
He falls and breaks his head on the water fountain in third grade and they award him
one hundred thousand dollars.
He can't use the third grade.
He's probably eight or seven.
And he can't use that until he's 18.
Right.
So at 18, he still considers a minority.
He goes and draws the check for one hundred K.
Right.
But why would they give it to him if he's a minority still?
So this duplicity is practiced on both sides.
That's why I keep saying if you know about law, you cannot be practicing attorney.
You cannot.
Because if you know about law and you start speaking to your colleagues and word gets
out to the Bar Association admin that, you know, law, they're going to disbar you right
away.
They'll give you like shut the fuck up or we're going to disbar you.
Right.
It's called Rule 11.
There's a rule for you look up Rule 11 for disbarment.
The judges threaten Rule 11 to lawyers when they bring in law, by the way, every time.
So where was I going with this?
Yeah.
If you work in any government position, doesn't matter how high or how low you know nothing
about government at all.
And how do I know this?
If you studied civics, which they don't teach anymore or civil law or anything like that,
and you go work in government and talk about it, they'll fire you and they'll make sure
you don't work in any government position again because all their computers are connected.
This is a fact.
Now, they do have like C-SPAN and CNN where they come out and they start asking questions
to Supreme Court nominees and all that.
That is all a show.
That is all scripted in a show and nobody knows what the hell anything means on both
sides.
So what kind of future do you have in a society like that?
I think the kind of future Diogenes talked about.
Yeah.
No, I was looking at rule 11, actually model rules for lawyer disciplinary enforcement.
Right.
Is that what it has?
Okay.
I haven't looked at it.
I mean, I just heard it before over and over.
I've never looked it up, but I figured if I dare to say, look it up and somebody yeah,
it's disciplinary enforcement.
Yeah.
Okay.
Use it that way.
Tangential language.
Yeah.
Like a garbage man is a sanitation engineer.
Sure.
Why not?
But evaluation, the disciplinary counsel shall evaluate all information coming to his or
her attention by complaint or from other sources, alleging lawyer misconduct or incapacity.
Capacity means you're trying to bring in something that's not competent, like law.
Okay.
So attorneys are at law.
What do you if you have a wife, her parents, are they called at laws or in laws?
In laws.
Yeah.
Right.
But they should be called out laws because you don't have a lawful marriage of a legal
marriage.
So this duplicity is is it's you know how they say the rot has gotten down to the core,
down to the bone, right?
It's completely rotten to the core.
And I could show you in any field, whether it's the religious field, the little pastor
that has a little, you know, 100 person church that hands out cans and feeds the homeless.
It's just as much of a scumbag as the pope.
Right.
Because he's in the same business.
He might be a little kinder.
Right.
Or whatever, right?
The pope.
You ever see the pope when people kisses and he wipes his hand, right?
Touches him, right?
Like George Bush did the same thing all the time.
Yeah.
He wiped his hand.
Because it's slimy.
So it's yeah.
So it's really, really, really rotten, rotten, rotten, rotten down to the core society.
But it's not as rotten as it can or will be before the mop up crew does its thing.
It's not bad.