Alright, Rated Y, Sonic Event 204, and we're
on the Jitsi again, but I don't know,
it was a little bit of a hot
noise to start with, and hopefully it's in
good shape now, I think we're good, Sonic
should sound good.
Anyway, how you doing, Greek?
Hey, pretty good.
Well, you know, on my end, this is
internally, you sound like one of those morning
shows where they have an echo, real loud,
but it's fine.
If you did the test and the recording
sounds acceptable, check it out, yeah.
Yeah, remember the morning shows in Asia, oh
baby, I'll tell you, that's the one that
took up TV last night, it was really
good.
And the more you speak, the more the
echo is, so I hope I can hear
what you're saying, but let's start off with
some questions if you got any.
I actually do.
Let's get to those, because that's usually the
most important thing, to get things kicked off.
Anyway, this one I barely understood, but let's
deal with it anyway.
In the code of Hammurabi, every punishment seems
to deal with death.
Greek mentioned that on Earth it builds up
a karmic tension for each death, so would
the code basically cease that karmic bond if
everyone just followed it and wasn't punished?
Or would that code be placed knowing humans
would break it and build up the karmic
death cycle?
Both.
Both, if you can say it that way.
The thing is, there's laws, and if there's
a, let's say, this is just how it
goes, everyone's got personal quote-unquote feelings and
ideas about it.
When something is a death offense, it should
be carried out, and when it's not, it's
actually worse sometimes, like when someone murders and
they're not doing it deliberately, right?
Yeah, it also goes down, they should be
put to death if they murder deliberately.
But then there's a fun aspect there, you
go to war and shoot 100 people and
you're given a medal, right?
So there's no natural aspect, it's 100%
spiritual based on law, and your law comes
from your god.
Right, and even within the text of what
I've understood, right, I gotta throw this in,
there is the possibility that you could commit
a killing that is not a murder, and
murder is a crime.
Yeah, by accident.
Well, not necessarily by accident, like even if
it is intentional, defending oneself is okay, right?
Yeah, that's right.
I mean, the idea, or defending others, even,
defending your home, defending weaker people.
Yes, it's intense.
Look, even if you say you killed someone
in self-defense, if there's evidence or witnesses
that you had malice towards them before, it
could become first degree, let's say.
Okay, but if it just so happens, you
know, a stranger happens upon you and is
violent, you put him down.
Yeah, self-defense is adequate, yeah.
But there's also more to it, like the
karmic side, you know, I'm using that word
loosely, the way people understand it, because when
you read, you know, let's say the ancient
writs about karma, it's very extensive, it's not
just what people think.
No, it's not a simple action and reaction,
it's not just that.
No, it's not.
But putting people in prison, for example, for
stealing is unlawful.
When you steal, there's no prison or jail,
what you do is you have to pay
back twice, let's say, what you stole, the
value, and if you don't have the money
to do that, or the value to do
that, you have to work it off, so
you literally become that person's servant until it's
worked off.
So it's not just murder, and when it
comes to law and the karmic side, the
spiritual side on how the earth reacts, it's
any mal-act that's not done according to
law.
So you know, like I always say that,
first of all, no one is in jail
or prison lawfully, or even legally, and having
people the way they do it, it's all
unlawful, because it's all commercial.
But if you look at the Code of
Hammurabi and other stuff, it's all commercial too,
like if someone builds a house, and it
falls on the owner's son, and he dies,
and we have to kill the son of
the builder, so it's commercial again.
These kinds of laws and things are for
nation-building, I've always talked about this.
When you read a lot of ancient writs,
it's for nation-building, kind of like the
Constitution of the U.S., or the Constitution
of a country, you got a new country,
okay, you got your post office set up,
okay, well, where's your Constitution, or when you
start a company, where's your charter, what are
you setting out to do?
Most of these laws, really, initially, were setting
up a new entity, if you could call
it that, and it had the rules for
that entity.
So right now, what's going on, mostly, is
adjustment of laws, or getting away from them.
It's good you brought that up, because I
was listening to Jonah Bay's recent audio, I'm
really enjoying Jonah Bay, I'm almost at the
point where I can endorse him, he's that
good, believe it or not.
Which one is Jonah Bay, is that the
guy who's telling you the West is poisoned,
or is that the other one?
No, no, that's Middle Nation, that's another guy.
I wouldn't endorse him, because I think he's
putting too much cultural pressure on people.
Just to switch over, that guy at Middle
Nation, Saeed, I think his name is, I
recently found out he was in prison for
murder during the Egyptian rebellion, or the Arab
Spring, and he was released for some reason,
and some people like him, some people don't.
I'm just saying his commentary, because it's culture,
is valid, mostly.
But with Jonah Bay, he brought up a
court case, United States versus Johnson, 1947, where
the essence is, the only rights you have
are the ones you can defend, and this
case was specifically about being a belligerent defendant.
So when you go to these courts, which
are, they're not courts, they're like Article One
courts, they have no power in law or
equity, it's all contract courts.
They give you charges, anything you say can
and will be used against you.
The idea of being a belligerent defendant is,
you go in there and you cuss them
out.
You say, what you're doing is unconstitutional.
If they arrest you, you have habeas corpus,
unrightful imprisonment, all this stuff, until you get
to the Supreme Court, and you just basically
cuss them out, right there.
And I've heard a recording of a young
man, Caleb, he went into court, cussed out
the judge, and she was like, well, the
judge was threatening him, he says, I don't
care what you say, if you're a public
official, you're fired, you know, that kind of
stuff.
And if they put you in jail, habeas
corpus, and it's really a quarter of a
million dollars if they jail you unlawfully, but
that's another story.
I kind of like, when you listen to
a lot of the stuff like Batman back
in the days, I know some people might
have never heard of him, but he was
like, don't be belligerent.
Actually, the Supreme Court says, if you're not
belligerent, and you accept anything they say, basically,
now you take liability for it, because by
the way, what they're doing in the current
legal system, the police, the lawyers, attorney generals,
all the courts, except for the Supreme Court,
is illegal and unlawful in that venue.
But if you switch it over to commercial,
you're writing contracts, right, it's all commercial.
So it's pretty heinous, it's pretty horrible, what
they're doing.
That's why I say, I can almost say
with little exception, no one is in jail,
well, I can tell you for sure, no
one is in prison legally, or lawfully, I
mean, no one is in prison lawfully.
Some might be there legally, because they agreed
to it, they'd rather be in prison than
doing other things, and that's fine, then it's
not really prison, it's a, what do they
call, what did they call people when they
put them in the Fed, it was club
fed, right?
Voluntarily.
So it's that bad, but no one really,
look, the stuff I've been talking about, I've
been saying for two decades, three decades now,
no one knows what's going on, no one
pretty much knows anything with little exception.
So any subject you approach, even if you
don't know about it, you could say, oh,
let's see how they're running this shit backwards,
right?
Let's say there's a new subject we, you
and I, never heard of, and someone brings
it up, I say, I never heard of
this, and we go look into it, and
before I even look into it, I say,
let's see how they're telling us what the
opposite of what it really is, and you'll
be pretty much on point if you do
that.
Now, some people might say, oh, that's really
sarcastic or pessimistic, well, look, I didn't make
this shit up, right?
Yeah.
So.
I got you.
Anyway.
Like, for instance, a new business could be,
you know, documents that you print that are
actually, you know, to replace other things that
people think they need.
You know what I mean?
Like the guy who turned around and created
that, what is it, the Republic of Contra
or whatever, they're on the tip of Florida.
You ever see that?
Oh, you can do that.
Micronations?
Yeah.
I like Slow Jamistan.
That one, well, there's that, and there's another
one.
That's the DJ.
Yeah.
Well, there's one in New Mexico.
This is quite a few.
There's about 10 of them.
Oh, yeah.
There's one in California, one in Mexico, one
in Florida.
Yeah.
There's one in Arizona, too, isn't there?
Nevada.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
They don't get much publicity.
I don't think they want it, but they
do button it up according to law, you
know?
Well, that's the thing, is that they actually
usually don't get messed with, and they tell
them, look, as long as you kind of
abide by U.S. laws also, it's fine,
which is weird to me.
Yeah, which is fine to a degree, which
if someone says, you know, you need to
abide by U.S. laws, fine, because when
you read the U.S. laws or definitions,
it's fine.
Yeah.
I'm not a fiction, right?
I'm not this.
I'm not...
Yeah, it doesn't...
Yeah.
The craziest thing is, well, they say, like,
the United States is in District of Columbia.
It didn't say United States is District of
Columbia, it says it's in District of Columbia,
so you go around District of Columbia, Washington,
D.C., 10-mile square area, three-and
-a-half by three-and-a-half miles,
whatever it is, drive around and keep asking
people, where's the United States?
You'll never find it.
It's in a file cabinet somewhere.
So their laws are totally, totally fine.
All of it, it's all perception, it's a
perception, what do you call it?
Perceived reality.
Perception, what do they call it when people,
consensus reality, which is when you get people...
Yeah, media, the media is very, very important
on...
Forget about any body of knowledge, it's the
media, you know, that really controls it.
Before the media that we have, it was
the church and, you know, stuff like that.
So, yeah, it's pretty bad.
It's pretty bad.
It's like herding cattle.
What I see, and if you've been around
cattle or whatever, like when there's a young
calf, it's not even a year old and
it starts to snow or rain, the calf
freezes, like, what the hell is this?
I've never seen this before.
They have to go out and get it
because it's standing in the muddy field, frozen,
stiff, scared stiff.
The rancher has to go out and bring
it back in because it never saw rain
before, right?
Right.
That's how I see most people, and especially
professionals, when I interact with, quote unquote, doctors,
lawyers, whatever, and bring up anything that they're
supposed to be doing, just ask simple questions.
They kind of freeze up and they're like,
oh my gosh, you know, I never thought
of that.
I mean, God damn, you're working on people
or you're a lawyer, you don't know any
of this.
Oh my gosh.
You know, it's pretty, it's like the calf
that gets, you know, never saw rain before
and it's scared stiff, you know?
It's pretty bad.
I always find it amazing when somebody's called
a doctor, but they really do not know
how to dress a wound properly, you know?
Well, they don't know anything.
What the hell are you doing?
Yeah, they're just serving a position.
Yeah.
Anyway, one other piece of commentary came in.
I like the casual mention of the coming
global cooling age.
I don't know what that's from anyway, but
he says Florida orange groves will become Florida
apple orchards and no more gators.
What do you think of that?
Well, the thing is, I would, I would
lean heavily on the archaics doctrine and narrative
about the Phoenix coming and going into a
vapor canopy in 2040, the beginning of a
vapor canopy, like all the volcanoes, you know,
one big, large volcano puts out more emissions
than all the cars in the world do
in 10 years, right?
So imagine hundreds of volcanoes going off, blocking
out the sun, greenhouse effect, and then ice
forming on that greenhouse on the outside, right?
So you're basically one of those, one of
those Christmas balls that you shake and it
snows.
That's what the earth, you know, our environment
will be like a snow globe, purple sky
snow globe.
Yeah.
Well, I don't buy ice age.
I buy the vapor canopy.
I'll lean on the vapor canopy, which is
neither ice age or heat wave.
And the way I would say that is,
I don't know if anyone's all here listening
old enough.
If you bought a car in the late
seventies, the on the speedometer, it accentuated 55.
It had it in orange or had a
circle around it or a square on it
because you're supposed to drive.
And if you find out why they put
drive 55, it's because that was the most
efficient speed for the cars they had then
to use less fuel.
So because we were going into an ice
age, we didn't want to accelerate it.
That was the reasoning.
If you've seen old cars that you might
remember, they see 55 miles an hour, accentuated
on the speedometer.
Yeah.
That was because of the coming ice age.
So I think that if you're confused about
this, that means you're you're OK, because you
should just focus on what has the most
evidence.
And believe it or not, the only person
out here or, you know, entity or collective
of information that has the best data set,
as they would say, is Jason Breshears of
Archaic.
He has the best historical data set.
You can't argue with it too much.
You know, the chances of it not happening
the way he's saying it's going to happen
is very slim.
So I would lean on that information.
Fair enough.
I also figured that that had to inspire
that Sammy Hagar song, right?
I can't drive 55.
Remember that?
Yeah.
Well, I wasn't a big Sammy Hagar fan,
but I figured you might have heard it
on the radio or whatever.
So look, I have one last piece of
feedback only, and then I'm done with the
feedback.
But it was kind of long.
And what they said is that they've been
listening for a little while and they decided
they wanted to listen to as much as
they could and go through rated Y.
They had gone through other, you know, permutations
of your sonics before.
And they said, you know, I want to
start applying this stuff, but I'm a little
concerned.
Now, I responded back immediately and said, look,
if I'm you, if you value the people
and things around you, don't because how socially
you want to be.
That's the thing, because you're going to immediately
change all that if you really engage with
every single level of this stuff.
And but they wanted to ask you, where
should I start if I want to start
engaging now that I've taken the time to
listen, evaluate, go with it, and now I'm
going to start changing things accordingly.
And I went, hmm, OK, so I'll just
throw it to the grease.
Simple.
That's real simple.
And the answer is that what are the
basic needs?
Food, clothing, shelter, by example.
So all the little tips and tricks and
hints and methods that I put out regarding
food, clothing and shelter start demonstrating that to
others.
If you have a household or whatever, and
they'll see, oh, wow, how come this, you
know, he's doing everything so much better and
then introduce the more subtle things, the spiritual
stuff, the lawful stuff, the other concepts slowly,
like, you know, and food, clothing, shelter, also
human body.
You know, I've had quite a few testimonials
over the years about people getting injuries and,
you know, everyone around them is like, oh,
you got to go to the emergency room,
you know, like a laceration or something.
And they're like, no, no, no.
Do this.
And like they show me a photo.
It's pretty gruesome.
And then like three days later, it looks
like nothing happened.
You know, with the electrical tape and paper
towels, you know, that's you don't have to
use that.
But that's the basics of it.
And so then when you build up, by
example, food, clothing, shelter and the human body,
people then will tend to be more accepting
and more, let's say, swayed over.
Oh, yeah.
With the cooking and everything.
I get all that.
But what happens is when you get to
a certain point, though, and you start going,
well, now I'm against the medical convention because
I'm telling you, you know, the heart's not
a pump.
OK, but hold on.
You don't have to be against it.
You could be you could run parallel to
it.
Right.
Because remember, I've always said these idiots in
the medical community, they've done a lot of
grunt work.
Right.
So if someone digs a big ditch, you
just don't go fill it just because just
leave it there.
It might be good use.
You may want to throw them in the
ditch right later.
And so, you know, so leave it open.
So so a lot of the things that
they have, like, you know, with anatomy is
valid, but they don't know how it works
at all.
And you know what they do, but they
won't tell you because it's we're at war.
We're an information war.
People don't know that, you know, the United
this country lost a war in 1871 and
even lost again.
Imagine a country like Iraq, right?
They invaded one in 91 and then they
invaded again in 2003.
That's what happened to the US.
They came in 1871, started the war, and
then they invaded again in 1933.
All administratively, all on paper, which is more
lethal, because if they blew up your homes
and killed your people, it would be very
easy and functional resistance.
But if they do it sneaky using paperwork
that they know and also they're going to
dissuade you from reading it, they're going to
win every time.
And that's how it works.
And just like whenever a fiat currency is
introduced as the only currency, it's the end
of a nation.
That's a maximum of law.
That's not even whatever.
So you're at war.
You just don't know it.
But it's a different kind of war, right?
It's an informational war.
So you run parallel to it.
You know, one of the best things to
do, the national the Germans did, this national
socialist is about 30 percent of the equipment
they had was salvaged from the other side.
Right.
OK, so you want to you want to
maintain a battle, let's say, break, you tactically
succeed and strategically succeed, but you want to
save as much of the equipment as possible
so you don't have to manufacture it from
the ground up.
It's kind of like the concept of the
neutron bomb kills all the people, but it
leaves all the infrastructure intact.
That's what they did.
And it's still going on today.
But they're killing you in many, many ways
that you don't even realize.
And now it's pretty obvious that they don't
mind killing you off.
I think the U.S., by the way,
is pretty close to a zero population growth,
isn't it?
Well, in other words, for every person that's
born, one person dies pretty close to that.
Well, no, it's it's at a point where
we're below replacement, OK, where you don't have
below population growth.
It's below replacement.
So you're replacing, say, one point two for
every two people kind of thing.
So that I see.
Yeah, that's the the math.
That's about so for every so every person
that first.
So for every person that's born, two people
are dying.
Almost hard to say.
Almost.
So we're not interesting.
Yeah, that's pretty bad when you consider, you
know, how humans typically are.
But that's that's another discussion, really, because there's
plenty of room for everyone.
You know, the entire population of the earth
could be put in Texas.
Right.
In a suburban setting.
So and by the way, I think I've
been pushing around videos.
There's some people that have been doing research
in China and people that defected from the
communist CCP.
If you look hard, they'll tell you there's
really like anywhere between three hundred and fifty
to four hundred and fifty million people in
China, not one point, whatever billion.
Right.
I've been saying that for more than 20
years.
And the reason they put up the figure
is because they've discounted their birth certificates.
Right.
So they need more.
So anyway.
Yeah.
So this is the population of who knows
what it is because the information is held
by the bankers and we know the bankers
always give us accurate information.
Right.
So, yeah, no, they don't confabulate.
Yeah.
But back to the question.
Try to do by example.
But yeah, I find I tell people if
you're in a relationship, marriage or whatever, whatever,
there's like a 70 to 90 percent chance
rate that if only one of you wants
to do this stuff, the relationship won't hold.
Right.
Now, I've heard of people that, you know,
like some new people, I would love your
stuff.
And are you married?
Yeah.
Oh, but she loves it, too.
OK, cool.
Because if she wasn't into it, it's over.
It's just a matter of time.
Right.
You're going to diverge.
I mean, it's just going to.
Yeah, it's a matter of time.
Yeah.
And the stuff I put out is is
better than what they're doing.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be putting it out.
It's pretty obvious.
I mean, to to once you put it
in practice, that it is a better method.
And the only reason I'm doing Sonics is
because 99 percent of the stuff I talk
about, I can't find anywhere else.
Right.
So so you're creating it and that's all
good.
So anyway, that's all the feedback I've got
for for this one.
Yeah.
Well, we got we did something different.
The last two Sonics was a part one,
part two of of the testament of the
robustness of the human or the man and
women.
Right.
And things you should be concerned about.
What I got into the basics, food, clothing,
shelter.
Someone did post regarding food, a cauliflower recipe
on the Greek chili and the Greek Chitango,
which is the right idea.
I did.
I've done a broccoli recipe and a cabbage
recipe.
The cauliflower.
I do something similar.
I haven't done it in a while.
The idea of using a lot of fat
with cauliflower, as in the video, is very
good.
So but that's the idea.
You can make a single vegetable, an entree
if you prepare it.
Right.
And yeah, that's that's definitely the idea.
And thank you for whoever posted that.
The other thing that's been showing up in
the chili and the Greek Chitango is this
the voices.
A lot of the some of them are
really some people apparently are when you're more
like one of the comments was, you know,
I kind of knew something about that a
little bit.
I sensed it.
But when the Greeks are talking about it
now, I really zeroed in on it.
I really see it clearly.
And a lot of negative stuff comes from
these things, kind of like look out for
Charlie.
You know, these finds these hidden voices are
always negative.
Yeah, that's basically the what's happening here.
But it doesn't mean you have to succumb
to it.
Now, it's OK to succumb to it and
let it flow through.
But but and it's also not OK to
always be fighting it.
And one of the things that I always
found is when I catch that, like chatter
in the head, I just stop and tell
myself, OK, so what did you say?
Say that again.
And it stops because they rely on you
not acknowledging it as being separate from you.
And the moment you acknowledge that these voices
and inputs are not yours and you buy
it by saying, hey, say that again or
I'm not having that bullshit or whatever.
They stop.
They literally stop because their whole memo is
to not be recognized as a separate entity
from who their, you know, their victim is.
And we're all victims to a degree.
The thing that I posted is the Mandela
effect.
Holy crap.
I needed a part, by the way.
It's an oil pressure sensor.
And I started looking around all the typical
places and it's discontinued, discontinued, discontinued, not available,
not available.
Even I went to Chrysler, discontinued, called the
dealer.
Are you sure?
Yeah, it's discontinued.
So I found a place that they could
order.
It came from another part of the state.
They came in.
It was the wrong piece.
It didn't fit.
I was like, damn, you know, the sensor
just the terminals were off and all that.
And then I was like, all right, let
me go back to the computer and start
searching again.
And I went through every place that I
had previously searched now had it.
Every single outlet had it.
Wow.
And I was like, OK, all right.
All right.
Now, I'm not that far off with my
memory because I remember spending an hour going
to many, many sites, looking up, cross-referencing,
making phone calls.
It was discontinued, discontinued, not available, not available.
I ordered the part that comes in.
It's the wrong part.
Will not fit, even though they assured me
it's the right one.
I start everything from scratch again.
And now suddenly it's available even at like
AutoZone or O'Reilly's.
It's just there, you know.
And I'm like, how can this be?
So at least on AutoZone or O'Reilly's,
you can go in and look at it
directly and know it's the right or wrong
part.
I did get it today.
I mean, I got it today and it
is the right one.
But how could it be?
I clearly remember last week it didn't exist.
It was actually more than two weeks ago
because well, because it didn't exist.
And I got the wrong one.
I actually repaired the old one, which exploded.
And the repair wouldn't hold because it's plastic
against metal.
And it has to be crimped a certain
way.
But anyway, I just sat down and took
a deep breath and laughed.
And I said, you mother effers.
See, I don't really you really mess with
us this much.
Now, this sounds very personal, right?
Because it's not like everybody remembers the Empire
State Building looking like this.
And now it looks like that.
This is very personal, meaning just me, myself.
And I had to meditate as I did.
I really recall I haven't had a notepad,
you know, taking notes that I couldn't find
it.
So and the notes were still there.
A bunch of other stuff changed also last
week or this week.
Something you see.
I often tell people that, look, when you
hit a wall like that, that you don't
think you should be hitting, walk away from
it, go back to it later and just
try it again.
Just from the beginning again.
Well, here's the interesting thing.
That's not this is not the case because
it was established in the past that this
thing was discontinued.
I gave up.
Right.
And then when the part that I got
disposed to work didn't fit, I said, well,
I got to start all over again.
And when I did, I noticed there's nothing
to stop because I noticed suddenly it's available.
Right.
So it means the entire world around it
changed.
So, you know, I didn't I couldn't do
anything.
I didn't have to do much because now
it's available.
No, all you had to do is continue
to try, though.
Somebody else might have said, OK, forget it.
Now I'm going to change my entire plan
because I can't get this part.
You know what I mean?
Right.
But I went back and started again the
logical thing.
Let's just start looking again.
And suddenly it's available everywhere.
That means that something happened to this entire
reality that flipped.
It changed.
And I'm just wondering if anybody else has
been noticing major changes.
And I don't think they're major.
Like, you know, the Empire State Building now
has two towers instead of one or where
nothing like that.
In personal, you know, I have had this
several times when I was actually made a
template.
Do you tell me the Empire State Building
has two towers literally or are you just
making that up?
No, I'm just making it up.
It's not obvious.
In other words, that's something that's happening.
And what I'm trying to say, it's happening
on an individual basis.
You're being screwed with individually instead of something
everyone can see.
Like, you know, like you get it's not
like the Golden Gate Bridge is now green
and everyone says, yeah, it's always been green.
No, I remember it being red.
And 10,000 people say, yeah, it was
red.
What's not green?
It was never green.
And then you have the rest of the
population saying, you guys are crazy.
It's always been green.
It's nothing like that.
It's very, very, very specific.
The only way I can make it more
substantial is to put out who else was
looking for this part two weeks ago, found
it's discontinued, but now it's available.
You know, I mean, that's going to be
too narrow of a call out.
Right.
So what I'm saying is these these things
that are happening are very, very personal to
an individual.
Right.
It's kind of like you will go home
one day and your bathroom, instead of being
pink or blue, is now green or yellow.
And but who are you going to tell?
Because, you know, maybe you and one or
two other people know that, you see.
Hmm.
Right.
So I think it's it's messing around on
a on a personal level.
But I'm not saying that there isn't, you
know, the Bernstein bears or remember, this was
it was like Haas avocados was H.A.
H double A.S. Not H.A. S
.S. A lot of people do remember a
lot of these things.
I think it's it also happens on an
extremely personal level.
Right.
Well, I went through your body moving to
another side.
Right.
I know.
I believe that that kind of thing happens.
Also, you know, I had a weird thing
with the World Trade Center where, you know,
we ended up talking a whole bunch of
9-11 stuff and people had this crazy
idea about when the World Trade Center opened
for business.
And I told them there's no way that's
possible because I remember getting a lunchbox with
King Kong on it when I was seven
years old.
Yeah.
And it was a World Trade Center.
Nineteen seventy nine.
And he was standing one foot on each
one of the World Trade Towers is the
way they depicted him on the lunchbox.
And they were like, that can't be because
it wasn't open.
And, you know, it wasn't even available to
be a picture in nineteen seventy nine.
I'm like, yes, it was.
And it was seventy three, I think.
Yeah, right.
But some of these other people had a
memory that it didn't open till the 80s.
And oh, my gosh, that's pretty bad memory.
That can't be.
I mean, what's this?
I mean, that's a fact that's really, really,
I think, too far off that.
That's a weird.
These edits are more subtle than that.
Yeah.
No, I'm just saying I've seen extreme weird
things like that.
And I was like, you almost made me
nervous when you said something about the two
you know, like spikes coming up on the
world, on the Empire State Building.
Yeah.
Which would be weird.
But because I've seen that my whole life
and I know it's a singular point.
So what I'm trying to try to underscore,
I think it's a lot of the changes
are very, very personal, like like, for example,
a good example would be you have a
mole on your on your left shoulder and
now you've always considered that and known it.
And then one day you look and it's
now it's no longer on the left, the
same exact moles on the right shoulder.
So who are you going to substantiate that
with?
Only people who know that you have that
bowl there.
Right.
So it's very personal.
So I'm bringing this up because it ties
in with the voices somehow.
Same general subject.
But the voices are something to consider because
it really stands the entire psychological industry on
its head.
You know, all the stuff they're saying that
they can't substantiate and tell you why someone
has schizophrenia or anything like that.
It's all external input and they won't they
can't go there anyway.
It's a fraud of an institution, the psychology
and psychiatry, especially.
They don't I mean, they're morons.
I mean, how can you have something like
psychology or psychiatry when the regular medics think
the heart is a pump?
I mean, you got to go back to
the basics, you know, and they don't know
about the biological vacuum.
I want to do also when I do
get some time.
And by the way, right now, the water
stuff that I'm working on is expanding and
expanding and I'm getting proposals for projects and
I'm trying to just stay on the engineering
side, just doing design work.
But unfortunately, I do have to build things
also.
It's here.
One Mandela effect is dealing with engineers.
And every time you you have a meeting
on something and then you meet with them
again and they ask you the same questions
as if you didn't have the first meeting.
Now, should I count that as a Mandela
effect or a mental defect?
But anyway, I have to carry a lot.
I mean, but either way, the things are
not up to snuff and you can't fix
them.
So but what I wanted to do when
I do get an opening with the for
time, if it's possible, is actually get a
bunch of people that have medical training together
and do like a webinar thing with them.
So bring up the basics, you know, the
biological vacuum, all the tissues are nonpermeable.
Right.
The lung tissue is not permeable.
When I say nonpermeable, you know what I
mean.
Right.
It's closed.
Nothing goes through a closed system.
Yeah.
But the system is open from the mouth
to the anus.
And then you have certain other things that
may be glands that have poor extrusion anyway.
And when I put out the information, ask
a small audience of medical people that have
the training in anatomy, especially for feedback in
real time.
And I'll be, quote, unquote, I'll be nice,
but I'll be pleasant and try to give
more explanations.
And I have put this out to half
a dozen people in medical training.
No one is coming forward at all.
They don't want it.
And I'm like, I won't show your face.
I won't give your name, maybe your voice.
But just with the voice alone, I think
you can identify people anyway.
Mostly.
Yeah, you can.
You can.
Yeah.
So I'm not getting any takers.
And that's fine.
I do comprehend why.
Because it's very, very subtle.
Imagine, you know, imagine how bad it is
for their reputation.
You know, imagine saying you're so and so,
whatever.
And you I heard you in the audience
with the Greek and we have to side
with the Greek.
He's got all the you know, the facts
and the data sets, let's say, for what's
going on.
And you're a doctor and you didn't know
this.
Oh, shit.
So I get it.
I get it.
Right.
I still get messages from medical people saying
Greek.
I never.
It's amazing.
Yeah, it is true what you're saying.
And, you know, so and there are voice
filters out there.
If these guys wanted to, they could like
mask their voice if they wanted to.
Yeah, whatever.
But that's just the thought.
I mean, and what why would you structure
something like that anyway?
Like anyone's going to learn anything from it,
right?
It's too late, you know, for that kind
of stuff.
But again, you don't have to go against
any of it.
You run parallel, just like with the legal
idiots, you know, just stick to the Constitution.
Right.
You have all the you have protected rights,
meaning not that the Constitution gives you rights.
It doesn't.
The Bill of Rights supports certain things, right,
which most people don't even know what they
are.
That is the Constitution, because it has limitations
on what the governing body should do.
That is your protection.
Is there your protection via the Constitution?
Is there a limitation holding them to their
limitations is what protects you?
Right.
So they stay inbound.
They don't go out of bounds.
Right.
So when you do that, anyone in the
legal systems thinks you're going contrary, but you're
not.
You're using the supremacy clauses.
Right.
And right.
In common law, which is court decisions and
the Constitution, you're running parallel to it.
So don't touch me.
In other words, you're going to keep the
legal stuff where it belongs and the law
stuff where it belongs.
Right.
If running power.
So you don't have to go.
So with the medical, the legal or anything,
even personal relationship, don't go contra, just run
parallel to it and do it better.
And, you know, show that's where the show
by example or demonstrate, you know, something better
comes from.
Yeah.
Hey, last thing you need to send me
that schematic on the aqueous Argentum.
Oh, yeah, I'll do that.
Yeah.
You got you got activity requesting that.
Let's say I've got I've got like two,
I think.
And I want to put them in.
I'll put them in touch with Joe also,
just because he's got one that works already.
And with the schematic, then they take it
from there.
Right.
Yeah.
Yeah, exactly.
And if you don't know how to put
together a basic circuit, there's plenty of people
that do.
Even if you went to an electronic supply
place and show them the diagram, I need
these parts.
They'll actually put it together for you right
there.
Usually.