Rated Y Sonic Event 2.10 and Greek,
how are you?
Good, 2.10, okay, we're still trucking along.
Yeah, I'm okay, yeah.
Yeah, just doing it, man.
Kind of goes with the synergy there, too.
Like, you know, when we go with the
numbers there, people are going back, and somebody
just hit 12 recently, and somebody else hit
120, and a lot of other people get
them as they come out.
So, you know, here we go.
Yeah, we've got some new people asking questions
via e-mail and all that.
Nice.
And I get some longer e-mails regarding
how thankful people are about, specifically, health, all
kinds of other stuff, even mechanical stuff.
So I figure for each one of those,
there's ten more that are benefiting extremely.
But I want to just state, like in
the news recently, you know, there's the Israel
bombing Iran and back and forth, or the
Ukraine conflict, you know, which is not really
a war.
Like, Vietnam was not a war, right?
Right.
Actually, this was question number one anyway, is
the Middle East.
Yeah, this has nothing to do with, for
example, it's about, okay, we live in a
place that has negative value.
In other words, it's fucked up.
If you're here, for whatever spiritual, whatever you
believe in or hold dear, you did something
really fucked up to be put here, number
one.
Or you're not supposed to be here, and
you're here in a fucked up place.
You came deliberately because you wanted to play
these video games that are really fucked up,
and they sent you here anyway.
This is a fucked up place.
If you are so insensitive that you think
that you actually enjoy walking on the seashore,
breathing the clean air, mountain air, beautiful sunset
and flowers, if you're that insensitive, stay in
your insensitivity and your lack of perception and
enjoy those things like a good meal, a
good conversation.
Generally, this is a very fucked up place,
like it or not.
Now, it's a physical place, and like I
was mentioning to someone, I think on a
podcast I did recently, we're on the paranormal.
When you're disembodied, it's very much like being
high or drunk, right?
So don't look forward to that either.
I don't know really what I'm saying in
terms of putting it all together, but what
I want to do is say this.
The Israeli-Iran attack was June 12th, 13th.
What is it roughly now?
Today is the 14th, right now.
Okay, the 14th, so it's like the third
day of the fourth month, which is very
rare you get a conflict starting around that
time and all that.
So that conflict or that exchange is really
more for not the Israelis or the Iranians,
but for everyone else, if that makes any
sense.
It's to signal to everyone else, look how
fucked up it is over here, right?
First of all, the state of political affairs
and people working in there, first of all,
go into a DMV office, Social Security office,
you can't tell me the people that work
there are fully human, right?
I don't know if you know what I
mean.
They're some kind of degenerate whatever.
Even State Department, executive stuff, I've seen people
work up in the Senate and all that.
There's something wrong.
Something seems to be missing.
I mean, you know, some people go with
the NPC deal.
There's something wrong with these people, right, in
the get-go.
And everyone has something wrong in their own
way.
It's not a general classification.
It's another species.
So this is the classification of what you
call authority.
The lizards that run this place, yes, I
haven't brought that up in a long time,
and that is about a 99.999%
sure the lizards run this place, lizard energy,
whatever.
Are orchestrating on a very low level.
Now, low-level stuff.
This is like, think of a real basic
video game like Space Invaders or Pac-Man,
level one.
That's what's going on.
The reality of Israel and Iran, I've been
saying this for 20 years, even archaics calls
it the exilarchy, the real heavy-duty Israeli
pawnbrokers of the world live in Iran, Persia.
They always have, still do.
I've always talked about how the Mossad and
the Persian mob are like hand in glove.
They're actually best friends.
Second of all, we're talking about the underworld,
right?
Second of all, the Persians, Iranians, are not
Muslim.
They put these scumbags, they call them fundamentalists,
which they're not.
They're radical.
Fundamental means being basic, and like a fundamental
biblical person follows the law, right?
Yeah, I've always found that.
You know what I mean?
They don't follow anything.
They're just radical.
There's nothing radical about Islam, by the way,
nothing at all.
Well, I've always found that.
See, it's not just about Islam, because they're
a Christian fundamentalist, this, that, third thing.
Well, fundamentally, it's been used wrong, just like
anarchy is used wrong.
Yeah, but I've always found the use of
that word really crazy, because it's like fundamental.
Yeah, like the word nice is used wrong.
Yeah.
But let me just continue on this.
Sure, sure.
So it was confirmed that during the first
Poppy Bush administration, up until Obama, there were
shipments of nuclear triggers to Iran, Persia, and
they didn't want it, so they have a
place on the border with Iraq that they
store these.
But either one can get them, right?
Okay.
Yeah, so all this stuff about nuclear, it's
total bullshit.
Okay, on the American side, I don't think
any of these people are real, right?
And what I mean by that, you could
use whatever.
They're not organic.
Look up, there was a lot of stuff
going on back in the 80s and 90s
about human robotoids, and it doesn't mean robot,
there's cloning, right?
Cloning was done in the 30s.
None of these people are real that you
see on TV or whatever.
I can assure you of that based on
my perception and opinion of what's going on.
So what I suggest is what I always
suggest, food, clothing, shelter, people are impressed.
Semi-intelligent to intelligent people are very impressed
when I give my defense on food, clothing,
shelter, right?
And this is what you have to proceed
on, because if there really was a conflict
between Ukraine and Russia, that would have lasted
72 hours, tops, with millions of people dead,
right?
Same with Israel and Persia, right?
I mean, if you can go look at
Iran, they showed about 200 miles of hardened
tunnels with thousands of ballistic and direct missiles,
guided missiles of every kind, right?
Now, ballistic just means they toss it up
in the air and it falls on a
trajectory where guided and, you know, cruise missiles
are guided and all that.
So this is all bullshit, and it's nothing
about attacking Persia.
It's about attacking everyone who is watching the
event, the same with Ukraine.
It has nothing to do with the people
of Ukraine or Russia.
It has to do with everyone who's watching
the conflict.
That's why there is an old adage.
You've seen, like, people, when they see a
gory scene, they're like, oh, I can't look
at that.
Have you ever heard that?
I can't look at that.
I can't look.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, so you don't take it in.
So my suggestion with all these conflicts, do
not take it in, just like their holidays,
their jack-off holidays.
Having holidays in December and January is like
taking a shower before you go jump into
a mud pit.
It's totally worthless, right?
So you're looking at what the medical society
is telling you the heart is a pump
and viruses and you absorb.
It's completely worthless.
There's nothing there to use.
The financial place, right, all the financials, the
lawyers that talk about, you know, like I
tell people, there's dumb.
There's dumb.
And then there's, right?
Three levels of dumb.
Attorneys, right?
Doctors.
I mean, you're talking about you are completely
surrounded in funhouse tactics here, funhouse strategy and
funhouse manipulation.
Nothing here is not even as it could
be.
You know how these are these idiots, environmentalists
and the people want to make the world
a better place.
Like, oh, one day, one day we'll make
it.
We just have to keep talking about jerk
off.
All you got to do is stop participating.
The thing falls apart and doing nothing.
Here's the thing.
Doing nothing is better than participating in any
of their stuff, especially with health.
Right.
Like if they diagnose you with 35 fictional
diseases that you think are real, if you
do absolutely nothing and do nothing to the
point where you retract, you'll get you'll be
fine.
So, yeah, the same with financial.
If you stop engaging in their tactics, the
value of the currency that you're using, the
value of the negotiable instruments will increase because
there's less of it being produced.
So actually doing nothing is actually the cure.
Not this activism.
The only thing you should have that's active
is yeast.
You know, I love it.
How they have a little thing.
Active yeast, you know, for bread making.
Saccharomyces cerevisiae.
So, yeah, there's that.
They say there's active bacteria and what?
Yogurt, too, right?
Yogurts.
Yeah.
Yogurt's different.
They call it culture.
The only culture they have here is in
their yogurt.
And not even then it's synthetic.
So I just want to put this out
because.
And here's the other thing.
If there were real protests, they wouldn't be
on TV.
How many times have you heard of in
the alternative media?
Thankfully, sometimes half a million people in Bucharest
and none of them made protesting whatever.
And there's no media coverage.
Right.
So if these protests and this thing going
on was real, it would not be on
TV.
If there was a real terror event, it
would not be on TV.
This is how bad it is right now.
Well, so today's today's no king's protest and
all that is what is completely synthetic.
You can trace it back financially back to
federal funding.
By the way, is what people don't know.
You know, the police, all the police, local
police, city police are federal.
How do you know?
When you get a traffic ticket or a
parking ticket and you go pay it, ask
for a receipt.
What does it say on the bottom?
U.S. dot gov.
U.S. dot gov is federal.
Washington, D.C. Anyway, all of the body
cams, all of the body cams are paid
for directly by federal.
Right.
Remember, there was a big I studied that
the federal wants to put body cams on
everyone.
All the body cams are federal federal property.
That's why it makes sense that they get
the tanks and everything from the Pentagon when
they're excess.
Yeah.
So the no king.
I just thought I saw like a guy
had a Tesla and it said Elon sucks
on the back.
No kings.
I don't even know what that was.
And then I saw I pulled into Lowe's
to get some furring strips.
I'm building these sunshades from cooling and all
that.
And then I saw no kings.
And then I saw this.
I saw that.
I was like, OK.
Then when I get on the computer, when
I got back, I saw no kings again.
OK, this is what they're calling the protest.
And then you just said it.
Yeah.
This is like three hours.
This is four hours of me being aware
of the no kings.
So ignore it.
Do not participate.
Just like it's a non participatory like their
holidays.
Don't participate.
Voting.
Do not participate.
Do not participate in anything political when they
do their wars, by the way.
They're not wars or conflicts where they kill
people.
Yeah.
It's about those watching, not those.
It's not Ukraine and Russia.
It's everyone who's watching that going on.
That's who it's for, because there's nothing to
be gained between Ukraine and Russia.
There's nothing to be gained what's going on
with the interchange between Israel and Iran right
now.
There's no gain.
There's nothing.
There's nothing to be gained.
So it's it's a show for those watching
it to get outraged.
That's what the lizards like.
So anyway, I'm just going to put this
out here because ignore it.
Even if they drop a freaking bomb on
your house and if you if it kills
you.
Well, then you won't have to think about
what I'm saying, what to do.
You don't have to worry about it.
Right.
So let's say someone in Persia or Israel
is listening to us in Tel Aviv and
they drop a bomb on your house and
it kills you.
What I just said doesn't matter anyway because
you're dead.
It's irrelevant.
Yeah.
But if you survive, think about think about
it.
What was the purpose of what's to be
gained?
Nothing.
And then move on.
So anyway, with that said, I just wanted
to put this out because I look, I
have so little faith in humanity's being able
to people in general, anyone being able to
string thoughts together and come up with a
rational conclusion.
So I don't mind volunteering like everyone is
entitled to my opinion.
You feel me?
OK.
Right.
Everyone's entitled to my opinion.
So that's what I just put out.
And I hope it helps.
I think it will.
Ivan, not now.
You want to be a shoulder cat?
You got to stay down.
That's a T-shirt right there, though.
Everyone is entitled to my opinion.
I think that's perfect for a T-shirt,
don't you?
Well, I don't know.
I don't know if it's perfect, but it
is so because I said so.
And that's my story.
And I'm sticking to it.
Right.
Speaking of stories and sticking to it, what
do you got?
Well, a couple of comments, you know, because
I posted that Arkham's Razor podcast, the guy
from Paranormies you just mentioned.
Yeah.
So people commented about that, that they had
noted that they had run into some synchronicity
with listening to the a few.
Actually, there's like three of them altogether that
they had noticed synchronicity during the day.
One of them said they were listening to
a Sonic from 2011.
And he you the Greek mentioned self-driving
cars happened to glance at my left at
a stoplight.
And right there was a driverless car.
Another time I was in Airbnb in Austin
listening to a Sonic from 2017.
And the moment he started talking about scorpions,
a scorpion literally appeared in the room.
And, you know, that's the thing about manifestation,
which came up in a comment or a
question, I should say here.
I'm connecting things together.
A question about positive visualization and all that.
And you've touched on it before, kind of
scoffed at it.
But at the same time, you do believe
in it.
Well, I scoff at it because ever since
a few weeks now, I've been thinking about
a slightly athletic Latin call girl.
And she hasn't showed up.
And someone said that it's not call girls
anymore.
It's apps.
You have to get an app.
Right.
But anyway, it's just a bad lascivious joke.
Whether it's true or not, it's up to
you.
But I think about a few years ago,
they used Craigslist a little bit.
But I guess they've stepped up now.
You go straight to an app because it's
stepped on.
It stepped on the independent.
They didn't want independence.
They have to do pimping.
Right.
Yeah.
That's to be controlled, made independent.
So the hoe breaks free from her pimp.
And most pimps are women, by the way,
these days.
These days, it's let's just say split down
the middle.
Having the pimps be half women, half men
is like saying they're women now.
Right.
Because it's unheard of.
So anyway, it's kind of like 75 or
50 years ago, the woman was a CEO
of a Fortune 500 company.
Right.
Just doesn't happen.
So anyway.
Yeah.
Manifestation.
There's more to it, I think, the idea.
Who was it, Jung, who talked about synchronicities
and all that?
The program that we're in.
There's nothing.
OK, so that makes it a tragedy.
You know the difference between a tragedy and
an accident.
An accident is not foreseen, but a tragedy
is foreseen and you go through it.
A tragedy, you know it's coming, actually.
They tell you at the beginning, this is
going to be a mess.
This is going to go bad.
And you wait and watch it happen.
But an accident just occurs out of nowhere.
So where an accident is completely unseen.
So that would make being here a tragedy.
Yeah.
Well, that.
OK, so being here would be a tragedy.
In other words, let me just finish the
thought, because, you know, there's synchronicities.
So in the back of your mind, once
you're aware of the concept, you're like, Oh,
if I hear of a driverless car, what
are the chances of me seeing it?
That's running in your back conscious, not in
your inner perception that's forward.
You know, you have forward thought and backward
thought, right?
Backward, you know, like people that do a
job for like an assembly line.
You don't even have to think about what
you're doing anymore.
You're an autopilot, right?
So we have these autopilots of new concepts
that run, especially when they're new.
And then we kind of forget about them.
That's a whole other.
That's a big topic to crack open.
But anyway, that was more of a comment
than a question.
How these things were just happening for this
individual, right?
Right.
And actually, like I said, it was about
three people commented with the same thing.
So somebody else talked about the biological vacuum.
And they give a story here about, you
know, giving blood and this and that.
And this is what they had to say.
I'm thinking how to make an experiment that
shows by the biological vacuum that demonstrates easily.
I thought about a can of food contaminated
with positive botulism, expanding and exploding.
The bacteria definitely are doing something to the
cell.
Well, canning, by the way, is a form
of vacuum, right?
Because it's sealed when it reaches its maximum
temperature.
And then as it cools, you have a
tremendous contraction.
And that prevents the imbalance.
There's still bacteria in there.
It's just dormant, right?
You can open some canned food and it'll
spoil once you open it, right?
Right.
And he just asked if anybody's brainstorming this.
He pointed out the thing about the can
and there's pressure.
But he was wondering if anybody had come
up with a way to sort of demonstrate
this and be able to do it with
a single cell all the way up to
maybe an animal.
And is anyone brainstorming this is finally the
question.
Oh, I'm glad because I put it out
there.
I need help in that field to, let's
say, make more of a summarial kind of
presentation and with examples.
I know the heart not being a pump
is easy to do.
One of the very, very old Frank Chester
videos, he has a silicone tube with a
two by four on a weight and he
increases the weight.
And he hits a plunger to move the
liquid.
And it hardly moves through the tube, right?
It doesn't even move five feet.
So how is it going to move through
the body, you know?
So there's various ways of doing that.
Now you have to think of the biological
vacuum as an ethereal effect.
It goes from low to high potential.
And it's going to be different.
The closest thing I can imagine that you
can demonstrate is probably the pleura, which is
the cavity around the diaphragm.
And that cavity, the pleura, is something called
pleurisy pneumonia, which is one of the worst
pneumonias you can get.
And the pleura is the area.
Oh, you think so, pleurisy, right, pleurisy.
Pleurisy, yeah.
So people think it's the diaphragm, right, projecting
the energy and fluctuations that create breathing, pulsing
sensations, and all that.
It's not.
It's the change in the pleura that does
it, right?
The diaphragm is there like a joint.
The diaphragm is like the muscle.
The pleura is like the joint.
So if you can simulate, like you remember
the iron lung people who had collapsed lungs,
they put them in a tube that they
pressurized and depressurized so their chest would expand
under a vacuum?
Right, right.
Yeah, that's an idea.
But you have to go further than that
because it's not purely mechanical.
It's energetic.
But it's not energetic because when you use
that word energy, people's minds going into plugging
things into a wall outlet or a battery
or burning something.
It's not energy per se.
You could call it a scalar condition throughout.
Scalar just means it's the same throughout.
Anyone says a scalar wave is a moron,
by the way.
A scalar wave would be so big that
it wouldn't be considered a wave.
But anyway, let's just say it requires a
little more thought for food and food for
thought.
But whoever just made my week, whoever made
that last comment about making an example because
that's what I'm looking for.
Also, I had someone, not to mention his
name, Neil, he gave me a really good
comment on the scalarator and how it has
the ability to manifest, and I said, well,
build it.
So that's great.
I'm getting a little more of what I
asked for, which is people giving input on
water and the body and other stuff.
So I really appreciate you folks, even though
it's just a few.
That's all it takes.
Well, there you go.
It doesn't take that many to get it
going.
So the last thing, of course, again, we
already covered the Middle East, obviously, but they
were asking about the idea of whether this,
because they're slugging back and forth according to
what's being shown on the news, and they're
asking about whether this is, again, the right
time to consider whether that Middle Eastern Union
that you talked about years ago is coming
in and stuff like that.
So I wondered if you wanted to just
add to that just a little bit, because
even though it's not really a war, it
is an event.
It is occurring, and it's being put on
for a reason.
And the reason I gave is for the
people watching it, not for the people being
conflicted.
I assure you there's an order of 1
,000 times more people dying in Israel and
Persia from medical care.
Really?
On an order of maybe 10,000 more,
right?
Millions of people in each one of those
countries.
Well, it wouldn't be a million, but, right?
Well, I do believe the reports that that's
happening and also that people are starving because
they've cut off everything.
Gaza, yeah.
And in Gaza, people are literally starving.
So I think they're using that as a
weapon, for sure, on people.
That's really happening.
Yes.
Well, Gaza is being run by the Egyptian
underworld.
Greek, how do you know so much about
the underworld?
Anyway, the Egyptian underworld is what runs Gaza,
and the Egyptian underworld, again, is tight, but
not as tight as the Persians are with
the Israeli underworld, right?
Okay.
Let me give people an example of what's
going on.
Okay, you have something called a – this
is a segue, but it ties in –
you have something called the DEA, right?
And that was created by Nixon, I think.
You're pretty good at that time.
Okay, you know about that.
All right, so that has nothing to do
with enforcing or limiting the use of drugs
and all that.
What that is is the cartels always had
a big influence on the politicians and all
that, and they all got together, the cartels
and the Americans, and it actually came out
– they used the army, by the way,
Delta Force, the DEA, right?
And they also go around for all kinds
of stuff, like arrest people for terrorism and
whatever.
Remember the guy – they made a movie,
Lord of War.
What was his name?
Oh, my gosh.
He was arrested by the DEA in Thailand
for selling the nukes that hit the Pentagon.
Right, right, right.
The P-700, granted, it was a nuke,
but it was – just because something's a
nuke doesn't mean it's going to go nuclear.
You need the trigger to be proper.
So the DEA is nothing more than this.
They had a big meeting, the American military
politicians and the cartels, and they said, we
need more stability.
So we have a pact here with the
way the cartels run, and when one gets
weak and starts messing up – when you
have an underground whatever – what do you
call them, mob?
What would you call them, associations, organizations, organizations?
A secret society, let's say.
Yeah, or an organization that does, let's say,
drugs and human trafficking because they also do
weapons, the cartels.
Let's stick with the DEA.
Sure.
When they start being disorganized, it becomes a
threat to all the other cartels because it
draws attention, so they have to be taken
out, decapitated.
So the DEA goes in and does it
instead of showing that another cartel is decapitating
them, right?
So the DEA is like a referee –
that's a good way to put it –
in a football game, but not the basic
American sports where you have one side versus
another side.
It's a team sport, like a cycling event,
or we have multiple teams.
And the DEA is the enforcement agency, literally,
for the cartels.
For the cartels.
So when one starts going awry, they decapitate
it so it doesn't draw attention, or if
one starts doing bad deals and dishonor, they
get decapitated.
They send in the DEA.
It's very plausible.
Then the Zetas coming in and hitting the
Medellins, right?
So they need a referee because you can
argue with the – was it Pete Roszarski
– arguing with the referee for his call?
Yeah, you can argue with the umpire, sure.
Yeah, I'm sure.
Or the umpire, yeah.
So you have the umpire referee as the
DEA.
That's all it is.
And the reason the DEA is there is
to stabilize the drug trade and stabilize the
relationships and also keep it to a certain
quality level of operation.
If you understand what I just said, you
will see it very clearly if you just
study the DEA and the cartels.
Now, another thing is like the FBI.
Before the FBI, there was another police –
I forgot.
It was like the Brinks – what was
it called?
Well, there was the Bureau of Investigation that
preceded the FBI, but then there was also
the Pinkertons.
The Pinkertons, that's right, and they got really
dirty.
And there was a lot of – always
when there's a lot of negative input on
something.
So the Jewish mafia came in and said,
our relations are so good with everybody, but
it's only going to be so good for
so long because when we get more power,
we're going to get feed – whatever, blowback.
Yeah.
So let's get – let's set up the
FBI, fund it, and get it to the
Jewish mafia so we could – when we
feel like there's going to be blowback from
the Italian mob, we go after them, and
that's all it is.
Look at the ratio of Italian mobsters versus
Jewish mobsters that are taken out by the
FBI.
Right.
The ratio is – so it's pretty obvious.
And if you study the history of it,
Department of Justice is very similar.
That's from the Bar Association.
So all of these agencies – another one
is very simple.
I think the FDA was also – there
were several FDAs, but the one that's recent,
it was, again, Nixon, right?
Well, he did the environmental – the EPA.
The EPA.
Yeah, but he didn't do the FDA.
The FDA has been around for a while.
Right.
As the drug companies, yeah, when they brought
over the Nazis or the Germans with their
drug potions.
Yeah, that's paperclip, like 1950, like later 40s,
all that.
Yeah, exactly.
Right.
Yeah, so you're looking at your – your
lizards – this is – okay.
The magic, the trick here is amazing.
You take the most vile, repugnant organization and
you have people worship it as an authority
or hold it in esteem, and this is
what's going on.
Oh, you want to get into Catholic Church,
the Vatican, talk about a vile, repugnant –
Organization.
And, you know, so this is the way
it is here on this – in this
realm.
You know, call it a planet, call it
whatever.
Anyway, yeah, thank you for whoever wanted to
set up, let's say, a demonstration of the
biological vacuum.
I think the best way to start demonstrating
it, but, you know, these academic morons can't
visualize and transfer, but would be with vegetation,
with seeds.
You know, I even got to a point
where years ago I brought up to a
medical professional that halide group elements cause sclerosis,
calcification in soft tissue glands.
We showed him, you know, that was like,
you know, bromine, fluoride, chlorine creates calcification.
Soft tissue, especially brain, brain stem, pituitary, all
that other stuff, right?
And I showed him all the studies, and
he says, well, that's not human, that's all
mammal testing, right?
They always have a reason, they're always going
to deflect.
Of course.
So I think the best place to visualize
and go is to start with seeds and
vegetation, and when you talk about going with
a single cell, you're going to have to
remove that cell.
Unless you go with protozoa, like amoeba, paramecium,
that type of stuff.
Fungus, I would say, yeast I would stay
away from, because yeast is neither mammal nor
plant.
Nobody knows what yeast is.
I mean, it's its own life form, right?
Its own category.
Fungus.
So, among us.
But start with the seeds and the vegetation,
and if you're going to move to cells
like blood and other tissue like that, remember,
it's dead.
Just like in the Chitango, someone posted, or
the same individual posted the thyroid and how
it looks like a raspberry.
Remember, all of the anatomy that they're showing
you is from cadavers.
So the living being, it doesn't quite look
like that.
It doesn't, it's a little different.
And I wonder how much the radiation, and
you know, when they do MRIs and CAT
scans and all that, the body knows it's
being, you know, it changes again.
But if you scrutinize the way organs and
things look, if you can, with other forms
of imaging other than the anatomy, you'll notice
that everything is a little tighter, smaller, more
upright.
Because you're looking at cadavers, right?
Looking at a dead fish is not the
same as going to the aquarium, right?
Well, even observing the blood outside of the
body, once it's outside of the body, it's
no longer participating in the process, so therefore
it's not going to be the same.
It has luminosity when it's in the body.
And there's more and more people doing live
blood testing.
The shameful part there is they don't know
what they're looking at.
But that's fine.
I don't think I have enough energy, life,
or whatever in me to pursue and advance
these fields.
But others probably do.
But even if you do have energy, life,
or whatever, and funds or whatever to pursue
these things, you don't have that much time.
These things take a long time.
But I think speaking on it and pursuing
it is still noteworthy, especially with trauma.
The main thing is trauma, unless you're traumatizing
yourself all the time, eating junk food and
being around stupid people.
So, yeah, what else you got?
No, that covers just about everything that I
got.
Oh, all right.
So we'll uncover some more the next time.