The Sonic 10th Event here on Oteli and the Greek Rated Y and welcome to you no matter
who you are, where you are, of course you are someone who did subscribe to this and
I always like to tell people that I appreciate them doing that.
So thanks for being along with us on this very interesting ride and the latest incarnation
of something that we had done before.
So, Greig, how are you doing tonight?
I am.
I'm doing.
I just wanted to mention the episode nine, or Sonic Nine, gave a lot of anecdotes there.
I can't get this out of my mind, is what large women, women with large feet are cruel, size
nine or bigger.
I didn't want anyone to really see that that way.
It was an anecdote, right?
Is that the thing that got a lot of feedback for you this time?
Because I find that interesting, considering all that was covered in nine.
No, no feedback other than I said it was in the mind, you know?
Oh, okay.
So this is the part-
Something around in the mind of the Greek.
I see.
Not in terms of the minds of whoever's listening.
Well, I was a little surprised by it because I always thought that and never heard anybody
else say it.
So-
Yeah, I'll tell you something that harkens back.
There was a mom back in the 70s on the same street that we lived in.
They were Hungarian and she looked like a witch.
Basically the long nose and the high cheekbones and-
Dark hair also?
Kind of dark, long, straight hair?
Well, actually blonde, blondish hair, but she put on a hat.
She had the profile of the classic witch and on Halloween, she would dress up like a witch
to make fun of her own visage, visage, right?
And she looked just like the witch from The Wizard of Oz, you know, the Wicked Witch of
the West.
Oh, no kidding.
Yeah.
And with no makeup.
So what do you say about that?
I mean, she was a wonderful woman.
Well, she wasn't green though, right?
She wasn't green in appearance because I know in the colorized version, they made her green.
Okay, so-
In other words, yeah, she wasn't green, no.
So yeah, we got into- I didn't really feel like we laid down enough where people could
listen to that and say, this is how a relationship should be.
But basically, without going over the subject, we put down some stuff that you're not going
to hear anywhere else, number one.
Number two, just like with anything, imagine that you already have it and you're already
in it, act accordingly.
Think about that for a minute.
Well, it goes with anything.
Like someone I knew who wanted a motorcycle and couldn't afford it, couldn't find one
that was what he could afford or whatever, I said, act like you already have one.
Because if you just got one today, you're going to go out and get wax, you're going
to go out and get chain oil or lube, you're going to go out and get this and that, you're
going to go out and get a helmet, you're going to get gloves, hopefully some leathers, right?
So if you fall, you know?
I said, go get all those things first, because you're going to get the bike and you're going
to find your deficient, you know, the motorcycle, of all these other things, get all the things
that you would need or want to have if you did have the motorcycle, right?
And guess what?
Within like a week of doing that, he found the bike of his dreams, right?
And it helps when I'm the one that gave him the motorcycle, though, right?
I should have left that part out, right?
I don't think that changes the story much.
Well, no, but did you have that in mind when you told him to go get the stuff and be ready
for it?
Or did you not?
Because your intention is part of the question, too.
No, I noticed that I was getting, I was in 40, late 40s, I was like, the eyesight's not
razor sharp, and I need razor sharp vision on this thing, you know?
No, I was thinking of just keeping it as a possession.
Okay.
You know?
I was riding less and less, and yeah, I kind of mentored this person and whatever, and
they were looking, and they couldn't find anything, and yeah, it was a classic motorcycle,
a very old classic one.
Yeah, yeah, it just turned out that way, but when, all right, let's just say it this way
in truthfulness.
When the person had accomplished all the things that are required or needed or want when you
do have a motorcycle, when I knew that they had that, I got this overwhelming feeling
to sell it to them, you know?
Let's just say.
And if you asked me a month before, I said, no, I'm going to keep this bike as part of
a, it's an antique, it's in perfect condition, you know?
Okay.
So anyway, one of those stories, and the same thing with relationships, people want to eat
Well, I'm just trying to do a, the reason why I'm asking questions, I'm trying to do
a chicken or egg thing here, right?
What came first?
Did your intention to give it to them or to sell it to them or whatever, did that become,
you know, was that the thing you had in mind?
Because I think that would change things a bit, wouldn't it?
Well, in this universe, the chicken comes first, by the way, right?
Fair enough.
I mean, you have to have a chicken capable of laying an egg to lay an egg.
Because here, the chicken and the egg, I go over this so many times, and it's interesting
to hear it.
Okay, this is one of the fundamentals of Greek-speak, right?
When you hear about something, it's best to go over things that you're used to.
But as if you're hearing it for the first time, you look at your source, and if your
source doesn't provide you with the history of that thing or a definition of that thing
or the function of that thing, you're on your own, you've got to do it yourself, right?
So, just like if someone uses a word you've never heard, you typically ask them what
that means.
Now, isn't it weird when they don't know, but they're using it, right?
Think about it.
Yeah, it is.
Someone uses a word, they don't know what it means, right?
And they can't provide a definition, I mean, that's, wow.
Well, this is the world you live in.
Well, let's just go back to chicken and egg.
Fundamentally, the chicken is the being, and the egg is simply its ability, it's the mechanism
and the function of it reproducing itself.
So it's still about the chicken.
So you can look at it two ways.
You can look at it as the chicken being the variable, and then 2x, you know, multiply the
variable into another thing, and I say variable because almost all things multiply.
So the chicken and the egg thing, if you break it down using Greek-speak logic and reason,
is the chicken is far more important than the egg, but without the egg, there's no more
chickens after the chicken reaches its, right, duration.
So the egg part is just the reproduction part.
It's not the creation part, how it came into being.
That's something different.
Fair enough.
I mean, and I had a couple of things in mind I was going to ask you about regarding the
container and what the container represents, because a lot of people will now go to the
idea that the container is ostensibly meaningless, and I object to that when I hear it, because
I don't believe it is meaningless at all.
And, you know, there are things that are retained in a container.
If you just think about a container that you commonly store food in, well, you know, you
keep food in it.
It retains certain aspects of the food sometimes, right, until it has been thoroughly cleaned
and repurposed.
So, you know, I wanted to talk about that maybe with the body a bit, but I think we
should finish with the relationship aspect.
I'm done with the relationship talk, or speaking on, but the container, okay, here, I'm going
to throw this in for a future thing, an NPC, you know, these husks of humans, they're like,
they call them soulless, but if they're alive, you know, the spiritless, low-level spirits.
Low-level spirits.
Yeah, that's when the being takes the shape of the container.
When the mind takes the shape of the container, right, that's one way to look at an NPC.
You know, when you pour, like liquids take the shape of their containers, right?
Right.
So when you pour this low-level spirit out into a body, it takes the shape of its container,
or some attributes of the shape.
That's why when you, when people don't like someone, what do they call them?
Hey, that guy's a what?
He's a dick.
Yeah.
Or that guy's an asshole.
Right?
Or whatever.
You ever notice that?
It's just for, how can you be a dick and how can you be an asshole?
You're, it's, you see, because they're taking that, you see what I mean?
Just one attribute.
So yeah, it's very interesting.
The container in this case is the five, we're the five-pointed, the star configuration, right?
Which is the most common, believe it or not, for this type of setup, this type of mind.
Well, it's five points, but six compartments, as we've discussed a long time ago.
The six compartments are pretty easy to recognize.
If you take a look at the general, typical physical form, right?
You have the head, you have the torso, you have the arms, two of them, and two legs.
There's your five points and your six containers, or your six compartments, I should say again,
in the one container.
So that's the representation, right?
Yeah.
And the container needs input, physical input, air, food, and water, and we're going to be
speaking on food, or I keep threatening to do these solos, which I get myself to sit
down long enough.
We might end up doing one like this, and then I might fill it in, because it gets really
intense.
But I wanted to just throw something in about the container.
And I've been doing some practicing and, let's say, experimentation.
You hear about people with health, quote-unquote, health problems, right?
All the time.
All kinds.
And we're talking about real ones, like real manifestations.
Not someone says, I went to the doctor and he says I got diabetes or I got high blood
pressure.
That's absurd, you know?
Yes, Ivan, I'm recording with Uncle Chuck right now.
The feline pipes up for a moment, but that's all right.
We might hear from one of my canines if it so happens to strike them to speak up, too.
Yeah, okay.
He's a baby panther, actually.
If he gets big enough, I'm going to have to find a zoo for him.
So what I wanted to suggest is real situations.
I kind of touched on the last time briefly what cancer is.
That's when food wants to revert back to its natural state as whatever it was in the body.
It's not what people are...
We kind of talked about it.
And then these odd manifestations take place.
But what I wanted to say about food is, and with illness, is that if you change the diet
and turn into, let's say, a whole food diet, in other words, when you buy rice, you buy
it in bulk.
Don't buy it in a plastic bag or a box, and I think I've discussed why in the past.
We'll get into it again.
And organic stuff, let's say.
By the way, you've heard me say I'm against organic.
It's existence of classification.
The reason why is what kind of society would allow organic food, which means no toxin added,
and then right next to it, another market or in the same market, food that is loaded
with toxins.
What kind of people would allow that?
In other words, there should be no qualification.
The non-organic food should have never been allowed, and it's allowed.
This goes into your politics.
This goes into everything else.
Well, that's not the case everywhere, you know.
You know, there are places where, ostensibly or allegedly, they don't allow the GMOed food,
right?
Supposedly.
I'm not saying that it's GMOed.
Well, it's beyond GMO.
When you add synthetic nitrogen-based fertilizers to food, it's like giving someone a dose of
heroin or cocaine either way.
You're drugging the plants.
It's not fertilizer.
You see what I mean?
There's a difference to it, right?
Well, drugs and poison are an interesting thing anyway.
I mean, one of the most common, maybe not so popular nowadays or trendy nowadays, but you
and I both, well, you do smoke sometimes still.
I smoke also, and they often say, well, you're addicted to the nicotine.
Nicotine's actually a fairly effective pesticide.
Well, when it's separated, when you separate something enough, the more it wants to go
back into its natural state.
But let me just, on the point that I brought up today about food and all this stuff and
real illness, let's say, people who aren't feeling well, you know, organ depletion, whatever,
whatever, skin problems, headaches, gout, all these things that have been around.
If you want to know what real diseases and real illnesses are, go before 1890s.
1890, 1930, they invented all these other things, right?
So what I'm trying to say here is when you go to, let's say, here's a simple way to classify
it, and every year there's less and less on the internet about it, but macrobiotic diet,
which is whole food and eating seasonally, it's kind of a turnoff to a lot of people
because it was promoted by Japanese and there's a lot of Japanese style in there, and some
people don't like that, but they also, if you study the history of it, just eat the
way people that, you know, don't get sick eat, basically, which is local.
So what I'm trying to say here, let's say you went to a macrobiotic diet or a whole
food diet, understanding the energies of the food, right?
What's uplifting, what's down, what feeds each organ.
If you are ill, you will notice a very speedy recovery if it's something that your body
can recover from, bounce back quickly, depending on your rate of recovery.
You know, you ever notice how athletes kind of retire after 40 or after 30?
They actually have more experience, which makes them a better athlete, but physically
they don't recover as fast, and they can't compete with the younger guys who recover
faster.
You see, the younger guys have less experience and less technique.
The older guys have more experience and more technique and are actually better at the sport
as any sport goes, but they just can't recover.
See, that's what I mean by recovery.
Right.
I mean, tracking boxing, actually, we saw a phenomenon about 20, 30 years ago where
a lot of older guys got back into the game, and you could see exactly what you're talking
about if you followed it very closely.
Larry Holmes, George Foreman in the heavyweight divisions especially, but Sugar Ray Leonard.
I don't know how much into boxing you are, but I appreciate boxing.
Yeah, they take a hit and they swerve for like five seconds instead of one second, you
know?
Right.
Which is an hour in boxing time.
Five seconds is like an hour by the watch when you're not boxing.
But overall, you saw these guys fighting much more intelligently.
You saw them doing better things in their training than they had done at a younger age
and all of that.
But the problem for them becomes how quick can they recover?
Because after a boxing match, you know, you do a lot of training in order to go in there
for that.
Say, you know, you got three minutes divided by 12, so you're talking 36 minutes realistically
of action with a minute in between each round.
That doesn't sound like much, but that is a hell of a lot of training you have to do
to prepare for that.
And they much more intelligently do it and they're much better prepared as older athletes.
However, recovery time after the fight, because obviously you're going to take some damage
getting punched in the face a hundred times, you know, not just the face, it's other parts
of the body too.
But that recovery time is the thing that would finally sideline them because they would
be like, look, it takes me too long to come back around and continue to fight, unlike
when I was much younger.
And also when they exert themselves the cardiovascular, you know, they can't recover from that, not
only taking the hit and running around.
But my point here is if you go to a whole food type diet, natural food, no pesticides,
no packaging, the reason why you don't want food in packaging is because you look at the
ingredients list, yeah, that's the ingredients that is placed in the package after the package
is prepared.
And what they do to prepare the packages, which is not in the ingredient list because
it's not in the food, is there the packaging is sprayed with fungicide and bactericide.
And because it's not added to the food directly, it doesn't have to be FDA approved, yada,
yada, yada. Right.
But it's the food is sitting in it for how long?
Most packaged food could be at least a month, two months, three months.
Right. Some of them say, you know, good for a year.
Yeah. Depending on it might be sitting in there for a whole year.
And, of course, we've read stories about how they spray meat with viruses in order to
kill other things.
They say ammonia.
But it's not. Yeah, there's no.
Yeah. That's like saying Al-Qaeda or.
Yeah, well, you know, in the common terms, I'm just talking about what happens is they
spray the package and the product, but it's not part of the ingredients list.
It is in the container, though.
Sure. There isn't anything that's dead and waste they can call a virus.
But, you know, originally the virus was the guy who came up with it was this degenerate.
He didn't know what to write his thesis on.
So he went into the hospital dumpster, started pulling old bandages out and looking at
them under a microscope.
This is about 80, 90 years ago.
Anyway, so my point is, if you can go into a natural diet, so to speak, but it has to
be balanced according to your where you live in the season, you can recover from most
ailments within a week or be at the point where, let's say you tried regular medical
procedures and pills and all the therapies and all these things, and it went on for
months and months and months or even a year or two or three.
You switch over to a really good diet and in one week you have more improvement than
you had, let's say, with all the other treatments.
Right. And within a month, it's almost full recovery.
And as your own personal recovery, meaning with age and other things, constitution, I
mean, there are many young people now that have old people diseases.
Right. You've heard of that.
So if you take like an average white Midwestern American, their body, their heart at
18 or 19 years old would be what a 40 or 50 year old would be living in a much better
let's say environment where they have access to better food, you see.
So what I'm trying to say is I'm a proponent for good food, healthful food.
Food is not healthy. You're healthy if you eat healthful food.
And the recovery rate, I'm just astonished at how fast one can recover.
And it takes planning and it takes knowledge.
And usually, unfortunately, you're going to need someone who has experience with how to
put together, quote unquote, a diet for your condition unless you learn it and learn how
to do it yourself if you're a quick learner.
But the reason I brought this up is because of recent experiments and observations, how
rapid how rapid the body changes, again, based on how old you are and your condition.
So, in other words, a typical American in their 20s will have the typical recovery rate
of a 40 or 50 year old living in another part of the world.
You see, so and I keep stressing American because we have the worst food on the planet,
bar none here, you know.
So in terms of quality, I always find that remarkable, by the way, because quite often you
hear from people, look, we have the cleanest food, the cleanest water, this and that.
And I find it laughable because it's not it's poisoned.
Yeah, it's precisely the opposite of that.
We're also the most medicated people on the planet in the American, you know,
geographical region.
Thankfully, I'm not part of that.
We don't know.
But listen, neither am I.
But I'm just saying that.
Yeah, it's it's it's not.
Yes, it's the Americans are going through one of the worst cursed earth periods, you know,
from the 1700s.
But that's another discussion when we get into the gods, which might be today.
But I just wanted to throw that in there, because when we do something on food, a sonic
on food, I want people to keep in the back of their mind.
It's not just preference or it's it's actually very, very important.
What's interesting is when you do an experiment with someone who has, let's say, an
ailment for two or three years and within a week or 10 days, it's 90 percent recovery.
Right. What does that tell just by doing the food in the water thing?
Right. Well, what does that tell you in bright neon that the reason why they were sick is
because of whether what they were eating in the first place is not amazing.
Yeah. So it doesn't we're talking about looking at a rate of about 50 to 75 percent of
the people just having a changing their diet to a really high quality food for two weeks
to a month. Let's say we'll recover 50 to 75 percent of the people.
I mean, think that I've ever done this with.
So it's quite amazing and it's kind of a shocker and it makes you want to sit down and
cry, you know, and how sad the food situation is.
But I just want to throw that in there before we got into whatever we're going to get
into tonight. Right. Well, even worse than that, and I wonder if you would agree with me,
is that quite often when I find somebody who asks me what they could do to improve their
situation, often one of the first and most primary concerns is actually their water
intake. And so even before they start to eat, even before food, water is a big problem.
They're not you know, they're not consuming enough or they're not taking in enough, I
should say. Well, I would have to I'd have to say that you should only drink when you're
thirsty or feeling like you should you need water to drink.
You don't have to necessarily be the feeling of of being said in Latin or Spanish.
Tengo sed, I'm thirsty or, you know, I'm thirsty when I like some water.
You shouldn't have to get to that point.
But that's a good point to drink water.
And you four ounces of water is enough.
Remember, the water stimulates the liver.
Remember those blood sugar test strips?
All they do is test your hydration level, not your blood sugar.
You could look this up, by the way.
There'll be no website that'll tell you sugar diabetes testing is a scam.
It really tests hydration.
But if you look at all the problems with testing strips, every website, everything I did
this recently, I was surprised to see it's still true from the 80s.
It says that you can't do it if you're thirsty and you can't do it if you just drank
water because it won't work.
Well, guess what? It has nothing to do with blood sugar anyway, because there is no such
thing as blood sugar, by the way.
It's blood quality. But what I want to say with water, it's we're going to get into water
again. Also, you don't you don't need much and you don't need to have it often because
the best water is the water that's inside the cell of the food that you eat.
And I would rather people drink less overall water, but more of the higher quality
water. And you'll do better that way, if that makes any sense.
Oh, it makes plenty of sense.
But the counter and I don't mean to disagree with you exactly, but the problem that I
find often with somebody who's not feeling well is that they're consuming food, which is
not giving them hydration.
So, yeah, Dr.
Dr. Batman, they call it for short.
Batman, not as in B.A.T., but B.A.D., Batman.
Dr. Batmangala, You're Not Sick, You're Thirsty.
Have you heard of that book? Or anyway, someone.
Yeah. He was a prisoner in Iran and he was healing people or helping people cure their
illnesses by just having them drink water.
And he helped so many people that when his prison sentence was over, he decided to stay
another year. I didn't hear I heard that story.
I don't I never read that book.
But a while back, yeah, he I was turned on him by Trevor James Constable, who we were
going to meet. And he died, I guess he was getting too popular, meaning Batmangala was.
Yeah, there's many issues on it.
But remember, years ago in the 60s and 70s, I would go to the hose and drink water before
it was fluoridated and brominated and chlorinated.
And it was good. Like New York City tap water was great.
Yeah, it was. Yeah.
Yeah. Based on, you know, all the rumors and myths about how good the pizza is and the
bagels. Right. Because of the water.
So, yeah, it's very tricky.
And by the way, even here at home, I'm constantly being reminded, like when we see
things happening with food or, quote unquote, the news or this or that, I'm always
reminded that, you know, you talked about this a few years ago.
Exactly. This, you know, and so, you know.
Nothing to be surprised about, but the water quality is even on the natural side is
getting worse and worse.
Everything is just telling humans that you've had so many chances to you screwed up.
It's OK. Make it better.
Do do what you do.
Don't do don't keep doing what you're doing.
Right. But they keep doing what they're doing.
So. So then eventually your natural environment is going to fight against you.
But I just want to throw that in there because it's been something resonating in my
head for a while. Well, it's like, how can how can it be so simple that a week's to a
month worth of eating right or eating well can reverse so many things?
It's it's just goes back to the same thing.
It sounds cliche that the food is making you sick, let's say, you know.
Absolutely. Well, there is an interesting thing there.
Did you happen to pick up anything from the chat this week that you wanted to address?
Yes, some things, general stuff.
There's someone through a whole bunch of questions in there that I think we've we can
address, not necessarily now, but there's more going on in there.
The people that are in the chat are generally, you know, when I see who's in there,
they generally ask the similar questions.
So it would be, you know, if anyone go to the O.N.G.
chat, the Unculting of Humanity, Chitango, it's usually about weather, well, time
keeping the gods and growing things, which is important, which we are in a season, by
the way, here on the this part of the world where the growing season has started and
and the other part of the world that's upside down, they're going into the winter.
And just because winter is coming, it doesn't mean you can't grow anything.
There's something called winter rye.
I'm not saying you should grow winter rye, but there are crops that are winter crops.
They're just very slow.
And there are plants that are, what do they call it, frost hardy.
Right. When you have a freeze, they don't they don't die back like Swiss chard and
things like that. So it's an all year round affair.
But one thing that I did mention in the chat, there was someone that was asking a whole
slew of questions regarding forms of almanacs, timekeeping for planting, astronomical,
local astrological stuff.
And that's an example of showing all the various varieties of systems out there.
Right. I don't know if you looked in the chat, but there was about two or three
different calendrical systems for planting brought up.
And they were, I think, more they were more like someone's website, I think.
And some of them were recent people that developed things in the 20s and 19th century
or the 20s and 30s.
And if you study this, you'll see with the age of media, let's say printing got cheap
in the 1800s and 1900s and YouTube and all this, you'll see every year there's more and
more systems coming up.
What I suggested in there, instead of looking at this calendrical system or that, what I
suggest is I looked at you have seven years of yin and seven years of yang, seven years
of expansive and seven years of contractive.
Right. So you'll have seven years where the summers seem milder, but longer and the
winters are milder and shorter than the contractive cycle.
You'll have the summer seems short and hot and the winter seems longer and colder.
Right. And a seven year expansive cycle, seeds will germinate very readily.
You know, you'll plant something and you'll have a plant that seems like you'll turn
around, walk back inside, come out and the plant's a foot tall already.
It's like, what the hell is that?
Right. And they'll bear a lot of fruit and the fruit will ripen quickly.
And sometimes you'll get two crops.
That's an expansive year.
We're in a contractive year.
Germination is really slow or low, lower germination.
You plant something you're used to, you know, coming above ground in a week or so.
It's been like three weeks and it's barely up.
Right. Right. And the fruit you'll have.
Let's say when the plant does grow like a tomato, cucumber or whatever, it's a beautiful
plant. But there's no tomatoes.
It's like, where are the tomatoes?
Like huge plants, like a tree tomato.
And it's got one tomato where.
So that's the contractive year.
So I've been observing this and using 1998 as reference and going forward from there.
So around 2018, 2019 went into a different cycle.
Right. And you be the judge of its expanse over contractive based on what I said.
And there was someone that did agree with this observation.
So we'll see how this year works out being in an expansive cycle.
So. Well, it's interesting because, of course, you have to pay very close attention to
where you are as you I mean, you give a very general sort of like, OK, so there's
Northern Hemisphere and sort of Southern Hemisphere ideas and cycles.
But there's a bit of a difference, say, where I am geographically than a couple of
states further north than me, even though it's considered kind of a similar region.
I'm in a slightly different temperate region.
So cross cross latitude.
We're about the same, though.
I'm 32 latitude and you're probably 33 or you might be on the same latitude as me.
It's just that it's different because of where the ether comes in.
The southwest is a desert because it was probably underwater about 4000 years ago.
And that desert energy is still there, you know, that nothing grows energy and the
East Coast would be would have been much higher.
That's why when you look at Google Earth, for example, the coast of Florida or the
East Coast of the US, if you look at the shaded areas and how deep the water is, it
seems the plateau goes beyond the coast about 30 to 100 miles and then it drops, you
see. So, yeah, I'd say that it's cross latitude.
But again, it has to be done within your region.
You can have drastic differences cross latitude.
Look at when you say Sahara Desert, let's say.
Right. Look at the center of the Sahara Desert and the general latitude and go across
the planet. It's not the same.
It gets tropical in some other places.
Right. All right. Like like where I am is considered like a subtropical as opposed to a
tropical because just above me is that tropical.
It doesn't work in exactly.
It doesn't work exactly along the straight lines of latitude is all I'm trying to say.
So you've got to be observant about that.
50 mile radius is a good guess, is a good.
So let's say you're trekking across the earth and you want to settle somewhere.
Wherever, whatever direction you came from, just recall the last 50 miles, what it was
like and where you land is probably going to be like that.
So the last 50 miles you trekked was an introduction to what it's going to be like.
You know, you say 50 mile radius is usually usually fair.
I'd say less than that if the elevation changes drastically.
So that's a general way to look at it.
So I would say that anything you look at is a guideline.
You're going to have to everything needs except for certain math.
You know, if I say two plus two, you know, and you say two plus two, regardless of where
you are, it's going to it's going to we should end up with the same result.
Right. So but that's math.
That's that's an abstract.
So anything that you get is going to need some fine tuning, even if you get into biblical
stuff. Right. You know, a lot of people like, yeah, I'm going to do this.
But if you study like biblical law, very little applies to you because most of the
laws in there and things are regarding things that you're not and things that don't
exist. See, so you have to learn how to narrow things down and see what applies best.
Yep. So, you know, so.
All right. So we've addressed the chat.
We've addressed the last sonic a bit.
Yeah. You know, you were ruminating on that.
A bunch, I guess, you know, we didn't get a lot of feedback about relationships.
I kind of expected more to come my way about it, but we didn't see a lot, I guess.
Well, that's like a relationship.
Don't expect more anyway.
Here we go. But, you know, but see, I'm still stuck on the container.
And I'll tell you why, unless you have some other things you want to get.
No, no, please. Please go ahead.
Yep. Because I was thinking about this, you know, the different organs and how they're
misunderstood. Right.
And, you know, the idea about the liver in the kidneys, they're not separate things.
They're part of the same system and all that.
Well, there was an interesting thing that just kind of came across like accidentally to me
when I was just letting a video thing run for a minute.
Right. And I was looking at organ transplants and stuff like that.
And there were people claiming that they had changed after they had an organ transplant.
And that it seemed as though the organ might have had a memory of its own.
And that might sound like a crazy idea to some people.
But to my mind, the physical container, again, does retain some aspects of what's put
into it. Now, like I said, breaking it down to the container, you might put food in.
Right. Which we did address for a moment.
But there is a way that some of those things that are put inside of the container leave
behind traces of themselves just in general.
Right. Yeah. Again, it is a very simple.
By the way, there's a very simple answer to why.
Yeah. Like someone gets a heart transplant who loves mustard.
And if they survive the heart transplant and recover, now they hate mustard.
Yeah. Then they find the family member who they got the deceased, let's say.
Got their dead, you know, their dead, dead dad's heart.
Right. Yeah. Dad hated mustard.
Right. You see. So now this person hates.
Very simple. Very, very simple.
Let me ask you a general question.
Sure. You said organ transplant.
Okay. What have you? You can take your pick.
You've got eyes, heart, liver, kidneys, on and on and on.
All right. Are those organs either on ice usually, right, to a degree?
They're not frozen, but they're cold.
Thirty nine. You shouldn't go below thirty nine.
And they don't usually.
Let me ask you, are those organs dehydrated?
You had water or are they hydrated?
Are they wet?
Well, I believe they stay wet at all times.
Yeah, exactly. Right.
Okay. So that water is from the previous body and that water's memory.
It's the memory of the water.
Right. So believe it or not, there was a
organization back in the early 2000s that wanted to use water instead of a hard
drive. And there was a bunch of stuff that made it to the Internet.
Then it was all removed.
And one of the articles was stating that actually they got inspired that water
could be used to, in other words, tap direct memory just because of organ
transplants. The in other words, the receiver of the new organ
felt that had the tendencies of the previous owner.
Yeah. Well, that's what was being discussed in this, you know, very basic sort
of video. I just want to give you a quick anecdote about it and maybe it'll give
you more things to expand on, because it wasn't just the things that you might say,
okay, there might be a chemical aspect to this where like you brought up the
mustard. All right. But some of the examples they were bringing up were things
like all of a sudden somebody had an affinity for classical music that they
never had before.
And they had received I forget what the organ was, but a variety of organs were
discussed here. Right. There was a heart. There was there was a liver trance, you
know, transfer.
There was I think there was some other there were a few organs.
Let's just say there were a few different organs that were transplanted and they
had issues where they suddenly had mental affinities for things.
They had physical desires for things, but they certainly had new interests.
There was a young girl who ended up with like, I think it was the heart might have
been the heart. Let's just go with heart heart of a 40 year old guy who was sort of
a handyman. And all of a sudden when she recovered and she felt much better, she
started wanting to work with her hands and found herself doing some of the same
activities. And then she did what you said, which was track down, you know, the
donor and learned about them a bit and found that they were somebody was involved
in that activity often.
And this all comes down to just the the memory in the liquid, you think, here or.
Yeah. And also the predominant.
In other words, the the person's ethereal, let's say, the spiritual state of the
individual, what level?
Let's say if you were to classify something from one to ten, right, ten being the
highest, one being the lowest.
If you were to classify the intensity of the spirit and its ability to imprint in
the water and the cells and in the organ, the characteristics of that individual
one, if you were to, let's say, let's take the the the girl that got the or the
young lady that got the heart from the four year old.
OK, if if she's if she finds the that one organ, even though the heart is has brain
tissue in it, by the way, to dominate her whole character, that means that the
person that she got that from had a higher order spirit.
In other words, more dominating, you see, what I mean that I mean that, take it
simply. You know, there are people that are dominant individuals.
Right. Like what do they call me?
Alpha, alpha males, alpha, whatever.
Right. Well, a lot of times and some people might think of it as influential.
Right. When somebody comes into a room and the entire attitude of the room changes
because they instantly sort of impart their presence in that room.
And therefore, you know, like the old life of the party thing, right?
Oh, this guy shows up and all of a sudden the party's fun because this person.
Yeah. Or they're more forceful.
Maybe somebody shows up and all of a sudden everybody becomes much more organized.
They're much more regimented, you know, when doing a group activity, whatever this
guy. The one that would be like eight, nine, ten.
And then the one, two, three low level ones would be that you're sitting in a room and
no one even knows you're there.
OK. Right.
Right. Not you.
But, you know, I mean, typically I've seen that happen.
Actually, once we were taking a headcount for a pizza and there were five of us there,
but we did only a four headcount, even though the other person was sitting right there.
Is that amazing? I mean, that's a very low, let's say, functioning, not not in
non-intelligent or NPC, per se, but most likely NPC would be down there also.
Very passive individual.
So this let's just say it this way.
From a scientific perspective, if you were to see the certain dominant traits from the
donor to the donee is not in every case.
It's in many cases.
And we don't know if it's 50-50 or 10 percent or what.
But I would suggest that the dominant persona or personality, it carries through.
So one organ, in other words, transplanted from a dominant individual to a more
passive one is enough to, let's say, what do you call it?
Override some of the person's, let's say, previous desires.
You see, it's very simple.
It's the same thing with like, let's say, in a computer you have corruptible memory
that could be erased and an uncorruptible memory that's in a chip, let's say, you
know. Yeah, it's just dominance and there's many variations to it.
But I would say that the mind is the overall tool.
And I just want to interject since you're, let's say, I don't want to say it this way,
but anything else on the organs?
The point that you wanted to bring up, are you are you OK with that or will you segue?
Yeah, it's OK. I just I had one other thought about it, which was that, you know, in
general, I think about there is what is imprinted based on the actions, the activity
and all of that. But also, I think we begin with a set of things quite often and some
people refer to it as genetic memory or whatever.
Things are passed along.
And there has been recent scientific studies about epigenetic reactions and how
something can be passed from generation to generation, right, based on things that are
imprinted in. And obviously, the genetic result is something that you would see.
You'd have to ask the same question.
Is the sperm and the ovum wet?
Right, right, of course.
OK, so it's a little bit of water.
OK, is enough.
No, fair enough, but I mean, I think it's an interesting thought.
It's not DNA or chromosomes like they tell you.
OK, well, but that was the thing I was trying to define.
So it's really just about this this passing on and literal sharing of the fluid which
retains characteristics and stuff like that, which I always find it an interesting point
that if you think about it very carefully, you know, a part of you was in your
grandmother's body. Right.
Because at some point the the ovum, right, which was a woman is born with all of them
scientifically, supposedly.
Right. They're born with all they're going to have throughout their life.
That's already in their body.
So it's that's why that's why if you cut open the goose, you get all the eggs.
Right. Anyway, bad joke.
Well, but the thing is that if you think about it, your mother in your grandmother's
body, she ends up developing all of her eggs before she's born.
And that egg at some point becomes you.
Right. Because it's half of the equation when it comes together.
So in a in a very serious way, you're connected to your grandmother at one point, a
part of you physically was inside of your grandmother's body.
The same water, the same water, which is still blood.
But it's it's not just because there are oils in there, lipids and things like that.
But it's all water in terms of it's not just oversimplifying it.
It's water. It's not DNA.
See, DNA and these other things are just you didn't bring that up.
But this is what goes to people's minds.
Right. They're just antennas.
Just like if you take the antenna off of the radio, do you expect to see a little jazz
band in the antenna? No, nothing.
You won't even see it inside.
It's in the water. So what happens when the when the organ, the or the egg or the
sperm, it has a certain shape because that's how it interacts with the ether.
And based on that shape and its interaction with the ether, it picks up the quote
unquote frequency.
It's more of a vibration than a frequency.
And there's a big difference between vibration and frequency.
And one is anyway, that's another discussion.
But what I'm trying to say is that when the water is in the organ, like you mentioned,
the heart or the kidney or the or in the egg or the ovum, right, that specific shape
and the amount and what the water is being exposed to being in that container, in
other words, secondary container is very, very powerful.
So let's take it from another point of view.
There's some myths or mythology.
I don't want to Harkin says a church where they have holy water in a little bottle.
Right. But depending on what intent is in there, they actually put curses in it, believe
it or not. But anyway, whatever a tiny amount of water you can, quote unquote, make
sacred or very special with some intense preparation, you can take that little vial or
what have you that fits in your pocket and go to a large body of water and just put a
few drops and that will dominate and take and the large body now will take on the
characteristics of the few drops that you put in there.
But the water has to be prepared to do that.
And believe it or not, when you have the that's why I keep asking, was there water?
Are they wet? Right, right, right.
When you have the water in the cells and when all the cells come together to form that
shape of whatever part of the body it is that is constantly being worked on from an
ether point of view and from the you know, how the system works to make the water in
there really do what you think the egg or the heart or the liver or whatever is doing.
OK, it's a it's a new way to think about it, you know, for me, so I'm finding this
interesting and processing it.
So, well, here's an interesting way to do, you know, one thing I've been putting in the
chat, it's induction.
We've got to really get this project off the ground, not we.
And that's just a small voice.
I'm realistic about it, meaning I'm not hopeful.
But once the concept of induction, right, no material transfer, but you have material on
one side, a barrier and then material crossing through that, not going through that
barrier, but appearing on the other side of that barrier, like Star Trek.
Right. Beam me up.
Right. This is how all living things are working.
Plants, animals, even the weather works that way.
Right. There's no there's no water in the rain cloud.
If there was, it would just fall to the ground like fog.
Right. See, the water is produced in situ by induction, biological.
Right. So once this is understood and a series of experiments are shown to positively
affect, because believe it or not, it's very easy to negatively affect biology using this
concept. Well, the all the hoop to all the stuff being talked about online about how
5G is damaging, for example.
Right. But no one's talking about what frequencies are helpful.
You see, but it's not frequency, it's vibration.
And just a real quick insert, a frequency is defined by a cycle per unit of time.
Right. And that cycle per unit of time is a vibration for a unit of time.
I'm suggesting get away from time and just focus on the vibration.
It doesn't matter how what the frequency in time is, because it's everything that happens
is instant in this case or within an instant.
And if you do have what was mentioned in the chat as hysteresis, which is action reaction,
but hysteresis is action, reaction, action.
And it keeps it's kind of like something you ever notice.
Put a magnet on a screwdriver, you pull the magnet away.
Now the screwdriver for about a minute or so can pick up nails and screws.
Right. Right. Yeah.
That's hysteresis. So what I know and from experiments is when you do have hysteresis
through biological induction, it produces poison.
Now, I think there's plenty of organizations like, for example, Ibrahim Karim, who does biogeometry.
He does these symbols that improve the environment just by putting a symbol in the room.
He says for every lab or group that researches how to use these things for positive,
there's 150 to 300 groups that are trying to develop the same technology for negative.
Right. Think about that.
So, yeah.
So, OK. Yeah. About the organs.
Yeah. Actually, what I wanted to segue into is what the next thing you brought up.
So we're OK.
Yeah. It's really about water.
And the easiest way to think about the organ or the liver or the ovum, like you were mentioning,
how those characteristics carry on is the concept of that holy water where they have a small vial.
That's all you need. Right.
But I hate giving that example.
There's got to be a better one because the next the only other mythical stuff I could think about is the fountain of youth.
But that's a fountain. Right.
Right. It's not really a small vial of or small given volume that can affect a large given volume.
You see. Well, you know, it makes me think oddly of the, you know, some of the scam artists that are out there, too.
Like the one of the most popular ones involving water.
I'm sure you've heard of it. Is this what is his name?
Peter Popov. Right.
You ever heard of that guy? The name sounds I've heard of the name.
I'm not familiar with their stuff, though.
He does this thing where, you know, look, we'll pray with you.
And, you know, he's all on the J.E.S.
U.S. kind of, you know, trip and all that.
But he sends you a bag of water.
Right. Oh, well, he cursed, which he says is, you know, filled with this great intent.
And it'll do it'll do for you if you take this water, you drink it.
It does great things, et cetera, et cetera.
And he sells that as kind of a, you know, like we'll send it to you for free and all that.
But it's kind of interesting to take a look at it one of these days because I'm not sure what he's doing.
But the premise is correct.
The execution is probably way off.
Right. But here's the thing.
If you believe that it's on, it'll work for you.
You know, years ago, they when they started bringing radiation therapy for cancer treatment in the 50s, they started inviting people in for it.
And it's basically a hopped up, hopped up X-ray machine.
Right. For radiation therapy.
Well, this man comes in.
He's like a bus driver or something, goes to a doctor and the doctor puts a thermometer in his mouth and walks out of the room, comes back in.
And the doctor noticed the man is acting like he's actually getting the treatment.
Right. So the doctor said, this is going to be interesting.
So he left the thermometer in the man's mouth for another week or so.
The man supposedly had throat cancer and he came in for this radiation therapy right through this weird X-ray machine, a broken X-ray machine basically is what they use.
Yeah. So he told him to come in next week.
He didn't give him any of the radiation therapy, just left the thermometer in his mouth.
It was one of these industrial type with a cord on it.
And he noticed that the man thought that was the therapy.
So he told him to come in another week, did the same thing.
He just had him lay back in the chair, puts the thermometer in his mouth 15 minutes, then tells him to go home.
He did this for about a month.
Then about a month later, the man's cancer was was healed.
OK. He never got ready.
The doctor kind of did this thought intention experiment with him.
He only had was the thermal because the man thought that was the therapy.
He didn't tell him it wasn't.
He just wanted to see if just having the thermometer in his mouth.
Right. The placebo effect. Right.
Right. Think about the placebo effect.
So it's again, going back to the induction and how the biology really works.
I think I gave an example of someone said, is blood alcohol real or is there another prank?
No, it's real. But the alcohol doesn't go through anything.
It's reproduced by the body.
That's why people who are known to hold their liquor are slow to reproduce alcohol.
Someone who takes one beer or one shot of whiskey and is drunk, they reproduce the alcohol very quickly.
You see, it's not that they.
Right. And this is a common thing.
I think anyone from a child remembers someone in a familial gathering or public gathering that just drank a little and got drunk or the other people didn't.
Right. We've noticed this all our lives and there's no explanation for it.
But here you go. Once you understand one person's body impedes production and the other person's body encourages it.
So this is the same with all kinds of things.
Like, for example, if your body is very quick to reproduce the food that is in the intestine into the bloodstream and doesn't do it completely well, that person is more susceptible to getting, quote unquote, what they call cancer.
Or someone who's a little bit slower to reproduce that, meaning slower with but less, no, no hysteresis at the same time, no memory.
So in other words, the person is more susceptible of getting cancer when they digest the food in the lumen of the intestine or the stomach or the duodenum and passes through the body.
If if the if the nutrition that goes into the blood from the intestine through and by induction has the memory of the original food and enough of the memory by hysteresis, by dwelling there, chances are that person will be more susceptible to cancer because the food will go back.
The nutrition that's in the body will want to revert back to how it was before they ate it.
And that's what forms tumors and toxins and things like that.
So that, again, the the ultimate story, we're kind of bouncing around here with induction is, you know, the thing is, you know, we look at devices like the Reif machine and all these other things that were developed in the 20s and 30s was a lot of these alternative medicine devices.
Even the Hieronymus radionics with the copper plates and the dials and all that.
Right. What I'm suggesting is the ultimate way to do this is strictly through the emo and the mind, believe it or not, not sort of in line with what they do.
But hand, you know, it's not airy fairy, though it has to be.
You know, there's Reiki.
There's all this other stuff.
Right. These organizations.
And, you know, I've spoken to people that do Reiki and I bring up the concept of induction.
They don't get it. I'm like, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
How could you possibly support the idea of Reiki and not understand the concept of induction?
I mean, yeah, they don't.
That's well, that's silly to me, because it's like, look, are you not basically saying that you are able to transmit from an intention, OK, to another place and manifest it elsewhere?
I mean, literally, that's almost exactly the same as the Star Trek example, right, where you're taking the thing, you're sending it elsewhere.
And well, it's not harp on the harp on the Reiki guys.
I mean, they're trying to harp.
I'm just saying, I think that's especially silly.
It is. Well, look at the medical doctors.
They don't know that there's no blood, you know, every doctor I've ever spoken to.
And I've shown him that there's no blood pressure, what it really what they're taking and how nothing passes through.
All of them say the same thing.
Really? Really, Greek?
Oh, wow.
You know, and I'm talking about people that have been in the medical field all their lives.
Right. I'm like, oh, my gosh.
Oh, my gosh. We are in big trouble.
You know, it's like how long you've been a car mechanic for 40 years.
And by the way, what is the steering wheel again?
Yeah, it's like, whoa.
So that's why, you know, that's why I keep saying all fields of study, all professions are wide open.
When you go to any professional field or body of knowledge, the reality of that body of knowledge is in storage.
It's archived. The people practicing that profession know nothing about that field.
Let me just give it to you this way.
Everything is being run like an illicit operation.
Everything's being monetized.
Whether you register to vote, go to the hospital, go to church, everything is being monetized.
Right. Okay.
Your signature. Okay.
So basically, very few people know about this and it's unlawful.
So it classifies as a RICO, racketeering, corrupt organization or an illicit organization.
Right. Everything that's going on.
So let me put it this way.
If you were going to set up an illicit organization on a large scale, the people that you have that are part of your organization that deal with
the public at large, the less they know about what really is going on, the better it is for you.
Isn't it? Yeah.
It's best that they just know about what they have to do as a job.
And that's it. Yep.
Need to know. That's it.
That's why you have all the specialization.
And I'm telling you, all fields are open, wide open.
That's why when I hear about Black Ops Project, Skunk Works, I laugh because it's not really Black Ops Project.
It's just more they're working on real stuff.
So in other words, unless they've gotten some ancient technology or reverse engineered or gotten, quote unquote, gifted by another society that doesn't have this protocol of subversion and illicit organizations, I'm telling anyone that once you do, I shouldn't say just a fair amount of Greek speak, but just open your mind and perceive and ask the right questions.
You can start your own Black Ops Project in advanced science and material and energy systems and all this other stuff on your own and catch up to them very quickly, because 90 percent, if not better, of these guys working in these secret Black Ops that have advanced technology, they came out of the bullshit school system, university system, and they believed it all their lives and probably still do.
So if you have an open mind and perception and ability to ask the right questions, you could catch up to any one of those, you see.
So this is how kind of bizarre the world is.
Continuing Rated-Y Sonic Event 10, as we had taken a break and the Greek was saying that all the fields are wide open, does that have anything to do with the orientation, the situation, the communication, if you will, with the gods, Greek?
Of course.
You know, I've always said to people, you know, when you have a discussion, the easiest way to do it is first you preface, then you inform, and then you discuss.
Right?
So a simple example of that is your cell phone battery is low and you're calling someone to give them important information, instead of saying, hey, this is this and I'm so and so, give the important information first, blah, blah, blah, and it may not make sense, and then start backing it up until it makes sense.
So when the battery dies, they got it.
You see what I mean?
Well, they got the most important part out of the way, so they have the key.
They have it.
Right.
Okay.
So the key here, the preface, inform, discuss is kind of like out the window when it comes to the gods, because first of all, let's give the important part, like I said earlier.
So right now, this is the relevancy, if you want to take it from the relevancy, meaning how important it is.
All the stuff that you see going on worldwide since the pandemic has been notched up a few gears, let's say, right, with like whatever opinion people have on it.
Right?
One of the big distractions is the socialist liberal banking, whatever agenda, but it's a much bigger agenda than that because it's been in place very firmly since the 1950s after what they call World War II.
What that is is you'll notice that after World War II, all of these fertility, let's say, medical practices started being introduced into society, right?
Incubators became popular, and then in vitro fertilization, so infertile, so-and-so, or a couple can't have a baby, they want a baby.
We're not talking about adopting here, right?
We're talking about impregnation.
Right.
All these technologies were now being made available to the public openly, right, creating children in ways that were not in recent times known, okay?
They were shown as medical advances.
Then you have the legal system coming up with this bullshit thing that everybody's got rights, right?
It's important, right?
No talk about law because you know there's no rights in law.
We've spoken about this, right?
Right?
Get it, right?
Right is something that you have when you transgress the law.
You shouldn't be treated like a dog.
You have a right to three meals, three hots and a cot or something in jail, right?
Yeah, that's one of those things, yeah.
Yeah, that's a right.
So if you're asking for rights, it's like what did you do wrong that you're asking for rights?
But anyway, they brought this stuff in with civil rights and then they started talking about women's rights, right?
Burn your bra all the way to now.
A minor is 18 years and younger.
By the way, I don't like hearing when people are of color and they say I'm a minority.
In law, a minority, unless it's specified by age, a minority means you're incompetent.
Because the majority, right?
Remember it's called the majority vote?
Majority means you're competent and you can make a decision that will influence the group.
A minority means you're not competent and you should not influence the group.
So when I hear people of color saying they're a minority, I say in age or in competence?
You have to specify.
And they don't know because they're deemed incompetent because it's quote-unquote a
There's many places, writings in the Constitution, all that, that it's the white male, right?
Landowner, white male, right?
That is the majority.
If you're not male or white, you're part of the minority.
Temporarily, they did used to say that you reached the age of majority,
which I always found interesting because it made sense considering that you were a minor before that.
Sure, but it's specific, right?
Because you're deemed incompetent, you need a guardian, let's say, right?
Where the age varies.
It's 20 in law, by the way.
When you hit your 19th birthday, it's not
Okay.
Anyway.
So you have that.
The legal system budding in now and they bud into the point where same-sex marriage, right?
And the minority now
So even now, 18 or 21, depending, is you're not a minority.
You can go and function in society, right?
But they're telling children at 7 or 8 years old to cut their penis off or cut their breasts off
and take sex change drugs, right?
It's pretty critical outside of the
So all these things and then you have the gender-bending chemicals.
They dump phthalates.
I like that word, phthalates.
It's spelled P-T-H-A-L-A-T-E-S.
It's a plasticizer, usually in chlorinated plastics, and it's a gender-bender chemical.
You pour it in the river, all the male fish become female,
and the female fish usually lay so many eggs that they're not viable or whatever.
That's what we were referring to a few years ago as estrogen mimickers that were being brought in,
and some of this stuff was literally leaching from the plastic bottles and the BPA and all that, right?
Yeah, those
Well, the polyethylene bottles, most of those don't leach.
They're pharmaceutical-grade, polyethylene, polypropylene.
It's the polycarbonate that has the BPA, the bipethyl sulfonyl, whatever.
Okay, so you have all the gender-bending stuff, right?
And then you have the attitude, right, the rainbow flag, all this other stuff.
Okay, so it started in the 50s with in vitro fertilization, all this stuff, women's rights,
all the way to what you see going on right now with children being told that they could pick whatever gender
or sex they want to be, right?
Okay, so what does this have to do with the gods?
Well, one of the earliest Sumerian  actually two Akkadian
it actually would be classified as an Akkadian  tablets has their chief goddess to be Inanna,
however you want to spell that.
It's a double N, I think, I-N-A, double N-A, however, Inanna, Al-Inanna.
Later on became Ashtarte, Queen Mary, you know, these goddess personifications, Maat in Egypt.
But the earliest goddess personification, veneration that has been known in a clay tablet, the poem to Inanna.
In that poem, there are several hymns.
I don't have the references in front of me.
The internet, I looked this up a couple of months ago and I couldn't find it.
But I remember if you go to an old library here, fortunately, near Tucson,
the Carnegie had endowed one of his private libraries here.
So you go and you look around and these little hardbound books that were designed to be put in a vest pocket.
They're about the size of a postcard and they're real small and they're jam-packed with information.
So when you look at some of the hymns, if you can find it, let me know on the chat or email.
The hymn to Inanna talks about her as being the creatrix, right, of all things.
Well, one of the stanzas in the verse is in the hymn,
Oh, Inanna, who turns men into women and turns women into men.
Think about that.
That's like really stark contrast to what you see in the biblical text, right?
So this is way before the quote-unquote penning or writing of what's called Genesis or anything like that.
So one of the earliest venerations of the goddess, she was touted as being able to, in a justified way,
her justification to turn, let me repeat that, men into women and women into men.
Wow, right?
Okay, so the veterans of Greek speak will go back and say,
Hey, Greek, you always talked about the revived goddess religion.
Anybody who's heard me speak since the early 2000s,
it's like what you're witnessing for not now,
but everyone wants to think the world's going to end on September 22nd every year, right, or something?
Something like that.
It doesn't work that way.
What you've been witnessing for almost three quarters of a century is the revival of the ancient goddess religions.
Well, we talked about evidence.
Yeah, we talked about evidence of that on early Ocelli in the Greeks regarding the concept of the justice goddess.
And the other representations of, and you would generally just say that's just a representation of the ancient goddess religion.
This is exactly what you're talking about here.
Yeah, and it's far-reaching.
It's far-reaching, and the reason I brought up what I did regarding the creatrix,
one of her attributes was not only creating everything, you know, mankind and animals and all this,
but she also turned men into women and women into men, right?
Think about that for a moment.
This was acceptable and justifiable, so as it is today.
You ever notice how, quote-unquote, political parties are saying it's justifiable for people to be, quote-unquote, transgender and do sex changes?
More than ever, right?
So this started in the 1950s by simply offering as a benefit those that could not, let's say, have paternal functions,
to having paternal functions with the aid of science, scientific methods,
and all the way to the legal system butting in to same-sex marriage, to the legal system butting in to rights for people who,
another thing now is which bathroom do they use, right?
Right, on and on and on.
This has nothing to do with some democratic, socialist, whatever, U.N. agenda at all.
They are simply administrating it, you see?
Okay.
Now, how many people are in that group?
Let's say the people that you see on the newspapers and the names that you see and hear of, whoever they are,
they're just puppets.
They're told what to do.
I doubt if any of them know that it's the revived goddess religion because, again,
these people that you hear about, the Musks and all the leaders and Bill Gates, Jeff Bezos, all of you can go down the list.
It doesn't matter.
The thing is that they're just like you were talking about with, you know, if you're going to run something OC-wise,
what do you do?
You give people jobs.
They don't need to know anything other than the job they're doing.
Exactly.
Their leaders do.
The people running them do know this, right?
So what's interesting is part of the Greek-speak thing is to bypass all that stuff, you know,
what's being put out and go right to the core of it.
And I just wanted to bring up that hymn of Inanna.
That was very important.
You could take that as a closing statement or you could take it as an opening statement to a discussion of the gods.
But once in your mind you consider what we just said, compare that to all the frustration the quote-unquote conservative types,
religious types are having with the current situation with what's going on with the gender bending and the children
and which bathroom to use and the same-sex marriage and all this other unlawful stuff, right?
Right.
How many of them are saying, oh, this is just the revived goddess religion?
And by the way, the more you fight the agenda that they're putting on the people,
the stronger the agenda seems to get.
You ever notice that?
Oh, yeah.
I was just going to ask you something here, which is speculation on your part, clearly.
But I'm curious.
What do you think would happen if somebody came out instead of saying, look, you know,
based on the laws of the Bible, this is usually their backing for why they're resistant to that agenda, right?
It's because of their King James book, et cetera.
Okay.
Look, if somebody came out and said, you know what, you guys are instituting an ancient goddess religion.
You guys are actually enacting this agenda.
And this is actually what's at the core of it.
If somebody came out and said that, which I am highly doubtful anybody would,
whether they were educated on it or not, I mean, if you went to one of the political leaders today
and you got, you know, 30 minutes to explain this to them, and you did,
and you said, look, this is where it comes from.
This is what it's based on.
What do you think would happen if one of these guys came out and said that publicly,
like really in a position of supposed authority?
I don't think it's possible.
I don't think it's possible for many levels.
I think we talked about the security apparatus.
Put it this way.
If you saw one of these guys, the influential people with a minimal security apparatus around them,
they're a clone.
You could kidnap them all day.
And another one will show up.
And it's already, this is already out on the dark web.
Don't bother with kidnapping operations.
They're clones.
The minute you got them in the room to make the phone call that we want,
we got Jeff Bozos or Gates or whatever, they're going to push a button and his head blows up.
And you see he's just useless.
I know this sounds kind of crazy, but I'm telling you it's something to think about regardless.
The way to do it, it's interesting.
That was the next point that I was going to bring up.
The way you deal with it, once you get the information in hand, but you have to know the information.
You can't just repeat what I just said because if you have enough people just repeating,
it will sound like a script.
You have to know it, right, backwards and forwards.
And you could be quizzed on it, let's say, right, to a certain degree.
Because who's going to quiz you on it anyway, right?
They don't know anything about it.
So let's say you're well-versed enough on the goddess religion.
The way you approach the establishment is not by, hey, what you're doing is this, ha, ha, ha, whatever.
You approach them in a shameful way, almost as if you're laughing at them for that,
like as if they've got poo on their face already.
In other words, you laugh at them like they got hit with the pie.
Don't talk to them like they're serious.
You would have to be all in jest because remember, I've mentioned the more that quote-unquote conservatives
or whatever, let's say, let's not even call them conservative, but people that are against whatever agenda,
what happens to the agenda?
It gets stronger and stronger.
But if you go after them with laughter and need to say with love, meaning you're doing the right thing, right?
Remember, love should be like light.
Love should not be like fire.
So if you're basically doing it as if you just threw a pie at their face for everyone else's entertainment, right,
not to prop yourself up and say, look, people, I just discovered this.
Oh, so serious, right?
You'll be marked as a terrorist.
But if it's done in the funnies, I guess they still have political cartoons, don't they?
Yes, they do.
They're not as good as they were 50 years ago or 30 years ago, let's say.
No, they're not.
Yeah, they're not as good.
Right.
They're not as hard-hitting, let's say, well, soft-hitting, let's say, or overall as they were years ago.
Well, they used to contain a lot of things that, you know, there was a lot of interesting things within the art
that transmitted many messages that, you know, now it's much more simplified.
It's, you know, one particular point is made maybe, if you're lucky.
It had more depth.
That's a good way to look at it.
It really brought the character that they were making fun of through more than just one, like, single-issue type stuff.
I mean, like they drew a cat.
They would put, you know, dollar signs in its eyes.
They would make sure that the cat was definitely, clearly a Zopdigger fat, right?
They would put a top hat on it.
You know, like, in other words, there were many different levels by which you were meant to recognize that this was, you know,
a fat cat who was interested in money, et cetera, et cetera.
And they put things, you know, even like, say, dripping from its teeth in the cartoon way to show that there were many points
to what it is they were pointing a mocking finger at, you know.
Well, let's give it to the AI art boom.
They should give it to the AI art now and see what the AI does with it,
even though, you know, it's just a computer program with multiple computers.
It's not really AI, but it would be interesting to see.
But in essence, it would have to be done to shame them.
And it doesn't matter what they do because no one sane would believe it, you see, is one way.
Because one of the things that I've noticed with these, quote, unquote, protester types, they're too serious.
They're too serious.
And there's two things going on because this always brings up the, you know, the ham-fisted approach, you know,
or the, you know, someone repeating something against, you know, that they've heard this counter, you know,
the conservative media or whatever.
They just repeat what they saw on Fox News or Alex Jones or whatever.
So there's an in-between point where if you're going to protest this or present a counter to it,
it should be in a very comical fashion, very lighthearted fashion,
or it has to be done numerically and geometrically the way they do it.
Okay, what do I mean by that?
When Biden announced the pandemic, whatever, it was at 3-11 or 3-22, I'm sorry, on the clock,
when he came on C-SPAN or CNN to do the three years ago, the lockdown.
They waited for him for it to be 3-22 on the clock.
And they show you the clock, 3-22, before he started his speech.
3-22 is a heavy masonic number.
Another coincidental number is the 11-11.
Another thing is the black and white, you know, the black and white checkered floor, right?
Another thing are certain days, you know, from Hitler's birthday to the equinoxes like March 21st and the other one, right?
Another one is they have their occult holidays.
So if you're going to do a protest, you figure out their calendar and use it.
Because the moment, okay, the last big protests that happened that I recall were the ones with the bankers,
the 99 percenters, what was that called back in 2011 or something?
Occupy Wall Street, that kind of thing.
There you go.
Whole masses of people showing up, okay, doing all these protests.
But here's the thing.
If they all came out at 9-11 a.m., like there was no one around,
it said we're going to assemble at exactly 9-11 or assemble so at 9-11 we're all in formation.
And we have 33 people wearing white and behind them 33 people wearing black, right, the masonic 33, right?
And then we go to 11-11 and then we bring in another group, right?
And then at 3-22 we do another thing, right?
This is all being watched.
They're going to say, holy shit, they're using the same magic we are.
What do you think the protests?
So if they did that, I discussed this back with Vinnie Eastwood when the Occupy Wall Street was coming.
I said they need to follow, you need to come out at 9-11, 33 this, 33 that, 3-22.
It just went over his head like it does for most people.
What does it matter?
We need to just get out there and protest.
You see the lack of order?
I'm not saying you should follow Freemasonic, but here's the thing, Chuck.
If the people do want to protest and they use the same numerology and the same visualization and symbology that they do,
the Illuminati or the Freemasonic Authority, they will see that as a serious counteroffensive.
But you could have millions of people.
What happens when millions of people show up?
Well, now it doesn't even make it to mainstream news at all.
An example right now is there's actually a very vaguely mentioned, there's a serious unrest in France as we speak.
Oh, Israel.
And Israel as well, yeah.
I'm just saying there are people showing up in significant numbers, but our media is kind of like, well, this is sort of happening.
Anyway, on to what we're going to be talking about in 2024 with the presidential selection.
They move right along.
They don't dwell on it at all.
And it gets, well, the symbology, I'm not saying that if you follow the symbology, what they do to a T, it's going to work initially.
But once you, it'll take notice, and the second time they're going to say, okay, this is too serious because you're actually affecting this reality.
This reality is an egregore.
This is the NPC also.
If you have parents.
I'm not aware of what the word egregore means.
Well, it's if enough people believe in something, it manifests.
An example of an egregore would be in the movie Ghostbusters, the first one, when this goddess, again, goes to manifest something.
And they're like, clear your mind, clear your mind.
And he says, oh, what were you thinking of when she went to manifest this magic?
One of the guys was thinking of a harmless thing like the Stay Puft marshmallow man, right?
Right, right.
So this 100-foot tall marshmallow man starts walking through the street in New York destroying everything.
Right.
Because he thought of it.
It's basically a thought form that's manifest, but it's a thought form that's manifest through the collective.
That's what the NPCs are also.
What I mean by that is you have enough parents believing what they were told in school, what they're told in church, and what they watch on TV.
You want to have a baby.
That energy in the water is being affected by all those collective beliefs they have.
That baby is going to be torqued and twisted into an NPC based on those beliefs, you see?
Okay.
But not always, because sometimes you have the black sheep.
Right.
Anyway, to go back to the protests and the gods.
What's interesting is what I just said is pretty obvious because there's a dozen conspiracy-type websites that always talk about these things.
Look how Biden came on and did the speech at 3.22 to announce the lockdowns, right?
Look at how they did this at 9.11.
Look, 33, right?
All the Hollywood logos.
He's doing the symbol with the eye, right?
And many people will show you different things that are in the background.
Look at these angles.
Look at the fact that there's the two pillars.
Look at the numbers that are directly over his head.
It seems like it's just part of the background.
But, yeah, all of that.
Right, right, right.
So what this tells me, when you look at all the protests going on, and it seems like a segue, but it's not, from the god.
We're going to go back.
But if you examine, let's say you just came to this planet, and you're trying to assess what's going on with these protests,
you know that all of the manifestations from the authorities are using these Freemasonic guidelines or outline or template with the 33s, 11s, the 9s, and all this other stuff, right?
They're using the 19.
Anyway, there's a whole handbook on this.
I'm sure you could find.
I don't know where.
But so if you're visiting this planet and you see the protesters are not using any of this, right,
you either say this is a planet completely full of morons, or these protests are actually not really, they're organized as counter, as a fake opposition.
There's a few people that got these protests together that work for the same people that they're protesting against.
Which I mean is very often exactly the case.
The latter is true.
Like, again, with the protests against the Occupy Wall Street, how many people were talking about 12 U.S.C. 411, where we're not supposed to be using the money?
We have no money.
It's a state of emergency, giving us worthless notes.
If it's a bank note, you should get money for it, you know?
So, all right, so how many people brought that up?
None.
So right away that told me it was a fake, it was a co-opted, right?
Okay, what's interesting is you're not seeing mass protests.
It's going to be, it's not going to happen that way because when the system flips and becomes ultra-conservative, still retaining the goddess religion but another form, which I have never, I don't know if I've ever gotten into it, but we will.
You will have the rise of the conservative, the biblical types coming to the surface.
You know, religious Christian type, not biblical.
There are no, there's only a handful of people that know what's in the Bible because there's a billion copies of it, right?
Very few people have the comprehension.
It's not because you have to be intelligent.
You just have to have comprehension.
So what I'm trying to say is it's all going to flip, but you're not seeing protests other than a few mom and pops on street corners about this.
And they don't even know it's the goddess religion, but what's going on with which bathroom to use and gender bending and all that, right?
Okay, so there's, I gave some of the reasons because as we go along, the discussion of the gods, the first thing that you can discuss, go back to the gods, about the gods is how evident is it?
Do you know how I just showed it?
It is evident that 99.9% of all the protests that you see are a co-opted, actually created or set up by the same people that supposedly being protested against for the very lack of having this Masonic template in place.
Because you don't have to be that intelligent to put a Masonic template to scare them back, right?
And so it's, don't waste your time.
In other words, if you saw a protest going on and it did have the Masonic template, it might be worth getting into, hate to say, even though I'm not that type, it doesn't matter.
But then it's probably the real deal, but it's not going to happen.
So what you observe, for example, what you see on a slightly deeper level reveals a lot.
So when you go back and speak about the gods, how many of us have actually walked into one overtly that had the t-shirt, I'm a god, let's say, recently that we know of?
No one.
I haven't seen that lately, no.
Yeah, so as you start looking around and going into this, from a material or immaterial point of view, you're going to notice that they're not around.
First thing you notice, can't help it, right?
Silence is something that everybody hears once in a while, right?
Right.
But what everyone will see is there's no gods around.
That's pretty easy, pretty obvious, pretty much.
Almost reminds me of that scene in Devil's Advocate, right?
The Pacino scene where he says, you know, where's your god? He's an absentee landlord.
Well, yeah, here's the interesting part of that.
Then they start breaking it down into subdivisions, right?
Because let's say if you read about the god of the Bible, he uses agency.
He does it all by agency, right?
Other gods are just so overcoming and overbearing and distant, and we just spoke about the goddess, for example.
Right.
Okay, so we don't see them around.
So what do they really represent?
This is back into fundamental Greek-speak, which is basic.
It's where you get your law from.
They're a superior being, so why reinvent things?
It's already been done.
They have things that are provable that work well.
Like, for example, the reason I do the Old Testament, let's say, template is because it works and it's true.
Even something like circumcision, which should be done on the eighth day, well, it's very well-known, established scientifically and medically,
that a male baby at eight days old has the highest coagulative properties in their body.
Not the seventh day, not the ninth day, but the eighth day.
So how did they know that back then?
So all of these different things, and they still hold true today because it holds true enough for the individual.
There's plenty of people that I've met that say, no, I don't do any of those laws because I do whatever I want.
But there's a certain limit.
We're not born with any downloads, so we're going to have to learn what we're  in other words, most people really don't know what they want.
They have to be told what they want.
You know that, right?
Well, they learn it one way or another through experiences.
They learn it, exactly.
You have to be shown or taught.
Like you said, they learn it.
Okay, so what is there to learn?
So the first priority one should have is if you're going to venerate something or someone as a god, how does that improve your life?
So right there you've weeded out 99% of all the religiosity and all these other things that you see.
We're not talking about how you feel about something, like the J-E-S-U-S stuff.
It's all about feeling and belief.
If there's nothing there that you can use that's tangibly going to help you or organize you into a higher quality of life
or anything on how to do something, like if you don't know how to tie your shoelaces, is there a god for that that shows us how?
And he doesn't have to be here.
It would be very inefficient if he could just have it written down, right?
Stuff like that.
So that's essentially, believe it or not, that's all I have to say about the gods.
What are you getting from that?
And I'm talking about if a god is all-encompassing, okay, well, that has nothing to do with the physical reality, right?
Or whatever.
There's a dualistic and someone put, what about monism?
Is that just another one of the things?
It is, but there is no monism or dualism.
So if it's a god, most people have justified that there is no physical benefit.
It's all spiritual and what you believe.
So then you just act like a poor sad psych here and you don't know how to function here.
It doesn't help you at all.
Well, what good is it, right?
Then go where they are then.
You can't.
So you're stuck here.
Then there's the other ones, like the science god, for example, tells you, or the legal god, how to do everything here.
There's no spirituality.
You know, when you're dead, you're done kind of thing, right?
The ultimate duality.
When you're dead, the laws don't apply to you because that's that.
Right.
But they're playing.
So either one.
It actually should be both.
It should be for the mind, the spirit, the non-physical and the physical.
So one thing to watch out for is when you're looking at the gods, what information are these gods transmitting and has been memorialized that could help with your daily life or weekly or yearly or whatever.
Again, when you consider this, you've weeded out 99% of what's out there, right?
Right.
So that's a very, very simple way.
It's like, why would you want to listen to Greek speak?
He doesn't have a great voice.
He doesn't have an agenda or something.
He's not whatever.
Why do people like to listen to it?
Because it brings forward things that are very simple that really anyone can think about and ponder.
And it's helpful.
If it wasn't helpful, I don't think people would be listening.
Well, there are tangible improvements that can be gleaned from various discussions, whether it's about reorganizing the way that you think about something
or it's literally changing the way you handle something like water or changing what we're going to get into food soon.
Or 30 other different things.
It shows you how to put conditions and put things.
It's a form of mental organization and manifestation.
So in essence, one of the things that inspired me to do this kind of speak is the way I got into the scripture.
When I heard someone discuss that all law comes from God and this and that, I said, there is no God.
What do you mean?
The Bible that was written by Shakespeare.
I've said this before.
People have heard it.
I said, you know, I'm knocking the Bible.
I've never read it.
It's like knocking a movie that you haven't seen or even seen a review of, right?
Or maybe if you saw a short review, you can agree with the reviewer.
But how can you agree with the reviewer without seeing the movie?
It's an uninformed agreement you're making.
Totally.
So it was extremely uninformed.
And this man brought up law.
So I just went and studied law in the Bible.
I said, no one ever told me this.
Right.
And I saw many things that were in there were actually already implemented.
So I started looking at other law forms.
And I started seeing that this was a superior law form because it was very hands off, but very stark, not limiting, but limited in many ways.
But if you adhere to what limited things there were, it had such a large effect on everything else.
You didn't need much more, you see.
So I played around with that a little bit.
I started using it as a benchmark.
And I'm sorry to say it's very difficult to find anything else that comes close in terms of mental, physical, spiritual organization in terms of how to organize oneself.
Now, there's many things in there like lawful timekeeping and things like that that are not mentioned directly because they're supposed to be taken for granted.
One thing that's lacking in the scripture is not directly, but it does tell you the times will be falling apart.
You won't be able to reckon time anymore to a certain degree until everything changes.
Because, you know, I think I've mentioned we're going to lose one-third of our time, right?
It'll be a 16-hour day and nine months out of the year.
You know, everything's going to be shortened by a third.
But how to measure the effect of a god is what, first of all, what you can access from that god.
Because, like we said earlier, how many have you run into lately or known anyone who's run into any of them lately?
So the only thing that we have is what's written about them.
Now, at this point, it doesn't matter.
Let's just say it this way.
If it's inspired or was a work of fiction or real or not or edited or whatever, are you familiar with it just like the film?
You know, there have been many things that have been put out there through the years that have been shown to be a fraud or a fallacy or whatever, right?
But whatever was called a fraud or a fallacy had to be examined first before it was called, right?
Otherwise, it's unfair, you see?
Well, right.
So you have to know what you're... yeah, of course.
Yeah, exactly.
It has to be examined closely.
So what I'm saying here is any god, any information that's put out there about the quote-unquote divine needs to be examined.
Now, when you start, let's say, taking the opinion of others without examining it yourself, then you're... you know, we just said what that's like.
How can you agree with a reviewer if you haven't seen the movie yourself?
Or maybe you do it out of convenience, which is fine.
It's also the most commonplace piece of trouble I see for people's lives all the time is they've taken somebody's word for something and they're parroting it,
and they're completely uneducated about what it is they're parroting.
They don't realize the attention they've released.
They don't realize the thing they're supporting.
I find it most interesting that people who, on the one hand, say, I have these certain principles, then they tell me what they're supporting,
and I'm often confused because I say, well, you're literally in support of the thing that is working against you.
Do you understand that?
Or you can say, obviously, you don't know much about it.
Well, I would say that.
I try to be a little kinder about it, and I just sort of say, do you realize that this is kind of working against you?
And usually a blank stare is what I get.
I think the time for kindness is over when it comes to a lot of these informational things.
But here's the thing.
With a movie reviewer, if I saw a movie reviewer and he gave you stark reasons and objective reasons that are sort of universal on why the movie was bad,
I may not want to watch the movie, and he just saved me a whole bunch of time.
See, that's the other side of it, right?
But if the reviewer is practicing heresy, heresy means your own preference, then I'd have to know the movie reviewer really well to see that in many other aspects of his life,
and then say, well, if he says the movie is not good, that's good enough for me.
You've heard that before, right?
If someone says it's an endorsement, let's say, right?
Endorses or doesn't endorse.
So one of the things that I like to do with people is when we discuss the gods or whatever writ, because, again, I haven't run into any of them physically.
Because with UFOs, they have close encounters, first kind, second kind, third kind, fourth kind, right?
I think third kind and better is when you have physical...
Some contact, some level of direct contact.
Right.
That seems to be gone.
So let's say you have a close encounter of the first, not even first kind with the gods, really, or second kind maybe.
So let's go all the way back.
Very little tangible, directly tangible in terms of what we consider to be meaningful in our lives, very little of that.
So then how do you judge what is being put out by them?
Well, you have to see, again, how does it affect your life?
Does it improve your life?
And that would be the shortest godspeak talk I've ever done for Greek speak on the gods.
In other words, so it doesn't matter, how does it make my life better?
And I'm not talking from a greedy point of view, just me, but everyone.
For example, if you had a whole toolbox of various things, information or techniques or whatever, to make everyone around you better or improve their lives,
and didn't use it on yourself, but everyone you've ever met did,
even if you never applied them to yourself, your life would still get better by contact with everyone else whose lives did.
Do you see what I mean?
Right.
So what you start seeing then is how is knowledge of the gods or what they're saying helping anyone at this point?
Not at all.
Because they either don't know it or are not applying it or whatever.
And again, if you narrow it down, I think you and I once had a talk with a woman who converted to Buddhism or whatever,
and her whole shtick was about why does God have to have a dick?
Why does he have to be male?
And I was like, wow, that's what you're getting?
This is your spiritual apex?
This is the whole, it's like, I kept saying, well, how does it make your life better?
What have you done that, no answer at all, right?
I'm not going to put a finger or point at anyone, but this is so common, right,
that people that go on these spiritual adventures, I call them, thinking that they'll improve.
And I ask them, well, how are you better?
Well, they can't answer that.
Well, the only answer I've ever gotten from somebody is that it makes them happier, right?
Sure.
And that's the only thing where I go, okay, well, tangibly I could say if you're made happier by these actions,
oh, you could mark that as an improvement, couldn't you?
Because you weren't happy before without it, right?
Are you happier when you're sleeping, though?
I mean, yeah, it's very, well, still, happiness is a big deal.
So essentially, yeah, essentially I wanted to start off with the current conditions,
let's say socioeconomic political conditions is the revived goddess religion,
and I wanted to give that hymn to Inanna about how she turns women into men and men into women
and how that applies since the 50s until now.
I wanted to give that first because if you want to talk about the gods, let's get to the most pertinent thing.
What is the sociopolitical environment that affects everyone?
Yes, believe it or not, the money system and inflation is still part of the goddess system, right?
So I just wanted to give that part first, and I think we'll maybe do a wrap on this one and continue at some other time.