56, and let's hit the ground running.
How about that?
Greek.
Interesting thing.
I brought up just before we started to record, but now we are recording.
So let's get it on the record, so to speak, right?
Although, you know what?
Records have made a comeback.
But anyway, I'm going all over the place.
I don't want to do that.
Well, anything you could access later as a record.
True enough.
But I'm thinking of LPs, you know, vinyl, stuff like that, like those came back around
recently.
You're overthinking it.
Yeah, of course I am, because that's what I do a lot of times.
Anyways.
Weird thing.
I mentioned to you just before we went to air, though, that because you'd played a piece
of music in the background.
A lot of times I call you up and you're listening to music, and I love some of the music, almost
every type of music I love to hear.
Anyway, you were listening to an unusual piece, and it ended up in a discussion about who
this lady was that was singing.
Not really relevant to get into particulars, but we ended up saying, well, you know, old
men can always have babies, it seems like, except in very recent times.
It seems like sperm counts are down.
The ability to reproduce is just down in general.
It's definitely discouraged, but physiologically it seems to have dropped off as well.
So, you know, what are your thoughts on that?
Why is that happening?
How about the why of it?
Well, I talked about it a long time ago.
It's the revived goddess religion, which will be coming in your face, but the revived goddess
religion is about things not being, well, the way things are wrong, and things should
be different.
In other words, procreation should not happen the way it is, right?
It should be technological.
The fake wombs, men having babies.
Well, let me ask you this, because you're saying it's going to be in our face.
Do you mean that it's going to be very much mainstreamed and that that's going to become
like...
It has been, well, tangentially it's been mainstreamed for over 75 years, 50 years.
Started with in vitro fertilization when there were public announcements about being able
to inseminate or create, you know, copulate without, you know, the natural standard way.
But I mean them pushing it as a standard religion, not necessarily all of the accoutrements or
so that they've all put into play here that all go along with it that are obvious if you're
paying attention.
But I mean directly, is there going to be like, hey, we've established the goddess religion
and you should come join it?
It's not going to be like that.
No, no.
What happens is that it's just like, look at the terrorism thing, right?
How do they do that?
They show it to you in movies first, and then there's like little incidents here and there.
And then they start using the word more, more often where it wasn't used before.
Right.
Then you have one big event.
Boom.
And now it's suddenly, now this is the mainstream.
It's a clash of cultures.
It's survival.
If you want to survive, you got to fight them over here so you don't have to fight them
over.
Well, you got to fight them over there.
So fight them over here.
And didn't they pass a whole bunch of legislation and stuff after Kennedy?
Oh, yeah.
About assassinations and about this and that and plot codes and right.
Well, the next thing you knew is that there was this, you know, rage to turn out what
the intelligence agencies were doing and how they were seeking to assassinate foreign leaders
and everything.
And that became a movement in and of itself.
Coincidentally, even though there was just one lone nut guy that apparently shot him,
according to the government conclusion.
But yeah, that's exactly what happened.
You know, again, pay attention to what they're doing, not necessarily what they're saying.
So so you mean to say the same thing with the goddess religion?
It's just like that.
It's not about what they're going to say.
But the playbook is the same.
It's the same tension.
You'll have it introduced in the minds and in language, in the society.
And then you'll have tension and then you'll have an event.
And then the event is the catalyst for putting in something new.
And then, of course, and then, of course, the problem reaction solution where it's like,
here's the problem. It was already there.
Now we're going to let you react to it.
And now we're going to give you a solution, even though it's a little loose
interpretation of the Hegelian dialectic.
It is useful because that's exactly the way it goes.
So technologically, you need answers because men are failing.
They're not reproducing.
People aren't reproducing.
We're not replacing ourselves.
So here's the artificial you don't even have to go that deep.
OK, it's we're in it.
We're in a script and the script has to play out a certain way.
And like I've been saying for a long time, there's only a few real people on the planet.
And everyone, you know how Shakespeare said the whole world's a stage, right?
Well, imagine a film.
You know, you've got your protagonist, antagonist, the star, wherever.
You've got a handful of characters that are on the bill.
And then you've got you can have a movie with, I think, was it Close Encounters
of Third Kind had a no, it was Gandhi that had a quarter of a million extras.
Right. It showed up for the film.
That was the world record, right?
Yeah, yeah. It was a huge scene where they had the yeah, exactly.
Yeah. So you could.
So when you most of the people could be friends, family, your boss,
they are not real people.
In other words, they're here to help.
You know, you can't have a theater that the script and the screenplay
has multitudes and populations without supplying the multitudes
and populations as extras. Right.
So here's the interesting part.
There's only even, you know, there's always been a very tiny percentage
of the human population that is actually really human.
And when the script changes, you have a big war.
Kill off everyone or a big disease.
You kill off everyone. Right. Right.
You see how it works.
It's very simple.
So the whole thing here is especially what I've been doing
is trying to address the real people that are here.
And it's always been this way, by the way.
It's always been this way.
And who are they?
And part of the mystic mysticism, by the way,
if the mystic, if the mystics are correct and they've always been correct,
you know, all the ancient mystics, even the modern ones, the good ones.
There's nothing to ever worry about. Right.
So, you know, or take anything to the point where that was
I was going to say, take it to heart.
You should always take everything to heart because without heart, there's nothing.
Right. So, yeah, it'll be interesting.
And we're coming up in the next few years that I was been talking about.
I'll have to organize my thoughts.
Also, I've been studying the chronology of the stuff.
Again, archaics puts out, you know, Texas, Texas country meets Internet.
Right, right. And he's got he's done some very good work.
And here's the thing.
If I'm incorrect or not sure, I'll tell you, hey,
if I was sure about something and not sure now, I'll tell you, you know,
I'm not invested in any of this.
The the whole reason I've always done the Greek speak
is because I was looking for other people to jam with.
Ergo, that's why we're just doing this little pitly,
you know, behind a paywall or whatever.
Otherwise, it would have been a YouTube channel like everybody else 10 years ago.
Right. Right.
And, you know, and be driving around a Mercedes, a new Mercedes
like everybody else's who's doing these things.
And that's you know, it's I'm just I'm being sarcastic. Right.
So I'm not that's not I'm looking for people to jam with. Right. Right.
So it's interesting.
Recently, I got something very much appreciated email from someone about the
you know, if you're selling these magnetic devices, you should check out the patent.
So they did a lot of work.
They did. I was very grateful.
Hopefully, I'll get more in touch with this individual.
To show me. So I went through all these patents and nothing is even resembling
clothes, because I think I mentioned once this is a tangent, but it's pertinent.
Console's C.O.M.
S.O.L. is like one of the state of the art computer
designing software for engineers
and entered pretty much all the parameters of what I'm doing.
And it showed nothing.
That's one of those things.
That's one of those things that you can create models and it'll show you, OK,
if I add this element, this action, this thing to this device or this building
or whatever. Yeah, actually, you go to the for example, you go to the category
of magnets, you put the shape of your magnet and the power in the gauss
and I'll show you the field.
They didn't show any of the fields that I'm working with at all.
Not even considered.
Right. So right away, if someone tries to imitate this from an engineering
perspective, say, oh, we're not going to bother copying because it doesn't work.
But what do you mean it doesn't work?
We put dirty water on one side and clean water comes out the other.
What's wrong?
So I'll just leave the whole thing alone.
It's too crazy. This is how they are, you know.
So so the the part of the magnet that I'm using is not acknowledged
and it's called the block wall, which is not a wall.
Right. Well, walls don't move on their own.
So if you take a magnet, you know, between the North and South Pole
is the block wall, right?
They're calling it right.
But if you break that or if you stack another magnet next to it,
it acts like one magnet.
Then the block wall moves to where the two magnets are joined,
not the center of each.
So it's not it's not a wall at all.
So I can't really gives a pretty good explanation.
He's a little limited.
And I have not shared what I'm doing with him, by the way.
He's on his own path.
And I think he would be very frustrated to show him what I'm working on,
because I could see that I could see it would take a lot of flexibility
for him to to come over and see what I'm doing.
But nonetheless, I was very appreciative individual looking out for me
because, you know, to go to start searching patents over
and send someone a whole bunch of stuff is a lot of work.
So I do always appreciate the work that people do and the messages that I get.
But I'm still looking for a group of people.
But I know, look, spiritually, it's not possible,
because if you have too many people that are alike, right,
and you start doing things that are so simple but yet extraordinary,
you become a danger. Right. Right.
So and not that I'm you know, it's not me.
It's what the stuff that I work on is is just, you know, extraordinary.
And history tells us this.
I mean, how many stories do you have to hear of somebody who heals somebody
and the next thing you know, they're a witch, you know,
and they get treated as such.
Let's say you put five healers in a room that, you know, that's
call the F-16 and drop a bomb and say a gas line exploded. Right. Right.
And, you know, I mean, I've actually got a thing in my family line
that happened like that with my my great grandmother.
That's exactly how my Irish ancestors ended up here
because they fled after something like that.
And all she did was use some basic knowledge.
Was she a widow? Yes.
Yeah, that's what they do.
They typically target widows and they call them a witch
so they could take their property.
But exactly. And once that happened, it was like somebody take the kids
and send them to America because, you know, or actually Canada directly
so that, you know, they don't get killed also.
And that's that's how my Irish blood got here.
But, you know, just saying it's just an interesting thing to me
because this is what happens when you take something that's not really extraordinary.
I'm very sure she used some very simple things and healed someone.
Sure. True.
You know, as far as everybody else was concerned, he's dead.
He's going to die. That's the end of it.
Well, I want to get into that, by the way, because it's it's not you're not really
you're enabling something that that, you know, it's kind of like
you walk in a room and the room is flooding in New York City, by the way.
A little pun there, you know, and everybody's complaining about it.
And you look over and you see the tap is open.
You go and close the tap and everyone's like, oh, that's amazing.
What do you mean? That's amazing.
That's so simple, right?
It's a simple answer to at least, you know, stop the increase on the problem.
You know, so, right.
So, yeah, these things are, you know, but if you don't see it
and you can't correlate the two, it's not going to happen.
But I want to get into the body a little bit.
Now, there was some stuff in the chat.
And someone is pretty much putting personal information out
that I think will help everyone.
There's there's what they call a long time ago.
Someone said, Tim, when we're talking about personal substance, that's TMI.
I said, what the hell is TMI?
But it's like too personal, right? Too much information.
Right. But nothing like that.
I actually it's very appreciated because it's in one of the purposes
of some people going through what they're going through
is so others can learn from it. Right. Right.
If they can communicate it.
And the purpose of life is to be alive.
There's no other purpose, by the way.
So once you understand that and your give
or should factor is really low, you start to experience
more and more of what it means to be here.
So, by the way, what happens if your give or should factor is too high?
In general, you become a stressed out individual, right?
Absolutely. Throughout history. Yes.
Yeah. Not just this society, any society.
So your give or should factor has to be low.
If your give or should factor is low,
it doesn't mean you don't do good work.
You can work in like, you know, protect Philippe or Seiko watches,
you know, very expensive watch Rolex factory.
And you have a low give or should factor overall.
But when you're building the watches,
you build them how they're supposed to be built. Right.
Don't mix that up. Right.
So when you cook a meal, it's the best meal you could possibly make.
Right. Anything you do is still the best possible.
But your overall give or should factor is low. Right.
So that's that's the key to being here and to experience life.
So I want to get into because this person put personal information.
This is very helpful in his personal experience.
And also, you know, he's benefiting from a lot of the things that are being said here.
What I want to put out, though,
there was a concern about the body type and the body changing or not. OK.
One thing I haven't discussed and I'm always assessing people this way.
You have two minds.
You have, you know, not not in the way people say, always dual minded. Right.
Because, you know, it's not good.
No, you have two minds within the housing.
And I've never gotten into this much.
But you know how I define the spirit as the personality,
the intangible information, very unique to you.
And there's the soul, which is the living physical metabolism.
And then there's the body.
Well, the soul and the body is the living aspect
that has a very, very basic mind of its own.
It doesn't have us. It has a spirit, a component.
But it's not very unique, like the one that you that makes you you.
Like I said, your soul is your metabolism.
So the metabolism from person to person changes slightly.
But generally, you're attached to a general field, a biological field,
a spiritual field that keeps that metabolism going.
Part of that is what we call the involuntary movements. Right. Right.
That's where that's where a similar shape participate
in similar behaviors, react similarly to no, no, not even that.
I mean, the body's will to live.
OK, OK. The body has a will to live.
And this is further along right now.
So let's say someone's really unhappy with the world.
They want to check out.
So they decide they're going to drown themselves.
Well, while they're drowning themselves, they're quite,
you know, adamant about doing that.
And they're they feel a sense of achievement achievement
because once the drowning is done, they're done and they can check out. Right.
But while they're drowning themselves, the body's mind,
the body's own little thing that keeps that desire to live doesn't want to drown.
Right. And it's like, what are you doing to me?
What are you doing to me? Don't drown me. Right. Right.
It doesn't even have a voice. It's totally silent.
But you will feel
the person that's doing that will be satisfied
and feel like they're accomplishing something of one side, the spirit,
the main spirit, but the secondary spirit will be trying to stay alive.
OK, so when someone is unconscious from a bullet,
you see this in Hollywood movies, they're unconscious.
They're really messed up, you know, hit by a car, shot by a gun, whatever, whatever.
And they have them on the hospital bed.
You see this and their heart is still beating and they're still alive,
but they're unconscious.
And what are the doctor? What do they say?
The medical people, this guy's a real fighter.
He really wants to stay alive. Right.
What do you mean? How do you know the guy hasn't said a word?
You know, he's been unconscious for three days.
How do you know?
Because they're measuring what the body is doing.
Right. And the body has its desire to stay alive, even if you're unconscious.
Right. So that part of the body is something that I've not talked about.
And that is very similar.
Like everyone's body.
OK, so imagine you have the most suicidal, most depressed person
that's ready to go ahead and do this or whatever to take themselves out.
The body doesn't want to be taken next.
The body is here to wants to live as much as possible.
Now, there are some exceptions when people do pass
and the body is like he's ready to go and he just went peacefully.
You say, well, I was just going to ask, doesn't it go the other way?
Where sometimes, look, the body's done.
And no matter what it is, you want sure you ain't sticking around.
And it's not fighting.
It's not fighting anymore to stick around.
It wants to go. Right.
OK. It also does that.
But generally and most active people, the general consensus,
the general condition for everyone is
regardless of your whatever, you have an innate ability.
The body has its own thing.
OK, I use this very often.
The human body has its own innate desires and abilities.
Like if you if you see something coming towards you,
someone's going to throw a punch, you flinch, right?
Yeah, typically. Right.
That you don't think about these involuntary.
OK, so various animals have similar things.
For example, like a cat,
you have many different personalities of cats,
but when something drops real loud in the room, they all just take off
and they run away, then they stop and look right.
That's the cat body.
They have no control over that. Right.
The same thing with a dog has its own tendencies.
A bird has different tendencies when it's startled, let's say,
how the way it reacts.
And they're all very, very similar.
That's this innate ability that it's like built in
the uniqueness that each body of each creature has.
Even plants have this.
You know, the most innate thing for a plant is to move towards the light.
Right. You know, it bends towards it.
And if it gets too much light, it droops. Right.
It's to move away.
But it doesn't move away from the light.
It just goes downward.
So everything alive has this innate ability to continue living
unless, you know, there's some exceptions when they've had enough.
OK, so that aspect now,
when when you have a certain mindset
that says, well, I'm going through some physical challenges
and what or I want to change the way I look or feel or whatever,
and the body doesn't react the way I expect it to or it's not reacting.
OK, that's OK. That's OK.
The first thing you have to consider is quality of life.
Am I constantly in pain?
Right. Right.
That's a big deal. Yeah.
Because that brings other for you don't want to suffer that.
And that's by the way, the medical industry has done nothing
for humanity and like they tout it. Right.
It's like police keep you safe. Are you kidding?
They are the ones that are running all the criminal.
And they're part of the criminal enterprise.
They just have the illusion. Right.
Or the military. Right. You see all this stuff.
So no medical isn't done anything. OK.
If you start looking, I've looked at this over since the 80s.
I was when I go to the main library in New York City,
no one's with the lions outside.
You know, when they sat in the same place, Tesla used to sit.
I didn't even know. But OK,
I've been looking at this stuff, the medical stuff since then,
in the late 80s and in real libraries with books that were from the 1800s.
And what I found fascinating is cause of death
in 17, 18, 19, early 20th centuries.
Causes of death were number one, by the way,
that I found that just not statistically, but the one that I found
that was called on the death certificates, it was called poisoning of the teeth.
Like, you know, you know, Woolworth, he died of that.
You know, the guy who started Woolworth. Yeah. OK.
Why would they put that on death certificate?
Well, because there was no quote unquote dental care.
People were not good at pulling teeth.
People didn't want teeth pulled.
There was oral infections, poor diet.
Right. Because right.
You know, financial system.
You remember, everyone's familiar with the Depression in 1929.
The Great Depression.
Well, there was a Great Depression in the 1870s.
It was a Great Depression in the 1890s.
You don't hear about those too much, right?
Another one was pretty rough in 1907, you know, just.
Yeah. Yeah.
There was a collapse of all securities and all that.
They were free. Right.
So these are these very, very bad.
OK, so financial stress.
And so the other thing I found was cholera, diphtheria.
A lot of people die to that, which is what you get that.
Those are things that are living in water because the people
just got used to parasites are thought to be right.
Pretty much. And they were.
Yeah. These things will eat you alive.
Basically, that's what they do.
They they make a comfortable spot on the inside of the body and they nest
literally. And then when they make their young, they have a life cycle
and that life cycle continues and they drill holes in your body.
Right. And you can see this if you if you've ever been around.
They overeat and then the body fails.
That's basically the holes in the liver are very calm.
Like if you go if you're a hunter.
Right. I mean, if you've ever shot an animal, hung it, you know, addressed it,
you know, it cooled down and then finally butchered it and all that.
And you look at the organs, you'll see holes through the organs, you know,
especially the liver, especially. Right.
OK, so that by the way, making a hole in your liver
or five or six or 10 holes in your liver hurts, you know,
it causes infection on that.
But anyway, this is in nature also. So
I found the causes of death to be basically hygienic
and dentistry and real just basic stuff,
not these drugs, vaccines or methods or nothing, nothing like that.
And the other one and certainly not the cop out we have now,
which is almost always what cardiac arrest.
That's it. I mean, which is.
Yeah. But your blood's OK.
Basically, if your blood's too thin, you're going to have a cardiac arrest,
just like if the the the the the heart is a braking mechanism.
So I don't know if you're familiar with drum breaks, you know,
from the cars in the 70s, if you're in the rain, you know, you hit them.
And it seems like the more you it seems like sometimes if you leave,
if the drum breaks are really wet, the more you lean on them,
it seems like you're going faster. Right.
It seems like they're not doing anything right.
Yeah. Very much like a heart attack. Yeah.
I'm just so I'm just old enough to remember that in driving manuals,
they used to talk about having to pump the brakes because we had to drive them.
Yeah. Yeah, exactly. It's like a wiper.
Yeah. So you don't trap a hydro of the water between the
caliper and the rotor. Right. Let's say exactly where the drum.
So, OK. So basically, the other thing was shock.
Basically, someone gets run over by a horse carriage
and they die within an hour, not because of their injuries,
because of fright and pain.
Right. OK. OK.
Shock to the body. Basically, they go into shock.
I've seen people go in shock. It's the most amazing thing.
It's as I have you ever seen a baby being born?
Yes. It comes out. It's like white, gray, bluish.
You're right. Yes. Right.
And when it takes as soon as it takes its first breath, it doesn't always cry.
It turns flesh tone in like five seconds.
It looks it looks purplish to me when it comes out my vision.
But yes. Yeah, it depends on the. Yeah, it looks great.
It looks like a cadaver. Right.
OK, so when someone goes into shock,
they are flesh tone and then they look like a cadaver within 30 seconds.
They lose. They turn completely pale and gray.
Yeah. The whole turning white deal. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
So that's what people die from.
You know, basically, I ran into a lot of fatalities in New York
where you get run by a car, run over by a carriage, horse carriage.
Right. It's pretty normal. Right.
Common injury. Yeah. Yeah. Falls. Falls.
Also, they didn't have guardrails and stuff like that in places.
So and the people, the injuries were minor, you know,
but they died of shock from pain.
So anyway, so what has happened was there was a just like I did
that analysis for myself, that analysis has been going on, you know,
since the industry, the medical industry has been around.
And they said, well, we need more dentists and we need some good painkillers.
That are easily available and easily administered and effective and cheap.
All those things. OK, there you go.
Then the main thing was water.
There was a big cholera.
A lot of people dying in England for for decades and centuries
because the freshwater was too close to the sewer water.
And when they brought in the Prussian engineers, they looked at that
and they said, oh, you got the cholera outbreak in London
because your freshwater is too close to your sewer water.
Why don't you separate them by a few hundred feet?
Watch what happens.
Duh. Right.
So, OK, so we have water, even though there's stuff in the water,
you know, whatever, you know, they put chemicals in there.
It's still far away from the sewer line.
You know, in some places, you know, the water, you know,
the water comes in next to the sewer line.
It's distinctly separate.
It would be better if there were more separate.
But OK, so it's basically hygiene and painkillers and dentistry.
You know, it's funny how the dentists, you know, they don't know much.
And I say, you know, it's because you people are living longer.
And he's like, oh, I didn't know that.
I mean, you know, of course they wouldn't, you know,
talk about anything meaningful in school.
No, I would. Yeah. Yeah.
So, OK, so that's basically this is like a long maybe tangent.
But the cause of death and what I've looked into right and all this.
And OK, so when you look forward, the body's desire to live
if the quality of life is good,
you're fine, right, especially if the quality of life.
OK, like, for example,
from being knocked around and being in like bike crashes and stuff like that,
if certain times of the year, my shoulder hurts from a previous injury.
Right. You know, you've heard of that, right.
Or whatever. And, you know, certain things like that.
I haven't heard of it. Yeah. But OK.
Yeah. But I mean, you've heard people have, you know, been certain that,
you know, had an injury and you kind of, you know,
conscious of that area for the rest of your life.
And absolutely. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. I like I said, I live it.
So, yeah. Right.
So if someone jumped into your body that wasn't familiar with this,
you would find that unusual, maybe uncomfortable,
but because you've gotten used to it, it's OK.
Oh, you've justified it. Yeah.
Somebody jumped in my body. They'd be going, holy crap.
Why does my back hurt like that?
And it's like, no, that's just. Yeah.
But you've justified it. So the history makes it better.
OK, so exactly the same.
There is social pressure, personal pressure.
I mean, like I've talked about sex, sex is one of the things
that is based on what your culture is.
Right. Sex is for having children.
That's it pretty much.
And then you have the desire, of course, and all that, you know.
And then the rest of that is based on what culture you're in. Right.
And, you know, I was having a conversation with someone recently
and I was like, you know, life kind of sucks.
You know, I've had enough. It's not that I'm complaining because I just
you just need a good party with.
You just need to go to a party with lots of sex and drugs.
And you'll find it. Yeah. Once a year.
But it has to be a memorable.
Like you ever go to a party that you remember for a year or two after.
Right. Everyone should have a party like that.
It's called, you know, Saturnalia Christmas was like that, by the way.
It was it was basically a big it doesn't have to be an orgy or whatever.
But in other words, within the moral framework that you so prescribed
subscribe to, you know, have a really good party
at least once a year or once a month or once a year, I think is enough.
In other words, you say once a month, you know, kill you.
If it's really a good party and do it once a month,
they'll kill you after the third month, let's say. Right.
So you don't want so everyone should enjoy something
at least once a year that is just rocking like it just, you know,
they call it Saturnalia Christmas.
That's like the most popular thing.
You know, even in the middle of summer, it's Christmas in July.
Remember Crazy Eddie or whatever? Oh, yeah. Right. Yeah.
So that was Saturnalia.
So the thing. Yeah. So basically, you know, the reason I'm bringing this up
and the sex thing and all that is because it's whatever culture you're in again.
Right. You know, the way you look, the way you might think your appearance fits.
Like, for example, since the 80s.
OK, if you go back and look at advertisements
on the 20s, 30s and 40s, they were ads on there for skinny girls.
You know, you're skinny. Nobody wants you.
You got to gain weight or the chubby girls are getting, you know, the attraction.
Well, in the 80s with the swimsuit models, it's like they're like
they look like 12 year old boys, real skinny.
Yeah. You know, if I see a skinny, skinny woman like that,
it's like not attractive at all.
It's like, oh, my gosh, go the other way.
Yeah. I'm not a skinny guy either.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. They got to have, you know, meat.
So, yeah. Tick.
There's thick and there's tick.
So, yeah. And this was the consensus for a very long time.
If a woman was skinny, it was considered she was unhealthy.
Right now, if a woman's not skinny, it's considered unhealthy.
So the culture can make you mad.
I mean, mad, mad, meaning crazy and mad, meaning like, yeah, I'm mad about that.
Right. It'll piss you off because it might shift on you when you, you know,
hey, look, I'm clearly in good shape now.
But hey, in a couple of years, when I was 25, 30 years ago,
so many women, I'd say, oh, I'm so upset.
Why upset? Because I'm fat. I'm looking at her.
She's she could use about five or ten more pounds.
You're upset because you're fat.
What are you talking about?
You're actually about 10, 15 pounds underweight.
Oh, my gosh. This is insane.
You see. So, yeah. So.
So, OK, so this stuff don't get caught. Right.
So the whole thing then ends up in quality of life.
All right. Health. What is health?
You know, there's no such thing. It's all fitness.
How do I be healthy? I say healthy for what?
What are you going to do?
You sit in the office all day, eight hours a day and then whatever.
Well, you're going to go. You're going to go climb.
You're going to go skydiving.
Are you going to jump out of?
Are you going to go to Mount Everest next week?
What kind of health for what level of fitness are you looking for?
I got you. See, that's why fitness is a better word. Right.
Because what it is, you're free to do what it is.
You're fit to do is what you're saying.
So, look, if you need to be fit to run a marathon, that's one thing.
If you need to be fit so that, you know, your legs stop aching,
that's another thing.
So, you know, therefore, what fitness are you looking for?
It's adjustable based on what your needs are, what you're going to do with it.
Right. Right.
The culture says, oh, be healthy, look healthy.
This is healthy.
What are you talking about? You're so far off the mark.
Right. But the whole discussion.
And by the way, I'm the only one that I've been looking at this.
The only one that I've seen available ever say this, by the way, this is a
this could be a study and a movement on its own, meaning a movement
to get out there to communicate to many people.
Start thinking on your own.
Did you consider this?
Yeah. Stop. Right.
Stop with the one size fits all healthy crap.
Let's get to what is. Yeah.
Or even if they offer you 10 sizes, it's not no good or 100 sizes
because there's a million different things you could be doing
that you need different fitnesses for.
There you go. So, yeah.
So, OK, so then we we get down to what the human body is now.
I think I've mentioned before about 99 percent of what the medical industry
does is unnecessary.
It's job security, right?
They got really ridiculous with the pharmaceutical companies,
which is the same thing, you know, like the
there was no pet food until the 60s.
And they had one can of pet food.
It was for dogs, cats, whatever carnivore.
And then they specialized it, right, because they started
pushing the vets and the vets were trained by the food and chemical companies.
Right. Right.
Anyway, so, again, by the way, if you go to a vet,
why don't they check the blood pressure of your dog or your cat or your bird ever?
You have no sign. They never do that pressure.
If it's so important to.
Oh, but it's not. I've had one say to me, oh, but it's not the same grief.
Oh, but they're mammals.
Yeah, they're almost like, yeah, they experiment on pigs.
You can actually put a pig liver in a human.
It's almost identical.
You know, we share more closer genes with pigs
and internal organs than we do with chimpanzees any day.
Oh, please. I went through six articles this week about pig,
pig organ transplants into people, you know.
Yeah. Well, if you anyway, you know, pigs eat their own kind.
So anyway. Well, that too.
Yeah. So here's the thing.
Why? It's very easy to uncover the what what's being pulled on humanity
are juvenile level pranks, juvenile level pranks with high level authority position.
I had a recent conversation with someone about the medical.
I said, just go look at the medical stuff.
But it doesn't work that way.
It says, well, you don't need to look at the medical.
So I say, man, look at the stuff that's accumulated through the years
that's considered the base knowledge of the medical industry
and what doctors are supposedly trained in.
Well, it doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter what they're trained in.
Just do what they tell you.
I was like, well, it was perfect.
You're not real.
You know, you're obviously one of the filler.
You know, you're one of the you know, it's like if you go talk to an extra
on a movie set, ask them, you know, what are the what's in the script?
You're like, I didn't get a script. I'm just standing here.
You know, I got no purpose.
I got I'm getting to show up in here.
Yeah. All I got to do is show up.
And that's this guy's whole life.
Right. Is to just show up here.
You know, so that's on that side. I'm with the elite.
Like, what do we need these people for?
You know, it's like you don't.
But you do need them now because now the scene requires seven billion
or whatever they're telling you.
But in the future, you won't.
And they're they make they make no difference if they're here.
Yes, I agree.
They're actually in many cases, they can be detrimental.
But just leave them alone.
They got no value. Right.
And this is kind of because we're taught the opposite. Right.
Right. Yeah. So it's always the opposite.
So, again, so I've covered several things there.
And the other thing I wanted to cover, which is really, really difficult.
I mean, it's almost impossible.
But there is a mix where the spirit commands just like a composer.
Imagine what?
What do you call the guys in front of an orchestra?
Not the composer, director, conductor, conductor.
Yeah, right. You have to play conductor.
But the thing is, usually when you say conductor, it sounds complicated,
but it's more like a train. You got stop and go.
Yeah. Right. OK.
Think of it like that.
So you have to keep in mind the body has its own consciousness,
its will to want to stay alive.
You have your own way of thinking, whatever you find.
And then, which is typically what most people think is their voices,
not their voice. And then there's the silent part.
If the silent part isn't getting through to you and you start thinking
and you're focusing on the voice that you're always hearing,
which is not you anyway, it's kind of like someone just tuned in.
I never heard the rest of this. I think this is crazy talk.
But anyway, the part of you that needs to develop and know more. Right.
Sometimes the part of you that needs to develop your consciousness,
that's silent, that makes it's really the you part of your spirit.
If you ignore it long enough,
it will project its desires around the people around you.
It could be total strangers.
And sometimes they will start saying things
to communicate what your spirit wants you
to hear that you're ignoring.
See, I put a stop to that a few years ago because that that was what I couldn't
understand for a little while.
The oddity of strangers walking up to me saying things that were relevant to me
for no reason, I thought.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Which I don't know.
Look, I advise anybody here in what you're saying right now to try and relate
this to something they've seen already.
OK, because it's a very difficult thing.
In other words, if you ignore yourself enough, it will not jump out of your body.
It will project itself in the field around you amongst other things immediate.
And someone might say who doesn't even know you or anything, say something.
But it's really your own spirit going over to their side
and reflecting back to you. Hey, dummy, you're ignoring me.
So this other person is going to say what you need to hear.
Right. So in other words, that's why.
OK, and again, what is this is kind of advanced, but I'm going to say it anyway.
What that means, then you should always surround yourself
with people that you find pleasure, pleasant and can communicate well with.
Right. So you can hear that. You can hear that.
So how many times? OK, here's a more mild way to say this.
How many times have you seen a situation in film or theater or wherever
where people say, I need to have a serious personal talk with you?
Come in the room with me. Right. Yeah.
And they sit down and they give the person not the right act,
but they just say things about what their behavior, their thinking or whatever.
Right. And one of the persons that go, I didn't know that. Thank you.
I'll take that in consideration. Right. Or whatever. Right.
Right. Imagine that scene, but not being deliberate,
but happening in the ether with your surroundings or with other people.
They will actually your consciousness will influence their consciousness
to say something to you.
And very often it could be in other influences.
But sometimes that person will say something so poignant.
You're like, oh, my gosh, that makes so much sense.
And if you ask them to repeat that, they're like, repeat what?
What did I say? I don't remember that. Right.
And a lot of people go, oh, well, that's like the angels coming at.
No, that's you. It's you sometimes.
Well, no. Yeah. If you could discern it, you could see the difference.
Sometimes it's an external influence that could do that also
because they know how this works.
See, how do you know the difference, though?
Well, that's the that's the thing that might be part of the unknowable category
for us here. Right. OK.
You know, it wouldn't be if we knew every if we knew exactly what was going to
happen, so that what time and what day we're going to die.
How interesting would that be?
Not too interesting. Right.
Well, I would try and load up everything in between now and then
in different ways, wouldn't I?
Well, that's why you have that party once a year
that you remember for the rest of the year anyway.
You see. So, yeah. So again,
the basic thing that I would suggest to anyone is quality of life issue.
What can you put up with? Right.
And we could put up with a lot.
Medical industry doesn't even exist.
OK, like I just showed you, it's about hygiene and painkillers
because you could go into shock.
Look, I have to stop myself from going into mild shock.
There's categories of it.
Right. When I nearly chopped my thumb off
with an ax about six months ago, which, by the way, there is no scar,
nothing visible.
If I had gone to the medics, they would have a big scar around the finger.
You know, 15, 20, 30 stitches.
They were trying to stitch it. OK, we got to get a guy in here.
Yeah. And it wouldn't have healed completely in five days or six days.
It would have been still, you know, so you would probably are completely useless.
But yeah, if you think, look, it's gotten to the point now where
many people had their loved ones, their family members
killed by the very doctors knowingly.
And they actually when they got the message that they're, you know,
with the covid thing, yeah, they put them on respirators,
didn't give them any food, any water for a week.
And they finally sedated them to the point where their hearts up.
And they shot him up with a vaccine, too,
because they get an extra 30 grand for that. Right. Sure.
So there's a lot of people.
I see the majority of these idiots who have one of their family members,
loved husband, my children, whatever, die or actually killed. Right.
By these doctors that are there's Scott free still. Right. Right.
And they're probably never going to.
They will be from another source.
So it's dealt with.
But well, eventually everything gets dealt with.
But exactly. But right now they won't.
But these people who had their family killed by these administrators
and doctors actually go and thank them for everything they did to help.
Oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh.
How that's such a bet. You know what I mean?
Yeah, it's crazy.
You know how many times you heard, oh, thank you.
She did. You know, your mom died or whatever.
Oh, thank you for doctors.
And we're going to set up a go fund me for your research and all that.
You know, they're laughing their asses off.
90 percent of the doctors know that they what they're doing and who they kill
and who they know. They're not that stupid.
They're stupid in terms of their profession.
But, you know, again, I had it.
Here's a conversation I had.
OK, so this is your Christian, right?
She goes, yeah, are you from one to ten?
What would you say? She's nine and a half.
So how much of the Bible do you know? Probably zero.
Right. Because, yeah, I don't know.
OK, so when you go to a doctor, if he says from one to ten, he's a nine point
five doctor, how much of the medical stuff, the information does,
you know, probably zero, maybe one or two.
But he's pulling it off as being a doctor.
You see what I mean? Right.
You see, it's the same thing.
How can you go say you believe in this and know nothing about it?
And you see, he's just playing a doctor.
There's no reason to be hard on them, because, look,
if you really want to be harsh on someone, they did a whole thing where,
you know, the car mechanics, right, they was at the television.
They marked the filter that they're supposed to change the oil in the brakes
and they get the car back.
They pay the bill and they didn't do anything.
And they actually had the thing marked, you know, right.
You've seen that, you know, they're busting them and all that.
So it's the doctors, it's the car mechanics, it's the accountants,
IRS agents, the police.
Do you want to go? I mean, is it fair to to just pick on the doctors?
No, it's the whole society's fucked.
No, exactly. You know, it would be like me
thinking that that that jackass in a blue uniform
that shot my dog when I was a kid, you know.
Oh, thanks so much.
You know, now, yeah, they say we shot him to protect himself.
It's just ridiculous. So you're in a ridiculous place.
It's a it's a wonderful place.
You know, it's it's like a terrarium that's set up with care.
In other words, it's set up in a way that everything stays pretty.
Like, give me an example.
You can have a screwed up ecology.
And if you leave it alone, if the humans went away for 30, 40 years
and come back, it will be overgrown and natural again. Right.
That's what I mean by it's well, well cared for.
The system itself cares for itself.
You know, the Earth planet.
So it could be very beautiful.
You know, if all the humans didn't left and came back,
let's say 500 years from now, the planet would be like this paradise, right?
Wild paradise with different temperate zones and all that.
You can see that.
Well, what was it?
George Carlin said the only thing we contributed here is plastic.
Right. Outside of that doesn't matter.
The rest of the Earth will reclaim it anyway.
Yeah, the Earth can reclaim.
So that's what I mean by it being a wonderful system.
There you go.