6060. That's the sonic event for this one rated Y recording. Okay. Anyway, Greek first
off, how you doing tonight?
I'm doing all right.
All right. And I do say night because I mean, it is dark where I am. So I call that night.
Yeah, certainly the day did begin at solar noon. I was up doing some other things before that, but doesn't matter what I do. Let's get into the discussions in the chat, right? Let's address those because that's been rather fascinating. Lately, you also got an email, which you might talk about later, or maybe not.
Well, it's an email that you forwarded. I usually get frequent emails. Fortunately, I've put out conditions and how I like to get emails. And those have been met. I don't get too many emails saying you've got talk about your stuff is great. Don't send me an email like that. Because I know it's great. Sounds cocky. But whatever. But yeah, stuff that can engage what the conversation had been about, add or take
away. If it furthers the conversation, then it's worth sending to the Greeks email address. That's that simple.
Uncommon sense radio one at gmail.com. That's numeric one. uncommon sense radio one at gmail.com. Right?
Right. But also, if you do wind up sending them to me, I do filter them down to what I think would be worthy of response as well, based on the same criteria most of the time. Although I will address certain questions. If they've got like one random question in there with a bunch of other things. I'll boil it down for you. So it's easier. Anyway, I like the chat room, though, because we get a lot of interesting back and forth in real time conversations between people that are listening. So very helpful.
And if you want to go and check that out, it's easy to find a fairly decent chat tango thing. I know it's a little antiquated, but it's accessible to everybody.
And also, there are very few people that are active in there compared to how many subs there are, which are still very few. But yeah, it's even fewer on the chat. But it's still I think gives a I don't know, wouldn't be right safe cross sectional view of what's going on. But it's the best we have. And it is appreciated,
though they are growing. And just one final little housekeeping note here, you do want to get over to the Patreon. Okay, which is Patreon, patreon.com and slash Greek speak, except when you spell speak, you got to spell it with two E's. All right. So if you go there, that's how you got to sign up now. All right. My signup should be disabled at my website. If somebody figures out how to sign up anyway, we'll sort it out. But
hopefully you have a banner there telling them where to go being disabled. Oh, yeah, yeah, absolutely. Okay. All right. Oh, I didn't take anything for granted anymore. No, you can't. But but there's a clickable link there. If you go to the site, you see you can click here to subscribe. It'll take you to that Patreon link. Anyway, all the housekeeping out of the way, let's get to what it is they had to say. In the chat, shifting maze or PKD. Okay. postulate instead of Mandela effect. All right. You know,
because we brought up the Mandela effect a few times recently. Um, I think the idea of a shifting maze, because obviously, if things are altered in the reality, however, you think the mechanism works, I think it's a fair thing to say. Yeah, it's more
with perception, perception is changing. Nothing is really changing. Because nothing can truly be objectified. I talked about trying to objectify and objectifying but you cannot truly objectify. A quick example is you know, infinity. It's usually a mathematical concept and it's numbers going out and you know, into where they might terminate and they won't terminate according to the rules of math. That's called
infinity. Right. But that whole process of doing that sitting down and doing that is within another reality that is not mathematical, which also has its infinity, you see. So it's like the Chinese dolls. And it's also like, when you do perspective drawings, you have a vanishing point, you know, the further away, you know, the right, the vanishing point, you know, you all lines go to one point. Yeah. So that shows that our perception is basically has rules to it. And the rules show that the perception is purely subjective.
Right. Same thing with photography, by the way, the vanishing points in photography. I mean, here's the thing, you can only capture so much within the photograph, because there is a limitation based on the amount that can be seen and absorbed into the data that is then represented in the photograph. Same, same concept, but photograph.
Okay, the Mandela effect and the other stuff, too, is just a signal from those that are operating in a higher look, if you're a fish in someone's living rooms, aquarium, and they're constantly changing the background, little plastic rocks, you know, they go to the stove and buy some more background, they pull the other ones out, drop them in. And all the fish are wondering what's going on is what is it a wonder about wonder about, right? Well, you know, tired of your ass, I'm gonna flush you down the toilet, right? And so they do that with fish.
Well, there's that plus, look, you know, according to that fish, look, everywhere I go, there's water. Not necessarily this.
Yeah, they are. Yeah, you'll have a philosopher fish comes out says, Hey, guys, I think we're in water. And they all laugh at him, right?
Yeah, well, but there you have it. And people have used that to try and explain many things. But okay, fair enough. Um, somebody asked about the percentage of peroxide when creating a, you know, the spray bottle, which is one of the most
don't dilute, don't mess with peroxide. The reason it comes in a darkened bottle is because light will dilute it just photo theresis or photo various photo reactions. It's very photo reactive. Actually, there are many photo reactive things in nature. That's how
that's how photography was first discovered by, you know, people drawing things out and leaves and things cover part of it. And as it dried, it changed, you know, change tone or color. Right? So they figured they could light has an effect and they found things that rapidly affected.
Also, why, you know, beer bottles used to be brown for that.
Yeah, the quality. Yeah, yeah. Yeah. There is a big quality change. Yeah. So so diluting it with water really, really changes it. And yeah, it'll still have the properties, but in a few days. Yeah, so. So what the key is to get the right dilution from the beginning. So the ones you buy at the stove, you know, the brown bottle at wherever you get, typically, whatever percentage it is, is a very, very mild solution. Then it jumps up to medium and
very strong solutions, which I don't recommend getting because that's getting stronger, it's rocket fuel. And also, if you combine, I've seen it even with the diluted, you know, pharmacy convenience store type hydrogen peroxide, if you have organic material, certain organic material will catch fire with hydrogen peroxide, because it's an oxidizer. Right? And chemically, and in physics, fire is considered an oxidizer. So when you burn wood, it's actually oxidized, by the way.
So aggressive oxygen, but don't mess with the proxy, get the dilution. And I don't qualify quantify too much, because I presume that most people are just going to go to a store, grocery store, whatever, whatever, and see hydrogen peroxide and those bottles on the shelf for about a buck or something. And that's the very dilute, fine, just use it just like it is.
Right? Yeah, no reason to mess with that. There are other things that you did suggest diluting some and those were more like the detergents and say, stuff to wash your dishes, which makes sense, actually. And it makes it a lot more efficient and saves you some money to practicality there.
Well, it's already here's the thing, when you go get a big jug of laundry soap, the liquid, let's say even the powder, but let's say the liquid, let's say you get a gallon size of laundry soap, right? Right. For washing clothes, it's usually like a thick syrupy, you know, blue or green or whatever clear color. Most of that 99% of it is filler, only 1% or less is actual detergent. Because if they actually sold you just the detergent in a little tiny bottle, that was enough to do 50,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000
000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000
,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,
million,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000
was sitting there and it was in Japanese Americans English subtitles and you're
saying yeah I wanted to buy the rice that I sell you but I didn't want to sell
it to them because why would you sell someone rice that they can't cook so I
don't know how to cook but what does that mean if you sell someone rice that
they don't know how to cook it won't come out well and they'll say it's your
fault for selling me bad rice no rice was excellent just you can't cook it
right sure right and I've given an analogy on this with quote-unquote white
people in vegan food I found that the most delicious food I've ever eaten was
vegan food prepared I think I mentioned this by the Krishna's Thompson Square
Park on Avenue a they pull up with their school bus and absolutely yes they they
will sit there and if you show up and you hang out with them for a little bit
there they're more than happy to give you a food yeah they put out these
tables and that wonderful rice basmati with coconut and all these dishes are
just cardamom and just delicious vegetarian food so then I started
running into places and veganism became popular talk about late 80s early 90s in
New York it seems like the rest of the country's 10-20 years behind these
things right so always yeah we see it about a decade or two ahead in New York
City if it's something like this oh so I went over to someone's house and I think
they were like the local weed dealer or whatever and they're having dinner and
so we'd have dinner it's vegan and I'm like oh yeah vegan foods delicious it was
terrible it was terrible she's like oh I said this isn't really prepared she
goes oh because it's vegan no I was like no no you suck at cooking yeah
that's what it is you just decided to vegan so you get away with your shitty
cooking and just telling everyone is vegan that's why it doesn't taste good
no you need to stop what you're doing and learn how to cook or just stop cooking
and I've said this many times the person in the house that has the best sense of
smell and the best sense of taste not grandma or mom needs to do the cooking
and in most cases unfortunately it's going to happen it's going to be the dog
but anyway does have a better sense of smell taste yeah so you don't want the
dog cooking but next up from the dog next in line who has the best and by the
way find who you could be living in a group with roommates too I'm not talking
so when I say family I mean gather group you know community whatever enclave
people and the dog is no good because look an opposable thumb is necessary I
mean the fur gets in the way and all that so or hair so so what I'm suggesting
here is this is highly measurable in other words if you're living with a
group of people meaning two or more you can easily test and see who has the
better sense of taste and smell that's very easy to test on your own you don't
have to be a genius to figure out methods for that right so you do that
and that person then is assigned cooking duties unless the one who has the
inferior sense of smell or taste has superior skills already but then the
person who has the superior sense of smell and taste should start learning to
acquire because then when they do acquire those skills in the food quality
will go up period that's it that's there's there's no secret to these
things but again when I recommend cooking these things they must be prepared but
you know I did the the sonic on cooking brown rice number seven or number eight
right you notice how much time I spent on emphasizing the quality of the pot
and the seal and and various other things like that right if you don't have the
right equipment which is not a big deal by the way or a heat diffuser don't
even bother so you know or a sharp knife to slice these things thin don't even
bother because if it does it's not gonna if it doesn't come out tasty it's your
fault it's your fault so you must have the skill to do it this is a DIY we live
in a culture where these things look cooking is not important but you know if
you went back okay so Greek romanticizing the days of old no no
people sucked at cooking always back in the day they sucked at cooking too right
so you have to find the right person that has the interest in doing it right look
and in fairness I mean there might have been a survival as a priority in some
cases and that's fine I mean you know look what works works which is
interesting too because I have one question about this with the quality of
and skill sets I mean frankly when we're younger things taste different I was
thinking about this earlier today because because Frankie was you know
wanting to put ketchup on something and I didn't have any ketchup and and I was
like you know like he would just drown a lot of things in ketchup just because
and that's makes him happy he's happy with it you know but and so there were
certain things that might have made us happy or pleasing to us as children which
changed over time and it does seem to me as though you know you get a little
older and all of a sudden the salt is a little harsher you know to people and all
these things like your tastes change over time yeah you have seven years of
yin seven years of yang I would suggest so what does that mean okay so you'll go
through a period of roughly seven years where you crave salts salty snacks
and then you'll go through a seven year period you'll switch usually in the
springtime where you start craving sweets and anyone recounts their life if
you're older than 30 they'll say yeah you know I don't crave the sweets like I
used to and now I craved you know salty snacks and then and then you switch back
to craving sweet snacks and you know and if you start looking marking when that
started and you know you'll see seven year roughly a seven year cycle I'll
tell you one exception to that and and I think you're exactly right about the
seven and seven and it just it does oscillate back and forth between the two
but there is an exception to it people who have had a particularly bad
childhood based on my observations from you know random sampling I'm talking
about a couple hundred people that I've interviewed and gotten into personal
issues with them a bit it seems to me as though if you had what could be generally
described as sort of a challenging rough or tough childhood you're very much
attracted to sugary things it seems like sugar is one of those things that your
brain calls out for when when you were you know basically he had a rough time as
a child I don't know how to really word that properly but you might know what I'm
getting at here where sweetness is then described desired more the Constitution
like some people will lean more towards sweets their whole life and so
other people will lean more towards salt their whole life but you'll still have
that seven-year cycle so what might what might the person who created sweets at
one point will say well that's too sweet now I want something less sweet then
they'll go back to more sweet right same with the salt that's what I call the
Constitution but being having a rough childhood could be a good thing or a bad
thing it depends on the individual well of course because you could take it as
character building okay this taught me how to overcome adversities and how to
come up with unique solutions for different obstacles or this is something
for me to cry about sure that's different ways people take it yeah but
the thing is the key point that you mentioned is taught like some people
just don't learn I know that I have personal experience with many of them
they just don't learn and I being very giving and time freely give my time I'm
like oh this person really is stuck here and let me work with them and you
give them all this time and you notice oh they can't learn they don't want to
learn although sometimes tell you I don't want to learn you know so if
you're not learning yeah someone who doesn't want to learn and doesn't care
about it or whatever it will have a bad childhood and that will ruin their life
but someone who does view it as a learning experience and wants to learn
how to learn and learn can take that around and view it as something positive
fair enough I also notice that those people that I say are very consistently
on the sugary side their oscillation might be okay now I want these salty and
sweet combination for a while and then they go back to the pure let me just you
know consume I mean telling you what they call oh she oh mommy in Japanese
would be any when I prepare a meal I make sure even if it's a savory dish
that there is a certain amount of sweetness in their natural natural
occurring and if I have something that is sweet like for example you should
always add a little bit of salt and pastry if you don't it tastes kind of
bland yeah it doesn't work right yeah yeah and of course you know the the soft
drink makers what is it like there's a tablespoon of salt in a tablespoon of
sugar and a liter of coke if you couldn't eat the amount of sweetener alone
and or you couldn't eat the amount of salt alone but together it makes a
delicious beverage supposedly there is an acquired taste by the way yeah I
remember when I first started drinking coal as a young child it reminded me of
a cough syrup kind of thing I did not like it until later on in life as a
digestive aid very often when I go out and eat something no I don't by the way
I don't eat out often but if I have a greasy meal like something that requires
a lot of gall to digest I say oh I need a I need a coke coca-cola because that
for syrup phosphoric acid and the and the coca-cola bean and all that combined
is a digestive aid but it's extreme it's extreme it's not good for the body
overall unless you you can take it which by the way I wanted to mention you
brought up earlier it's there's been for every let's say for every two people in
the chat that post something about the rice and the burdock I imagine there's
ten others that are not that are doing it that are not posting the iceberg kind
of yeah you only hear from yeah you only hear from a small percentage of the
people that are literally having the same reaction it's the you know if you
have representative right of a group that's silent let's say right like yeah
like in the old days based on the you know the the information you could
gather everybody who called into a radio show was literally representative of
about a thousand people listening in in fairly populated areas say that that
would be and that was true it was like for this one guy to say this there's a
thousand of them out there it was similar outlook or question or yeah
interest right so with that said it's if I keep it up I'm probably gonna be known
as a Lundberg which means moon mountain by the way you know Berg is mountain and
moon is my moon in German but if you keep listening to what I've been saying
and I keep going I'm gonna be known as the guy who tells everyone to eat
burdock and special kind of brown rice and that's not not at all and what I'm
what I'm trying to do is offer a quick solution to something that is a major
problem which is the food intake of most people and the easiest way to do it is
by simplifying it and and but but not only simplifying it but what once you
simplify it what is suggested as food is so good and so positive to the
individual that you know you use that as a springboard to then get creative with
other things built around that principle and the main thing here is the brown
rice and most people consider a carbohydrate which get away from the
carbs and protein idea there's no such thing there's just one nitrogen molecule
that separates them that's a lie it's a lie that came up a long time ago in
science the other thing is the burdock which is basically a thistle root thistle
plant is one of the most common plants and it's been very typically used as the
most common typical medicinal plant in other words not medicinal like take this
pill and drink drink this potion but to harvest and eat to have a good health
condition typically and it's not in the vernacular nobody talks about it at all
right right I mean you can see remnants of that actually that the fact that it
was commonplace in an ancient sort of way in in old children's stories right
where you literally see that there are you know people or the animal
anamorphic Lee represented animals right that have you know human qualities to
them in the stories or whatever you'll see that this will actually comes up as
one of their staples in their diet different that's that's good yeah the
other thing the other question was about someone putting together a celery mixture
with various other things and herbs and spices and the whole thing about this is
when you are going to eat vegetable even animal by the way you know clean animal
there are qualifications chewing the cut and having a cloven hoof four-legged
animal right so so there is an appearance factor and there's an appearance factor
with vegetable imagine if you're not growing the vegetable find out what it
looks like when it's growing and it has a certain balance in other words how
much of it is above the ground and how much of it is below the ground and then
when you combine it with another vegetable let's say you pick a carrot
which you could say more of the masses underground but you might have equal or
more height above ground less mass so now you want to combine that with a
vegetable that has more mass above ground and less massive below ground so
now they're balanced you see so if you let's say you look at four ingredients
and all four ingredients have a lot of mass under the ground and very little
mass above the ground you combine all those four you're going to take on the
quality of of things that have more mass under the ground and less mass above the
ground right and it's going to have a certain effect on you where if you start
pairing things that are their opposites or balancing geometrically you're going
to have a more balanced energy you know what it when you get energy from one the
energy from the other is going to be different and they're going to balance
for your body because actually we are very balanced the way we are you know
the center naval right and everything revolves around that and then you have
another revolution point so very similarly as the human body is balanced
our intake should be balanced right so that's basically and it's not
eventually if I keep on this burdock and rice thing I'll be known as the burdock
and rice guy and then you fall into I know I'm just saying I don't think it'll
happen I've never been typecast or whatever but although although you were
the Bible guru for a little bit that's what I would say is it's about finding
out something that works really really well that's easily it's temperate you
know it's not tropical where it's easy to get now I thought all this stuff was
easy to get because I always tend to live in a place that's more international and
Tucson Arizona I wouldn't say is very international but it's the biggest
little city I've ever lived in you can pretty much get anything I can get
anywhere else here better than LA I'll tell you that for sure
and you say LA you know no easily that's understandable I mean look it's not
going to be New York but yeah if you have access to things like that on you
know from various sources yeah most of the variety and choices yeah well
actually all the veg that I have mentioned I have three or four sources
here in Tucson I could go and buy them available right so in other places you
know you go to LA may yeah I think you will there because they have an Asian
community you know just because it's Asian is on this this is not a modified
Asian diet these things are also used to grow here but they were there no longer
they were in a careful environment a lot of these things grew by rivers that no
you know what are rivers these days they're industrial dumping grounds right
right or whatever so yeah so these things were part of a subtle ecology that was
wiped out or disregarded but if you live near a park or you know how they
have lands what is it called medians around highways oh yeah dividers and
dividers yeah and there's usually a berm of dirt that you know before the
neighborhood starts if you know what burdock looks like you'll find it
commonly all over the country by the way but you know what it looks like above
ground but you know if it grows in the wild you won't be able to dig it out
that easily I found some in a park and I wanted to get out and only broke off
like a two-inch piece off the top it just cannot pull be pulled out must be
dug dug out or grown in a way where you can harvest it easily so yeah by the way
there is so much crazy you know I always by the way there's a thing going on
right now it was a keto or carbon protein the keto diet deal with the yeah
yeah and I keep you know my joke about the diet or what died there is oh yeah
we keep changing the diets every 15 years because mankind's only been around
for less than a hundred years right so we saw you know we don't know what to do
because we've only been around for less than a century so that makes that make
sense we need to keep changing the diets it's just a joke and the people that
fall for these no carb or it was no red meat then it was no fat right and then
it was no carbs and then it was no gluten then for a little while it's all
red meat just read yeah and then that idiot that it was all about that is all
fat what was his name he fell down and broke crack and said the old was Tucker
Atkins on ice Atkins yeah oh my gosh I'm not but when I heard he fell down
cracked his head on ice I was like good cuz he was not doing good for people and
he went away when he went away fortunately yeah all this stuff is so
stupid so stupid and you could actually you know how I said you could tell the
character of a person by food yes that when people fall for these diets not not
a flaw but it's definitely a fault when you fall for these items shows that you
have no knowledge of the body no knowledge of this that or the other you
want it you want a snapshot of what you should think of of the Atkins diet I
mean Rob Lowe is the like corporate spokesperson for all the Atkins based
products now you know just say it's perfect right that's a Rob Lowe yikes
anyway interesting history on that guy we've gotten into that before so look I
don't want to take up too much more of your time but if you wouldn't mind I
mean a brief a couple of minutes on it has there been any change or anything
that you've noted given given a couple of things first of all we just had to
what they call an eclipse and indeed there is a reason for calling it an
eclipse and that just happened I saw that through some welding goggles old
school welding goggles the welding mask the automatic welding mask I have would
not adjust to it yeah it's pretty neat to get that kind of light on your eye
and it was interesting at nine o'clock in the morning here at 930 you had this
silver sodium electric lamp kind of almost noon kind of sunlight right right
and Madame Calisco who was a metallurgist in France turn of the
century 20th century she was could be attributed you shoot her and Hoshka and
other people like that Germans in that part of the world Austrians about the
effects of solar and moon and stars on crystallization of metals and solutions
and when there was a solar eclipse yeah metals would not crystallize like if you
have a I assure you if you're running like a chrome metal plating plant you
know like for plating doorknobs or bathroom fixtures or whatever you had a
lot of defects today if you were running the shop today so it is important yeah
yeah that's the eclipse couple weird things actually just because of the
electromagnetic kind of atmosphere that I think is also sort of disrupted I had
a little you know a couple issues with computers and things today but thankfully
I was away from the computers again at the flea market I kind of wish I was
able to take pictures of some of the stuff that that Chinese guy was selling I
didn't understand half of what he was saying he was trying to speak English
but it was just fascinating to me that he had a whole bunch of things there that
were totally unrecognizable to not just things like what jewelry shoes what oh
no the the the vegetable section he did have other stuff too oh so he was a
Chinese guy selling groceries okay got it he had to get a picture witness you
know he had some groceries but he also had some of those other things you were
talking about too like you know here's other products too he had like you know
traditional Chinese products no like ribbons for craft the craft working like
you know people that want to get ribbons to make craft projects stuff like that
and then he had a brick yeah brick ribbon fabric stuff and another table
indeed for like well electrical products not electronic but like you know like a
leaf blower and some other things that were you know sounded like he raided
someone's storage locker go ahead seemed like it yes but apparently he also
consistently brings in these vegetables which are that's okay the high point of
my day was was almost as bad as that but go ahead sorry yeah no it was I went to
the flea market did a little work and you know I was hustling a little bit
trying to get some money because we're gonna have a little interruption in the
rated wise coming up in a few weeks guys because I will be on the road and it
will be impossible for me to really sit down and record with the Greek for about
a week so I figured that'll give you time to do that and then when I get back
we'll get right back to it but but you know just little disruption you knew
about this a while ago I told you sure but but anyway I'm just letting people
know in case they don't see him they don't think oh you know they're not
gonna do him anymore that's I think the worst yeah yeah so just wanted to make
that note so before we're done though um just a really quick check-in on has
there been any change or anything that you've taken note of regarding this
situation over there we mentioned the you know the prime ministers and well
nothing yet I mean no it's the same old same old it's just on a different scale
and what I what I predict is there's going to be more conflict other nations
like there'll be another conflict breakout like India Pakistan or there
was a small note on Azerbaijan and Armenia and there's a Turkey might go
invade somewhere they have to do a couple of you know how they do these
forest fires now right you know or the Great Chicago fire you know started by a
cow kicked over a lantern but it the fire crossed over the river right you
know rivers 300 feet wide and started the fire on the other side of its out
in the bullshit right of course so they have to start a few more fires yeah yeah
to make what what's coming more let's say plausible yeah how does a fire
literally stretch you know 300 meters across water 100 meters yeah and this is
Chicago fire I'm talking about which doesn't make sense at all none of this
is going to make sense so you already have the Ukraine battle going on there's
at least 20 or 30 conflicts going on that the media doesn't cover it all on the
continent of Africa hot-hot conflicts yeah that's been that's been a case
minimally I've been able to observe that for the past decade by the way that it's
like why are they not even mentioning this but okay yeah good well because
they're isolated and they have their own world and we're not you know they don't
have a flood myth you know they're like in their own little enclave of reality
and yeah and they're smart they've gotten fortunate that continent has
gotten smart enough not to fall for the white man's tricks you know the banking
tricks too much you know right the way you know why that you know how they do
that is when someone let's say does fault a group of a country or an
organization or an institution or a group of people let's say a village or
neighborhood does fall for the Western banking system stuff they get a lot of
flack from everyone around them for doing so and it's like almost like a
lesson so other people don't yeah but anyway you'll have those conflicts but
I'm talking about more Eastern Asia well South let's see South Central Asia a few
more battle breakouts and then some bad shit happening in the West probably a
few false flag type you know what a truck will drive to a crowd of 200
people or a couple of wild shootings you know some impossible guy with a 40
rounds and manages to shoot 120 people you know you know some you know you
don't have a traveling stage show for that they kill real people they kill
people oh no no no yeah that's the thing I never by the way I mean I would argue
with you if you said oh people don't really die because I think that's one of
the most idiotic things no it's a state you know look the more realistic it
looks the better so therefore yeah yeah absolutely well just just the last
question of clarification though when you say the West I mean it doesn't
necessarily mean what they call the United States it could be Europe right
or yeah I say from from Germany West all the way to California when I say West
fair enough yeah it's all of what's considered Europe proper and the states
here including South America okay well then then there you have it I mean
potentially what you're saying is looks if something really insane happens in
Canada even still counts yeah it's gonna get it's gonna go crazy but to justify
the means for what's coming which is basically a religious war the only thing
that I've noted and again this is why I tried to tie it to cosmic censorship and
maybe I did it incorrectly last time but just really fast is that you know I'm
taking note that there are people that are I don't know if it's self
censorship or if it is a condition of just you know the situation here but I
mean literally you have people that deny realities where it's like look can we
even begin the conversation by accepting that this or that happened there are
people that just know that's just not the reality regardless of what you put
in front of them regardless of what you can demonstrate or etc etc they just go
with an NPC yeah yeah which is 90% of the population by the way yeah sad state
of affairs in my mind but it's always been that way so we're welcome to a
planet Earth right you've been on this planet for more than an hour you should
Accept that as fact, yeah.
Exactly.