A sonic event a 79 on rated Y and here we go now a couple of contacts a couple
things happening in the chat room yes there was something mentioned regarding
the last sonic now I did take a little extra time putting it out so you'd have
to check out 78 to understand this but yeah apparently you're gonna be doing
something in the very near future Greek but how you doing I'm doing okay yeah
we're just talking about water and stuff but we'll get into water again soon I
put out there we'll be doing like a water seminar that's open to anyone by
the way people you know people you don't know it's just we're gonna do it on
Skype because I know the tech and the tech is solid more solid than zoom or
anything else I've seen Google someone did a international Google something
Google has their own version what a piece of crap oh there's terrible yeah
there's horrible yeah oh yes so Skype if you don't like it too bad but yeah it's
it because you don't recognize what's good a lot of people I know and do Skype
I'm like you're not really thinking right you don't really see what's right in
front of you do you and it's amazing when zoom came out how many people ran
to it and just Skype I was like you are not paying any attention at all
whatsoever I got your number though I see where you're at yeah you know where
the crowd runs yeah it's total garbage all the other stuff and I'm not look I
don't Skype doesn't give me anything to say that I'm just telling you so yeah
actually I mean they don't give me anything either I've been using it for I
don't even know how long is probably probably a little less less time than
you but still yeah it's the most reliable thing I mean what are you gonna
yeah they've tried to downscale it like nothing over 20 megabytes and this and
that for files and it's it's the bomb diggity it's the bomb diggity yeah you
know what's weird though I think they don't do that to you on Apple devices
oddly enough like they do that only on the devices that are native to the
company that owns it which yeah I want to get the kind of thing we were
mentioning also don't if you guys have computers with hard drives ditch it it's
like having a cassette player in your car get away from all that magnetic
SSD is the way to go and just look on Craigslist try to get a used machine I
fired up some stuff today that had a hard drive I was like even though I was
like oh my gosh because I'm just using a laptop and then the stupid rectangle
which is my seven from ten years ago now almost or eight years ago whatever yeah
what are we and 13 or 14 there or something yeah it doesn't matter to me I
mean the you know to me the operating system is the problem I think there's a
way to reroute or something that's called it also works more like a
computer but yeah the hard drive stuff is just silly nilly stuff it's just get
away from it if you can it's get it's lighter less electricity you know SSD
whatever I know it sounds snobbish but you know oh by the way back in the 1980s
I was at the Chicago Electronics Show when the big thing was the Philips and
the Sony CD player and I was talking to someone there and he's oh no yeah this
is all coming up but eventually it won't even have that it'll be on a chip and he
had a device that was the precursor to the you know the mp3 players right right
right this is back in the 80s so right now there's even more holographic stuff
ready to you know that's being used and I don't think society society at large
is going to get it might be into that but anyway yeah get away from it a
spinning magnetic disc hard drive are you joking you know I mean yeah they've
been they've really overplayed that junk for a long time should have never
been anyway enough of a rant about that but yeah back to the water Skype we'll
just put it out I have to I'm either gonna wing it and put images up in the
text or just do a presentation like a PowerPoint or something to walk everyone
through it because okay that just a little thing what's going on with the
water kind of retracted I was past few months I was out showing the scalerator
mark one and all that which was good success and moved quite a few of them
for it being so new with people in the water industry and whatever and I've
noticed that there is a communication problem no matter how intelligent the
person sounds right member they still can't follow directions no matter who it
is and right now I'm the only ones that will be you know I've seen pictures of
installation like why is that like that that's not how it's supposed to be you
know and right so so right now they're all gonna be emanating from me right
here in Tucson like in other words I'm not sending any more out at the moment
I'm gonna just try to get as many as I can within a 50 mile radius here just
because this this is a new device it's well on the surface no what I mean I'm
the only one right that's that can explain it pervade or whatever the last
thing I want is it being you know not installed at the right application the
right location the right following certain protocols I'll get into all
that with and I'll demonstrate pictures of what how it's been being used and it
still works by the way it's just not optimal it's like I don't know following
direction seems to be like I don't know I'm almost impossible well you know it's
not bad about that as you can almost do a YouTube University on it and if you
record that whole thing one way or another you can record it into a video
file and somebody could upload it to a platform whether it's YouTube or not
yeah I don't mind if they do actually that I think I might have to be
presented a little better I'll probably do I'll get one of the spare laptops I
have by the way the reason I'm looking for other computers because I'm using a
laptop as a main computer and a laptop is like a Swiss Army knife right you
don't use it all the time for everything so you know so anyway you can
get a fresh new computer for a different kind of stuff and do a
PowerPoint if anybody knows how to do all that stuff reach out let me know and
I could send you the information and you could put it together if you like or
whatever if you're interested just images and maybe some text files because
it's going to be very interesting I just want to show what's going on with it
and state of Meg let me just put it this way magnetic reactors they have nothing
it has nothing to do with magnetism as people have been using including the
physicists and scientists scientists I'm spelling with a PS why right so this is
we're going in new territory this is completely new physics completely and
it's all tangible I mean if you've got like $2 in your pocket and there's a
magnet you know basically you could build stuff right so this is nothing
elaborate I remember someone you saw we said group Skype calls more than a
decade ago someone who was a venture capitalist for IP like ideas like take
people's scientific ideas and you know get investors and he says oh I'm gonna
have a call tonight talk about this so he starts talking I'm like I don't
really care about that he's like why is it because you need like this expensive
thing and this thing that's hard to get whatever don't you got anything you can
make in your kitchen or buy it the hardware store to make something unique
you know it's like you know how they hear all these scientific discoveries
and you're like that stuff is out of reach I think it's coincidental how all
these new scientific discoveries always shown like the materials and the methods
are out of reach from common people right I think it's by design well it's
like a little you yeah it's like the guys who tell you look I've got the best
way it's an absolutely foolproof formula for you to make you know all sorts of
money and this and that and then you get there and you realize yeah only if you
have X amount to invest if you have certain things that you can put into it
one way or another and it's like well if I don't have that to begin with what's
the point of even being here except oh I already paid this guy a fee so he's
making money right sounds like you fall for an old one I remember I'm not being
accusatory but I say that when people bring that up because back in like 1974
on the back of the magazine that I was checking out the magazine right like a
mark was a comic it was mad I was into mad magazines there were lots of
magazines that had similar things yeah the backs in that if you put a dollar in
an envelope and send it here we'll show you how to make money and with magazines
so I did that and sent me back a letter and he says you put an ad in a magazine
and you tell people to send a dollar and and you send them a letter that says
how you make money in magazines right it's a closed-loop system right yeah no
no but that that is funny but that is one of the things they actually did in
comic books and mad magazine I think too maybe they did it in that they
offshoot the the you know the bad copy cracked right a couple of things like
that they probably was later yeah yeah basically it was instructions on how to
put an ad in the magazine which was fairly cheap back then right and tell
people to put a dollar in there that was just a close-up by the way the same
magazines in the back a live monkey for 20 bucks which is $500 in today's money
by the way I think by the way because gold is over 2,000 announced that means
that the Federal Reserve note in trade value is less than a penny by the way
so the dollar buys less than a penny than it did when gold was $20 by the way
a 20 is the score so you know in the in the Westerns they'd say you know I've got
a score to settle people think it was a grudge no doesn't mean the guy owed you
a gold piece right so it right now because it's over 2,000 right do the
math but right 20 into 100 right mm yeah 20 times 100 right so it's less 100 is a
hundredth so yeah so the dollar is now less than a penny buying power so I just
want everybody but anyway back then you can get a monkey in the mail and someone
did get it it was a it was a rumor that got out pretty quick and by the end of
the day when I went to go see the monkey was already gone because the parents
came home and you know how people have arachnophobia I think the mother had a
monkey phobia she flipped out and I didn't get to see the monkey but I saw
all the packaging and all that and it was about a cardboard box inside of a
cardboard box with poo in it and grass you know dry hay so they did get the
monkey everyone witnessed it and I think they took it away to the ASPCA or
something but yeah you could get monkeys in them so I didn't directly witness the
monkey but I witnessed everything else it's about it getting there it's got
like and then later on I saw people you know I didn't get involved in these
things but I saw other people do it like you know get all dedicated to Amway for a
minute yep you know isn't and Rubbermaid or Tupperware and I'm sorry and then
Rubbermaid put Tupperware out yeah because they decided to get into it also
Tupperware was a big yeah but Amway was big I was like yeah I'm so funny it's
like well that sounds interesting and I and then I started recommending it to
people because people I knew parents did it or older siblings did it right and it
was like $10 for a bottle laundry detergent normally be $2 I was like that
doesn't sound right how you know remember that yep she's not how it was
yeah I think it was really those what they call multi-level marketing yeah well
the only interesting part about it was the only useful part of it was that they
they started trying to get you to sell the cleaning products and when you sell
the cleaning products actually it's same methodology that you are talk about
where look you don't need this detergent you can water it down and still use it
because it doesn't need to be made this way and stuff like that like you know
actually putting the thing in the spray bottle and stuff like that like if you
follow those sorts of directions along with selling your stuff you could sell
a year's worth of you know what I'm saying instead of the $2 versus $10 yeah
but you have it now for 12 months instead of spending $2 so they were
selling concentrates yeah yeah what's cheaper and shipping that way to imagine
exactly instead of a gallon of laundry detergent you buy like a cup of it and
you know how many more you can fit on a trailer and how much more value right if
you charge this well right and as I said you know even if it is a $20 or a $10
bottle versus a $2 bottle okay it's five times but if you could use it for
12 months instead of buying a $2 one every month you've just cut your cost in
hand which made sense but that was the part that nobody would follow right so
you know it's like anyway oh yeah they use it normally yeah by the way when I
was at a place in California and and I was there like months at a time and you
know I didn't get very domestic meaning like I didn't I lived there but I didn't
get too domestic we're gonna do shopping it was for a few days worth of food or
whatever I was trafficking in high-end water spring to oh yeah and I'd go in
the apartment area had a laundry area and I was like you know I haven't bought
laundry soap I need to get laundry soap so this is mostly white people here
they're not very frugal or they don't see what they're going or by the way
white has nothing to do with the color your skin just meaning bland so in the
laundry room they have the the garbage can and the garbage can was full of empty
tied you know the various liquid detergent bottles right because people
went out they throw it over they're not gonna bring it up to the apartment
again so I said I bet if I go through this garbage gets a clean garbage can
it's a laundry room garbage can right it was basically lint lint from the dryer
and empty bottles and boxes of soap right so it within a few minutes I pulled
out about four or five bottles and I looked in there I took the big you know
the big-ass cap I look in there soap in there soap in there soap in there I put
water in one of them slowly rinsed it out you don't want to agitate it too
much because you have nothing but suds rinsed into the next bottle rinse in
the next bottle before I knew it I had two inches of soap diluted in a bottle
right and I could do my laundry I don't have to stop what I'm doing go buy
laundry soap as a matter of fact they use it for another month so that is like
listen don't buy laundry soap communal laundry room they've got they throw away
their laundry bottles they're still soap residue and they're diluted a little
right because it's super concentrated right because as the bottle gets to be
low the dry out right and you'll have like a you know a pretty decent amount
you know a couple days or weeks worth of laundry just that's being thrown away
on the residue on a big bottle right exactly so people it sounds you sound
like a bag lady or a crazy person when you say that but it's the point you see
it's the idea of the waste and all that so yeah exactly yeah always the case by
the way I haven't bought anything it's time for me to go out and buy dish soap and I
think the last time we've got that was around the midsummer you know the last
year right what you know the pagan year right so that's a long time because if
you don't dilute these things it's like you know you run out of juice like oh
you put it on your list and not every time you shot maybe every other time and
it's like now it's like you're hardly and everything's just as clean by the
way so yeah well as long as you're getting the same result I don't see why
you shouldn't do it you know if you're getting a bad result obviously don't
right but you're not gonna if you if you do it the way that you described a long
time ago in these Sonics here it works just fine I mean oh it does yeah when
you when it's diluted and you cut it comes out of a sprayer it hits such a
large area versus concentrated you put it a little dab on a sponge right that's
not going anywhere even doesn't matter how concentrated it is you know right
right yeah so anyway it's just it's it has nothing to do with laundry soap
Greeks lost his mind what is he doing going through garbage no it has to do
with efficiency and there you are you actually paying attention you know well
and that's the thing is why waste things that are just as useful you know it I'm
not telling you you know pick every bit of food out of the garbage right well
that's that's the other point the other day I brought up restaurants throw away
anywhere between 10 or 20 percent of the food they buy because the patrons don't
eat it so and I was part of a Vietnamese restaurant a decade ago short story made
long here or long story made short I fought the enemies for this place was
off it's kind of like an industrial part of town they're really good and I went
there once and their bathroom was unfinished I went there a week later
again bathroom still unfair said hey listen you guys make good soup here why
is your bathroom finish it was new construction oh my uncle he's 85 years
old he's I'll finish your bathroom I got a redo the most of the plumbing and all
that so then I'll do it you know professional job for you and we do a
barter and soup and they said great so I had like free meals for nine months
for me and the wife there right maybe more nice and it was great but I watched
how much food was thrown away because I would you know when I you know I was like
part of the restaurant now right and you know why because we made fun of white
people anyway that's as you say that yeah yeah anyway by the way with your
Vietnamese I just like South Vietnamese all right when you get invaded if your
country gets invaded because you're having problems in your country that's
like if you believe that the part of parts of the country that are having
difficulty with each other are gonna stay separate and you can join one side
you're an idiot what will happen is if you're a foreigner you come in even
though it looks like those two sides within the country are fighting they're
gonna band together against you both how do I know this because when we had ex
military veterans and stuff come into the restaurant you know they'd sometimes
say I was in Vietnam and the people the patrons at the restaurant would say oh
yeah my father he worked with the Americans always you know oh thank you
that's great but when the restaurant closed and we sat back and had shots
and had dinner like oh yeah we would hunt the Americans with bamboo spears we
would make traps the same traps we would make for wild pigs and we'd catch them
and cut them up into pieces you know yeah so and I said because yeah the
Americans are further you're having supposedly a issue and by the way it was
communist north and south whatever no no no the north was Soviet I'm sorry the
north was Chinese and the south was Soviet they're both communists I hate
to mention to you right yeah they had more of a Soviet influence in the south
and more of a Chinese it wasn't communist versus non-communist so look
at your look at what was really going on well the north appeared to really you
know and first of all there's another issue there too and that's religion
which was a problem which nobody talks about in the history books because the
no Buddhist versus the Catholics was a problem there yeah yeah what but Buddhism
is part of Catholic in other words if it Buddhism exists for more than it's part
of the Pope's approval yeah well you know the whole thing is about to make
everybody feel separate you know and fight each other instead of you know and
by the way the most people would say they make us fight each other so we
don't fight them you don't have to fight the powers that be at all all you gotta
do is stop using what they're putting out and do everything with conditions
that's all there's no you know people say we're fight the government why why
didn't fight any government ever that's why I keep saying the Revolutionary War
was a hoax you know the American Revolution was a hoax all you got to do
is just okay you stamp tax or whatever you whatever whatever under these
conditions that's all and just don't feed it it's all a hoax there is no such
thing as a proper revolution it's foolish it's it doesn't work it doesn't
matter what good it's all it's all you know the fake history all you got to do
with any anybody in power all you got to do is say yeah I see what you want
you're talking about can you define it and these are the conditions sure or just
don't feed them right right so that's the thing if you don't participate then
they have nothing to work with so you know there's no fighting yeah it's all
that's it's such a hoax it's such a hoax you know all the stuff we've been fed
from all sides all right and that's why you know even even in the preparation
you know the people that get all I'm gonna prepare you know because there's
gonna be this you know situation we're gonna have this civil war and all you're
doing really is just lining somebody's pocket because you're gonna buy all the
stuff well well if you say okay hold on this is more than semantics if you say
I'm going to prepare means that you're preparing to prepare so why prepare to
prepare why don't you always remain in a prepared state in other words whenever
right it's like when you you know when I leave the house for example I have my
shoes on right sometimes I don't wear socks as I bring a wallet I bring a
lighter some smoke something to drink right you know with me right I mean you
know that's I mean isn't it's a don't you when you wherever you dwell when you
plan on going out whatever it's let's say to commute to work or go out
somewhere don't you bring a few things with you don't be like your keys right
maybe whatever whatever are you do you call that preparation or is that what
you normally do to be more self-sufficient right or to be more I
don't know I want to call it independent whatever so when someone says they need
to get preppy that means they're preparing to prepare to prepare prepare
prepare prepare he sits like looking in the mirror that infinite never it's
never gonna happen right right means that yeah you should always be that bug
out bag thing I've always done that my entire life always I always a as a
matter of fact that you can ask the wife say what's that's my homeless coat
what's that the homeless coat everybody should have a look I call a homeless
coat it's like if you had to leave with just one thing right it's a certain coat
you have and it's got its water resistant it has lots of pockets right
it could be made if the liner is removable it's got a hood so in other
words any temperature you right well-suited that what I liked is they
had one in Europe for homeless people where the coat actually turns into a
seen that yeah you're giving it away to homeless people right there's a shelter
it's a the coat itself becomes a shelter okay that's your you know I've always
you know we've been together for more than two decades as that's the homeless
I've been telling people since the 80s you know where's your homeless coat
what's your homeless guy if you had to grab one thing and that's all you had
you know what would it be is it ready you know so you got lots of pocket you got
cash and some you got your knives in the other right you got some sewing thread
some you know bet right a little bit of everything in the coat right yeah yeah
and that's what you end up carrying you know what one way or another you're
gonna you're gonna wind up creating that if you because I you know I wound up
homeless at one point and that that's what you have is you okay now I've got
my pocket for my clean cloth right which is always good to have around
regardless of what conditions you're in and then you got a couple of you know
your your basic medical supplies sort of stuff right might be a bottle of
rubbing alcohol that I would have with me a small one you know things like
that we're essentially actually better off instead of rubbing alcohol just
drinkable alcohol a flask yeah all these things in other words always have right
because they flood the drink the hard liquor will work just as well as right
it actually does yeah you're not you're not a Russian aviator because the right
member of the Russian aviators they would save the ice the alcohol instead
of de-icing the wings on test flights and so the wings would load up with ice and
they'd crash these MIGs and they figured out that they weren't the pilots were
deliberately not de-icing the MIG to save the alcohol so they started giving
alcohol out instead of that but then they were too drunk to fly so you can't
win yeah they're the gun they're either gonna be too drunk to fly or they're
gonna be crashing the planes that's the Soviet Army Soviet Air Force right there
you go yeah so is it the alcohol problem or the people right and that's
why they also started making the MIG so they didn't last more than a few flights
anyway because I don't know about that you know the MIG is the fastest
airplane well up until the Americans decided you know the Americans are given
the go-ahead and it's American technology the the impellers the way to
make the anyways long story but all the titanium used in production comes from
Russia anyway but a lot of you guys know about aviation but nothing nothing was
faster than the MIG other than the SR-71 but the SR-71 didn't have any
armament so no look speed I understand but what I'm saying is they didn't
really make a lot of flights because they weren't very durable they didn't
need to be oh yeah I guess not yeah yeah that was the way it was explained to me
is that well look they didn't need to make a lot of flights because they knew
they were not gonna last and they were designed like that I'm like wow why
would you do that yeah and that was another power play you know the the
whole political situation as far back as you can see it is just yeah you know
I think I've gone over in private Skype calls and maybe other stuff with you
maybe as much not as much with the Parthians you know everyone talks about
the power of the Roman Empire was more of a Roman era but the Romans could not
go east of you know the Jordan River in that part of the they would get their
asses kicked by the Parthians right and it wasn't until a few hundred years
later that the Romans said hey why can't we be friends is there a song like that
why can't we be friends right yeah so cuz they yeah but everyone thinks the
Romans were invincible and they were to a degree in the European market let's
just say but when they came to you know southwestern Asia no as a matter of fact
they even mentioned to people you know the Knights in shining armor you saw in
the Middle Ages and all that oh yeah that was nothing new that's all barred
from the Parthians who had that for hundreds of years prior to that right
because I something popped up recently where oh the new technology in the
Middle Ages where they use our what do you mean new technology is already a
thousand years old the Europeans just decided to use it oh my gosh so it's
easy to distort you know everything so no absolutely true absolutely speaking
of distortion I had a wonderful call with a wonderful individual recently from back
east and I said you know I'm gonna be doing a sonic later with Ocelli what do
you think I should talk about he says yeah it's the new year so why don't you
talk about something hopeful give people some of us said hold on a second how
could be the new year at the end of the 10th month he's like yeah I get you so
you know I wanted to spend a just a few seconds on that yeah is no matter where
you are you know on the other part of the world it's midsummer right you know
South America all the other places yeah down there so and we're up here right
cold it doesn't matter the time is reckoned very similarly if not the same
in other words they have Christmas in Australia it's summertime right on the
beach they're right so anyway how how obvious is it that septum is 7 octo is
8 specially octave no of them is 9 and deaths and this 10 it was destined I
think is even more obvious right of course except the word decimate is
never used right when the people who still you say with their estimate that's
all you can pretend and they've usually use that word estimate refer to total
destruction it's not accurate yeah that destination is way too often used to to
project the idea of complete destruction but as you said yeah it's not only by
a tenth yeah yeah it's a good again a Roman thing so and it's like apocalypse
means to reveal apocalyptic yeah reveal yeah so if everything is destroyed when
it's revealed oh my gosh what kind of a world is this right anyway the whole
thing is it's very obvious what's going on and the thing I've mentioned a few
sonics ago is that everything is an intelligence op what you do is you put
out stuff that is so blatantly contrary to what it's supposed to be and watch
who goes for it and if everyone goes for it that means that you could pretty much
say anything contradictory like 19 Arab hijackers with box cutters vaporized the
World Trade Center and people will believe it right or right you know what
was who was the comedian who I remember he talked he did a JFK joke where they
went to the museum where Oswald's opposed to oh yeah this is very accurate
because Oswald wasn't there right right he says yeah I went to the 6-4 museum
and I'll tell you I look right in that window and a whole bit and I'll tell you
it was extremely historically accurate Oswald still not in that window brilliant
you see the simplest comedy it works the best so and actually the what is comedy
stuff that's so simple that everyone can relate to but doesn't talk about right
so so what's going on with all this stuff doesn't matter what it is is is an
intelligent everything is backwards and I think it's not it's by design it's by
design because you want to use it to measure engage just like the mercury in
a tube that's graduated with numbers you look at where which number is that it's
that it's that and we all say that's what the temperature is right just like
that it's a measurement tool all of these things that are being put out and
it's in then what happens is if you have the majority go for it then anyone
that's contrary to that then it's it's open it's open game you could say
anything about them you could say oh those people in their contract oh they're
elitist oh or they're geniuses they don't think like once or they're
terrorists or they're crazy you see what I mean right because there's no way to
gauge anymore anything you see so you can so if you're not part of if you're
not going along with the collective or the normal think it can go anyway for
you don't know and you can steer it into that direction in other words you can be
called right you know how many times have you seen people go to court for the same
exact traffic ticket one guy gets dismissed the other guy pays the fine
the other guy gets a double fine but the other guy has to go to jail for the
same thing right right so yeah so basically it can go any anything to go
anyway anyway you know like the one guy could be called you know what they call
them freedom fighters right or martyrs or whatever or they could be terrorists
right so the same thing yeah it goes either way and that's tag that along
with what I've said that all subjects and I mean this because I've been
speaking to people professional people lately in their fields and I'm like oh
my gosh this person says they do this they know nothing very little about it
so someone who is in a professional field you what it is I'm not gonna I
don't have to say it's irrelevant any professional field they what they're
working knowledge in that professional field is as not any more than anyone can
learn within a few hours just by punching on the keyboard on that subject they
don't have to use any more than that so it's like everybody's getting some kind
of like just floating slacking along no matter what they're doing it's it's
amazing how it is so attach that to the idea that I've always given that all
fields all subjects are wide open for study doesn't matter what subject if you
want to let's say get into a subject that's already has a domain or a
professional category let's say like brain surgery and most of you say I'm
gonna study brain surgery most people are gonna be like oh that's so
intimidating actually if you spend one week on the computer studying brain
surgery you will have about the amount of functional knowledge that your
typical brain surgeon actually has to know to do brain surgery believe it or
not not more than a week's worth of study that's all they're using it's
insane how soft and weak and how would you say underused knowledge and things
are right so what I'm trying to say let's go back to brain surgery or
neurology or whatever specifically brain surgery okay if you studied for a
few weeks or a month brain surgery and you actually applied what you studied
with just online you would actually be able to perform and be at the top of the
field right this is how little knowledge is being used by any field at the moment
couple that with everything being automated oh my gosh even before it was
automated they were hardly hardly applied anything okay so what's going on
is I've always I've said this before it's a testament to the robustness of
the human condition humans are tough so for example back with medicine the only
reason you have doctors offices and emergency medicine emergency room is
because the those that are controlled the earth don't want any of that at all
the only reason it exists is because if it didn't exist there would be public
outrage so what they did was they set up the medical community so it gives the
absolute minimum of presence in society absolute minimum of presence in society
and does the absolute minimum right I'm talking about even the specialists right
just to prevent public outrage and they also have to throw in there's actually
more effort being put into propaganda and media and all that about medical
stuff right I don't have to say the pandemic to promote it as being something
wonderful right and the people believe that more than what they actually see
them doing you know it's insane yes let's forget about the actual results
it's about the expertise and and the knowledge of how the system works really
that's what you go to anybody for anymore is their knowledge of how the
system works not really about their particular profession I mean we talk
about law all the time and that's a perfect example right the lawyer doesn't
know law he just knows he just knows where the court is he knows who he's
got to talk to and where he's got to put the papers yeah anything up to
anything of the case he's like oh did you cooperate with the judge you do what
the judge said I'm like what judge isn't supposed to say anything he's a judge
right what are you talking about I'm getting railroaded here oh well it
doesn't really work that way you know I'm like oh yeah really it's I said it
saying doesn't really work that way how about I tell you it's not working at
all and you guys are yeah yeah you guys are just playing a different game here
and calling it something else and that's what it comes down to is your your
medical professional doesn't know anything about me it's the same thing
same thing you wouldn't believe you ever get a message that it's the wrong
number but they leave a message anyway yeah and I think I've gone over my
greeting oh yeah I love that but when I side-track that have a greeting on the
answering machine guys when you call it's a woman with a British accent and
she says you have reached the number that number that you have just dialed if
you believe you've dialed it an error hang up and dial it again now you
wouldn't believe how many times they see a number that I didn't recognize and they
let it ring they get the greeting and they hang up and then like 10 seconds
later 30 seconds later they call back right away I don't know who's calling I
know a lot about that person that greeting gives it up what it tells me
is this person doesn't know how to listen they're not listening all they
got was dial it again or something yeah yeah instead of let instead of letting
the greeting got right so yeah yeah so it teaches me a lot right now it's
radical analog engine tuning right with a British accent like I thought there
was really some kind of what is that I'm like anyway yeah so yeah so you set up
these things to let you know what people really are but anyway on the phone
with the pandemic you wouldn't believe how many some number that I'm using must
be similar to some medical place the nurses would call back and leave a
message and not even listening to the greeting and saying that yeah you can
come and visit the doctor only if you show that you've gotten your vaccine and
this is the nurse's doctor's office putting this on the people that's
criminal yeah you're talking about criminals yeah so anyway I don't want to
hear about Nazis or this or that or Ku Klux Klan or all these other things what
was it what was it Oh Mel Brooks blazing saddles like the worst people in the
world memory showed like some Nazis and Ku Klux Klan and like what Americans
consider to be the worst right parts of society right in the end right do you
remember that movie is the film there's a whole string of like you know all the
worst societies maybe maybe a couple of communists were thrown in there all the
propaganda stuff right they did an open call for like the worst people and yeah
yeah that's right yeah and who showed up yeah so you expecting to see in some
film to tell you that the medical community is in that league also are you
is that what the public is waiting for it's not gonna happen guys or the legal
community legal community was even car mechanics there are films out there
that show you that but but here's the thing they're not taken seriously right
it's like the message the message on the machine that tells you you reach the
number that you're supposed to have reached that just tells you yeah you got
the right number according to this and they still hang up and call back yeah
one of the things also the conversation I had before we started this sonic was
that it's very similar to this how it's all gangsterism in a sense tribalism
right and it's like feudalism but tribalism but the problem with using
that term is when you have tribalism those that are leading the tribe have
care for the tribe they make sure the tribe is well equipped that they're
strong they're fed they have weapons right right this type of tribalism is
weakening the tribe exactly exactly because when you actually have a tribal
leader they care about that that's the only reason why they are a leader is
because they maintain the strength of the tribe that is how that works on a
ground level it makes sense but when you have people that are you know
adopting these false tribes right these tribes that have nothing to do with them
but yet okay you're gonna put on a uniform you're gonna put on a certain
color you're going to wear certain things you're gonna identify yourself a
certain way that it you're given all these false prescriptions right to
identify you in some fake tribe well of course your fake tribalism doesn't get
anywhere real tribalism actually works yeah real yeah right and feudalism I'm
looking forward to the days of the the anarchist feudal warlords again because
at least there you know if anybody's ever had any dealings with the mob and
the if you watch like Sopranos or something like that which is very
accurate by the way they are far more honorable than attorneys and doctors and
government people and priests and all that stuff right that you see you far
more honorable if they tell you they're gonna do something they do it and if
they don't members of their own organization admonish those who didn't
follow through you don't even have to you know what I mean exactly that's the
thing I've always said that that is the one guarantee you have is well two things
really you know they wear better suits than politicians and they absolutely do
some of the things they say they're gonna do because otherwise there's no
reason for them to exist yeah they enforce their own yeah they enforce
their own right you know and that's and that's how you get a more honorable
result regardless of what the activity is look if you if you go into an
agreement you better follow it because they sure as hell are gonna hold up
there and yeah it's not like Darth Vader it was at the second movie we kept
changing the deal right with Colt 45 was the actor 40 Billy Dee Williams yeah
yeah yeah right I bet if you look at this one black people and Asian people
do not age right and some Latinos also you ever see like you know I don't know
if it was Billy Dee Williams or somebody so he's got to be in his 80s and he
looks like he's in his late 50s or something I see some actors like that
he still looked good in the last Star Wars movie they just like dropped him
into that Star Wars movie a couple years ago and it's like dude that's 40 years
later look at him I know yeah yeah he looks like he's 10 years he looks like
he's 10 years maybe right right right and yeah I don't bring him up as he
kept telling Darth Vader you know you it's not our original agreement you
know he's like you think I'm that big Darth Vader's like you don't think I'm
being fair with you I don't alter our agreement further so this is so what
they have to show you that stuff and like Darth Vader by the way I think
Vader's is cool as shit so but anyway I mean this is the stuff that's going on
right in front of people and they still take party sides and all this other
stuff it's like whoa there's something wrong here but just maybe to end this
summer on another thought because no matter how they keep altering the
agreement Greek and they keep adjusting the people keep adjusting to it so it
doesn't matter if he alters the agreement but again that's why Darth
Vader's not in the mob because he's just on his own league but they're that
league that mentality is being pushed on people constantly and they're going for
it right and they don't have to and but the thing is also if you really want to
find out like there's a the silent part we've segue we talked about the voice in
your head is not you and it changes as you change right if you were to make a
big lifelong change like let's say for example you're just strolling along or
whatever as a normie and you decide to become a Scientologist right and you
study all that stuff and now you join that group the voice in your head will
change they're gonna have to put another one in your head who's they I
think I've gotten into it yes it's a spiritual thing they're gonna have to
get rid of the one that's giving you the voice in your own tone that you think is
you and switch to another voice that is more in line with what the Scientology
narrative is but if you're so lucky or fortunate they may not have one
available right away so you might have a few days or a few weeks even before they
find their replacement for that voice in your head and you will have an extreme
sanity and peace during that time that's why very often when you hear people I
converted to Buddhism I became a Scientologist or a vegan or blah blah
change like that when they first change over and you can relate to them speak
to them they are so happy and they are so at peace it's not because of the
organization that they're going to it's that they change the narrative in their
head now another being has to be dispatched to assign a new dialogue in
your head that you think is you see I think that's scary they should make a
movie about they really should because that perfectly explains to me why it is
you know when people get full on you know they make that decision and they
go okay I've given myself to the JES oh same same doesn't matter what you give
yourself to but they give themselves over to that and they are so joyous and yeah
for an interim for an interim and I looked at him and I go wow how do you
get that joyous over something that you know first of all I know you're
following some BS here but nonetheless because they've gone into that
changeover mode they are elated it is the thing the reason why is because the
being that most people think well the voice in the head that people think is
their own voice is actually another being doing that right and that being
may not be suited to provide the narrative the voice in your head because
you've just changed your narrative so they have to dispatch another they have
an entire organization for that and or it's better to put another being in your
head than to try to train the current one right and in that interim it may
sometimes not true sometimes they might find a replacement overnight but
typically when I when I talk to people and seeing this it takes usually about a
week to a month sometimes to find another being to give them the voice and
during that time now there is when they they're elated and also when the new
being comes in they they notice a radical change like maybe they didn't
make the right decision but they already told everyone so they have to stick to it
and they romanticize that time right so when it was quiet when the being wasn't
in their head giving them the voice so here's the point the point is this find
if you can convincingly change your ways it doesn't matter what it is you you
meat eater become vegan become what really it could be religion social
change whatever whatever join the KKK or the Nazi neo-nazi party right whatever
you found your passion found your purpose you found a better way you're
enjoying the Red Cross I like that was a movie The Black Klansman right yeah I
haven't seen it I have to stream that but you got to make fun of all this
stuff because none of it is and I'm sure there are black Klansmen by the way so
the whole thing is just a radical change but you have to be convincing enough you
will find peace and quiet because not because of the organization again I'm
repeating myself it's very important to remember it's not what it is it's how
it's being done in other words you are changing your entire outlook on life
because when someone let's say becomes a born-again chicken sandwich like the
Chick-fil-a right and and yeah that's not true they're a Christian organization
I know yeah I called the born-again chicken sandwich so anyway when you do
anything like that anything it doesn't matter doesn't matter what are you go
become a Satan I'm not saying Oh Greek says become KKK or become a Satanist no
no it doesn't matter just change you can dedicate you're gonna notice doesn't
matter what you change to again I can't underscore emphasize that enough a
quietness okay so why not why not evict the voice in your head by constantly
anticipating it whenever you hear the voice in your head just say okay I hear
you what do you have to say next but you're not supposed to say that to your
own self right they'll say oh my gosh they he this one knows what's going on
and seek that quiet now if you can't do that enough I'm not saying that they
won't ever leave you alone no because what will happen is they'll bypass the
one that they were sending over and they're gonna send the swap team over
what I mean is they're gonna send one that's very hard to find but they do
have them and this one will anticipate your all of your moves so you're gonna
think you're psychic because you can tell what's gonna happen in five minutes
for ten minutes or next week and you could tell what people are thinking and
you know what it's provable and that you ever hear these people say I'm psychic
or they've fallen for that everyone is if one person is psychic that means
everyone is psychic right I'm not talking about special training like
Tiger Woods where you're raised at two years old you have a rattler in one hand
and a golf club in the other that's different if one person has a natural
ability to do something that means everyone has that natural ability it's
just late so what'll happen is if you keep bugging them about you know that
what their game they're playing they're gonna send one like Darth Vader but you
won't be like Darth Vader he will that entity will make you sight literally you
will be able to anticipate I don't know a few seconds a few minutes whatever you
will be a functioning psychic and when you get you get so impressed by that
you'll fall for it right don't does that make any my making any sense yeah
so in other words you can't escape this right right yeah it was so but so does
it mean you have to mess with them no because it'll take eventually they'll
mess with you back so hard that you might have to be locked up but there's a
fine balance where you can spend anywhere between 0.3 seconds to 5
seconds a day entertaining what thought they put in your head anticipate it and
watch it go silent and that 0.3 seconds to 10 seconds of silence is really who
you are and you could pick up on that emo and that feeling and then it's it
you'll notice how we're here to forget we're here to be confused and all that
on the outside is happening and on the inside it's total silence and and
confidence you know and no fear