The sonic event 115 rated Y, here we are, how are you, Greek?
Yeah, 115, interesting, that's a Freemason number, whenever you see stuff in the news,
15 million is owed to hear, 5.1 million, 51 people, it's either 5-1 in any order or 1-5,
5.1.
Well, a lot of lawsuits, a lot of lawsuits right now, right? There's a whole bunch of
51 million dollars.
Yeah, it's a signal, it's a signal, very much like if you remember Men in Black, the hot
sheet, they were running to the star, what are they called, tabloid papers, and they
said, why are we getting the tabloid, that's the hot sheet.
Well, hot sheets in general are supposed to be the things that come off, the reason why
they say that is because it actually comes off of the heat-sensitive paper, and it
comes off a printer like that, so they used to call them the hot sheets because they were
literally hot, right?
Yeah, because, well, the fast mechanical, anytime you do a fast mechanical movement,
it's going to warm up the object.
Exactly, so that's what used to happen, and in the days of fax machines with the rolls
of paper, you remember those, right?
Well, I was around, we had a Telex machine, back in the 70s, you know, for doing stuff
like that, you know, the family did, but yeah, Telex was, I think, Telex was kind of
more interesting than the fax, it was more, fax looked like junk, but yeah.
Telex was like a full-on typewriter connected to your phone that literally banged up at
things, right?
That's right, it was very, yeah, it would be 20 grand in today's money to get one, it
was probably around 1,500, 2,000 bucks in the 70s.
By the way, just a quick reiteration on money, you know gasoline is cheaper now than it was
in the 70s, a lot of things still are cheaper because it's a 10 to 1 factor, what that means
like if you watch the price is right for 1974, and a Wishbone salad dressing bottle, you
know, not the large bottle, but the small bottle, is 79 cents, that means in today's
money, it's $7.90, so if you go even to whatever and get a salad Wishbone, I don't think it'll
be more than five bucks tops, four bucks, right?
Right, now the thing that warps that reality is that, you know, the pay scale, so to speak,
right, the minimum wage rule, that never went according to that.
If it went according to the scale, yeah.
Minimum wage should be $25 per hour.
Right.
Now, and the way you figure that out is you figure out what minimum wage was when they
first started it, it was around just under $2, right?
$1.80 an hour, something like that.
Well, at a bare minimum, I mean, I remember figuring this out.
You multiply that times 10.
Yeah, to go from, and I always like to use the year I was born, you know, 72 is a good
year to work with, because that was, you know, one of those transitional years, and if you
go and compare it, yeah, $25, $26 is what you would need to have the same purchasing
power.
Now, again, like you said, it doesn't mean that the thing isn't cheaper.
Well, a little bit more, but you would need to announce this, another way to look at what
a dollar should be is what the silver index is.
It's below 30 right now.
It's between 23 and 30, bounces around 25, 23, let's say.
I don't know what it is right now.
So, it's around that.
So, gasoline, when silver was $1 an ounce, and gasoline was $0.75 a gallon, which was
still considered expensive back then, that means it would be 75% of $25, so it would
be roughly $18, $19 a gallon to be in parity with 1970s prices, and it's not.
Even in California, it's $7 or $8 a gallon.
Here in Tucson, it's just under $4, $3.50, something like that, if you get a gas buddy.
So, yeah, so it's still, things are, yeah, but what they call the earnings, never call
it income.
By the way, words to watch out for.
Eliminate these from your vocabulary if you know what good advice is.
These are legal terms, which are not good.
Anything legal just means that it's either licensed or no license, right?
Everything has to do, anything legal, illegal legal, means you have license or no license
from the authorities.
Okay, so that's an easy definition.
It has to do with contracts and licensing.
It has nothing to do with law.
Right.
Never did and never will.
Like we talked about drug dealing, the real problem is that you don't have a license to
deal with the drugs.
Exactly.
That's what the problem is.
It's not the substance.
Yes, the substance is part of the definition of blah, blah, blah, but truth is, you don't
have the license to sell the drug.
Yeah, they rate substances, any substance, the commodity, they're rated and controlled.
It's called rating and controls.
By the way, strange.
Controlled substance is what they call drugs.
Strange thing.
I don't know if this means anything, but I just decided to look up the silver spot price
while you were talking and it's actually a little high today.
Like?
Today's price is at 32.35.
It's even worse for everyone if you're not making 32 bucks an hour.
By the way, if you want to hire the Greek, it's 150 an hour.
That's my going rate.
I do discount it a little bit for sometimes and sometimes I just do a flat rate for 1,000
a day, which is a discount.
Yeah, so anyway.
How many hours do they get out of that grand in a day though?
They get at least 10 hours out of you?
It depends.
I'd lump it up and it wouldn't just be one day.
No, no, no.
It's sometimes more, sometimes less.
I don't get too many calls like that to do that, fortunately, because I don't like to
work that way.
Here's the thing.
These are legal things if you know how to take legal advice and all that.
Eliminate from your vocabulary, if you could, if you would, words like income.
Income.
Income is technically derived from people that do, or merchants that sell stuff in commodity
markets.
Okay.
Right?
It's like money you make from percentages, like interest.
What is a more proper word than income?
Earnings.
Okay.
Income is legal.
Earning is law.
Another thing is, what's another?
I had a whole list of them before we got a little diverted on that.
But income is a big one.
Employee.
Bad, bad term.
Now, you could replace that with several other terms.
Associate.
Associate would be a better one, or the title of whatever you do.
But no, no, no.
Employee.
Employee is a bad term.
It's a legal term.
Some job titles have you as a sales associate in places.
Well, yeah.
Anything other than employee that you find in the commercial or whatever industrial parlance,
use that.
But don't go to work tomorrow.
I've had people that are so naive.
They'll go to work tomorrow, and they'll say, people go, you said don't use the word employee.
I went to my boss the next day.
I'm no longer an employee.
He says, good, now you're fired.
Greek, you got to be fired.
Right?
I mean, if you're that dumb, you should just not even be listening to what I'm saying.
What I do, basically, is handing out double-edged razor blades and loaded guns.
You know what I mean?
So be careful, right?
It's up to you how you use them, too.
Yeah, yeah.
So double-edged swords.
Employee income.
There's a whole bunch of others.
Oh, home.
Home, home, home.
That is another legal term, right?
Home, don't use that.
You use dwelling, inhabitants, house, building, artifice, anything other than home.
Don't use the word home.
No, that's a legal term.
These are all enforceable legally, by the way.
Yeah, not as a destination?
Okay, so residence is better than home.
No, resident is another word.
Oh, resident is a bad word.
Yeah, resident, okay.
Residence puts you in a vagabond category, because if you ask someone where they live,
and then you ask them, are you a resident there?
They'll say yes, which is a contradiction in terms.
By the way, what they've done to the idiots, meaning the common human, is they have them
entertain two conflicting ideas at the same time in harmony.
You cannot entertain or hold two conflicting ideas at the same time.
That's what most people do, by the way, and that's the definition.
One of the ways you define someone who, quote, unquote, mental health issues, right, which
is the majority of the people.
Look, if everybody's insane, where are the insane people?
You can't point to, because everyone's insane.
If you point to everyone, then, right?
Okay, so all of these terms that you see, insurance company.
By the way, why do you, insurance companies have no money.
They don't insure anything, right?
You understand how the Fed window works?
When you have a claim, so you don't have license to go to the Federal Reserve with a piece
of paper and your signature and get whatever number is on the paper.
So you have to subscribe to an insurance policy.
They do it.
When you pay an insurance premium, that has nothing to do with, you know what the right
term is?
Indemnification.
Yeah, you don't want insurance.
First of all, it's a religious term also.
Insurance policies include acts of God, and they can't define that, but they're telling
you, right?
Okay, yeah, almost every type of insurance policy at some point, it has a section on
acts of God.
That's like a guarantee in the writing.
Well, insurance policies, insurance companies, are like the Federal.
It's a religious thing.
In other words, you're snubbing your nose at the will of what they call the heavens,
the will of God, to you're covered no matter what, right?
That's what they say.
Indemnification changes.
Indemnification means you basically, it came out early in the ship days.
Merchants, when a merchant's family invested in a ship and it sank and they were a wealthy
family, well, now they're not wealthy anymore.
So what they did was they grouped up into corporations and they said, instead of each
family has its own merchant ship, why don't we get five families to have five ships together
and we share everything?
So if one of the ships sinks, you don't have total catastrophic disaster in your family,
but you still get a one-fifth share of what's left, right?
That's how the insurance companies started.
By the way, the insurance companies are the ones that sent the pirates out.
That's where the term watermark comes from.
Pirates would board you and they went to the captain's chambers and they would ask for
your indemnification, your papers, and if you had one and they put a watermark on it,
meaning that it was authentic, they would leave you alone.
The pirates were sent by the same, just like the terrorists, right?
Terrorists these days are sent by the, right?
Everyone knows, right?
Remember the shoe bomber was let in on the airplane, no security, right?
Yeah, the supposedly non-government entities are always backed by a government entity.
And that's the other thing.
It almost reminds me of the weird linguistic game that Jordan Maxwell used to play, which
I think is valid, where he explains that, look, what actually guides the currency, the current,
like water, the banks, they actually guide the currency, right?
And all that.
I mean, you know that.
Well, the water.
Yeah, they use the law of the sea and land.
And also a captain on a ship, when he lands, he's no longer the captain.
When he's on land, he's now the governor.
So they're still right.
It's called maritime admiralty.
Admiralty is the ground, right?
It's interesting, maritime, because admiral is in the Navy, right?
Right.
So, but he's not on a ship.
So, but yeah, admiralty has to do with land.
Okay.
They don't like this kind of stuff.
They, meaning attorneys.
Attorneys are dumbasses, by the way.
They all are, because just like the medical students, and this is not a rant or event,
you know that.
You could look up a small community college like Harvard.
Look at law school.
They put their curriculum online and go through all four years what they teach each semester,
what they offer.
Is there any law being taught?
Nope.
No, there's what?
Ethics.
Yeah.
Now with medical school, you take the MCATs and all that other stuff, by the way.
They have you entertain two ideas.
You do biology, and you'll have a chance where you go into a lab and look at anatomy and
things like that.
Yeah.
And they will actually tell you what you're physically looking at is not what it is.
It's something else, and you have to agree to that, right?
That's why we had the medical person recently email me.
He gives one out of a hundred over the years.
Yeah, I've examined the gastrointestinal tract, small intestine, large intestine, stomach,
and they're hydrophobic, just like you say.
There's nothing.
There's no way anything will absorb it, of course, right?
So medical school, you have to entertain the laboratory aspect, what you see physically
with the bullshit they tell you that that is, right?
Now, some people that are sensible, you hear the dropout rate in the legal schools or law
schools and medical schools is high, not because it's difficult.
It's because they're asking you to entertain two contradicting things.
The dummies that stay through the courses and all that are able to...
That's why if you run into people, especially doctors or lawyers, they're a little nutty,
right?
And I've told this to people, and they're like, yeah, my sister, she was not the smartest
in the bunch, and she became a lawyer.
She's successful.
So yeah, it has nothing to do...
You're filling a position.
It's a machine.
It's very much like when you open up a car engine.
Years ago, each part had the manufacturer's hallmark on it, and they don't anymore because
this gear might be made in China.
The other one might be made here.
The other one is sourced from there, right?
So that's what they're doing.
We need a certain amount of attorneys.
We need a certain amount of...
And here's the crime.
This is a real crime because it does harm to humanity.
There are victims.
Parents, a popular thing, especially when I was growing up, inspired their children to
be a doctor or a lawyer.
Have you ever heard of that?
Yeah, we should be a doctor or a lawyer.
That's criminal to say that.
The two highest callings, supposedly, right?
In some houses, it was doctor, lawyer, priest, which makes it even worse.
Especially the more Catholic.
Yeah, it was venerated.
So that is criminal.
By the way, in a real society, if you want to change society, any parent that tells
that to their children, the children should be taken away from them and put into a proper
institution and raised properly.
Yes, there is a way to do it.
It's funny.
When I used to do sonics in the past, talked about laws and that, and people would say,
well, yeah, who's going to tell us the law?
Who's going to make the law?
I said, you are.
You are.
It's always by consent.
Even if you read the scriptures, it's about consent.
It says the people with one voice all agreed, right?
Or they didn't.
Or they murmured.
Okay, it's all by consent.
But if you're a band of morons, you've been bred and groomed into this moronic state,
right?
Now, here's the thing.
I'm offering shortcuts.
You have to do the long work yourself.
I recently got off a call with someone that I've been speaking to for a long time.
And I basically – the crux of Greek speak, let me just reiterate.
It's for people that have skills.
Cover your ears.
But personally, if you just have like keyboard skills, you don't have skills.
What I mean by skills is you could cook a meal, a delicious meal or a good meal.
You're thrifty.
You're a savvy shopper.
You could fix a flat.
You could dress a wound properly.
You could make health recommendations to people, right?
You get it?
You could – when a door falls off, you can hang it, right?
When there's a leak in the – you don't call a plumber.
You could fix it yourself.
Now I'm getting a little more elaborate because most people – now I'm starting to – a DIY.
Someone who has skills.
I'm talking about physical skills, the stuff that you're going to need when this – everything is reset and redone.
You might be a little too old for that.
You may not survive it.
But when you get thrown back into a stone-age type society – by the way, there's no age.
It's a stone society where there's no – when there's no electricity – OK.
No electricity, no utilities, right?
That means like your gas, the car – there's still gasoline in the tanks underground at the gas station.
But you can't get it into your car because you need an electric pump, right?
To get it out, right?
So when there's a blackout, nobody is tanking up, right?
I hope people know that.
Well, you'll need to know how to create energy for your own use.
You'll need to know how to gather water for your own consumption.
You'll need to know how to make food for – yeah, OK.
Yeah, you don't have to be like – I remember – I don't know how many people remember Gilligan's Island.
Gilligan's Island had a professor and he made everything out of bamboo.
You don't have to be like that.
But yes, that's what I'm talking about.
If you fix stuff, you know how to do stuff and you can produce stuff.
Someone comes over to where you live and you can make lunch.
Yeah, you should listen to Greek-speak.
If you can't do that, you're just not wasting your time because you're going to get more out of this than anything else you listen to obviously.
Well, I'll give you an example of something that's great that nobody ever thinks of is that you might actually need a shoemaker.
Somebody who can create shoes that will be useful for –
Improvising.
If you can – all right.
But you're in a society now – by the way, with Gilligan's Island, TV was so –
there were just a lot of old-timers watching it in the 60s and 70s I guess when it came out.
One of the biggest requests at the TV station was, why don't you go save those people off the island?
These people are serious.
It's a naivete.
Let's not use the word stupid anymore even though they are.
But they can't figure – look, I remember I was about five or six years old and an older relative from Greece was sitting on the couch watching Cowboys and Indians
and then the Cowboys are shooting the Indians and the woman from – she was my great-grandmother.
She was crying because people were dying on TV in front of her.
So is she stupid?
Naive.
I would ask, is this real?
I wouldn't just be dragged into it presuming that it's real crying.
You see the difference?
You just have to add a few more words and when you're thinking, vocalize.
Learn how to vocalize and communicate.
But the Greek-speak is for people who want to do stuff.
I'm talking about physical stuff in the world.
Now let's go back to the keyboard.
Are you worthless in a fully functional society?
Absolutely.
Right?
But is it still necessary to do that kind of work?
Yeah, of course it is.
Are you a fully formed human in my view if all you do is keyboard stuff?
The answer is absolutely not at all.
Now I've never really vocalized this specifically but it's important that I do.
I'm like the – what I like is the junior college shop class teacher.
When you go to woodwork in class, they offer classes on home economics where you cook and sew or woodworking class.
You build a little jewelry box or something or machine class or whatever, welding class.
I'm the guy who teaches that.
What I'm doing is trying to – I'm just wondering how – when I give out these little unique recipes like the cabbage and all the way to rice.
For a while, I was known – I used to get sarcastic messages about, yeah, it's more than just cooking perfect rice, stuff like that.
So I'm presuming that if – you're not into cooking at all because I'm not into just cooking.
I can talk about cooking for 10 sonics, eight hours long each and not repeat myself.
The thing is am I just about cooking?
No.
But if someone is listening to this and they absolutely do not cook at all and have no desire to, if they're really listening, they could still get something out of it because it's not just about –
when I give the order or the recipe or the framework on how to prepare something, it's more than just about food, right?
You see?
So if you can take that – like if you're locked up in a room for a year and you have just books of things you're not interested in, would you still try to read them?
Of course.
Probably, yeah.
Because if you'd read enough variety of subjects, you'll notice that even though the subjects are very diverse, there's something in common there, right?
There's something in common.
But those that are doing stuff, by the way – and here's the thing.
There's people that do stuff and stop and get lazy, right?
Right.
Like for example I'm having a conversation with someone and I'll have a ranking system.
The guy says I've been doing carpentry for 35 years.
OK.
And if I'm having more than a minute and a half conversation, like have you invented anything, an improvement?
They say no.
Right away, I know where they're at.
They need a manager.
They need to have a limited scope.
So what I mean by that is people that work in any field for more than a certain amount of time should start inventing stuff.
You know how I've said before every field is wide open?
Yeah.
Every field.
Every field, especially all the stuff they're talking about, the high sciences, especially those because that's all bullshit.
I'm talking like medicine, astrophysics, nuclear physics.
All that stuff is bullshit.
By the way, Jonathan Butts, who passed away in February, he was a nuclear engineer on a Navy submarine, right?
All the top secret stuff we discussed, which wasn't very – I said that's really dumb.
Yeah, they're really dumb there.
They're running nuclear submarines with nuclear arsenals, right?
They don't know what they're doing and the stuff is not very advanced, right?
Well, it is to the common whatever.
So even that field is open for improvement in a major way.
First of all, the nuclear stuff is not what we're told.
It's the bankers.
They tell you it's dangerous to protect it.
If they told you it wasn't dangerous and the stuff is a million dollars a gram, now you need an incredible security apparatus.
People will be driving concrete-reinforced pickup trucks into nuclear reactors to steal the rods, right?
If it wasn't dangerous and it was that expensive, yeah, that's exactly right.
Well, they tell you it's dangerous, right?
If you look at old nuclear power plant videos and they're saying here's the heart of the nuclear –
you hear the old-fashioned voice in black and white.
Now we built a nuclear and this is the new nuclear age and here's the heart of the nuclear power plant coming right now.
You see a truck and they're unloading the uranium rods, look like two-inch or one-inch rods, eight feet long,
and two guys are holding it with just cotton gloves and a white coverall suit.
That's it, right?
But they said, oh, uranium is going to kill you.
It's to keep people away and it works, right?
Like imagine suddenly you go to a planet and there's no diamonds or precious stones
because the people are told that it's radioactive, right?
It could hurt them, right?
By the way, speaking of radioactivity, those really fancy granite countertops –
by the way, if you're – anyone who has a lot of cooking skill does not want granite countertops in their kitchen.
When you go to a house and you see granite countertops, those people don't cook.
They do more takeout.
They think they can cook.
They're really warming up food.
They might – if you ask them what the best thing they can do is, the grill a steak.
That's all they can do, right?
So granite countertops, by the way, is vanity.
A real cook has stainless steel tops or butcher block tops, not granite.
If I had granite countertops in the house that I was given, I would remove them right away
and put in stainless steel and wood, right?
Because it's workable surfaces.
It's all vanity.
But anyway, back to the granite countertops.
The real thick ones, the big slabs, the Brazilian granite that have the most interesting colors of deep reds
and burgundies and metallic stripes, do me a favor.
Go get a Geiger counter in your kitchen and see what happens.
I'm not going to say anything else.
You'll be surprised.
That's why a lot of people that spend time in the kitchen with these super fancy –
they like to spend time in the kitchen.
I've been to see these McMansions, these two $3 million houses with the $50,000 granite countertops.
Everybody, instead of gathering in the living room or the dining room,
they like to gather at the kitchen counter and have the meeting there, right?
Yeah, they put like a bar in with stools so you can like sit right at the kitchen.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, and they like to – why?
Because it's invigorating.
Okay, I'll say it.
The amount of radiation that these – so not all of them.
Depending on where it's sliced from, which mine, they're very radioactive.
Far more than – imagine having five or six cell phones strapped to each side of your head.
More than that, but a different kind of radiation, right?
Okay.
And it's invigorating.
If you want to take it to another level, they kind of told you in the Marvel – the Hulk,
you got a big dose of radiation, right?
Right.
It was very invigorating.
So in the right dose – by the way, in the mitochondria and all of the cells in your body,
there's a little bit of uranium.
You can look this up.
Yeah, it flips back and forth.
It's not static.
That's another conversation.
So just to bring these things up, to go back to the Greek speak, it's for people that
do stuff.
Like for example, there's someone that repairs pianos, high-end pianos.
When he got in touch with me, I was so happy.
I was so happy to hear from someone that does that, right?
You can't just go and – you don't use Elmer's glue and masking tape to fix Steinway
pianos, right?
No, you don't go get two weeks' worth of training and go do that.
This is like someone who does – it's like Rolls-Royce.
It's up there.
Please, even the guys who tune them.
Even the guys who tune them, it takes a while to figure out how to do that, just to tune it.
Well, yeah.
You have to – right.
Yeah, it's more – and it's like – it's an art.
But more than that, like if someone – we had someone who welds.
He's a welder.
I'm like, oh, I'm so happy.
Someone contacts me and said like they weld or they do this or they do that.
I'm like, oh, I'm so happy to hear from you, right?
Because you can definitely use what I'm talking about, right?
Years ago, they used to call it working with your hands, right?
But there's another level to it.
Like again, I've run into people that have been doing – I've been cutting hair.
I've been doing plumbing.
I've been doing electric.
Once it goes over 15 or 20 years, have you invented anything?
When they say no right away, it's like this person is just going along for the ride.
What do I mean by that?
Anything that you do, any field, any skill or whatever,
if you're like slightly awake and see what's going on,
most of the people are just – they're fitting into a social culture, climate
or whatever that trade or type of work is.
It could even be a keyboard.
You could go back to that because I know someone who's redesigning interface with the keyboard.
So when you're going to go type a letter, it gives you a choice of words,
kind of like how the phone does.
But it does it in a daisy chain kind of way.
So now you're typing words instead of typing letters.
But he's working in a way to rearrange it on the screen.
But anyway, what I'm saying is if you're – when you go into any culture,
dentistry, medicine, nursing, aircraft structures engineering,
carpentry, truck driving, whatever,
you will notice that you have to kind of adjust to the tools or the way things are done.
Then when you start working in that field, it doesn't matter what it is,
a service, a product manufacturer, anything.
When you start working, you'll start noticing that you might –
everyone is doing this slight adjustment because it works better,
but it hasn't been done by the industry.
That's what I mean about being inventive, right?
Have you invented anything?
How many times have you gone to a place and they have like a –
it's a place that's furnished that offers a service,
but they have something taped together and glued together
that holds something else because it works better.
That's an invention, right?
In other words, there's no progress in the field as much as one would expect.
That's why I always ask people in any specialized skill, a carpenter,
a plumber, a hairdresser, a doctor, a dentist, whatever, have you invented –
like one of my clients was an ER second in charge of the emergency room
and he filed for a patent.
I said, oh, that's going to be real tough.
They don't like that in the medical industry.
What it was for is that about half the people that come in for trauma
in emergency rooms, the femur is dislocated from the hip bone.
Let's just not get into the anatomy.
The thigh bone comes out of the – and the hip is out of joint.
So they have to get that in place.
It's basically a pulling.
You get an orderly and you have to whack it.
The joint comes out of its socket.
About half the people, like people that get hit by cars,
people that fall off a cliff, people that fall down the stairs.
It's a very, very common thing.
So he invented this rack, a thing that the person leans against
and the medical technician adjusts it to the person's body
and then one motion with a lever returns the bone back into its socket, the femur.
The feet, the thigh bone.
Okay, I can picture that.
Yeah, it's a very common injury.
The next one is the shoulder, the shoulder being dislocated.
Even here, dislocated shoulder.
Dislocated shoulders are constant.
Yeah, it doesn't matter if it's a sports injury.
If you have a dislocation, you probably have a fracture in the clavicle,
which is a collarbone.
But anyway, so he was in the field for less than 10 years
and he started inventing these devices to help in ER, save time.
Now what's interesting, when you talk to him,
you can have a conversation about anything,
where the other ER guys are like,
I don't have time, I'm going to go play golf.
What a pathetic sport, by the way.
Golf, the most pathetic sport.
Do you know that they house people that applaud?
I don't even know that that's a sport.
I don't understand how it's a sport.
It's a rich man's activity.
It's a signal that you're signaling that you've made it
in a certain level of capitalist, upper middle class,
and upper class, whatever.
It's a signaling thing.
Very few people that play golf actually like it.
They do it because it's to signal that they're part of a group.
A status symbol.
What I'm trying to say is don't be afraid of being inventive.
It doesn't mean go run and do a patent.
No, no, no.
What I'm saying is be inventive and share it with others
and many other people.
When I worked in the bicycle industry,
I'd go to bicycle shows and tell manufacturers,
hey, why don't you do this, this, and that?
At the show that lasts several days in Las Vegas or New York
or Philadelphia or wherever it was,
oh, well, let's have dinner together.
So I'd have a four-hour conversation.
They're like, oh, I don't know about that.
Then a year later I'd go to the bike show
and they've actually implemented what I suggested.
I'm not like, oh, that was my idea.
No, it's just because it helps everyone.
I could give you the clipless pedals.
I said, why do you have a whole body for the pedal?
This was back in the late 80s.
Why do you have a body for the pedal and a body for the cleat?
Why don't you build everything around the cleat
so it has more support to the shoe and just a basic spindle on the pedal?
Oh, no, everybody wants it.
Oh, if somebody looks at a bike,
just a spindle on the crank with no pedal body, it looks weird.
I said, well, it's going to work better.
It'll stiffen up the shoe.
You put all the mechanics.
Well, when I started, the Speedplay came out
after I made a big thing about that.
A whole bunch of models started.
Then I said ergonomic hood covers for brake levers.
Why is it just a straight brake hood?
When you put your hand over it, it should be ergonomic,
like an octagon shape instead of just circular or rectangular
so the hand fits in.
Oh, no, people are used to this.
I said, no.
What?
I go back to you.
I started doing ergonomics, and I went to everyone.
I didn't say, hey, you got an idea?
Let's go patent this, and then we'll have the rights,
and if they want to do it, they have to pay us, right?
That was one thing I was doing with the Scalarator
when I was with John Butts and other people,
people in Europe, engineers, physicists.
Oh, how many people have you told?
How many people have you told?
Oh, I tell everybody.
Oh, stop talking about it.
Stop talking about it.
It's like you have to make a cover for it.
You can't show what it is.
I'm like, what the hell is wrong with you people?
Wow.
Creating scarcity, and they don't even know that the scarcity,
all the scarcity that can be has already happened,
and it's virtual scarcity.
It has to do with scarcity of money, not ideas and all that.
So am I knocking patents?
Yeah, I know enough.
I was brought up like everyone else, told to be a lawyer and a doctor
and get a patent and all this other stuff,
and when I started meeting inventors,
I noticed that they all had something in common,
the ones that failed and are failures in what they thought.
I'm going to be rich, and I know one guy 20 years later,
he's still not doing well at all because he fell in love with his invention.
Just like your children, let's say there's a parent.
When an inventor falls in love with his invention,
it's like a parent falling in love with their child.
I'm not saying loving their child, falling in love with their child
because you're doing a big disservice.
You know how they have the favorite, mama's favorite, papa's favorite?
Oh, yeah.
Right?
Okay.
That child gets oversheltered and has more privileges and immunities
than the rest of the children, and when it goes into the real world,
now it's handicapped.
It's like how come I'm not getting the attention?
Because of what they're accustomed to.
Right?
Yeah, because of what they're accustomed to.
So you're not preparing the child well, and also the other children.
Yeah.
Or they get smothered, and then they want to break away.
So I don't really give them all the love, and, look, they left at 15.
I haven't heard from them in five years.
Right?
So you've got to treat them.
As a parent, you're supposed to raise them biologically,
and you're supposed to bring in others for the culture
and all the other things.
Right?
Right.
Yeah, you see?
That's why the wealthy, they had people come in for their children.
They had a nanny raise you to do all the dirty work.
They had piano lessons come in.
They had etiquette teacher, grammar school teachers come in, all these different.
If you grew up in a very wealthy family.
And a governess who ran it all, if you had a really wealthy situation.
It was not unusual to have three or four people,
different types of instructors coming in every day or every week
to show the child, to expose the child to various things.
So if you're raised in a family where the only contact is the parents or grandma,
you're at a big disadvantage in terms of many other things.
Not always.
I'm just saying generally.
Right.
So these inventors that fell in love with their inventions did not change them,
did not take criticism very well.
They felt like if they tried to do a business deal,
if it didn't make them wealthy, they wouldn't do the business deal.
Right?
You see what I mean?
They set themselves up for failure.
And I see this.
And I'm not going to mention names.
I was going to actually say not mention names and mention a few names, but I'm not.
Actually, in one of them, on one of them,
I had drawn a few things to extend his invention.
And he says, oh, this is great.
And he says it has to be redrawn by an attorney because the line thickness isn't
proper for the patent.
So anyway, the patent continuance came out.
And they put my drawing in just like I sent it on an e-mail scan,
exactly like I sent it.
And you can see the patent is still up there.
It might have the pencil drawings.
So I do have stuff that's patented, but not under the Greek's name at all.
I have no interest in that at all.
So you can reach out to people and have a working relationship with them also.
So if I had grandchildren, I'd say, look, I see this drawing.
It's up on the U.S. government patent website.
Look at that.
I did that.
I came up with that idea.
But it was under someone else's.
It's called a continuation.
Anyway, be inventive.
So one thing I ask.
Now, this is kind of a tall order.
When you run into people, let's say someone is a dentist and you say,
have you invented it?
How long have you been in dentistry?
25 years.
Have you invented anything?
It's a tall order.
Usually most people are going to say no.
But what is this guy Greek talking about?
What an asshole.
Everybody I ask who's worked in any field for a long time,
have they invented anything?
And they usually say no.
I say, yeah, my point well taken then.
My point well taken.
How can you not?
Even if it's a small thing.
Like even in the workshop.
Of course.
If you notice that somebody has come up with a different way to set up
their tools because they've come up with a different storage system.
Or when I was working as a glass glazier,
we had a way of wrapping around and protecting the edges of finished
pieces of glass that was utilizing certain materials.
And actually I ended up teaching that to other people because they had
no idea about it.
It was kind of invented by the guy who, not me.
I'm not talking about like Inventors Club where you go on TV.
I know a guy who worked as – his whole family were linemen and either
for power lines or cable lines, any kind of whatever, right?
Okay.
And he didn't – he wanted to be – he didn't have the singing ability
to play guitar well enough.
So being a rock star wasn't going to work for him.
So he went and got a job working in a linesman.
And after two years in working there,
he's the one that invented in the 90s the cutter that cuts the wire and
strips it at the same time, different gauges.
It's like a – you squeeze it and it strips.
It cuts the wire and strips the little piece off so you don't have to cut
the wire and then go back with a dikes or a blade and strip it, right?
He invented that in only two years working in the field
and he got a patent for it.
He also applied for – he was very ingenious.
He applied for a patent to shoot – for an advertising company to do like
ads on the moon using lasers.
So everybody on the ground would see Coca-Cola on the moon for a short time
and then change to Jiffy Popcorn or General Ford motorcars
and using lasers scan the surface of the moon just like they have skywriting
with planes but use lasers on the moon.
And they said, no, no, that's against national security, blah, blah, blah.
But anyway, that's – you see what I'm – that sounds kind of crazy
but it's such an obvious thing to do,
put a laser projection of a corporate name on the moon, right?
Wouldn't that sound great?
You only have a few days or maybe let's say a week or so to do it.
How about running – that's one hell of a public –
what is it, a public relations firm if you think about it.
I mean even if it's just for one night honestly on the moon,
how many people are going to look up at the moon that night?
Yeah, so people like that really get my juices flowing
because all these possibilities.
Eventually you're going to run into something
that's going to make your life immediately better.
That's why I get into a lot of the food talk that I do.
One thing that I was asked to get into recently that I will
is some of the spiritual stuff that's hard to talk about.
I'm just going to get – we'll just end it right after a few comments
because there's some talk going on in the chat and all that.
Also with Archaics.
By the way, I don't endorse Archaics.
I'll bring up Brashears again.
I don't endorse him.
I have benefited greatly from his chronology.
It's not watertight.
He talks about the Phoenix event, but there's some publication.
I might have even put it up on the chat about a year ago.
There was a lot of crazy stuff happening throughout the 1800s and the 1700s
that does not line up with the 138, but that's fine.
That's fine.
Also in ancient times that I was aware of.
You could look up, but that's fine.
It doesn't mean that the 138 is not valid.
But he's been making a lot of ruckus about Scripture
and religious stuff and all that other stuff.
Now, one thing that I've warned people about for two decades now is this.
When someone begins a – and I've stuck with this for 20 years
and I will not change from it.
When someone brings up the biblical subject, they must,
within a few minutes of the subject being brought up,
qualify that the Scriptures have not been translated outside of Hebrew and Greek.
There is no translation.
They're all versions.
If you want a translation, you're going to have to do it yourself
through what's called an interlinear.
It just gives you word for word in the original language,
which is not a translation because it's not pieced together right.
So there's no literal translation.
Now, there's Young's literal translation or whatever.
No, they don't have the – OK.
Because certain words, what you do in a translation that is not translatable,
you must carry it over.
Like Elohim is not translatable, so it would be Elohim.
Yahweh is not translatable, so it's Yahweh and vice versa.
But all languages have something like that.
That's why when you go to certain countries,
they'll start using English words, technical words.
They'll say Windows for a computer.
In France or Spain, they'll say Windows, not Ventana, right,
because Windows is the name of the program.
It's not translatable.
Names are not subject to translation, right?
Proper names, yeah.
Proper names.
Yeah, he doesn't do that.
He doesn't – also, the other thing to watch out for, big red flag to me.
It doesn't mean I'm discounting.
These are just minus points.
These are things that drop your stock value, right?
OK.
The other thing is if you're going to be accurate and transmit information,
you have, let's say, something you want to convey,
and there are many other things that can be discussed.
You could discuss them another time, but keep them valid.
Don't invalidate them.
What I mean is by this.
When you go to someone like Bashir and you say there is no crucifixion,
that's kind of harsh, but you bring it up.
You know what he says?
It doesn't matter.
That's the typical stuff.
When you hear it doesn't matter from anyone,
I've never said that, by the way, ever.
Everything matters.
I might discount something, but I'll never say I don't care or it doesn't matter.
That's complete apathy.
One thing might matter less than something else though, right?
I mean there might be a scale here, but it's not that it doesn't matter at all.
Well, you know, what I've seen him several times,
he was reading a comment, there was no crucifixion.
It doesn't matter.
OK.
The reason why this is not good at all is because that's one of the Christian,
you know how you become a Christian, you cut the top of your head off,
dump your brains out, put your head back on,
now you get the certificate you're a Christian, right?
There you go.
What that means is very clearly, very simply,
the typical Christian thing is you go to them and it's all doesn't matter,
doesn't matter, doesn't matter.
It's the political side.
So you go to a Christian, well, you know, it's a Bible believer, right?
Yeah, absolutely.
I say, well, that's not in the Bible.
It doesn't matter, right?
You see?
And also he quotes a lot of biblical stuff and then says it was not right.
It's written by a bunch of evil Jewish rabbis, whatever, tiny hats,
whatever he calls them, but yet they're inspired by God.
So too much of this stuff – people like that want to be rich.
They don't want to be right.
Now if you say, well, Greek, you want to be right?
Well, no, because you're going to put on the gravestone he was right.
It doesn't matter.
You're dead, right, what they put on your gravestone, right?
So, by the way, I'm supposed to be buried in a dumpster anyway,
but the problem with that is the dumpsters are locked these days.
They're locking dumpsters, right?
So, yeah, so anyways, the whole thing here is you take what you can,
use what you can, but those two qualifiers,
whenever you don't hear a preface that we don't have a translation in any other language
outside of Hebrew and Greek,
it doesn't matter on the aspect of what the subject matter about the Bible is going to be.
That must be made.
Let's just say it doesn't matter, right?
In other words, that is a given because most people think when they go
and access whatever version they have,
they're actually looking at what's been memorialized originally, right?
And that doesn't work ever.
The other thing is when someone starts getting wholeheartedly serious about a subject
and you bring up their misinterpretation,
it's like I've also heard him over and over, archaics,
talk about, well, you know, the day starts at sundown, right?
That's a Jewish Babylonian thing.
It's actually, it was done, it's an unusual, there's many different histories why
and it's not touched, but the day starts in the Bible, Scripture,
and in old culture, and in merchant culture, and legal culture, law culture,
and in scientific culture, it's noon.
It's very easy.
It's actually, once you know that, you could find it.
But if you don't know this, you will never find it because it's hidden.
Any Astronomy 101 spends about five minutes.
Every course in Astronomy 101 tells you the day starts at noon, right?
So when you go look at all the stuff in the biblical stuff,
like he, what's funny, again, I'm not knocking archaics,
but he says, look, even Genesis says it was evening and it was morning the first day.
No, that's noon because evening, right, and morning, right, where do they meet?
At noon.
They meet at noon.
Right, right.
So he's trying, it's like you're not even thinking about what you're talking about,
not even thinking about it because it would say it became evening
and it's the next day if it was evening, not evening and morning, right?
It's a moment.
Also, you can't keep precision records and all this.
Anyway, the full moon is the new moon.
It's just really tiring and you hear this.
Why don't you reach out to a character?
I said, I don't have any money to give him.
He just wants money.
So, you know, it's all he wants.
So anyway, so look, I am very grateful about the timeline and the chronology
set forward with the various objects, the 2040, 2046, 2052,
and a lot of his followers, by the way,
I don't care if people say it about Greek-speak followers who are dumb.
They're like, it's the end of the world in 2046?
And even archaics, he'll get on.
He says, I never said that.
So it's like, oh, my gosh, you need to have a good memory.
That's one thing that's very important.
You must be able to retain information in its proper way.
It's called memory.
You must have a good memory.
If you don't, then everything is entertainment to you, right?
It's very important to have a good memory with facts and figures.
Otherwise, it falls into entertainment.
And it's very excusable.
It's very excusable.
Everybody pats each other on the back for not retaining things
and not knowing things, right?
But if you come off retaining things and knowing things, oh, he thinks he's so smart.
He's a real nerd.
I've talked about that before.
So you're not welcomed here.
It's not welcoming, by the way.
People are very cruel if you tend to do things more properly than they do.
But you can't be too sloppy either, right?
Because then they'll call you a slob or dumb.
The worst thing is to be called dumb by a normie.
That would be really bad.
But the hard things to discuss, we'll start piecing something together,
because when you're talking about a non-corporeal world, the spiritual world,
when you are in a corporeal situation with a body,
it's kind of like trying to watch television with the television unplugged.
You know what I mean?
It's like, okay, let's talk about the things that are hard to discuss
about the spiritual world and spirituality.
What's on TV when there's no TV around?
What's on TV when it's on?
Is there anything on the TV?
Is there anything playing on the TV when the TV is not on?
Or when it's on, when the TV is playing,
is there another message in there that we could see?
And there is, by the way.
Almost always is.
Yeah, yeah.
So this is the mindset that you're going to require yourself to be in
when we start getting into a couple of discussions in the next Sonic or two.
We'll just preface it and leave it there.
Seems like any time there's energy running through,
then there's always something that can be gained from it.
But without the energy, it's just an object, right?
Can be, yeah.
There we go.
That was a little long.
Yeah, okay.
What about four?