Rated Y, Sonic Event 109.
So here we are.
Greek, how are you?
Hey, I'm doing okay.
I figured this might be one of the longer ones, the Sonics, because kind of interesting
stuff came up today and yesterday.
So I figured it's a, what do you call it, a muse over, or when you talk about things
and it brings them forward.
In other words, you know, I was out in public and, you know, I tell people I'm just visiting,
taking notes, right?
And before you know it, this is at a construction supply showroom type thing, and I had a small
crowd.
And usually when the crowd like that develops, you know, I'm giving them Greek speak, right?
And someone in the jump on, say, you need to write a book.
Oh, yeah.
Of course.
You know what I say about that?
Right?
No point.
Well, here's the thing.
There is a point to it.
That's what I want to bring up.
And I got a few things.
I'm going to do them backwards because that usually comes later.
You know, when I'm proselytizing Greek speak, they, you know, after a few minutes, if they're
still there, which is they'll be there as long as I'm there doing it.
And then I realized, am I disturbing the business because I'm inside of a business, right?
You know, years ago, people didn't go to share information in school.
They were at the Agora, the marketplace, right?
And I tell people that this is a marketplace for thousands of years of information, right?
So the thing is, think about writing a book.
When you have important information to convey, yeah, stuff that could be technical or let's
just say, like a recipe or methodical or science or whatever, we have that information to convey.
It's very difficult to do it live or on a sonic.
If you have information that's important that can be used, let's say, as reference material,
let's just that encompasses a lot, right?
Okay.
It should be written down.
It really should be or should be sequestered and separate where someone can put it in their
pocket.
Now, we know we don't.
Right.
It would be on a thumb drive or on a file.
And they can access it when they because when you do a speaking or a sonic live, especially
people are there for the emotional effect that you're going to give, right?
Because if you're if you're doing a sonic and you sound like this the whole time you're
speaking, no matter what the information is, you're going to lose them.
But if you're real emotional, like look at these preachers, right?
Right how they are.
I think the people there for the content or the emotion, right?
Right.
Now, part of right.
It's the second part.
Of course.
Yeah.
It's the showmanship.
The other part to that of doing a live is when people are done.
See, this is one of the one of the reasons why I did the I was insistent when we started
the Sonics do the chat angle right away.
Right.
We didn't even have one sonic.
Why?
Because even though these are recorded, these are most, you know, you'll get the emotion.
This is not AI speaking, right?
Right.
Not a bot.
And either of you.
So, although I've taken notice, there are many, many more of those things now, even
YouTube videos that are apparently Yeah, the undead Internet, like one third of everything
on the Internet is not human.
Really?
Okay.
Yeah.
So I insisted on getting that you tango going.
Why?
Because when there's an emotional or a live presentation, like people leaving the theater,
they want to talk to each other about what they just heard and experienced.
Right.
Well, that's why I always like going out to eat after a movie, because you could sit down
and eat and talk.
And, you know.
Well, no, no.
I'm just talking about, well, if everyone well, I'm saying like when you're exiting
the venue, yeah, people will discuss what they just saw or heard.
Like, for example, like a really dramatic movie.
Some movies were so dramatic when everyone left, everyone was silent.
Right.
You hear that in the review.
Oh, yeah.
But other times people are coming out going, oh, my God, did you believe that that's the
way that went?
Yeah.
Right.
So that's why.
So also the comments section on the YouTube section is important for that.
Right.
Well, kind of.
I know.
I mean, this.
No, it's important for that reason.
Not.
Oh, my gosh.
You really want to lose, quote unquote, faith in humanity or hope in many.
Go read all the YouTube.
It doesn't matter what video the actually some of us.
All right.
I'm not going to say it, but a lot of the stuff that I've done online that people comment,
it was usually very positive or the people really sounded like their head was screwed
on.
Mostly.
Yeah.
You actually do get a different set of commentary, because, I mean, generally speaking, you could
put up a video of a cat and, you know, you'll get something racist, something political,
somebody arguing about Donald Trump and you're like, yeah, no, no, that's.
Yeah.
So.
OK.
So the important thing.
So should Greek speak be a book?
No.
No, because there's something about people getting information from a book that's not
for their job.
By the way, when you have a job or a career or whatever, you're always looking for time
off.
Right.
Where if you really like what you do, there's no time off because on your time off, you'd
be doing that anyway.
Right.
Yeah.
There's no difference.
Right.
So what when this this information goes out on these sonics and the way I just present
some.
I had this one guy.
I'm not going to mention names.
Bruce McDonald.
He's an editor or whatever.
This stuff for books.
He says, I sound like a robot.
You sound like Hal 9000.
You've got to be more emotional.
I'm like, you've got to be kidding me.
You've got to be kidding me.
But, you know, everyone's got their own critique.
That's fine.
But here there is there are certain certain poignant things that I discuss that are manual
type reference type material.
And I could get I when I used to do the sonics on Revolution Radio a long time ago.
Oh, my gosh.
Michael, all that that that station, by the way, I had to take a shower after calling
in, you know, every actually I was always asked to call in.
Right.
And I just felt that place had like an orc stench, like a spiritual stench to it.
You know.
But anyway, agreed.
Unlike American Freedom Radio, which was just like so mellow and cool, you know, it lacked
dimension, even though Danny tried to create more dimension, you know, he wanted more right
away.
It just lacked that.
It was kind of like paper thin, but it was cool because it was just us being ourselves
on there.
You know, but it was a cool space.
No, I was like, you can only be yourself.
Me separate from you even.
It was just me.
You can only be yourself.
I mean, you really enjoyed the time or not.
You know, I'm just going to interject something and people say, oh, I need to go find myself.
Well, who are you now?
No.
But what I mean by that is that I didn't feel pressured to try and do anything other than
what it is I was already doing.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
It was a good space.
This is like in the 80s.
You know, the energy people.
So I was fortunate.
Since a young age, I was around some new age types.
Not holy.
I wasn't raised by hippies.
No.
Not at all.
Very Spartan Greek family.
Right.
They came over on an airplane in the early 60s.
And I was not raised by earthy, crunchy new age people.
But I was around.
They were.
I had their info.
I saw them in this in the 70s and 80s before it became popular.
Right.
And one thing they would say is that's a good space.
Like, even though they have a safe space, the stickers on doors for children, right.
Whatever.
So anyway, I just want to bring up a few of those little comments.
One of the things that I brought up, there was some scientific types.
And also, I'm I have a client who's a medical person, which I actually here's the thing
about cover yours.
I'm thinking of doing a band and not selling to anyone in the legal field or the medical
field or not offering any of my services or anything.
And I'm just kind of like boycotting.
Right.
But anyway.
OK, I'm covering yours now.
So I'm going to bring up two points.
OK.
One point is one of the scientific types talking about time machine.
I said, of course, time machines exist because it doesn't matter when you invent a time machine.
It's one of those things.
You know, it's like you ask a crowd of people, what do you want?
And they all say, we want a time machine.
And says, when do you want it?
Irrelevant.
Right.
So if a time machine is invented a billion years in the future from now, a time machine
is invented a billion years in the future from now.
Can you come back and affect that?
It has the range.
Sure.
So it doesn't matter when it's invented.
That's literally my argument for why there is no no time machine having been invented,
because we would have already seen it.
You know.
Right.
Well, but but I'm saying the influence.
So this is the way this is like non-paradoxical language, because there really are no paradoxes.
Once you start thinking non-linearly, like thermodynamics, you know, all these people
say, well, science was the third demoniacs.
Yeah, that's fine for a linear system with chemical degeneration.
But thermodynamics has nothing to do with a rising, rarefied cold and a descending densified
heat.
Thermodynamics laws don't work there.
No one talks about it.
Right.
Plus, you're not accounting for the possibility that anything is completely without end,
like energy.
Well, that would be a closed system.
Yeah.
But here's the other thing that came up.
Time and space.
Yeah.
OK.
Now I say there's no time and no space.
Those are just simply measurements.
But both are relied on motion.
This is what I was explaining was half the people got it.
The other half didn't.
And I pointed.
I said, I'm going to go now.
And half the people that got it, I said, explain it to those guys there that didn't get it.
I'm leaving now.
Right.
So because if I stay anymore here, you know, I'm going to like leave the meter running
like the cab, you know, and there's no meter.
Right.
I need to walk around with a meter on my shirt.
You know, I mean, leave the meter running.
Right.
Remember that a lot of people didn't grow up in an urban environment, wouldn't know what
that means.
No, I get it.
But in other words, you need a punch card system where, you know, here's something just
a punch system maybe.
But anyway.
So what's interesting is punch clock.
Time is a matter.
If there is no motion, everything, the environment and any object is completely still.
There's no time because time is the recordation of events.
And space is actually.
A derivative, a byproduct of communication to explain things that are moving, like moving
through space.
Right.
If there's absolutely no motion, there is no space.
So time and space are both based on motion.
And it is somewhat of an impossibility to not have any motion somewhat.
But that's the part where once we understand what it means to die and be asleep, we don't
fully comprehend that yet.
But the thing I brought up.
Because of these because we're locked into change, like with the Dallas thing is one
thing for sure is change.
All things change.
Right.
Which makes sense.
And because of motion and everything has its own independent, slightly independent motion.
That's why no two things can be identical.
You can make, let's say, cut two diamonds that are exactly identical from the same one.
And you can if you have the equipment with the tolerance, the closer you look, you'll
see that they're still they're not identical.
There's something different about them, whether it's the workmanship or the way, quote unquote,
the molecules are lined up.
Right.
So two things will never be identical.
There's someone an old guru says that nature doesn't do carbon copies.
Right.
So.
The ability to understand that no two things like, you know, I don't know if you remember
saying I was at no to bread, loaves of bread or bake the like that's a saying that I it's
an old saying anyway.
Well, no.
So no two objects can be absolutely completely alike.
No two movements can be exactly completely alike because that involves objects and things
moving and therefore there is no such thing as exact copies.
There's always going to be some deviation.
Right.
Now, the static, the ether, for example, is it moving or is it static now?
It doesn't matter because it will create motion in both cases.
One is if it has a pressure that would create change and motion, meaning the ether static
to static objects pushing against each other.
Right.
We'll still create motion where they touch.
That's why when you get a package opened up from a product, you notice how it's in a box
with styrofoam ends and it's wrapped in plastic.
The plastic is there.
So when it's vibrating as it's moving on the truck, it doesn't scratch the surface.
Right.
OK.
That kind of thing.
Packaging is there for that movement.
But from a human perspective, they're trying.
We're always going to try to find something that's static as a reference.
And we're never going to find that.
You know, it's kind of like the one thing I like about the flat earthers, you know, do
you feel like you're moving at six thousand miles an hour?
Right.
Well, what should that feel like?
Yeah.
If you're on a well-behaved quote unquote drivers on the highway on a Sunday morning,
you can have a three lane highway with full of, you know, let's say full of cars just
cruising along.
And you could look inside each car, right.
The dash and the contents and people inside the car, especially if you have a higher car,
you could look inside.
And for a moment, you're examining the car next to you.
You're moving down the highway.
You don't feel that you forget that you're moving.
Right.
You see, just like to remember the express train and a local train crossing the bridge
in New York City.
They're on parallel tracks.
And as we're crossing the bridge, trains moving 40 miles per hour.
But you just look inside, you can almost read the paper of the train, the next train over
if you're moving at the same speed.
If you're moving at the same speed, it appears as though there is no movement.
But for a moment, you know, you're moving.
But for a moment, you act like there is no movement because you're trying to read the
newspaper from the next train over.
Or you're trying to see what what's in the T-shirt of the person in the car next to
you on the highway.
Well, both.
Right.
Sure.
Yeah.
So or read a bumper sticker.
Right.
Or something.
So for a moment, we're able to forget and push aside that there's motion and consider
things to be static.
So anyway, there was a physicist in there works on a telescope.
But anyway, I gave about 45 minutes of Greek speak in public and it got me going to a
certain point.
But then I had to stop because earlier before I spoke about that, going back to someone
that I'm providing a device for that's in the medical profession, I know I know them
for two decades now.
What I said to them and not completely, I'll say completely what I wanted to say here.
But this is the I'm going to what I brought up to them was very, very soft.
I'm not going to say what I brought up to them because it'll it won't it won't be what
a sonic should we should say in a sonic.
I'm going to say what I the background than the meat and the bones.
You know, I basically provided a skin.
I'm going to give the meat, flesh and bone right now.
OK.
There's a certain level of arrogance amongst these people.
Very, very arrogant.
But because they're amidst a society that is so apathetic and ignorant, they get away
with it.
But it doesn't mean they're not arrogant and it doesn't mean the society is in ignorance.
But together, it makes a lethal mix.
And this is what I mean, 2020 and 2019, actually before the Department of Health and Human
Services was sending to hospital administrators letters that if anybody tests for covid-19,
they get fifteen thousand dollars.
If they're put on a ventilator, respirator thing, they get 50.
If they die from it, they get one hundred thousand.
So they're basically incentivizing all of that.
Right. Yeah.
For example, do you know there was a guy, a couple of instances, motorcycle accident,
unconscious. He wakes up and he's on a ventilator in the hospital.
He pulls the tube out, runs the fuck out of there.
No reason. Right. Right.
OK, so scores of thousands of people were killed this way.
In other words, this is the typical procedure.
They were incentivized to be put on ventilators and then starved to death and asphyxiated.
That's why the early diagnosis of people dying in the hospital was thrombosis, blood
clotting or asphyxiation.
Right. Everyone said there's nothing there's nothing wrong with them.
They just have the same.
They look like they have an autopsy.
Someone with extreme altitude sickness and thrombosis, blood clots, thickening of the
blood work that can't flow anymore.
So there's several many, many reports where they you know, there are people were
starved to death right while they were on the ventilator and asphyxiated.
Scores of thousands of people across the world and in the U.S.
scores of thousands mean it could be 50,000, 100,000.
They said they use the Zionist number.
Six million people die from covid.
Right. You realize that. Right.
OK, so anyway.
Hundreds of thousands of people, I would say, no, no.
Remember when they said Tesla is going to get involved into producing ventilators
because we need them when this word got out, by the way, that the hospitals were
killing people by putting them on ventilators and asphyxiating them, whatever.
A lot of the truckers that were doing these emergency shipments all over the
country found this out also.
And they would just pull over on the side of the road and dump the ventilators out
in the wild on the side of the highway.
Are you familiar with this?
I'd never heard that.
No. Wow.
OK, you can look that up.
There might be still news articles about it.
Quite a bit of like the smaller journalists, like, hey, look, it's talking
about they need ventilators, all these ventilators, you know, industrial grade,
hospital grade ventilators and boxes dumped on the side of the highway or dumped
near a swamp, like near a bay.
Right. Right, because they knew what was going on.
Basically, there was like sending execution.
If you go with the old let's bring up the National Socialist Party, we're going to
call them the Nazis.
Right. Those people.
Yeah, those people.
OK, well, they did what they did started really in forty four.
What started really in forty two, forty three.
They had the final solution and all that other crap.
Right. OK. Forty six.
They had the Nuremberg. So they got away less than within four years.
Of what they did, let's say, with death camps, by the way, half of the
half of the death camps were made by the Russians, by the way, not the right.
And they're attributed to be made by the Nazis and they're not.
This is if you can get the accurate information.
Right. And it was a political thing, not a direct religious one, because there were
over a hundred thousand, quote unquote, practicing Jews in the German war mocked
in the army and they were not put in camp.
Right. You could look this up.
This is academia, University of Kansas or whatever recently did a paper 10 years
ago. If they were so anti-Jewish, how come there were over a hundred thousand
troops fighting in the in the Vomit, you know, the Nazi army.
Right. Why weren't they put in camps?
I see. So there's a lot of technical stuff.
What happened there?
Well, I'm trying to say it was around four years time.
That they, let's say, committed whatever atrocities they did, quote unquote,
genocide and the Nuremberg trials, roughly four years.
Right. Forty two. Forty six.
Nuremberg. Forty seven. Right about there.
Yes. You see where I'm at.
Right. That four year mark right now.
So what I'm trying to say.
These doctors, they do they think they're going to get off scot free?
Apparently, probably.
And the people working there are so arrogant that then what did the Nazis do when
they figured out the people figured out what was going on?
They ran and hid.
How many of these medical people are still working in the hospital administration
office and doctors, whatever, that were culpable?
They actually laughed about it.
There's one nurse I talked to and she said, I'm quitting.
And I said, why? She goes, you know, I went to the head nurse.
Why are we putting people on ventilators?
Right. And the head nurse says, well, you know, you know, that's all she kept
saying. Well, you know, you know, you know, that's a blow up.
That's like, you know, well, it is what it is.
Yeah, exactly. So, OK, at this point, the people that are culpable, which is most
of the medical community, by the way, that's involved with administrative
hospital, this type of stuff.
And they're still in their jobs, cushy, cushy.
There's a lot of doctors that did quit.
But that doesn't make any kind of media, by the way.
Not a lot enough to notice it as a trend that would be reported on where
people go to get sort, you know, normal sources of reporting.
But they would learn and it would still be hard to find who's quit.
But there's quite a few.
There was I know I've gotten one to quit before it all started.
Yeah, there was like a couple of weeks there where they were reporting that
people were threatening to quit and were going to quit at hospitals and then
poop that went away. They were fired, too.
Yeah, they were fired, too.
Yeah. But that's fine.
That's good. But OK, so here's the thing.
Is there going to be any retribution for all this or is everything hunky dory?
Or can you say.
They're so distracted with everything else.
Right. So the there's a level of hypocrisy
here that most people that are sort of aware know the facts that I just gave.
Notice I called the facts.
I can't call it the truth because I I wasn't there directly to witness it.
Right. But I don't need to be.
You know, I don't need to get hit by a car to know that it's bad.
Right. So true enough.
Yeah. So that's a fact.
You don't want to get hit by a car if you want to be have a pleasant life.
So at least at any speed.
So, of course, the level of ignorance.
This is just going to continue.
So in other words, another thing that comes up often
when I bring up medical, so to say, oh, are you a doctor?
Then, you know, then you can't talk about that subject basically. Right.
And I'm like, do I need to be a criminal to be to accuse someone of a crime
or do I need to be an attorney to accuse someone of a crime?
You just got to know what's going on.
Yeah. But that's not the programming.
That's not the brainwashing they have.
When you start bringing up medical stuff.
To whatever, you know, the collective, are you a doctor?
Then that means that anything you say, you know, is cast to be disregard.
Or if you bring up legal stuff, are you an attorney?
Right. Yeah, exactly.
That's exactly the response.
Yeah. So they so in other words, that's part of programming brainwashing.
I think I bring I keep bringing this up. It's very important,
especially younger people, but especially older people.
Wait a second.
What I say, especially younger people and especially older people.
How about those in the middle?
Let's include them, especially middle people in the middle.
So I got everybody sounds like everybody.
Yeah. Sounds like everybody.
OK, so I'd say that more than half of their response is on anything,
whether it's private stuff they're doing in the bedroom,
the dinner table at work, on the way to work, brushing their teeth
or whatever, combing their hair, whatever, feeding their dogs and pets or whatever.
Their behavior and the way they think is because I mean, this is formulated
and and emulating and mimicking things that they saw in the media film.
Television, right, even read in a book, but fiction.
Isn't that interesting?
How many times have you if you actually you might want to recapitulate
and think about it when you speak to people that are, quote, unquote,
more of the collective and filter out
in this way, filter out, like set aside what responses
and behaviors they use, observe them that they have
that comes directly from television, let's say.
And you're going to see a tremendous amount of what they say, think and do
comes from the way they've seen it done and said and thought of on television.
So that's why I've always I've been bringing up, especially on Rated Y.
This is the as seen on TV people, right?
There's a there's a big thing about, you know, for a while,
not even I use it about the NPCs, right?
Yeah. But people are not pointing out.
These are more like most part of the NPC lore.
And and it's not more than lore.
It's a fact most common people is there as seen on TV people.
They really are.
And I think I even brought this up in a recent Sonic.
When you see a scene in the kitchen where someone, let's say, in a diner
or a coffee shop is breaking eggs over a griddle, how they drop them from
a foot high or six inches on. Right. Right.
You ever see how eggs are broken in the movies?
Right. Whatever. That's how people do it at home.
You shouldn't do that.
You should lower crack the egg and lower it to the pan.
And where the shell touches the pan and then open it slowly.
Right. That's what makes the most sense.
But yeah, like you said, they saw it done on TV.
They saw it done. OK.
How about lighting cigars?
These assholes are nice to go to these bars.
They were like the not like a seedy bar, but it was like the the what would you
call it was a steakhouse bar.
You know, it was kind of like the Golden Ghetto part of even when I was in New York.
I remember, you know, the the more high end lounges.
Right. You know where you could, you know, order a four hundred dollar bottle
of wine, kind of whatever, or get, you know, a fifty dollar shot of tequila or
something. Right. OK.
So there were there were the better places and the not so better places.
I mean, I see an asshole sitting there and he lights a cigar with the flame
right on the tobacco.
Right. Now, most people, sorry, if you don't know, you should always light
a fine tobacco, especially wrapped like that by induction.
In other words, you hold the cigar away from the flame
and you let the heat of the flame, like the the tobacco, never put the flame
on the tobacco because of the oils, fine tobaccos that are rich in oil.
When you put the flame to it, you ignite the oil and it makes the oil that didn't
ignite rancid. Right.
So you always want to light a cigar by induction where you rotate the cigar and
you have the lighter at least four inches away and you rotate it slowly, take
puffs until you feel a number.
Right. Never put the flame on the tobacco, even with cigarettes, if you smoke
cigarettes or enjoy cigarettes, try to light them without touching the flame to
the tobacco. Right.
The only thing that was if you're doing a bong hit, it's kind of hard because the
fire goes the other way.
Yeah. So I wanted to invent a bowl that that's upside down so you can light it by
induction. And it tastes completely different once you experience it.
Well, they have bowls like that where you actually heat the bowl instead of.
Yeah. Yes. It's an element.
Yeah. Screen screen that gets hot.
Right. Right. Right.
But you're you know, it's electric.
You heat the screen instead of heating instead of lighting the stuff on fire.
You. Right. So it'd be no flame contact.
So why am I talking about this?
Because this is a very stark example with where the wrong thing to do, say or
whatever, is mimic because it's been influenced by the media again.
So by the looks of it, the arrogance of the medical community where they're not
quitting or droves or, you know, the word isn't getting around that they're working
with murderers, basically.
This is premeditated murder, by the way, because they were sent they were
incentivized by the Federal Reserve, basically.
By the way, you know, the Federal Reserve announced the covid thing.
Right. And then the second announcement was by big tech.
And we were in Silicon Valley.
They told people don't come home, work from home.
But the the the head of the Federal Reserve and then the Treasury guy came out.
I forgot the day they announced the lockdowns and he said they were the ones that
announced it. Go go look it up.
Right. It was very short.
You probably find it on C-SPAN.
It was only like two. You know how they make two minute speeches because, you know.
Anyway. Right.
The other thing I want to bring up is the fraud of the medical establishment is this
is the basis of it. Then I want to get to an email.
This is the established fraud of the OK, the medical society, the medical side is
very powerful, pharmaceutical, all that.
So is the legal societies, the Bar Association or the the Crown, you know,
whatever. Then you have the industrial.
Everyone talks about the military industrial complex, which is just really a
distraction. The medical industry and the legal industry is way bigger than the
military. Right.
And insurance is bigger than all of them, but they're all put to wrap together.
Right. What's going on is the people that run.
There's a very small group. You want to call them a cabal or whatever, but it's
actually a beyond cabal.
And by the way, if you've ever heard of them or their name or seen them or in
history books or in media, that's that's not what I'm talking about.
These people are completely secret.
They view society as a bunch of idiotic assholes or moronic assholes.
And they don't think you deserve any hospitals, medical treatment, drugs, anything
at all. If they called that and they said, OK, let's just deny them of all that
stuff. The people would then go and try to do it on their own.
Right. Right.
So they figured instead of that scenario happening, because trust me, they would
not want they don't want any any cures, any proper care, proper diagnosis, proper
training of doctors at all, at all.
That doesn't exist anymore for a long time, almost a century.
Or more, it does not exist.
So they figured it's very smart, but it's very basic, smart, like, you know, eighth
grade. If we do that, the people then will do a grassroots thing and then it'll
take off. And because, you know, right, it's not incentivized by money or whatever.
Let's say credit. So what they decided to do was invest in it propaganda that it's
there to help you.
But in the meantime, they're making up all these false diagnoses.
Right. In diseases that don't exist.
Right. Yes.
People are sick, but not because of what they're telling you.
Right. And develop all these methods.
It's all tied in basically with the central banking.
Right. If you don't believe that when you go to a hospital, they give you this legal
form. It's it's got a white copy, a yellow copy and a pink copy, maybe even a green
copy. And when you write on it, it goes through all pages.
Right. Whenever you see anything like that, that's that's central bank paperwork.
If you read all of that, you should see how vague the pricing is.
It says you're at the hospital and the cost will be what's commonly accepted.
You know what should be the charge or whatever.
It's like never anything very vague language because it's all monetized.
If you go to the hospital with anyone asking insurance, definitely not.
Don't say no. Say definitely not.
And they look like, oh, what do you mean?
Definitely not.
And he said, if I'm going to fill out this registration form, I need a cash receipt for
it. And they're like, well, what cash?
I'm like, I just need something that says cash receipt on it and signed by an
administrator. For how much?
No. Yeah, exactly.
For how much? How much are you monetizing this for?
Right. Well, I don't know.
Nobody knows. But I just need evidence that I provided something with cash value.
Well, you know, that's paper. Yeah.
You know, there's proof of what you're saying here is that you take two people that
go to the same hospital, get for the same reason, get the same treatment.
And guess what? The bills never, ever or even remotely similar.
No. Well, not only that, the bills come from third parties.
Yeah. But they monetize.
But we're going to get to the email question.
We that this is going to tie into it.
Well, I'm just saying monetize it.
Right. So when they monetize it, though, they monetize it in such a way that it's not
like a doctor costs this, a pill costs that a bad cost.
None of that. There's no consistent pricing.
But most people are confused about the monitor.
OK, I got an email from a wonderful young chap.
He's young because he's around 30.
OK, I enjoy speaking with him.
I have spoken with him and I enjoy corresponding with him.
But I also want to bring up there's a level of naivete here.
It's a healthy level, though.
You know, when you say someone is naive, that doesn't sound right.
Right. Yeah.
Yeah. It almost sounds like you're degraded, denigrating the person, you know.
No, there's there's also a healthy level of innocence and naivety, right?
Nations, let's just say.
Right. So there's a healthy level of it that exists amongst people, especially when
they're searching. That's not even to be more forgiving, but it's more giving.
Right. Because the person is actually in terms of spiritually, they have a pretty
clean bill of health, let's say.
Right. And they'll bring up a question that some might say, some that are more
seasoned on the subject may say that's a stupid question, but it's not because it
shows that, again, people that are raised by the television or the media.
Right. How do you how do you show them another way and try to anchor to them that
the way that they know is pure fiction?
It's very difficult.
That's where that's where I have what's called the replacement theory.
Right. You offer them a substitute or an alternative and it's there they have to
pick. Right.
Right. You don't say that's wrong.
Stop it. Do this.
Right. You don't do that.
You just offer.
I'd make an offering.
And if they don't take it, then they're free to go with however they want to go.
So let's bring up there's in this question and we're going to we're going to do a
sonic on this is about twenty five questions and they're all very pertinent.
But you said about monetizing and all that.
Now, by the way, I did mention this about the form being monetized for a cash
receipt and the person got a harsh response from the administrators because they
just didn't say it right.
Yes, there is a wrong way to say it.
But you have to, for example, you know, there's this Patriots, they go into court
and they talk about the straw man and all that.
And the judge just destroys them because they if you go into a setting like that,
they know when you just found this out online or someone told you to say and you
really don't know. Right.
Just like people like when I see people say and do things that are on TV, I just
shake my head. I'm like, oh, you got that.
I don't always say you got that from television.
So you really don't know.
Right. You shouldn't.
But when you go into a legal setting or administrative setting and they see that you
just pick this up because you don't really know it, the ins and outs, you just felt
that it was a way to lash out and say that they'll they'll tear you apart.
Yeah, because you just picked up a couple of phrases, a couple of keywords.
And yeah, you're messing with their bread and butter because they're there.
You know, that's what they're there for to deceive.
And you're going to say, oh, yeah, you know that it's all deception, but you really
don't know how you're just trying to throw some one liner at us.
So fuck you. Right.
Is what they basically jump on you.
So each that's why there's nothing you can say in any situation.
Yeah, I could give advice on what to say here or what to say there or to who to
whatever. But you can't just take it and say what I'm saying, because I wouldn't
say that. You see, I don't know what to say when depends on the situation.
Right. Well, it's like people who turn around and they give you a solution that
they heard from somewhere, like, here's the answer to that question.
You go, oh, really? Well, how'd you come to that?
They have no idea how they got there.
Yeah, well, here's the thing. That's not even that.
But even if they do that, if it's still a one liner, it'll be picked up and you
really have to know the material and feel it because each situation will
be completely different.
But I was going to say that happens to me every time with the JFK thing where somebody
goes, well, I know this and I go, really?
OK, how do you know that? And they have no idea.
They might be the same question or the same fact, but it's a different person and you
have to bring it forward in a different way.
I can almost tell where they got the stupid thing.
Of course. That's what I'm talking about.
Oh, I hear exactly that phrase.
And you know what? I know very well that comes from this person's presentation that
you saw online because I know all this stuff already.
It happens all the time. It's like I know exactly where you got that nonsense.
And this is, you know, yeah, OK, you got some of it right.
But yeah, I hear you either.
Yeah, you actually know you're not invested, right?
Not at all. Someone who's investing in ripping in doing ripping really society
because that's their whole life is depending on and they like it.
And when they hear someone trying to, let's say, object to it or they see it as a
baby protesting. Right.
By the way, if any reject the saying like taking candy from a baby, reject that.
That's very difficult. Have you ever tried to take candy from a baby?
Man, they hold on to that thing.
You could lift the whole baby carriage and everything with the candy taking.
I'm serious. They got like one hell of a grip.
No, it's it's right. A really resistant small child is not.
You cannot take it from.
It's not that easy.
You're right. No, no.
So these things again, those are I've seen on TV again, disproved.
All right. So here let's just get into this.
I'm going to start from the bottom.
This is all tied in signature.
This is a question. The title of the question.
You mentioned when someone votes that the signature gets monetized for fifty
thousand dollars. Well, around fifty thousand.
Yes. Maybe more.
I still don't understand how a signature can have so much value.
Just thinking even a signed Michael Jordan rookie card may not even be worth that
much. What am I missing?
That is a very healthy, naive person.
OK. Right. Do you see that's a very well asked, but it's like
third grader. Right.
And I'm speaking on fifth grader level, but I always start on the third grader.
This is third grade, right?
Eight years old. Third grade.
Something like that. Something like that.
Yeah, that's honest. And right.
So how would you explain this to children?
Because the use factor with an eight year old is really minimal with money.
The only experience that I have is coins.
But now I think they get cards and accounts on the phone.
Right. Well, that's where we used to ask for change.
Yeah. No, see, that's the thing.
We used to handle getting 50, 50 cents in 1972.
Was not bad. It was pretty good.
Yeah. You got a slice of pizza and a soda for a quarter.
Oh, look, five bucks.
I could do a lot with five bucks.
I mean, you know what? Yeah. Yeah.
So so now I think they get it.
So electronic. I mean, whatever.
So, yeah. OK, so this is all right.
So this is very naive. OK, let's go do a very rapid history.
And what's interesting is there's whenever I repeat something,
it's never identical, right?
You might get maybe something else will come out.
What money basically is. OK.
The Greek speak money, if you want to go on a very high level,
not because it speaks to you, but a very high level.
Money is portable land
because you're supposed to live off the land.
And everything you need is.
And what I mean, like a society,
you can have 50 million people living off the land.
Here's the mining. This is where the mining done.
This is where the manufacturing.
This is the agriculture.
This is the red light district.
This is this. This is that.
And everybody gets along by exchanging whatever they exchange.
We're not talking about barter now. Right.
But once you leave that area where you have a semi closed system
and I said semi closed, because let's say you do imports and exports.
Right. So you're not a closed system.
You're not isolationist.
Once you leave, personally travel,
you lose the benefit of doing that exchange, that network that you're in.
So you have to bring something that represents your land.
That's why when you look at money, you notice that each geographic
region has its own name on it, like this is Japanese currency.
This is EU. This is the United States of America.
Notice the country name is on there because it's land based.
Right. Not bank. Not right.
OK, so portable land.
So it was decided a long time ago that
portable land is precious metals.
Why? OK, so you're going to carry land with you.
Enough topsoil to represent, you know, to do barter with.
How much or you can carry an ounce of gold.
Right now, how much topsoil will an ounce of gold get you?
A truckload, two truckloads, 10 truckloads, maybe more. Right.
So it's not practical to carry 10, 10 truckloads of topsoil.
Right. It's more practical to have a gold coin.
Ah, per portability. OK, so this is this is the way things are.
There's no there's no very little inflation with this, by the way.
So the price of things are the same.
Actually, the the the price changes, but the value of things are the same.
Let me just get into this.
A gold piece is twenty dollars.
Dollar is a weight measurement.
OK, so when you say a one ounce of gold is twenty dollars,
it doesn't matter if it's a thousand years ago or a thousand years from now.
It's twenty dollars because dollar is a weight.
OK, so that's what twenty is known as a score.
That's why in the old cowboy movies, where are you going after him?
I got a score to settle.
Right. Means the guy owes him a twenty dollar gold piece, an ounce of gold.
Right. OK, here you go.
A little trivia for you.
So remember Lincoln's speech for score and whatever.
Right. You know, 20 scores, 20. So.
What you have, what a twenty dollar gold piece got you
would have been, let's say, 300 years ago,
200 years ago, 150 years ago,
500 years ago, if you were a man, it got you a very nice hat,
a nice jacket with nice pants and a shirt
and some undergarments and a nice pair of shoes, not the best,
but quality stuff.
You're able to get a full outfit, a very high quality shoes, boots.
Right. Choose your boots.
You know, you don't buy shoes by the pound, right?
You can get boots that are cheaper than shoes and vice versa. Right.
Of course. OK, pants, you know, the whole outfit undergarment,
but very, very, very high quality stuff with one ounce,
twenty dollar gold piece for hundreds and hundreds of years.
Today, gold is over two thousand dollars an ounce. Right. Right.
It's could be in the twenty two hundred or something.
I don't I don't think it broke over twenty one. But anyway. So
with the value of one ounce of gold, which is not two thousand
because it's fiat currency,
you can still outfit yourself very well with a nice pair of shoes or boots,
nice pair of pants, nice shirt, nice undergarment, underwear,
nice jacket and a nice hat for two thousand bucks.
You'd be pressed to spend it all on nice stuff.
I'm not talking about going, getting Gucci, Fiorucci or whatever.
Talking about, you know, where normal, where
none were the majority of people shop for clothing,
go in there and buy the best stuff they have to offer.
I'm not talking about thirty thousand dollar handbags. Right.
Or twenty thousand dollar cowboy boots. No. Right.
So if you're in an urban suburban environment,
you go to the best department store, the best shops and say,
what's your best hat? I want it. What's your best jacket? I want it.
Your best pants. I want it. Your best things to put on my feet.
I want and it'll be still around two thousand dollars
to outfit yourself with the best stuff. Right. OK.
So things don't change.
But the the reason why it's two thousand dollars, by the way,
when when gold goes over two thousand dollars means that the buying power
of the Fiat Federal Reserve note dollar is less than a penny now
because at two thousand right.
Twenty times one hundred is two thousand.
So that makes it a penny. Right. Right.
So the buying power of the dollar today, the American Federal Reserve note,
a version of the dollar is what is what a penny bought you when it was gold back.
It's pretty scary. Right.
What I mean by this also, I haven't gotten to the question.
I'm just giving more background that I don't think I've ever discussed
in 1680 or 1750.
The years you went to buy a shovel, it was about a dollar,
which is a silver piece. Right.
An ounce of silver is a dollar in 1910, 150, 180, almost 200 years later.
You went to the hardware store.
Guess how much a shovel was still about a dollar.
No inflation or the price to stay the same because they're based on
precious metals or things that are hard goods.
Right. Hard material. Right. OK.
But there is inflation with silver.
When a new silver mine happens and they flood the market with silver,
the silver could lose its value, but they still use the they trade it on par.
It'll never it could lose its value, but it'll still be a dollar.
All right. It'll still buy what a dollar buys you or less
to a degree, depending on where the inflation is happening.
OK, so what happened basically when the banking system
started to grow and they got more technical with, quote, unquote,
merchant methods, the way that merchants deal with each other.
You know, when a ship pulls into a harbor and they have a manifest,
that manifest can be used as money.
What's on the ship, right?
I'm not going to get into that now because that's getting into
what's called the Tontine system.
T-O-N-T-I-N-E.
Look that word up.
It's even it's even hard to look it up.
So it's an insurance based merchant system, the law merchant.
By the way, when you an attorney is a law, it was a law merchant.
They hate that when you call them that. That's what they are.
A law merchant. In other words, it's all about merchant law.
So these bills of exchange and these paperwork, just like, for example.
OK, Chuck, I'm going to go mow your lawn.
Right. But you can't pay me.
I mean, use a loose term.
So you're going to give me an IOU for mowing the lawn.
Right. And I carry that. OK.
And so let's say five dollars.
You owe me that. Right. OK.
Now, I could go to this person over here, Billy,
and I owe him five dollars.
So I give him the IOU.
So instead of being paying me five dollars, you pay Billy.
And proof that you pay.
I don't have to be there because he has the paper and I could transfer.
I do what's called on a lawn on it, which is a transfer.
Pay, please pay.
Chuck, please pay to Billy this and I'm signing it. Right.
So now here comes Billy, who you've never met.
Knocks on your door because he knows the address.
Right. Right. And who are you?
He says, well, you owe me the five.
I get the five bucks from the Greek. Oh, really?
How do I know you're not frauding me?
Well, here I have in a launch.
So you see how I can get into all this, but I'm not. All right.
What I want to get into is what the bankers did.
What's called fractional reserve banking.
When people were bringing their gold to the banks for safekeeping,
just like people today put things in safe deposit box.
Big mistake. Don't do it. Right.
They deliberately raid FBI, FBI raids boxes to tell you stupid people.
What are you doing? Right.
Anyway, you've heard of that, right? Yeah.
OK. Yeah. And they just do it for no reason.
I mean, well, they do because you never did anyway.
Conditional endorsement.
Let's get back to the subject.
Fractional banking reserve banking is based on this.
When the bankers were holding on to people's gold and giving them interest,
they noticed that less than 10 percent of the people
were frequently coming back to take their gold out.
So they said, hmm, if for every dollar's
worth of gold or silver we have, we can write bank notes
that are good for for the gold at a rate of ten to one, because
not everyone's going to come and take the gold.
So when there's a bank run, everyone comes in, they're in trouble. Right.
And what the note does is
like the portable land did for having gold.
You can't bring topsoil.
So if you have gold coins and you want to go make a big purchase,
you're going to lug along all these big gold coins.
No, it's easier to have paper money. Right.
Doesn't weigh anything. You put it in your purse, your wallet.
That's what the bankers took advantage of. Right.
So a thousand pieces of silver is a thousand ounces. Right. Right.
That's quite a few. Right.
What's a thousand divided by 16? Right.
Let's say let's say it was 10 ounces.
It would be 100 pounds of silver, roughly about 75 pounds of silver.
You're going to lug that around. It's too damn hard to carry. I got it.
Yeah. So you got paper money.
And what the bankers did, they announced it. No, not too many people.
There were some complaints.
There were some problems with the fractional reserve. OK.
So you get a ten to one.
Right, so that ten to one doesn't mean if they deposit a thousand,
they turn it into ten thousand becomes nine thousand. Right.
I'm sorry. It's it's nine times, not ten times.
And they keep the one in reserve.
So it's always a multiple of nine.
But it's easier to say ten because that's what they call it. Right. All right.
So what's going on now is if you're familiar
with the gold confiscation clause that the Federal Reserve
16th Amendment, Federal Reserve, all this other stuff came in.
Seemed like a good idea.
They put together a reason, you know, we can expand the money supply.
Elastic money, elastic money is where rubber check came from, by the way,
because the law does say elastic currency, which is rubber checks.
They always made fun of it.
By the way, back in the 20s and 30s,
if you said you were going to pay someone with a check, they laughed at you.
So you're trying to pull a scam or what?
Hmm. All right. This I'm serious.
Workers were paid in cash.
That's why if you look at any black and white movies,
when you have a corporate boss, there's always a big safe in the corporate office
because every week someone would go to the bank and bring cash
and the workers would come in, they'd sign a slip and they get their pay
weekly pay in cash paper.
No checks, no bank big. Very rare to have a bank account. Right.
It wasn't until the 1950s.
So they started doing big propaganda to get people to get checking
because before that, it was considered a fraud, which it is.
OK, so what happened now with the gold confiscation clause
when all the gold was sent overseas and you can find articles
on this every month, 50 million dollars worth of gold
was sent to Europe, Germany in the 30s.
You could find the articles on your own. Right.
No more gold.
They bankrupted the country on March the 9th, 1933.
So it's the Federal Reserve.
What's in on reserve?
Is your signature the government through certificates
provided the banks with collateral?
How can you prove
a human being is your collateral
by providing a birth certificate that they agree
that you have agency over them?
Right. Just like the car, just like the house, whatever.
So now, since your signature is just like gold.
They still apply the ten to one fractional reserve banking.
So let's say you do a credit card.
Let's just explain for the question.
OK, and what maybe we'll just end it here and we'll pick it up again.
Because there's so many parallel ways
to talk about this.
OK, let's say the person who asked the question on the email.
Think about it this way.
This is exactly what's going on.
It's probably worse.
But exactly the principle.
You have a discover card, master card, American Express, whatever.
And you go to Ace Hardware or a hardware store and you get exactly.
Let's just say it rings up exactly one hundred dollars.
And you swipe the card.
Doesn't matter if it's debit, cash, credit, whatever.
Forget it. The same.
Oh, it's all the same. It's just a different show. Right.
So a debit would be a magician pulling a rabbit out of a hat.
And credit card would be the magician pulling, you know,
you know, something else out of his sleeve.
It's the same form of trickery, just different part. Right.
I think I've explained what happens when you when you're dead.
But it's either right.
It's all a show. The money's still there. Right. OK.
So you go to the stove at whatever store.
I used to use Sears as an analogy.
And you swipe the card exactly one hundred dollars.
What happens at that moment?
Something pops up. It used to be paper.
But what pops up is, is you agreed you agreed to perform
authorize everything according to the cardholders agreement
is what it says on the screen.
Very vague language, just like the language
that's that you see on the hospital registration form. Right.
OK. Now, soon as you sign that, by the way,
I sign everything void like a doctor.
It looks like a looks like a signature.
Some people say, what kind of signature is that?
So I think it's like a doctor signs, you know.
But if I tell you if if I tell you on the side, hey, that's void.
And you look at it. Oh, yeah.
Now I see it because there's a little dot over where the eye would be. OK. Right.
So you should you know, this is all fraudulent.
Why do you want to put your name on something anyway?
I got some money.
This is I have a long story about that.
I have to make it short, but not this time. OK.
So remember, as soon as that pops up that you agree to sell, you sign
according to the cardholders agreement. Right.
Through the processing power of whatever
A.I. or computers have been doing the same computers for a long time.
I think they're so cheap, the bankers that they're still trying to use
the same computers with DOS from 1980, really.
You know, they are. Yeah.
So there was no DOS in 1980.
But anyway, Fortran, Cobalt.
But what happens at that point, the computers pull up.
The transaction number and what's pre-programmed is the ten to one
immediately on the banking side, nine hundred dollars is created
soon as you authorize that on the terminal.
Right, because ten to one remember for the every dollar of gold
they had, ten dollars was in existence.
Nine was created by the bankers. Right. Right.
So what happens now, the hundred dollar payment that you swipe
and you authorize right there in a millisecond, whatever long it takes,
sometimes it takes a little longer than a millisecond.
Nine hundred dollars is created out of that.
Nine hundred dollars.
A hundred dollars is sent to the merchant.
Boom. Right there.
Eight hundred dollars is left. And that's it.
Right. Eight hundred dollars is left.
And that's divided between certain government agencies,
the banks and the people.
At the end of the month, though, let's say it's a credit card.
Yeah. You still get a bill for that hundred dollars.
And they're laughing at you.
They're like, if you know anyone that's higher up in the debt collection,
they don't want to talk about what they do, because it's like
people should know that they don't know anything, basically,
is what you get out of a conversation with an administrator
in the debt collection business. Right. Right.
It's because they don't know they don't know anything.
We owe them, actually.
So what should be going on?
Five to 10 percent is reasonable interest when you create money. Right.
What should be happening is when you go swipe that
that credit card for a hundred dollars or debit card,
they should be giving you the hundred dollar
whatever payment, plus another hundred dollars on it for using the card.
And they keep now seven hundred.
By the way, that is being done.
But on a smaller level, how many times have you seen commercials
for use master visa, whatever, and get what cash back cash back?
Yeah. How much do they give you?
Twenty bucks or something. Right.
Two, three percent, something like that. Yeah.
So what I'm telling you, they're applying.
If you know and the Volkswagen sign and drive, all you need is to sign.
Yeah, sign and drive. Right.
And I can go on to give you more evidence and more evidence
and more evidence and more evidence.
By the way, if you look up the FTCPA federal laws,
the government feds at the time did put a little remedy in there
that if someone says that you owe them money, they have to send a letter
of validation and it has to pass federal standards.
In other words, has to be under penalty of perjury.
All you need to do is cite the code FTCPA validation letter.
And they made it so it works for the people.
But people don't know about it.
Use it. There's what lies in your debt group.
If you want to join them, they're a little convoluted,
but they got the right idea.
It's called what lies in your debt group,
not endorsing them, but they do good, good work. OK.
Validation letter, if they don't say if the next time they contact you,
whether it's by phone or mail, if it's not a validation letter,
it's a five hundred dollar time per instance and what you can do.
You know how they love sending letters, right?
Oh, yeah. Let them rack up the letters to like five or ten letters and then say,
hey, you know, you FTCPA violation five thousand dollars or you got ten letters.
I'm going to draft a federal lawsuit
and I'm going to email you. What do you want to do?
They always settle. They never go to court.
And there's and it doesn't go on the credit report
because there never was a debt to begin with.
There's people that could make a living with credit cards,
just rack up the credit card, do FTCPA,
and they pay you the fines and then you write.
You see, I'm not promoting this because that means working in a demonic system.
But this is no, you don't have to.
But this is the reality of it.
Well, if you're going to do it that way, you'd have to, though.
That's the only way you can work with you.
I mean, the only way to make that work for you is to work within it.
Yeah, good. Right.
But so let me answer that question directly.
Michael Jordan's signature is hard to get 50,000.
But how are they monetizing your signature is your signature?
Is what they did is when they if you look up how gold is fractionalized,
fractional reserve banking from the early 20th century.
When the gold was obfuscated, they replaced the gold with your signature
and they're doing exactly the same thing with your signature.