Sonic Event 31, Ocelli and the Greek rated Y.
Yeah, I'll announce that every time anyway.
Greek, interesting mood tonight.
I guess we should kick it off with pork.
Bacon.
Kevin Bacon.
Why not?
If you want to know what I'm thinking, listen to what I'm saying.
I said, Chuck, I stopped listening to you about 30 seconds ago.
Let's get, let's start recording, right?
So we started off talking about bacon and it was funny what you played, right?
Some cartoon thing.
But I retorted saying that the reason I've discovered what I've discovered is because
I stayed away from all the mainstream stuff.
If you showed me a picture of Kevin Bacon, I'd call him Tom Cruise.
All the white guys are Tom Cruise in Hollywood to me and all the black guys are Will Smith
or Eddie Murphy.
My wife, the wife always laughs about that, right?
I said, look, Tom Cruise is a new movie.
She looks like this.
That's not Tom Cruise.
That's so-and-so.
I'm like, yeah, it's a white actor.
It's Tom Cruise.
Black actors, Eddie Murphy or Will Smith.
That's how much I care about anything they put out for the no Wesley, no Wesley Snipes
in there.
No, no.
James Earl Jones.
I've heard of those guys.
When I was much younger, actually, I have a family that's in the film business pretty
high up.
There is about as high as you could go.
And I'm still not interested because I know I actually, uh, I played around with film.
I was a scout locator, you know, a long time ago and, uh, talking about, let's see, I'll
give you a, what, 1985.
How long ago is that?
Well, it's almost, uh, it's two, it's a two years shy of 40, right?
38 years ago.
So yeah, yeah.
It was funny story.
These guys, I was being a scout locator.
It was contracts for them, but they paid me a salary and they figured if I work real quick,
they'll pay me the salary or the wages and they'll keep the, they'll keep the, um, the
balance.
Okay.
It turned out it didn't take that.
It wasn't that quick.
And, uh, it took a long time and they ended up, you know, uh, getting upset that they
didn't make money over the money that they were supposed to give me, if that makes any
sense, right?
It's like a hundred bucks to Chuck.
Maybe I'll get him to do it for 70 and I'll keep the 30 and it works out that you need
120.
So anyway, yeah, I lose money on it because what I did is I, I basically, uh, put you
in the contract, hire you out for a certain amount and then it ends up costing me more
than what I actually collected on your behalf.
Yeah, I got you.
Right, right.
So in other words, when they got the contract amount, it was under, it was really, really
short and they didn't know it.
And I didn't know it was a con I say, if you guys told me it was a contract thing, I would
have kicked back 20, 10, 15% to you anyway, and would have done it for the contract without
keeping time.
But your lack of, uh, what would you call it?
Uh, when you're, when you have open rec or openness, uh, is what candor or transparency
or honesty or whatever, so that we're working together, but everyone's trying to subjugate
everyone else.
Right?
That's, you know what I've been saying?
Not everyone, but you know what they do is they, you're, the population is trained to
give 99% of their effort to the corporations and then stab each other in the back for the
remaining 1% where it could be the other way around.
Give 1% of the corporations, uh, and don't stab each other in the back.
99%.
It's interesting.
I recognized, uh, this week, actually, you know, in a personal situation that somebody
asked me why it is that people, you know, constantly try to push certain things out
of me.
I said, because I make the mistake of being too honest.
See, they expect me to be the one trying to, you know, by subterfuge con and extra something
or other out of them.
And I'm not, I just know this is what it is.
Like, okay, somebody comes to you and says, uh, look, um, I need a certain amount of money
to do something.
You agree to pay him.
Okay.
They come to you and they say, okay, you ready to do that?
And you say, look, I don't have the money right now.
They don't hear, I don't have the money right now.
Literally.
They think he's holding back.
He has the money.
He just doesn't want to pay it right now.
Or he's trying to get, get it for less when literally I've actually communicated the honest
thing.
No, I just don't have it at this moment.
It's called mindset.
In other words, that person will do that no matter who they're talking to.
Not just, in other words, you know, you've heard the term, don't take it personal.
Yeah.
Well, but that's the thing is it's like the problem I'm having is that I honestly communicate
it.
See, I'm not going along with the way everybody else is doing business with them, but you can't
be honest.
In other words, it's in that other person's mindset.
There's no such thing.
It's my, this is the way I see the world and people.
And that's it.
There's no possibility that I just simply told the, well, come on, if we do this, if
that doesn't change what I just told you, I already told you, I didn't play a game
with you.
I told you up front, this is what is, you know, they're confused in games.
You've played poker.
Yeah.
Games.
You don't have to be honest because it's a game.
So I don't know, but that's anyway, let's when, no, but when you're honestly, okay.
When I honestly deal with some, it's like, listen, I told you what it was to begin with.
So that's what it is.
They, they, they so can't compute the idea that I've just honestly told them it isn't
here yet.
It can't be done yet.
They think that I'm somehow doing something else.
So therefore it just never gets to their mind that, Oh, he didn't just tell me that to save
us all time and energy and just to be straight with what's going on.
No, that's not even possible.
You know?
And it's like, uh, so this is the thing is like, I realized my mistake is that I didn't
do like everybody else does.
This is, this is why I'm not getting the proper communication from them because they're insisting
on something that can't be done.
You know, it's the weirdest thing.
Well, well, you want to talk about weird things?
Yeah, sure.
Yeah.
Pork.
We were talking, we brought that up.
I've said this many times.
If, if you're a pork eater, like a Jimmy Dean sausages, Italian sausages, stuff, 10% would
no doubt.
No doubt.
I assure you.
I don't like to use the word guarantee because guarantee means you need to put up if it's
not.
So, right.
I assure you that five, two to 5% of all the pork you've ever eaten is, is, is human meat
in there.
Right?
Um, so anyway, that's, that's one.
And this has been known since ancient times and that practice has been done since ancient
times till now.
And you know what?
So now even more because it's very efficient years ago, if you wanted to process a human
being into a massive ground pork, you had to have people do it right now.
It could be fully automated, right?
So there's no witness other than the guy pushing the buttons and even then he could look away
for half an hour.
Right?
So yeah, it's pretty interesting.
Uh, well back then, if you go way back then, more things were automated.
You know, we were, I've been saying this since I was on with Seth Michael and revolution
radio in 2009, 2010.
Uh, if you dig down any major city in North America or North Africa under the Sahara,
I mean down more than 30 feet to 150 feet, you will find advanced civilizations.
As a matter of fact, they got this guy, Bob Lazar, right?
Area 51 guy.
Oh yeah.
Thousands of hours, hundreds of hours was taught.
But if you look at it very care, the part that I'm interested is where they find the
stuff.
Right?
And, and one, and one interview says, Oh, it's a, it was archeological dig.
They find the flying saucer, right?
Archeology, right?
Right.
And so anyway, um, yeah, pork, uh, don't do it.
Um, for many reasons, uh, the prionization, if you eat enough human and you're human,
you have problems.
If you eat enough cow and your cow, right?
The same cow.
Yeah.
Right.
Yeah, exactly.
Uh, so yeah.
And it's, then there's ethical and moral reasons, but we've always, I've talked about in the
past Sonics, the, the voice in the head, that's not you that keeps switching up as your consciousness,
let's say expands, um, that consciousness that's not you, that's you think is you, that
voice you hear in your head has a, it also lends you your morality.
In other words, you know, the cartoon where someone has the angel on one shoulder and
the devil on the other, right?
And one is that getting them on.
The other guy says, don't do it.
Well, that voice in your head does both that voice in your head tells you, Oh, go do that.
And that, and that same voice will say, but wait a second, you know, better.
So when you transcend that, when you go beyond that, you'll notice there is no right and
wrong.
It's what set of rules you agree to live by what covenant you live by.
There is no right and wrong.
And most of the time is nothing to do with it.
And most of the time when they show you that angel and that devil, the truth is, is that
the angel, the devil, or the same person, just one has horns.
One doesn't, you know, pretty much, right.
And that's it.
Uh, they're usually the same voice, even if they, uh, uh, anthropomorphize it using a
different individual.
Right.
Uh, you know, say they put you on, on my shoulder, uh, both as the angel and the devil, it'll
still be the same voice.
Just a, you know, that's my moral reasoning and the, and they have no more, they know,
but they see, they present this fiction known as a right and wrong or moral reasoning and
all that.
No, that, that only depends on what rules you go by.
You see that all the time on cop shows, you know, they do something unusual to a person
and they'll say, well, the law allows for us to do that.
Right.
We never heard of something so bizarre.
You see?
So, uh, yeah.
But, uh, the devils and all that, you know, a little spackle and paint makes a devil look
like a saint.
Right.
So anyway, the, the demon, a lot of the devils that you hear about through culture are actually
people that were demonized.
Right.
Yeah.
Or yeah, actually they were demonized.
Well, you know, look at history.
Right.
Yeah.
Most of the, it's all backwards.
So yeah, there's a stuff in the chat about, uh, lawfulness in terms of, uh, you know,
the covenant, let's say, uh, about mixed fibers.
That's real easy.
It states about, uh, don't put mixed fibers on your body.
It's not animal and vegetable.
Like, uh, if I see linen and cotton blend, I don't, I don't wear it.
And linen and cotton are both vegetable.
Right.
Okay.
Uh, right.
So, but, but you can have a one sewn onto the other.
I have a, a, a wool jacket that has a silk liner and the silk is a hundred percent silk
liner and a hundred percent wool coat.
And it does state, you can sew one fast and one onto the other, but don't weave them together.
Okay.
And it's not, it has nothing to do with animal or a vegetable.
It's interesting how people try to stretch these things out, like only wear natural fibers.
So well, wool is natural.
Cotton's natural.
So we'll cotton blend.
Right.
No, you know, you, you hear stuff like your food is your medicine and your medicine is
your food.
That's from the Bible.
Right?
No, it's not.
Right.
And you don't find stuff like that.
This is very, that's one of the things.
Here's the thing.
I live, I don't believe any of this.
I don't want to believe anything.
I decide, make a decision.
I make it.
Okay.
You have choices.
You make a choice and then you decide on that choice, right?
And when you do it, it's all or nothing.
You can't cherry pick, right?
But you need to resolve before you make that decision on the choice.
Listen very carefully.
Now you have choices.
You make a choice and then you decide.
They ask you that all the time.
Have you decided it?
You read an order?
Have you decided yet?
You got all the choices, right?
I made my choice.
I want the tuna fish, but I want it on, I don't want it on a sourdough.
I want it on rye.
All right.
You see, that's the decision, right?
Okay.
So you see the fine points here?
And before you make the decision, you have to see, are you going to accept it or not?
Like in marriage, for better or for worse, right?
That says there's no divorce, right?
Yeah.
Well, you've already accepted that you're going to eat here.
You're going to eat at this place.
You're going to eat food from this place.
A whole bunch of things have already been decided, right?
Now you get into the-
About marriage?
That could get real lascivious on that.
Well, no.
I wasn't going to the marriage.
I was back to the restaurant, but that's fine.
That's not eating at the place.
Okay.
So here's the thing.
I know this is never put out that way.
You have choices.
You make the choice.
And within that choice that you made, you decide whether it's really the decision part
is the committal.
And when you say something like, you know, when you, I give the sandwich board a lot,
you know, because you have choice, you know, unless you go to like a nice European place
that's price fix, then you could either have it or not be, right?
Okay.
You know, your price fix menu is one, you know, this is the appetizer.
This is the entree.
This is dessert.
That's it.
Well, I don't want the appetizer.
That's your only decision you can make.
You can't get another appetizer, right?
So that's a good example for there is no option for cherry picking.
But what I find with ancient Ritz, especially the Bible, people like the cherry pick a lot.
I'm going to do this, but I'm not going to do that.
Or this could mean that, you know, there was a, a very, what do you call it?
Reformist synagogue in the Bronx back in the sixties and the rabbi, you know, when they,
when religion seemed dogmatic and orthodox, they have reformists to make it more liberal.
Let's say, right.
Right.
And, and liberal, by the way, used to mean a good thing, by the way, you know, used to
be stuff, of course, is called liberal arts within the person who was a liberal arts major
or whatever.
It was very well versed in many different fields, you know, now it means something else.
But anyway, there was a liberal reformist synagogue in the Bronx and he basically said,
well, Torah says you shouldn't eat pork, but what it means is in certain restaurants.
Okay.
I don't know where that came in, but okay.
Yeah.
Well, I don't know where a lot of this stuff comes in that people bring up in scripture,
right?
Crucifixion is another one, right?
Well, that one's easy.
That one's easy to fall into that trap.
You know, a trap means you don't know better.
Right.
Because if you know avoidance of a trap is knowledge of its existence.
Once you know there's a trap there, there's no longer a trap.
Now, if you fall into it, now it's a tragedy.
Right.
So you mean you willingly went into, it's no longer a trap.
So so what I mean by this is the reason I've been speaking on these things for decades
now, it's not to make people believe, as a matter of fact, that's how people stay away
from it.
Because why?
You're not going to understand anything in it, because you need to have a high level
of comprehension.
And that's gone for most people.
Gone like gone.
And those that want to get interested in whatever they're going to read that's ancient or old,
they have to gain comprehension, general comprehension first, and then go back into it.
But the crucifixion part is really easy trap to fall into because they actually state it
in all the things.
Crucifixion, they actually write it in the version, the King James or whatever, right?
You see what I'm saying?
So and, and even the Greek, you know, these things don't mean any, they've actually, it's
called adulteration when you put something in, it shouldn't be there, right, right.
You can adulterate directly by putting in something, redacting something, taking out
something or putting in something that is a vague term that could be taken different
ways.
You know, so, so all of these things are quite simple.
And I've been coming out and speaking on law, legal matters, code statutes, a lot of people
like, um, you know, with law and stuff like that, you know, Oh, that's codes and their
policy and force.
That's okay.
You should know that too.
Because if you look at the definitions for all the codes and statutes and municipalities
or whatever have, those are good because they, if you look at the definitions, it only applies
if you're an employee, right.
Or a resident, right.
That's another big thing.
They make you a resident.
And the reason why, you know, you can only be a resident in a, in a hotel, a jail hospital,
right.
Okay.
And if you ask people, are you resident and they're like, yeah, well, where do you inhabit?
Where do you live?
Well, what do you mean?
I'm here.
Okay.
So if you're parked your ass here as a resident, guess what?
You go in the constitution, there's something called the vagabonds.
You can look it up, look up where the word vagabond is in the U S constitution and how
are they to be treated?
Right.
That's all I'm going to say on that, you know?
So, uh, so it's kind of like 14th, 14th amendment, there's no slavery unless you're convicted
of a crime and that scumbag Scalia that they strangled at that ranch, molesting children.
Right.
Yeah.
I wasn't there and I didn't see it.
But look, if you say that you're pretty much on the money, right.
Well whatever, uh, you know, he said the constitution doesn't say lawfully or rightfully convicted,
just convicted.
So you could, the constitution allows room to be falsely convicted.
It's not, if you're truly lawfully convicted, it's that you're convicted, you see, isn't
that interesting?
Right.
So, uh, yeah.
So I, it's good to get into all this stuff.
Uh, uh, you know, one, one guy, an attorney once says, are you a constitutionalist?
I know that document that's written by a bunch of saboteurs, uh, they wanted to commit Regicide.
Regicide means kill the King, right?
And uh, and cause King George did the King George proclamation around the 17 seventies
and the proclamation.
You can look this up.
You said, uh, to the colonies, uh, you're to leave all indigenous lands and indigenous
people alone.
I want to preserve them.
Oh shit.
Right.
That's like tailing the pelting at Pentagon.
You got to leave.
Uh, imagine a president, imagine Kennedy tells the Pentagon, you got to leave everything
in the Middle East alone.
Yeah.
Right.
You see?
That's why we'll never know why he, why they took him out.
Right.
Uh, you see, he could have said that that's enough to take them out.
We don't have anything in writing, but you see what I mean to the point?
It's just open.
So, but this is in writing what I'm saying, you can look up the proclamation of whatever
17 whatever.
So, you know, these saboteurs, uh, George was, someone sent me a, an email, uh, a very
well-respected listener, a subscriber also that frequently mails me.
I let him know.
I enjoy listening to his, uh, reading his messages, uh, about, uh, military handbook
defense, uh, where forest fires in the U S will be used as a weapon.
And I said, well, George Washington was known as the village burner, right?
If you didn't like you, you know, the whiskey rebellion was bullshit by the way.
You know, uh, the whiskey rebellion was about people that were promised a salary for fighting
in the revolution.
Never got it.
So let's accuse them of something else and go kill them for it.
Right.
There was a whole tobacco war too, uh, that went on, uh, same, same kind of thing where
they were okay.
Well, we'll, we'll, we'll work for you.
We'll cut down, you know, they will do all this work and harvest the tobacco and all
that.
And then when it came time to pay them, they stiffed them.
And uh, then when that happened, they turned around and said, well, they're actually committing
sedition against the state.
And uh, then they just burned down their, uh, their, their farms and everything.
Yeah.
Right.
And the masses go along with that because they unquestionably would go, you know, go
along with what the state or the authorities tell them where in actual actuality, they're
supposed to be participatory, uh, and they're not.
And if you try to be participatory, go down to a courtroom down here and say, I need the
courtroom.
I'm going to be, you can't do that.
You know, you can't say you can't, this is a private building, but you can look into
all the different stuff they did with the people with tobacco in Virginia and, uh, and
also in Kentucky.
Uh, exactly what I'm talking about here is that they just, when it came time to pay and
they just didn't and, and you know, okay, well they were criminals.
So we had to, uh, take out their farms and they ended up, uh, not sure how they have
something called letter of Mark.
A lot of people pronounce it Marquis, uh, it's great.
And that means that, uh, if I don't like you, I could just, uh, go into seizure, you know,
seize your stuff.
And as long as I divide it, see in a letter of Mark, uh, you can go and take someone's
stuff, but you can't take the, when you take someone's stuff, you can't keep all of it.
You have to divide it amongst the authorities and then it's okay.
By the way, if you read what the letter of Mark allows you to do, a bounty hunters used
to have one, but you can't have a lawful bounty hunter anymore because you know, you're under
a legal system, but they, a letter of Mark doesn't work anymore.
Seals don't work anymore.
You know, if you have a seal for your family or whatever, they'll say, Oh, uh, that's a
notary seal.
You're impostering a notary, you know, cause everything is, yeah.
So in essence, uh, in the chat, what I did promise someone, I was going to speak about
a yin and yang a little bit more, well, that's a, that's an Asian term and I don't like it
because it's an Asian term, but not that I don't like Asian stuff is we should have a
Western equivalent.
We don't.
Well, and everybody equates it to that, that, that black and white symbol, right?
You know, which is kind of the equal, yeah, it should be instead of black and white, you
know, they say nothing's black and white.
It should be multicolored.
You should have a, the color wheel divided because certain colors are yin, certain colors
are yang.
Just like I showed, you could keep the bugs away from your nightlights by painting a blue
stripe.
Well, could you divide that along the lines of a, what they say are hot and cold colors
pretty much?
I mean, exactly.
Yeah.
The cold colors would be young and the hot colors would be yin.
Okay.
But, but, but, but hot is young and yin is cold.
Oh my gosh.
Isn't that confusing?
It is a little bit, but the cold, they shouldn't be.
So when something is something like yin and it becomes extremely yin where it can't get
any more yin, it flips and becomes its opposite.
When something is young and gets extremely young, it flips and becomes yin.
Perfect example is making a magnet.
Now, I don't know if you ever see a go on YouTube university.
They have a, how do you make a magnet?
Basically an iron slug with a coil of a thousand amps, three volts.
And if you overcharge it, what happens?
Boom, it explodes.
Right, right.
So, uh, uh, the core of a nuclear device is another example because so tight, the detonation,
it's either the rifle detonation, the barrel or the old style uranium, which is atomic,
not nuclear.
Uh, and then the nuclear, which is based on implosion to concentric spheres with a beryllium
mirror.
Ooh, I'm not supposed to talk about that.
Um, anyway, uh, that implodes, right?
An implosion pushes, makes something so young when you get to a point and then it becomes
yin and explode.
Grenade.
Grenade is very young.
It's very heavy.
Right.
It's very dense.
And when you pull that pin, the gases react.
It makes it even more dense and more dense and then can't take any more density.
Guess what happens?
Well, it's a grenade.
Right.
Boom.
Interesting.
Yeah.
Okay.
Same thing with people.
Uh, but here's the thing, the yin and yang is, is an easy, it's just a tool.
They're words we use in language, right?
I don't like that.
It's Asian centric and to a Western audience, but we'll work it this way.
Let's define it.
Let's work with it anyway.
It's what we've got.
Right?
What?
First of all, there's nothing online and there are very few books you can get on, on
what I'm going to give out right now.
And this is through many years of discussion, which people I looked up to and contemplation
and looking at old, old methodologies, Taoist methodologies, right?
So, um, the, the thing about, um, the yin and yang, when you look up, uh, anything like
that online, they're going to give you a list, a chart.
These things are yin.
These things are yang.
And that's how people, you know, move forward on it.
And many things are in oversimplified and dumbed down like that.
Are those things incorrect?
No.
But if you dumb something down so much and that's all you offer and you try to apply
it and it doesn't work, you could say it's incorrect because it's not working.
You know, if it's a functional thing, right?
So, so what I'm trying to say here is this, let's start all over.
So yin, when people, you talk about like, uh, you know, they'll, they'll give you a
list.
These are yin foods.
These are yang foods.
Okay.
The human body, anything that's alive is yin.
It requires yin.
So all the food you eat is yin, right?
Life force giving everything you eat.
Now, if you eat a rock, right?
The ability to get induction to transmute that rock and digest it is very rare, if not
impossible.
It is very young, right?
But it's not food.
So all food, anything that's considered food is yin.
Now all food, if all food is yin, then how come there are yang foods?
Okay.
Anything the body takes in for nutrition is yin.
And within that category of everything you take in, those can be divided as more yin
and more yang.
You see?
Okay.
Now, where does the yang come in?
If all the, if everything in the body is yin nourishing that you take in, including the
air and the water, where does the yang come in?
Well, when the body, when a living being, whether it's a bacteria, a plant, a human,
a whale, a cockroach, bird, once it's nourished with all that yin, some of the yin is dedicated
to become yang as a protective element.
And so the yang protects the yin, the life.
What I just gave you, you will not find on the internet anywhere or in books printed
that simple.
So this is actually, we make a good transcript, by the way, and someone post it to a degree.
This is critical.
This is very serious stuff, by the way.
Okay.
So what do I mean by some of it breaks off and becomes yang and to protect the yin?
You know, when you eat that nutrition, the quality of nutrition regenerates your skin
over time, regenerates your bones over time, right?
You've had, you've heard of diseases where people have deficiency in their diet and their
skin goes bad or their bones go bad, scurvy, crickets and things like that.
Right?
Okay.
So when you have a good diet or the yin that you take in as a balance of yin and yang within
that yin, the yang manifestation are the protective elements of the body.
So the protective elements of the body is the ability for the body to regenerate skin, right?
Bones, you know, they say, well, the milk commercials help to build healthy muscles and
healthy bones, right?
Yeah, well, they tell you that these different types of food will build different parts of
the body, right?
Exactly.
That's the yang component.
Okay.
Of the foods that you've already subdivided as yin and yang.
So this is going to take a little thinking about, but also energy.
If you eat food that zaps your energy and you've got to sleep and you have no energy because
you're eating 14 snicker bars a day, right?
How much yang protective elements does the snicker bar develop for your body?
Nothing.
Very little, right?
Some, but not enough, enough to keep you alive, to contain that life force.
Because when all the young leaves, the life force leaves the body.
Just like in a cartoon, when someone dies and you see the spirit leave the body, you
know, like Casper, the ghost or something.
Yeah.
That means there's no more young to hold it in.
So when you're talking about a living being, whether it's a plant, a whale, a roach, a
human, a bird, whatever, everything that it takes to nourish, including for its soul,
including water and air is yin to support the yin, the life force.
And the product, how that being uses what it takes in, a certain amount of it is dedicated
to become yang, to protect, to create the actual, to facilitate the container, right?
The container that holds you is yang.
So for example, like when I go to places like Houston or the rainy season here in Tucson,
I don't get bit by mosquitoes, very rare, because I have thick skin, ha ha ha, right?
You have to, if you talk, speak this way.
Of course.
Yeah, you do.
And thick blood.
So if someone eats a lot of things that thin out their blood too much and thin skin, the
mosquitoes know that, they can see that.
They go to that person and the person's like, oh, mosquito, oh, it's bad, you know, it's
biting me.
No, mosquito senses.
It won't go to the one that has a thick skin because if it goes to the guy or the woman
that has the thick skin and the thick blood, it tries to put that needle, you know, that
stamen thing into your skin.
Right.
And it'll, it'll break.
It'll break off.
And the mosquito will die.
Well, so mosquitoes are attracted to the thin blood and thin skin because it's easier to
get nourishment.
Well, yeah.
Think about it.
Think if you have a tool that you use and you know that if you're, you're very well
familiar with the use of the tool and the methods of using it and you're very well skilled
in it, you know that if you do this with this tool, you'll break the tool, right?
Yeah, of course.
It could be any tool.
For instance, a drill.
I got, I got a couple of drill bits.
I know they go just fine through wood, through sheet rock.
No problem.
But if I decide I need to drill a hole in cement, I'm not using that because I'm going
to break it.
Yeah, you don't even have to try.
I already know.
It's going to, you know, no good.
You know, even intuitively, even if you weren't told or even if you didn't do it.
Mosquitoes are not that dumb, right?
So, uh, so, okay, I just, this is a side note, but so the, the ability, so does the mosquito,
it sees the, how much yang you have, right?
Even though you're yin, right?
You see?
Couldn't have, so if you have enough yang to protect you, right, to protect the yin,
it won't come if it sees the yang, right?
So this is where the yin and yang is energetic.
Okay.
Let's go back to the food.
People who have various things, now here, here's the thing.
Anyone who was lived near a Chinatown, they, uh, they have these apothecaries, right?
All these herbs and you walk into all these jars and before you buy anything, they have
a doctor in the back or someone who diagnosed you.
They look at your palm, they look at your eyes, they ask you your date of birth and whatever.
They ask you how active you are sexually or do you sleep and all this.
They could put the puzzle together and then they write a prescription, you know, these
roots, this here, this, that hopefully, you know, it's nothing too unlawful, right?
And they do that.
Now, why don't they have a, a one pill fits all people for people, but it doesn't work
that way.
Cause everybody's a little different.
Everybody's in a slightly different condition.
So that's, that's the, that's how, you know, right away, the vaccines are a scam because
in their own paperwork, it says that a blood type, body weight, age, and race are a factor
when you inject someone with something that's supposed to do with that, right?
So that's why people, you know, I think I've mentioned before, you know, someone was being
made fun of when he was telling the nurses, they're giving vaccines that aren't tested.
They all, all the nurses laughed at him, but I said, are you taking consideration, you
know, things I just mentioned, then they packed up and left, right?
So anyway, uh, in a real world, those people will be taken the back of the building and
shot by the way, in a real world.
So we know it's a fake world, so they just keep doing what they're doing.
Um, okay.
So when someone says they can't sleep or this or that, I don't, I can give you the generalization
and then you self-diagnose, which is the best thing that goes back to learning how to fish
instead of asking for fish, right?
So what I'm trying to say here, emphatically, emphatically, indubitably, right?
Is that everyone is, is very different.
In other words, you can have four people with headaches, uh, at midnight and there's four
different solutions, completely different, right?
There's no pill.
Now the suppression, we know the allopathic medicine, by the way, uh, there's still a
confusion about Western medicine.
It's allopathic.
They're only supposed to treat the symptoms.
It's a treatment, no cures that are allowed, right?
So that, you know, you're, cause they're, you're at war.
They've been at war with humanity for a long time and people don't take the hints.
So, all right now, um, very simple when, uh, even from doing weather work, if you look
at the atmosphere, when the sun starts approaching over the earth, the atmosphere expands like
a balloon, right?
It goes up, literally, um, uh, expands physically.
It's measurable.
And, but etherically, etherically and energetically, uh, also, and that is a young quality of reaching
up, right?
This is where it gets confusing when you start looking at foods, by the way, because certain
plants, for example, like sugar cane or corn that are taller than wheat and other things,
they're considered yin because they rise up, right?
So that's another discussion.
Maybe we'll try to tag it on here.
So people maybe after listening to this can do some diagnosis on their own.
All right.
So when the sun goes down, it contracts, right?
And, uh, the atmosphere comes down on the earth.
By the way, for weather work, that's how you make hurricanes.
You know, those currents go from west to east.
So I'm in, let's say the American Southwest.
So I know that, um, when it's afternoon for me, east of me, even when, as the clock says,
I think we're three hours apart, right?
Right.
Three hours apart.
Okay.
It's already sundown over there when it's late afternoon for me.
I know what I did three hours ago here.
If the atmosphere is like a rubber membrane, if I push my finger, you could see my finger
coming through the rubber, pushing up.
I can do that ethereally.
And naturally when you, uh, elongate something elastic and you let go, what happens?
It snaps back.
Right?
Right.
Okay.
So what I do is, uh, I push up into the, uh, when it's, um, when it afternoon here, I push
up vertically.
And as it goes towards the east, um, it's going to want to shoot down a snap back down,
but it's naturally going to want to snap back down more gradually because it's getting nighttime.
It's contracting.
So it's going to have the nighttime contraction, uh, and the elasticity contraction that I
created.
And you get a, um, tornado.
Sorry.
I said hurricane.
The hurricanes are made the same way.
So you could really inflict bad weather downstream by doing that.
What I just mentioned, uh, using a simple tube and things like that.
This is a weather engineering.
Um, I think you've witnessed that in real time with Danny once when he asked me to stop
the rains in Washington because his brother was visiting about eight years ago and he
came back and says, thanks.
It was no rain.
It was any rain or forecast.
Yeah.
It was all written in the forecast.
It was no rain.
And when he came, so that I said, don't ask me again.
Cause that took like 20 hours worth of work, right?
It's a lot of work.
You have to monitor it.
When I was doing hurricane stuff on the roof, I had to get food and drink brought to me.
Well, you know, so cause you really, that's how delicate the device is, right?
You have to constantly be working on it, I guess.
Okay.
You got to stay on it.
Yeah.
Think about like someone in a B29 machine gun turret, you know, they show the guy sitting
in the back, you know, he's freezing his off, right?
You got to bring them, bring them a cup of coffee or something, you know, right, right.
Can't get up from his post.
Uh, yeah.
So anyway, back to the, uh, elasticity and all that.
So when the atmosphere is contracting at night, right.
It's yin, but it's contracting, but it becomes more yin, right?
And yang when it raises.
So when someone says they can't sleep, that is the environment around them is contracting.
All right.
And contraction normally means yang, but it's actually creating a yin condition.
So everything is contracting, uh, coming down and you can't sleep because somehow your body
cannot be aligned with that energy.
Right?
Right.
So what I mean by being aligned with that energy, let's take it from an emo side.
Imagine going to a place where it's really quiet and you come in and you're all high
energy and all hyped up.
Right.
Even if you're not saying anything, everybody looks at you, they turn around cause they're
all relaxed and chilled and they look at you and they're like, wow, this person's all hyped
up.
Even though you haven't said anything.
They could tell from your energy.
Right.
Yeah.
Disruptive.
It's disruptive.
Even if you haven't, you know, no matter how quiet you try to be, they feel that, you know,
it's a, it's okay.
That's the energetic part.
So somehow, uh, you know, nighttime comes down, you can't sleep.
It's because you have too much energy going up, but that's young considered young, but
it's actually contrary to the yin condition that's being created by the contraction.
That's why it's so simple to take a sedative, right?
To make you go to sleep.
But what's happening here is, uh, as the atmosphere contracts your body, whatever you were eating
or during, during the day should be in sync with that.
So as you get to the point where you want to sleep, you're winding down naturally with
it.
You're in sync with it like a dance.
So when you can't sleep at night, it means that you're out of sync with the environmental
conditions.
Right.
Now, the simplest way to do it is like, well, I can't sleep, but why don't you take this
pill?
This, uh, they have stuff to make you sleep, right?
Yeah.
Right.
Or a tea, a certain teas.
Uh, uh, we make, um, uh, lemon balm, chamomile and mint, uh, lavender, uh, lavender.
Is it lavender?
Yeah.
Lavender.
You're sure about that?
Yeah.
Lavender.
I have lavender.
I've cooked a little lavender.
Often people, uh, you ever heard of herbs, the herb, the Provence, they put it, they,
it's a good dry rub.
When people do a roast, uh, whatever, the secret ingredient is lavender in there.
Like, oh, I love herbs to provide.
I use, I use it very often.
The lavender plants are wonderful, beautiful, uh, blossoms and it smells wonderful.
Lavender is very common scent.
Yeah.
No, I wasn't aware of it using it that way though.
I was more aware of it like, oh, for eating, yeah, as a scent, as, as in cosmetics, right?
Right.
And cosmetic stuff.
Yeah.
No, it's edible.
It's, it's in the sage family.
It's like a sage.
Uh, uh, yeah.
So, uh, lavender lemon balm, which looks like a nice triangular leaf, looks like a mint leaf,
but it's like lemon.
It tastes like lemon.
Uh, chamomile.
That's what when you say I'm having tea, I'm like, this doesn't make any sense.
It's not like when people say tea, it's not like coffee because when you say coffee, it's
a bean.
It's a very specific, you know, then you have varieties of growth, but when you say tea,
anything can be a tea.
I have compost tea outside, you know, when you compost and the water runs out, right?
They call that a tea.
So a tea is anything that's steeped in water, boiled.
That's why I've asked you, I wasn't giving you a hard time.
I said, is it a leaf tea, a twig tea or root tea?
Well, you can make, you can make a mushroom tea also.
A mushroom.
There you go.
Yeah.
Anything in water, right?
Pretty much.
Sun tea.
You don't, you don't leave it in the sun.
Right.
You've heard of that stuff too.
Cold brew.
No, I've done that.
I do that a couple of times a year.
I make a few gallons of that.
Yeah.
But with what?
Right.
So you can do pine needles, right?
Which have an incredible astringent value to it that lasts, you know, if you do a pine
needle tea, it lasts about two weeks in the body.
You know how they say the cannabis THC is like 30 days or something.
Pine needles are two weeks, especially if you do it during the moon phases and it's
astringent quality anyway.
Okay.
So I would suggest that the main thing, okay, let's, without repeating why you can't sleep
because you're out of the natural order, you should be winding down as the environment
is winding down.
Right.
And you could supplement that, but people, you know, why should you be dependent?
Now the opposite is true as well.
What if the sun is coming up and it's expanding, but you still want to remain sleeping?
That means you're out of touch with the natural order.
Everything's expanding.
You should be expanding with it, you know, getting levity, right?
Waking up, let's say, but you stay in bed.
Yeah.
A lot of times if I don't try to do anything and I just let myself run normal, I want to
go to sleep when the sun's coming up a lot of times.
Okay.
Well, that's another condition, right?
So that means that you have a lot of one thing and when the sun is coming up, it's nurturing
to try to bring you in balance, but you can't receive that unless you are laying down, right?
In that other condition.
So, um, so in other words, when a fireman don't usually show up with fire hoses and
water, if the house isn't on fire, right?
So the two, the condition of the house being on fire and the fireman showing up, putting
water down, it's very rare that you see a fire truck and, uh, breaking a window and
just shooting water into a house when there's no smoke or no flame.
So you don't want to get it.
You never want to get to that point, uh, the classic, in other words, that's a classic
situation.
You know, if you saw a rendering fire trucks and hoses, you see in the background, the
building and the artist will have to put in flames and smoke.
It would be, it wouldn't make any sense if there was no flames and smoke in the picture,
right?
So it's that you can take it that simply.
So what's in the picture?
Uh, now if the person, it's easier by the way, let's look, let's go this way.
Remember how I said all the food is yin and it could be within that yin, yin, all food
being yin.
It could be divided as yin food and yang food, but what the manifestation of the food is
feeds the yang that protects the yin.
Okay.
Um, within that also is certain things are harder to do than others.
Take, go back to the example.
You can't sleep.
The reason why you can't sleep at night is because your body is not in sync with the
environment.
Contracting.
Okay.
It stays expanded.
And how do we treat that?
Well, we consider that and we say, I need to wind down, right?
Or take a supplement, you know, whether it's a over the counter, I think they have things
that make you sleep and where the tea, uh, that I mentioned or others, chamomile will
do it.
Okay.
That seems to be very normal to do that.
And it's not that difficult to do.
Right.
Let's take the opposite one where the sun is now appearing and the atmosphere and the
environment is expanding, but you can't get up.
You still stay in bed.
That one, that condition is much harder for the individual, right?
Okay.
What are you going to do?
You know, uh, I'll sip on some coffee while I'm laying down and my eyes closed and snoring.
No, it's very hard to do that, right?
It's much more difficult for the other, the other one.
You see, to, to go from the yin laying down, to go into the expanding environment, to get
in sync with something that is becoming more yang.
So when something is becoming yin, it's much easier.
Here's another example.
You're standing out on the shore or on the side of the deck of a swimming pool and you're
young because you're not wet, right?
You jump into the pool, which is yin, water is yin.
And now you're yin.
You're all, you're wet instantly, right?
Right.
Okay.
That would be the analogy of, you can't go to sleep, but then you find a way to go to
sleep.
Now, the other way is more difficult.
If you're wet from the pool to become yang, where you're totally dry, how long does that
take to stand there with your clothes?
Even in the desert, it takes a long time.
It takes a while.
Yeah.
So your shoes might take days.
Good.
Yeah.
Okay.
So basically that analogy is when the sun is appearing and the environment is expanding,
but you can't expand with it and you stay in bed, let's say, or you're really tired.
Okay.
You see how you see the difference there, how one is easy to become wet, but it's harder
to dry.
It's easy to go to sleep, but harder to wake up.
Yeah.
It's easier to get wet than it is to dry off in any case, because just, yeah, that just
makes sense.
That's an analogy of yin and yang.
So just because one condition is yin and the other one is yang, oh, it just becomes, the
response time is very different.
Right.
It's very different.
Much easier to think about it again.
You can't sleep or you want to relax.
There's things that you could take that will put you out pretty quick.
Some people, 10 minutes, five minutes, 15 minutes.
But if you're really tired and you want to take something to wake you up, something that's
going to wake you up that fast is considered dangerous.
It'll probably do liver damage or kidney damage or brain damage.
Right.
Yeah.
Cocaine is a hell of a drug.
Yes.
That's from Rick James.
Yeah.
Dave Chappelle.
But yeah.
Yeah.
Cocaine is a hell of a drug.
But even then it doesn't do it.
Yeah.
I've seen people do whatever and yeah, and go to sleep.
So yeah.
So mind you, they show yin and yang and that little symbol, the black and white, if you
look at the black and white symbol you mentioned earlier, that's the classic representation.
Everything looks pretty balanced in there, right?
It's a circle and the amount of black is equal to the amount of white, whether it's the dot
or the circle.
Right?
No, that's not how it works.
That's not it.
That's something somebody, some school put out like 200 years ago or a hundred years ago.
If you were to make that more accurate, depending on how I just explained it, it would not look
like a circle.
It would look more like an egg or an ellipse and much more of it would be black than white.
See, you'd have more of the black and more than the white and it would look elliptical
in that round and on one end of the ellipse, right?
That would be more accurate in terms of the way, the working principles of yin and yang,
not just the symbol of it.
Excellent.
Okay.
So, what I just gave was something that it's very rudimentary, but if you work on that
and you think about what I just said, it leans one more to a more correct working understanding
versus just a simple understanding of it's, in other words, what I mean by that is you'll
be able to start working with it versus just if someone asks you, do you know what yin and
yang is?
And you say, yeah, yang is hard and yin is soft or whatever, right?
That's not workable.
You can't work with that.
There's nothing to work.
Now, I want to just add a few more things.
Again, this sounds very macrobiotic.
Again, I don't, if there was another alternative, but eating whole foods.
You don't like that term, but yeah, got it.
Yeah.
Well, for many reasons, if you go online right now and start, look, there's nothing there.
I mean, there's not much there.
And then, you know, it sounds very dogmatic, but here's the thing.
Even with like a skin manifestations, you know, typically someone would run to rub something
on it.
You know, the, the classic dermatology, look, if you want to go to dermatology school here,
I'm going to save you a, what is it a quarter of a million bucks and five, 10 years.
This is everything you need to know about dermatology.
If someone shows up with a dry spot, make it wet.
If someone shows up with a wet spot, make it dry.
That's it.
That's the extent of dermatology.
Yeah.
Pretty much.
That's it.
They have no concept of anything else.
What I'm saying is if you learn how to cook brown rice, short grain Bloomberg, I keep
saying this.
Why?
Because the highest quality Nishiki makes a brown rice.
I don't know if you could get it here.
Very high quality brown rice, organic, of course.
You learn how to prepare that properly and then have a root vegetables with it, sauteed
root vegetables.
It'd be burdock, burdock and burdock.
Did I say burdock?
I think you did.
Hold on.
Okay.
It's very binding and bracing, but burdock, carrots, onions, right?
Parsnip.
Right.
Learn how to use, cut those on a bias, very thin, potato chip thin on an angle, and then
lay the bias slices down and cut them again vertically.
So they're like julienne.
Well, that's all root stuff that's close to the ground.
So it's, that kind of energy is young.
So right.
Very young.
And by the way, you know, the 28 elements in the soil are what we're made of.
So it's going to drag you into that realm.
And guess what?
If you eat like that, you will be in sync or how, what's another way to say it?
You will be in accord in resonance with that basic material.
Let me ask you, is the soil outside and the ground outside in sync and in resonance when
the environment expands, when the sun comes up or when the environment contracts, when
the sun goes down, is the soil in the dirt in accord with all that in balance with that
answer is yeah.
As a matter of fact, no, the answer is fuck yeah.
So you're putting, you're setting yourself up, right?
It's kind of like, um, you don't have to think about it right now.
Here's the thing I was saying, even with skin manifestations, which is supposed to be a topical
thing to the Westerner, even the Eastern now also, uh, doing a whole food diet like that,
the skin manifestations disappear very fast.
They start, you start getting relief within a few days and they're gone a week or two
usually when we're in about 75% of the cases, right?
So very, very simple.
Uh, and I keep, I keep leaning on variety is, is the key to health by the way, unless
you have superior quality.
So years ago, people said, if you read an ancient text, we're starving, give us bread,
right?
Literally, that would be enough because I don't know, most, most Americans have never
had real bread or real cheese or real milk or right, even so someone I've been, I've been
to some American's house and it's whatever for dinner, uh, string beans.
And I go over and it's Kansas string beans, string beans come in a can, right?
That's how you get, that's what string beans are.
There's something that comes in a can, right?
So away from that, but back to the bread, uh, if you've ever had bread, have you ever
had bread?
People say yes, but have you ever had bread that was baked, uh, from flour that was ground
a certain way?
So while it's being ground and never reaches a temperature, it doesn't touch metal.
And also it was from the same people that are doing this also grew the wheat, right?
No, the answer is no.
When you have that, it's like you feel the love and you feel the energy.
You can actually survive off of just something like that.
But if you're in a modern world and try to survive on just bread, you're going to come
down with a whole bunch of diseases in like a week.
You're going to feel like crap in like two days guaranteed, right?
Well, that very much explains why I enjoyed the bread in Sicily.
When I went to Sicily and saw relatives there, of course, because they, uh, grew the wheat.
Yep.
And here's the other thing I want to fast forward.
I was having a long conversation with someone who was traveling recently.
Uh, you've heard of homeopathy where it's how little of something you put in it that
actually makes it more effective, right?
Homeopathic remedies.
And it's, it's actually been, uh, poo pooed for many years, but now they're finding out
since you could use radio frequencies to create things in water.
I don't know if you're familiar with that.
You can have a test tube with water with DNA in it and another test to be there in another
room or another part of the world and send hit, hit the tube with their DNA, with radio
frequencies and the radio frequencies that bounce off of that, get recorded and sent
to the tube.
That's just pure water.
And within a day that other tube doesn't matter where it is, uh, will develop the same DNA.
Are you familiar with that?
I have not heard this.
Okay.
Look it up.
DNA recreated with radio frequencies and water.
It's all over the internet.
Well, I should be able to find it.
Someone, I'm sure in the chat, we have a very active and vibrant chat.
Uh, someone will put a link to it.
Uh, there's a French, uh, he's not the only one.
There's many people that did it.
Reif has done it.
I mean, Tesla was working on stuff like this, but not DNA and water.
Yeah.
That was the only thing I was thinking of when you talked about the radio.
I thought about the Reif stuff and I said, well, yeah, but I never heard of them like
transmitting DNA basically, which is, yeah, well, DNA is a new thing that wasn't heard
of before the sixties.
Let's say publicly.
Yeah.
This is the experiments that were done in the eighties and nineties.
Uh, and you can do it also, by the way, it's not that difficult to do, uh, with, it doesn't
have to be DNA.
It could be any material.
Okay.
So that was when, when they studied that, they said, wow, the homeopathic people are right.
You just need the frequency of the material, not the quantity.
Right.
Okay.
So with that in mind, what I'm trying to say is growing the wheat, right.
And right there locally and, uh, processing it into flour and making the bread is a whole
product, a wonderful product, right now.
Why is it the other one is not, well, let's just say, here's one variable.
Let's say you wanted to make really good bread, but the wheat was a thousand miles away there.
How are they going to get it to you?
Most likely it's going to end up, even if it's by train, it's going to end up on a truck
because the trains don't come to your doorstep.
Right?
Right.
So here you have this wonderful flower and it's packed in a semi truck or whatever truck
and it's a powered by diesel.
There's a diesel tank strapped underneath and the diesel is being combusted.
Now your flower, your container that holds the flower is totally airtight, but the energy,
the homeopathic resonant frequency of that diesel engine, no, I don't know if you've been
around diesel trucks, it's a nasty, I mean, I don't mind the smell of diesel, but it's
all the lubricants and the carbon and it's just like a rubber residue.
It's like a nasty chemical residue.
Yeah.
And the rubber and the brake liners, even with a, you know, air brakes, you know, the material
from the brake dust and the, you know, all this stuff, right?
Diesel vehicles just stink.
Again, I, you know, when I worked at gas stations in Jersey and I just had to deal with, cause
you know, you're not allowed to fuel up yourself in Jersey.
I had to fuel up the diesel trucks and it was like, they always had a residue all over them
They stink.
The exhaust smells more, everything.
Yeah.
And actually, if you work with that stuff, you will stink like it, right?
So I remember growing up in the seventies, sitting next to someone who's Matthew Gavinelli
and his family and his uncle, they had fish stores where they sold fish and he always smelled
like fish.
And I said, dude, you smell like fish.
You need to wash.
I wash all the time.
I know I've been told before.
I can't help it.
I eat fish.
I work at fish.
I smell like fish all the time.
Right.
So he sat next to him.
I don't want to sit next to him.
Right.
So anyway, going back to the homeopathic, the virtue of it being transported the way
it is now is going to affect the quality of the flour from a homeopathic resident point
of view.
You see, even if you're, so in other words, if you ship that flour that was grown by the
people you were with Sicily or the one that's here, Barrio bakery, uh, ship it to another
part of the country or the way it's not going to be the same because of the virtue
of that homeopathic residents or the D you see what I mean?
Right.
So what does that mean?
Am I a big proponent for growing it locally and eating local?
Yeah, of course you should be.
Anything that's organic is subject local.
Well, but anything that, but that wasn't what I was going to say.
Anything that's organic is subject to pick up on, uh, some of what it's exposed to no
matter what that is along its travels.
So, you know, the people handling it, the way it travels, if it's in a truck, if it's
in a train, if it's in a plane, it doesn't matter.
Everything around it.
It's, it picks up some of what it's exposed to one way or another, right?
That's right.
So, so in essence there was a local movement about eating local and all that, that's more
correct than most people have given it, uh, uh, you know, it's attribute for it because
of that.
Now here's the thing.
Well, what if we use electric?
Well, you know, you got the big lithium power pack, right?
That they're using.
That's very toxic.
So eating local.
So in other words, um, uh, we attempt here to, we have box gardens cause the soil is
very alkaline in Tucson.
If you try to do even amend the soil, if you work with soil in your hands or even with
gloves or without gloves, you get alkaline burns, right?
That's how alkaline it is.
Cause it used to be an ancient seabed.
So everything's on a flat.
What you do here is you just get some wood and you make a box and you fill it with top
soil that you acquire or you make, you amend the soil using compost or, you know, hopefully
you'll get something that looks like soil and try to grow as much vegetables seasonally
as you can, or a farmer's market or, or, or.
So if you go to these organic markets, uh, if, if it's the more locally it's sourced,
the more eating it'll be meaning energy and all that.
Yeah.
So I think we'll just consider this a primer, just a place to start for this, uh, Sonic
31.
Fair enough.
Thanks.
Bye.