Rated Y 114 or 114. And here we are. Greek, how are you? Where you are?
I'm doing you're doing? Well, there's been a few questions.
My answer to how are you is I'm on a stinking rock still. So I know how can we be doing, you know, it's just Bushido.
So you're always doing fine. You know, Bushido, Japanese culture, you could be dying of stomach cancer.
I want to ask how you're doing. You always say you're fine, right?
There's another version of that, though, isn't there?
Kind of in the English language where you're always supposed to give the banal answer regardless.
To me, it's a waste of time. Like everyone's always talking about the weather.
What one is someone going to do something about it?
So when someone when you ask someone how they're doing, are you prepared to do something about it?
Well, normally anyway, that conversation is well, normally that conversation goes normally, as in typically that conversation would go, well, you can't do anything about the weather.
However, if you're speaking at which I just want to bring a couple of things up.
That's someone kind of offered to work on a Web site for me, the water stuff.
And they just had it looked like crap. And they had it was like, why is it so crappy?
I give this person like a 45 minute lecture in design and they just hand me it over and I go and log on, try to work.
It's WordPress dot com and some other element or whatever.
And you almost have to be a coder to do it now on that particular editor.
You see, when I did the Web site on on common radio seven, eight years ago, it was just like using paint program.
Very logical, very, you know, you want to move text and change the font.
It was the same way you do in paint or any any any right click Apple or whatever program that you've had for the past 20 years.
Basic stuff. You want to plug in a certain element. Here's the element.
You can either plug it in or not your choice and fill out the information.
But this stuff here is got columns and they keep changing their format and it's got a whole bunch of codes.
They can't use English and the icons that look like you would change font.
No, it doesn't. You have to go to another section.
OK, so this is what pissed me off, really pissed me off for the lack of communication between people.
This is let me just give you an idea. Yeah, because the person knows me well.
OK, this is what I'm talking about. All right.
So it's very common to order a pepperoni pizza with a Diet Coke.
OK, sure. So this person happens to be one of those people, let's say.
And then they offer it to me, a pepperoni pizza with Diet Coke.
First of all, you know me well enough that I don't eat pork and I would never do a diet drink anyway.
So if you didn't know me, it would be it would be forgiving.
It would be like, well, yeah, they don't know things, but no things.
They don't know that you're a not a cannibal, you know, because of the diet drink.
Just to say, yeah, they both be cannibal feeding the pepperoni and the pork on the fork.
So what makes it worse is a person knows me. Right.
Which made it even worse for me. And I expressed it. Right.
Because the whole thing is no communication.
All you had to do, say, Greek, I'm handing the site work over to you.
Yeah. And guess what? You got to almost be a coder.
This is total dummy load, geek shit. And the reason I couldn't do it so well is because of that reason.
But, you know, I never told you and I'm handing it over to you to edit now, but I'm not going to tell you.
It's like, oh, my gosh, no communication. But you didn't.
This happens with the wife. It's been, I mean, for, you know, right now we've been together 22 years.
And a lot of times it's like we just met yesterday. It's like, what?
I have to go over this again and again. It's like, oh, my gosh.
So all I do, no matter what your proximity or your relationship is, it seems as though communication.
So what the way I've been rolling out for a little while is as if I have only known any relationship.
I have the acquaintance online, offline.
I've just met the person and I've known them no more than two or three days.
It's very forgiving when you think that way.
Well, yeah. If everything is based on a short term memory, you can't expect them to have.
Yeah, they would. They know you. Right. So.
So back to your mind, they're like, this person knows me and they didn't communicate what they could have communicated.
Is that what they should have? There's no such thing as should. Right. There is. There is.
Well, I should have known better. I mean, should is there.
This has been going on for a long time and my tolerance for it now is at zero because, you know, as you get older.
So you're not developing a emotional or psychological callous to it.
You're telling me that it's getting worse. You're getting more sensitive to it?
Oh, of course it's worse. The reason why it's worse is because there's something called about looking ahead.
So you when you want to do something new and build it up, forget it, forget it, forget it.
Don't don't bother. Don't bother. The the entire spectrum of this is for me or my my life.
The entire spectrum of development is I have to do it on my own. Right.
And it's fine here. Let's transition. In the chat.
It was talk about looking and, you know, this is totally fair and fun.
The dark scriptures stuff from archaics. I didn't go in. I didn't look at it.
I remember it from a while back and I was like, OK, the intention is good, by the way.
I don't endorse archaics. I think I am very appreciative of the chronology.
And I checked it. It's not airtight, but it's close enough.
Especially the Phoenix stuff and the explanation of the timing of the Book of Revelation.
I do appreciate that. But he's more interested in being rich than being right.
Like I said, he's basic Texas country boy, ex-con meets the Internet.
OK, basically, that's his whole character.
So if you went to someone who was a screenwriter and said, you got a Texas country boy meets the Internet.
Ex-con that read a lot of books without telling him anything else about archaics,
you come up with a character that you'd be like, oh, that's pretty much him.
OK. Right. OK. So he's very materialistic. He's into, you know, making money all of a sudden.
Today I was on YouTube. I was looking up some stuff.
And because it's nice to see how to, you know, on a video.
You know, the sidebars like archaics was some guy, Jesus, something or.
Oh, man, Jacob Israel. So you're doing YouTube University and somehow the algorithm is live.
So I go on it and I was like, oh, my gosh, this is total materialism.
You know, I mean, no way. And by the way.
OK, let's let's put that aside because he was this is the part where I'm saying that
people are using his stuff for mentioning a lot of stuff that he's come up with.
And he wants to sue them for doing that. OK. For the money. Right.
So that's fine. It's fine. You know, he's found a group of people that he could work with and develop things.
I haven't. But he's saying, but he's probably presenting it as, look, this is the principle of I put my blood and my sweat.
Yeah. It's the standard baseline corporate culture now to go back to the thing about the biblical stuff.
I never hear him qualify anything other than like Zeitgeist stuff.
You know, the Zeitgeist stuff is like the Christian religion comes from all these other religions, basically.
Oh, yeah. The plagiarism. Look, you can see it in previous incarnations.
But nothing. You know, he keeps harping on the burning bush. I don't see there's no burning bush.
That's like folklore. That's like Noah parting the Noah. Yeah.
Moses yellow. Right. Yeah. There's no parting of water.
It's it's the word parting. Does it mean what Cecil be demotion?
They walked on an ice bridge essentially because, you know, it says they walked across as if they were walking on land and not, you know,
and and when the morning came, Pharaoh tried to pursue and he fell to the bottom.
Well, if they're already walking on the bottom, how can you fall to the bottom?
Anyway, look, we have different here. We have two different.
I had somebody once explained, by the way, I had somebody once explained that to me as in the tides had changed.
It wasn't the freezing, but it was more that at one time.
Well, look, yeah, there's there's look, you could say the tides changed.
You could say froze. You could say they'd split open. It was a miracle.
The water went away and they walked on the bottom silt.
You could say there's maybe a few more things that doesn't matter.
But is anyone saying what's exhibited in the text?
And I'm and I'm the only one, my only myself and historically would be maybe Ernest L.
Martin on a bunch of stuff. But those guys are a little bit like archaic.
So I confronted Ernest L.
Martin's 20 years ago, tough people about timekeeping because they were arguing on a certain holiday.
Would it be on Monday or Tuesday? Right.
Biblical holiday. Right.
And I was like, no, it doesn't work that way.
And says, yeah, we've heard about what you're saying, but it divides people.
So we don't want to do it. And also, if we do what you're saying, Greek, we're not going to sell any books.
Well, wait a minute. What you're trying to tell me is that you tried to introduce.
I laid it out for them.
Well, I was about to put that was going to be the punchline of what I was saying.
But let's let's rewind.
What you're telling me is that you basically tried to assert.
Look, if you actually use proper timekeeping, then this lines up differently.
And also, you're lining this up to the Pope's work schedule anyway.
So and so you went into that sort of direction.
And they said, yeah, and I'm the only one that does.
The day starts at noon. Full moon is the new moon.
Oh, no, you're absolutely you're absolutely the only person I've ever heard say out loud.
And probably will stuff like this isn't popular.
OK. Well, I haven't said anything yet about what the comments were in the I'm just building up here.
We're speaking about completely different points of view and stuff now.
I want to read it. I want to revisit the tech issue.
I want to revisit the tech issue when you're done with this, because this is this is going to come back around full circle, I think, to the tech.
What do you mean the tech issue? What do you mean tech as a technology where you started on the Web site and everything?
Because and communication was the if people know me really well.
Right. It's less forgiving for them to do stuff that because they know me well.
You know, it's like, you know, me so long. Well, that's about communication.
Pepperoni pizza and a Diet Coke. Why are you offering me that?
Well, and it's just as well. And look, it's just as solid as when people say to me, well, just go ahead and jump in your car and go drive.
And I go, whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold on, because I have to explain to them.
I don't drive because of my eyesight. Right.
If you don't know me, you could be forgiven for saying, well, just jump in your car. Do this.
I can't do that. OK, it's not one of the forces not thinking and all that.
But this is OK. Someone was there. I wasn't thinking. I'm sorry. No. OK.
You're sorry. That's fine. You're sorry. But I'm not.
In other words, if you're not thinking now, you weren't thinking yesterday. You won't be thinking.
Well, now I have to question the whole process. What the hell are you doing?
If you weren't thinking about the simplest, most obvious thing.
Well, it's a matter of perspective. But and yeah. So here's the other thing.
My perspective is, you know, when someone says, I love you all, whatever on the Internet, that's bullshit.
I'll tell you why. A friend to all is a friend to none.
Let's let's harp on our kicks again a little bit. How many people have you seen?
That's one thing. Someone was ragging on him.
The other person is like, oh, anyone who knows him personally, except where, you know, it's like this guy's an asshole.
Right. But online, he seems right. Different. OK.
So if you get to know me in person, I'm exactly like I am right now.
No, I'm the same thing. I mean, I just might get a little louder on the radio. That's it.
If I can just find one or two people that I can work with, that's fine.
And I mean, not just, you know, showing up and doing a sonic, you know, and the rest is whatever.
My motto is why bother? Why bother? But you got to put it out there.
Part of me is like, you know, there's a time of recompense in the future.
If you know something, you should share it. And that's why I'm doing this.
But I don't see any. All right. OK. I don't see any movement or any not a movement like an organization cult type thing.
But furtherance of my work, the stuff and my stuff that I put out, it's not my stuff, but the stuff, my presentation, I should say.
Yeah. But I've seen but I've seen results from this that I think sometimes you don't take to you know, you don't take very seriously.
No, no. I have over 150, maybe 200 serious emails over the past years.
Right. Of people that said I've changed the way I think I change the way I eat.
My health has changed. My family life has changed. My money life has changed all for the better because of your stuff.
And if you've changed. Well, and look, just realistically, if you've changed a hundred lives directly. Right.
More than that. Yeah. OK. Well, let's just go. We'll just go with the hundred.
The hundred. There's also a bunch of people that are connected to them that are around them that you may never hear from.
That's right. Someone mentioned that in the chat that they've. All right.
OK, so yeah, I have nothing really to say about the dark scriptures thing, because if you listen, it's kind of hard.
I haven't gotten into anything with this new project. Rated Y, it's really older stuff that's still posted somewhere.
Talk about scripture. Very, very different. Yeah, we haven't really gone into it, even though people keep requesting it, to be honest with you.
We haven't really got here. We could do it in five minutes because it's a point of view.
It's OK. It's not like which fish we're going to catch. It's how to fish. Right.
So the whole idea is whatever subject you tackle, any subject you want to learn about.
If there is enough or some or a lot memorialized information, meaning in writing could be digital or whatever.
And it is subdivided and it goes into detail, goes into the history of the stuff.
And categorically, it's it's it's been accepted and proven.
Right. You don't have any license to start saying stuff that's not in there.
In other words, you have to know that stuff first before you start discussing it.
Now, what I've found with scripture is no one is discussing it like I do at all.
Zero. Because of the many reasons.
One is if you're going to be a discusser, a discusser, like archaics, whatever you know the whole thing about,
you have to say things that people are going to like and people that will buy into what you're saying.
And I tell you right now, 99 percent of the time you can't be saying more than five or 10 percent of what's in scripture,
because you start going more than five or 10 percent of what's in scripture.
People are going to leave. It doesn't matter who they are.
It's one of these things that rubs people wrong. Same thing with the medical.
Well, yeah, actually, everything I was looking with the money, I start going the other way.
So I had to learn the hard lesson about politics this way.
Greek, I know you think that's silly or whatever, but I had to learn this very hard lesson that if I'm not saying some of the things
that people come to the table wanting to hear, then I'm guaranteeing that I'm slimming my audience.
Like there's a guarantee that I'm going to reduce.
Now, I could be telling them some brand new information that they will get nowhere else.
And the thing is, they'll run away. And you know why?
Because I didn't put the hook into them to say, look, you're right about a whole lot of things that you think to begin with.
Well, let's go back to the. If you got more than five listeners, you got to start questioning where are they coming from?
Why are they here? You know, five, it could be several hundred, even a thousand or two.
And you have to ask yourself, why are so many people coming?
Because I know what people are like and why are some of them coming?
Right. Because, you know, I must you know, I must be a big pile of poop and all the flies are coming.
You know, is this for the perspective that I'm saying? Right.
But if you can get the message, Freeman told me he's not over all the five interviews I've done with about a million downloads.
And there's only been a handful of people that have contacted me and reached out of a million.
Let's say or let's say let's say half a million or a quarter of a million if you really want to be conservative.
Because statistically, one, I don't know if it delineated where they one person could have listened to it five times.
But no, it doesn't. Yeah. It doesn't help you divide that out.
Like it could be that somebody's got it on their iPad and then they get it on their phone.
Yeah. Yeah. That's more correct. That's about right.
Because now a million people, let's say, hear you and only five or 10 or 20 are interested in what you're saying.
Now you're in good company. Now you're in good company, meaning with the good, the real philosophers.
Right. Back in the day. And you're really putting out real information.
Right. Anyway, this is a big topic.
But you notice I didn't address the video that was put up called Dark Scriptures because I don't see what he where he's going with it.
Right. I don't I don't see any point. And his sources are not very good.
And the point, you know, where there's no burning bush, by the way, in the Bible, you could read that.
I could reiterate it for you if those are people are questioning it.
If you'd like and you have time, sure.
I want to throw something at you, though, to see if you can relate this to what you're discussing, because I did something very unusual recently.
I gave a video talk. They wanted a short talk over at Apple.
OK, Apple corporate wanted to hear from different people that are handicapped.
OK, I'm going to use a whole lot of really a lot of surface dwelling language here that I don't like to use.
But let's go with the slave talk.
So they want to hear from handicapped people about their accessibility to technology.
If you have to work with newer technology as it emerges, we want to hear from you so that we get ideas about the perspective from somebody who is limited in their abilities.
OK, before I go before you go, let me just say this.
The reason why they're doing that is because someone in the company who's a friend of someone gave them a grant to do this.
They don't need to do this. They already know.
And they gave them an extra bunch of money so they could start a little department because they were a friend of a friend.
Get it. It's a hookup deal. Right. You get it.
Sure. It's kind of like the university hookup deals where they allocated.
This is real. Some Midwestern university 20 years ago, two million dollars to find out why water is good for plants.
You mean that place where there's no intelligent life?
Right. Yeah, that's right.
Because all that is, is come here, I'll give you a sweet deal.
You know, when you run away with it in two years, we'll split it kind of thing like that.
So anyway, go ahead.
So that's what I'm part of, apparently.
But I thought it would be interesting to give that presentation and tell them that effectively the only reason why technology has adapted is because you had an audience, an aging audience that was going to have visual problems.
So particularly for me, it became advantageous only because you guys were in search of a greater customer base.
If that customer base shrinks because the population shrinks and you don't have an agent population, I think they'll lag behind.
Yeah. But look, let me just say this.
Yeah.
Apple, Microsoft, Raytheon, they have access to time manipulation.
Right. So they know every, like I said, all these things that they put out that seem benign or innocuous or whatever is just because to help out someone.
Right. You know, here's here.
OK, we're going to do a special search research thing here.
Here's a bunch of money.
Just, you know, do this.
We already, you know, it's all.
Well, I would have no problem.
That's from what you just mentioned is Apple politics.
Right.
Well, kind of.
But this is for an internal thing.
It's not meant for the public.
Like you said, it's a project.
Yeah.
But the reason why I did it is because I wanted to see if somehow I could get involved, maybe in, you know, getting a few dollars for telling a few real stories or giving some real input to these guys, maybe, you know, regardless of what they.
Well, then getting a few dollars, let's say, or credits from these guys would be the only thing, because that's the whole basis for it.
They really don't care.
They know the deal.
Well, I do.
And it's not going to be able to begin anybody else.
So why not?
Look.
Well, do you find that to be a bad thing that I'm doing?
No, no.
I wouldn't say.
Well, I wouldn't say I don't say it's bad, but I wouldn't say it's good if you want to do other things and it's taking you away from them.
If you don't have anything else to do, let's say it had been a priority.
You're going to get, you know, rewarded.
Do it.
If my.
I would look at it purely.
Whenever you're dealing with these things, it's monetary.
Like someone asked me if I wanted to do a study on smokers, how much they pay it right away.
I said, you know, because they were.
So what we want to know is, you know, how much you're paying first.
It's about money.
Well, I want to know two things.
What what is my level of effort that is required of me?
And then, yeah.
What is the what is the reward for said?
Exactly.
Well, yeah.
Compensation, let's say.
Compensation.
Good word.
Remuneration.
OK, so that's what I was after is I wanted to be put in the, you know, running for some
compensation.
I wouldn't think a company like these big companies, whatever they are, are just playing their
everything they do, even if it's nonpublic or is still part of their politics.
So think of Apple, Microsoft, GM, Tesla, Raytheon.
They're all political parties.
In addition to the Democrats, Republicans, libertarians.
Sure.
That's that's how prominent they are in the public eye.
Well, it just so happens.
It's all political.
Yeah.
It just so happens a relative of mine works for them.
So that's how I got considered in the first place.
Right.
And well, you revealed it, though.
You said the only reason why you even get into these things is for that.
So, yeah.
Yeah.
I'm just hoping to be offered up as a resource because if all I got to do is give a 20 minute
talk and then maybe somebody is going to pay me to do that.
Look, that's what I'm after here.
What I'm after overall is being able to.
As long as they're not coming to take bacon off your back.
No, nothing like that.
But I mean, if all you're asking for is a few minutes of my time to sit and talk and
I can be paid for that and do something that I view as productive during my discussion,
my speech, whatever, I see no problem with that.
That's kind of what my whole business is.
Right.
Sure.
But let's get back to the conversation.
Well, so my point is this is an addendum about communication.
And I was communicating an idea that I don't think they were exactly after, but I thought
it would be different enough from the, oh, let me give you my complaints and my direct
experiences.
And instead I said, you know what?
Overall, I think if you're serious about this, there's a way to do it.
And if you're not, then there's another way to go.
And that was my old presentation, which I did.
Oh, that's fine.
In a hot seven minutes actually on the video.
And I did very little preparation work for it.
So it was a little effort with the potential for something in the future.
However.
That's profound.
This is the way it should be done.
I should get something out of it.
Okay.
But this is me communicating, right?
And I communicated this to them because I had some fair instructions and we had an exchange.
The problem is that a lot of people come to you claiming they want some sort of communication.
And even if you follow their directions.
Sorry, they don't.
I've never had that.
No?
No, no.
They have an itching desire for something.
It's called in scripture, it makes their ears, it tingles their ears, right?
Something unusual, something different.
Your ears are itching.
Your ears are burning.
Somebody's talking about you.
Kind of thing.
Yeah, it just tickles them a little.
But no, no one's ever approached me about communication.
I had a big problem, both personal, social, whatever, with not being able to communicate.
And anyone I started doing any work with, personal or business or whatever, I said,
Listen, when you communicate, the way you do it is you preface what you're going to communicate.
You inform about what you're going to communicate.
And then you discuss.
Preface, inform, discuss.
Those are the three factors.
Right.
So and I could give you a dozen examples, but it's not necessary.
And then there's the physical communication that goes all the way from how you're working
relationship with someone all the way to, you know, a sexual partner.
Right.
That's also communication.
And that begins with very big.
I just got 10, around 10, 11 years ago, I threw my hands up and I said, OK, if they just
learned how to communicate the surface to earth inhabitants, that would solve that would
be a 90 percent jump in improvement in their direction that they need to go in, not to
fix 90 percent of their stuff.
But if they learn how to communicate and actually just put a little more effort into structure
and communication and someone will say, well, why do we have to do it that way?
OK, let's do it the other way.
What what they're really doing is they're discussing.
You have to play a detective.
What the hell are they talking about?
Then they give you little bits of information.
And then when they notice that they didn't preface it, then they give you the preface
in the end.
So when I listen to people speak, I'm like, don't bother pausing.
Say it as fast as you can, because I have to play detective when you're done to figure
out what the fuck you're trying to tell me.
Right.
So just let it all out.
Give me a few minutes to piece it together.
Yeah.
Right.
So.
So it's like, why?
So if they learned how to preface first, inform and then discuss, that would put them on 90
percent leap in the direction that they need to go to start working on everything.
Right.
It seems to me as though that's literally the solution to 90 percent of the conflict
everywhere.
I mean, and I'm talking about everywhere.
But it doesn't mean the solution to the conflict doesn't mean you're not going to have conflict
because you have to implement the solution.
Right.
You get it.
This is implement.
We're not talking about implementation.
We're just talking planning stage.
No, look, it's like cleaning up the yard, though.
That gets rid of most of your leaves.
Now you got to go around and fix up the edges and stuff.
You know what I mean?
But I'm saying it would clear up most of the eyesore.
Look, there's there's enough going on in reality.
Look, Mandela effect.
I use that term.
I drilled holes, five holes, five three 16 holes in a steel ring yesterday.
All right.
This is one of these items.
OK.
I approached it this morning and there were no holes drilled in it.
You're saying that this literally occurred.
Yes.
Literally occur.
How is that possible?
So you got some kind of time slam reality slam again.
Right.
And I know I didn't dream doing that because I had cutting oil.
It was OK.
Now, you can be incidental if somebody makes a change to something else, small somewhere
else, it could incidentally have a butterfly effect in there.
We got the past three days have been very odd where I had.
Anyways, numbers were mixed up, you know, quantities were mixed up, numbers of things
written down, sent, and they didn't get there the way they were sent.
So is it just the order of the numbers or were the numbers literally of the numbers
like a mistake?
And yeah, it's just really, really odd stuff going on.
And it's been it's been not building up.
But for me, it was a big one recently.
So how do you take that?
Right.
I mean, you know, they built a tremendous amount of insane asylums in the mid 19th
century, end of 19th century.
Right.
So enough to house about 10 percent of the world's population.
So some weird stuff was going on back then, too.
Yeah, for sure.
A lot of the big loonies.
Let's go.
Let's go back.
Let's go back to where we were.
So the chat has been working a lot of times.
I don't I'm too busy.
Like I have to catch up on emails for the past week.
So I try to look at the chat.
I know I try not to be away from the chat for more than three days.
Look at it.
I may not respond.
But when I see someone ask a question myself or someone else, I don't jump in
and answer it right away unless it's one of these smoothing questions that if you
just just answer it because that's it.
It's not a discussion type thing.
Right.
And I like it when other people come in and put in their points of view, what
they know, what they found out, what what could be.
Right.
And that's what happened on this recent chat thing going on.
I've been watching it.
It started with a few things, including the post with the archaic dark
scriptures.
Now, the thing is, I'm being I haven't really said anything about archaics on
that matter because I there's nothing to say.
It's a complete we're talking about two completely different subjects.
So just leave it at that.
OK.
For the people that know old Greek speak and have been on the Skype and on
the older stuff, you'll know that they know exactly that archaics is not
talking about the same thing I am.
Right.
As a matter of fact, anyone that gets on this starts talking about the Bible
and the Internet isn't talking about what I am.
So, yeah, I'm not that original, by the way.
There are others like that, but you but it's very unpopular because it's
unpopular.
You probably never heard of them.
The only one that I cited was Ernest L.
Martin, but they were a sellout also.
So and that was new with Ernest L.
Martin.
It was very new when I was getting into it.
But I got into where I took two years off to study it and I was very serious
and hardcore and they saw it.
But I scared them because on one end, they're like, oh, we got to do what's
in the Bible, you know, whatever.
And I'm like, you're not your timing thing.
You're arguing over Pope's work schedule.
And they freely admitted to me it's about what, you know, they won't do that
because of the money.
Right.
So I'm like, oh, OK, so we are merchants after all.
You are merchants after all.
Oh, you are worldly after all.
Right.
So, you know, they.
Yeah.
OK.
Same thing.
Like with archaics.
You will not go and do an interview unless someone's got more subs than he
does or are very popular.
Like if someone with 500 subs asked me, he's going to say no because he wants
to be rich.
He doesn't want to be right.
OK, so and his narrative is running thin.
I don't really bother with it anymore.
I got what I needed to get out of it, just like with, you know, any other deal.
You get what you need.
You don't you don't admonish them.
You don't go after and say bad things or even too many good things to me.
If you say too many good things about someone that it's also like something's
wrong because there's nothing that good, you know, or nothing is perfect.
Nothing is even good enough to be whatever here.
It's a mess, such a big mess.
But when I see what's going on, it's like, you know, just take it, walk away.
You know, it's just like in my past.
I've been I've been offered things, you know, like positions and be part of a
business. And I look at it and I'm like, you know, anybody else would have
jumped in right now because it looks so good.
But I kind of run the program.
I run it through.
What would it be like after a week, after a month, after a year?
No, it's going to get shitty at six months.
You know, and it's not like I'm being negative about it or whatever, but I
watch the and then I watch the organization in six months and I look at
the process. I see.
I'm glad I didn't jump that thing.
So I have a very good sense about these things.
And ever since the beginning of Greek speak, I've said if I've got more than
20 people listening, it's probably I got to examine what I'm saying.
Right.
It's not, you know, on the other hand, doing the subscription thing and having
input and credits coming in basically doesn't even cover coffee and cigarettes
for me. Not even shy of like 50 or 100 bucks a month of cigarette money.
So what I'm trying to say is if the if the Greek speak stuff took off and I've
always told anyone who wanted to work with don't call it Greek speak, expand
it into something else. And it hasn't.
But my whole thing was if this point of view with.
All right. Let's call it a point of view was to expand and grow.
It would be for its own sake, not for mine anyway.
Right. It would be a group of people now saying, hey, all we got to do is go
back to see what's already been written about this.
Right. That's all. That's what our cakes did.
You know, with the chronology.
That's why from the beginning, our kicks, I just said, I don't feel like I'm
talking about our kicks off for half an hour.
But he just said, what's what's been memorialized about it?
Great. You know, big applause for that. Right.
But the rest of the stuff, man, not really.
If he was at a bar, I wouldn't even go sit with him kind of thing.
So the point here is take what you can that you find to be useful.
That's not bad. It may not be good, but as long as it's not bad and use it.
Another thing, let's just jump around in the chat.
Total Segway jump into it about skin ailments.
OK. Years ago, I talked about skin and teeth are going to be vulnerable as we
go into the future because of the radiation, both natural and manmade.
And let me just go back to a few things.
I did post something which I did have private e-mails exchange with that person.
And I had an ailment on my left arm, which I explained what the left side is.
Right. It's a blocking. Right.
Both right and left block. But it's energy going down.
Right. And whenever I made the cabbage pot roast, pot roast cabbage.
Now, I just want to reiterate to people.
I don't know which episode we did it on.
Maybe a dozen or so or score ago.
Episodes pot roast. How to cook the cabbage.
It has nothing to do with cabbage that you've eaten before.
It's not cooking cabbage. It's cabbage pot roast.
In other words, it's made a certain way that not only does it transform.
It's actually the reason I did it is a meat substitute.
Someone asked me, is there my spouse?
I want to get him off of eating meat.
So how about pot? Does it like pot roast?
OK, how about we substitute the beef for cabbage?
I engineered that and it worked.
So if anyone's ever cooked that and actually I've gotten about a dozen e-mails
saying it's amazing because people have eaten cooked cabbage before.
Even you mentioned it.
I stop you when you start talking about because this has nothing to do with
cooked cabbage.
The way that you cook it, the technique changes the overall finish on it.
And it's actually it works like a meat substitute.
I had some recently and I was like, this is like eating steak, you know.
So it has to be cabbage.
Yeah, it has to be different because compared to the stuff they usually,
you know, serve around St. Patty's Day, I think is one.
Oh, no. Well, the way it's made. Right.
OK, so. OK.
Cabbage is a wonderful it's one of the primary vegetables.
And not only that, it does reflect the skin and the brain.
Now, what I wanted to bring up is when I would do that twice a week,
I noticed any topical ailment, skin ailment I had started regressing and
going away into remission.
If I also put in the point of the moon phases are important here also.
I just want to jump into the cabbage, the broccoli, by the way,
if you're going.
Someone did send me a head of cabbage and a head of broccoli in a box.
Now, I appreciate things being sent.
But for the past 20 years that I've been involved in making things and
sending them out, people sending them back or sending me something of theirs.
When you send something in the post, it doesn't matter which carrier it is.
It has to have packing material in it. Right.
So whenever I get a box and I told the spouse this or the wife all the time,
whenever you get a box, just don't give it to me.
If I'm not there and you pick it up,
if you move the box and you feel something shaking from right to left and it's
rolling around in there, chances are it's damaged. Right.
In other words, whenever you get something in the post, it doesn't matter.
When I say post, it could be postal, post service.
It could be FedEx, DHL, UPS. It doesn't matter.
The content should not be moving around. Right.
Because there's something called a ball mill or a tumbler where you put
things with rough edges and it keeps tumbling to make them smooth,
like river rocks are smooth. Right. It breaks down.
So anyway, I got a head of cabbage and a head of broccoli in a box.
And it was basically like a five pound potato and a 10 pound box. Right.
So a lot of room in there bouncing around. It came kind of.
The cabbage survived. The broccoli didn't.
So if you have enough love to send the Greek something,
put some newspaper in there or something and take up all the airspace.
And if it's a vegetable, it's perishable.
You should have something, a cooling packet in there.
But anyway. Right. That's me.
People that when I ship stuff to people, one of the usually people that are aware,
get back and say, I can't believe how well it was packed.
Well, it didn't. That's just how it should be done.
You know, so. But anyway.
I do get remember no live animals,
but I do get vegetables and things like that in the mail.
And I still I know there's a bag of salt that I have to pick up.
And thank you. Who sent that as well? Celtic salt. OK, cool.
But all the other stuff you guys send me.
So where I want to go with this is the the cabbage aspect.
If you do it now, raw is different because of the high content.
Your body's not the high raw content.
It takes a long time to break down unless you're a UPS driver or a postal carrier.
Right. Or construction worker.
OK. The rule of thumb with food is this.
The more raw the food, the more active you have to be.
And I'm not talking about active. Go to the gym for an hour a day.
I'm talking all day activity like someone who delivers the mail or UPS driver, construction worker.
Who else would be active? What other fields?
An aerobics teacher. You know, you have to be moving constantly.
Yeah. OK. Yeah. In order for your body to break it down.
Military drill instructor kind of guy. Yeah. Yeah.
But constantly moving. Yeah. Not a cop. Right.
Now, the more sedentary you are, the more sedentary you are, the more cooked food you should have.
And that's the rule, by the way.
Now, you can there are exceptions to those rules, but that's the rule for actually balancing, structuring your life.
OK, so there's a lot of people that want to go raw and go vegan.
And I'm like, you can get really sick going vegan if you don't know what you're doing.
Right. In other words, if you eat a lot of raw nuts, which are high in oxalates, you could really damage your kidneys.
You could really your teeth start breaking off at the gum line.
Eating raw nuts and raw killer damage.
Raw nuts and raw food, if you're sedentary, can cause these problems if you're not moving around sedentary.
Or also, if you if you're if you're eating too many raw nuts, even if you're active.
Right. OK. You'll have muscle cramps and things like that.
So people who are vegan don't know about food, the stuff that we're getting.
We've all I've always gotten into. OK. And and and also what we're going to get into right now regarding the skin.
OK, so the skin I mentioned years ago, skin and teeth are going to be a problem.
Let's just deal with the skin right now. The cabbage would be well cooked.
Now, the cabbage pot roast, by the way, is the cabbage pot roast.
Those of you know, there's no meat involved.
They call it a pot roast because it gives you the effect of eating a pot roast.
Right now, if you really want that effect, add some soy sauce or tamari to it.
Right. When you're cooking, it'll make a nice, dark, rich color to it.
But with purple cabbage. But but here's the point.
The soothing elements just use the terminology. It's bracing and soothing.
Bracing means you're not going to eat it and be hungry an hour later or get the shakes later.
Right. It'll it'll keep you for quite a while.
And soothing is that you will feel your body healing.
Now, when your body heals, when you sleep like, OK, you see a bodybuilder, someone who's really fit.
You're like, oh, he must go to the gym a lot. That's what everybody says. Right.
Oh, must be working out a lot. You know what I think?
He must be getting some good sleep because when you go to the gym, your muscles don't build.
Your muscles build when you're right. OK, sleeping.
Yeah. So when I see someone who's really fit. Right.
I never say that you go to gym a lot. They sleep really well.
Wow. What a point of view. Because let's see what's going on.
Could you. OK, let's just be ridiculous for a moment or maybe more than a moment.
Let's say you're constantly working out at the gym and you don't sleep.
Well, first of all, you'll die without sleep for seven days.
Sleep will kill you within seven to 10 days. Yeah, exactly. Yeah. OK.
All right. So, right. The rule that out.
So so let's say there's always in the gym and they sleep for two hours or three hours a night.
They're going to look like crap. So it's the sleep that does.
It's a combo. Is it is it just the sleep? Someone who just sleeps will not look like that.
The combinations. That's what we're speaking of here.
Now, one of the combinations I want to bring on that I didn't emphasize all along,
but on the earlier sonics I brought up is moon phases.
The state of the cosmos, as we are right now, the moon is a major, major effect on us.
Why do you figure that out when you look into it in your own researches?
When the moon is full, it's at its maximum expansion, its effect. Right.
You never hear about the effects of the dark when everyone's talking about the effects of the full moon. Right.
So you'll find a lot of stuff in culture also that, you know, that is actually a signal to what I'm saying, signaling a lot of these methods.
Now, when the moon starts to wane and go towards the dark moon, these contractive energies start setting in. Right.
So you go accordingly. So as the moon goes from full to dark moon, which is the middle of the month, what they call a new moon,
your diet should start contracting also less expansive. So at the full moon time, that's when you would eat the sweetest food.
You would have the more yin foods. Right. You look up what yin and yang foods are.
As you go towards the dark moon, you could use a little more salt.
You can eat some animal, eat more dried things, you know, like things that are concentrated, you know, even the grains.
You do your buckwheat and your rye, brown rice. And during the full moon, you would do more of an oats or a millet or a barley. Right.
More expansive. So you go with the moon. So as the moon is at its dark middle of the month, when it's the darkest, that's that's the time you have some meat or more salt in your food.
If you're not, you know, an animal, you're right. More salty things, you know, cured things.
And then as as the full the dark moon passes, then you go. It starts expanding and waxing towards the full moon again.
You start decreasing those young things. You start eating more, eating it more towards the more liquid, softer foods, a little sweeter.
Right. As you get more greens, more salads. Right. OK.
OK. And then the moon comes and then as it comes, go back to the dark moon, eat less salad, maybe a little more denser foods, more root vegetable.
Right. And then the meat and then you repeat that. So the reason I'm saying is listening to someone is so ridiculous, vegan.
And they've been vegan, they said, for 30 years. Something that I just mentioned would make their head explode.
And it did, by the way. It only took me about 10 seconds to have them implode.
So they imploded. Yeah. And about I would say 10 seconds, about 11 and a half seconds.
So so they're like, oh, I eat nuts. I eat this. I eat that.
But when do you eat them and you know, and how do you know I have to be wrong?
And I'm like, well, but all the time, you know, so there's only so much punishment.
So what I'm trying to say here, OK, well, people have to be very careful.
I just want to point something out. You know, some people will go to look things up after this.
And you're going to get very confused if you begin to look it up.
There's no place to look this up directly, like I'm saying. Well, there are.
I have to write a treatise on this. Yeah. But there are tons of ways actually to look this up.
They're not correct, is what the problem is. There's all kinds of things.
There's a few chapters in some of Michio Kushi's old books somewhere.
But here, let me bring this up again. Let me just reiterate full moon.
As we're approaching the full moon at the full moon, you start eating more salads, more of the sweeter foods that you.
I'm not talking about sugar candies. Sweeter foods would be whatever you tend to have more dessert.
Let's say whatever, you know, sweet squash is sweet.
You know, you cook carrots. They could be really sweet. Right.
So, you know, as more salads, leafy greens, expansive food like that.
Now, as you go towards the dark moon, more contractive food, a little less sweet foods, more salty.
I'm not saying eat salt. The things that tend to be a salty food.
Like, for example, when you ask me what salty foods do you like?
The first thing I say is bacalao, which is salted codfish.
There are many ways to prepare. You could have it cold as a salad.
You could have it hot with a little tomato based soup. Right.
Whatever. I like canned mackerel, you know, things like that.
OK. So pastrami sandwich. Right. It's a little salty, but not too. Right.
OK. Example. OK. Whatever. A good, a good hot dog or something.
OK. So when I say good hot dog, let's get a good hot dog on the street in New York, by the way.
The ones with the sabrets, you know, with the skin on. Pretty much.
Yeah. The dirty water dogs. Yeah. Dirty water dogs. Yeah.
I try to make them here. I came pretty close. But anyway.
So as the dark moon comes, you have more salty foods.
Now, as the dark moon comes and it passes, you start transitioning out of that back to what?
Slightly sweeter foods, more green salads, leafy greens, softer foods to accommodate.
So you see it going towards the full moon. Expansive yin, a little sweeter green salads.
The moon passes as you go towards the dark moon. Work practically slightly saltier, not as sweet.
Maybe some animal time. OK.
One one people don't like those. What do you mean animal? You know, fish, chicken, beef, whatever.
Yeah. So when you start doing that. OK. Yeah.
No, just one. When you start doing that, your body starts to go into the natural order and now you can apply your healing.
All right. Take take a little break on this, because I want to.
First of all, I don't know. You moved around or something, but it broke up a little bit there for a second.
Yep. There we go. Having a little communication issue here with this guy.
Anyway, it'll it'll correct. Yeah, you're.
You're not you're not being heard so well. So just hang on a sec.
Maybe even hit mute for a second if you want to settle down, because here's the thing I want to provide a warning for for anybody listening.
Anyway, there is a ton of stuff out there that sort of says what the Greek is saying now.
But you cannot follow along what he's saying with what they're putting out.
There's a bunch of books. This is Dr. Sears. There's a whole bunch of people talking about these things to eat.
Do not get confused with that, with what the Greek is talking about right now, because it'll contradict it.
OK, this twenty nine point five cycle and circadian rhythm.
Well, there is no twenty nine. OK, if you OK, these idiots that talk about.
That's what I'm saying. There's a lot of crap out there.
You think the moon is twenty nine by five days or twenty because you're using midnight as the start of day.
Right. Right. If you use noontime, which is scientific, astronomical, biblical, classical, traditional.
If you start, can you imagine how they wiped it out from society now?
Anyway, the moon is 30 days. Right. OK.
Or 31 in the summer as the in the summer months, you can have a slightly longer day a month.
OK, so, yeah, but I don't know. I've never heard of these guys or whatever.
But what I'm getting into, I started off with the cabbage and then you have to understand when to apply these things.
Now, here's someone who might have three pencils, sharpened pencils in their pocket.
If you want to do skin therapy, I would eat cabbage at least every other day or every day for the time period from the dark moon waxing to the full moon.
And then keep eating it, but start then eating less of it.
To the dark moon. And then I would eat a quality salted food that is that resembles cabbage in its own whatever.
I mean, you can go what goes well with cabbage that resembles cabbage, but goes well with just keep eating the cabbage for a month.
Just to check that I understand what you're saying. It's around that time when the moon starts to get dark.
This is when you can begin to add in a little bit of like, say, animal products.
Is that right?
Right. Right before like three. Yes. So when you go from full moon to dark moon, you've already built up to your salads and all that.
Now you start tapering off on the salads and going towards the salty and the animal.
And your most animal would be eaten on the dark moon.
And then as the dark moon passes two or three days later, you start working up to the salads and the sweeter foods again.
Now, once you start getting into the swing of things, it's called a swing.
There's a lot of swings in history. I mean, in health where they call it the acid alkaline swing was one that I learned in the 80s.
If you can't beat something, eat acid food for three days and eat alkaline food for three days and acid food for three back and forth to knock it out of your body.
That's fine, I guess. You know, it's very simple, but it's not it's not holistic and a holistic means the whole thing.
So the reason I want bring up the timing is because the timing is important.
Like, for example, one early episode we did, if something you have a pain in the daytime and it only hurts when the sun is up.
Right. Other times you might have a pain only at nighttime and when the sun is down.
So that right away is a big clue. Right. Because when the sun is up, it's expensive.
You have too much. If it hurts when when the sun is down, it's a young base thing.
Right. That's why people who have a young surplus will have a hard time sleeping.
Someone's a hard time sleeping. I told this to many people through the years.
You're eating too much salt and too much meat. Cut back on the salted and the meat and you'll be able to sleep.
And like I've always gotten back with him. Yeah, it worked. Right.
And if someone has like pains and headaches during the day, but not at night, you're eating too many sweets, too many sugars, chemicals.
Are you taking pharmaceutical drugs? The answer is yes. Right.
So that's a very simple there's the day thing. There's the month thing.
And then there's the seasonal thing, which is you have to combine the day and the month.
I'm not going to get into the seasonal thing now because I'm still working it out.
But what I have worked on, I know works is the day thing, the day swing, you know, where the when the sun is up, it's expensive.
And when the sun is down, it's contractive. And I have worked out the moon thing.
In other words, when the moon is full, it's the most expensive time.
You know, sweet, soft lettuce. And when the moon is dark, it's the most contractive time, more salty, possibly animal.
Now, if you're not doing animal, that would be the time during the dark moon to do your buckwheat.
Right. Your and your brown rice. You just do your whole buckwheat. Right.
And things are more contractive. You would do like a fermented soy if you do tempeh.
Right. Or fish. Right. Salted fish. Things like that.
You'd have to figure out what I mean by, you know, yin and yang, you know, or yin and yang foods is plenty of charts.
But this aspect now, you know, OK, we thought we started speaking about skin and the remedy.
Cabbage is a very good remedy. There are other things you can do.
And I'm going to mention one other thing that's being I might develop it in the near future if I see time.
But let's say let's forget about all this and say, let's say you have a remedy or something.
You go to buy a remedy in a store. Right. Doesn't it have directions when to use, how to use?
Doesn't it doesn't actually say that on the bottle or the packaging?
Usually take take one day, take one every three hours. This many hours to put on.
Yeah. So what I'm getting into now, just eating cabbage, but when and how and why it's as directed.
This is where I take as directed. Right. That's what I'm talking about.
The direction during the day and during and during the moon cycle is the direction of how you should eat.
This is for a healing diet. If you want to fix something now other than the cabbage.
I don't know what else to recommend at this point for skin ailments, but eating clean. Right.
Now, the other thing about repairing the skin and having the skin come back together, avoid any oil, any oil at all fat.
It doesn't matter. Animal or olive oil. You know, they say olive oil is really good or macadamia oil or whatever.
No, no, no. All that. Why? Because when you eat those oils, oils are essential for skin development.
Your body will induce that oil into its organism and try to modify it to repair the skin.
And it's already having a hard time with the skin. If you have no oils at all.
The only signal for oil is the only signal your your your DNA knows to produce for the skin.
It's very clean. It's going to produce what's encoded.
It's what's encoded in you to repair the skin, because that's what it's constantly doing anyway.
And it won't be as confused or as challenged by external oils, because it sounds like, for example, when people have dry skins, they eat more oil.
Right. But more some olive oil in your diet. That's why. No, it's actually because you're having too much oil and your oil production is screwed up because it's being influenced by external influence.
Right. That's another Greek saying external influence, all external.
So when you avoid oil completely, your body will produce it and in the right amounts and in the right type that it needs to recover.
Right. So when I mean no oil, here's an example. If you have a severe skin condition and you can put one drop of oil in your food a month and that's you just screwed it up.
That's how critical it gets when you start dealing with induction.
OK, now what can be done with the skin?
Now, don't hold me on this. What I mean by this is like I was on a conference call about 10 years ago.
I said, you know, I'm going to make a pipe that you put dirty water on one side, clean water comes out in the other or hard water comes up.
Right. OK. Comes out soft. Ten years ago. And it didn't come around to where I could produce it and consistently and talk like the scale of it or only the past year.
Right. So this would be the next project. The skin is a surface reaction.
When you notice something on the skin, it's a it's a surface covering the skin. Right. Right.
OK, so there's several phenomenon in nature and in the construction industry known as efflorescence, where you have a particular salt or white powder that forms on a brick wall and it's a salt and it's like and it eats away the brick wall and they try to put waterproofing, but it doesn't bond to it.
Right. By the way, that's where saltpeter comes from. Years ago, if you go to France, some of the old in Europe, some of the old buildings, you'll notice that near the ground level, a lot of the brick and mortar is scraped away.
Because if the military would come by and scrape this white powder off the building because it was an ingredient for gunpowder, it's called saltpeter.
Right. And if you didn't allow them to scrape the building, it was a substitute for paying tax.
Right. So if you didn't have money, you let them scrape. Anyway, that's just a little trivia.
But one thing that can be done and I was the first person to do this about 23 years ago with Eric Means at Eric Means Design.
That's some Adobe buildings that have an efflorescence. By the way, this is about skin assault building up on the outside.
They had a poly salicylate waterproof and they you can't you can't put any kind of coating or waterproofing material on a building if it has salt on it, right on the on the structure.
But the salt is always a surface reaction. So what I said, why don't we fool.
So what in other words, what they did was they try to scrub the salt with water and pressure wash it.
But the moisture just made more of it come out. So this is what we need to do.
We need to fool this salt. So what we do is we pressure wash the building.
At the same time, we put up some furring strips with some three inch cotton batting on the wall while the wall is still wet.
And when the salt is going to want to come to the surface, is it going to deposit itself on the Adobe brick or is it going to go all the way through the cotton bat?
Deposit itself on the cotton batting. Then we remove the cotton batting and all the salt is gone.
Guess what happened? That's exactly what happened is the first time they ever seen anything like that.
And it worked. And as a matter of fact, I used to go every five or 10 years and check on it.
There's still no no efflorescence buildup. So the idea is the same for the human body.
When you have a skin ailment, it is happening on the surface covering of the body on the surface layer.
All right. Why isn't it happening on the muscle right under the skin?
It's because it needs to get to the surface. A type of gauze can be developed and most likely be linen.
And it will most likely be treated linen, meaning soaked in a solution of some kind.
And that is wrapped on the body and it's undisturbed.
In other words, you don't take it off and you can't subject it. If you're going to bathe or shower, it has to be hermetically covered with plastic.
Remember the people years ago is very common. Got into a fight. Someone broke their arm.
And when you take a shower, you put a plastic bag over the cast. Right.
Kind of thing like that. So you'd have to yeah, you'd have to completely cover it.
And this would be left on for a period of anywhere a minimum of seven days to two weeks.
And then you would remove it and you'd have brand new skin no matter what the condition was.
Right.
Okay.