Sonic Event 101, Rated Y.
And here we are.
Now, last time we did discuss the container briefly, but more about the care and maintenance
of the container last time, Greg.
Yeah, I needed to just put the most important stuff out, so what do you do once you find
out how something works?
It's kind of like, you have a car and you got an oil leak because you didn't use the
right oil, and you got to fix the oil leak on the gaskets, a several hour job or whatever,
but you never discuss what the right oil is.
So just say, here's an oil leak, this is the right oil, use that.
And now we get into fixing the gasket or whatever that broke, right?
So now we'll get more into the technical stuff, which is pretty much a recap on, I think,
back in the original ONG, the second episode called The Container.
I'm going to revisit that just mentally, I have no notes, I have never heard it.
I just recall that was part of my standard shtick when I told, you know, whenever I had
the spotlight on explaining what the human body is, including the doctors, by the way.
By the way, the medical people, it's programming, it's brainwashing, it's, they have a state
certified education.
If it's state certified, it's crap, right?
I hope you guys know that.
Well, why would they certify something that's good for you as if they're on your side, right?
It's always yours.
Well, you did, they did before the central banks came in.
They're just, okay, doctors, attorneys, priests, accountants are central bank clerks.
That's who they really work for.
They may not know it, right?
They may not know it.
It's kind of like any other operation that's, what do you call it?
Like when the mob owns a, he's got control of a trucking company and the trucking company
tells the driver to go make a delivery, he doesn't know that it's being ordered by the
mob that controls his boss because he's getting it from his boss, right?
Oh, of course.
That's why you leave the bosses in place and you buy the bosses.
So the AMA, all these medical, they're basically part of the central bank conglomerate.
Every time you hear alphabet agency, that's part of the central banks except for the FBI,
which was created by the Jewish mafia, which is another story we can get into.
It was called, it was Pinkerton before that, super corrupt.
So they said if it's, if we, an organization like that will always be corrupt.
So let's dress it up the way we want it.
I mean, how many mob, Jewish mob bosses have been busted versus Italian mob bosses?
Think about it.
Way less.
By the FBI.
I mean, yeah.
Oh yeah.
Like maybe two versus a 50 or a hundred.
Yeah.
I mean, they busted Lansky, but I mean, they, they didn't bust a hundred other guys.
I mean.
No.
Yeah.
And just like the DEA is, has the full might and military of the U.S. Army, right?
And what they do is they mitigate the cartels.
It's kind of like the DEA does what OPEC does for the oil producing nations.
The DEA organizes all, everyone who is the cartels versus regional geography, that they
behave a certain way.
And when the cartels, let's say, you know, like the mob boss, they have a meeting and
they say, well, this cartel isn't really playing with us well, guess who goes and takes them
down?
The DEA.
Well, I pared it down this way when somebody asked me about the drug war and they said,
well, what is the purpose of the DEA and your concept of what the way the drug war is actually
fought?
You know, cause he was mocking me about how I said the biggest drug dealer is our government.
Well, it's not, it's not, again, DEA is, is from the Nixon administration around there
put forward, right?
FDA, DEA.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's again, it's a central bank operation.
He's also responsible for the Environmental Protection Agency too.
Yeah.
I know.
Okay.
I'm not going to use names, but the, one of the best snipers, if this guy, if you look
at Pablo Escobar, there's a picture when he shot on the roof, it's kind of like Photoshop.
He's dead.
And there's a guy that's holding dead Pablo Escobar from the shirt and he's smiling.
That's the guy.
He's a sharpshooter.
Uh, he used to work for the state department and he's part really high up in the DEA.
And he says the biggest drug dealer in the world is the DEA.
Yeah.
And DEA is also used to, to clean up and FBI, um, sick situations for, for, uh, public relations.
Well, this guy asked me and I told him that the DEA is really there just to control the
price.
Yeah.
That's really what it is.
But when it gets really dirty, really, really dirty business, like, you know, when they
nuke the terror, you know, the terrorist bombings that are actually really nukes, they don't
even use the, any, any triple letter agency.
They use, um, Wackenhut.
That's whenever you see a Wackenhut security show up, it's usually a Fed contracts that
something really dirty is going on, like super dirty.
So this whole thing, this is very well known.
This is like, uh.
Well, Kraft too, right?
You live in a bad neighborhood.
This is a bad neighborhood, meaning the world.
And one of the benefits of living in a bad neighborhood is you're not surprised when
bad shit happens.
These people that live in these, you know, uh, ticky tacky McMansions or whatever, they
get really surprised when bad shit happens, right?
It's the same thing.
So don't, you know, don't be surprised.
But anyway, the container, one of the things that we got into on the early ones is that
the body is a sealed and closed system.
It really is mostly, um, nothing ever goes through the body directly.
Just like, for example, when you are at a picnic or at the beach years ago and you
had a radio with speakers, because I always hear radio, people always think headphones
if you're not 30 or 40 years old and you hear jazz music playing, do you think if you open
that radio, there's a little jazz band inside playing it out, it sounds like a ridiculous
analogy.
No one's that stupid, right?
Well, then how do you, why do you believe when they tell you things go through the intestine
and absorb that, you know, through the skin, you know, through the intestines, through
tissues in the body, they're completely sealed.
So how does the music play through the radio?
By quartz crystal induction, there's a perturbations in the ether, well perturbations merely like
a waveform crystal is tuned into that, picks it up and it goes through a series of amplifications.
It's exactly how the body works, but it works on a material sense.
Now the reason why it's never discussed how induction works is because if this is taught
at a young age, you will literally, I have to say this slowly because people don't really
get it.
And I never had, the reason I'd say slowly is because all the years I've been talking
about this and using this principle, no one's really said, Hey, we need to develop it and
talk more about it.
It's amazing to me.
This is the amazing thing.
I'm going to say it very slowly.
If you were taught at a young age, how induction and how the body really creates things and
eliminates things and builds up self and however, whatever function you might consider, if you
were taught how that it really works, you will be spending the rest of your life, never
feeling there's anything you can't do because it literally compares to magic or superpowers.
If it comes down to it, right?
It's just about putting the right stuff into the right part of the induction system to
create the right reaction.
And that's all there is to it.
I mean, look, here, here's the thing that I think really confuses people because we were
taught about digestion and you've been through that and you talked about the intestines,
but I think the thing that confuses people is what you take in air though, don't you?
So you take in air, you must use the air and it's the same function, but that's the
same by induction.
Whether, okay.
Think of the air as being the jazz station, right?
The food is the rock and roll station.
The classical music is the light, you know, it's all different tunings, different frequencies
by a material and materials all have different frequencies.
There's a Jack Fresco comment that he says, instead of naming the elements, whatever,
why don't we, each element has a specific frequency.
Why don't we just use that number instead of the name of the element?
It's far more specific and it tells you more, gives you information about the element.
Well, you know, beyond just what it should be designated as.
So this is the primer.
This is where I always start out, get on the computer or whatever, even you can do this
long hand in print, but type in cross section of intestines anatomy and you will see anatomic
drawings.
I've verified them.
I have microscopes and all that.
The cross section looks very accurate, right?
And you will see at least two or three hydrophobic layers.
Hydrophobic layers means that they reject water.
Hydrophobic means that, for example, a freshly polished car hood with water on it, well,
the water will bead, which is hydrophobic, means it repels water.
Just like roots of a plant.
Hydrophilic is when it absorbs water, something like a sponge.
But here's the interesting thing without going on a tangent.
A sponge, usually a natural sponge, a living sponge, as a sea, I was going to say sea vegetable,
it's a sea animal, looks like it's hydrophilic, like it absorbs water.
But if you look at the structure of the cells of the sponge itself, it's actually hydrophobic.
So in other words, if you magnified a very small, tiny piece of sponge inside the cellular,
not the molecular cells, just a very tiny, too small to see by the human eye, but you
can see it under a microscope, put it near a drop of water, it will reject the water.
Why?
Because all living things do that.
So let me just go back to the analogy.
Put in the intestines, it doesn't have to be human intestines, but you can, cross section
anatomy.
Do a split screen and then do a cross section of a steel belted radial tire or a car tire.
And they look the same.
Why?
Because what is the purpose of a car tire?
It's to have a certain pressure, so it performs its function and it separates that pressure
from the environment, doesn't it?
And right, so what I mean is the tire is inflated and it's supposed to keep that pressurized
air in order for the tire to perform its function.
When it no longer can perform its function, it equalizes the pressures and right, okay.
So it's flat.
So look, do the same thing, cross section of skin, epidermis, and you will see pores
and hair follicles, yada, yada, yada.
And start researching the cells and then they actually designate different cells and they're
all hydrophobic.
A healthy person, when they come out of the shower, by the way, it's not too hairy.
If they just stand there, they start drip drying, you know, the water starts beating
on the surface of your skin, doesn't it?
Yes.
Yeah.
Because it's hydrophobic, repels water.
Right.
So, so here's the other thing, and I'm not going to make this about being hydrophobic
or hydrophilic, but it is a quality that shows the direction of things.
You will also see that the skin, interstitial spaces in the cells that they show, interstitial
spaces means that they're packed together, just as if you go to the store and buy a loaf
of sliced bread, you notice how it almost doesn't lift a really, you know, fresh loaf or it's
packaged.
Well, you can't even see the slices sometimes, right?
Until you start moving it, right?
Right.
Because they're packed really tight.
Okay.
That's exactly how your cells are, but imagine irregular shapes or basically oblong shapes.
That's how swelling happens, by the way, when those spaces disturbed lymphatic fluid flows
into those spaces and you get swelling.
That's why we've gone into the remedies of that, uh, wrapping things tight to prevent
that fluid from going in there and the body doesn't get the signal that you have an injury.
So by the way, five times a second, the, the, uh, every cell in the body or group of cells
sends a message to the brain, we're okay.
And five times a second, the brain sends a signal to all the cells in the body saying,
are you okay?
Right.
This is happening at that rate, generally at that rate, five times a second, there's
a correct, a test back and forth check 300 times a minute.
This is going up 300 times a minute.
Yeah.
Some people, healthy people, uh, more physical, faster, and obviously, you know, less and older,
less healthy, less, but older people slower.
Um, this is not discussed by the way.
Also, by the way, blood cells literally have serial numbers on them, not like numeric numbers.
But when these idiots, medical idiots are looking at blood slides, they don't know what they're
looking at, by the way.
You know, by the way, blood testing is, is all algorithms now.
It's put in a machine.
It kind of reminds me of, um, you go to these, uh, Home Depot, whatever stores now, and you
know, when you wanted a key made, you had a clerk make a key, tested it and everything.
Now you just stick a key in a machine.
It's automatic.
It makes a key automatic.
It doesn't always work also.
Right?
No, they kind of automatic key.
The automatic key machines suck.
Yeah.
The blood, the blood testing is similar like that.
You never go, this is protocol to charge you a bunch of money.
Oh, we got to do blood work.
And they do that for animals.
Vets doesn't want to talk to you unless you do blood work and they hear it.
It's all useless.
They don't even know what they're looking at.
Okay.
So what I want to say is when they look at red blood cells, the morons don't know that
the each blood cell has a designation point.
What do I mean by that?
This red blood cell is for the eye.
This red blood cells for your big toe, right?
This blood cells for the ovary.
This blood's red blood.
So all red blood.
They don't see that.
And by the way, if you work in the medical community and you start using this kind of
language, you're going to get fired.
Just like, for example, when I used to go, when I learned about the system more than
24 years ago now, I used to go into the bank and mess around and say, these people are
really dumb, aren't they?
Let's prove it.
I had someone with me.
I'd give them a check.
So I'd like to convert this to federal reserve notes.
And the clerk, the bank teller looks at me, uh, just a second.
And she started talking to the manager on the side.
And the manager's like, oh my gosh, touches, you know, does the chin scratching thing and
tells the bank teller to go on break because the, the, the bank teller doesn't know what
a federal reserve note is, right?
A bank note doesn't know.
And then the manager would just come and sit down looking straight forward.
How would you like it?
You know, in twenties, fifties, a hundred, whatever.
And I'd be like, oh my gosh, you know, I'm looking at her and we're both looking at each
other and we're like, yeah, these people are really dumb.
So imagine someone who is working with federal reserve notes all day and they don't even
know what they are.
If someone asks for one, this is the medical community.
Well, this wasn't always the case though, because when you look at older medical texts
and I've been through a lot of textbooks, you know, that they were supposed to teach
doctors and nurses and different practitioners at different times, right?
Um, they used words like induction in a lot of older medical books.
But not on the internet, you're not going to find it.
I've been looking, actually this past, I didn't spend as much as I should have or could have.
A few hours is plenty, but look, the status of Google right now and other search engines
that are similar.
If you can't figure out that they're hiding stuff or not showing you stuff or it's watered
down in like 20 minutes or an hours of research, you're, you're not that bright.
And I was looking around, looking around, nothing.
It's funny when you put in a search and it tells you 8 million results, right?
And then you go, okay, you got 30 or 40 results on a page.
You go to page two and you got another 30, 40 results.
You go to page three, page four, page five.
So you're like 200 results.
And then you look up and it says only 500 results left.
Wait a second.
I've only gone through a hundred sites.
How did you go from 8 million to 500 now?
I've only been through like a hundred or 200.
How do we do that?
You ever noticed that?
Have you ever done that?
Yeah, absolutely.
I've done that.
Uh, and, and it's, yeah, you keep progressing.
It's 8 million research results.
And someone will give you some excuse.
Oh, the search results mean on words that are in within the document, but not 8 million.
What the hell are they trying to do?
So anyway, you can't find stuff.
The NIH, um, NIH document.
Okay.
There was a document that I downloaded a long time ago, 900 pages on virology, vaccination,
immunology.
And the whole thing was about finding the effectiveness all over the world that compiled
all these researches that some were done with a five year, some were done over 20 year periods
on all that's all that subject matter.
And I had some graphics and all that stuff also.
So by the time you got to the reading this entire thing, I said, wait a second, let's
go see what the conclusion is.
The conclusion clearly stated that this is all inconclusive and we still don't know what
the, if there's any primary mechanism, what the, uh, you know, how it's induced or whatever.
All right.
So why would you spend, you know, I don't know, a week, two weeks reading this 980 page
document if it's inconclusive in the end, just go right to the conclusion.
It's inconclusive.
So, but basically you see what they went through and they went through every possible process
that that is known to them to look for causes of disease, immunology, virology, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
And then you have no conclusion on what causes it.
So you can walk away.
There's no reason to really get into the details.
You can, it's important to have it as a reference manual.
So if you're going to quote unquote debate or argue the point, you could bring up the
more critical example set in the text.
Right.
But ultimately the conclusion is thus.
That's why it's very often you'll hear me say like, okay, the three letter alphabet
agencies in any country, they're all central bank clerks.
Oh my gosh.
How'd you get that?
I don't see it.
You start researching how the central banks have infiltrated and taken over.
You'll see.
Yep, exactly.
After about a year's worth of research.
Right.
There's also people that work in there.
It's like JP Morgan said, there's two reasons why people in organizations do things.
First is the reasonable, logical, good reason that you tell everyone.
And then the second is the real reason.
Right?
So the reason why the first logical reason with the three letter agencies is that we
need controls.
We need regulation to protect the population.
That sounds good.
Right.
But the real reason is so the central banks have controls of all those things.
And that's basically what you end up with.
We're here to protect you from the irresponsible actors out there.
Which happen to be them.
To be them.
Right.
Exactly.
This is a repeat over and over.
So let's go back to what we were discussing.
The community, meaning not only the people that, okay, you have people that have their
quote unquote jobs or yobs, either one.
I think we've discussed the difference between a job and a yob.
And they have their interests.
They have their families to take care of.
And let's say, you know, it takes up most of your day.
And you're not the type that comes home and watches four hours of TV, but you're interested
in astrophysics or you're interested in the biology or medicine or miniature trains or
whatever.
Right.
You're going to look at people that do that as you're going to say, well, I'm interested
in astronomy, so I'm going to go read what the astrophysicists write about.
Right.
So because I have to trust them.
You know, I don't have the time to do what they write.
So what happens is you end up repeating the junk that they have learned and they're not
smart enough to realize they're being fooled.
Actually, a lot of them are and they leave.
And now this is how you keep, what do you call it?
Dog chasing its tail.
What do you call a situation you can't get out of?
Catch 22, whatever.
Right.
So, again, this is how the medical system is.
And they've brought it up to a level where you can't question it just like priesthood
of some sort.
I say, why bother question it?
Because here's the thing, right?
What it sounds like you're saying to me-
Just reject it unless you're dying.
Even then.
Let it go.
And now let's get back to the real thing here, which is, again, you're saying it's a closed
system.
The body.
Let's go back to the without the changes, because this is very, this is very, very important
because it's more important to discuss other things along with the container, how it works,
like the things we are, because it's such a drastic deviation from what the programming,
the culture, recent culture, you know, 150 years.
Well, the culture has been all kinds of teaching.
All kinds of constructs.
It's all BS.
It's all central banking stuff.
Around it.
But the central banks are not the base, you know, there's stuff beyond that too.
But it's a spiritual decline, you know, the way I want to call it, right?
It's cosmic.
It's a cosmic thing, it's a spiritual thing, and it's an attack, and it's a constant hindrance,
and all of that.
But back to the container itself.
It sounds to me like there are a bunch of subsystems here, which are contained in the
singular system.
Just like in a radio.
And yeah, just like you said.
Or anything that hasn't, all of the devices that you have today work by this same principle.
There you go.
The speakers in the wiring in a radio, they have a purpose, and their purpose is not to
receive stuff.
Their purpose is to then put it back out for you to hear it, right?
Okay.
Yeah, let's just get into something that I haven't gotten to before.
One of the main purposes of the different systems is scale.
Scale meaning size.
So if you were to be much larger physically, 20, 30 feet tall instead of the average height
of a human, or you were to be one inch tall or two inches tall, certain systems would
be very different.
The scale adapts to the energies based on the mass principle, the physical size and
things on this planet, on this earth, however you want to view the earth, this domain, this
realm that we live in.
And one of the ways you can start looking at this is the differences between men and
women physiologically.
And we're not talking just the reproductive organs.
For example, when you have a man and a woman in a room, the women tend to prefer the room
to be a little warmer than the man, usually.
Why?
Well, proportionately, let's say the man and the woman are the same weight and the same
height.
Until they get to a certain age, yeah, they generally prefer.
The man's liver is larger.
So one hundred and fifty pound, five foot eight man compared to one hundred and fifty
pound, five foot eight woman.
The liver in the male would be larger than the liver in the woman, right?
So you have certain organs that take precedent in size and scale within the body based on
what we're supposed to be doing, right?
Think about, you know, there's a certain amount of some some medical side.
This is not really discussed.
Have you heard this before?
No, I haven't.
Equal proportion.
The proportion of the liver is larger in a man, right?
No, I've never heard that before.
Yeah.
You will start going and seeing things similar to this with various organs that are not discussed
because it has to do with doing whatever job you're doing.
Typically, the male would be more active.
A lot of what some stuff that was written about this is that, well, the liver is larger
because of because of testosterone, right?
And that there's no proof of that.
Right.
There was no relation to that.
I once saw a study that said that women would be better astronauts because they more efficiently
utilize water than men do.
And there were a bunch of reasons for that.
Is that does that have something to do with this as well?
What makes a good astronaut is that people believe that there is such a thing.
No, but what I'm saying is to be away from the earth for a long time to conserve water
and like a woman would use less water to survive is what the idea was in this study that they
did.
You could go.
Here's the other thing we'll get into.
I haven't been there to maybe I have, but I don't recall the further you get away from
the earth and what you call if you look up and you don't see a blue sky meaning during
the day, the less you can control your sanity, you will get to the point where you will start
to see things that you will not function.
I mean, not like DMT, but it's just you will not be able to function.
In other words, it's all mental.
It's all mental.
So, OK, well, if you don't believe that, look into when they when they put people in isolation
in incarceration.
I mean, when when you're in, you know, when you're I'm the wrong person to talk about that
because there's people that have spent months and months and even years in caves alone and
they're in total bliss.
Yeah, but I are.
So I might be one of those.
I'm you know, I'm if I don't see another human ever again, I'm I'm fine.
Well, a lot of people when they're forced into isolation.
OK.
Right.
But that's because.
Yeah.
That's because of programming.
And that's because the individual just like the liver is larger.
Right.
So there's a there's a there's a I don't want to be like Jimmy the Greek.
He said something that got him in trouble.
Remember?
Yeah.
Well, yeah.
OK.
So, yeah.
So I don't think it's across that line, but I think it's more individual.
There's some people that must be around like you don't have to be antisocial.
This.
OK.
The real gurus, the real people that you hear about that go into isolation.
Yeah.
You never hear about them.
You know why?
Because they're in isolation.
Right.
The ones that you hear about are the ones that are going batshit crazy.
You know why?
Because they're batshit crazy.
Not rip from go.
You see what I mean?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
People that people that are quiet and conduct and conduct themselves in an impeccable manner
where it never get any attention.
Well, most times it seems to me like people just amplify what they already had.
Yeah.
So like this.
Right.
So anyway.
OK, let's get back to the body.
Sure.
There's the scale concept.
OK.
The other thing is go back to the induction.
How does it work?
This is just imagine a process.
OK.
You have a lot of this law of attraction, all these gurus.
You just imagine something and it comes, which is true, like Nisha and Daikon in Buddhism,
where you chant Nam-myoho-renge-kyo.
And it's basically if you want something physical, there's like a swan or one of those other
birds that are not swans.
They have long legs and they fly cranes.
Crane.
Yeah.
And Tina Turner.
Most people Westerners find out about it because she's like, I want a red Corvette.
I want a red Corvette.
Nam-myoho-renge-kyo.
And you end up getting a red Corvette.
Right.
This is for a lot of people.
It kind of works.
OK.
Regarding to the body, the chant for the body or the mind idea is that everything is energy
and energy.
You can just use the simple academic term of what energy is.
Then it's then it starts to become a plasma for a very, very short period of time.
And then it appears to be a gas.
And I mean a gas just like a gas that could be odorless, colorless or may have an odor.
And then it becomes a liquid.
You could pick your choice of liquid because there are liquids in the body that are dark
purple.
Right.
And red and clear.
And then it becomes a gelatinous soft tissue and then it goes to a solid like teeth or
hair, chitin, bone.
This is the frequency change.
Not necessarily frequency as in radio waves, but in other words, the frequency of how it
goes from one thing to the next to the next.
So and I've discussed this with a neurosurgeon and he said he didn't know about something
as simple as this.
He started observing it and came back.
So, yes, exactly what's happening when you have a wound, let's say a cut, you know, a
quarter inch deep in your skin, something that you have to mind, not like a paper cut
or a scratch when you're working construction and you're like, oh, I'll just I don't have
to worry about that.
Right.
But something that you really have to mind for a little bit.
OK, so it doesn't get infected or if you don't tighten it, it bleeds a lot.
Kind of thing like that.
If you watch a wound like that, first thing you're going to see once the bleeding stops
and you close the wound, there's going to be a light colored fluid coming through.
But prior to that, you're going to feel a tingling sensation depends if it's sore or
inflamed.
Right.
So that tingling sensation is the gaseous atmosphere forming around the wound.
And then that becomes a liquid of that's what scabs are made of, blood and other things,
you know, it's dry on there and yeah, yeah.
And then that becomes a soft gelatinous material, almost like a pure white.
You could see through it.
And then it starts to become skin.
Right.
And that is the process.
And it always goes from an energetic to a plasma, which is an energy sort of they call it another
state of matter.
Let's just say, oh, boy, in manufacturing, when you're making anything like a food product,
you know, you get the raw materials distributed and they start getting mixed up and then they
form doughnuts.
Right.
And then they fry the doughnuts and they get packaged system very similar like that.
The raw material for the human body is energetic.
Right.
And the energetic gets organized, just like you have a power, let's say, cable coming
in and it energizes a fan, a light or whatever.
That would be the plasma.
And when it energizes a fan or a light or whatever the purpose of that is, would be
the gas.
You see, there's an analogous.
So what you why is this important when you're dealing with the human body?
Because you know, you know, the stages that it goes through, just like if you want to
open a doughnut factory, you got to have the flour delivered, you got to have the oil delivered.
Right.
How are you going to handle those deliveries and process them into final to doughnuts?
So when you have a wound or don't have a wound and the body is growing or recovering, do you
understand that it's energetic first?
That's why the quality of the food is very important.
The energetic part of the food, the component, which I saw in the chat, let me just digress
a little bit.
The fine energies, for example, there's something called homeopathy, placebo aside, the purpose
of homeopathy is to put the energy of something into a substrate like sugar.
And when you take that substrate, it has the absence of the material that's supposed to
have the remedy, just the energy of it.
But it's called a preparation.
Right.
So there's actually nothing that's a lot of Westerners like, well, it doesn't work because
there's nothing in it.
It says it has this particular herbal extract, but it has doesn't have any of it in it.
Well, it goes in angstroms.
Right.
They keep reducing it.
So it's like you put a drop.
Let's say you're going to do an herbal texture of THC homeopathically.
So you get a drop of THC and you put it in a fifty five gallon barrel of water, just one
drop of THC in a fifty five gallon barrel of water.
Right.
Then you prepare that fifty gallon bottle of water.
They usually put rubber pads on it and hammer on it.
Right.
So vibrate it.
OK.
And they certain processes few days and then they take one drop out of that fifty five
gallon barrel of water.
So they only have one drop of THC in it.
Right.
I put it in four or five other fifty five gallon barrel of drugs and they prepare those and
then they take one drop out of each one and put it in even larger.
So it's like, oh, my gosh, the reduction is like millions of times, right?
Less.
But it has the effect of THC.
You see.
OK.
So if it's something that is so subtle and it works, homeopathic stuff works.
One of the most effective anti-toxin, anti-venom preparations you can take are homeopathics,
by the way.
It's and it works better than chelation for some.
That's another discussion because we can go into specific things and have a hundred episodes
just on biology and how to treat things.
Right.
So it's not necessary because you should be doing this on your own once you have the basics.
This is the fundamental stuff.
So give me an example.
When you have wonderful organic vegetables that are very healthful and they go into a
diesel truck with a refrigeration system that uses compressed freon, let's say, right, or
refrigerant, which is a very volatile.
Sometimes it's not system.
Do you think the diesel tank?
How far away is the diesel tank in the exhaust pipe and the engine from the cabbage that's
being transported by 10, 20 feet, 50 feet?
If you've got cabbage on the end door and the exhaust, the engines on the other side
of the trailer, maybe 50 feet away, I think 5, 10, 5, 10, 15 is your maximum probably
any given.
Yeah.
Right.
Okay.
And it's sitting there for how long?
And it's vibrating going down just like they make homeopathic remedies, right?
That's to be vibrated.
Not just sitting there.
Right.
But if you're ahead of cabbage in a truck, diesel truck going down the road, you feel
any vibration?
Hell yeah.
So all this vegetables that are transported by diesel trucks or locomotives or however,
Right.
It's they're preparing this for me.
It's got.
Right.
So anyway, very interesting.
That's why even people that eat really healthy food, here's something.
Oh, I don't know.
There were health foods since the 1970s and they got a certain cancer and you'll notice
that's the same cancer that people that work with petroleum get.
How could that be possible?
Because they basically got eight, mostly veggies that were transported.
They didn't have their own garden, for example, or if you have a local garden, it's probably
never going to be in a diesel truck.
Is it?
Right.
Yeah.
Local meaning.
I don't know.
20 minute walk.
Half hour walk.
Right.
Okay.
So if you're in, you're right.
You know, half hour walk.
Yeah.
Half hour walk.
You cover about a mile and a half comfortably.
I was going to say mile, you know, mile, two mile and a half.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah.
Comfortably.
All right.
So what's, you see how it works?
Very, very simple.
This is so simple.
You know, like people that were ill, what do I do?
I said, well, okay, let's just get to the end of it.
If you want to get better, you're going to have to live in a straw hut with a mud floor.
How's that?
And then anything that's not that or deviating from that is how harder it is going to be
to heal.
Right.
Okay.
So if we go back to the body and the sections where it's energetic, we got into the yin
and yang and previous episodes, how certain energetics and food, the left side of the
body, the energies exit the body.
They want to go down.
And on the right side of the body, the energies go up.
I know someone, John Butts recently passed away by the way of natural action technologies.
I was working with him.
He died at 49 when he was in his 50th year.
Anyway, he worked as a nuclear technician on a naval submarine.
He was like the number one or number two guy, depending on how drunk the number one guy
was.
Okay.
And it was kind of those weird, one of those weird ships where the captain of the ship
shot his wife and then shot himself kind of like you, who the hell knows what's going
on in these things.
Right.
Yeah.
So he was around the reactor and he did all this kind of stuff with water, of course.
And I've known him, we speak and speaking for over a year.
And because of the radiation toxification that his body was still dealing with, kind
of a hard head, though, he wouldn't do any of the remedies I suggested, but it was interesting
to see that if you would.
But he didn't.
He would say, you know, he went into the car and he felt something on his ear and he squeezed
it and it just all this liquid came out.
It sounds kind of gross.
I said, oh, yeah, it was your right side, right?
It was your right ear.
Right.
And he's like, yeah.
I'm like, yeah.
How do you know?
Well, the right side is radiation.
Yes.
It goes up.
Right.
If it was a toxification like a salt or from animal protein, it would be the left side
and down.
So every time he mentioned he had an ailment or something, I said, oh, yeah, it felt like
this and it was on this side of the body.
He's like, yeah, exactly.
What the hell?
You know, I'm like, this is simple stuff.
This is simple.
I mean, once you start applying this, right, but you have to have more information.
If he just said, well, I squeezed my ear and all this liquid came out my earlobe, I would
and I didn't know he worked with radiation.
I wouldn't be able to determine which side it would be, you see?
Okay.
So, but let's say he ran Jojo's barbecue pit in South Carolina, right?
And he said he squeezed his earlobe and all this liquid came out.
So that was your left ear, dude.
Right?
He's like, yeah, that's my left ear.
How do you know?
Anyway, these are these things.
That's why I keep saying these things with the yin and yang over and over.
But the problem with yin and yang discussing it with the body is it's constantly flipping.
When one thing is yin, it has a yang manifestation towards it to make balance.
And then that yang manifestation then wants to go back to being yin, right?
So it's kind of one of these things that's very difficult to grasp and there's very little
into good tutorial online, but we'll get into it again.
So the left side of the body, when you have manifestations on the left side of your body,
it's the body doing one of two things.
You have too much energy going down or the body's creating a block to prevent too much
energy from going down because it'll create other harm.
Well, is it unfair to say that anything that is hard is trying to get soft and anything
that's soft is trying to get hard?
I mean, that's pretty much seeking.
It's seeking that, but it may not achieve it.
Right.
It's hinting you all the time.
OK.
Yeah.
So the body has its.
Oh, by the way, another thing, there's a therapist that I know we had a discussion with someone
else.
Yeah.
And I said, the body has a mind of its own and he's like, you're the only other person
I've heard say that this person is doing physical therapy for 40 years.
I said, well, yeah, give me an example.
The body has an innate mind of its own where, well, OK, when I say mind, it's not the brain
either for you or the body.
Right.
It's a culmination.
The whole effect of the whole thing to a medicine is the medical community, scientific community
is doing.
It's hard to efficiently explain what each thing does, but efficient explanations of each
part of the body does not mean an efficient explanation of the whole.
Right.
So basically, the mind's body, an example of it would be someone who wants to commit
suicide because their mind is so much at the end of the line.
They want to go drown themselves and they type concrete blocks or lead or whatever while
they're drowning.
The body is saying, I don't want to drown.
I don't care if you're depressed or not.
I don't want to drown.
Right.
And there's this fight.
Internally.
Right.
Let's say that's why, you know, blowing, you know, using a shotgun or something is usually,
you know, a gun is usually one of the better things.
People that hang themselves while they're hanging their bodies, I don't want to die.
I don't want to die.
Right.
I mean, there's people that do want to kill themselves so bad, they actually take a hammer
and a knife and hammer the knife into their chest and halfway before it breaches the sternum,
they call 911 ambulance for help because the body overcame is the way you do it.
This is stupid.
I don't care if you're depressed or not.
I don't care if you want to kill yourself.
I don't want to die.
Well, the inverse can work as well, even though you want to live, you want to live like a
lot of people do toward the end of the line.
Thank you for bringing that up.
Yeah.
If the body's mind decides it's time to go, it's time to go.
You just, you know, it's one of those things where it's like, I don't know, they seem great,
but something just the body just said no.
And that was it.
Well, it depends on how they seem.
Great.
We've gotten to that before, because the last thing to leave is the same great feeling.
Right.
So the young.
So.
So there's aspects to that also.
So is it simply here?
Would you do a sonic like this?
The easiest thing to do because of the audience's propensity to be in a certain culture and
the programming that we all have and had, let's say, plural past tense is that it's
all material, something you can draw on a piece of paper and something you can explain
as a basic function.
No, it's not like that, but it is generally.
But if you think that's all there is, you're going to negate the overall function of the
thing, which is a completely different thing.
So in other words, if we're let's say we're going to have an episode and discuss a specific
organ of the body, the eye.
Right.
And you have to pick.
Do you want to talk about the left eye or the right eye?
Very specific.
In ancient Egypt, there's evidence that when there was two ophthalmologists, one for the
left eye, one for the right eye.
Oh, of course, because they had a surplus of eye doctors.
Right.
No, because the left eye is connected to a certain group of organs and the right eye
is connected to a different group of organs.
You see the same with the ear.
Same with the mouth.
Upper teeth.
Copper quadrant.
Lower quadrant.
Right.
Because left or right.
Because most people's eyes act in concert with each other and they do triangulate things.
There's a calculation there where you determine depth and distance.
That is the way most people's eyes work.
If both of their eyes are indeed functional.
Except for if you're a bird.
In most birds, prey birds, the right eye is for flight, navigation, and the left eye is
for foraging, pecking, food, the young.
It's a split screen.
Yeah, well perhaps I was a bird in another life because I got to tell you, my left and
right eye don't match.
They do not match.
I can only use one at a time, in fact.
Oh, okay, yeah.
Maybe you got the bird in this lifetime.
I have an odd configuration there as part of my situation.
But no one has ever been able to solve that.
Why it is that they act independently.
Well, it may not be neat solving.
Very often problems end up being a plus, right?
In many.
I don't have to give any examples.
Most of the most creative and advanced things we have in this world, including creative
people and whatever, are people that had challenges that initially would be considered non-conformist
and need to be solved.
But they ended up, right, being.
The common stories of many of the so-called recognized geniuses being dyslexic and things
like this.
Yeah, obviously.
Right.
The thing that appears to be a hindrance can actually be turned into something that is
an inspiration or a motivation to examine things from a different point of view.
Like for instance.
Well, you have to realize that genius is a limitation, like what's the difference between
genius and stupidity?
Genius has limits.
There you go.
Right.
Okay.
So, but anyway.
Yep.
Like odd thing, right?
I got this terrible eyesight.
Sure.
But you know what?
Whenever you need to find something in the house that's lost or whatever, guess who finds
it?
Me.
Well, yeah.
You're not filtering out the rest of the things that you used to find people or other people
are relying on their eyes, which actually acts as an omission for all their other faculties.
Right.
Exactly.
So there you go.
Because I have to utilize other things, I have a different way of accounting for things.
Yeah.
Now imagine, yeah.
Because when you're taught as a child that your ears are for listening, right?
Not the bottoms of your feet, right?
Or your hands or whatever.
You will always rely on your ears.
Where someone who is sensitive enough and didn't get that instruction, if he's in a
room with people, in order to listen carefully, something in the distance, they'll put the
both palms of their hands on the wall or the floor to pick up also, right?
Besides their ears.
I'll give you a very practical application for that.
Crossing the street.
Again, I have terrible eyesight, can't see the car from a distance, this and that.
Tell you what I can do though, is feel with my feet if a car is close or not.
Sure.
Exactly.
Yeah.
So basically we've been trained, the more training you have, just like what is the definition
of a professional?
It's someone who is learning more and more about less and less.
Like I've worked with people in the engineering field and physicists, physicists, I usually
spell them F-I-Z-Z-Y-S-T-S-S-C-Y-S-T.
Not one of them, with the scalerator and the water for the past year, these are people
active in the field as physicists and engineers.
Not one of them, even frequent discussions, frequent discussions, hours long, frequently
came up with one suggestion or one recommendation of what was going on.
With all of their background, they couldn't, and all they did, kept doing was asking me
the same questions over and over and over, real dumb questions too.
Stuff that we had gone over, it's almost as if there's not even, they're not even real.
They're like some kind of manifestation.
Anyway, let's just stop on this one here and we'll do one more if there's any comments on
this one because I said we would maybe be more adherent to what we did on the container
on O and G, but I just wanted to stress again, just like the last time we spoke on the
container, I just talked about cabbage and burdock or basically thistle and the cabbage greens.
The reason I did that is very simple, is that in order to be able to diagnose and think clearly,
you must be in a good state of mind and good state of health to do so.
Remember, there's no such thing as health, it's only fitness.
When someone says, are you healthy for what?
Climbing Mount Everest, doing deep sea diving or sitting at an office?
It depends on what you're going to do.
There is no health.
General health may be idea that you're not suffering or in pain or don't look, right?
You fit within a certain parameter of look, right?
But there is no health specifically when you're operating on a higher level.
It's fitness.
What kind of fitness do you want to do what?
Well, it's preparation for what it is you're going to do.
I mean-
It's just fitness, yeah.
Are you fit for climbing Mount Everest or doing deep sea diving?
Or are you fit for sitting in an office chair?
And that's fine.
Well, are you fit to be able to just get through your day without falling asleep?
Or are you fit to be-
Yeah, there's a level of fitness, not health.
For example, if someone ever says, well, sitting in an office chair eight hours a day for 20 years,
you're going to get sick.
No, it's not true.
There are ways to balance that, right?
You have to eat food that's well cooked and blah, blah, blah.
Yeah, just like, for example, if your UPS driver is basically like jogging all day,
right?
Lifting heavy weights, you're going to be healthy.
Not true.
If you're not eating the foods to balance that, you have to eat more raw food if you're more active.
And we've gone over this in the older container stuff, right?
We've gone over many, many direct points.
So I just want to say where we are now.
It's been almost, what?
More than 10, about, I want to say 10, about nine years since that.
I think you could find it on the site, ONG on the Patreon site, access to the second,
the container, ONG, the original ONG.
Listen to that and supplement it with this one and the last one that we did recently.
Because you cannot, so that, back to what I wanted to say, the reason I talked about
cabbage and burdock, but basically thistle roots, is because in order to diagnose and
think clearly, you must be in fit to do so, right?
Just like, for example, it was very common back in the 70s that in a business meeting,
when this, how food relates to mind, certain, like an advertising agency would take a client
out and they wanted to have an upper hand, you know, for lunch or dinner.
Everyone in the advertising agency would order a vegetable dish and they made sure that
the client only ordered heavy meat dishes.
Like the clients, the opposition, let's say, or the ones they wanted to take advantage of
was eating dead animal flesh.
And those that wanted to stay on top were eating vibrant vegetables.
Think, right?
And this worked very often.
Yeah, the steak versus the salad.
The steak versus the salad.
The person who ate the salad would be a lot more awake, limber.
Alert and more prone to seem taken upper hand of the situation.
The, no matter what it was, whether it was emotional,
you know, calculative, financial, rational, whatever, creative.
So if you partake in thinking about the things about the body, let's say to help yourself
or help others, you must start getting on a clean food, veg based.
Now I've gone over in the past, if you eat McDonald's every day or fast food every day
and you get criticism that you need to eat healthy, most people think they have to go
cold turkey.
No, you just keep doing what you're doing and just start introducing the healthier food
and phase out the unhealthy food over a gradual period of time.
Usually a month is fine.
You start, you'll notice it'll be a month by the moon.
So if you start in the middle of the month where the dark moon, it'll probably, you'll
probably pass that full moon in two weeks and go to the next full moon.
So it might be more than a month.
It might be six weeks, depending on when you start.
Again, people have been listening to this Greek speak stuff over the years will understand
what I'm saying.
Maybe not, but that's why I'm bringing it up again.
The moon cycle is very, very critical to, by the way, there's a lunar, we're probably
doing another episode before the lunar eclipse that's coming.
Archaics has done some pretty good videos on that, especially the last one, which basically
reverse psyop using reverse psychology.
Also, it's going to line up a day or two or three after the Passover.
Remember the, these, they, they use the biblical days, like nine 11 happened on the day of
atonement on the 10th day of the seventh month.
The Corona virus was declared to be a national state of emergency type thing by the federal
reserve.
Do you remember it was Google and the federal reserve was a short speech about doing the
lockdowns by the bankers, right?
Who own you on the Passover in 2020 or whatever it was.
So these, these days are interesting because of the biblical alignments, by the way, you
know, not Jewish, by the way.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
You know, just a quick note too.
I saw in the chat that, uh, what was it?
A Freeman recently had a brochures on good, you know, so, uh, good.
He's got, I really, I'm thankful and grateful about the, the, uh, the, uh, chronography
chronology that he's done.
Right, right.
Because I've always, I've always been known as someone who looked at old books, but not
like that, you know, and, and putting piecing it together.
My whole thing is to do a broad, a broad sweep over this existence and dig down a little deep,
which isn't that much.
You don't have to dig deep to be advanced on any subject.
And, uh, he went really deep on the chronography and that's pretty much, and that's what he
is.