Sonic Event 80, and here we go now.
What has been on a lot of people's minds lately, according to the emails and messages and even
discussion in the chat, looks to me like there's a lot of questions about water.
And rightfully so, after all, it's the element, right?
I mean, they used to call it an element.
They used to say it was an essential to life, and certain cultures venerated water as something
to be taken more seriously than just that essential thing that you need to have a little
bit of it each and every day in order to, I don't know, thrive and do well, just like
everything else on the planet.
What do we have in common?
I mean, pretty much, if you're alive, you got water in you.
That's the way I've always looked at it.
But anyway, we're going to see how we should be looking at it with the Greek.
How are you doing tonight?
Doing all right.
You got water on the brain, right?
Water on the brain, the knee, wherever.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, all right.
Yeah, there's a little talk on every, I've stirred up the pot and what's called the
water magnetic reactor slash seminar, and we'll announce, just like people found out
through the Sonics and through the chat, Chatango, I think it's Greek-speak, right, Chatango,
and double E, double E. Absolutely.
It's available.
Look, if you're subscribed to Rated Y, you should definitely see a link somewhere.
If you don't, it's pretty easy to find.
But if not, you can always message us and I'll send you a direct link if you're having
trouble finding it.
But there are people interacting in there, and some of them have been talking about water.
Some specifics lately, but yeah, sure.
Yeah, it's a place for posting.
So what we'll do is I'm thinking whether it was, well, it's going to look into a PowerPoint,
so share screen and go through all that.
I may not do that.
I might just do something less involved, put some images and talk and then do wait a week
and then do another one because there might be questions.
So it'll be in about two weeks.
I'll post it sometime next week, the time for a week after.
So that's just generally the time.
It's been a very good response.
I've gotten at least 20 to 30 people responded already, and I'm sure you've gotten a good
fraction also.
And so, yeah, we're going to get into basically is just the state of water, water work that
I'm in right now, not from the beginning.
It won't be how to handle water, but we'll do a cursory recap of many of the things that
you heard in the water episode that you had on the members only, right?
Some requests came up for that.
So if you want to clear that up, maybe it's not on the rated Y.
Right.
It's not under the rated Y.
I still have it on my website.
If you sign up as a member on my website, it is accessible to you under the Ocelli and
the Greek tab.
If you are a subscriber to rated Y, though, and you would like it, contact me and we'll
work something out.
I'll make sure you get your hands on it, and maybe we can include it in the future somewhere
else.
But for now, that's where it resides, and I don't want to confuse people.
So get in touch with me and I'll make sure you can find it one way or another.
But that gave us a lot of basics, a lot of interesting stuff.
But one thing that wasn't covered there that has been questioned in recent emails, and
I'd like to get your take on this, is the relationship between the science, the obvious
that it is an essential of life, and all of that.
And I think, again, one of those things that's not focused on when people start talking about
their spirituality, their religion, their laws, and everything else, they ignore water in
a lot of cases, even though water is a part of, well, everything.
Even Jordan Maxwell.
I know you found some of what he had to say kind of laughable.
But I mean...
No, the other way around.
Oh, okay.
Most of it laughable, but some of it valid.
But look, him, David Icke, even Alex Jones are gateways to get people out of the collective
thinking, right?
So anything that'll get you out of it, right?
Yeah, absolutely.
Collective thinking.
But even when Jordan used to do this, and believe me, I heard it many times, he would
talk about, take a look at the relativity of how important water is.
Water is so important that most of our terminology, most of our behaviors are dictated by it and
rightfully so.
In commerce.
Yeah.
In the context of commerce.
Well, in commerce, in commerce also regarding relationships, like you get involved in a
marriage and this and that, and what do you have when children are born, they're born in
a birth canal.
Take a look at the terminology they use.
Yeah, because of the geography of the earth.
It's to travel large distances and control the land, you need sea power.
So the law of the sea, maritime law and admiralty is the same thing.
Admiralty is when the captain, so you're captain of a ship on the sea, but once the captain
embarks or disembarks and is on land, now ruling on land, he's now called, no longer
called captain, he's called governor.
So states have, right?
So you see governor and captain are the same thing.
One is an admiralty which is on land and the other is on the sea.
So yeah, the law of the sea.
That's what George Maxwell's crux of the matter was.
And he would show you, look, when you talk about cash, it's liquid, right?
You have liquid cash, you're working with banks which are the same thing that govern
rivers and how things flow and, oh wait, cash flow.
You know what I'm saying?
Like the words for water go along with it.
Yeah, freezing assets.
Freezing assets all throughout it, right?
The terminology used, it's almost like water and money are the same thing.
Energetically, to some degree, they should be when they're properly utilized in a way,
right?
Because, yeah, go ahead.
Yeah, but let's get into the spiritual aspect of it because I've been trying to, I haven't
really hammered a very simple methodology.
Like example, if on the past couple of Sonics, maybe the last, before the last, I mentioned
looking up the John Mace, like Mace spray, you know, the pepper spray, Mace, M-A-C-E.
There's a psychological technique where he explains that the mind only sees images, stores
images, not events and other things.
And those images have a powerful emotional connection.
So the way you mitigate any psychological condition is by basically recalling that image without
having, or bringing up the event that connecting it, finding the connecting image, eliminating
the image, right?
That's like an in-your-face hardball way of, you know, doing psychology.
So let's do a more hardball way of the spirituality, right?
I think people like that.
It'll explain a lot of the things and why I say the things that I do and how I say the
things that I do.
But before we get into that, I got some update messages.
We did one on someone who had a sore on their leg, a relative of someone who had the sore,
a relative who had a sore in their leg.
And I went through a whole thing about the energies and what they could do.
And I got a little bit of an update.
They pretty much are doing better, like not wrapping it, you know, the not wrapping it
has helped because I think I went over the differences.
Right. When you when you have a sore that is, let's say, quote unquote, oozing or
secreting, you don't want to wrap it tight because that's contrary to the purpose.
If you have an injury that breaks the skin, you want to wrap it tight because not doing
so is contrary to the purpose.
Meaning if you have a laceration or a cut or an injury, you want to immediately make it
tight because that's how it was before it was injured.
Right. But if the body organically or naturally goes to an area and opens up on its
own to release something, you don't want to wrap that tight.
You want to encourage it. And one way of encouraging something like that is with a
ginger compress, grate some ginger or slices of ginger in in very hot water for 20
minutes or bring it to a slight simmer as soon as it's not even a simmer.
When it approaches the summer, turn it off because the heat will really degrade it.
And just wrap, just put a washcloth in there, wring it out, put it over the area for 20
minutes, repeat every when it starts to cool down, dip it again, wring it out, put it
on. Right.
What I do, I've evolved the ginger compress for a sore or something that needs to break
through the skin. By the way, a ginger compress could make things worse if they're not
intended to come through the skin.
Right. Like a breast tumor.
The worst thing you could do is a ginger compress if you're trying to go after it
with a diet first, because a ginger compress will bring it to the surface and it gets
very messy. I think I went over that a few sonics ago also.
Right. And so you got to look, the first step here is to evaluate.
Hold on. Yeah. Hold on, Chuck.
Just hold on. I just want to finish this thought.
What the way that I have evolved the compress, the ginger compress, chamomile
compress is something for calming.
There's a whole bunch of stuff you can do.
What I do normally, imagine a bowl of hot liquid or a pot of hot liquid.
You are very Japanese fashion because Japanese like to their apprentices to
experience pain. So they make them dip their hands in hot water to wring a towel out.
Right. Hotter than normal.
Instead of being like that and wringing it out, what I do or have been doing.
I haven't done it recently, but this is the technique that I recommend if you want to
frequent, this is get a Ziploc bag, the heavy duty one.
The Ziploc is a brand name, by the way, like Q-tip.
Right. So, you know, one of these sealed heavier bags.
The reason I say Ziploc is because it's at least two mil, not the cheap one.
You're the heavier duty one and you just poke a bunch of holes in it.
So how do you poke a bunch of holes in it?
You know, however, but you could use the end of a blade, but put a piece of
cardboard in there before you punch the hole.
So you only punch the holes on one side of the bag, not all the way through.
OK. And what you do then is you fold it out or lay out your terry cloth towel or
fabric in the Ziploc bag or some of the liquid in there and then let some of it
come out. So now you have the bag retaining.
Most of the liquid and through the holes in the bag, you know, perforations, the
liquid, you know, and it's kind of held together, right.
It also keeps the temperature together.
Right. You know, imagine a hot walking down the street on a cold day with a hot
coffee in your hand, get to your destination.
It's not so hot. But if you have it in a little brown paper bag and you walk to your
destination, it's up, it's much warmer than it would have been without it.
Right. Just an insulator.
Right. So I just wanted to bring these little tips up.
But basically the the they're doing like cranberry juice, basically when I suggested
doing something that would be very similar for gout treatment, because this is the
lower half of the body.
And the other thing now, since it is working is it is improving.
It's been a few weeks to drink the teas.
Now it's time to reinforce.
And this is a direct statement to the person.
Now it's time to reinforce those energies down there, because if the sore is
improving. Now it's time to start recovering the structure on the lower half of the
body. So the thing that I would remember, this was most likely brought on by an
onslaught of eating too much animal meat and the kind that is not of good quality.
But excuse me. So now it's time to reinforce that lower.
And that's and I'm going to say something.
And I mentioned a vegetable that I've been probably the only one on the Internet
pushing it this way. Yes, I am pushing it.
It's called burdock root.
You're going to have to get a hold of some burdock root and start making burdock tea.
Yep. Either fresh or dried.
Fresh is always better.
And start eating burdock if you know how to prepare it, which I doubt where it's
delicious. By the way, I was mentioning earlier, you know, most people say they
like to cook. When I came here in Tucson, you know, it's a different culture than
New York. And I wanted to meet people that like to cook.
And I kept meeting people.
I said, you like to go? Yeah, I do.
Come over. So I'm watching them and I'm like, this person doesn't really know how
to cook. What they're actually doing is reheating stuff, frozen foods and things
that are prepared and canned is not cooking right.
If you fry a pork chop and open a can of string beans and a packet of gravy with
water and butter, that's not cooking.
That's basically reheating.
Right. Right.
You're not really cooking.
So most people, when they say they like to cook, if you that I observed actually just
heating food up, they're not cooking right.
They're not on the level that they understand what can be done.
Right. So when I say making delicious food, I'm not talking about reheating things.
So so anyway, what I would recommend here in this case, because I brought it up
extensively on one of the previous Sonic, maybe three or four Sonics ago or more.
Now it's time to rebuild the lower part of the body.
If you can't get a hold of the burdock, which you're going to have to inevitably
will and I will mention this person did send me the relative bag of dried burdock,
which I appreciate.
I still have it because I have access to the fresh and I'm kind of like reverse
envy. I almost want to say, get one here and use it.
But if you can't get the fresh burdock now, if you can't get burdock at all, don't
have it. Any root vegetable.
Right. Because the root anything below ground, but not as much more of a parsnip
variety than a carrot. Carrot might be too sweet.
But yes, go for root vegetables.
Tubers are not root vegetables.
Peanuts, potatoes, sweet potatoes are not what I'm talking about.
They have to be a vegetable that grows vertically, not outwardly.
Straight down into the ground.
So that's that's I just want to do a public announcement on this.
This was a very appreciative email.
I like it when people keep up with me on things.
And I just want to bring this up as more of a of a collective, let's say, info put
out there. Right. So just to recap, it was a sore leg and basically applied some
Greek speak. It didn't work because they made it tight where it should be loose.
It's a sore. Right. So and then we went over the animal being the cause.
And then for easy Western application, get some cranberry juice.
Right. Treat it like you have gout.
You know, echinacea, golden seal tea is one of the since the 80s.
It's been one of the most popular health food sort of teas.
You'll find it anywhere. Right.
You know, Kroger fries, Ralph's, whatever.
They'll carry these brands of teas.
You'll see an echinacea golden to that's antiseptic.
So I just wanted to recap on that.
Now it's time to rebuild the lower energies.
Now, one thing I don't want people to misinterpret because it's always this way
or that way, black or white, not anti animal meat at all.
With the animal meat, it's more of the quality of the animal meat going down and
down and also frequency that Westerners, most people, let's say in America, eat,
eat it. And after a while, the bodies will not take it anymore and manifest in
different ways, usually on the lower half of the body.
That's why, you know, you hear people, especially Westerners, whether they have
colon problems, prostate problems, right.
Gout, things like that.
So anyway, that's that was it on that.
Let's go back to what we were before about the spirituality in the water.
You were going to lead on to something.
And I said, hold on. So.
Yeah, well, the one thing was just really quickly that evaluation is really
important when you're figuring out whether to wrap something tightly or to figure
out, you know, whether it's the body trying to get rid of something or the body
needs to be pulled back together again.
So you have to evaluate this properly to begin with.
I think it's worth a minute or two to just explain that.
You know, how are you to tell the difference between these things?
Well, well, well, hold on.
It's always restoring, right?
It's restoration. It's restoration.
Exactly. But yeah.
Yeah. So if you were fine and now you're not because of the trauma, you should wrap
it tight. But if your body is ready to burst open part of it and release something, you
want to encourage that. Right.
Right. You don't want to. Right.
So that's why I've always said when you have an injury, a cut or a bruise, wrap it
tight. But I didn't include, well, if you have a sore, don't.
Right. But this is a case where it came up and very blatantly that they were doing
what shouldn't have been done.
And I and I need to make more of a point of it.
See, these subjects are very broad.
Right. Right.
Well, here's the question I have, actually, is is there a difference in your mind?
Because I know I handle it slightly differently if I find that it has taken root.
It's trying to get rid. Let's just say you have an injury that's trying to get rid of
something and the root of it is more in the muscle and it's trying to get through the
skin. Now, it has gotten through the skin, but the problem is not in the skin.
It's lower down in the muscle or something.
Right. Yeah. I would get do that with diet.
In other words, then you get rid of it the same way it got there, which is internal.
Right. And it's what's called internal medicine, not surgery.
Surgery. Right. Is obtrusive.
You know, it's intrusive, intrusive, not intrusive if it's not intrusive, if it's on
the surface and breaking out, that's lymphatics, by the way, not blood.
And it will it will be very quick to recover if it's assisted, assisted with, you know,
warm. Right. But if you're so restless, but if you're sure is more or less rooted in
the skin, it's a little different.
I mean, indeed, diet can improve what is causing that problem because the problem could
be caused and stay.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
They may not improve it. It might make it worse in many cases, even when you're eating
better. Right.
Because the body's adjusting.
This goes back to where people want to eat better.
They stop everything that they're doing and introduce something new.
Not at all. You always just start introducing the new thing.
And then phase out what you normally did.
Right. Because the body set up, the body will adapt.
Right. It's the real, you know, the real most intelligent thing, believe it or not, is
the person when you see people, you know, for many years, some people are not
intelligent. As a matter of fact, it's quite the opposite of intelligence.
Their bodies are more intelligent than they are.
Right. In other words, the consciousness that the body has, the way it keeps is far more
intelligent than most people's open consciousness is.
Right. Or awake, you know, what they exhibit when they open their mouth, let's say.
Right. So like you were saying a while back, and I don't remember which sonic it was,
doesn't matter. But the thing is that, you know, when you were talking about somebody
who's, say, eating fast food every single day.
OK, so now they've developed a skin problem.
What you want to do is not immediately cut off all the fast food, but turn around and
introduce the newer, better food into your diet.
And then vary the quantities.
Yeah. So so the first day, first week, it's 20 percent good food, 80 percent.
And then the next week is 50, 50.
And in one month you're eating 10 percent junk food, 90 percent good food.
Right. So it's going to take that long.
Usually most severe elements, you know, things that could kill you take over to six
between six months and two years to recover.
Here's another example. Women with breast cancer, by the way, most breast cancer is
misdiagnosed. You don't have breast cancer.
I've seen reports where they said they found two cells.
You know, microcells.
And that person went for full treatment.
They didn't have cancer at all.
But because, you know, anyway, so I said, I bet they had a good insurance.
But, oh, they had the best insurance policy.
They work for the state. I was like, that's why they're doing it.
So you have to be savvy.
But for example, there's a lot of mastectomies.
The breasts are removed, you know, because of whatever the person usually doesn't
survive. If you're going to have a suggestion of removing a body part because of
cancer, you should and must heal it before the part is removed.
Then you might say, Greek, why remove it?
Right. Well, yeah.
So women that have a hard time or anybody, a hard time with an organ, you should
fix it with diet and other things before you remove it, because removing that organ
apart of the body does not fix the problem at all.
And then the person usually passes away very shortly after that, shortly meaning six
months to two years. So these severe things that people have, especially if you're
older than 30, I've seen them seen in people, you know, much younger as as time
goes on. You should always heal it, have it healed.
And, you know, before any surgery, you know, it's almost like I'm not saying I'm
against the surgeries and all that.
But if you don't heal an infection or a cancerous part of the body before surgery,
it doesn't. Yeah, it doesn't mean that the actual tissue has been removed, but the
condition is still present.
So anyway, yeah, this is a very, very big topic.
And the background, I've never really sat down, you know, or done a sonic extreme.
What we did with O and G, the container, the second episode we did the vintage, you
know, O and G, right, was about the body.
That was still very general, but basically laying out what a well-functioning body
is, a medium, you know, when a body starts to break down and then poorly, very broken
down. And then you have the other side, which is the trauma side.
You know what? Different injuries all the way to toxins, you know, getting bit by a
snake or a spider or something, which is basically drinking some of your own urine.
You have 30 seconds to do it.
Yeah, that's a big open subject.
And I think I've been giving smatterings over the years on it, which have helped quite
a few people. But, you know, there's never look, there's never if you did a school
set up on this, you'll get in trouble if you don't, you know, if you make it public.
So maybe something like that might be important, a short encyclopedia, which, by the
way, I recently posted an encyclopedia, a universal encyclopedia that has everything in
there from chemical formulas to how to build a bridge, 1,800 pages long, it's in the
chat. Let's go back to the water and spirituality.
And I mentioned doing a strong, let's say, forward presentation and really short, you
know, why I say and how I say the things that I do, what why maybe distill it down.
Well, right. And people have asked recently, like I said, you know, what about the, you
know, the connective tissue here?
How does this all line up?
The idea that it is too specific.
Those those specific questions really answer themselves once you get a working
understanding, a working understanding of the broad overview, just like with the water
device. Vandy was in there in the chat.
He showed a water scaler that he built.
And if he didn't build that, he wouldn't have a working understanding right now that he
that he has built it and showed images of it, a double one, as a matter of fact, water
device. He has much more of a working understanding of things that I've never
mentioned. And when I do mention them, it'll really be much more effective.
Right. So a working understanding is the most important thing.
So but getting the reference and base basis for it.
But but let's go back to what what maybe this this sonic is about or the spiritual
connection. And remember, spirit is nonphysical.
Right. So everything is anything that is thought or precedes physical manifestation,
meaning speech is physical, is spiritual.
So let's just say this is, you know, very often you're like, I do lawfully, you know, I
eat lawful food, clean food.
Right. You know what? The way the Old Testament prescribes.
Right. This, that and the other.
Because I chose that as a law form.
And it is sensible, by the way.
It's very sensible. Right.
Many, for example, when most people you bring up, you don't dig on swine.
Most people think it's because of sanitary reasons.
And it's no, it's not because of sanitary reasons.
It's because it doesn't it doesn't requirement of having four legs, a cloven hoof and
chewing the cud. Right.
So. Right. So because it has cloven hoof, but it doesn't.
So now if the pigs chewed the cud, it would be fine.
And pigs, by the way, are not dirty animals only when they're in captivity, because in
nature, just, you know, if sharks or tuna stop swimming, they die.
If pigs, pigs have to constantly be moving around.
The reason they sit in a stye is because they're depressed.
The pig is a type of animal that is constantly on the move, constantly.
Now you put it in a stye or pen.
It's totally against its right.
So. OK, well, that's why comparatively speaking, if you were to absolutely insist on
eating pigs, you're better off with the wild pig because it's a much healthier or give
them more room so they don't know how to complain properly.
Yes. But there are wild pigs out there.
Yeah. Well, that's in most countries.
Well, now it's hard to say, but they were always they would be in the Bible.
There's a herd of a thousand pigs roaming around.
Right. Let's say the biblical story right where the spirits were put into the pigs.
There were thousands of pigs around roaming around.
So, yeah. OK, so I just gave that as a stark example.
But if you just focus, if the person just focuses on the cleanliness, that's why.
And there's no reference. Somebody not to mention names, Douglas Dietrich or whatever, say
the reason they it's OK to eat pork now and because we have refrigeration doesn't get it.
Right. There's many people that give these analogies.
Oh, they didn't have refrigeration.
Right. Has nothing to do with that.
But let's just keep that stupid analogy.
It's a dirty animal.
Yes, it has trichinosis worms and all that more than other animals and whatever.
But sort of rabbits, by the way.
But anyway, if you keep that stupid analogy, the lack of refrigeration is why they had
these laws or whatever like that.
That still works.
Because if you look at pork, it will be more tendency to be parasitic, laden with
parasites and decay more than others.
So even the stupid analogies, which are not the reason to use the prescribed laws in
the Bible, still work, right?
Still work. Even with the person who doesn't understand.
Right. The same with fish.
If it comes out of the water, doesn't matter.
Freshwater or saltwater should have fins and scales.
So clams are out.
Lobsters are out. Right.
Shrimp are out. Now, something like catfish, it's got fins, but it doesn't have scales.
Shark has fins.
It doesn't have scales.
Eel. Right. Now, they'll make up another reason for that.
The dummies. Oh, that's because of whatever.
Parasites again or other things like that.
No, no, it's a it's complete.
It's more on a spiritual plane.
But even their stupid analogies work.
And that's what I want to bring up.
The stupid analogies of separating the spirit from the material completely is a
stupid analogy, but it still works to separate it.
OK, so I've said this before.
If it's not physical, it's purely spiritual.
But the spiritual part proceeds.
Your thoughts should precede your actions.
Right. If you act without thinking, you've heard of that criticism.
OK, so the bold part and the part that I don't say wrapped up is this, that both
sides work. In other words, you know, when people say I have a criticism and they'll
say, well, does that make them bad?
I say it doesn't make them bad, but it definitely doesn't make them good either.
Right. So like are Catholics bad?
No. But are they good?
No, definitely not good.
So what's going on here?
You see that black and white one or the other doesn't work that way.
So, again, from the spiritual side, to say there is a spiritual and a physical and
what's the spiritual is, again, it's not a good analogy because it doesn't work that
way. But it works overall, just like, you know, right, like I just gave the examples
with the food. So what I'm trying to say here is very simple, is when you let's say
you have no knowledge of anything other than what the collective brings forward to
you. That's it.
You're born in the hospital or home or whatever, and everything around you will be
about materialism.
Right. Do you have enough food to eat?
Do you have a roof over your head?
Right. You know, even the religions that they give you that you subscribe to are
basically materialistic.
Like if you do this, you go to a white cloud.
If you or if you do that, you go to a fire underground.
Right. You see materialistic again.
Right. It's material.
Believing that you're going to go to heaven if you're good or hell if you're bad is
purely materialistic.
Right. So everything you're being paid for your actions, you know, I mean, here it is.
How much and what am I getting out of this is what it is.
And that's not materialistic.
Again, it's materialistic.
Yeah. As opposed to compensation.
Yeah. It's karma.
Karma is materialistic also.
Right. Right.
All these things are material.
So in other words, if you stick to the ideas of the collective, they're stupid
analogs, but they still work.
They're trying to create a spiritual analog without telling you everything is
spiritual. So what is the base?
What one other thing I've been saying for years and years, food, clothing, shelter,
food, clothing, shelter, food, clothing, shelter.
Oh, what about spirituality?
My answer to that food, clothing, shelter, Greek.
What about what do we do for our spiritual self and food, clothing, shelter?
You don't separate, you incorporate it all.
So when you're going for food, you choose the food based on your spiritual
knowledge and guidance of it.
Right. Right. That's why, you know, if you want to go scientific with those stupid
analogs that they give, you know what?
If I say science is a religion 20 years ago, people wouldn't believe it.
But now more people are believing it.
That's a religion. There's no they don't give evidence for anything at all.
Of course. And that's the thing.
You got to have faith in this and they change things based on, you know, well, we
did this or that, but we've just decided this is now different.
You know what I mean? Right.
So so let's let's continue.
When you make a choice of food, there is that is a spiritual choice, because when
you're thinking about food, is that physical or spiritual?
It's spiritual. It's thought.
Well, of course, you're choosing what you're putting.
OK, let's go back to one of those basic stupid things.
Right. They always say the body is a temple.
That's one of those basic right.
Just what do they call those platitudes that that people lay out there and say the
body is a temple. OK, so if the body is a temple, it doesn't say that directly.
But yeah, I know. But I'm I'm going with the stupid platitude.
Right. So if the body is a temple, then what you put in a temple is very important.
What you put on a temple is very important.
How you treat the temple is very important.
Right. So spiritually, even with their stupid idea, it still makes sense.
What you put in there, what you put on it, these things count significantly.
Right. Well, they're presuming that you'll be able to make a better choice.
They're presuming that. Right.
And you're free to do so.
Right. So give me an example.
Like if you go to the Asian market, when I go to the Asian market here, Grand Stone
Market or Lili Market, it's real hardcore Asian stuff.
I mean, it looks like you ever see the vegetables they show on Star Trek.
Oh, yeah. Right.
And that's what I don't recognize a lot of stuff because most people wouldn't
recognize. So they know me there and Asians at the cashier.
And I play I do my basic conversational Chinese.
I basically say, how many white people buy vegetables like this?
How many white people have you seen buy a vegetable?
They're there. Laugh their ass off.
None. None.
Because you see the only one what looks like a purple potato, you know, and white
person. Don't don't knock that because there are purple potatoes.
No, I know that. That's why I'm bringing it up like a purple potato, though.
Average white guy, you know, and I don't necessarily mean white skin.
You know what I'm saying? Looks at that and goes, well, that's not supposed to be
purple. I'm not eating it because they have the idea of potatoes brown
or maybe it's this other color and you break it open.
It's orange because it's a sweet potato.
That's it. Yeah.
Where do potatoes come from?
McDonald's. Right.
Yeah. So. Right.
So there's not that bad.
Not that bad. But yeah.
But we laugh because it's like, you know, I'll be I'll be there with Lotus Root
and other things, you know, you know.
So anyway.
And what I mean by this.
OK, let's go back to the core point.
What how you think about things is your spiritual aspect of the thing and you
whatever level you're at.
And it's OK. Let's let's go back again.
Let's segue and come back.
What you read of the gods of the Bible and the gods in all of the religions are
just humans with advanced technology.
Am I denigrating them by saying that?
No, because that's actually the truth.
It's not a denigration.
I'm saying it respectfully.
All of them.
We have no connection to what's called the creator of the universe and all that.
That is beyond anything that's ever been discussed here or even thought of.
So even Yahweh or all of the various other pantheons, Zeus, you want to go to.
Those are all people.
They're people. As a matter of fact, Exodus 15.
Yahweh is a man.
OK, so ish.
And I was speaking with someone who's a Hebrew Israeli and brought that brought
that up and he's reading and he says, oh, my gosh, it does say she's an ish.
Yeah. So I was like, oh, my gosh.
You know, but then it's like right away.
Two minutes, 35 seconds later.
No, he's not. Right.
Because your mind can't handle that.
Well, I've always found the contradiction really strange, where it's like, look,
you're created in God's image, but don't you dare compare yourself to God?
It's like, well, that's fine if you're that's fine.
Your parents, this is parentage created in God's image as parentage.
It's a totally different thing because you belong to the earth.
Yeah, of course. But here's the thing.
But that doesn't mean that, you know, it's like a complete horror to compare
yourself to your parents, does it or what?
Well, no, no, no. But here's the thing.
If you're here in a physical state, you belong to this ecosystem.
Literally, you belong to it.
You are part of this. It's not you.
You are just happen to be in the secret, just as if you transferred
your mind into a machine, a computer.
Now you belong to that computer.
That's where you are. Yeah. OK.
It's the same thing. So you belong to the earth.
Yeah. Right. That's why when you die, the body stays here. Right.
And vice versa. The body is grown here.
Right. So we've gone on the into the body being an upside down plant.
OK, so everything spiritual that you can attribute to water.
Let's just indirectly tie this back to the question.
Sure. Is everything spiritual that you can attribute to water?
So someone who doesn't understand, let's say not the stuff that I'm talking about,
but because let's just say it this way,
quantitatively and qualitatively, the recommendations that I've made about
how to treat water and handle water is pretty good.
Anybody who's done that will.
Everyone has always said, yes, it improves the water quality. Right.
Yeah. Not because I'm saying it.
It's just I'm the only one that could distill it down to a simple
step by step that you can easy to remember and apply working knowledge again.
No, I'll tell you the truth.
There are people that, you know, when when I put up that
that that one sonic that we did a long time ago
and you gave some basic recommendations in it,
there were people that, you know, really were not big fans of yours, let's say,
who said, you know what, I tried this.
And regardless of what I think of him, it's not about him.
The information is solid.
This works. This actually makes sense.
It made it better.
You know, the different things about what type of light to expose it to,
what kind of container to put it in.
This was all in that.
So, you know, or just the basic treatment with the Brita and the magnet
and the zeolite things you can get easy to get some very high water quality
very quickly for.
I mean, if you go to Walmart and get one of those picture filters for ten bucks
and then go to the next aisle at the aquarium and get this, they call ammo
chips, it's carbon and zeolite for less than 10 bucks or 20 bucks.
You could produce out of your tap water in two days.
That'll taste just as good, if not better than Fiji or any bottles of water
that you can imagine you've ever had anyway.
So, yeah. Anyway, so that works.
So that is a spiritual treatment of the subject right there.
In other words, if you look at let's just segregate this again, break off,
piece off and segue it back into again.
We've talked about the Vita, the Vita showing up, the Kari Krishna, Krishna
boys and girls showing up at the Thompson Square Park, handing out food.
When I first had that in the 80s, it was the most delicious food I've ever had.
And he explained to me it was seasoned in a way that if you put this plate of food
down here at the beach, the turtles, the seagulls and the crabs won't eat it.
It's only seasoned so a human can eat it.
So it's cut. So it keeps your spirituality on a human plane.
Because if you're eating a food that if you put your plate on the floor and an animal or
an insect comes and can also eat it, you're on that same plane is the philosophy.
Right. You're sharing the same thing.
OK, so this is another segue of how that's spiritual, but it's also physical.
Right. So the water treatment, someone who doesn't know how to treat.
In other words, you see water being delivered to a 7-Eleven.
They're stacked up, wrapped in that tight plastic on a dolly, and they leave it outside
and bring it inside and sitting out there in the sun.
Room temperature and a clear plastic bottle.
That's just totally fine for most people.
Right. That's their level.
That is a spiritual level.
That is all spiritual, all mental.
Right. So anything mental.
So how do we treat?
So if you start incorporating higher, higher level practices, food, clothing, shelter,
and those higher level practices, if they get to a certain point now, they say, oh,
that's very spiritual.
If you notice, some orthodox religions have stringent practices.
Right. And I would say, let's go back to the Krishna showing up at Thompson Square
Park and the school bus handing out food.
That was the most delicious food I ever had back in the early 80s.
And then explaining to me, it's seasoned in a way.
Right. There's no onion.
There's no animal.
Right. At all.
That it keeps you on a human plane because other animals won't eat it.
That's a science.
That is actually a science.
What he explained to me.
Yeah. Right.
Yeah. It's very strict, stringent.
And it's high level.
Right. But most people say, oh, that's his religion that does.
Well, what's you see where I'm going with this?
Well, yeah.
So when you start going to higher levels of thinking, they all overlap.
You know, it's like those those books that they showed us as kids.
I don't think they make them anymore.
The transparencies that lay over one another to form a, you know, it'll form the whole picture.
But you can peel away the different layers and you can look at a singular layer
and it still comes together to make a coherent picture.
Right. So the higher spiritual practice, which turns into a common practice
that has a practical purpose just for survival on a daily basis.
Yes, indeed. They are all interconnected.
So guess what?
Your science, your practicality, as far as your day to day living
and your spirituality do all come together.
They are all one in the same.
Well, substitute the word spirituality with your thinking.
Yeah.
Your thinking is your spirituality.
Well, so when people talk about what's the connection of spirit and water?
Well, just separate. Don't use the word spirit. Use the word thought.
OK.
Right. So what do you think about water is what it is now?
Vida Austin, Vida Austin, V-E-D-I Austin, like the city in Texas, A-U-S-T-I-N.
Yes.
She's a New Zealander, a Kiwi, that talks about hydroglyphs,
where a little petri dish, I've done it, it works,
little petri dishes with about an eighth inch of water.
Put the petri dish on a photograph, put it in the freezer till it frosts up,
take it out, it resembles a photograph.
And it resembles your thought, or you can ask questions,
you know, and it'll answer it in the hydroglyph, she calls it.
So that is a spiritual, it's scientific because it's repeatable.
It's all thought.
In other words, the water records and imparts,
well, you can impart your thoughts to the water and the water reacts.
Right.
Right. So the spiritual side, again, I don't know how else to put it.
You know, I wouldn't, but here's the thing.
You have a qualitative thing.
Let's say you go to a strip mall or a food court, food court.
OK.
And you're hungry.
You know, food courts, they have like a McDonald's next to a Chinese place,
next to a Japanese place, maybe in Middle Eastern place, right?
Maybe there's another place.
Yeah. Some of them might be mom and pop operations.
Others are big chains.
You have choices right there.
Right.
You know, it's so funny.
I go to a food court sometimes and there's like a local mom and pop,
Middle Eastern place, falafel place.
And then but the line at the McDonald's is longer.
Yeah.
Oh, my gosh.
Why didn't you take advantage of the right?
The mom and pop falafel joint?
Why? You know, you see, that's a spiritual problem.
You know, McDonald's is supposed to be a last resort, not a first choice.
So these people are making their first choice.
Are they are they bad for doing that?
No. But are they good?
Definitely not.
And they've certainly made a choice.
And now you can see why this is all.
It's spiritual.
There's nothing to do.
Right.
Because the quality.
Because remember when they they were somewhere else before they got online at McDonald's.
Right.
Yeah.
They're anywhere else.
Right.
This is not a joke or pun like I've done before.
But they're somewhere else.
But so what do you think they just got online on McDonald's because they kind of slept walk?
Maybe they are sleepwalking.
But you know what I mean?
No, they made a conscious decision.
That's a spiritual action to wait online.
Any conscious decision is indeed an act that could be called spiritual.
Right.