And Sonic Event 176, here we are, and
we're actually live on a screen tonight, trying
this out on Saturdays, looks like.
Greg, you wanted to do this, right?
Yeah, let's see if we can get some
interaction.
That looks like there's about nine people or
so, or eight people.
Yeah.
Me on there, now there's seven or whatever
bouncing around, so I don't know if they
can hear us.
If you guys out there can hear us,
type something in the chat, right?
Yeah, please do.
You can type in there as anonymous, or
you can use the name on the chatango,
if you like, either way.
Yeah.
I think there's a delay, right?
About 30 seconds or less?
Yeah, it could be.
It could be about 30 seconds, depending on
compression.
It's a little irregular.
I use a slightly cheaper streamer, so it's
a little irregular, but it works, you know?
Yeah.
Anyway, so, should we start with the yin
and yang right now?
Because I think that's a good one, and
we've been getting feedback about that.
Yeah, it's important, that's how you use to
discern what's going on around you, whether it's
physical or non-physical.
Right.
And it never lets you down if you
do it right.
Here, I'll start with it, okay, yin and
yang, the concept of yin and yang is
yang.
So, when you're approaching something to see if
this is yin or yang, or using universal
principles, it's a yang principle, because it's focused,
right?
So, if you're looking at something to determine
whether this is yin or yang, meaning expansive,
cooling, soft, or is it contractive, warm, and
hard, right?
Those are the two contrasts.
When you approach something to try to diagnose
that, to see what it is, because you
know the opposites will be involved, and a
balance is trying to be found, that is
actually a yang approach, and a yang condition,
let's say.
And because of that, now that's funny, because
we're trying to objectify yin and yang, right?
See how difficult it is to objectify?
Well, yeah, and some things, you know...
You'll say, well, what is it?
And because you're still searching, that's the yin
part of it, because you don't have the
answer yet.
So, the question, questions are always yin, and
answers are always yang.
What if you ask a very specific question,
that's more of a yang question, but it's
still in the yin category.
So, a very narrow answer.
Specific.
Specific, okay.
Well, let's say you ask a specific question,
and all questions are yin, but if you
make it really specific and poignant, that's more
yang.
And if you get an answer that is
kind of general, that's a yin answer, even
though answers are yang.
So, there's a category within each...
Pixels are very much like this.
Gray matter, if you look real close, a
gray pixel, a gray tone will look like
black and white, varying amounts of pixels, right?
That's why the yin and yang symbol has
that, right?
Black and white.
But it's not really black and white.
It just shows you how it's broken up.
So, I've always, like I was in a
four-hour conference call with engineers and investors
and all that today, right?
And now, you don't want to be in
a four-hour conference call with me about
water and how things work, right?
No, you don't want to be in a
call like that, because...
Anyway, actually, you might want to, you might
want to, but it all ended up okay.
It was fine, but I was being very
yang as I, you know, giving, you know,
and they were very yin, and I expected
them to be yin and not get any
pushback.
And if I did get any pushback, it
was a very yin push.
They couldn't be specific because the specifics I
give are undeniable.
You see how it works?
Yeah, okay.
So, it's back and forth.
So, you can actually use the yin and
yang when you interact with people over a
meeting, you know, over...
It was a conference call over the phone,
partly other parts of the world, and yeah.
And I know how it's going to go
because I, you know, I see the question
is yin, you know, and it was very,
very yin questions, you know, right?
The questions were very unspecific.
So the only...
I said, let me fire back with a
very hard specific, right?
The opposite and see what happens, and it,
yeah, pretty interesting.
So, you know, you could say four or
five people got educated today, and the whole
time I'm analyzing what, you know, what's going
on back and forth, and it stayed in
harmony for four hours.
It was supposed to be a half-hour
call.
That happens to me all the time.
But you have to be conscious of what's
going on, and you have to control.
How many times have you heard me said,
if you go into a situation with other
people and you don't take control, that situation
right there is out of control.
Because, right?
I'm not saying some people could interpret that
as like you're a control freak, dude, right?
No, not at all.
You're just making the best of what's going
on is the point, right?
Okay.
Well, what happens when it does get chaotic,
though, and people are speaking at a turn?
I mean, would you consider that as a
situation like that, either yin or yang?
It depends if it's specific chaos or just
general chaos.
General chaos would be a public show or
a wrestling match or a concert, and someone
throws a chair.
And then suddenly, within 10 seconds, there's another
brawl here.
It's very unspecific, right?
A specific chaos would be someone says something,
and the whole crowd answers against them specifically,
right?
So there's different ways to look at it,
yeah.
So general, okay, here's it.
When you have that general, someone throws a
chair, and then before you know it, the
entire audience is in brawls, right?
The only thing you could do there is
let it peter out on its own, right?
Because it's too unspecific.
Or you come in very specifically with just
one thing, tear gas, one thing, a loud
horn, right?
Something very separate, you know, the boys in
blue or something.
You have to be very, there's no multiple
ways.
When you have general chaos, you have to
come in with one hard insertion.
Sort of like, I hate to do this
because it's like, you know, school teachers, right?
They come into a room and there's a
lot of conversations going on.
There's noise, et cetera.
In my school, a lot of them used
to take a book and slam it on
the desk and create.
That's right.
You have to, we normally do these principles
anyway.
We don't think of them as such, but
think of the advantage you have is if
you start breaking things down, universal principle, you
get to it much faster, much quicker.
Now, things that people usually do is because
they've heard about it or they did it
repetitively and it worked, but they didn't never
approached these things with a methodology on universal
principle.
You see?
So you have a major advantage that way.
Right?
Right.
Okay.
That makes sense.
That makes a lot of sense.
Now, the one of the yin and yang
questions that came in, actually, I found it,
I didn't have it when we first went
live here, but, um, is, uh, you have
various states that water can end up in,
uh, and obviously a young state for water
would be ice, uh, but a yin state
would be steam.
Now, if water is simply at room temperature,
hold on ice, when it goes young hard,
it also exhibits yin, which is expansion and,
and water vapor, regardless of temperature is young
because it's small.
Like the most young element is hydrogen, not
has nothing to do with H2O.
By the way, I recently posted, oh yeah,
that was water is water is not H2O
and the AI agreed pretty much.
Yeah.
And when I had been saying that I'm
the only person that I've ever heard say
that and for 20 years now, but at
least the, you know, AI knows.
Yeah.
Uh, yeah.
How did you discover that?
How did you actually discover that though?
Because you know, to me by reading, just
by reading their stuff, yeah.
The initial, I discovered, well, how do they
figure out water is H2O?
And I read the original experiment 300 years
ago, it has to do with metal plates
and ionization and breaking it into a gas.
And in three days they decided because it
separates into hydrogen and oxygen gas, water is
made up of those two gases, rubbish because
you can't take any given volume of water
and reduce it completely to hydrogen and oxygen
just can't do it.
So also for people that are listening live,
I can see you in the chat room
and all that by all means.
Uh, if you have a question or a
comment, yeah, absolutely.
Feel free to type it in.
Uh, you know, I, I see, uh, have
you noticed a TX, a two nine, you
know, and a Vandy Vandy man's land.
Okay.
Uh, I see those names specifically and a
few ainons, but ainons can type in the
chat room as well.
It doesn't wait.
I was just, you know what?
I might have to change a setting.
I might've actually shut off the ainons.
Let me fix that.
Uh, I forgot about my chat settings, you
know, cause we have a chat room for
Ocelli in the Greek and uh, no end
ons on that.
Yeah.
Well, because it kind of gets bombed.
I think it's a bot doing it or
it doesn't matter.
It's been very civil.
The atmosphere around the stuff that I do
has been very civil.
Um, and when people get uncivil or whatever,
they just need a little bit of schooling
or what they call a touch up, a
little touch up.
Right.
Okay.
So we do have a text question by
the way, and it is, let's see, let
me lean over here so I can make
sure I get it right.
Uh, swelling in the left knee.
Is that a young condition?
I know below the waist is young, but
in an expansive condition, what's going on there?
It's a, it's blocking a moment.
Yeah.
Well, it's, it's a yin.
It's okay.
What's happening.
It's young going.
The left side of the energy goes out
of the body, goes downward.
So something is swollen to slow down because
there's too much young flowing through there to
slow it.
Remember, these are roadblocks.
Whenever you have a physical manifestation in the
body, it's no different than a physical manifestation
known as a roadblock, right?
Whether it's a speed bump, you have speed
bumps, barricades, right?
You don't want the, what is it called?
The chain with the spikes.
You don't want that one, but essentially that's
an analogy.
So what it's doing there is the increasing
mass.
It's becoming more yin because there's a lot
of young going down there.
So the increasing, because there's more young traveling
down that side than the other side, because
that's the side that things go downward.
The initial balancing is to expand the area,
which is yin, which is right.
And then the, the other thing is because
it's leaving the body, it has to leave
at a certain rate.
It's either leaving too fast or too slow.
And if you have swelling and it's not
due to a very hard action, like, you
know, jumping off, you know, hurting the knee
and it's just manifesting on its own, it's,
uh, the young is in the protective side
of the body.
The young is trying to leave the body
quicker than it should.
So one way to fix that is by
becoming more yin by sleeping more.
That's why I'm a big proponent of sleep
therapy for many things, right?
Well, quite often when you feel a little
off, actually, I think you tell me I'm
going to like take a nap.
Kind of.
That's one of your practices for sort of
resetting, right?
It can be.
Yeah.
I'm big on it.
Anything.
Even from a two.
Yeah.
Whatever.
Just sleep therapy.
It doesn't have to be adding hours to
the amount that you sleep during the night.
It would be like maybe every three or
four hours, take a one hour nap and
that would be more therapeutic than resting for
20 or 30 minutes.
We actually fall asleep.
Yeah.
But if you, I found that if you
try to schedule it, you say, okay, it's
two o'clock time to do some sleep
therapy.
You'll be sitting there staring at the ceiling
for an hour.
Yeah.
I noticed that when I decide there's a
hard time to go to sleep, it's always
right.
Yeah.
What would you say?
That's the, you're telling the body to be
yin.
It's like, no, let's balance that off by
being young and focused.
It's kind of like the same thing when
you say, I'm going to fast on Monday,
Monday comes around and you are so hungry,
right?
Not on that day that you scheduled for
fasting than you normally would be.
It's really odd how that works.
So we're distracting yourself when you're waiting for
a pot to boil kind of thing.
It seems to go quicker because you're now,
it's, it's the emo kicking in.
It's emo.
Okay.
And yin and yang and emo are related.
Oh, there's another piece to that question.
Sorry.
I just rolled on it.
They ask about fire because a fire has
different effects on different materials and it in
and of itself is a yin reaction, right?
That's what they're asking.
But sometimes it creates a young reaction and
other times it creates a yin reaction.
It seems like something turns to, I'm just,
yeah, it's flip flips, right?
It's like the checkerboard pattern.
So imagine the checkerboard pattern, each adjacent to
whether you're looking at a black square or,
or a white square, you know, a red
or black or whatever.
There's another opposite color adjacent to it, but
in a different direction.
Hmm.
See, I'm thinking of those, you know, remember
those old desks, stupid things with the, you
know, the metal balls that bang back and
forth.
Yeah.
The momentum can sell conservation, Newtonian, the thing
about that is the fact that it goes
one way and hits and goes the other
way.
It's like a practical demonstration of union because,
because it went that way, it's got to
go and then come back.
Yeah.
And what's cool about those, I like the
ones that have five or 10 balls there
and it's only the ones on the outside
that are moving, right?
Yeah.
That's a, that's an energy.
You have to ponder these things and it
requires very fast thinking and analysis.
So people that are good at doing math
in their head will be able to do
this very quickly.
By the way.
Um, and if you can do, by the
way, I've mentioned people that are good at
math are also good at language because math
is a form of communication back and forth.
And people who are not good at language
are not good at math.
Typically.
I'm not saying always, but very general.
Like if you know someone who's not good
at math, ask them how many languages they
know and they'll say no.
Only English.
I don't, I'm not good at languages.
They'll volunteer the information for you.
Oh yeah.
We went over that before though.
That's a reaction based on something they'd seen
in the past though.
But it's, it's more of an attribute.
If you're not good at math, you're probably
not good at other languages learning.
Like I, I am proficient in three or
four languages and can say hello, goodbye and
thank you.
And maybe 20 languages because I, I see
it as being a form of communication.
And one of the problems we have, uh,
well, it's a systemic problem for forever.
It's been recorded history is, um, lack of
communication or effective communication.
You know, it's actually used against, uh, whoever
it can be used against, you know, look
at the, we've been talking a lot about
the financial stuff lately, right?
And that's about communication.
Um, that was today I had a conversation
about someone and they, and they said, uh,
I want to get rid of my mortgage.
I said, no, I can't get rid of
a mortgage.
You shouldn't.
Well, I want to, or I want to
get rid of a hospital.
I heard, you know how to get rid
of hospital bills.
Why?
Why do you want to get rid of
it?
Well, it can be monetized.
So why not do that and turn it
into something else?
The proper answer would be, don't you want
to be fair and equitable to want you
to go approach them.
They tell you, you can change the contract
with a hospital.
It's very simple.
They send you a bill.
You say, I just want to be fair
here.
You guys are an institution that offers services
that requires compensation or you ask for compensation
and you'd like to receive it, right?
No.
Yes, yes.
That's right.
Well, here I've given you a social security
number and I know, I know you have,
you could look up their trustee, you have
a so-and-so financial and they've already
accessed it through this act, this act, this
act, which you swear to uphold.
So you've been compensated.
So now you want to be compensated twice.
What does it say?
If it's set in the contract, you have
to pay us twice.
You have to pay it twice.
It doesn't say anywhere.
It doesn't.
But there's a spiritual element to honoring contracts
as well.
That's right.
So you just want to be honorable because
yeah, and usually they, they either call security
on you, which I've had done and here
they come.
You always know when security is coming.
It's all you to sit down and the
person you're speaking to is all the way.
These hallways are very long.
You look all the way down.
Why are they talking to these two security
guards and he's on the radio and he's
getting a third and they're walking faster as
they're getting towards me.
I think I should get up and maybe
walk out for you.
I always find that interesting.
Actually, I've observed many times that people really
just stay there in place and wait for
security to show up.
And I often wonder, you know, you could
have easily escaped.
Why?
Yeah, because they're not going to get in
the car and chase you like the popo.
Well, they're not going to go that far.
You know, I mean, you get off, you
get off hospital property.
Now it's a liability elsewhere, isn't it?
Oh yeah.
They will.
If they see you're at the door, they'll
just, they'll, they'll go outside and stand there
and look, stare you down.
You just, you just step over the property
line, you know, and stand there too, you
know, because right.
Like a little child, put your foot over
the property line and see him take a
step forward and take a step back.
They stop.
Right.
I was just going to say, it's like
shoplifting.
You know, once you get out of the
parking lot, it's over, you know, it can't
be.
Yeah.
But yeah.
So call it shoplifting and not stealing.
So yeah.
The same thing with a mortgage.
It tells you you can amend the contract.
Go ahead and amend it.
Take away their power to sell your property.
Remind them that it was, you, it says
in every mortgage says that you hold the
property fee simple.
Most people don't know what that means.
Fee simple means you own it and you
get, you put it in there and your
trust store, you're the grantor and you're firing
them as trustee cause you don't like why,
you know, the job they're doing.
Right.
They're appointing another trust.
And, uh, by the way, um, the most
taking away your security interest and I'd like
to take part in any kind of securities
tradings if you sold it more than once
and, uh, you sworn and I know your
trustee and all this and the sec is,
uh, very, it's got, they're overstaffed with people
that are underworked, uh, you know, sec, uh,
FINRA and these other regulatory authorities, they have
offices with 30 or 40 people that are
doing nothing.
They're watching porn and playing video games all
day.
Those are the, those are the ones that
are hired to do consumer affairs and none,
none of the consumers are calling.
The consumers go to attorneys or they try
to argue it themselves.
You call the sec on one of these
companies, they'll put you on speakerphone and like
they'll tell you and put you on speakerphone
cause there's like four or five agents that
have nothing to do and they all want
to be part here.
What you got, what you have to say
and they're on your side.
Yeah.
It's crazy.
I think they do that during the time
they're, they're giving you the, uh, the spiel
about, you know, this may be recorded for
whatever purposes, you know, training purposes.
No, it's different.
It's very different.
Believe it or not.
It's very humane.
I should say.
So, uh, yeah, it's quite interesting.
Um, by the way, I had this four
hour conversation today.
It's a conference call actually with water engineers
and investors and it basically gave them the
thing that, you know, this world is, if
you've been here for more than 30 days
on this planet and don't know these things,
you're kind of in trouble and it's a,
and the world is populated by idiots and
morons, you know, very few exceptions.
And they took that very well.
They said, we'll keep you away from the
idiots.
It was one of their responses, you know,
but not the morons.
Wait a minute.
Yeah.
Right.
What happened?
Yeah.
So I, you know, you're the way I'm
here.
I'm, I'm, I'm, I speak, you know, this
is, this is who, you know, this is
how I am.
So and, um, and it's for the people's
around me benefit cause they're not going to
hear it from anyone else at all.
But all right.
So I got another question, um, which, uh,
I, I just found, uh, just now actually,
and I missed it last week, I guess.
Um, could Greek talk about the cult and
in parentheses prank that we are all born
with gifts in quotes and are psychic and
can develop it.
Uh, the inner knowing we think we have
is, uh, that our spirit or question mark,
uh, is emo work at all?
Like psychic development, uh, okay.
So it is, it's all the same.
Don't separate it.
If it's nonphysical, completely nonphysical, it's psychic, spiritual
emo.
The emo is the part that you sense
with the body.
As your emotions change, there is a physical
reaction in the body, right?
You know, I don't know all the things,
you know, when you're happy, it's endorphins.
When you're sad, it's a whatever.
Yeah.
And there's a bunch of reactions that occur
that are measurable and that's what they base.
It's not reliable necessarily, but the lie detector
tests, right?
The, uh, the polygamy galvanic, you know, um,
you know, on the surface of the skin,
the electrical charge changes slightly.
So, but the, the, there's chemicals there.
So when I started pondering this decades ago,
that chemicals are released with emotions, well, aren't
chemicals material.
So that means that we can manipulate material
around us with our emotions.
You know, here comes, um, the Jedi, right?
Or these PK people, you know, you hear,
of course that they, that's all emo work.
When you see PK psychokinesis, right?
That's all emo.
That's not, um, a separate thing from emo
or spirit or psychic.
It's all the same.
It's the mental energy, let's just say, and
the potential of the mental, because when it's
energy, it's no longer potential to affect the
physical world.
And your first proof when you're trying to
develop this is notice how you change physical
attributes in your body, the way your body
feels chemically and looks.
Uh, and the reverse is true when someone
is sad or depressed and you don't know
why for specific reason.
And if you know the specific reason, address
it.
But if you don't, I usually tell them,
look at the ceiling and smile, force a
smile and do that for about 30 seconds,
which is a long time, which changes the
posture and all that.
And it will change the way the chemicals
in your body, just cracking a smile or,
you know, gesturing a smile, looking up and
you in every, you know, every time it
works.
So that's how the physical comes back on
the emo.
And that's also true.
Like if anyone's ever taken ecstasy, it's a
chemical changes your emo, uh, quite favorably.
Usually everything is so much more interesting and
everyone is so beautiful in their own way.
All of a sudden you feel the air
much more, uh, acutely on your skin and
you, you feel tempers.
And that's, that's pure, but not that air
is so physical.
I mean, what it'll do is we'll change
the emo, uh, you know, drugs, drugs, do
the physical side of the emotional side so
that you can changing the physical will change
the emotion and vice versa.
But the, the emo precursor, the psychic spiritual
emo precursor is far more powerful than the
using the material to change the emo.
Right.
And, but then that's how we're misled and
misdirected.
Again, when you look at the current science,
it's, if it's, there's no material.
And if you read the current science, you
know, they have to have some kind of
material evidence.
They tell you if it's, if there's no
material involved, we're not interested.
That's why they talk about electrons and protons
and all these bogus things, you know, uh,
and light as a photon.
So, um, they're directing everyone towards materialism and
it should be directed the opposite way.
And those that know that are going to
be much more advanced.
And this, this ties into like finance again,
because you know, the crypto craze, oh, you
better get crypto before they go digital.
Cause if they go digital, you don't have
crypto, you'll be Paul.
Right.
They don't understand that, that, um, the real
finance will always be wet ink on paper.
Always, always.
It'll never go completely digital for the poor
people.
Those that are losing, uh, there's a bunch
of what some person commented.
I think it was on the archaic thing
about, you know, your bills are actually checks
to you.
It says, no one, unless you're 80 years
old, everyone's doing electronic payment now or whatever.
Right.
Now I'm not interested in that.
So that is an example of a totally
slave circuited person.
Yeah, they're done.
They're finished.
Uh, they, they don't know what they're giving
up.
So in other words, they're putting out that's
perfect slave where you could be like mining
diamonds and you create, you, you find $100
,000 worth of diamonds a day and you
only get a piece of bread and, and
your shoes and have caught regardless of how
many, right.
That's the kind of people that you have.
Those are the people that are interested in
crypto.
Those are the people that, um, uh, are
afraid of the digital currency.
What they don't know is the secret.
Nothing will ever go purely digital.
The people going and signing stuff on pads
all the time at the bank or that
those are people are slave circuited.
They're done.
They're finished.
They're locked into brave new world status.
You know, um, they don't understand and they
never will get it.
That paper, wet ink signature, wet ink on
paper will never go away.
Uh, now for the majority it will, but
if you demand to know how to operate,
it doesn't matter if we had a hundred
years or a thousand years left or 10
years, it'll always be wet income paper.
You know what I mean?
Wet ink stuff, right?
Yeah, exactly.
On, on.
Yeah.
So that's, let me just put that out
because a lot of people think I do
a lot of doom and gloom, but actually
if you listen to what I'm saying, I
put out a lot of positive, very forwardly,
positive thinking things.
They may not be positive in mind, but
you know, well you can't say you can't
change the nature of the way this place
is set up.
You didn't set it up.
That's right.
I didn't.
Yeah.
You have to just know how it works.
And then you ain't, no one's going to
change it because that's too much momentum.
But what I'm saying though is that the
wet ink transactions will never go away and
that if you focus on that and stay
with that and learn how to work it,
you'll see what I'm talking about.
Those around you that go all digital are
completely slave circuited, very hopeless.
They're stuck in that system.
They don't have to be, but if you
do enough of it, you will be.
So be careful.
Yeah.
Now my whole life that I've been alive,
I mean, you absolutely always have to, if
anything is really significant, you have to put
a pen to paper, uh, even, even though,
yeah, absolutely.
But, but in the sense that, that, that
system going, that convention going away, just like
the banking conventions have changed the electronics, the
real, um, you managing what your potential is
will always be on paper and ink always,
um, the electronic part, it works because of
several things.
One is they want the speed of electronic
stuff, right?
They want to be able to take your
signature off of a pad and put it
on other things that you don't even know
exist.
Right.
So, uh, they can also do that when
you do the paper, uh, stuff also, but
what you're more minded, you're minded in a
different way when you're doing stuff on paper
and you keep checking on things differently than
people who just do things electronically.
Now, also the electronic part, um, works for
the banks and whatever group you're working with
because they can easily say, we lost it
electronically.
We got hacked.
Right.
Uh, and also it gets them out of
a lot of the securities protocols where they
have to send copies and things cause it's
electronic.
It gets them out of like showing, evidencing
fraudulent activity because if you copied someone's signature
electronically and put it on other electronic documents,
it seems less severe than if you actually
wrote it out on a piece of paper,
you know, 10 times on 10 pieces of
paper and sent them out.
You know, the one that has the hard
copy will get you indicted much faster than
the one that's electronic.
Right.
So it's to get them themselves out of
that position.
It gives them plausible deniability.
Exactly.
Very much so.
Yeah.
And so we can't access those records right
now.
Right.
Cause it's not, they're not physical.
So.
Right.
And that's always a good excuse to, you
know, suddenly the computers go down, you know,
stuff like that.
Yeah.
All that stuff.
Okay.
So a couple of comments in the chat
room.
I don't know if you're watching, but I
just wanted to bring them up as they
go.
And you know, God, by the way, guys,
feel free to add more.
I had the branch manager at the bank
called the police because I asked for a
complete record of all transactions on a loan
account to prove that I owed them anything.
No, no, no, no.
But go ahead.
Yeah.
And then there's one more.
I had words with the security thugs, but
I left before the popo arrived.
Yeah.
You.
Okay.
When you got a loan and all that,
all the performance that you people are, they,
that structured that contract was structured in a
way that whether, you know, they didn't lend
you anything or you did, you have to
perform according to how they tell you to
TV.
The TV tells you to perform.
You have to make all your payments to
them and they loaned you because right.
That's what the contract says.
The actual thing to do is if you
read the contract, you could have given them
a letter that you are taking full security
interest away.
And since they have your security, you want
to take control of it.
Right.
Because it's done already.
You're pointing.
Here's the other thing.
You never gave.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
You never gave them anything of values.
This is what people mistake also.
And I'll be getting into this more.
When you sign a promissory note, it's a
pay to bear type thing and they have
to keep selling it.
So when they have it, the bank or
whatever, and it's open, it's very little value
to them.
They have to keep selling it over and
over to get a value out of it.
But when you sign it, if you actually
gave it value conditionally by saying pay to
the order of Wells Fargo Bank where the
signature line was.
Now you're giving them value.
Now you're telling specifically where to put it
in their account and they can hold it
in their account as an asset.
They don't have to keep selling it.
You see the difference?
And that makes it that makes you puts
you in a stronger position.
Right.
And very often they'll say, what are you
writing?
You know, I say, well, this is just
how I signed my, you know, legally legal
documents, you know, this is more voiding it
out.
Right.
You write.
No, you're not voiding.
You're you actually want to give them value.
Yeah.
There's a whole process on this.
If you're going to get a loan to
use.
In other words, 12 USC, 1431 powers and
duties of the bank talks about the powers
and duties of the bank is basically to
borrow money and pay interest and also run
debentures.
Debentures are unsecured credit notes.
Right.
Which is which is a short way to
describe what cash money is.
It's a debenture.
Right.
But so they're the borrower, according to law.
But they made you in that contract.
They made you the borrower.
It's different than it depends on who you're
dealing with.
If you're going to a bank or a
car dealership, when you go to a car
dealership or more, you're cosigned.
The dealership is getting the loan for you
from their financial company and you're cosigning for
the dealer.
Right.
So each thing is different.
Credit cards are different.
Credit card.
You're an investor in their financial company, not
not the retail company, the one that has,
you know, the name on it, but their
financial company.
You're an investor.
It's not Discover Bank.
It's whatever bank and trust their trustee.
Yeah.
They might have Discover Bank Trust and then
it'll be Bank of Mellon.
There you go.
New York.
OK, that's the ones that you're investing through
the second company that goes through the Bank
of Mellon.
You see.
So I'm going to do a thing on
this because there's a lot of people out
there talking about.
But you get little snippets and pieces.
What I'm going to do.
I like doing Venn diagrams and flow charts.
Right.
Because, you know, it's easier to remember what
a flow chart looks like than a bunch
of bullet points.
Right.
So I'm going to do a bunch of
a flow.
And what's cool about flow charts, you can
have one bubble next to another and then
you have arrows going both ways.
Right.
With another flow chart.
You see.
So that's how it works.
So they now I didn't think the person
who got chased out by the police did
anything wrong.
I just think he wasn't speaking to the
right person on their side, because remember, people
that work in banks or financial institutions, they
don't know any of this, because do you
think they'll be sitting there for 20 or
30 dollars an hour if they knew how
to do this?
No, they're given.
That's why they're given a procedure to deal
with.
If something comes up, you just automatically press
this button or you call this number or.
Yeah.
No, they're just workers and they're slave circuited.
Now, it's the word of the night.
Slave circuit.
It's a short circuit.
You know, short circuiting is, you know.
Solid band name, too.
Yeah.
Slave circuit.
I remember years ago having these lunch breakfast
club type stuff.
We'd meet for breakfast.
It was a bank manager there from one
of the banks.
I don't know if it was Citicorp or
something.
And he was so interested in the financial
stuff.
And it's like I did.
He was the most interested.
And I said, what do you do?
He says, oh, I'm a bank assistant manager.
I'm like, oh, shit.
Why don't you say so?
You know.
Well, he got fired.
He would go there and start asking questions.
And they came to his desk asking him,
do you like your job here?
Do you like your job here?
He said, yeah.
And then they just walk out.
They didn't tell him, if you like your
job, you better stop asking questions.
Then he got fired from working in the
bank, right?
Just like if you know, if anyone that
works in the government, we used to have
someone in the chat says, well, my sister
works in the State Department.
It means she knows nothing about government at
all.
Right.
If she works at the State Department.
My brother works at the IRS.
It means he knows nothing about the IRS
or taxes.
There's no way they'll hire you if you
know anything about what's going on there.
Now, there are, for example, with the mob,
you do have to know what's going on.
Yes, you do.
There are a lot better.
I'm telling you.
How many times you hear me?
The mob is way better than any government.
Right.
One of these banks are way better.
This is one of our mutual agreements.
And I always say this, you know, they're
pretty direct, except occasionally they come to you
and say, you know, you have a lovely
family, you know, you know, stuff like that.
You know, you got to watch that.
That's a little more subtle.
But I don't know if you guys remember
the story.
I opened a bike shop and I asked
the previous tenants, I'm going to bridge it,
make it real short here.
What's your garbage?
I know we have a retail.
You don't rely on municipal garbage pickup.
You have to pay for your own garbage.
Right.
So I said, what do I what should
I expect to pay here?
This is about 150 a month.
I could do that.
I figured you guys were a hair salon
and I'm a bike shop.
I'm probably probably be double that tops, you
know, because sometimes they go by quantity.
Right.
Restaurant would be more.
You get a shipment.
Maybe you got a lot of packing materials.
Yeah, exactly.
I figured between 150 and 300 would be
fair.
So the guy comes in real tall through
the long leather coat and he just marches
through the store and he goes, I'm your
garbage guy.
It's going to be 750 a month.
And I'm like, oh, really?
What am I going to do now?
Right.
It was like Cavuto, you know, whatever.
Dino's specialized.
Dino Cavuto refuse service.
Dino's.
Really.
Dino's environmental.
Yeah.
Dino's environmental cleanup.
You know, really, really typical, you know, slime
bag, mob type, you know, whatever.
Right.
And low, low level foot soldier.
And I'm like, what am I going to
do?
So I know that the assemblymen in Brooklyn,
they have assemblymen, councilmen.
Right.
That are below the congressman.
They do the districts and the war, you
know, whatever they call them.
Burroughs district.
You got your mayor assembly.
Presidents.
Then you got the guys under him.
Assemblyman.
Councilman.
There you go.
And one of the guys was I remember
he came in and says, listen.
No, actually, I went to his office.
It wasn't too far away.
His name was very similar to the garbage
company's name.
And I said, listen, this is what's going
on.
Everyone here pays this.
And I'm a new business.
And I said, you know, they told me
750.
How am I supposed to manage that as
a new shop owner?
Right.
And he says, what are you doing?
What are you doing there?
And so the councilman said, well, it's a
bike shop.
He says, listen, I got I like to
rub my bike.
I haven't ridden it many years.
I got one for my wife and my
children.
I'm going to bring these bikes to you.
I want you to tune them up.
Fix them up.
Give them back to me.
I'll take care of it.
So about two days later, the same guy
with the long leather coat comes is OK.
All right.
It's 150.
It'll be 150 a month for you.
And he walks right back out and I
cut him a check or something.
They're on the spot.
Right.
Now, did he say anything like do me
a favor?
Don't go to the councilman again.
No, never.
Nothing like that.
But you see how they're all connected.
It's all connected.
One big freaking connection.
And I was kind of racist in that.
Not racist.
How would you say?
Because the councilman's name was very similar to
the garbage company's name.
I said, maybe they're related.
They're not the same, you know, but very
Italian name.
Very Italian guy.
I bet he can do something for me.
And he did.
Yeah, that used to happen to me, too,
because of the Italian name.
And you see somebody else like, you know,
I got the L.L.I. at the
end.
So they see somebody else with an L
.L.I. And that's not that uncommon.
And they go, you know, if you look
around, Mazzilli, Minnelli, you know, right?
So people would convolute it like, oh, you
got a name just like his.
No, we're not even similar.
But, yeah, I got you.
Yeah, but this is, you see, this goes
back to why they called the cops at
the bank.
You have to know the business, how they
do business.
And I'd like to find out more.
Whoever posed that, was that an email or
something?
No, that was in the chat.
And they did post a little more.
I'd like to do an investigation on that
more, like what you said, what they said,
and, you know, more details.
I'd be glad.
You could shoot me an email.
You could do it here or whatever.
Well, right here, I got a few lines
already.
They said they don't keep records for longer
than seven years.
And when I asked how they prove anything,
the cops were called.
That's right.
And then he responded to you, like you
were saying something.
So he said, yes, I didn't know any
of that back then, you know, regarding what
you were explaining about the bank.
He didn't know all that.
He just knew it's challenging, you know.
So anything else you want to add?
You have to challenge it on paper.
Now, what happens with a lot of bankers,
you don't hear about this because the last
thing you want is a lot of them
are threatened because there's, believe it or not,
there are multitudes of people finding out that
banks don't lend money.
It's actually almost mainstream, just like the recent
court case where the man didn't have to
honor the mortgage contract because fiat money would
never satisfy, right?
The court case, right?
So this is becoming more mainstream.
Even recently, speaking to an engineer, I said,
I do stuff about financial awareness and security
agreements and things like that.
And he says, like mortgages?
I'm like, yeah.
He says, you know, I gave him a
little bit.
And he says, you know, it's funny because
my brother said he had his mortgage set
off somehow, and now I believe it, you
know.
And I was like, you should go talk
to your brother.
As a matter of fact, have your brother
talk to me.
I want to see what he did and
how he approached it.
He says, all right, I will.
Let's go get in touch with, you know,
and all that.
So in other words, there's so many people
finding out.
And what I'm trying to say with the
banker, a lot of them are being threatened,
and it's not being reported publicly because the
last thing you want is to see a
trend or a movement.
You know, like people say, yeah, go to
the bank and threaten them, just like this
other guy did in the news last week,
you know, or whatever.
You know, they want to put the idea
in people's, you know, copycats.
No, they want to keep it quiet because
somebody says something like, you know, if you
see, look, I just showed up at this
place and they fed me for free, and
you see that in a newspaper, somebody else
is going to show up at that place
to eat for free, right?
Yeah, yeah.
So in other words, people are vacuous and
they take all their ideas and everything from
their environment.
We all do.
That's why you have to be very careful.
And you said set off, by the way.
I think you meant offset, right?
That's right, offset.
Or no, set off.
I think set off is the proper term.
I thought it was offset because they used
to do that with taxes where they would
say they offset it because they satisfied it
before they ever sent you the papers.
That's possible, yeah.
I wouldn't stick to that terminology.
But basically, you could see what terminology is
being used as you follow along each institution.
They have to swear to the SEC that
they're going to do these things, and that's
what you hold them to.
Very simply, if you got a loan last
November, right, in their SEC who gives them
the permission to trade these securities, they stated
and swore to it that within 30 days
they discharge and set off or offset, set
off all their loans.
So that means if you got a loan
last November, by the end of December or
middle of January, because it could have been
the middle of the month or whatever, it's
been already zeroed out and cleared out.
They've settled all liability.
But they're still sending you for the next
three, four years to pay on it.
So you contact them and say, hey, do
I owe you or are you lying to
me that I don't owe you because according
to the SEC I don't owe you, so
which one are you lying to?
Do I need to go to the SEC?
That's all you got to do.
They can't prove anything.
They already did prove it by signing up
to the SEC.
That's why it's the same thing that people
do when a car drives erratically or is
a hit and run.
Did you get the number?
Did you get the license number?
Why?
Because you go to the authorities with the
license number, right, and they have all the
records supposedly, right?
That's what they're supposed to have, yeah.
Yeah, and that's what you do with these
banks.
You find out what their SEC filings contain,
and they all contain the same thing, and
you hold them to it.
And the SEC is just waiting.
The SEC cannot take these people to court.
They can't because there's no subject matter for
them, right?
So, yeah, it's very interesting.
I mean, the FBI cannot just say we're
arresting the whole mob without arresting someone from
the mob.
So it's case by case.
It's quite interesting.
The reason I've been leaning on this more
is because there was a resurgence of this
online, and I said, you know, I've been
studying this for 20 years.
I personally don't care too much.
I just want what I need here.
But I've noticed that people's behavior, attitude about
life, or whatever, is based on how much
money they have access, or money they can
earn or spend.
That's really sad, you know?
So if this money thing is so important,
why don't we start seeing how to put
it together, right?
And be on the front end.
Whenever you're on the front end of something,
see, eventually the banking system will be watered
down, and there'll be some financial chaos.
But get on the beginning of it, right?
Get on the front end of it and
do it soon, like now, and like this
year, next year, the year after that.
Because after that, it's going to be so
chaotic that it won't matter.
You know, you'll have like the type of
inflation that it doesn't matter how much money
you have, you know, you're going to have.
So you do these things now to prepare,
not in a survivalist kind of way, but
in an understanding that the economy is going
to, your ability to perform in the economy
is going to go to shit, right?
Now, I'm not saying buy gold and silver,
but it would be good.
I think gold is almost 3,000 now.
I'm glad I bought it when it was
around 400, and so on.
But I don't think that's a major point
because, again, that's capital investment.
Gold and silver, you can't go and use
it down at the stove.
You really can't.
But it's capital.
So there's many ways to think about it.
And as we go down, I say we,
whoever we is, have to think about it
some more.
But right now, take responsibility of what's out
there is the main point.
No, absolutely.
And, by the way, I looked up Offset,
and number one, just a funny thing.
I always find it funny when phrases become
the name of a rapper, first of all.
So there's a rapper named Offset.
And, apparently, the usage of the word currently,
according to Miriam Webster, anyway, is to place
over or against something.
Yeah, and set off.
A set off is when it's no longer
on the books as a liability, right, or
something owed or something to be given or
whatever.
So maybe both apply here.
Yeah, the financial stuff, now that I've kind
of worked studying it more and more than
ever before, I'm beginning to realize how important
it is.
You get more sensitive.
You know when you're studying a subject, you
start noticing the subject more around you, right?
It's kind of like that.
It's kind of sad because, in other words,
the state of affairs that most people are
in with their family life and whatever career
or life they have, the people around them
just can't stomach this kind of information, even
in its simplest form, just approaching anyone around
you and saying, you know, it's a credit
-based economy.
And they go, yeah, I know.
That means it's not money anymore.
And they're like, oh, what are you talking
about?
And then you start drifting off.
And you're not going to get any support
in this at all.
So it's really a solo journey, just like
these spiritual quests that people go on.
Yeah, it's a spiritual quest.
It's no different.
Like you can want to do something about
your spiritual whatever.
Don't look for support around you.
It's a personal thing.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
That's why when you do find support, it's
invaluable.