Rated Y, 136, we could sit here and talk about the stuff that everybody else does.
But if that would be the case, you wouldn't be here listening to this, would you?
You wouldn't want to come here and hear us talk about what, the Democratic National Convention.
Which side are you on?
Does it actually matter?
It's so retarded.
Once you start looking at definitions of terms and definitions of government and law, you
know, you remember the Federalist Papers that people have heard of them, McGrath has read
of them.
It said that it's not the government's duty to control the behavior of the citizen, citizen
meant something different then.
It's the citizen's duty to control the behavior of the government, right?
That's just a thing, right?
And then it gets flipped by that idiot Kennedy, that's not what your government could do
for you, what you could do for your country, you could do for your country.
That was taken wrong, right?
But either way, either way, it's very, yeah, when you look at what they're discussing,
and it's pretty evident and pretty obvious what's going on, and the people are in a stupor.
It's kind of like, in early Greek speak, I used to really badger, you know, badger people,
you know, before the MPC term was popular, I was calling them space heaters, because what
do they all have in common?
They take up space, they're alive, they give off heat, so they're a space heater, right?
You know, don't step on my cord, right?
My cord is kinked.
Yeah, physical characteristics, I mean, that matches up.
You know, I thought you might have actually kind of enjoyed some of the DNC stuff that
they were spreading around, though, because there was a little bit of a dance party feel
there.
Did you, did you, did you hear about that at all?
No, no, but here's the thing.
It's entertainment.
Yeah.
Because I will give, look, I'll give anything to prove that no one there, none of the politicians,
none of the, know anything at all about law, about government at all.
Of course not.
It's not, it's a total misrepresentation.
You know how Eisenhower warned about the, you notice I didn't want to entertain the
dance thing, but when I was in the military industrial complex, he was correct.
I've been looking at, I've been trying to summarize this for some fairly intelligent
people behind the scenes.
What's going on in lieu of what we've been speaking of with definitions, with Brandon
Joe Williams coming on the scene, being popular and all that.
It is the military industrial complex.
I've looked at it in every aspect because the institutions that are blamed for the woes
of the quote unquote citizen can easily be put down with by the military and they're not
because the military wants it that way.
That's why I've discussed in the past, there's a military base in each state, which is not
required.
It should just be on the borders and on the, on the, on the fronts, right?
The waterfronts.
Yeah.
They're in each state because there's a chain of command.
See, police are paramilitary.
If they want to go arrest someone and they SWAT them and he just destroys the SWAT team.
Well, they get on the horn and they're like, call the army base, right?
And bring a tank.
Yep.
You know, if they don't have their own tank or call the air in here in southwest of the
air force and they drop a bomb, which is why they gifted to all these, uh, you know, local
police departments.
People were outraged for a little while.
Like, why is it that my local police department has armored personnel?
No, I'm not talking about armored.
I'm talking about chain of command.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
But what I'm saying is they bring an armored, armored vehicles are very easy to take out.
They have a big Achilles heel.
Do you know what it, yeah, it's, it's the undercarriage.
Yeah.
Of course.
You never, you never hit where the armor is.
Right?
Right.
That's the undercarriage.
That's why these guys throw these improvised devices underneath.
That's where to go.
But it's a, no, but it's funky.
I'm just saying they distribute this equipment for a reason so that it's there and accessible
for their guys when they step things up.
That's all.
Yeah.
No, no.
I'm talking more of the chain of command.
And if the military can't take you, then they do NATO.
Then they do the bigger international, right?
Military and satellites.
You know, they go out to space.
Now the military is for hire.
They do blow up people's homes and they, you know, if it makes it to the media, it's always
a gas pipe explosion.
There was a famous one that happened during the Obama years.
There was a critic, a journalist that criticized Obama and his car exploded.
They said it hit a tree, but it exploded before it hit the tree.
It was in a Mercedes.
Right.
Do you remember that?
Who that was?
I actually do remember that, but I don't remember who it was either.
Yeah.
There was a video.
They, they went around confiscating all the video, but one got out.
You can see the car bursting into flames as it's going down Santa Monica Boulevard or whatever.
And then it hits a tree and the engine is ejected.
And they even consulted Mercedes and it's like, no, that doesn't happen.
Normally, it was supposedly they hit him with a drone, in other words, a low flying drone
and then an air to ground missile.
Right.
Yeah.
So anyway, this happens often.
The most popular one was during the Obama days.
There was some lady, quasi-government agency, ex-employee, working with the press back and
forth with the, I forgot which agency it was in California.
They dropped an F-14 or F-16, came over and dropped the bomb on her house.
So, I mean, that's pretty much what all the neighbors said.
A plane, a jet plane came by and dropped something on the house and blew up the house.
When it showed up in the media, because it was in the San Francisco area, you see the,
they said it was a gas line explosion.
And the gas company shows up with this truck and they unload these old gas pipes and dump
them in the street.
I'm serious.
You can actually see them, you know, from the helicopter news.
They really botched that one up.
But it doesn't matter because these people are so stupid.
Here's the thing.
Years ago, I would criticize people, but it's no, there's no sense.
It's kind of like you're, you're studying them and I make up these terms, but I really
have no malady or ill will against them.
It's kind of like, let's say you're a geologist and you're studying rocks and you find a rock
that you trip on or falls on your foot.
You don't argue with it.
It's a freaking rock, right?
So this is what people, it's hard for people to understand.
They can do, they, meaning anyone, can do anything to anyone and no one cares, you know.
There's no outrage.
You know, like if someone's been wrongfully imprisoned, all you got to do is show up with
not even a thousand people around the prison and they'll let them out.
Let them out every time.
This was more in the past, not anymore.
It's amazing how quelled it is, you know, the, the human instinct to, to not fight back,
but to be more aggressive for what is right.
But again, it's all military.
For example, if you look at the courts, the court system, there is no judicial branch
anywhere anymore.
They're all administrative tribunals.
This is the proof throughout the world.
What they do, like, you know, it's supposed to be three branches of government.
There isn't.
There's just executive and legislative.
The only place there's any standing in judicial is the Supreme Court because they have the
judicial group there, the justices, Supreme Court justices.
But guess what?
You can look this up if you don't know technically.
The Supreme Court of the United States is not a court of record.
It's an appellate court, right?
Whatever they decide has to be bounced down to a district court again, right?
The people don't know that it's not, it's the highest court in the land.
But if you read the constitution, there's an article that states, let it not be in the
constitution.
Let it not be misconstrued that any court in the United States has any power in law
or equity.
So they're telling you they don't have a judiciary.
It was never properly set up.
Here's proof.
When you go to any court system, the prosecutors are all attorneys and the judges are all attorneys
and they're all governed by the attorney general.
There's a reason why they call him general, duh.
It's military.
And he's part of the judicial branch.
Wrong.
He's part of the executive branch, which is military, right now, how does it work?
They appoint judges that they say they elect them.
But even if they're elected, they have to be sworn in and still they have to be confirmed.
And that is done by the legislation.
So basically you've got the executive appointing confirmed by the legislative.
Where's the judicial in this?
There is none.
So that's why it's all done by contract.
Now there's a famous case in the United States.
It's Tompkins versus Erie Railroad, 1938.
And that made everything sway towards contracts.
Doesn't matter what you kill someone, you damage state property.
That's what it is.
It's not it's not murdering a human.
You kill, you destroyed human state property.
You have a birth certificate.
If you kill someone that doesn't have a birth certificate, they don't care.
They're like, whatever.
You know, they won't they won't do it.
They won't take the case.
This is very well known also, but it's not publicized, right?
So the the other hand of this is what the people think.
Ninety nine percent of the people, you know, like I go to Reddit to look up things to see
what the people, different communities, special, especially local, are saying.
Yeah.
And they have no clue.
And the more educated they are, the less they know.
So they're running this whole thing under a military industrial complex, all based on
contracts, bonds, you know, monitored the banks.
Right.
The the military loves the banks.
The banks love the military.
The purpose of the U.S. military is to represent the full might and force of the bankers, not
the government, which doesn't really exist, as you are told.
There is a government, but it's a corporation.
But somewhere in the CFR Code of Federal Regulations says that a corporation cannot be a government.
Ah.
But if you look up Title 18, Chapter 3002 titles, Title 18, I think it's three thousand
section three thousand and two subsection 15.
A got it right.
It states the United States is a federal corporation.
Now, you bring this up to an academic or say, oh, that's for the purposes of banking.
What?
No, it's not.
Because the United States is supposed to issue the currency to the banks and the banks are
not corporations either.
They're associations, national.
And then they started.
Oh, I know.
It's not like that.
They can't tell you.
They'll say, no, it's not like that.
You misunderstood.
I misunderstood.
Oh, my gosh.
So and this is why I tell people, if you study the definitions of law, not just reading the
law, because when you read a word person state, depending if it's upper or lower case or whatever,
you have to know how that word is being defined and go look at the definitions.
Now, if you study the definitions of those terms for, let's say, 15 minutes a day for
three months, you will know more than all the attorneys in the country put together.
What kind of statement is that?
Why do I say that?
Because let's say there are two million attorneys in the country.
I've said this before.
What's two million times zero?
Still zero.
So they don't know any.
None of them do at all.
So this is the situation that you're in.
So now when you get to the political scheme that's being pulled right now, it's nothing
but a show.
I someone wants to look it up.
There's a website that does statistics.
I looked at this back back in the day.
Just see if I could give out rough figures to see if they were right.
Like how much of the GDP is spent on entertainment industry, the whole entertainment, whatever
you want to brag.
You know, you can you could you could bracket the entertainment industry wide or narrow.
You know, narrow would be Hollywood or, you know, theater, radio, whatever.
Right. TV, the wide bracket of entertainment.
How much is being spent and then how much is being spent on all of education?
And you know what?
More was being spent on, guess what, entertainment and what.
By the way, what what year should I look at for this?
Because of any year, usually these these studies that kind of stick.
The latest you're going to find is probably twenty nineteen because they're always five
years behind.
Oh, I see one for twenty twenty three.
So I was curious.
Oh, that's that's very that's a fast one.
That's a fast one.
So I was going to look at that.
What do you think?
Should I look at that one?
Just for reference here real quick.
Yeah.
Go ahead.
Because I used to look at this stuff.
So when I'm giving analogies or anecdotes about things like, you know, I have a rough
figure and some people used to come and I have a good memory.
So it was people say that sounded outrageous.
I looked it up.
Yeah.
It's pretty much on there.
So.
Wow.
So I know it's about.
Yeah.
So that's only the digital.
But that's only the.
Yeah.
I mean, there's narrow scope and then there's overall, you know, what's the whole piece
of the pie, not just the crust or crumbs.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
There's one here that says it'll break it down by industry.
Yeah.
And how many industries and you add them up.
Right.
Yeah.
It's probably close to a short of a trillion.
Let's see, Bureau of Economic Analysis.
The Bureau of Economic Analysis?
Yeah, that sounds about right.
Yeah, there's other groups that do that.
Like there was a famous one that showed, that made the rounds recently about how the U.S.
population was going to be reduced down to below 60 million, right, or 100 million, remember
that one?
Yeah, I saw that.
That made the rounds.
Yeah.
Real GDP by industry, okay, privacy.
You get the point.
No, I'm taking a look at it.
And it's actually, well, there's more than double, the rough figures that I can read
here real fast show me that it's more than double on entertainment, and that's the generally
accepted surface stuff, like the digital and a couple of other things that they added together
to create the entertainment aggregate.
Yeah, it's more than double what is spent on education in the private and public sectors
combined.
Okay.
No, I'm just looking at it just factually.
That's what it is.
It's more than double.
Yeah, so what I mean by this is, considering the level of education the people in the legal
industry and politics have, they would follow the entertainment example.
They would be under entertainment.
They would not be under education, the current political circus, you see what I mean?
Right.
And that's what they've done.
I mean, really, I compared the two different conventions.
It's like one was the WWF convention, and the other one was the dance party.
Oh, yeah, I want Camacho.
If they had Camacho, remember from President Camacho running from my idiocracy, I would
vote I would actually register and vote and then repeal the registration.
If you know what's his what's the actor's name?
The black actor that is really he's always a muscular dude.
He's an old spice commercials.
Yeah, I forget his name.
But you know what?
It's hilarious because I talked about this and he said exactly that on Friday night on
the call in show where I said, you know, I'm looking at this, I'm looking at the two
different conventions and I'm thinking to myself, wouldn't we be better off with the
guy from Idiocracy?
And I played a clip, his State of the Union address.
I love it.
By the way, that that clip is hilarious to me.
But yeah, that's worth watching.
Yeah.
Who was the actor?
I mean, you only get that information while you're talking.
But go ahead.
Continue.
Because if I could pull up a soundbite because he's he does it well.
He always plays a thug or whatever in a lot of films.
Terry Crews.
Oh, it's him.
Yeah.
Terry Crews.
He does.
He's also the the father in that TV show.
Everybody hates Chris.
The Chris Rock.
Yeah.
They didn't cast him well on that.
He came out saying that they were touching his private parts, producers and all that
just to give a little signal on that.
She's down with them.
I'm sure he's at the cloning centers to this guy on that show.
They were touching him.
No, no, no.
He was in the in the media about what to producers and directors party and they were want to
touch his private parts.
Yeah.
Terry Crews.
Somebody's not bringing up a visual idea who this guy is.
Usually he's bald in a lot of his stuff.
But the Camacho thing, they gave him a big old wig, like a Jerry Curl wig.
Yeah.
We're running out of French fries and burrito covers.
But I got a solution.
That's what you said last time, didn't you?
I got a solution.
You're a dick!
What's up, Gary?
Anyway, that's that's it.
Terry Crews.
Yeah, absolutely.
No, I was going to get a clip to there.
But it's worse.
It's it's much worse.
Yeah, it's worse.
But the thing is, you know, this is if you.
Well, here's a statistic.
I remember reading a while back, in ancient Greece, you know, the place where they tout
his model of democracy, he was 99% slave, right. And they were, you know, in terms of,
you know, their citizens were categorized as slaves, right. So, I mean, it's just a distortion,
maybe if what how people feel or think about it, but you know, they're acting like, you know,
you know, school is not education, right at all. It never, never really was, even when the grammar
schools were happening and the edge level of educate, you know, you had a, you know,
in the 1800s, you know, you were done with everything by the time you were 13 or 14.
And you were done with university before you were 20. Even then, there was a lot of complaining
about, you know, rash conventionalism and ignoring things that, you know, should be taught, right?
Right. Right. I love it. By the way, I'm just looking at, because you made me look it up a
The House of Representing.
Idiocracy is a documentary. I came out, I did a talk once on,
it was a talk show, like one of these blog talk radio things with a group.
Here he is.
I know she's bad.
That was bad right now, but I got a solution.
But I got a solution. Then he goes through a whole thing. We got this guy.
That's exactly what's going on right now.
Exactly, exactly.
Exactly what's going on right now.
Okay, you beat me to it again.
Well, yeah. And the attorneys that were in there, there's a skit in there. But anyway,
I was saying I was on a blog talk radio thing there. And they were talking about the movie,
The Matrix. And I was saying, well, there's a movie called Idiocracy. That's a documentary.
And then I heard her recording the next week after I did this interview with them.
I was like, oh, the Greeks said, you got to see this movie called Idiocracy. I never heard of it,
but you got to see it because it's even better than The Matrix. They didn't know it was a spoof.
I thought that was really funny in itself, because it is true. They just didn't know.
They were just taking my word for it, which is true. It is more pertinent than The Matrix.
It is.
You're seeing it right now.
Quite appropriately made by the same guy. It's Mike Judge's thing.
The guy who made Beavis and Butthead.
Yeah, perfect. Yeah.
He knows. Mike Judge knows. He's another guy. He's been enthralled in controversy
privately, I think, also.
You know, I don't think I've asked you too much about this before. But what about this idea of
the since we're talking about entertainment, the entertainment elites, there are some people that
are in the know that, you know, know the whole agenda that are the insiders, so to speak,
and are getting the privilege to produce. What are your thoughts on that? I mean,
you know, is there a group of people that like have the privilege and already know what's
happening and are just, you know, making the movies just just for fun at this point
to rub it in people's faces and all that? I mean, what do you think about all that?
Nothing much to think about. You can go all the way back to the literary world with Dickens and
all these other guys when the Freemasons and started making they took Freemasonry underground
and they kept whatever they kept on the surface and they experimented with it. So when you look
at Dickens and other writers that were his contemporaries, they were pushing an agenda
back then. So was Samuel Clemens, Mark Twain pushing an agenda. We're talking about when
they're before TV and radio. Yeah, definitely. You know, that system, that mechanism was started.
Yeah. And long before 1984, because that's another thing that comes up. Well,
1984, which was made in 1948 and it was made by an MI6 guy. Well, he in an interview,
several interviews, he's mentioned that he was told to write.
Yeah. Eric Blair, I think, was his real name, actually, by the way. Right. But he was told
to write it. You know how like they have this secret pact that you're supposed to say what
you're going to do before you do it publicly. Brave New World is relevant, too. But people
often go to that and they don't look at that classic literature stuff. They think it's benign.
You know, the the Mark Twain stuff and whatnot. Yeah. I like Brave New World, though, because
when they tell you you're pneumatic, it's a good thing. It's interesting, too, the way they have
stuff divided. You haven't seen brain, you know, you're wondering that's a joke. It's a lascivious
joke. I understand. But there's a lot. Well, there was one. OK, here's the thing for people
who don't know. There is a BBC three hour YouTube on Brave New World. Brave New World decided to
make a film. It's actually stuck to the book. Exactly. So the book, Brave New World, you could
watch it on YouTube. If you haven't seen it, you should you should check it out. But when you wanted
to have the you had the alphas, betas, gammas, deltas, when you had sex, it was just like a normal
thing, like brushing your teeth or whatever like that. It wasn't, you know, it was very erotic.
You had whatever aids and aid, meaning help you needed. Yeah. And tools and and people were
described in sex. They were pneumatic, very pneumatic, very good. Right. Right. You know,
I guess pneumatic, like a jackhammer, I guess. So no, but it was all, you know, it was all rather
devoid of any of this, you know, forget about romance. As a matter of fact, they get in
trouble there. Yeah, for romance. Yeah. I just found it. It's still up there. Brave New World,
full TV movie reedit, three, three hours and two to three hours, just three minutes short of three
hours. Well, I don't think I've ever watched that whole thing. But the BBC does some interesting
work. Well, they're they're just like the rest. But they in other words, if you're to recommend
a movie that was based on a book, you need to know both before you make a recommendation. And I
familiar with the book. I read the book, I started reading it, put it down the 10 years later,
I finished it right, without going back and rereading it. So, you know, it'd be best to read
it in one shot, because there's a lot of start, you know, criticism in there. And in a way called
sarcastic. But the movie holds the book gets into a lot of fine details of what I call interjectory.
There's a mechanism in literature, when you bring up something new, you pause the story,
and you explain what that new thing that was just brought up is an interjection. There's a lot of
that in the book and like hand signals and tools and things. And it's actually done in the movie,
those things are shown in the film, the BBC film. So I will tell you the truth, I enjoy the Library
of Congress version of the audio book. I've never listened to the commercial version. But I do have
a copy of it. Actually, I got a CD copy of it. But but but I listened to the one that the Library
of Congress made. And I think it's interesting in the audio form. You know, it allows you to track
a lot of stuff that's going to say just watch the film for three hours. Three hours. It's pretty
good. It's on YouTube, brave new world. Well, they go free out there for people to catch. Anyway,
so recommended reading from the Greek. There you go. Um, yeah, it's not it's not Look, it's not
great. Neither is 1984. Because you it's just that stuff wasn't really put out even to me,
for me or to me, I just saw it as a social thing. Because it's even deeper than that. It's even
worse than that. That would be like the the level of reality that most people think they're in.
1984 and a brave new world shows another level of reality, right? And as a comparison. But there's
even another level and another level behind that. And that's more like what we get into the,
you know, like Dimitri Kolozov says, you know, there's three truths, right?
The first truth that goes to the groups, the main group, and then the second truth is those that run
the group. And the third truth is really what happens. So we're into third, fourth and fifth
truths, you know, because the facts don't always have to be what people think, you know, like,
again, the 911 analogy, I'd rather just say, you know, like, people search for the truth,
but you have to have your facts straight. The 911 analogy I give is, it's a fact that
people who witnessed the event on television saw the towers hit by airplanes. That's a fact.
It's also a fact that the people who were boots on the ground on that day did not witness did not see
and did not hear any airplanes, they just saw the sides of the building explode. That's a fact.
Another fact is that the media had interviewed people on the ground in New York that day
morning, who said that they saw airplanes go into the building. That's a fact. And there's another
fact, you ready, that those same people that were interviewed on the ground in New York that said
they witnessed airplanes going into the buildings were also witnesses at events all over the country
over a subsequent decade, like school shootings and other things like that. The same people.
Fact. So you'll figure that out. It's hard for me to figure out because I knew people, you know,
look, I knew people in New York, I lived in New Jersey at that point. But I knew people still in
New York who gave me various stories that day. And well, this is how Yeah, I know people there.
My niece, she was 10 years old, and she said she saw the airplanes go into the building. And then
I pushed her into a corner and said, Tell me what you saw. Well, we're in the classroom teachers
said go to the window and look, she really didn't see a plane go into the window. But it's so
convenient to say that, right? Give you an example. There was a psychological lots of psychological
studies on people's memories, and they would show, let's say 10 people separate, separate them
and show them the same film of a car accident, right? And the car like one car was red, one car
was white, people in one car wearing bright yellow, the other people wearing black, very
distinct, so very easy to see, you know, Party A, Party B, Car A, Car B, you know, right. And
all right. So they said, Take notes on all that. And after they did, they went and asked questions,
I took them out of the room what they saw in the film. So I asked a bunch of questions is was there
broken glass? And nine out of 10 of them said yes. And there was no broken glass. They went back and
saw the film, there's no broken glass, and other windows were broken. And, and they asked him,
why did they say there was broken glass? So well, because usually there's broken glass in a car
accident. Wow, wow, they weren't asking. The questions were not usually is there broken glass,
they were asking questions about what they saw on the film, you see. So when you hear all around
that there are planes going into the building, it's if you say no, you're the odd man out,
lady out. And in some cases, they transpose things where it's like, well, I heard this sound.
Yeah, but we asked what you saw. See, and they decided they saw what's the same with
Yeah, say with a JFK. Yeah, there's JFK is even weirder than, than it's actually simpler. Like,
I believe, okay, 911 was a botched job. Right? That the building that they blew up first should
have been blown up. Second, they screwed up big time. Right, right. Because you notice that the
one that got hit second came down first. That doesn't make any sense if it's a fire, right?
Right. True. So but they pulled it off, because they had to do it that way, because they wouldn't
be able to blast the the building that was closer to building seven. I've gone over this before.
The building that got allegedly hit with an airplane first, if that were taken down first,
it would have damaged the tunnel. And the other building would still be there today.
Right? Because these these devices are delivered under tunnel by tunnel had to be done in that
order. Yeah, it had to be done in that order. So they really screwed up and their screw ups in the
JFK. Yeah. Also, when you look at that, and the biggest screw up is what people are using as
evidence. There's a pruder film, you could see it almost starts to look like stop motion photography,
where the rest of the frames, right. And I wonder if that wasn't even a plant. Right? Because part
of the thing, you know, there's a pruder film, right? Yeah, of course. Yeah. Well, I, you know,
I got a different view on this, because I've studied that thing, you know, granularly. So I
mean, I've got a lot of different views on it. And all right, so just one of you, would you say
the film is intact? Is it duped? Well, I don't think it was duped. Is it intact? No, it was
frames missing. Not what people have seen publicly. No, it is not intact. And I can tell you right
away that there's no way if you saw a film that appears to be remotely stable, like the camera's
not shaking all over the place, then you didn't see the original. That's step one. Yeah, right.
In other words, whoever was filming that was told to film that. Well, I don't know that. There are a
lot of people that say that. But I know that if you saw a film, you personally, if you've seen this
film, and it's kind of stable, then you've not seen the original. Because the original film is not
stabilized the way that he's got it. Okay, that's right. Yeah, yeah, that's right. Same with the
same with the World Trade Center. The raw films that were put out the ground shook like a mighty
earthquake, like, you know, like five or six on the Richter scale, right? And then the building
comes down 10 seconds later, right? The newer films, there's no shaking at all. Yeah, the ones
that ones that show the shaking are no longer online, or they've been redone. So there's no
shaking. There you go. But any copy of the Zapruder film, though, it's just, it's not stable.
The original itself is not stable. And I've seen the film that shakes around. But it hasn't been
shown to the public any copy you buy from anywhere or anything else. It's not been shown to the
public. So I'm just saying, and there are differences in it. But I but to tell you that it
was duped or all that, that's, I would have to prove that by saying I know how it was done.
Or I, you know, so on and so forth. But it is, in other words, you remove frames, and then you
you double up the frames that were previous to make it to kind of fill in. So it doesn't look
like stop motion, right? Yeah, but it's only 400. And then also, there's the psychology
of Jackie, right? I never really understood that. Why is she crawling off the back?
Right when he was supposedly shot from the back.
A whole lot of weird things going on. Yeah, I think. Yeah, you want to really if you listen,
I bet he's still alive. And they faked the whole thing. That would be one pot. Could they have
faked everything? Yes. And all that right. Not still alive. He would be 110. Right?
Yeah, exactly. He'd be dead. Yeah, for sure. Yeah. So there's a lot of setting. Anything
that's put out is fake. I've been around long enough looking at antique shops, looking at
people's diaries, I should have acquired them. Diaries from the late 1800s diaries from the 1910s
and 1920s. And you read these diaries. And you're like, this is not a world that I've been told
about. This is a completely different world than what we're being told, you know, right?
I mean, honestly, even the closest eyewitness to the shooting that day
says stuff that is not in the Supruder film or did all the way up until somebody showed him
the Supruder film. There you go. There's their broken glass. Yes, there's broken glass. You
know, that kind of thing where like he says that Kennedy jumped up during this event, like he
actually jumped up is what he said. He said it all the way up until the 1980s. And then somebody
was real. Yeah, yeah. It's like flat earth rounder if you could prove both.
Right. And somebody showed him the film. And they said, Do you see him jumping up? He says, No,
but that's what I always remembered. And it's just really strange. And actually,
that's that was done on TV in a weird way, too. It was it was really bizarre. That guy's name
was Bill Newman. He's standing like a feet away, like 10, 10, 15 feet away, actually, at the time.
Wow, that's like, it's like you could feel 10 feet away on something like that is like you're right
on top of it. Yeah, yeah. So anyway, so with that in mind, and all the fakery that goes on,
it's no surprise that there's a dance party and a WWF reunion at the other place, right? I mean,
Hall of Famers getting together from the WWF. I think the people wanted if they didn't want it,
they could put a stop to it. Well, that's 5% 5% is all it takes. And yeah, get me out of here.
That's the thing about complaints. When people complain about this stuff. I always say, you know
what, it wouldn't be produced, it wouldn't be happening. Unless there was a waiting audience
that wanted it. That's, that's the hard part about this, you know? Yeah, but there is movement.
Like, that's why I was so happy with Brandon, Joe Williams and Chris Hauser, whatever, you know,
about using the trust, you know, the all capital name. For example, people becoming state nationals.
It was like 2000 p you can do this, you know, not to be US citizen, right?
Through the State Department. And I have something like that even more official,
because I did that 2006. And I've got paper, I think I showed you some of the paperwork, right?
A while ago. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. So I did it. You don't have to do it the way I did and get
detained and all that trying to come back into the country. But for about 10 years,
the State Department showed that there was 2000 people that did that over 10 years, right?
And when it started at a certain point, when information started to get out,
I think it was like five years ago. Now it's up to 50,000 in five years, did it?
And most of those 50,000 are attorneys, believe it or not. But they never tell anyone, right?
No. The other thing is with the IRS. Now, what people don't understand the death and taxes thing
is it's a subscription. And how you get into the subscription is with a W-9. When you're 18,
they rat on you and they say, in other words, oh, he's 18. Send him in the mail. They send
little tiny form that you sign and send in from the IRS called W-9. You don't even know. It's
like you don't have to do it. You don't have to take any action. You don't have to pay anything.
Just sign and send it. And you just subscribed. And then every time you do anything with the
IRS, you swear to it. You swear, actually, that you live in the District of Columbia,
right? Like telling someone says you have to sign that Greek. I'm like, okay,
why don't you sign it and swear that I live in the District of Columbia? Oh, I see what you mean.
Right. So what happens, people don't understand why there are people getting beaten up by the
IRS. It's not because it's the IRS or taxes, because you're swearing to it, which is called
penalties of perjury. Now, let me give you an example. And this is true. Any attorney that
doesn't even know definitions won't know this. In other words, it's like saying go to a nine-year-old
and they would know this, right? If you walk into Goodwill and you say, hey, I'm going to donate my
couch to you. And I'm also going to fill out this form here where under the penalty of perjury,
I'm swearing that I'm going to give you this couch. Do you know that if you don't give them
the couch, they could call the marshals, they could come kick down your door and take the couch
and still put you in jail for a year? I'm serious. That's how the law works. It has nothing to do
with the IRS. So the IRS has a way to unsubscribe, just like any other subscription, right? It's
called Form 56, or every IRS form has, or you use this form, or what does it say in the instruction
book? It doesn't matter what form it is. Use this form and say, fill out this form. And in the very
end, it says, or make your own statement. In other words, write us a letter, right? So this has been
going on. So, and then the 10, go ahead. Oh, I was just going to say, we talked about this,
that Snoopy did this in the, uh, in the PSA. That's right. It says, please unsubscribe me.
They put it out there in the seventies, right? Please, dear IRS, please unsubscribe me. And
that's what it is. It's an unsubscription. Now the other people, when you, when you have a debt,
it belongs to the treasury. There's a 1099A. Another thing that's been going on, you could
call the IRS. It's one of these triplicate forms where it has, uh, they're all put together.
You've seen them where it's a white, uh, pink and yellow. And when you write on the white one,
it writes, it's like a form of a carbon hospital. The hospital is the same exact way. When you do
registration of carpet, it's got the white, the yellow, and the pink. Whenever you see those three
forms that goes to the U S treasury, but okay. So the IRS was kicking around. You can't get these,
you have to get them from the IRS, right? You can't print them out. It was like,
they were sending out like 40 a month, 50 a month after some of the word got out,
people would order a thousand of them. Right. So now they're like, they're not available. Like
3 million were ordered one year. Once the word got out on how to use them. Right. So actually
it was more than 40 a month because the, um, if you get a mortgage, you'd give a mortgage or buy
a car and you do a forensic audit on it. It will show the 10 99 paid your social security account
to get the money to give you, right? It's crazy. So now what's happening. So what I'm trying to
say, there is a movement behind the scenes. There are a lot of quote unquote, Americans that are
using the system to get out of the same system. In other words, you're using the tools that was
put in by the system to get out, to opt out because the whole country was based on throwing
tea in the Harbor over a 2% tax. Right. Allegedly. So one of the IRS chair, people were
interviewed, you know, about people get in trouble with taxes. No, no, it's voluntary. It has to be
voluntary. Otherwise it wouldn't work. The thing is you just don't know how and when you volunteered
and how and when to unvolunteer or unsubscribe. And this is, this is going on. That's what got
my juices flowing to speak about Brandon, Joe Williams. I don't endorse him because a lot of
stuff he says is, is not correct, but it won't get you in trouble versus what other people do
more severe things like putting liens on public officials the wrong way. Uh, uh, if you didn't
like a court decision, people would go put a lien on a judge and then the judge's wife wants to go
buy something and they deny her credit card because there's a $40 million lien that gets them very
upset and they have the power to kick down your door. Right. Even without a warrant, they never
have a warrant by the way. Uh, warrants cannot be issued by a nonjudicial entity. Do you remember
a training day when, uh, he breaks in and he says, well, I want to see the warrant and he gives her,
he gives her a Chinese menu. Yeah, that's exactly what's going on. It's the same thing. It's never
signed. It can't, they're not because it's not judicial. Uh, so anyway, the thing that gets my
juices flowing is I know there is a movement it's hidden. It's never talked about where it was a
few hundred people. Now it's in the tens of thousands that are actually using the remedies,
you know, this, you know, to get out of the sickness, right? What do you need a remedy for,
right? To get out of being sick, to get out of the system. And I'm watching the, uh, the surface
reaction of that. Right. So when people are understanding how to get out of unsubscribing
from the IRS or citizenship or all these other things, uh, by the way, you may not be able to
do this in other countries. I'm speaking about America, by the way, United States of America.
If you're in Canada, um, UK, Europe, let's say, uh, heaven forbid you're in Bulgaria. Cause Bulgaria
is being run. Like, um, Romania was being run under Chichesco, right? I don't know if you know
anyone from there. That's really bad. Still. It's just as bad as would have been in the eighties
or seventies, you know, these, uh, Eastern block countries. So anyway, if you're in Australia,
New Zealand, you're a subject you really, there still is ways because if you have a, uh, a
universal tax laid on you, like an income tax and you have a social security number or social
insurance number, it's the same as here. It's just a different method. I know that all the
countries in the world have clauses when you do transactions, for example, to make a conditional
endorsement. So you don't create a tax liability every time you sign a check. I know they like,
um, someone recently asked me, what's it for Canada? I said, I remember for Canada,
you just look up in a search engine in the codes, uh, restricted endorsements. And they,
you do, you know, write down lawful money only. And they can't tell you not to write that because
you're allowed to restrict an endorsement. Right. Right. And that prevents a tax liability. So
everywhere, there's a way to get out of it. Um, uh, yeah. And you know, who's to blame? It's not
the government, your parents, they didn't do due diligence and their parents. Right.
So that's why I've always been saying, you know, it's, it's the people around you,
you know, the, the people like when you're listening to this, it could be the people
that you're in the same room as you right now that are, while you're listening to this Greek
speak, right. It's usually the people that are closest to you that mess you up the most, you know,
parents, especially because they didn't do their due diligence.