Rated Y, Sonic Event 120, Greek, how you doing, man?
Mouthful of kratom and coffee, I just let it smoke, chill it.
There's not much going on in chat other than a spell correction.
It's Jim Cartin, C-A-R-T-I-N.
I might have passed away recently in Oro Valley, I don't know.
Yeah, yeah.
So, yeah, I just want to bring up one thing I noticed.
How do you sum up a lot of the Greek-speak stuff?
I've been speaking with people along the years about wanting to do stuff with it,
and one thing I'm adamant about is this is a free-flow public service, sort of, public-private.
And if you're going to do a project, don't call it Greek-speak or Greek or whatever.
You're supposed to take the—
Oh, is somebody trying to do that?
Well, Sam, you know, is doing it. I don't mind that.
But what I even mentioned to him, when he first, first started it seven years ago,
call it something else because it's not about me.
It's not about—this is about holding people accountable.
So if you go to a bank, they're supposed to know what banks are supposed to do.
If you go to a doctor, they're supposed to know about the human body.
If you go to a lawyer, there are no more lawyers or attorneys.
They always give me a hard time, and they look it up, and they say,
well, a lawyer is an attorney now, of course, because there's nobody left.
I want to get into how the country's been abandoned.
So the whole thing is to—By the way, anyone—
Okay, John Butts, who passed away—
I've had a lot of conversations of natural action tech, by the way, technologies.
He passed away, and he would call me and say,
I was in a conversation the other day, and I used a lot of your stuff.
Like, you know, I'm just visiting here, taking notes.
I said, that's fine. I mean, it doesn't matter to me.
I mean, saying these things in a way—
Okay, so you mentioned to me that you're saying what I'm saying. That's fine.
All right, so say what I'm saying.
But what's the next level? What's the next level to that?
Take it on. It's going to be your stuff now, right?
So adapt it into your stuff, and now apply it.
Then you've got to apply it, right? Not just say it.
Yeah, use the stuff that I'm the first to say, let's say.
Because that's what drives me, and that's what drives me crazy.
Look, you're not actually taking ownership of this, because you're the Greek, right?
So anybody could be—no offense, but anybody could be the Greek.
2010, I was doing my private audio with Angela Stark.
She wanted to interview me.
And really long Greek name. She goes, you've got to get your nickname.
I said, I will figure something out.
A week later, right before the call starts, she goes, all right, we'll just call you the Greek.
Sure enough.
And it stuck, right?
But it was also—that had come up before, right?
When cell phones first came out in the late 90s,
someone says, I've got your number right here.
Someone asked for my number.
I said, it's all right, I have his number.
And he pushed the contact menu, and I looked over at the phone, and he had the Greek.
So anyway, it seems to be recurring.
But what I mean by this is I would like to see—and not just on any specific subject.
Lately—okay, just expansion.
Expansion, that's all it is.
Okay.
So it's kind of like when a country—you know, the country expanded.
It just didn't become the westward territories.
It became all the different states west of the Mississippi, right?
Kind of like that.
It's an analogy, right?
Well, fair enough.
Because it was the western territories, you know, before the French-Indian War.
So it starts with an idea, and then here's some substance.
Now we're going to give a name to that substance.
Now what do you do with it, is the question, right?
Well, we talked about a few sonics ago, what we do to do with it.
This is for people that do things and have skills.
Yes.
Because it's going to help you, right?
Because, you know, if you're a snowflake and you cry about somebody saying something about you
or your parents raised you with a silver platter and you can't handle adversity or whatever,
this isn't going to help you because this will create mental adversity, like I've told people before.
You try to live the stuff that I'm saying.
You say goodbye to your relationships and family and all that there, right?
The collective can't mix it.
So it's true.
But anyway, anyone who's doing anything with it, as long as it brings good, that's fine.
What did I say I was going to catch up on and mention just now?
Oh, there's a guy, Brandon, John Brandon Williams, something like that,
talks about getting rid of contracts.
It came up recently.
Someone said, listen to this guy.
And he discovered recently about all kinds.
Brandon Williams or John Brown is pretty popular right now.
He's only been at it for a year or less.
And it's all about releasing contracts.
But I had the videos that I'm working on a packaged AC unit.
So I had hours and hours of background.
Let some of this stuff play.
Not once.
He talks a lot about money, but he doesn't mention the conditional endorsement.
So he's going to get a lot of people in trouble.
You know, the 12 USC 411, right?
Because the Supreme Court case, basically,
there's people that argued the money any which way till Sunday,
you know, with gold and all that.
And the Supreme Court opinion on it was I don't see where he made a demand anywhere.
So he loses.
They're not going to tell you what code you should use, but they'll hint, you know, right?
Because the code is explicit.
You have to make a demand for it.
It's sort of like the famous case where, you know,
the bank was going after a guy for a mortgage,
and then he proved that the bank didn't actually own the property to begin with to sell it to him in the first place.
And when you do that, yes, if you break, you know, look, contracts are contracts, right?
I mean, yeah, but it's different.
That's what I wanted to get into.
But if you voluntarily sign something or you ascribe something with your signature,
that's a fairly powerful thing.
Legally and lawfully, right?
Both legally and lawfully, isn't it?
Well, legally, it's powerful for them, not for you,
because you've abrogated all of your defenses and rights, let's say.
But here's the thing.
Okay, so this guy Brandon Williams, whoever he's talking,
he knows more than 99 percent of 99.999 percent of all the attorneys in the country put together.
And he's only been studying for two years.
Of course.
Right?
I've been looking at this for more than two decades.
I can say I know more than 99.999 percent of attorneys and Supreme Court judges in law, right?
How does that help us?
Absolutely nothing, because now they go into savage mode because, you know, like animals,
if you go to them, it doesn't matter.
Doctors are the same.
Yes, I do know more than 99.999 percent of doctors in the country or the world.
And these things are just sort of rudimentary.
I've said many times, you want to be an expert on something, believe it or not,
contrary to what you've been told, if you study it for five minutes a day in like two years,
you'll be in the world authority on it.
Yeah.
You know, even let's say an hour a day in a couple of years, you'll be very simple, very easy.
All you have to do is amass everything that's been amassed about it, get familiar with it,
and then see how it's being applied and then do your own applications.
And you'll be a world authority.
I mean, workable world authority.
They won't recognize you because you're not part of their clubs, their respective clubs,
whatever topic you're studying.
Right?
So these people, what they do, and I've had lunch twice, not once, twice.
Do you know the Miranda rights?
Yeah, of course.
Right?
Everybody, they even popularize them and say, okay, the person who penned that is a Supreme Court,
is a Supreme Justice.
His name is John Fitzgerald Malloy, and I had lunch with him twice.
And he invited me.
So he doesn't know much about law either.
He's passed away now because this was more than a decade ago, and he was about 90.
Yeah, he was old then.
A decade and a half.
Yeah.
So he was in his early 90s, and this was in the 2000 single digits, like seven or six or something.
The 20-ops, whatever you call it.
Yeah.
So he doesn't even, so basically what he let me in on, who are you going to tell this to?
Meaning they've got everybody.
Okay.
There's a guy in town, Josh Alberton.
He's in prison now.
And I did a lot of studying, helped him out with a bunch of stuff, and vice versa.
He-
Doesn't sound like a ringing endorsement right away there.
I helped him out with a bunch of stuff.
He's in prison now, but sorry.
Yeah, no, no, but he's in prison for going.
Anyway, it's a long story, but he didn't, his legal stuff-
He didn't go to prison as a result of what you told him, is what you're saying.
No, no, not at all.
Okay.
No, he was just very aggressive.
He showed that you could buy a house with a social security number, right?
Okay.
Just put your social security number, make a check, and it clears and everything.
So I was like, oh, they're going to, I said, why are you doing this?
I want to be wealthy.
I'm like, oh, wrong planet, wrong planet, wrong planet.
And I stopped talking to him.
But anyway, he, where was I going with this?
Well, you had given him some advice.
Yeah, good.
Yeah, but okay, but anyway, just as an example, he was doing all this legal stuff very, very, very aggressively.
Right.
And what happens is when you start working and understanding stuff, none of the people,
like when you're doing legal stuff, you're going to deal with attorneys, judges, bankers, right, people.
None of them knew anything, what he was talking about, even though it was in their own rule books, right?
So they're like animals.
So what they do is, oh, this is what I wanted to get to.
He put in a bunch of paperwork to get people released from jail.
And all of a sudden it was working.
So what they did is they put him on the nightly news where you want this guy, the police want this guy.
Right.
And they put his face up because, you know, and everything.
And so wherever he went, people were giving him funny looks.
Everyone watches, you know, the collective.
Right.
I've seen clients, by the way, years ago when I was out in the field more and more at large, especially older clients.
Oh, you know, it was like five to six.
I got to go.
Where are you going?
I have to watch the news.
You know, it's like it was like a religious, you know, I have to go to church.
You know, I can't be late.
Right.
So wherever he was going, people were looking at him funny because they kept putting it once.
I think they did it on the nightly news primetime.
They're looking for this guy.
They put his name out and all that.
So that's all they have to do.
How many times have you heard where they plant things on you?
Right.
There was there was the Jim and Joanne Moriarty, the people, the oil people from Libya that got caught up there and they escaped ISIS.
Oh, right. Yeah.
And they were talking about it when they came here.
And he went to Wal-Mart to have some tires changed.
And the guy found a package under there.
They let him have it because they got pulled over by the police later.
And they were all looking under the car.
Remember that story?
And they're like, she was here, supposed to be here somewhere.
But the guy who then there was the police strapped a box of drugs under their car.
And when unbeknownst to the police, they stopped at Wal-Mart Moriarty's and had some tire work done.
And the guy, they said the guy was full of tattoos, looked a little worn.
He probably found the package, took it off, took it home.
Right. Probably.
And the sheriff that was there, the police that were looking under the car after they were pulled over for no reason.
He's on his earpiece.
And they hear him saying, keep looking.
It should be there.
You know?
Yeah. Right.
Yeah. Also, I've seen one of those trackers on a car, by the way.
I knew someone who had one.
And he said, why don't you take it off?
I said, no, no, take it off.
This is your chance to fuck with them, you know?
Take the car, put it, you know, can you get another car?
Do you have to use this one?
And just start, you know, let someone else drive it.
Someone else that's got a weird route.
And we knew someone that was a drug runner, a legal drug runner.
You know that drug stores don't keep a tremendous supply.
They rely on every two or three days getting a delivery from a warehouse.
Right.
Also, they don't stock up drug stores, you know, in pharmacies and pharmacies.
When I was growing up, we called them drug stores.
Right.
In supermarkets that much because they could be robbed.
You know, imagine they, you know, certain pills are popular and they know they've got 20,000 of them, right?
Yeah. That's why they don't.
They go to the cash register. Yeah.
Right. They don't keep a huge inventory because you get away with.
I mean, it's a lot easier to carry a couple of those big bottles, you know, with 500 pills.
Yeah, they're huge.
Yeah, that's right.
They are big bottles.
You know, they're kilogram size.
Yeah.
Literally, it says one kilo on there.
Over 5,000 capsules or whatever.
So you take a bag full of those home, you'll get more than you would a bag full of cash and it weighs less.
So, yeah, go ahead.
So Don was a real estate guy and he was running drugs out of a warehouse in service.
He serviced all the supermarket grocery stores out of pharmacies.
And he used it.
Anyway, so I could write a short story, make a short movie about all this stuff.
Oh, I've heard of people taking those.
Yeah, I've heard of people taking those and sticking them unbeknownst to, you know, the taxicab guys just sticking on a taxi.
You know, it's great, especially in a busy area.
But the interesting thing here, though, because he was a drug runner.
Yeah.
Meaning, you know, a licensed drug runner because he was taking wholesale drugs to grocery and resupplying them.
So I thought it was a funny thing.
Yeah, no, definitely.
So anyway, this legal stuff, when you end up knowing more about the people that are supposed to know,
they have the collective on their side to turn against you.
Now you become Dr. Frankenstein.
And here come the angry villagers with pitchforks and they don't know what they're angry about.
They've never seen the monster. Right.
So this guy, Brandon, he's what he's saying is mostly correct.
It's not airtight.
I use that term very often.
I hope it gives a good analogy.
Right.
It's mostly correct.
But right now he's in two years.
He's gotten to the level where he knows more than ninety nine point nine, nine, nine, nine, nine, nine percent of attorneys on the planet.
Right. Is that good?
Yes. Overall, it's good.
If you're going to do a tour group from someone for a group visiting this planet wants to learn about it.
Right. But the idiots that are born here, the morons that are here, it's just going to make them mad at you.
Right. So you have to keep that in mind.
You understand where I'm going.
Like, for example, because when I bring up to people that work in the medical field, biological vacuum.
Right.
They know I just mentioned something profound, but they can't associate with it.
What does it mean?
Well, it's a natural living.
Imagine an object, just an object doesn't have to be living or anything, just an object, a container.
Yeah. When it's not completely sealed or it could be this.
It's the same pressure inside the boxes outside the container, right outside the box.
Same pressure because it's open.
Now, if you close the container, seal it, it still probably is the same pressure until a temperature difference takes place.
If you drop the temperature through the container, the pressure goes down.
Right. Vacuum. Right.
And that's why, you know, people, old people have a hard time opening jars.
Right. Right. Because they're sealed when they're hot.
And then if the pressure inside the container goes up, the pressure increases.
You take the lid off, the lid pops. Right.
So. OK, so we understand things that are closed systems can have varying pressures.
Right now, when you go to all living things, all with a capital L.
All living things. OK.
Have a biological vacuum.
In other words, once they are formed from seed, literally humans come from a seed, also two seeds.
Right. All the way up to maturity till death.
There's a biological vacuum at death.
The vacuum ceases to exist.
And then you have the onset, the onset of chemical decomposition.
Now, let's go back to the container.
Let's say you have a metal container with aggressive acid.
And you have a very thin lining of plastic to prevent the acid from attacking the container.
Once that lining goes away, the acid inside the container is going to aggressively attack the metal.
Right. And go through. Right.
You know, it's funny, a lot of people say, I don't like drinking from plastic.
So they drink out of a can.
What an idiot.
The can is lined with plastic.
Actually, there's an experiment you can do.
I saw it on YouTube. I've been telling people this for 30 years.
Take a Coke can, whatever aluminum can, and put it in sodium hydroxide.
Don't open the can. Leave it closed.
Which is lye. A little hot lye would be even better.
And you'll see the aluminum completely dissolve.
And all you'd be left with is a very thin-walled pouch.
Plastic with your drink still inside of it.
All the aluminum will dissolve and you'll have a pouch of Coke or Sprite or whatever's in the can.
Beer.
There's a couple of YouTube videos.
Someone said to me, I heard you talking about this and there's a video on that.
I'm like, great.
I'm going to have to look that up.
Sodium hydroxide lye will completely dissolve aluminum.
It turns into hydrogen. Don't make too many sparks either.
It'll make a big fire if it's closed.
Flammable.
Yeah, even though hydrogen is very flammable, it moves at 700 feet per second.
Just under the speed of sound.
It's the fastest moving gas.
That's why they use it in a rocket.
All rocket fuels, the main constituent is some hydrogen compound.
So it's almost bang for your buck.
No pun intended.
That's why I was laughing at people still using gunpowder.
People are into guns.
Here in Arizona, into guns.
I said, oh, that's that gunpowder shit.
Get away from it.
Start using hydrogen-based stuff.
You'd be able to shoot a tennis ball through a brick wall.
But anyway.
If you could shoot a tennis ball through a brick wall,
could you imagine what you could do if you had a hollow point?
No kidding.
Yeah, it would be armor-piercing very easily.
So anyway.
Idiots. Idiots. These humans are idiots.
Anyway, what I wanted to bring up was just because people don't know something
doesn't mean it doesn't exist.
Again, I'm commenting on the guys doing the legal work.
I think it's John Brandon Williams or something.
Legal stuff about getting rid of contracts.
He knows so much, and I'm impressed that he's learned a lot in two years.
No mention of the other things that I mentioned that are important.
But that's fine.
I'm not saying it works.
But he's going to have a lot of hard-knock experiences,
even though he has some successes.
Because you're on planet Earth.
You're a bunch of savage morons, basically.
That's why early on in the...
And by the way, no one did anything to piss me off.
I'm not saying...
I'm saying this with the most amount of affection possible.
Okay.
Just like when you hang out in the ghetto,
women are affectionately referred to as bitches.
Right?
It's not, right? Okay.
Where in other situations, when you refer to a woman as a...
Right?
And also, if you're not around dog people,
and you see a female dog and say,
that's a really nice bitch,
people around you get offended.
You just said something, right?
Yeah.
So you see the context of how it's used?
Of course.
This is exactly what's going on also.
Now, just because people don't know something,
people in the plural or singular,
it doesn't mean it doesn't exist.
But most people have the emotional attachment
that the latter part is untrue.
In other words,
if people don't know something,
they inherently believe it doesn't exist.
Right?
You know the old saying,
I think, therefore I am?
Right?
So thinking what you know and what you think
as bearing on your proof of existence.
So if you don't know about something,
and you're made aware of it,
you have to prove that it exists,
because if you don't, it still doesn't exist
to the person, even though it was mentioned.
This is exactly what's going on.
On the other side of that coin,
the more something is repeated,
no matter how ridiculous it is,
it becomes more believable
simply by virtue of the fact
that it was repeated over and over again.
So people hear it over and over again.
They start saying,
well, it must be true.
I keep hearing that.
Because the repeat is an emo.
It's kind of like the woodpecker.
Not the woodpecker sound,
but when you're cracking a sidewalk,
it's repetitive hitting
that gets the job done.
The only thing worse than a woodpecker
is a two-headed woodpecker, but yeah, go ahead.
So when you say the word person,
they think it's a people
because they're emotionally attached to it.
Where in legal and in law,
it doesn't mean that at all,
because if you look at old documents
that were written in law,
they said the people of the United States.
Never use the word person
until they get into the corporate side,
the fictional side.
The people have been taken so far away
for so long
from what they could know,
not what they should know,
because they are where they should be.
There's an emotional attachment
to the word person.
They think it involves them.
They don't know the definition of it,
just like the word nice.
They have an emotional attachment
that nice is something positive.
That's my point.
There's an emotional attachment there.
It doesn't matter what the word really means
or what it actually applies to
because they think...
It's the emotion attached to the word, the sound.
For example, when you ask someone
your name, you know what you're really asking them,
what sound do you answer to?
Yeah, of course.
Right?
I was at a Chinese restaurant once
and the woman was obviously very Chinese from China.
Just came here.
Barely spoke enough English.
By the way, in China they have
schools to prepare you
for coming to America to work in the restaurant business
specifically.
It's a crash course for two weeks.
I've heard this before.
I've never seen it for myself,
but I've heard this before.
Yeah, and also in China men do the cooking.
But anyway,
you won't see a woman cooking in a Chinese restaurant ever.
They're always the waiters or wives.
Yeah, I was just going to say,
I don't think I've ever seen a woman cook
in a Chinese restaurant,
whether it's the old-fashioned ones.
You remember there were the old-fashioned ones
with the red tablecloths
and the guys all had the same uniform?
Yeah, that's the stereotypical one.
Yeah, like the one you saw
in the movie Christmas Story
when they do the...
Yeah, they all wear black.
They wear tuxedos, bow ties, white shirts, black pants.
Velvet, red velvet.
Yeah, but whether it's that
or it's the strip mall style one
now where everybody's in a t-shirt
and the kids are there too,
I've always seen the men do the cooking anyway.
Never women.
I was going to go work at a Chinese restaurant.
By the way, Asian people love my food.
I was close to a Vietnamese restaurant here.
I helped them out.
One day I said,
I'm going to cook dinner and I came home.
I cooked it here and I brought it in.
And the waiter got in trouble
because he kept saying in Vietnamese
how good my food was, especially my fried rice.
And he got in trouble with the owner.
He said, what are you talking about?
We have fried rice here.
He got kind of shamed.
But I've done this for more than one Asian restaurant.
I kind of befriended them and then cooked for them
and they were amazed.
They were amazed that I could work a wok
because I could hear them.
For example,
Vietnamese and Chinese happened.
I approached the wok. They were really busy.
I said, I'll make the meal.
They're like, no, no, no.
They saw me working the wok and they all stopped
and started talking to each other.
I don't believe this white boy could do it.
Look at this white boy. He's got skills.
They gave me mad respect after that.
But anyway,
where was I going with this?
Sound you answer to.
I saw her
and I said,
her name tag said Jane.
J-A-N-E.
I said, what's your name in Chinese?
She said, Ting.
Very simple.
You would spell that T-S-A-N-E,
let's say phonetically.
Ting, not Jane.
Jane ended up being really close.
She was fortunate.
You could pick an English name
or Romanized English name,
American name
that's very close to your original name.
That's why one of the biggest tell-tale signs
that they really fucked up the Bible
is when you look at the names
of the prophets
and what they changed them to.
Yeshayahu is Isaiah.
Come on, guys.
No.
They're trying to tell you
what's going on,
but they can't define it for you.
People just go along with it.
I can't underscore
this enough.
How important the emotional attachment
is to the meanings of words
that you think they mean, not their proper meaning.
We've done enough talk
about the emo.
You can actually drive people,
control people,
whether they know the
correct meaning of the word or not
by what emotion is attached
to that word.
Nice is the easiest one.
They even have shirts and bumper stickers.
I saw one recently that said,
Have a nice day.
With a smiley face.
They'll take it momentarily.
That's why I always tell them
to look it up themselves
if they have a stupid rectangle.
What's a stupid rectangle?
The reason I don't like
defining it is because when someone
looks something up, they do it with a little effort.
Now they're a little invested
and it has 70-80% more punch
when they look it up themselves.
Then they go right back
to the little red flashy thing
in Men in Black.
I talk to people and say,
That's incredible.
I give people in public
2 or 3 minutes, 5 minutes, 10 minutes
of Greek speak.
That's wonderful. Thank you.
I say, You're not going to remember a thing I said once I walk away.
They're like, Huh?
I actually do tell them that.
You're not going to remember a damn thing
you heard here once I leave.
That's why I've been able to repeatedly do the whole thing
where I look at the etymology.
The etymology website, I love that by the way.
Etymology online or whatever it's called.
It's bookmarked.
Sure.
The dictionary is diction.
How you should pronounce.
That's why when you look up a word in the dictionary
it always shows the phonetic spelling first
and then the common definition.
Not the etymology.
Sometimes they give some etymology.
The only reason why they do that
is to give you an indicator
as to identify the word
specifically.
That's why it's like that.
The purpose of the dictionary
was to create uniformity in society.
Because they were going for the industrial age.
Yeah, that's the uniformity.
The oldest dictionary you can find
is the Industrial Revolution.
There were no dictionaries before that.
You were educated or not.
The dictionaries are a product
of the Industrial Revolution
because what they did
was they didn't
gauge people on character.
They gauged people with a stopwatch.
In other words, you showed up to work,
they put a stopwatch on you.
Your character was not important
because how many pieces you made per hour
times how much they could sell them for
equals this.
They wanted productive workers.
Ford was not the first assembly line.
It was Dodge.
But Dodge didn't move the cars.
He moved the people.
Ford moved the cars and didn't move the people.
As a matter of fact,
Ford, from the history
there are several things I can talk about Ford.
I studied him a lot in the 80s.
He did a free
energy thing too. You could probably
still find it online. It's called the cow magnet.
I'm not going to get into the
free energy that he did.
If you bought a Model T or a Model A
after you owned it for a certain while, he secretly
sent you a box of cow
magnets and instructions.
See all those holes around the cow
that everyone asks what that's for?
You put these magnets in there and then you'll find out.
Basically, I'm not going to get into it.
But once the engine warmed up
and you had the cow magnets in there, it just ran and ran
and ran with no fuel. Very little fuel.
Basically, the vapors. In other words, if your
gas tank, which was the size of a large
coffee can in those days,
ran out of fuel, there was enough vapors
in there to run it for as far as you wanted to go.
But you could look it up. Ford cow
magnets. So you wouldn't believe
how many people that are car historians have never heard
of it. It may not even be online.
Who knows? This is what
the benefit of reading old books.
But the king
of old books on the Internet is archaics,
by the way, not me.
I'm pretty much telling you what I've
read, and I'll paraphrase, and you can find it great
if not tough shit. Because I ain't
going back to the New York City Public Library.
The main one with the lions outside on 42nd
and right
by the park there.
Yeah, is that even there anymore?
You know that Bryant Park, by the way, by the library?
They spend a quarter of a million dollars
a year on the flowers and the landscaping
of Little Park.
Yeah, and they also spend another
quarter of a million a year on maintaining
the bathroom. Have you been in the bathroom in Bryant Park?
I don't remember being there.
It's like a luxury hotel. It's a public bathroom.
It's a New York City Public
Park bathroom. It's like being in a luxury hotel.
Is that one of those things with the couch in it
and all that? Is it like that?
No, no couch. It's just all marble gold fixtures.
Yeah, it's beautiful.
There's an attendant. Super clean.
Then they have the automatic
down by City Hall. They have the automatic bathrooms
that look like these big stainless steel cylinders.
You go in there and once you're done using
it, it seals it up.
No one can go in there for a minute and
it sprays down the whole thing.
It dries it and then the next person can go in.
Are you familiar with that one?
No, I've never seen that either.
So anyway, I used to go to the library there
and Henry Ford
worked with Dodge.
This is his story. This is very easily
to access and he left the company.
He took his name and
he still ordered engines
and things from Dodge.
When he ordered engines, he specified
they should be crated
in a certain kind of wood and a certain species
of wood and when the engines
came, not in those specified
crates,
he sent them back because he
salvaged the wood from the crate
to put the wood into the body because there were
real wood sides on cars in those days.
This is how stringent
he was and how cheap he was.
He was a real bastard too.
Henry Ford, but you look where
it got him.
It's the real bastards
in the world. The real hard, like Vanderbilt
was a real bastard.
When there were strikes and stuff like that
with Vanderbilt, he just paid the army to go
and shoot everybody. There were
massacres and strikes back in the day.
Many industrialists paid all sorts
of different people to just go in and either
beat somebody to death with shovels or shoot
them. That's right. It was brutal.
Also, what was it?
The fruit company.
The American fruit company where they killed
2,000 workers picking bananas.
You could look it up. Massacre.
United Fruit and then they were followed by...
Yeah, United Fruit. There you go.
And the sugar company right after.
That's what I was going to say.
You're domino sugar today.
Right. Go ahead.
You're dealing with some people who say,
oh, good old days. No, it wasn't.
It was brutal. It was brutality. Extreme
brutality. Law is great,
but if you're
subject to it and you're on the wrong...
If you have witnesses, it's brutal.
You don't want to be under it on the wrong side.
In West Virginia and Kentucky
alone, over 10,000 people were killed
over tobacco fields,
by the way, just during a little
time of consolidation.
A consolidation with the tobacco
companies.
A company
in Labor Day.
These farmers
wanted to sell their tobacco at a different
price. They thought they could bring it to price
for a different market.
And then the big company
said, that's not the price that we're going to
endorse. So therefore
they just sent people onto their farms.
Like I said, they would beat them to death
with pharmacopoeia. It didn't matter.
Right now,
disturbing commerce
is the highest crime in the current system.
It's like
literally 10,000 bodies on that.
And people don't even talk about it.
It was literally like a domestic war
that nobody writes about.
They don't know about it.
Like we said earlier, if they don't know something, it doesn't exist.
Right? Exactly.
Not only do you make them aware of it,
it's not just making them aware of it.
Some people, maybe like us,
just have to hear something
that can be referenced,
and it sounds, trusted from a trusted
source is good enough, usually.
But I still would check it out if I took interest
in repeating it, right?
You know, Pearl Harbor
in the U.S., Douglas Dietrich
is good on this.
You know, the Japanese did not attack
the U.S. They were trying to free,
they attacked the U.S. trying to free the kingdom
of Hawaii, right? Because the Marines had the
kingdom of Hawaii under house arrest.
The king had already died. They had the queen.
Right? And
it was also a cover. What you don't hear
about is the Japanese took over
the Aleutian Islands a day or two later,
a week later, and the reason they did
that, and they didn't leave
until after the war.
The reason they took the Aleutian Islands is because
if the Americans, they knew they were going to go
into a full-blown war with the Americans, and it was going to be
an aerial war. If the Americans had the
Aleutian Islands, it would have been an hour and a half
flight, hop, skip, and a jump to Japan.
So because they held the Aleutian Islands,
the Americans had to go
island hopping through 7,000
miles of islands for refuel, right?
You had to keep refueling to get there, yeah.
So it's very simple. It says the Japanese won
the war. Of course they did. You don't even have to
be told that. You could look it up on Wikipedia.
All the various battles
that are listed in Wikipedia
between the Americans and the Japanese, I think there's
like 20 battles listed, and 17
out of the 20, or 16 out of
the 20 are favored the Japanese.
So the Americans only got 3 out of 20, right?
Or 2 out of 10.
So it's very simple, and you know
the Mustang, the
plane, the real killer plane
the Americans made, the PT Mustang
or whatever it was, copied the old
they couldn't make that until they got
enough Japanese Zeros to reverse engineer.
So anyway,
the whole, but people, again,
this is an example that the Americans
lost World War II. You can't, who are you going to tell
this to? It's stunning to tell this to anyone,
you know, because they, you know,
right? So...