Sonic Event 74, you know, it's funny, I keep making that same mistake at the beginning,
now it's become the intro accidentally.
And that's okay, sometimes patterns are meant to emerge a certain way, and sometimes you're
meant to break them, and I gotta tell you, it's inspiration.
Anyway, maybe we'll get to that, maybe we'll get to some other things.
Greek, how you doing tonight?
I'm doing all right.
Any messages we should look at?
Anything we got noteworthy?
I did get one, I was gonna see if you wanted to record something short, but you know, we
could just combine this all together into one, and, well, still make it short if we
want, I mean, we can go any direction you want to.
The only odd thing I got in a message, which I wasn't sure if I should bring up to you,
is, you know, look, I've separated myself from participating in a whole lot of rituals
and things like this, this is the message that I got.
And I'm still surrounded by people doing, you know, Christmas.
That's fine, it's fine.
I'm going to talk a little bit about something like that, which we also did on episode 47.
Yeah, yeah, so, but the thing is, I'm still surrounded by people doing Christmas, and
I'm out of place, you know, how should I handle this?
Because I have a want to be kind of mean about it, but I don't want to be mean about it.
Yeah, so, go ahead.
Very, very simple.
I've been running all week, not into the Christmas thing, because usually here, there's some
spiritual protection that you get after a while, or maybe you get it before you know,
or after or during you know what's going on.
I'd be standing at the register for checkout and register, you know, the cashiers wishing
everybody a Merry Christmas after the transaction, right?
I get up there, do the transaction, have a good day, and they don't even know me.
It's almost like it doesn't apply.
We all know intuitively what's right and wrong with every individual, let's say.
But what I wanted to bring up, well, a couple of things we before we got on, we started
talking about burdock and food and all that.
Yeah.
And I don't like to say I told you so, but anybody who's done the rice number seven or
number eight, I told you so.
It has nothing to do with, hey, this is how you make this dish, you know, to taste good.
It has nothing to do with taste, but it will end up tasting good.
No, but you know how to do that too.
Yeah, you know how to do that too.
You know how to make things to taste, but that isn't what this is particularly about, which
is funny because look, if I got a report back that, hey, this sucks, I would definitely call
you out on it.
But no, everyone, you do get the energy.
Excuse me.
You do get the energy and the vitality and what would you say, revitalization and recuperation
properties if you keep it up.
Right.
Because we're, you know, you actually end up, the humans were made to eat grain.
We were made as grain eaters.
And it's funny how they, you know, oh, well, the grain is carbs.
It's not, you know, I think I've gone over this other thing as a carb or protein.
There is, but it's just one little nitrogen atom.
If you look at the molecule, it's the same thing.
It's a scam.
Well, some people have also taken the idea that, look, you feed the grains to animals
and we're not like other animals.
Well, no, but some people want to go with a whole, you know, look, I'm a special animal
route.
And I mean, physiologically, are we all that much different when you get down to it, the
mechanics when it comes to nutrition and feeding a body?
Are we actually all that much different from a lot of other animals?
Maybe not so much, right?
We are.
Yeah, we don't.
Well, you can go to many directions on that.
We are, but we are not an animal per se, either, because the spirit is not.
Remember, the animals are very different.
They come downloaded, pre downloaded software programs, operating systems.
We don't remember.
But is the food the same way?
See, that's the thing.
Is the food the same way?
Yes.
All that other stuff.
So what you're telling me is that we come still blank slate pretty much at that point.
OK.
Go ahead.
We're like those empty hard cases or whatever, but we will adapt to whatever food we eat.
You know how they show the eagle being very noble, you know, on the American thing or whatever.
I don't know if anyone's lived in an area where the eagles are naturally, you know,
inhabitant.
You know, I stayed up in the White Mountains in Arizona and they have a very large eagle
population.
I've seen them try to hunt at the lake and all that.
But most of the time they were scavengers.
What do I mean?
You leave the garbage can lid open.
An eagle will go into it.
There's roadkill.
An eagle will go eat it.
It sounds like seagulls, man.
Seagulls do the same thing.
Yeah, exactly.
Very much so.
Yeah.
So they're scavengers.
But it doesn't sound very noble if you call them a scavenger.
So anyway.
Yeah.
So we've got that trade as well.
But yeah, I just want to bring up the food part is very important because it's what you
are, what you ate.
And you kind of go that way regardless, you know, whether if you if you want to eat well
or not, you're going to, you know, anyway, you know, it's about blood quality, really.
Well, yeah.
But you don't need to feed this to your cat, though.
You know, I mean, right.
They'll eat it.
Yeah.
Well, you know, I remember hanging out in Manhattan near Thompson Square Park and the
Krishnas would show up in their school bus every so often and give out free food.
Yeah.
Once a week.
Once a week they sit down.
And if you'll sit and listen to their thing, they will bring out a tin of completely vegetarian
food.
In Tompkins Square.
Yeah.
Right there on Avenue A.
And they park along Avenue A facing south and they come out and they play, you know, the
little finger drums and they're chanting and serve food.
And it was the most delicious food I've ever eaten.
We're talking like 1986.
Right.
Yeah.
Well, even still in the 90s, because I live between 1st and A on 9th Street.
And believe me, I could just walk right there every I think it was every Thursday they were
there.
Yeah.
Once a week, roughly.
I was on 11th Street between 2nd and 3rd.
There you go.
Not too far.
You and I could have been the same bodegas, except it was a decade apart.
But good.
Yeah.
Anyway.
And the food was I was like, my gosh, this is so delicious.
You know, I realized right there, you know, so the veg, you know, being total veg, only
veg, there's no onion, you know, they use hang, you know, because the onion sucks your spirit
right down and all this.
But anyway, I was talking to one of them.
So once food is really good, it says, yeah, it's spiced in a way that only humans would
eat.
In other words, so what do you mean if you're eating this at the beach and you threw it
on the sand, the seagulls, you know, the crabs or wouldn't eat it.
So they have a spice profile that is strictly for humans.
It's just, you know, that's the spirit, you know, the mental notion behind it.
Right.
So it's spice specifically the Vedic way.
Vedic means knowledge, by the way.
That only fit for human.
Again, if you scavenger would not find it appropriate.
So that's why that came up because you asked if you could feed it to the cats.
And I was like, well, if you really do Vedic food that's tailored for just humans, you
know, tailored specifically, you know, we're talking about traditions that go thousands
of years.
The cat wouldn't eat it.
The dog wouldn't eat it.
The seagull wouldn't eat it.
The mouse, the rat wouldn't eat it.
Right.
So that's another level.
And this is sort of on that level, but without spices.
And again, when I speak about microbiotics, I really don't like using that term because
they're very dogmatic.
If you watch some of the Michio Kushi, one of his last lectures, he starts bringing up
stuff that he was against.
Or, you know, it seems like people get to the end of their life and they realize that
it's time to loosen up a little.
You know, so I never I never bought whenever I heard dogma and rigidity.
I always called it out and I never went for that.
So hence the lascivious comments once in a while.
But yeah, what I wanted to talk about was I noticed that.
OK, what do we do?
Let's go back.
OK, let's go back to what you said.
What do we do about Christmas without getting or what you do is very simple.
OK.
Somebody wished me Merry Christmas the other day.
And I said, you too.
But I want to tell you, I reap the I reap the benefits of it, but I don't fall for I have
without getting the pitfalls.
Right.
And the person didn't want me to explain what that was.
So, in other words, let's say there's a big part.
Let's just do it this way.
This is a big party in the middle of the week that everyone does for the great pumpkin in
the sky.
And every middle of the week or right before the middle of the week, everybody gathers
and they bring out they have to cook organic, delicious food for the great pumpkin in the
sky.
So go ahead and eat some of it and you get the benefits.
But when it comes time to do reaching to your pocket for the great pumpkin in the sky.
No.
When it comes time to write, do all these other things for the to support the great
pumpkin in the sky organization, you tell them, fuck yourself.
Right.
But when they're giving out stuff for free and having a good time, you go there.
So what you're saying is I can go to a birthday party, but I don't have to participate in
the ritual or give a crap about that.
Yeah.
Go and I'll bring a gift or anything.
So if you go to a Christmas party, it's packed with people.
Cop a couple of feels on, you know, and then leave.
Have some pizza, have a couple of drinks, even a piece of cake.
Yeah.
And then take off.
But don't participate in the game is what you're saying.
Right.
In other words, reap the benefits without those also.
Without without having to feed the monster.
Right.
Okay.
Fair enough.
So my apologies for your squeak in the back, because I do have a box full of puppies.
I got seven puppies, little itty bitties.
Again, a couple of days.
Oh, my gosh.
Yeah.
I got a house full of dogs.
Just you wait.
Actually, about four weeks, they get even more chewable.
They'll find any anything that's below waist height.
They're going to chew on.
You know, I absolutely know.
That's why I'm going to try and find homes for them.
They're mighty many months.
But anyway, sorry.
I just want to know about clothing, laundry, anything, you know, armrests on chairs.
If it smells like oil or an animal, they will eat it.
Yeah.
So, yeah, I know.
I know.
But anyway, I was just so squeaky noise.
Sorry.
Go ahead.
Yes.
A very simple like, you know, someone gave me these to give me Christmas gifts.
And I said, look, I'll take you can transmute these things to here's a birthday gift or
a Christmas gift.
I say, well, look, I'll receive it if it's true as tribute.
Right.
It's OK.
How would you would would you give it to me as tribute?
Well, let's say yes.
They just transmuted.
It's no longer.
And you know what tribute is.
Right.
Well, hang on.
I mean, let's put a pin in tribute because I want to continue on with this concept.
Let's get back to tribute in a minute, because what you're saying is to this person who's
worried about the fact that he's got people with Christmas all around him is that he could
participate in, you know, getting the benefits of it, like you said.
But he doesn't have to embrace the ritual.
Now, does that mean.
Right.
No, you're not participating in the ritual.
See, if you're just going there to reap the benefits, you sound like the IRS now.
Right.
Well, what I mean is you're just taking the benefits.
You're not taking you're participating in the ritual at all because part of the participation
is give and take.
You're just going there to take.
They're stupid enough to do that.
They're definitely stupid enough for you to take and not give them anything.
So let me say, OK, OK, when you run into what you're doing business, if you run into someone
who's a bonafide sucker, in other words, they whatever color their skin is, they've got
sucker in all caps, tattooed on their forehead, the same color of their skin.
You know, I'm talking about.
Oh, yeah.
OK.
Right.
So white guy would have sucker tattooed in white.
On his forehead.
Someone I once said so is I didn't see such a sucker tattooed on the forehead.
So like, hey, dummy, I mean, because, you know, for sure.
OK, you take their money.
Why?
Because if you don't take their money, they're a sucker.
Remember, they're going to give it to someone else.
They'll find somebody.
And it's better than you take it than someone else, because they're going to lose their
money anyway.
Well, OK, I understand that.
And believe me, I heard that mentality said to me several times from various Italian businessmen.
But the thing, you know, because that's the deal.
Look, if they're not going to give it to me, they're going to give it to somebody else
anyway.
So you might as well be.
Yeah.
And that's how I was taught when I was young.
But another thing I was taught when I was young, which I want to run by you in this
context is I always was taught to to try and be respectful of where other people are at.
If you're going to deal with them, if you're actually going to do business with them or
interact now on one level, when you're going and you're dealing with a cashier, you're
doing business with them.
Right.
It's not their business, but their job is there.
That's what they're occupied with.
So, you know, you get through there politely by acknowledging stuff.
Right.
I mean, I used to say assalamu alaikum to people who were Muslims and I'm not a Muslim.
I never have been.
Not even close.
You do that out of respect.
I think I mentioned a Korean client here shy on the English.
And I said, oh, I'm going to come here to hang some artwork.
His wife's relatives were old Korean royalty before the Americans got there.
And they had some priceless stuff they wanted hung.
Anyway, I learned some Korean when I went there just out of respect.
And he felt so comfortable.
He was so uptight with everyone.
But he was very comfortable with me because I just took some time out.
I mean, you can make somebody happy if they don't, you know, English is not their first
language and you learn to just say simple things like that.
You do it out of respect, just like you send a diplomat right over or representative.
Right.
But you simple, you know, thank you.
Excuse me.
And how are you today, sir?
You know, basic stuff.
If you learn that in their language, it's a way of showing respect and it's a way of
making them more comfortable.
But that's not acquiescing to all of their rituals.
Right.
I mean, so where's the line is what I'm getting.
No, I won't eat dog.
Like.
All right.
Give me an example.
Like, I'm very fond of the Vietnamese.
I've worked with Vietnamese.
Right.
Sure.
And I could kick it in Vietnamese.
And very often with when I'm with the wife or I say, watch this.
And she knows what I'm going to ask.
I'm going to say, I'm going to tell.
And basically, that means, do you eat dog?
And they say sometimes, like, can you please say it again?
And they're like, no way.
Nobody else around us knows what I asked.
Or sometimes they'll say not here, meaning in the US.
Right.
And I'm like, whoa, that's cool.
He's honest.
Right.
So he does eat dog, but not here.
Honk again.
So anyway, it's a very simple language.
But so.
Well, I read it.
I read it.
Take whatever you want.
It's give and take.
Right.
But in this case, you're just going to go there and reap the benefit.
Look, if they're stupid enough to do it, that's what I'm going to get into.
Let's get into.
Let's just segue.
Because this is better.
This is better.
Sure.
Let's segue.
OK, so you've got you've subverted the power structure of one country.
You're a private group.
No one knows who you are.
I was talking about someone asked me, what about Elon Musk?
Elon Musk existed as Elon Musk.
Everything.
Everyone talks about him 50 years before he was born.
He just fits the role.
He has a handler.
And the moment Elon Musk says, I don't want to play anymore.
Suddenly, every news station is going to have the same story that they found cocaine like
DeLorean on him.
Right.
Or child porn or somebody.
He raped four women.
Something terrible is going to remove three women.
See, they do this with rock stars, too.
The same thing with rock stars.
Like for a little while, they influence the culture.
They are the king of the genre.
They are the pop star.
No, no.
They do that with everyone.
I brought up DeLorean because when I bring up cocaine, that was that time.
Now, they wouldn't do cocaine.
They would do other things that socially, you know, in the in the mix.
Right.
Because in the 80s, cocaine was in the mix.
Cocaine is an 80s thing.
But that's a hell of a drug.
Is that by the way?
Cocaine is a hell of a drug.
Rick James.
Look at this thing.
He fit perfectly with that.
Anyway, look, what I'm saying is, though, is that there are certain roles out there
where there are people like that.
And it's not about the person exactly.
It's about the role.
Donald Trump.
Hold on.
That's why when you were going off with this lady that's got a New York accent all the
time about Donald Trump, I tuned in.
I was like, oh, my gosh, Chuck, don't you know that Donald Trump is a puppet?
He's a TV actor.
Right.
Just like the rest of them.
That's my point about the guy, actually.
It's exactly my point about it.
But so is the one with a New York accent.
You want to see a real TV actor before there was TV?
Sure.
There's a there's there's a YouTube video.
Lift up.
I think it's Coolidge.
He was one of the.
Maybe not Coolidge.
Maybe.
No, it wasn't cool.
One of these presidents in the 1920s, an early film, not 1920s, 1930s.
It's a film on YouTube.
Very short.
President U.S. talks about people should start filing to the IRS.
And he looks like a zombie.
He's like, do you remember the the trope with Bill Clinton?
They're putting makeup on him.
He looks like he's in a trance.
Talk about MK Ultra.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
I'm almost certain you're talking about Woodrow Wilson.
But go ahead.
No, it wasn't Wilson.
It was after his two presidents after Wilson.
It was before Roosevelt, I think, or after Roosevelt.
No, it's before Roosevelt because after Roosevelt was the Truman Eisenhower stuff.
Right.
Before Hoover.
It wasn't Hoover.
It was somebody early on between Wilson.
It's a film because it's very rare.
And he's like a zombie and he's looking like.
Right.
So there are George Washington.
OK.
Sorry, George Washington.
He was killed early on in the Revolutionary War.
They found his body frozen solid.
They buried him right where the monument is in Brooklyn at Brooklyn Heights.
There is a little monument right by the promenade.
And it's a tribute to where the battle of Brooklyn, a battle of where the British chased
them out.
Right.
Well, anyway, they went back.
There was a battle anyway.
They replaced George Washington with a lookalike.
The problem was the lookalike didn't have any teeth in his mouth.
So they spent so much effort to put teeth in his mouth.
Right.
It's like George Washington lost all his teeth.
Wait a second.
And then when he started going to the Freemasonic rituals, he was like, you know, I'm tired of
this.
Guess what?
They bled him to death.
Right.
The the the the the second one.
So this has been going on for a while.
Another thing, Napoleon.
Napoleon was not banished to an island and died.
He had a brother who looked just like him.
His brother took his place and Napoleon came to the US and lived here, you know, because
Incidentally, Taft is the only guy in between.
Theodore.
It must have been.
Thank you.
It's probably Taft.
Yeah.
OK.
It must be Taft.
Go watch it.
It's a YouTube video.
Find it.
Talking about people will follow.
Everybody laughed at that.
Right.
OK.
And that's what the IRS does, by the way.
They find people that are high every 10 years.
They get someone that's high profile and they beat him up in public.
And we talked about this to get everyone scared.
Right.
OK.
But that's not what I wanted to talk about.
Let's go back because it sounds like a mega tangent.
And I and I do go on mega tangents.
But it's OK.
So go around to the same thing.
So we're getting there.
Don't worry about it.
Yeah.
OK.
So you're you're a private group.
And when people when you have someone ask you, who is their handler?
Says once you find out who they are, they're no longer a handler.
Right.
So this group has been running this influencing.
There are several groups.
The power structure of a nation.
Well, could they they successfully do one, two, three, four, five, six.
And they now they've got been running for over 150 years.
All the power structures of all the nations.
Right now, all the puppets that are the government's kings, whatever.
And some of the kings and people didn't want to play.
So between the 1700s and the World War II, they got rid of all the monarchies and all
that stuff, too.
And if any monarchy that's left is down with them.
Right.
So anyway.
What they do is when they're in control, you need a security structure and a
policing structure to make sure that when you give an order, it's done.
And if it starts to not be done, how do you structure?
You know, what kind of enforcement structure do you have?
Right.
So you have to.
That's why I always refer to them as policy enforcers, because police.
No, no, no.
That's what they do.
That's way down.
That's the secondary group.
I'm talking about the primary group.
Now, the primary group that runs all the governments behind the scenes also need a
security apparatus and an enforcement apparatus.
So all the state departments and presidents do their thing right now.
If you're going to develop an apparatus like that, you have to learn how much you
have to find out.
Engage.
How much do you invest in that apparatus apparatus?
Because it's intelligence agencies also.
Right.
And then eventually you'll find out it's also the schools and it's the churches
and it's the media.
Right.
And when I say schools, I mean universities also, because when you have a grade
school teachers teaching, they usually have the college degrees.
So you got to get them there.
So you to find that instead of setting up a separate security apparatus or
whatever, how much how much discernment the population has, what you do is you
start putting out total bullshit information, stuff that is unfounded.
And you see what the reaction in public is.
Will they go for it?
Like you tell them there's a big bang.
The sky is blue because it reflects the color of the ocean.
Right.
You tell them that, you know, you absorb nutrition through the intestine.
You tell them they have an electron that spins around the atom and it's a slow,
slow cousin, the proton and its fat brother, the neutron.
It's all stupid.
I mean, stuff that, you know, is beyond any reason.
Right. And you watch the reaction.
You watch the reaction.
If everybody absorbs all that and goes along with it, you need a minimal
security policing apparatus, minimal.
Absolutely.
If you tell them everybody get on the roof on Monday.
And what do we do now?
Tune in at seven.
All right.
Now jump 40 percent of the population that jump off the bill.
Wow.
Do we need to start enforcing and policing?
It's like a percentage of people that when they said, you know, AIDS is this
big disease that's killing you.
Well, what happens?
What does the disease do?
Well, nothing.
It actually doesn't do anything.
Other diseases kill you.
The disease is ignorance.
If you cure ignorance, there'll be no AIDS.
Well, there is.
There is STDs.
That's different.
No, no, no, no, no.
There's plenty of those.
There's like 18 different varieties.
But what I'm saying is that most people get STDs, get the treatment for AIDS
and they tell them they died of AIDS, which actually died from the epithelial
drugs from the problem, from the treatment.
It's the treatment that kills you, not the illness.
Yeah. The treatment, again, just to reiterate, when a cell is replaced in
the body, you have cells that replace themselves in 30 minutes.
You have other cells that take seven years to replace.
It releases a hormone.
It's a form of whatever you want to call it.
A simple way to say it's a hormone to let the body know, hey, I'm replaced.
So what they do is they give you that hormone.
So when the cell naturally dies and falls off, when you take that hormone, it
thinks the cell has been replaced and it hasn't.
So it stops growing new cells, whatever region of the body.
Oh, my gosh.
So you look like you've got a starvation diet.
You start getting sores and most likely your lungs will fall apart and die of
pneumonia, which are typical.
Or if you're very young, you'll have these fat tumors develop that will kill
you. All right.
I mean, if you're two years old and you get a fat tumor in your head the size
of an orange, it'll kill you.
Right. So this is how they're killing people and getting away with it.
And the doctors, they know this, by the way.
The ones that are at the top of this, they know.
And by the way, how do you know AIDS is a total scam?
Most doctors did not find about it through a medical journal.
They found about it like everybody else watching television in 1980.
Yeah. Watching the.
And then they went watching TV.
They're like, what's this?
And they start then they started the ones that inquired, they fed them the
bullshit. There is no study, medical study on that, that the doctors received.
They got it just like right.
They got it like everybody got 9-11 and covid.
No. And I recently tried to on TV.
I recently tried to explain this to somebody.
And to tell you the truth, the conversation ended with me saying, you know,
what you're talking about is hepatitis.
It's not even this imaginary AIDS.
And besides.
But what is hepatitis?
It's a it's a pathogen pathological condition of what?
The liver.
Yeah, exactly.
But that's the thing.
And but liver pathologies.
It's not AIDS.
It's just over and over.
They're telling me all these different symptoms of what happens.
And I said, those are the behaviors.
The behaviors, the exposure, everything is the same as.
So what do you think?
AIDS is not.
But hold on.
AIDS is not AIDS.
There is no immune system.
If you ask someone to explain the immune system.
Good luck.
You know what they're really explaining?
No.
What they're really explaining is the eliminative system.
Yeah.
But that's the thing that filters things out, which again, gets back to what?
No, there's no filtering.
There's no filtering.
Well, it's the elimination system.
But that's what I grab it.
OK.
How do they do garbage in Star Trek?
They open the thing and dump it out or they put it on the transporter and send it somewhere
through the transporter.
No, but that's my point, is that it's through a system that grabs all the crap and takes
it out and does what?
Sends it out.
It literally does not take anything.
It sends it out.
In other words, it reproduces it on the specific body parts that are made to handle it.
The waste management part.
And it reproduces it in there.
So in other words, yeah.
In other words, the induction works both ways.
I hope people got that.
I've never really got into, you know, I only got into showing the stark example of nothing
passing through the intestinal lumina, intestinal walls into the body.
What happens is the right is it's by induction.
The food actually de-energizes into the blood vessels around the intestines.
Right.
But I never got into how things get out.
They get out the same way.
Right.
The pores in the skin develop moisture inside of them, just like a thundercloud develops
rain before it.
Right.
And then it's ejected.
And that energy that's required to create that material as waste is gotten from the
right makes the stuff on the inside disappear.
And isn't that another that's another kind of induction anyway, because look, when you
look at a big old cloud over your head, it's not carrying around millions of gallons of
water.
No, it couldn't.
It would be fog.
It would hit the ground just at 27 feet per second.
Right.
Because that's actually towards the ground at 27 feet per second, because that's actual
water in the air.
When you got water in the air, it becomes a mist or a fog.
And that's different because that's that's there.
That's water vapor.
Yeah.
There is no water in the cloud.
Right.
Like I mean, as such.
OK.
Anyway, sorry.
Sorry.
We got away from this whole thing with Christmas and the cashiers.
And again, you know, when so the when they're saying to you, have a nice day because they
intuitively have picked up.
Maybe this isn't the guy to bring it to.
Now, I'm sure that doesn't work 100 percent of the time.
Sometimes somebody will say to you, Merry Christmas or whatever, because they're on
auto.
Right.
I mean, they're not really.
No, we didn't.
We didn't get away.
No.
This is part of the security apparatus.
It's part of the security apparatus.
In other words, everybody, if you watch a documentary on Christmas Day, tell you everybody
knows that it's not December 25th when J.E.S.
U.S. was born.
But it's a pagan holiday.
The biggest Christmas documentaries on PBS say that just like when they bring up dinosaurs.
It was 60 million years ago.
Now it's 65.
And then it became recently 66.
Right.
Because six, six is very important.
By the way, I recently talked to someone who was teaching a yoga class and what and they
specifically said no refunds.
But a woman decided her church told her while she was taking the classes that it's satanic
and not to do it.
And he didn't want to have problems with her.
He said, you know, there's no refund.
You agreed to that.
But, you know, I'll give you if you think it's satanic.
I'll do a religious exemption kind of thing.
I'll give you your money back.
So he reaches into his checkbook and refunds her the the refunds her the tuition because
she thought in her church told her was satanic two weeks into the classes.
And guess what number was with an off plan.
Guess what number you get one guess.
The check number was six, six, six.
That's right.
And he gave it and she didn't say anything.
She didn't notice.
And she cashed it.
So how funny can it be?
So you see that you see the side, the different sides to this.
Right.
I mean, it flips, you know, yin and yang.
Well, yeah.
And there's always an irony attached to any of this stuff, which which is always hilarious
to me.
Like a lot of times the people that think that they, you know, suddenly struck it rich, but
they did it through, you know, ill gotten means.
They often pay for it because.
Yeah.
But look, let's let's go back to the whole thing.
So they put this false narrative out.
It's been going on for thousands of years and everybody goes for it because it's a good
time.
All right.
So now if you want to do another narrative that you're going to have to wear a mask because
they got these little viruses around, are you worried about people not believing it?
I don't know.
They're going to believe it.
So it's part the Christmas, the covid, the 9-11, all of that is part of the inner core
security apparatus to test and see now what happens when you have people that don't go
for it.
Oh, there are the whack jobs.
There are the nut jobs.
They're ignorant.
They're not trained.
Right.
Or.
And the ultimate is, oh, they're terrorists.
Right.
That's the worst.
Being called a terrorist now.
Right.
So.
So this is part of the security apparatus has been going on for a long, long time.
So instead of looking at it as Christmas holiday or covid or AIDS or you got to pay taxes or
whatever, it's part of the security apparatus, which, by the way, speaking of the trigger
word terrorist, just really quickly, I was looking at a documentary on Vietnam and, you
know, the U.S. military.
And it's so funny to me that they were using pretty much the same terms that they were
and calling the Vietnamese terrorists, by the way, the North Vietnamese, they were
terrorists.
Good.
Yeah.
Before.
It started after the 50s.
Yeah.
In the 60s.
Right.
Yeah.
Before that, they called them insurgents or whatever.
You know, most people think they mixed it around.
But what I'm saying is when when they started to battle it and they started making these
films in the early 60s and they were talking about the stuff that had gone on just post
World War Two, which is when the conflict actually started in Vietnam, you know, with
the French and all that.
And we had been food.
But anyway, the bottom line is that they were saying that our special forces were there
to do what?
Battle terrorists.
It was the same kind of thing that they said that we had to do in Iraq.
And it's just it's just the same story recycled.
I mean, history.
People think it's a different.
Well, that was a different thing.
They were fighting fighting communism.
Yeah.
But if you take a look at the motivator, it's the terrorists again.
It's always the terrorists.
Well, no, it's a new thing.
You know how things change, like, you know, the Civil War was the war of northern aggression.
And then in the late 1800s, it became the War of the States.
And by the 1920s, it was the Civil War.
Well, what I'm saying is in the modern age, in the modern age where we're, you know, disseminating
things by, you know, what's the next bad word?
The next bad word is going to be something religious.
It's going to be some religious connotation.
I don't know what it is.
I'm sure it's out there already.
Pick one.
Yeah.
And if you stay, it's going to be based on, quote, unquote, your faith or allegiance or
like allegiance.
That's what religion is.
But again, all of these things that you see and now it's gotten to the point where pretty
much all of it is false.
Right.
If if you don't if you hear if you if it's not a report of a dump truck falling over
on I-10 or I-95 or someone getting hit with a, you know, baseball bat in a parking lot,
it's false.
Right.
You know that we know that already, because if you bring this up to, you know, people
like like let's go back to you said the Vietnam recently, I was one of these Vietnam vet morons
in there.
Seventy six years old.
He's actually an inventor and I've known him for almost 20 years and I brought up the draft
is voluntary.
You just don't know what part of the process you're going to be volunteering.
He couldn't remember.
I said when they draft you, it's still voluntary.
It doesn't sound like it because, you know, they have to make you feel, you know, little
and fearful.
But when they've got you standing there after the medical checkup, the physical checkup,
they have everybody walk into a side room in their drawers and in their shirts, underwear
and socks.
And they say, OK, everyone that is going to join the army, take one step forward and everyone
takes a step forward without thinking.
But if you just stand there and don't take that step forward, they have a sergeant come
up to your face and yell at you.
What's wrong with you?
And if you put up with that, they pull you to the side, they say, get your clothes on,
they give you 20 bucks for your bus fare home.
Yep, and they have you down, I forgot what it's called, medically unfit or something,
but it doesn't look bad on your record.
One of these medical.
In other words, you got discharged at the medical point, not at the performance, you
know?
Yeah.
So anyway, and basically says, well, I saw he's like, oh, I was in whatever hostilities
in the field.
I said, I said, have you seen, I said, you were fighting on the wrong side.
And he says, I'm fighting on the wrong side.
I said, yeah, you don't want to be a loser, do you?
And he goes, no, we didn't lose that war.
Yes, you did.
If you even on Wikipedia says Vietnam was united under the northern Vietnam after that.
Right.
Yeah.
Even Wikipedia got it right.
And so you're basically a loser.
Don't you want to be a winner when you fight?
I mean, what you and it's like, you know, I was like, I will leave this guy alone.
So anyway, it's all of it is part of the security apparatus.
The dumbing down is part of the security apparatus.
It has nothing to do with dumbing you down for whatever reason.
Yes.
Rockefeller and those guys said we want Americans not to be educated.
We want a society of workers.
Right.
And all these other things.
That's also part of the thing.
Yeah.
They tell you what's going on, but it's part of the security apparatus.
You got to put out falsities has nothing to do with whether the information is true
or false.
But it has to be false to see what kind of reaction they get, because if the people go
along with the false stuff, guess what?
You don't have to give a reason for anything.
The other part I wanted to maybe a bridge, abbreviate a little bit.
How do they get the information across you with rhyme and reason, rationale, science,
logic?
No.
With images and repetition, 9-11 and repetition, images and repetition.
With the covid, they show you a cartoon of this little spiky thing is actually a dog
toy.
That looks a lot like that spiky ball.
Yeah.
That's true.
I never.
Wow.
You just snap a little on my head.
I never I never thought of it.
But you're exactly right.
There is a common dog toy in.
It's for gums.
It's to stimulate their gums.
No, it's like you think it's actually useful as a dog toy.
But you can see it.
I swear on any like any aisle in a Wal-Mart that has dog toys or if you go to any pet store
where they've got the plastic toys, it's probably a funky color and it's exactly this
thing.
Oh, my God.
Sorry.
Yeah.
It's supposed to stimulate because dogs typically have problems with their teeth.
Some do.
Anyway.
And years ago when someone needed a teeth cleaning, I was like, I didn't go to a dentist
for a teeth thing.
Just gave him this.
Your husband's got unsightly teeth.
Just give him a few milk bones.
You'll be fine.
Anyway.
So, yeah.
So that those were the days when, you know, somebody's talking and talking and you pull
a quarter out of your pocket and you hold it in front of them.
What's that?
I said, here's a quarter.
Call somebody who cares.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
Anyway.
Yeah.
So that was the old days.
Now, no one knows what the hell that means.
Right.
What do you mean?
Call what I need a quarter to call for.
Right.
Not only that.
What's so what the hell is a quarter and how do you make a call with that?
It doesn't fit my cell phone.
Yeah.
You give you give someone who's under 30 one of these rotary phones and it's funnier than
watching a monkey try to fuck a football.
But anyway.
Anyway, did I say just say what I think I said?
I used too many medical terms there.
You did.
Anyway, a lot of them.
Yeah.
So so they're using symbols.
9-11.
Everything is a symbol.
So they put the symbol.
What's that?
Oh, must be.
Right.
So they're like Confucius.
It's not laws and words and things.
It's symbols that you're controlled by.
Right.
You symbols and images.
Thick state.
So how is this done?
And why is this done?
Like I said before, most people are not real humans.
There are backdrop people.
Yes, they're real humans, just as much as, you know, the army of clones was in Star Wars
or whatever.
Right.
In other words, most of the people here are no different than as if they were grown in
a tube and put out into the world as extras in this giant movie called Life on Earth.
Right.
They bleed and cut the same.
They scream or whatever, whatever, whatever, whatever.
So.
Right.
So that's all they are.
Now, if you've ever seen a big movie set when they have a lot of extras, what they do is
they gather them.
They have some forgot the name, the crew chief, not the crew chief.
But what they do is they get the extras before shooting starts.
And they do basic keywords, basic hand signals and things for what the how the people should
react and be the extras.
Right.
Very short, abridged, abbreviated signals to the crowd.
So they get an idea.
Right.
Whether it is, you know, we're filming, not filming.
Do this.
Do that.
Right.
OK.
Just like if you've ever sat in the theater or where they're actually shooting a sitcom.
Like I've been to the car when they're shooting the Kate and Ali show and the Cosby show.
I was actually in the audience.
And before they start the shoot, they say, OK, when you guys see this and somebody holds
up a big thing that says applause.
Right.
What do we do?
And everybody applauds.
All right.
Let's do it a little bit more like this.
And then and then like, what does this say?
Right.
This is boo.
What do we do?
OK, good.
And they do several times.
People come with these signs and they walk between the aisles right in front of the audience
to see what the reaction is.
Right.
And then when they start filming, they get a live audience.
And then they got another signal for like, you know, a lot of action, a lot of noise.
Do it.
Make a lot of fuss.
And they have another one where it's like everybody kind of slow down and just, you know,
hang out in place.
Yeah.
Actually, I've been an extra.
So, yeah, I've done this.
Yeah.
OK.
So they do these signals.
This is it.
So when you look at what's put out to these morons, meaning ninety nine point nine nine
nine percent of the population, doesn't matter what country, religion, color, creed or whatever.
Actually, there might be quite a few people on the southern continent of Africa and eastern
Congo area that actually do have the ability to think.
And maybe some in the past June area of Afghanistan there that are independent thinkers still maybe.
But the rest of the world doesn't work that way, the way people are told.
So they are just following along exactly like extras.
You need a simple image and a simple instruction.
So all this stuff, if you realize that you're not part of it, there's a lot more that you
can realize than they will.