Rated Y, Sonic Event 38, and here we go.
I asked just before we started to record about, in the chat room, I said, hey, anybody got
any last minute suggestions?
Somebody dropped a word in there, and I'll be honest, when I see it, I don't know what
that word means, but the Greeks saw it, and he does.
Meanwhile, I don't know where else we're going to go.
We'll see, and we never do know, because there is no script.
Anyway, how are you doing tonight, Greg?
Doing all right.
Yeah, I think I asked you, do you know what that means, by the way?
So let's start the recording.
You know, I'm one of the few people that does this kind of thing, that admits that, you know,
almost everybody I see, they go, oh, I know what that means.
They never do.
Yeah, or they know after you tell them, of course.
Oh, yeah, I knew that.
Oh, yeah, of course, of course.
I get that all the time.
I don't do that.
If I don't know, I don't know.
And I don't know what that is.
How do you pronounce that word?
Well, Bereshit.
It's not English.
It would go, it's part of Sefer Bereshit.
It would go like Bereshit bara Elohim et ha'shamayim v'heta'aretz.
Ah, OK.
OK, well, now I know the context, where it comes from, but OK.
It's Hebrew for beginnings.
So you would say Sefer Bereshit, which would be the scroll or the book, and then Bereshit
bara beginnings created Elohim, the gods, et ha'shamayim, et ha'shamayim, et ha'aretz,
the heavens and the earth.
Right.
So that's in Hebrew.
Should I keep going?
No, you want to go through Genesis, go right ahead.
But yeah, that's that's what he wanted to know, the beginning.
I could talk a little bit about it.
I know I know the interest in it, but I always said I wanted to get into what I've discovered
Now before I do that, we'll be real quick
It has nothing to do with any religion and what you've been told in school or on TV
Genesis if you read it actually, right
Just like anything right? You know how you got these people they want the Constitution. I'm like Constitution
That's horrible document that promotes
Unlawfulness and slavery and cheating and right and so
You know if you read it, you know, like for example, you know in the Constitution
It says that you know, there's a section in there about vagabonds, you know
The you could do anything you want to him. Basically. I'm just paraphrasing, right?
Right. So that's what a resident is when someone says I'm a resident of the United States or I'm a resident of whatever city
Ask him. Where do you live? Where do you inhabit? Where do you lawfully inhabit?
I don't know what you're talking about. I'm just a resident
Okay, vagabond laws apply to you because you can only be a resident at a hotel a hospital a jail, right somewhere transient
So they've actually have the entire country admitting that they're transient so they could beat them up
And it's so funny when they had the protest the free speech zones
They have a little six by six cubicle fenced off with chain-link and that's your free speech zone. You know, you've seen that. Yeah
Yeah, I love it. I love it because these are idiots
They deserve that because all they got to do is read same thing with Genesis. It's a
It has a radical statement in the beginning
but before I get into it, there's been a lot of nitpicking on the historicity of it and
They've got the various hypotheses that mostly German scholars came up with in the 19th century that well
It's not as old as they say it is
Probably written so-and-so and it has this hypothesis that I put a different different like the Yahweh's the Elohim
They're probably they break it up how academics do now. Here's the interesting thing
Went back in the day. I think revolution radio is off the air, isn't it?
Cuz the other day somehow I looked it up to see if someone was still alive and I couldn't find it
You know freedom slips. There's a horrible place by the way. Oh, yeah
No, I remember that and you know, it was there a couple couple months back. It was
Okay, yeah because I went to the direct comm and it was a game online gaming
From Thailand. So Wow, right. So I know a far doesn't even show up anymore
I think yeah, it's a 404 or it just doesn't show so
I'll have to check into that as well again a few months ago
Those those two things did exist, but I haven't checked. Yeah, I think about a year ago for me. Yeah. Anyway when I was on there
Talking about this stuff
10 12 13 years ago
I was saying like they have this thing called cancel culture
If they don't if you become unpopular they cancel you like you never existed
Just like right now
The stuff that you found in libraries that was a hundred, you know
When I was studying the stuff the books weren't quite a hundred years old. It was 60 years old
And you can't find them now. They're there. They're burning them throwing them away putting them in underground
Facilities and they're putting everything online. It's been digitized, which is a form of
rewriting, right
So a lot of things are gone
And the subject matter will still be there, but the Google version is nothing like the book, right?
And this has been happening in our own lifetime in the last 40 years or less. I should say the last 10 years
intensively, right
so
What's interesting is like even I don't promote or endorse archaics he has this whole thing
About dark scriptures and how he speaks as if these he knows what the academics are saying are for sure and I'm like
It's three holes in your argument. So I don't blame that. He has a beef with Christianity, you know what I mean? Right?
Because it's a gateway to
It's a gateway to being a good slave by the way
Alright, well, if you want to enslave people you make sure they're a good Christian, by the way, you know
I said, you know how you become a Christian?
You get a saw and you cut the top of your skull off you lean over some brains fall out
Brains fall out then put your skull back on now. You're you get the certificate. You're a Christian for sure
They're the same with all religions, but that one's the worst by far because it promotes unlawfulness. They have no laws at all
Love your brother Jesus said no, I said that nasty work or whatever
It's not a law. All right, that's Mary Paddy. Whatever paddywhack kick-a-whack. Give a dog a bone type stuff, right?
It's not these are nice sounding sentiments that are meant to promote certain feelings. I mean, you see there's an exact emo
Through spellcasting right because this is somebody placing an emotion on you
Through these words
Yeah, like when the Ukraine war came out was oh, what about the children and then I heard someone else say what about I said
Do you see that on TV?
They're pushing the children. You know, they always use the children or Christmas is satanic, right? Oh, but the children right children
Yes, anyway, but the thing about Genesis want to throw that in because we don't really here's the thing
It doesn't matter. The thing is do you know what it says like the constitute back to the Constitution? It doesn't matter
For father's my ass
What does it say if you're gonna promote something, right? It's a form of communication, isn't it?
All right, so any any book let's say you you give a book and its author. Well
Years ago, it meant that you it was black ink on white paper
And then it became let's say made into a movie and then it became an audio book and now it's digital
So what is it? It's a communication. Yeah, it could be given many ways
So when you bring up the Bible and you bring up the Constitution you bring up
Who wrote Moby Dick not Emerson
Melville
Yeah, and all these other things it's a communication now
We can't just say it's an old book anymore because it's been reformatted and somewhat retained. So here's the thing
There's so much criticism about everything in anything both pro and con but yet there's no comprehension
All right, that's why you'll never catch me look if you put a gun to my head told me write a book
I said you're gonna pull the trigger right now because I'm never gonna write a book
right, because the reason you write books is for people to read and hopefully you're presuming at that point that people have
Comprehension and that's a big mistake
All right, because they don't know what the hell they're reading. So
Two presumptions to begin with anyway
I mean first of all that they'll make the effort to read then on top of it
Even if they make the effort to read it that they'll understand it. Isn't that like two steps?
Well, there's more than understanding. It's comprehension
in other words
The understanding is really when you string all the words together to make a point or a moral point
Oh a moral, but the comprehension is when you run across a word
Do you know what that word means and do you know what the significance of using that word is, right?
Okay, so it's a more like the bricks not the building the bricks and mortar not the building
Okay, you know when you look at if I show you just a close-up of bricks and mortar
You could you know could be any building right it could be a sidewalk even sure why not, right? Sure
So so this is the comprehension. Do you know how it's put together?
Why so back to the Genesis thing there were a few people that have taken it apart and looked at it studied it
Because it's not popular to do
So if you start talking about these things you and you spend enough time to learn them
And now it becomes a vocation. You will not have it as a vocation
You'll be eating out of garbage cans and sleeping on a park bench because that's just how the world is. So
so in essence what it is, it's basically a
Compilation of thoughts that are distilled down into another thought that's trying to prioritize certain things. Oh
Boy, what the hell did he just say because you know when there's seven days of creation there really are three
There there are three days and three days are mentioned again in similar context, right?
So it sounds like seven days. There's
There but there are seven days that pass and also there is a concept of they're not 24 hour days or a thousand
Year days, that's a good concept
But I'm telling you that the whole thing was a thousand years and broken up into seven and it gets complex
It gets you have to bite. This is the kind of thing where
you know when you go to like cats is deli or the
Carnegie deli in New York and you order a sandwich and it's like four inches thick. Yeah, right
It's not like it's like oh my gosh. Hi. Where do I start? How I hold this thing, you know, right?
Okay, this is how this is. So when you say let's take a bite out of Genesis
It's like oh my gosh, you really can't bite that you have to kind of like you need a nut fork and a knife
You know what? I mean?
You got to open it up or something
You see it's not that it's not a sandwich that you could just take a bite of like, you know
A jail sandwich you can do it. This is really different. So it requires very
Well, it requires a conversation not a
Discussion, right? It's like what do you want to talk about? You know about Genesis, but here's the other thing
Regardless of when it was written who really if you know, whatever do you comprehend it? Okay
The other thing is what's going on with chapters the way they're divided. Yeah, that was supposedly so
It's like a grid system
So when scholars are communicating they can target the area that they want to talk about right just like when you give coordinates on a map
Right. Well, I thought also because people used to verbalize this wasn't it?
Also designed to help with that because this way you had measures
So you could break it up in even parts. I mean because it was being verbalized
Right, it's a disadvantage to do that. We're in maps and cartography. It is an advantage, you know GPS, right?
Okay, so so know what they did was they started dividing it to break the context out
So when you read Genesis chapter 1
It shouldn't end there and it doesn't end there
It actually ends in the after the third or fourth verse of chapter 2 because that's when the after it's an affidavit
It basically at the end of an affidavit, you know when you write you you sign it or state who's making this claim
Right that that is not in chapter 1
It's in the first after the first few verses of chapter 2 and when that claim is made
That's where you you you know, fold it up put it in an envelope, right?
You don't make a an affidavit three-quarters of a paragraph put in an envelope mail to someone
So where's the rest who wrote this? Well, that's coming in the next envelope
Then you just got three sentences that finish the thing it you just don't do that kind of stuff
No, you have to at least attach the pages together and say look this is part of this
And they're all together and and the thing is with an affidavit, right what you would do with anything is first
You would describe the parties involved the things at issue
What when where right is all right there at the top and then
Yeah, well the Y comes last because that's the thing that you know tells you what's happening
Right and then and then like you said who is actually attached to this is at the end
So there you go. That's a that's like a complete affidavit and that's good
It doesn't happen in chapter 1 and you finish chapters
I'm reading chapter 1 as soon as you finish chapter when you close the book. I'll have a sandwich, right?
You didn't finish it. You didn't get and then you pick up chapter 2. It's like, all right
This seems like it's just like coming out of nowhere. But you know, it's a whoa and who's this guy right here now
You see so anyway
Yeah, that's that's the what I just mentioned is what I've been hammering. It is not a creation event. It is a remodeling event
They're right. It's everything is redone
huge super
super bad cataclysm
if you want to get into the
chronography a lot of the
Chronology stuff. I'm usually off between 50 and 100 years over a 6,000 year period
It's not so bad what I'm saying if you go to look at Archaic's his stuff again
I don't endorse Archaic's but his product, you know, I may not endorse someone but I can't but I can I'll admit one there
They're certain whatever work. I'll specify what's worth looking at, right?
You know, so a part of their work may indeed be very sound even though the whole thing is not
But yeah the chronology because he gives so many sources
Which I've come across also, but that's not my shtick
My shtick here is that I figured out that everything's wrong and it's not that hard to figure out right now. I'm not a
chronologist but
Usually when he states the the chronology of the flood when this was done with this
I'm usually like I usually say the the flood was 2,500 BC. Well, it's 2239 or
Pretty close right over 4,500 years
Right hundred years is not bad. So
It's it's less than 1% So, you know, it's a little bit over 1% but anything less than 10% is good
So I'm usually between 1 2% off on the chronology
So so here if you want the chronology on these things go look at Archaic's again. I don't endure. Yeah, I
Don't endorse his stuff
And if you know enough Greek speak, you'll you'll be able to call him on it
So but here's the thing
It's a big deal I might get into it on a solo
Because it's not a sandwich. It's more like
When you when you want to eat this sandwich, you know again if you go to Katz's or Carnegie Deli
Forgive me for people who don't know the places I'm referring to be actually if you look it up on the Internet
There's plenty of YouTubes. I'm sure on Carnegie's daily and Katz's deli sandwiches, but they're as tall as they're as thick as they are
Long or wide, right? I don't like Second Avenue deli myself. But yeah, go ahead. Yes second Avenue deli
It's a better deal. Not the big lines. It's just as good. Right? Yeah, they actually it was not as commercial
Yeah, where the quality matter went down on the other ones. These guys kept it
Yeah, so
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, don't the New Yorkers know the secret spots, right?
So you but you were technically bridging tunnel. You didn't live in Manhattan. Did you ever I know I lived in Manhattan a while
I lived on the East Side. Oh, okay. So, okay. So you're not bridging tunnel
Because we used to make fun everybody's gonna go Times Square kidding that's all bridging tunnel people usually Jersey and suburbs, right?
No, I I think I might have said put in Times Square once and it was only because incidental
I mean, I really didn't go there. I I was in these village. I was over there right by Tompkins Square Park all the time
That's where I live. Yeah, and I lived there. Yeah
You know, but I also lived on 11th Street between 2nd and 3rd and why do you I mean NYU neighborhood?
Yeah, I was between 1st and a and NYU wasn't in there yet it was you know, Alphabet City was kind of a
Yeah, that went down when you got popular that share bought a building to turn it into co-ops or condos
remember Thompson Square Park was here's the first one her and someone else say they
Renovated a building to make it condos. I was like I'd say there goes the neighborhood
Yeah, and then there was somebody came in there
That was like secret and people were saying might have been Michael Jackson
But it wasn't and it was somebody else that didn't didn't go there to live but bought up a bunch of stuff for a little
Bit some some artist. I can't remember. Yeah
Could go down there when the Krishna's would show up with their bus and give out all the free food
I don't know if they were doing it when you were there. Yeah. No, that was it
Yeah, they would they would they and they would feed anybody
If you should it wasn't bad
It was not bad at all and they if you would sit and listen to their little spiel then you could have a tin of food
Yeah, oh, yeah our plate it was great. I love the basmati rice
I just asked you know, Michael about you know, the herbs and the focus, you know back then I was still into cooking
I was into cooking since I was a child
so anyway
You know these these sonics they go on tangents hopefully they come back but you can't set them to music, you know
They're all over the place sometimes. You know, I mean true enough true enough
We but but still with the Genesis thing it's interesting that that you have described this before as a
You know as a legal notice you used another word to that. That was really after the legal affidavit
Remodel. Mm-hmm. Oh, and it's yeah, that's the other thing is that when I've heard people say well
It's kind of like terraforming as opposed to creation. I go. Yeah, I think that's about right
you know, it's terraforming like climate change and
a
eugenics genetics
Right, it's taking something that exists. It's like molding with clay
You didn't create the clay, but you're working with it to take the clay and make it into something else
I mean that that's right about like that, right?
because the first Adam in the the first Adam the men and women are made together and
But they're classified as animals, by the way
Because it does it basically doesn't say ish and isha it says
Zahar and
Nicobar which are terms that you used to like male and female goats and cows and dogs and sheep not
It's not man and woman. It's male female, but typically using
the pronouns that you would use for livestock, right and
They were told to repopulate the earth and they were blessed
Now the the second one that was in the garden
he was pretty pathetic and
Because you know, there's no man. There's only man and there's no woman and then later, you know, you know the joke about the rib
right, so
They make the woman and they don't get any blessing and they're ousted and ostracized
Right, and there so the first one was a eugenics and the second Adam in the garden is a genetic
You know, whenever you see the EU prefix, yeah
that means good like
Evangelion Greek or
Euphoria the EU right euphoria eugenics means to make it good. It's the Greek prefix for good or satisfaction
So but it's been turned negative now like oh, that's part of eugenics program means like genocide and stuff like that
Usually it's used in that just like the word
Just like the word
Anarchy is used wrong, right? They've turned it the word gay is turned wrong, right?
all these things so
anyway, the first group was a eugenics and the second one was a basically a degenerate the the Adam that you read about in the
garden and
there's a reason for that and we can get into that when we discuss it basically the first group was too much like the gods and
The second group they made sure that they he wasn't like the gods even though he you know, I mean
So because the first one is very it says that the made him in the image of the gods
But the second one doesn't say that it just says it took some dust from the earth
You get it. It's very subtle sometimes
You know in
intelligence
Interrogators good detectives or whatever
They they teach them how to be a good interrogator and what you look for, you know, the four things for interrogation
Okay, no, okay
You'll like it. All right. First one is
Listen to what they're saying
Right. Yeah, the second one is listen to what they're not saying
the third one is
Look at how they're saying what they're saying and the fourth one is look at how they're not saying what they're not saying
Basically body behavior right body language, right? Oh, yeah, and then there's the whole system that goes with that
I okay now I know what you're talking about
Yeah
And then they go into the whole system where there's all the different cues, you know
The raise of the eyebrow the change in pitch etc. Sure
Why is part two and part four which is listen and look at what they're not saying so important
Because when you selectively leave out something
It should be just as blatant as if you said it or pointed it out right when something's missing, right?
Well, yeah, for example, let me call it
Show me the virus, you know, how come there's no cure no remedy
How can we not promoting any remedies show me the virus they show you a cartoon and there's no remedy, right?
Okay, we know it's a fraud right right by omission the much I revealed by omission
I forget where it says that but it says it somewhere. Anyway, yeah, the thing is it's
the the most subtle one by the way is to
Look at how they're not saying to well, obviously listening to what they're not saying and how they're not saying, you know
Right, so how they're not how they're presenting the the omission not just the omission
Because you can actually say you forgot about this part, but you don't right because that's that's part of the study, right?
So there's a lot of that in in Genesis and this is more like chapter two and three. So
yeah, that gets
Again, it's a it's a you can't just take a bite out of it here and there you either decide you're gonna split it
You know, let's go get that. We'll split it, you know the sandwich, but it's if you're gonna need it by yourself
It's probably lunch and dinner or you're gonna be really full if you try to eat it by yourself, right?
Right, so we'll we'll address that somehow
So you think we did all right on that could move on the next subject that we don't know about yet. Absolutely good. Okay
One thing one thing I want to interject I say it's really hard to set music to these sonics, isn't it?
Right, you know what I mean by that?
It's like you got to pick a theme right either violins or happy dancers or some whatever, right?
You can't do that because it suits anyway
I wanted to bring up the
extol the purpose and use of spray bottles around the house predominantly with the silver and hydrogen peroxide because lately
We're having a heat wave here and I'm a little under the weather because of exhaustion heat exhaustion, which I'm doing something
I'm changing the weather right now
because I let it go and
You know, like I said, I'm involved doing some stuff in industry. So
I've been focusing more on
Thinking about what I'm doing so I could talk about it to help others. Let's say right. Yes to help others
So what I noticed my usually around the house here is we've got a lot of stuff in spray bottles, right?
dollar store spray just empty spray bottles and the most useful thing is the
I
Said colloidal silver, but it's not when I say colloidal silver
It's got to have an asterisk next to it in the footnote is it's aqueous Argentum. There's no coalesce. No particles in there
I did drop an article in the chat about how nano
Particles meaning like the smaller the particle the better it is for the nervous system and the brain, right?
so
How about you get something that is imbued with the full quality of the substance, but has no particle at all
So they're telling you as the particle gets smaller to infinity
Because femto would be smaller than nano right a billion times smaller again or a million times smaller than a billion
Okay, so it'd be a trillionth not a billionth. But anyway, so so they're telling you as it gets smaller and smaller
It gets more beneficial. How about you imbue the substance into a fluid?
With no particles then what does it do? Oh my gosh homeopathic
So all the people who were lied about like you have made fun of and lied about right?
There's stuff on your bathroom are extremely powerful because there's nothing there, right?
The material it's all energy
And the thing is I was talking to someone recently
Midstream and they were kind of tolerating me and I was tolerating them. That makes any sense. Okay, right?
So I ran into them and I was like, oh, this is an intelligent person
I'll be easy on them, but they can't take what I have to say and they reciprocated the same with me
I could see it in their eyes, right?
This guy is saying stuff that is in the airy fairy cattle category, but he's not airy fairy
Back telepathic kind of thing. Okay. So anyway, I was saying that energy medicine. There's no proof of that. I said energy
Okay, so, you know anything that radiation electricity is energy. Yeah, it's energy the
Electrons don't really are not particles. You know, this is yeah, that's a theory. I understand it's energy
Okay, so when people are sick with cancer, don't they give them radio radiation therapy in the main in the mainstream, right?
So what isn't radiation energy?
Right
Substance their best I can so yeah. Yep. So they do use they do acknowledge but it's toxic, right?
Look, it's it's so ironic that chemotherapy for cancer treatment chemo is what causes cancer and radiation therapy for cancer
The radiation is what causes cancer. So they're actually giving you more of a poison
I always found that to be bizarre
Actually the idea that like radiation can give you cancer and yet they give it to you when you have cancer
I always was like isn't that kind of a contradiction guys?
It is if it's not some of the hair of the dog that bit you or drinking it when you have a hangover
And it's nothing like that. No, it is deliberate. They're putting it in your face
You know, it's gotten to the college university
Education is in your face because it's very well known every anyone spoke to it's well established that anything past an eighth grade education
There's potential to do irreparable damage to the victim and everybody says yes
So what the hell are you doing from the 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 because you know
The grades keep going up to until doctor, right? So
Four years 13 14 15 right 16
Great, right, but somewhere around the second grade. I had that thought of like why is it you know, cuz it was just you know
Let somebody explain an adult explaining the world to me, right?
Yeah, you you get cancer. You can get cancer from radiation. And then when you have cancer they give you radiation and
I shake in my head like well, wait a minute if one thing causes
Yeah
Here's another way that tell you it's in your face on TV. They promote a drug right commercials
I don't know 30 seconds 40 seconds. I like three-minute commercials like in the 70s anymore, but 30-second commercial age
Okay, first 10 seconds. The drug introduction is over in the last two-thirds of the commercial is what?
Side effects. Yeah, don't take this. Yeah may cause this that third thing
Hey, look, don't take this if you have a vaccine if you're gonna be near other people blah blah blah, you know
Chocolate milk can walk around breathe. Yeah, they cause it fatality, right?
Consolidated consult with your pharmacist to make sure your drugs don't interact with it because you might be taking other stuff to interact with it
Oh, yeah
Yeah, and they're telling you how bad it is and you still want it
Just like you want a college degree
Where it's already you should have been out of school when you were 14 or whatever
But anyway, it's that sick of a society back to the spray bottle in the aqua Sargento, right?
Okay
What it is?
You can apply the standard
Colloidal silver methodology, right? I think you even got involved with that, right? Yeah one point you so you familiar
They say oh, it's kills bacteria kills fungus. If you're sick, it'll knock things out of the body, whatever. Okay, that's fine
Does that as well, but it also changes things because silver is a
Noble metal. It's a master metal. Yeah, even in the Bible. It says silver is good for health. So
But we know the attributes let's say it's bacteria static
Bacteria side fungicide and all these other things. So it is a form of cleaning and stabilizing something
so let's say you're gonna put something water in a bottle and you're gonna put it away spray some of that in there first and
Put the cover on it with the fluid and put it away and you probably won't spoil right?
they do that chemically anyway, they
you know, I was at a
Pharmaceutical convention a long time ago boy the gifts they give you know the pharmaceutical convention
They invite doctors and people in industry
You go to the convention you go in the door you show your invite and all that and man the gifts they give the women
Got pearl necklaces the men get cigars and ties and all kinds of stuff. I'm talking about expensive stuff gifts, right for the attendees
About the bar and I was talking to the guy. So what do you thought I was impressed?
No, I'm just here with somebody else. And so what do you do? It says I probably never heard of it
I said try me he says well
I do fungicides and bacteria sides
but you never heard of it because it's not on the label on the ingredients because we add it to the package if we add it
To the package and don't add it to the food. It doesn't have to be listed or approved
But listen, if you spray, let's say you got a box of cereal
You got the liner inside, right?
You spray the chemicals in there and no one knows it's in there because it's not listed on the box
Do you think when you put the flakes in there or whatever the fruit and the nuts?
Then you seal up the bag the chemicals gonna mix with the stuff you put in there. Of course it is
Right. Absolutely ingredient. It's an indirect ingredient legally illegally. It's not an ingredient, but you and I know right? Yeah
Well, that's the thing though
Look if you don't believe it
Look, you take a standard perfume of any kind spray it in a bag and then put something in that bag
Even though you didn't spray it directly on the thing take that thing out of the bag a little while later
Guess what? It's got some of that perfume in it now
Or whatever substance it is or what? Yeah, I mean, I'm just going with the perfume because that's obvious
But I mean, it's extremely obvious you spray it
You'll be able to measure it with the olfactory
You could measure it. There's allergies and things like that
So I want to bring that up because storing fluids pickling things
So you're cleaning a jar now if you have a table, let's say you have a plastic bottle
You might want to save for later. You know, you wash it dry. It still gets sour
Okay, what you when you put it away, there's two ways what I do. First thing I do is I turn it over
drain it out dry it a little bit and I spray a little hydrogen peroxide because you'll never open a bottle of anything else hydrogen
Peroxide or you'll be sour, right?
The other thing I do is when I put the lid to close the lid on it
I put a piece of paper towel on the threads
So you don't really lock it down what that paper dowel does is it leaves a pathway for the everything in the bottle to breathe?
This is just for empty storage. All right, so you could pull a jar out and open it. I'll never be sour, right?
Okay. So the other thing I do this is I'm bouncing between hydrogen peroxide and the aqueous Argentum
When you're doing laundry, sometimes you got some sebum or BO left in the clothes or whatever
When it goes into the dryer the clothes dryer the tumble dryer
You put the white clothes in the tumble dryer and go ahead and spray some of the aqueous Argentum the silver solution
In the dryer with the clothes it's amazing because I was like, oh, these are like white t-shirts work shirts
I'm not gonna wash them again. It's summertime
Whatever that I do smell a little bit of BO even though it came out of the wash
I'm gonna spray some silver on it. See if it works right? It was like, oh my gosh it worked, right?
It's very simple stuff like that. The other thing is
I've mentioned this before have a bottle in the bathtub the aqueous Argentum and
And the hydrogen peroxide for people that have mold developing in the baths in the tub surround area
I don't back east if you you know
Sometimes you might live in a space and it's got a little tiny bathroom window or no window just a vent you get start developing
Mold mold on the grout on the tub surround almost always, right?
Yeah, I don't hear because it's got a big window and it's against the Easter wall
So but anyway a lot of sunlight a lot of UV here
Anyway use the peroxide instead of those bathroom cleaners, right?
The aqueous Argentum the silver solution is when you're done with the shower
You're still drip drying your water is off
Go ahead and grab the bottle and spray yourself with it before you towel down
What that'll do is it'll keep the towel smelling fresh and pressure longer, right?
Because the skin that comes off when you're drying will be stabilized
And also it'll get all over your skin and it actually by induction. It'll be almost the same as drinking it
I think about it, you know, like smoking, you know, what do they do? They give a patch
Right, it's topical. It'll be a topical thing. By the way, you know, it's a big deal in the public pools or whatever
Don't pee in the pool, right?
And if you sit and if you're laying in the bathtub with water in it, you want to pee whenever you get into water
You want most people feel like they have to pee that's because of an induction of water through the skin in the body
In other words the this entire
Surface of the skin is surrounded with water
Guess what?
It does if starts producing water inside the body and it displaces the existing water energy through the bladder
Well as soon as I get my hands wet washing dishes, I feel like I want to pee, you know to be honest
Which is my hands are wet even
For the old one when someone's sleeping put their hand in some warm water
Yeah, I always think of that but but seriously
I mean you don't get the urge when you're when you're washing dishes sometimes as soon as you get the water
Keep my urges to myself
No, no, I get you know, but I do have the urge when I get into a body of water
Yes, I feel well in the body of water too. Sure. Good. Yeah any body of water
You've been a shower because you are inducing that so that that legitimizes the patch therapies for different their patches
They even have a birth control patch, right? Yeah, there's nothing like that. Yeah
I
Want to throw this in there, you know the dollar store that pregnancy kits right for a dollar
Oh, you mean they did to detect pregnancy with the whole yeah, they can't stick. That's the same
That's the same thing modified. They charge three people corporate insurance people $3,000 for cancer screening
So if you know, you're not pregnant and you're a guy
And you're gonna go get cancer screening you get one of these dollars you pee on it if it shows you're pregnant guess what?
It's the same
Implement they're using when you pay 3,000 bucks to get cancer screening. It's the same things the dollar store
Pregnancy test. Anyway, I was always told I've detected growth hormone. I I don't know for certain just told
Cancer it means the body's working. Okay body wants to keep you going. It's a roadblock. It's like hey, dude
You've been screwing up for so long
Hey, let's say I give the analogy of a car accident
Hey, you're screwing you you're texting or changing the radio you get into a car accident
Right chances if you're looking at the radio or texting while you're driving with your chances of getting to a car accident increase like tenfold
Right, right. All right, you do that enough. Guess what? It's gonna catch up with you
You're gonna get into an accident, right?
And then what happens the cancer comes in other words, they block off the road don't think right
Okay, it's safer to block the road and direct traffic than just leave the accent in the middle of the road true
That's what the cancer is it's just saying hey you got these energies moving
Too much of this and the body's natural flow has been disturbed. So we have to put a block you get it
No, like no cure it cure it and cure it
Right. That's why usually when they go after the block
It doesn't mean there isn't gonna be another accident. So you have to go after that don't change, you know better driving skills, right?
so anyway
Yeah, I just wanted to bring up those points because we're in a heat wave I've been doing some domestic work and I
Notice, you know when I speak and bring up things in a sonic and I do them in my own a day-to-day life
I noticed them more right and then I said, oh, you know, I didn't mention
this that and the other
and I
Am I am at the moment standardizing for someone wants a
Aqueous Argentum kit and I'm at the point now where I could standardize it and I and I have one or go
I have two of them here, but now I have a standard version and it's called
Silver made easy. Okay, and that comes from an old commercial called quilting made easy anyway
All right, so silver made easy
Okay
Why well, it's got the proper setup for the electrodes and the proper silver and guess what power is USB
USB so who doesn't have USB power
Right. It's easier, right? You got your anybody's got a phone or a computer's got, you know standard USB, you know
One or two or three, right?
And they're even building a lot of lamps and other stuff if you buy a new lamp
There's a lot of them have USB ports and I'm just a lamp by the way
Starbucks counter as it right when you go to coffee shops, they have it
That's what I call silver made easy and it has the it's five volts, which is way too much voltage
But it the it's got three neutral plates positive negative
I'm deciding whether I should do a fourth plate to lower the voltage more
But it seems like the three neutrals and the positive negative work. Well, I've got it very stable
It's in a case and it's got a two and a half foot USB cable
Think about it in the car, you know where they got the cigarette lighter the power accessory all the cars have it now
Most people that have a car to have a cell phone have a charger like that, right?
Okay, right. So now you can make silver at Starbucks. You can be at a coffee shop
You can make it in the car
You can make it at home pretty much and in most homes you have those USB charges not just in one part of the house
But many parts of the house, right?
I actually bought one of those, you know
You put it in the two plugs and it may gives you six plugs one of those two things
I got one of those and it's got USB ports in it, too
You know, I just got one recently so
Yeah, no, absolutely
Call out a bus. Yeah
Well, you have a branch but yeah, so it couldn't be any easier than that because otherwise
Hey, honey, go get some batteries. I want to make some silver right? None of that. Mm-hmm, right, right and where's the battery?
I want to make some silver. What do you mean the battery? I didn't see it. Where is it? Right?
Okay, and also it will be very effective now it will
When I have the unit the one I send out it will be the standard one, you know, I think they are a
Sub here as well, and I did message them recently
It'll be the Cadillac. It's a Cadillac man of the silver
What's that it's a Cadillac, okay, it'll be the Cadillac of the silver and it'll be
They'll make really really good silver and consistent
And you don't have to clean it. Yeah, I wouldn't put it in coffee or coke just water
All right bottle what it's designed to use any type of water. You don't use distilled
Right
You said that before anything that is just, you know, a good clean steady kind of decent water cool clean water
Anything you would drink, right? That's what you know water any water that you portable bottled water is fine
you know as a better the water the better the
Situation whether you're making silver or not and also by the way, you know using the spray bottles to dilute the
detergent for laundry or for the sink
Very helpful, by the way, because I started doing that
Yeah, so what I'm gonna offer here is when I do this you ready?
When I'm gonna you know, the first rule of government spending why make one when you can make two or twice the price, right?
So what we're gonna do is when the first one goes out
I'll be field tested you're pretty soon and I'll feel test that what we're gonna do is we do a giveaway
So once it's the other ones ready
Chuck you're gonna go through all of the
Member all the subs here and randomly randomly pick one
you can either number them and have a random number generator picket or whatever randomly picket and
We'll announce
You'll probably send them an email if you would that you won this
No problem. I'll just send them an email and tell them to give us a postal address to us and I'll send it to them
Yeah
This first time I've ever done a giveaway. Okay, great. All right. Sounds good
Might as well. So that's what we'll do. So we're gonna give away a
silver made easy
To somebody when you're ready to put it out there to just one of these subs here
One of you guys who is a subscriber will get it and I'll set it up so there's a randomly picks
Yeah, so do a random pick you could have the dog picket maybe I don't know somebody they put your paw on one
Well, well when you do random giveaways
We do is put all the names on a piece of paper in a jar you pick one out like the bingo
Or you could just assign a number in the whatever order they're in
You know
So if you pull a number if you let's say ten people you've got one through ten and you count down the list who's ten
Right, but let's say you pick seven who's the seventh, right? Well, I got Buster the weenie dog
I'm very sure that I could put him up to the screen and he can put his paw up on the screen
I can do that easy. Yeah, okay, either way, but however random pick and
Yeah, okay. So what that said
Enjoy your water. Enjoy your sober. There you go, and we'll do that