Is it's going to be 32? Yep. Did you check chat? Yep. Okay, I did. I'm trying to stay active.
Looks like we got some pretty good, pretty good bunch of folks. Actually, it's the best bunch I've
seen ever, which makes me happy. It doesn't take much to make me happy. So yeah, I look at it when
I can. I also try to take frequent breaks from what I'm doing. So I don't, you know, get too crazy.
And, uh, I've been looking at the chat as a hobby. So there you go. Well, it's a different,
definitely different from you doing something that's, you know, completely organized and
whatnot. So, right. Let me take, sorry. I just bumped into my mic. Let me take a quick look
at myself. Why don't you just, just, just do it, man. Hit it. 32. Oh yeah. Yeah. No problem. I'll
do that too. I just wanted to look real fast. Just get a quick cursor. Look, let's see. Uh,
contemplate what I said here. Thanks for the insight. Okay. Water confirmed. I miss how to
detox energetically. Energy. Are you trying to do your homework when you're show up at class?
No, I'm not doing homework. I'm just kicking my mind. I'll give you the cliff notes. No,
I don't even want them. I'm just kicking my mind into the right set. That's all. Just so I'm not
surprised. It's just a quick peek around the corner. Not a full analyzation. Let's see. All
right. Anyways, they're talking about the, uh, how do you spell that? Analization. Yeah, that's
true. Is that how you spell it? Well, the anus is an important part of the body. Is it not? Yeah.
It depends on whose it is. I've seen walking anuses too. Have you ever seen those? Uh,
I believe so. But you know, I guess, uh, no, no anus is created equal. Yeah.
Um, all right. Not after I'm done with it. Well, listen, I don't know what you do with
them yourself. And I'm just joking. Hey, I'm Greek. You know, the word Greek means to analyze.
Oh, I know. But not, not analyze, but analyze. It's a, it's a pejorative term from old French,
not common slang. Still is old prostitutes in the seventies. You know,
I don't do Greek, right? You know what that means? It wasn't just the seventies though,
because I remember how I learned this as a kid was, you know, the personal ads,
uh, like in the, you know, like in the village voice or in the, or in the rock magazines,
you know what I mean? The, uh, the rock newspapers on the East coast. Well,
yeah, we do Greek. Yeah. The ones that say that go Greek. Yeah. Yeah. It'll be a bunch of things
then. No Greek, you know, or no Greek, no Greek. That's right. I'm like 13 going, Whoa, no Greek.
What? They don't, they don't want to bang Greek guys. What are they saying? No, it just means
this. Oh, okay. Then. So I'm supposed to be lascivious when we're, when we're recording
that one. We're not. I know. I know. You probably are. So let's go, let's go hit it. Don't worry
about it. Just follow my lead. Right? You got it. Okay. So hang on. I'll play the intro and all
that. And, uh, what? 32, right? Yeah. 32. Okay. Here we go.
Oh, Charlie in the Greek rated Y Sonic event 32. And, uh, there's your announcement as per usual
and all that good stuff. So how are you doing this? Uh, well it is evening here. I don't know
if the sun is down where you are yet, but, uh, should be. Yeah. Almost. Speaking of the sun,
it's been really hot here in the Southwest. And I said, Hey dummy, you can do the weather. So
let's try it. So they're about two hour hop. I call it an op op short for operation. Uh,
and, uh, actually I set it up the night before, did it in the morning and that following 2am
lightning. I'm like, okay, there's lightning. And then a thunder and then
raindrops, you know, the big raindrops, you know, you could hear them on the roof
everywhere outside for about five minutes. So I'm like, yes,
still got it. You know, it's kind of like riding a bicycle, you know? Well, and you're doing that
what in between, uh, you were doing some home improvements. You're not done with that yet.
Right? No, no. Uh, going around the house, I got most of the elevations done. We had something
called roof thrust, which, uh, is, uh, it goes, uh, decide misdiagnosed by architects. If you have
cracks in brick walls, you call an architect engineer, guess what they say? Oh, that's
foundation work. You need foundation work, right? Yep. And what they do to foundation work,
it's, uh, tens of thousands cause they dig below the existing foundation and poor gobs and gobs,
massive amounts of concrete as they're supporting the old foundation. They fill
that and they go all around the building where they think it's necessary. 90%. That is not the
problem. Uh, when you have what's called a gable roof, which is a pitched roof, uh, 90% of the
time people do that and the cracks get worse and you'll see why. I'll go back to why the cracks
get worse after they spend 50,000 on foundation reinforcement and architects. Engineers don't
know this by the way. I started a movement on this a long time ago and now there's some of them
catching up on it and I shouldn't say I'm taking full credit for it, but anyway, what is really
happening. Okay. Well, let me just, uh, with a gable roof, you know, it's on an angle on a pitch.
If you don't support that roof and the peak starts to sag and lower the edges of the roof,
push the brick walls apart at the top and the bottom is pinned to the foundation. The bomb
doesn't want to move. So you get cracks and they get bigger really fast. Some of them are scary.
I've seen them where you, it breaks the plaster and, uh, the brick outside and you can actually
see light right through, you know, literally like it's coming apart at the seams almost
at the mortar. Yeah. And people get really frightened and they call the, you know,
and then they reinforce the car. Now what happens is the roof is pushing at the top,
the foundation's holding it stiff at the bottom. So the cracks follow those lines.
What happens when you make the foundation stiffer and don't support the roof? The cracks continue
even more, right? It's kind of like when you get more attention. So, and then what happens the
next step after that, after 50 to a hundred grand worth of improvements that don't work, uh, they,
they abandon the house, they condemn it. And somebody comes in, figures it out,
fixes up the house, you know, they buy the house for a dollar, you know,
and put it on the market again. And I've seen that over and over. So anyway, this house was
suffering that. And I did re-support the roof and you have to go along the ridge of the roof
and prop it up. The only problem when you do that is that you actually end up loading the
interior walls and you could, if you're a slab on grade, you end up cracking the floor, the ground
inside, but it's minor. Uh, so yeah, so doing all that and, uh, doing some additional work at,
you know, add ons and, um, yeah, no, it's pretty neat. And restoration. It's a 75 year old house
or 70, let's just say a 71 year old. Well, that means it's kind of about due for some maintenance
work anyway of that type, right? I mean, generally speaking about 75 years is the lifespan of just
any of these buildings where you have to do something. Well, this is before that time was
deemed. I mean, this house, like, um, uh, give you an example. Uh, this, this is the same
construction that's been used for thousands of years. Uh, stone foundation slab on grade,
no basement, you know, brick masonry and the masonry, the mortar is just lime and sand.
You know, you could scratch it with a screwdriver. It's not like cement and sand, you know? Okay.
And, uh, but it's still pretty sturdy. And what I mean by that is I remember back in
1976 was the U S bicentennial, right? Right. And everybody celebrated that. Wow. We're 200
years old. Like I was on, I called someone in Europe. I was a family friend and I said,
it's the 200th bicentennial. What are you doing in the summer? I said, it's the 200th bicentennial.
They're like, really? I I'm in France and I'm living in a house. That's 800 years old.
You know, so much for your bicentennial being a long time, right? Right. Because,
you know, uh, if you build it right, you know, if you support the ridge of the roof,
if you go online, for example, well, 15 years ago, 10 years ago, there was nothing on roof thrust.
Now you go there, there's like two or three people talking about it and they'll actually,
some of them will mention stories. We hired architects and engineers and they told us it
was foundation work. And it's a simple concept as the roof sag, it pushes the walls out, you know?
And, uh, yeah. What have I said about attorneys and doctors? Now we can say that about guess who
else? Uh, well, architects and engineers. If you want to know about architects, it's all ego.
It's all ego. Look at every, any city is total chaos. Oops. I used a medical term there,
but it's totally chaotic. And people look at postcards of these cities. Look how beautiful,
beautiful, it's total chaos. This is total. These are all ego driven phallic symbols.
And I've, I've learned this, not the ego driven phallic symbol part, but working with architects
firsthand, they want to show that they do expensive work. So they, right. So when they build a house,
they want to set this house costs this much. And then I was, Oh, wow. Well, what I do,
they, I used to work as a liaison between the, the owners and the engineers and builders and
architects. And I used to look at the plans and how to make it more efficient and cut the cost.
And the architects hated that. What do you mean? It's going to be cheaper. I need it to be, you
know, expensive for my portfolio. You know, it's kind of like, uh, it's kind of like these prosecutor
jerk offs that, uh, they, they want during election time, they, we put up, um, uh, attorney
generals or whatever they put up, uh, attorneys, they put up the, uh, billboards. Uh, we have an,
I have a 98.9% prosecution rate. Well, that just means you could prosecute a ham sandwich,
right? That people don't know. It's like, why, why would you say that? Because 99% of the
people in jail are innocent, right? You can't tell me they're the 6 million people in jail
in this country are all murderers. I'd say about 600,000, right? Maybe.
Well, yeah. And they count their conviction rate is usually what it, what they, what it is, right?
If you're running for office, it's about your conviction rate. Oh my gosh. And yeah, well,
that means they've convicted a hand sandwich, you know, it's all, you know, so anyway,
I'm not saying that, you know, I used to have conversations with people that worked for the
city and the state like this. And they would say, they wouldn't address anything I said. They would
say, are you trying to say we shouldn't exist? And I heard that from one guy, I was like, Oh shit.
And then I months later, I had another conversation with a different part of the office.
They said the same thing. Like they all have the same spirit, you know, like they're robots or
something. Are you trying to say we shouldn't exist? I'm like, Whoa, this is interesting.
Getting the same car. And also I found out attorneys give Pat statements and soda doctors.
So it always goes down to that. And look, and there's the next logical step after, you know,
are you trying to say we shouldn't exist? The next thing is, well, what do you want? You want
anarchy? You want chaos? What? There should be no law and order. You're against law and order.
This is the right, which is a sidestep because they don't know anything about law. It's about
order. You can definitely keep be lawless and keep order. Yeah, right. Go to a Nazi prison camp.
Listen, you could have a human slaughtering facility and it can be very orderly. It doesn't
mean that it's lawful. That's right. And all the human slaughtering could could be grandmothers,
you know? Yeah. Yeah. It could just be grandmothers, you know, that, you know, whatever.
Yeah. Yeah. So it's pretty interesting. I thought we'd bring that up because it might help someone.
Maybe it won't, but at least you'll have people listening to this that are knowledgeable about
something, a phenomenon called roof thrust. Speaking of thrusting last 31, I got into the
basics of Yin and Yang, which is still haven't found another word for it. Someone, I think,
suggested calling it something else and didn't really. I thought it was OK, but it didn't strike
me enough to even remember it now. Right. But something come universal compliance or something
that sounds legal, doesn't it? Well, that reminds me of what the universal product code,
right? The UPC. OK. For the universe. Yeah. Yeah. But a real the real one. Real. Yeah. Not the
thing on paper, but the thing that's actually built into the structure. I have one of those,
by the way. It costs around 750 bucks a while back. I have a UPC product or you could change
the product. Oh, yeah. Organic UPC, so to speak. Right. Yeah. It was it was registered with all the
financial and all that, you know, to be legit. I mean, anybody can make a UPC, but there's there's
the one that's a registered one for commerce. Right. Oh, yeah. I used to make bootleg CDs.
I would slap UPC codes on them all the time. Matter of fact, occasionally, just to be funny,
I would take something like, you know, a box of Cracker Jacks and put that, you know, and like
just paste it on as a UPC code. And that just looks legit. You know, we have a little bit of
an age difference, not much. But the last time I bought something bootleg was on Canal and Canal
Street off of West Broadway. I remember it was a rainy Sunday night. A bunch of guys from Staten
Island in hoodies. And they were selling tapes. And one guy had a little walk. Let me hear. I said
the audio quality is not that good. Like there's no highs. It's all mid bass and low lows. And
it's all right, man. It's Wu Tang. It's Wu Tang. It's me, man.
That's Wu Tang. You go dig it. You know, I'm Wu Tang. He's my crew right here.
Right. That was the last time I got a bootleg tape and it was 10 bucks.
And if you guessed it, yeah, I got it from those guys from Staten Island. Yep. Yeah. No,
but I never got a never got a bootleg CD. That was after my time.
No, but I listen, I did the tapes and the CDs. I did all that. Matter of fact, for a short time,
I even had the little record pressing machines, you know, at my disposal for a bit there when
I was, you know, more involved with guys that were more organized. And it was great. You could
actually press records, you know, straight up, though. I mean, I would only get maybe about 100
of them a day or whatever. But a regular record sold in the store for like seven bucks. You sold
these things for 20. So how about how about old office equipment? You ever heard of Pitney Bowes?
They made office equipment. Oh, yeah, sure. And they also made these things called cashier check
machines. And it's like a thing. You put the check, slide it, and it puts the amount you type
in the amount. It's like an old you have to move the pegs. Right. Oh, yeah. And it puts the amount
with a color bars over it and like a rasper looking thing. Right. Yeah. That's the thing
where you actually got to manually move the dial with your finger. Yeah. Two, three. Yeah. And it
writes it out in cursive the amount. And it's it's it writes it out in like almost like a scan line
with different colors. Someone I know got one of those for about 50 bucks. It's a two thousand
dollar machine a long time ago. And he caught he did some research on his Social Security and
birth certificate and actually got a routing number from the Treasury. He used he had a bunch
of numbers attached to that. I guess one of them would have been the routing numbers. He put the
routing number on the check and he wrote it out for seventy five dollars. He went to a bank and
said, is this good? Actually, he sent it in somewhere and they said it was good. Right.
Because it was a signature. And then he kept going up. I said, you keep going into the tens
of thousands. It'll still be good, but someone will investigate and you'll get busted. And they
got busted. Yeah. Once you break. I think it's once you go over on a personal level, if you go
over, what is it, nine thousand nine hundred ninety nine, like even a penny over that,
you're done. That's that's where it triggers. Well, I'm not because in other words, if you
well, I'm not anyone who knows how it works. GE doesn't write. Microsoft doesn't. People do
because people are unconditionally endorsing means you can do anything to me. Right.
But you have to know how to do conditional endorsements. Like, for example,
when you look, let's say people that might have sight impairment get leeway. Right. With the IRS
and other authorities. Right. It's not because they're sympathetic to your condition. It's
because they have not put out any of anything official for the sight impaired. Right. I happen
to be familiar with this. Yes. Right. And because they haven't put out statements for the sight
impaired officially, they can't hold you responsible for what they want to do to you.
All right. It's very interesting. We used to have fun. Homeland Security at the border used to
seize boats and cash and all that in the Mexican border. And they have to post it. The Treasury
does to post it under the Treasury Department. This is what we seized and all this. And you'll
go up for auction. So we used to call up down there by Nogales and say, we want an appointment
to have access to the cash that you have. And they're like, why? I said, because I want to
take all the serial numbers down and claim them, you know, each serial number. And they wouldn't
let us. And finally, we got through to someone. So why are you letting us do this? This is according
to law. You're not doing anything illegal. What you're saying is not illegal, but we just don't
want you to do it. So when you get to that point where they want to hurt, you know, right, blatantly
tell you, we don't we we know what the law is and we know that, you know, but we just don't care.
No, you can't do it. Right. So it's interesting. Yeah. But you can do that. By the way, when cash is
out there, you just say, hey, look, I need to go and get the serial numbers off of that.
And if you do, people used to ask me, someone said, why don't you talk about that? You know,
writing serial numbers down. The serial numbers are on commercial instruments paper for a reason.
It's for what's called competent record keeping. But and it's on commercial paper, by the way,
if you could find it, there's a statute, you know, the bank notes, checks, anything you that has a
serial number or index number or transaction number is called commercial paper. Right.
There is a code that says that anyone dealing with it is expected and presumed to be an expert
in commercial paper. Right. That's pretty ruthless. So if you don't act like an expert in it, guess
what they're going to do? They're going to act like expert scumbags to you. Right. So and you got
to kick a third to them somehow. That's not that bad. But most Americans are paying about 80 percent,
not 30 percent. Slaves used to pay 10 percent. Average Americans pay 80 percent. How? Well,
they get 30 percent off their paycheck and then everything else gets taxed. All the utilities
are taxed. All the sales purchases are taxed. And then the ancillary fees that are added on
taxes and inflation is a tax. And I think I've said that before. Chuck, let's say 20 years ago,
if we put 20 grand away. So and we have a time machine and we're going to show up 20 years in
the future. And when we show up, we want to look cool. I don't want a time machine. We're going
to buy some new dig, some new clothes and we're going to go buy a new car. Right. So we already
put 20 grand away. So we show up 20 years later with a time machine ready to buy a new car,
20 grand. They're going to laugh at you. Right. I think the cheapest car now is 30
or something. You know, some there might be something under 20, but you know what I mean?
Well, let's say in 1950s, you put three thousand dollars away to get a new car.
You show up in the year 2020. Right. Seventy years later with your time machine, you don't
want to look dated. So you go buy a new car with three thousand dollars. Right. Well,
even all the way up to the 1970s, 10 grand would have covered a new car for you. No problem. Yeah.
Average car was under four or five. I remember in 76, the Cadillac Seville was the first car,
American car to go stock, American car to go over ten thousand dollars. I was 1975. It was a big
deal. They advertised it. First American car to sticker price more than ten thousand dollars.
Cadillac Seville coming out. You know, I know that because of my neighbor. Neighbors bought one.
But anyway. So what does this have to do with anything? Yin and yang. It's just the way
things move. It's just the flow. But anyway, 80. When you factor in inflation,
80 to 90 percent inflation is a tax. Right. Yeah. So, yeah. Anyway, I think the dollar,
by the way, now buying power is less than a penny when you measure it against lawful money.
The actual current dollar that people call a dollar is less than a penny in value compared
to a real dollar. Right. I mean, you can take a look at if you wanted an interesting comparison.
OK, you take a look at a 1923 dollar, a silver dollar. Right. So how much is that dollar worth
today currently? Right. And you divide that. It's about 30 bucks. It's really
conservatively 20. So that would make it a dollar, a nickel worth of nickels buying power. Right.
About what? But what the it hasn't. They're leaving. There's many reasons to leave the
silver market low. Right. You understand that because it's an industrial commodity
and they know that they'll shoot themselves in the foot if they bring it up in price. But even
with the manipulation, you're still looking at a nickel to the dollar. So, you know, with silver
as a measure. Yeah. And if you use silver as a measure, gasoline is pretty cheap because
it that means that gasoline back in the 70s cost about 12, 13 dollars a gallon in today's money.
Right. Remember, it was about 70 cents. Yes. Right. So it's a big be around 12 or 13.
If you measured a silver, then was a dollar. You can go to a bank and get, I think, for a dollar
20. You can get a silver dollar. Right. A little bit over a dollar. But nonetheless, the actual
buying power practically, you know, when you're going to the stove, buying stuff, it's about a
penny. In other words, if you look at what it costs to buy a shovel today and what it costs to
buy a shovel before 1913. Right. It's about that much difference. And when you have fiat currency
like this or inflation, what people don't understand, they're in a culture. That's why I
say you could do anything to humans if you wipe out the previous generations in memory of history
and the new ones that are raised are raised in a certain society where things are a certain way.
They never they will never figure it out. So in other words, what a shovel cost in 1913 is what
a shovel cost in the year 1613 and what a shovel cost in the year 13. Right. Because it was based
against the fixed price of gold and silver. So by the way, the score, you hear the term,
I have a score to settle. You know, of course, that means the 20. It's a 20 dollar gold piece
as a score. So you're right. Score was 20. Even young again. Let's let's not forget.
We won't. I'm famous for tangents and I'm famous for taking a tangent off of a tangent. But
and I'm also famous for going back. So how famous are you? Yeah, right. We got into the basics last
time, like the contemplative nature of it. But what's what's what really here's the thing. The
most functional aspect of when people hear the balancing of energies and all that is regarding
to health. So maybe we'll steer towards that more now. OK. The yin, I think, talked about
anything you eat to nourish is yin all. You know, if it's if you water, air, food, any food is all
yin. All things which you can gain energy from are energetic and therefore for life that had to.
Yeah, right. In other words, in other words, to sustain a living soul or a life form is yin.
So that which is life sustaining is yin, period. All of it. Yeah. Now, once you look at that food
as a category, then you could subdivide it. Well, this is in the middle. This is very
yin and this is yang amongst that entire group. So then where is the yang come in? Well,
once you take that sustenance and it rebuilds the effect of the sustenance, develops the yang
once it meets the body. Right. So let's say the hardness of your skin, if you have a thick skin,
it's more yang than a thin skin, that soft skin, which is more yin. Right. So depending on your
diet, if you're eating things that are more yang, but not too yang, more near the middle,
but leaning a little towards yang, you'll have a durable skin, which would be yang.
But if you're eating things that are very yin or leaning on yin and near the middle,
you'll have a moderate skin, but a very yin, you'll have a very thin skin and which mosquitoes
like. And they could see that. They know that. By the way, animals know their prey.
They know their food. Right. So don't blame the mosquitoes. We should get bit. I don't get bit.
Even in Houston, Texas, where it's very swampy in some areas, the bayous and all that,
people would just, if they didn't run from the car to inside and they walked, they ended up
with 10 mosquito bites just walking from the car to the front door. Right. With me, I just sat
outside all day. I didn't get bit at all. Right. But if you saw us eating together, how I ate and
what I ate, even though it was the same dishes and all that, you'd see I was very different. Right.
Well, what about the how outside of the what? Because you talked a bunch about the what,
how about the how? What's important about the how and the preparation?
Yeah, let's do that. OK, give an example. Years ago, more than three decades ago,
I was thinking it would be fun to work at the Alaskan pipeline. So I went to this thing and
they talked about it and they said, well, take this home and read it. You know, I went late
to the meeting and they give you these things called cut sheets, which is like, you know,
just whatever old fashioned way of calling something that's Xerox copied. Take home and read.
Right. And it said that if you decide to go up there two weeks before you go up there,
you're supposed to for two weeks go to the stove and give yourself a tub of cool whip,
miracle whip. Well, I mean, cool whip, whip cream, a tub of that. Right. Get yourself a
bottle of corn oil and put a cup of corn oil in the cool whip, stir it up and eat a cup of that
every day for two weeks before you go up there. Right. I was like, oh, my goodness. And I said,
you know what that is? That's synthetic seal blubber, isn't it? Right. OK. All that oil and
fat. Right. And basically it said, if you do this, you'll have an easy time up here in Alaska.
Right. And I was like, hmm, that's very interesting because it sounds a lot like
you're eating seal or whale blubber or something. Right. Guess what people up there live on?
Seal and whale blubber. Well, not anymore, but typically that was traditional. Right.
So it was good to build like a natural insulator. Right. It would help to keep you warm.
Yeah. Sort of. Sort of. What it would do, it would it would sounds a lot like eating seasonally or
eating locally. Right. If you were to go to the tropics and work on the Panama Canal back in the
day when the French tried, what did they eat? Oh, French food from Europe. Well, that didn't work
too well. So we got all that malaria. Right. Right. And don't believe the quinine aspect. Yeah,
it is true. If you take the quinine from the quinine tree or whatever in tonic water. Right.
Let's say I think they denature that, by the way. Anything you buy that might have something that's
medicinal, like rye or quinine or poppy or whatever, they make sure it's denatured
right before you get it. So it doesn't have most of its natural properties.
So what they did was they were looking for people that were used to working in those areas or from
those areas because they were more in balance. So this is the how. Very simple. You could use the
moon. You could use the sun. OK, if you use the sun, that would be a daily event. If you use the
month, it would be a the moon. It would be a monthly event. Or you can use a seasonal event. And
basically you would look at it as the three main seasons that do you have with seasonal. You have
the two main seasons, summer and winter. Those are the main. And then you have spring and fall,
which are transitions. Transitional. OK, don't most people say, well, there are four seasons,
Greek. There's winter, spring, summer, fall. You know, well, you know, right. I'm like, no,
no, there's actually two seasons. There is winter and summer and the spring and the fall are
transitions. OK, so once you see it that way, it seems like now you what do you mean transition?
Transition means I shouldn't, you know, transition means change. Right. Transition means it's not
steady. Transition means I'm going from one thing, one thing to another. Yes. Yeah. But when you
establish it in your mind, the spring season, well, it's just spring. What do we do in the spring?
You know, what do we do in the fall? You know, take pictures and whatever, fly kites, whatever,
you know. No. So these transitional seasons are when you transition from winter to summer and then
from summer to winter. Right. OK, so that's the how the in other words, what the reason I'm
emphasizing this because they've done a big disservice to even children. You know, there's
winter, spring, summer, fall. Right. You know, as well. Then you grow up thinking, well, you know,
this is just how I go about things because this is how I was told without realizing really what's
going on. So in essence, if you were to look at the basic energies, it takes summer. Let's just
take summer growth. Right. Energy is going upward. How do you know? Well, the things are growing fast.
Right. Which do when things grow fast and hardy. Which way are they going? They're going up.
Right. Upward and outward. Yeah. Yeah. The typical heat concept of chemical heat rises. Right. Goes
up. Right. But actually upward, upward and outward. Both. Yeah. Same time. But what's
interesting is if you go to in summertime, the atmosphere is colder above, by the way,
than it is in winter. The higher up you go, the colder it is in the summer. But that's another
that's more on the ether discussion. But the typical chemical idea of heat, if you, let's say,
let a room or a box heat up. Yeah. The heat wants to rise up. Right. You open the windows at the
top, let the heat out. It's chemical heat. OK, so everything's rising and expanding and going up.
Right. But the direction of of it is young and heat is considered young and the effect will be
Ying. Right on you. It will slow you down, make you soft. And then when you run out of things
that allow that you to slow down and become soft, you end up becoming young. You dry out. OK.
OK. All right. So that is the fundamental aspect of summer. Now, the fundamental aspect of winter
would be things are not growing. Leaves fall down. Fruit falls down. Everything's going down.
Right. Nothing's coming up. Things are going down. The leaves fall. Snowfall. Right. Snow.
Not only does it fall, but it stays on the ground. It doesn't stay up in the air. So everything's
going down. And that would be Ying. Right. The cold is Ying. Right. But if you get something
too Ying or cold, it starts to get in. It runs out of its ability to balance that Ying. It starts
to get hard. It becomes young. Right. Comes its opposite. So like water. Right. Or things
freeze and they become hard. That means they've got too much of the winter contraction. Right.
All right. So most people, if most people do actually, I was thinking most people have
problems in the spring and the fall because of pollen. Right. But that's one way to look at it.
But really, the overall challenges come at the height of winter and at the height of summer,
because when you're most heated up, you have difficulties. You know, it's harder to breathe
just in general because and I've always thought of it as the air is larger. The molecules of the
air are larger. Therefore, you're getting less air. That's the chemical. Just in other words,
if you can die from it, you know, let's just get to the point. Sure. You'll probably die
in the summertime from overheating and you'll probably die in the winter from freezing to death.
But in the spring and the fall, you won't die from the extreme, you know, extreme conditions
don't come in and do the extreme thing. So until the winter. Yeah. How many times in New York? Oh,
it's a hundred degrees in New York today. Twenty five people died. I'm like, damn,
what? Right. Or in England, there was a big thing. They hid it from the media. They
pensioners couldn't afford to. Old people couldn't afford to warm their flats and they were
frozen solid. Right. Right. Because the pensions were so low they relied on. But OK, so most I
want to address the transition point here, which I did once just to recap.
And I'll do a recap of the recap. What I mean here is in the springtime, you transition from
the winter to summer, which means now things are starting to go upward. Right. And people say,
oh, it's the pollen. Yeah, it's the pollen. But it's the energy, the pollen carries.
You know, here's the thing. What's interesting about it. You can take someone who has allergies.
It's very, very sensitive to pollen, you know, in spring blossoms and things like that. Yeah. And
put them in a clean room, totally isolated, and they'll still have those allergies because it's
the energy, not the the material. Right. In other words, the condition won't be as bad because the
material is not there to aggravate it. But they'll still have that feeling. They'll still be very
sensitive until the sun, until the season is completely over. Right. They actually say it
like I don't want to go outside. I feel it. I'm very sensitive. Right. But you're inside. There's
no pollen in here. You've got to have a filter here, have a filter there. Right. Well, OK,
so there we go. There's something to it. You can literally change the actual chemical condition.
Right. Like, for instance, if I'm in a house and it's very hot outside, very hot, very humid
outside. Now I've got air conditioning. So the conditions in the place where I am have been
adjusted by the air conditioner. Chemically, chemically, they've been adjusted. So around me,
I should feel fine. Right. But I don't. I still feel the effect of the heat or
when it's very rainy outside. I have a lot of injuries I've had. Right. So I've got, you know,
achy bones. I describe it as all the time. Arthritis. Well, I don't have the arthritis,
but I do have to get it. I feel pain in places where I've been injured before
when the atmospheric pressure changes. So the thing is, it's raining outside. I still feel
the effects of the rain outside, even though I'm in a dry place.
Sure. Well, that's the energy part. You see the and when you learn to go into balance with the
energy part that takes care of the chemical material part. Here's the I've done experiments
with this. You can have a room at seventy five degrees, dead seventy five degrees and boil water.
Water will boil at the temperature normally boils up, but it'll take in the winter time. It'll take
longer to boil than in the summer, even though you have to do an experiment all year round,
keep everything the same temperature, the temperature of the room, temperature of the
water. And you'll notice that it always boils faster. It takes less time to come to a boil
in the summer than in the winter, even though the room temperature and the water temperature is
exactly the same. That's an energetic effect. And this is always excluded in science, by the way.
They leave that out. That's why they keep repeating experiments so they could do this
exclusion. No, we don't want this one. We want the ones that support what we want to tell people.
Right. Of course. So. Yeah. So. OK, so here when we go into the springtime, things transitioning
to going up so you can get a head start on that. We covered this already on one of the I think
single digit episodes. You get a head start by getting a light leafy teas. You know, I don't
like the word tea because you can make tea out of anything. Right. I think I went over that.
So a green tea, if you don't want something caffeinated, you can get a mint tea. Look at
the plant. And, you know, the was it the Autobahn drawings. Right. Or compare or a
plant comparison in height. Learn what you do. Wikipedia, believe it or not, is pretty good for
this. When you want to pick a tea, put in what the tea is from, let's say mint and then go to
put in the mint plant and it'll tell you how high it grows. Right. OK. Gives you a height. Right.
And then if you let's say you want green tea, right. Go look up the green tea, whatever,
and the plant and how high it grows and the higher it grows, the more it's going to stretch
you up into that direction. Right. Well, let me ask you about the pine needle tea,
then, in that case, since you mentioned these other two, because that's another thing you can
do. Right. Pine needles. Yeah. Pine needle. It's an evergreen. Now, most people have the idea that
an evergreen doesn't change. It's the same. It's not. It does change. The color changes extremely so
between seasons. And of course, it has a different type of most evergreens are not single trees. You
know, they're connected at the roots. Right. And they like to do that. And also the way that they
make pine cones and all this other stuff. Right. And their shape. They only grow at a certain
altitude also. Right. As you go higher, you take a hyperbolic. The energetic part of the evergreen
is thus a hyperbola or a funnel, a vortex funnel. Right. OK. Turn it upside down and the trees will
always start to turn the hyperbolic shape upside down. OK. And the bottom would be sea level or
slightly below sea level and start doing horizontal lines and scale at thousands of feet throughout
the hyperbolic shape going up. And if you start cataloging what trees grow at what elevation,
they fit exactly in that hyperbolic shape. So the hyperbola, if you turn upside down like a
trumpet, it would be very wide and low at the bottom. And as it goes up, it gets skinnier and
taller. Right. Right. A hyperbolic shape. By the way, science completely academia. They avoid
hyperbolic shapes. They might talk about parabolas because that has to do with military weapons.
Right. The parabolic curve on a projectile. OK. Right. Yeah. But they avoid hyperbolic. So if
take a hyperbolic shape, put it upside down, draw a horizontal line and you start fitting your
trees as they go up and you'll notice the trees follow that hyperbolic shape. Exactly. So as we
get to the higher, higher elevations, you know, the hyperbolic curve is very narrow at the bottom
and very pointy at the top. Guess what that looks like? Yeah. Right. Yeah. Yeah. And then, well,
there's different types of evergreens that are shorter and squatter at different different heights.
Oh, yeah. But it's a typical like typical pine tree, Christmas tree kind of deal,
you know, common. Right. I'm not talking about the holiday. The pine tree will do both. It'll
accommodate you see pine trees. If you go out in the summer and look at a pine tree in the forest,
it's chilly, chill. Right. It's fine. Right. It's not burning in the right. It's not like,
hey, man, you know, turn on the A.C. or cover me. The sun's killing me. You know, nothing like that.
Yeah, it's just fine. And it's just fine in the winter. It looks like it does change quite a bit
in the winter. You'll notice it takes on more of a bluish gray green. Right. Yeah. People don't
realize the shift in the green. They just think it's green all the time. Yes, it is green,
but it's different shades. It's a metallic it's more of a metallic green versus a very,
very deep forest green in the summer. But all right. So what that does for you, it will it
will take you very quickly up into an uplifting, both energetic, uplifting and very narrow,
right. Energetic beam through the body. Good for like I said, if you take a pine needle tea or
something like that, it's a very strong astringent. It will stay in the body for a long time because
it's very focused energy. But someone it would I would not suggest it for someone who is having
trouble in the springtime with allergies. It would probably have a strong astringent quality,
meaning they they have clean. They go to the bathroom really well for a few days. Right. But
then it'll just lean over and it might actually weaken some aspects that could be nurtured with
something that is not as extreme as that. And I wouldn't call it very extreme. But for the purposes
of this recitation dissertation, I would say it is more extreme. Right. The point only because of
not seasonality, but its location. Right. But but here's the thing. If you live in a higher
elevation place that does have pine trees, yeah, you could work on it. But the thing about the pine
tree, it's not transitory. In other words, it's not it's not it's perennial versus an annual
or something that doesn't really react very much like something like a mint plant will react,
be more reactive from winter to spring to summer than a pine tree. Because if you look at a mint
plant or a mint tree or mint bush, it's pretty much dead in the winter. Right. And it comes to
life in the spring and really blooms out in the summer. So that would be a representation of
something that has transitory aspects. Right. In other words, it's following the seasons more
more than a pine tree would visually. So that would be more recommended. OK. You see, because it has
that transitory energy, you see, when you do things that are medicinal like that, if you
you're doing it as a medicinal, it's it's good to have something that transitions. It doesn't
really last that long when you're doing something as a stable, stable staple or stable staple.
Right. Adding it to your diet and it's geographic, a pine tree like the pine needles. You can do that
all year round and incorporate that in your diet. Right. Let's say it would be a consistent thing.
So what I would suggest is when you start looking at your plants, look at how tall they grow and how
fast they grow. Right. So if you look at something like corn, for example, which corn is pretty tall
and it grows so fast, you can actually hear it growing. You can do a recording of it as the
fibers are expanding. I don't know if you've heard that before, but it's it's known by people in
Nebraska and places where they grow it. No, I can't say I've heard that before. I mean, I've seen I've
seen a lot of corn growing. I mean, you remember Jersey corn was always good. Yeah. Yeah. If you go
to a big place, a lot of cornfields and it's not too windy and you spend the day there and you leave
the cornfield, you notice how quiet it is. Yeah. You go back to the cornfield and you're like,
it's really noisy here. Well, because it has a very subtle crunchy. It's almost below audible,
but it's still there. It's kind of like ambient noise. When I play music during the day, I turn
the amplifier, let's say up to like 10 or 11. But when at nighttime, when all the ambient noise,
everybody's asleep, there are no cars in anywhere around. I'm not I'm not in a noisy place at all,
but just in the city. If I turn it up to nine, it's too loud because of the ambient noise. Right. You
could do this experiment at home. You ever notice if you want to listen to music late at night while
you're sleeping, you have to keep it really low because where the normal, even low, low,
normal during the day was too loud. Right. Because it's the ambient noise. So it's an ambient. So
again, look at how fast things grow. So if they grow very as they grow vertically, here's the
thing. They are more and more young, but at the rate of their growth and their final height
determines if they got from the ground to that height very quickly that now it's a yin energy
because yin is expansive. Right. You see. So even though going up is young, something that grows
quickly and to a height ends up having a yin manifestation in the body. Right. So, again,
just to recap, if the spring comes along and you're having what they call sensitivity to it,
it's because you're not in line with that seasonal transition. So the way you get in line with it is
by taking things in that are transitional, that grow. Here's a very simple way to do it.
Sprouts. Start eating sprouts when the springtime comes. What are sprouts? Right. New growth. Right.
That's what you expect in springtime. Right. Sprouts. Things that grow to a moderate height.
My thing is not growing more than chest height. Well, who's chest height? Right. Or waist height.
Okay. Right. If it grows higher than that quickly, it's going to have the opposite effect,
even though it's going in a young direction. Okay. That gets more advanced. But this is just
generally, I want to give generally, this is the recap of what we did on a previous episode on that.
Now, if you do the contrary, which is the wintertime, as wintertime comes,
you want to go towards the ground, things that are very low towards the ground or things that
are in the ground, like root vegetables. But there are a lot of things that are in the ground as root
vegetables that are considered nightshades. Right. And they are there for a different reason than
the nightshades are mostly there to nurture the soil. Right. Okay. To pull excess nitrates out.
Right. Like, you know, beans put nitrates. Okay. You can study what plants do in their
complementary plants. Right. But, you know, it's interesting. Here's here's one. If you're Italian,
you'll like this. You know, if you plant basil and tomatoes together, they complement each other.
Right. Naturally in, you know, in the garden. But you know what else? They also complement each
other in the pot. Right. Absolutely. Yeah. Yeah. So you can you can go that way. That's why
there are many things that may even consider a nightshade that complement
up another plant and they go well together in the pot, you know, like potato stews and things like
that. Okay. Now, recently, what I've been doing is suggesting that people get Lundberg brown rice.
Lundberg is a brand only because it's the highest quality you can get still reasonable,
more fairly accessible and Burdock root, which is in the thistle family. There's wild thistle.
There's very but Burdock. And the reason I suggest this is because let's say you're new
to Greek speak or you're listening to the Sonics and Greeks talking a lot, but not showing anything
or whatever, you know, for all this stuff. It's a lot of talk. So what I do for show here is here's
a simple way to create a condition for yourself that is very bracing and binding internally.
In other words, it's it's it transcends all of the seasonality. Right. It's just like a basic.
It's like, you know, when you're painting, it's good to put a primer under it. Depend.
Doesn't matter what color. If you're putting a summer or winter color on the wall,
you put a primer. Right. It's a better paint job. Right. So this is like a primer in a mechanical
sense. The the rice. A lot of people say it's carbs. Yeah, it's carbs. But it's a whole it's
a whole grain which has more digestible, quote unquote, amino acids. I don't like saying protein
because no one has ever seen a protein. They just see amino acids, which are both in you'll find
amino acids and carbohydrates and what they call proteins and what they call carbs. So it's
right. Don't I'm not even going to get into calories because, you know, calories are irrelevant
unless you're pooping charcoal. Right. Right. So the whole joke about that. But the the whole
the wholeness and the thing is, I haven't suggested this in the past and I'm going
more into it. The burdock and the brown rice, because first of all, you never want to suggest
someone make something that they can't make well. You never want to. Here's the thing. And
even in Japan, they have certain purveyors of fine ingredients and they will refuse to sell
it to someone who cannot cook it. Why? Why? Because if you have this wonderful, exclusive,
quality rice and you sell it to a restaurant who can't prepare it well, what is that restaurant
going to say? That rice ain't shit. Rice isn't so good. It ruins your reputation. Right.
So to make the brown rice properly, you need a pressure cooker, a pseudo pressure cooker.
Personally, I don't use a real pressure cooker anymore with the rubber gasket because I could
taste that rubber. It's exposed inside, even though it's thermal rubber. So I make my own.
I have very fine, let's say, pots with a fine fitting lid and you put a weight on it and it
just as well. Learn how to cook that medium, whatever instructions they give you, run the
medium heat a little bit more, not just low. But we'll get into that on the cooking and the burdock
root. You cut it on a bias, which then it looks like an ellipse, very thin. Right. And you lay
the ellipses down and you cut them again vertically in a julienne cut, very, very fine cut matchstick
cut. And you saute that with some seasonings and you eat that with the rice in addition to whatever
else you want to have with that. Even fish or beans or I wouldn't suggest meat because that's
like an over to overkill. A lot of these restaurants, they serve like this health, healthy
food and they'll serve brown rice with salmon or brown rice with it. Whenever you do an animal,
do a white rice. Don't do a brown rice. It's too much for the body to handle. Right. Do a white,
a plain starch, you know. Right. Like in other words, if you're going to have pasta,
don't do a whole wheat pasta when a bolognese sauce with a meat sauce to the regular. If you
do a whole wheat pasta, do it with just a veggie sauce. Right. Right. Right. It's its own, quote,
unquote, protein in air quotes. So I've been suggesting that I've gotten some feedback
from people. They were like, yeah, that Bloomberg race on this. How do you feel from it? You know,
just like you said, you get this energy. You know how when you have a really good steak dinner and
you don't overeat and you feel this rush of energy in your body. Yeah. Right. Or power or whatever,
you know, it's I call it bracing and you'll feel that, but it's longer lasting. It's not like a
carbo load or anything like that. So when people start doing something basic like that and they
feel the difference, right, then it's easier and it's more credible to start looking at the rest
of the stuff. Right. Because you've already started. You see the effects. Right. But if
you start talking about, oh, do this and do that and do this or you could do this or do that and
haven't done any of it, it's like, well, what do I do first? It sounds like, you know,
foreign, you know, whatever. So that's why I just keep suggesting people start with the brown rice
and the and the burdock root. Right. Because the burdock root is the most bracing vegetable you
could possibly eat. It grows a straight taproot down into the ground. The top of it looks like
you have these pointy, jagged leaves, blossoms that look almost like clove blossoms. Right.
And this is going to do during any season, any season, any season. Yes. But particularly in
the winter, if you were to do the brown rice and burdock, burdock soup, burdock saute, burdock added
to ingredients, you'll pass the winter very, very well. In other words, you'll be cool. You won't be
cold. See, in the summer you want to be warm, not hot. And in the winter you want to be cool,
not cold. I noticed that most people, especially Westerners or Americans,
they want to be cold in the summer and hot in the winter. That's too extreme.
Warm in the summer, not hot and cool in the winter. Right now, not cold. Don't try to
adjust your body to the lower temps and adjust your body to the higher temps.
Now, I've had this weirdness. And look, the way that I see it is people I've encountered
over and over again throughout my entire life. During the summertime, they turn their houses
into iceboxes. I mean, they crank up the diet. It's ridiculous. Yeah. That was more with
the millions and billions of tons of coal were probably burned to keep the air conditioners
going when salmon, I was just joking, when salmon was in vogue. A decade ago, remember,
it was like salmon, this, salmon, that. In the news, they said, oh, the government says it's
okay to put collar in salmon. Salmon, this, salmon, that. You're killing people with salmon.
You go into someone's house and they have the thermostat turned on like an icebox, right?
What'd you have for dinner last night? Oh, I love that salmon. What'd you have for lunch
yesterday? I love that salmon. Yeah. Save that for when I've met someone 20 some odd years ago.
I was out in a shirt. She was out in a jacket. It's a fall. She was cold and I wasn't. And I
went over to where she lived and she had bananas on the counter. It was like, you know, in the 50s
and 60s outside. I took the bananas away, poached some salmon, said, eat that for three days. In
three days, she was outside with me in a shirt feeling just fine, right? Because the salmon
will adjust your body. Right. Right. Now this, uh, you notice how it always goes back to, you
know, how I say eat seasonally, you know, how I make a short metaphor on that, you know, notice
now how I'm getting a little more detail into this. It goes back to eating seasonally. It does.
Right. Yeah. But seasonally, a little finer. You see the problem with commerce and getting your
food is they bring it from far away places and it's exotic, right? And it doesn't pertain. So
you feel like you're, you're an advantage because you can eat anything you want. Right. You hear
people say that I'll eat anything I want. Right. You think that that's an advantage to you. Right.
You know, uh, here's the thing. Uh, I use the car analogy, you know, Mitsubishi
engines in the early nineties. If you talked about getting one, oh no, don't get those men.
They, they, they smoke after like a year, they start smoking. You know, you hit the gas pedal
and the smoke comes out the back. Well, I was like, oh man, Mitsubishi, they're famous for
precision. I looked into it and they were one of the first car manufacturers to ever specify
using only synthetic oil only. And what did people do? They went to a Jiffy lube or whatever
those places. And when they went, they got the special oil change. You think they're going to
put five quarts of synthetic glue, which was very expensive. It was way more expensive. Yeah. Yeah.
You think they're going to do that or they're just going to, you think they're going to look
at the manual, you think they're going to look at the sticker where it says synthetic only,
the guy doesn't even know how to read probably English. Right. So anyway, so what do you think
happened? They got a bad reputation for right. Well, who is it? Mitsubishi's fault. Maybe they
should have took it a little step further and said, Hey, if we sell these cars here,
no one's going to pay attention. Right. But that's not how it's done. So the body is very
much like that. Right. So you go to the store, uh, grocery store and you see pineapples all year
round or this, you know, if maybe sometimes not all year round bananas, bananas or year round
though. Yeah. Bananas. Yeah. Yeah. So I've done this analogy many times where a school teacher
who I've known a few, I got sick this winter. I got, I caught it from the kids. Right. You hear
that? Right. I work kids. I caught a cold. Okay. But you know what? Here's something really
interesting though. The woman from Calcutta, India who teaches math and the guy from Beijing,
China who teaches science in the same school didn't get sick, right? They didn't get cold
from the same children because they know how they change from period to period, right? Yeah. So same
kids go to a different class. They're, they're exposed to those teachers that came from other
countries and still adhere to their traditional diets. Didn't get sick. Why? That's why you tell
me because the children, if you follow them on the grocery store with the mom and the shopping cart,
what look, examine what's in the shopping cart. The teacher goes to a similar grocery store,
look at her shopping cart. Guess what? In the winter, almost identical food with some,
but similar, you know, you see no concept. Um, and this is approved. I've done this. I've,
I've been looking at this concept now since the mid eighties and I've studied it. Whenever I heard
someone said, even in a conversation in a restaurant or somewhere, yeah, I got a cold
from, I caught it from the kids at school. I'd get up and say, hi, I'd like to meet you.
You're a teacher or so-and-so. Yeah. Uh, which school? And I would actually take time out and
investigate all the teachers get sick or just this one. Right. And it turns out just like I gave it
over and over. I would look at these scenarios. What's funny is that sometimes I tell people
I've been studying medicine for over 35 years. They look at me and like, wow. You know, cause
doctors don't speak that way. Right. Right. They don't speak that way. They never study anything.
Well, unless they're told to, or unless some of them do, some of them do, but the specialty guys
will tell you, you know, continuously whatever. Yeah. So are you a doctor? I'm like, no,
are you kidding me? In order to be a doctor, you have to, you have to be state certified.
If you notice anything, the state puts out, you know, first of all, anything past the eighth grade
is a shame. Right. But, oh, but when you go to apply to medical school, uh, uh, they put this
pixie dust on your head and suddenly you become intelligent. Right. Yeah. The magic dust. Yeah.
Right. Yeah. Some of them do take magic dust by the way to stay in those schools. You know,
if you know what I mean? Well, there's that. So anyway, uh, so what I'd like to do is share
these perspectives and they're very, very, very, very simple, but here's the thing from mentioning,
hearkening back to the last one, you can have five people with the same condition and they go
into a Chinese apothecary, you know, and the guy comes out from the back to do a diagnosis.
All five of them have the same thing. I don't know what, what do you want to say?
What's the condition people typically get, you know, the sniffles, sore throat, right? Sure. A
cold, a cold. Yeah. Right. Well, I assure you the five people that go in there, it doesn't matter
if they're white, black, yellow, green, whatever, they're going to have to be diagnosed separately.
And they're going to get a different prescription. You know, what, what the, he writes something down
and the lady behind the counter goes, opens. He looked like fish bowls, but you know, take some
mouth, put wraps in a piece of paper, boil this in a pot and drink it. Right. So it's going to be
different for everyone based on your condition and your constitution. Now that is very different
from now. They have TV commercials. If you have this, go take this medicine. Is that just for
one person or for everybody watching the TV commercial to do it? No, no, that's everybody.
Here we go. The same chemical compound, because you put a description, well, not all of the
symptoms, but many of them. So therefore this. Yeah. Yeah. So how the contrast there,
and I hate to say Eastern medicine. Yes. Cause it's been preserved by the Easterners is more
accurate to the Western medicine, which is all pharmaceutical, whatever, which is fine. I mean,
well, actually it's not fun. The word pharma means poison in Greek. They call it pharma key,
which is poison. Um, but, uh, the, the knowledge base, for example, that one has like, again,
let's take the four people that have the common cold and they start using the principles that I
mentioned when they study root vegetables, they will naturally gravitate to some, some of those
people will gravitate to some things and others will gravitate to others. And that will probably
be more correct for you on that level. What I found out with this, usually when people
understand the principles of energy, this is where the individual intuitive, the spiritual,
all this stuff comes together is I find that when you have a person that says winter's coming
and I understand it's energetic and I need to, uh, my intake of food should be things that growing
downward, right? In other words, root vegetables are very low to the ground or Hardy. Like for
example, if you grow things like kale or collards or a Swiss chard, it seems like those things have
antifreeze in them. If you have a winter freeze, everything dies, but these plants are still fine.
Right. Right. Imagine a lettuce in a freeze, what it looks like the next day, right? Mush
collard greens or a mustard greens or something like that. No problem.
Most likely not the mustard, most likely the collard, the kale, the Swiss chard.
You think it's pumped up with antifreeze, right? It looks just fine. It could take the freeze.
Mustard greens don't stand up like that. I thought they did.
They, no, not the ones I have here. They're very too thin. No, they, they will. They can. They're
in between. They're in between. Let's say, yeah, they can, they can, uh, the more peppery they are,
the less they hold up. All right. But here's my point. So if someone is looking for those,
uh, greens that have the antifreeze built in, you could look up frost Hardy greens
and root vegetables. Four people have the same cold. Instead of going and watching the TV,
I take the robot tests and whatever the, whatever, whatever they tell you to take or pills.
When they start researching, researching on this on four people, same condition that they need
winter's coming and they need to go for this, uh, frost Hardy plant or root vegetables.
Uh, you put four people, uh, let's say four computer terminals and you have them to pick
out on their own, which root vegetables they would prefer to go and shop or cook or, or have
someone shop and cook for them and which greens you'll notice, uh, the, the four people most
likely will have four different menus for different desires. Some might be, it'll be a little similar.
Some will overlap, but not, not all four will be identical. And believe it or not, once a human,
a man, woman, mankind understands these principles, they will make the more specific
right decision to suit their own body and specific on their own. You don't need someone to diagnose
you. Isn't that fantastic? That is that you will naturally gravitate towards the right thing for
you. Yeah. That's what, that's, what's so interesting about this concept is that you end
up being your own quote unquote doctor. How, I mean, how self-sufficient is that, right?
That's the best way to be. I mean, look, if you can prevent the problem to begin with
by staying in tune with what's going on and utilizing the energetic guidelines, the guideposts,
uh, it helps you avoid more things than you ever had to contend with, which is better to avoid,
right? Yeah. The point to underscore though, is that, uh, the fine tuning, like which vegetable
you would prefer, even the four root vegetables, one might prefer you, you might have four people
prefer two of one and one of the other, whatever that will, you'll find is more correct. So there's
like this natural order that takes over, but, but here's the thing you said, it's a problem.
You know, it's not a problem. It shows the body is working. What's happening in the body is losing
biological vacuum. Right? So it has to clog you up because obviously it's like, uh, you know,
it's like, Hey, you know, uh, it's like the idiot lights on the dashboard, you know,
that check engine light and all that. Right. It's very much like that. It's like, Hey dummy,
you don't know that you're compromising the vacuum of the body. So what we're going to do
is, uh, where, where do you lose vacuum orifices, right? So we're going to start
plugging up your orifices. And if you don't believe this, by the way, the medical establishment has
taken on this term for that, um, for that, uh, application. And when a woman is pregnant at the
bottom of the cervix, it's what keeps the baby and they call it a mucus plug. Yeah. Yeah. That's
what it's called. So you get, so I used to make jokes about that. You got mucus in your nose.
That's like, you're a pregnant woman's cervix. You know, it's the same thing. And they're looking
at me like, what, you know, it's the same, same reaction to hold something in. Well,
it's true. Now, one of the things about like natural guidance and the things that can be
provided to you, you know, by a simple, you know, just understanding the signals given,
right. It's going to sound strange, but just bear with me a second. In other words,
that's not a problem. Having a cold is not a problem. It means the body's working really
well, but it's uncomfortable to you, right? It's discomfort. But the thing I was going to get at
next was this, uh, the idea that signals are given to you and you have guidance,
which is provided to you by just paying attention to certain things. Okay. You have a desire for
something. Cause you were talking about how people naturally start to pick things. It seems to me as
though sometimes, uh, when you seem to have a desire to eat something, you, you, you suddenly,
uh, have a craving for something. Often this is created out of necessity. I think it's your body
telling you that you need that thing. You know, uh, the typical pregnant woman cravings and three
in the morning, she pushes her husband out of bed. You got to go get me pickles and ice cream
right now. It's just the pregnant woman craving, but I mean, you ever just been sitting, I'm really
in the mood to eat this or that, uh, you know, maybe. Okay. So you're, you're in need of a root
vegetables. Well, maybe you want carrots. Well, here's, let me, let me say something about that.
But if you have no idea of the energy flow and the energy contained there in of these things and how
it really matters, you are pre-programmed and you're going to express what I call emotional
laziness. So you're, you say, uh, most people won't say root veg. Most people will say, I crave
chocolate ice cream or chocolate cake or Doritos or right. Because that's all they know. Right?
So the, the reason for doing these discourses is so you understand that there's these energies
are important and to become familiar with them. Right. And then once the, these choices are put
in front of you, you make a decision. Uh, and that decision, what I'm saying again,
I can't underscore this enough. Each person will make the more proper decision,
but here's the thing. Let's say you're craving a sweet, you know, for example,
as people ask me, what's your favorite food? I'm like, uh, what do you mean? Uh, savory or sweet,
you know, a favorite for dessert, favorite as an entree. You can't ask someone what's my favorite
food. It's like, well, what's your favorite color? You mean for, for what? I mean, interior space,
my clothes, the car, what, what these are stupid questions. Don't even bother. If someone says,
do you believe in God? That's another stupid question. There is no such thing.
Yeah. But with the idea that you're actually, you have some education on this, where you have
an idea about how these things can be addressed. Then it might guide you to, okay. Uh, since I have
a certain feeling, then you, you could have simply a craving for it. Right. So I, you know what,
I really want to eat some potatoes. Okay. Well, why do I want the potatoes? Uh, it starts to come
across. It might start to work together, right? Like both things work together and then your
cravings can become potato. A potato for example, is a nightshade. So it's going to be very yeen,
very expansive. So you don't want to eat much of it, but here's the thing. Let me just get into
potatoes for a second. I'm going to do some solo Sonics on, on this stuff. And I think someone,
Sam posted, it's all ready to go and it will be happening or it is happening. It needs to be
worked out, but on cooking, but here's the thing you ever go to a fast food establishment or a
restaurant, they say French fries, right? Yeah. And like, let me give you an example. A direct
example is a place called in and out burger. And I want to tell him, you got to change that on your
menu. They're not French fries. Why? Because you see the guy, Oh, this is a really good French
fries. Cause they make them fresh. Yeah, they do. You see the guy there, he's peels the potatoes
and he cuts them right there, fries them. And then, uh, salt some and serves them. Those are
not French fries in order to be French fries. You're ready. You take the potato, you peel,
you cut it, you blanch it in boiling water, right? You take the potatoes out, you let them
cool. Then you fry them until they're still white. Take them out, let them cool down. And then you
fry them to crisp them Brown. So it's, it's three times cooked, right? French fry. So if you're just
frying potatoes, like they do it in and out, those are not French fries. Those should be fried
potatoes. I always make a big deal. I go in there and said, you got to change your menu. They're not
French fries. They're fried potatoes. Big difference. Well, that's why the ones in McDonald's are done
that way though, where they take them, they blanch them, they do that already. No, actually. Well,
they're the ones that these main they're, they're pre they're frozen. They're frozen to the second
stage. That's my point is that they're, they're frozen up to that point. They freeze them after
they've done all those other things. Those are still French fries, but when you actually just
cut them up fresh like that and you fry them, you're right. They're just fried potatoes. They're
not French fries. They're fried potatoes. Right, exactly. So here's the point. Why are French
fries so popular and why do they work better than any other potato basically is because the very
yin gets subjected to a young treatment first with water, then young fried, cool down back to
eat and then young fried again. So it's more balanced, believe it or not, than just a fried
potato because you're hitting it. You're hitting it with the young. You remember cooking and food
and heat is young. So, and then the salt is even more young. So a little bit of French fry would
be more balanced than let's say something else. That's why I always suggest big potatoes. I've
seen too many people heat up a massive oven and put two lonely potatoes in there. It looks kind
of stupid. You know, you open the oven and they let the thing go for an hour. I'm like, Oh my gosh,
what a, you know, you could have heated like 15 homes in China or Japan with all that heat,
you know, and that you burned electricity or whatever. So I tell people par boil them
20 minutes in a pot and just turn the dump, the water put, leave the potatoes with the skin on
in the pot, a low heat for five minutes, turn it off, come back, you know, tight lid and low heat,
five minutes, turn the potato. And guess what? What you have left is resultant. Almost what
is a baked potato and discernible really. And you've using so little energy, a tiny little
burner, right? Right. I think we, you have a listener that really got, I think is, I don't
mind him mentioning him, Joe. I think he was really excited years ago. He says, that's all,
that's all the only way we do them now. Right. And it's much faster also. That's how he got into it.
Yeah, exactly. Uh, that was like one of the first big things, you know what I do the potatoes. I'm
like, okay. And I hadn't even heard it yet. He got excited. He got really excited. And I love that
because it is exciting. Look at the amount of put a meter on the gas meter and see how much gas
you're going to use. You doing it the traditional way and how much gas you're going to use doing it
this way. Stove top. Yeah. Next to nothing. If you do, and the time is in half, right? Yeah.
And it's indiscernible. Uh, and if you really want to fool people, when you're almost done,
wrap them in aluminum foil, put them back in the pocket, you know, they'll say, Oh, wow. You know,
big potatoes and a half hour. Wow. Plus the skin isn't as dried out. You know, that's the other
thing is that the actual potato skin is a lot more dried out. If you do it in the oven, if you do it
this way, you can do it. You can make it indiscernible, especially if the, if when the
potato starts to soften and it's laying on the bottom of the pot, it'll get that, that bright
orange, golden brown, caramel thick. You know, when they have a baked potato and it's leaning
against the oven, it's kind of, it gets a little hard and caramel colored and it's real tasty,
real strong potato flavor. You can imitate that. You can imitate that. Of course it takes skill.
Some people have more skill than others, but here's the thing. I hate the, I don't want to
get into the big feet thing, you know, again, but if you, if the better sense of smell and taste you
have, the better, the more delicious your food will be. So if you're living amongst others,
I'll say that again. If you're living amongst others, whoever those others might be, women,
children, wives, husbands, grandma, whatever you need to figure out who has the best smell,
sense of smell and the best sense of taste and guess what their job will be.
The chef will cook nothing. Yeah. There are going to be ones that do in the cooking. And guess what?
Once you figure that out and you appoint that person to do that task, everyone will be a lot
happier, right? It doesn't work that way. What if you live in a traditional family,
which may not exist anymore, where the woman does all the cooking and between her living home
parents and her husband and her children, she's the one that has the worst sense of smell and taste.
Guess what the food's going to be like. Yeah, it's going to be rough for everyone. So when people say
my mom's cooking sucks, I say, oh, probably she didn't have a good sense of smell or taste.
Yeah, she she never had a sense of smell. She had a problem. See, how do you know? I'm psychic. That's
why I'm psychic. The other one is when you go to a diner or a restaurant and you order an entree,
you go with someone else, they order another entree or whatever, and you're eating it and
you're like, how's your food? And you're like, oh, my food's a little salty. Everything's
a little salty. Let me taste yours. Hey, yours is salty, too. And then the waitress comes. How's
everything? I said, you know, the way the cook eats a lot of sweets, doesn't he? And she's like,
yeah, how do you know? Do you know? No, no, I'm psychic.
No, because he eats a lot of sweets or internally he's overly leaned and his body needs to express
some young, but he's eating all the sweets. And if he eats the young, he'll crash. Right. So what
he does is he starts adding all the salt that he should be taking to everyone else's food. Right.
Because you need the salt to balance the sweet, you know, Coca-Cola recipe, right? A teaspoon of
sugar and a teaspoon of salt. Right. Yeah. Yeah. Of course. Yeah. OK. So so this is what's going.
So, you know, people like, oh, yeah, he's psychic. That's how he knows. It's like, oh, my God. So
once you understand these principles, you start to get more on a level where people find this is a
very interesting guy, you know, a very interesting gal. You know, you see what I mean? So do you see
how these principles work and they work every time as long as you get the right information and
the information is accurate? That's what's cool about it. And yeah, you know, you too could be
the most interesting man in the world or most interesting woman in the world simply by examining
the surroundings.