Rated Y, Sonic197, anyway, Greek, you know, the
chat's been interesting lately, but how are you?
Is times interesting your way or what?
Everything's good.
I'm making coffee, feeding the cats, I got
like a chicken puree, you know, I buy
a big bag of 10 pounds of chicken,
I par-cook it, you know, every few
days and I make like a baby food
for them and with veg and stuff and
yeah, par-cooked, just it's all pink, you
know, how they should be and you got
to give them organ meat during the shedding
season.
People don't know that the organ meat, most
animals, you know, when they first had zoos
and they fed carnivore steaks, they got sick
and died because they eat the organ meat
first, right?
Yeah, because they were missing the other parts,
all the other stuff.
Well, that's essentially what they go for, so
I basically buy chicken livers, beef liver, beef
heart and it's amazing how cheap it is,
I got a huge hunk of beef heart,
it was like two bucks.
Oh, nobody wants to buy that.
A big package, right?
I was going to ask you if you
were still getting the chicken cheap, actually, because...
Yeah, it actually dropped in price.
Really?
It went, it's down to $6.87 for
the 10 pound bag, it was almost as
high as like, just under eight dollars, when
I first started buying it, it was five
something.
Damn, I got to move to where you
are, the prices are dropping.
Tucson is cheap, yeah, but you know, they're
still paying $10 an hour over here right
now.
I'll give you an example, in 1986, I
was making $25 an hour and it was
good, you know, I wasn't wealthy, but I
never thought of anything that I needed, I
couldn't afford, you know what I mean?
Taking home a thousand bucks a week in
1985, 86.
85, 86 in New York, New Jersey area,
you were doing just fine at 25 bucks
an hour.
Yeah, I lived in Manhattan too, and because
back then, a good starting salary at a
college was 30 grand, which is not a
thousand bucks a week, a thousand bucks a
week is 50 grand, right?
Oh yeah, well, the way I understood it
is, see, I'm a little younger than you,
so for me it was 50,000 was
the good way to go, right?
Yeah.
And you could start there, you had a
good job at 50 grand, about a thousand
a week.
Yeah, and the interesting thing, what I did
through the weed man, the weed man was
the best, because you go and you sit
there, he prepares it, and there's other people
coming to get their weed, I met like
the great chefs of the world, I met,
this one guy, he came in, I said,
what do you do?
He says, I do decorative plaster restoration, Jason,
and he says, we're, you know, in the
old theaters, they were taking out the stuff
they put in the 50s and 70s with
the drop ceilings and they revealed all the
plaster ornamentation and the beautiful mural work, so
in a way it preserved it, but when
they put sprinklers through, they just blasted through
the beautiful ornamented, gilded, you know, ornamental plaster
and stuff, like little cherubs cast out of
plaster, pulling a bow and arrow or a
heart, that thing was broken, so these Texas
oil people were buying these theaters and wanted
to bring them back to their 1902, 1890
glory.
Plus they were busting holes for cable wires
and stuff at certain points, too, you know.
Oh, everything, and then they put the drop
ceiling in, right?
Right, and then the other terrible thing was
when they centralized some air and they just
ripped entire sections of stuff out.
Yeah, so all that had to be repaired
and restored, and the company, Kasloff Landau, they
were, and a long story, he says, we
need some laborers, and it was winter, I
was a bike messenger, which one of the
best things I've ever done in my life,
and in terms of an occupational quote-unquote
job, and bike messengers, you just split the
ticket, right, so it's $10 delivery, you get
five bucks, the company gets five, there's no
taxes, nothing, you're a subcontractor, right, you're really
wild, you know?
So anyway, I figured I'd get off the
road for a little while, so they started
me at $8 an hour as a laborer,
and to make a long story short, in
two weeks I was making $25 an hour,
because after a week and a half I
was like, you know, I could do that,
I see what they're doing.
They imported people from Hungary and Romania in
their 70s and 80s, because no one here
knew how to do that kind of stuff,
and they brought these old guys over, and
one of the Hungarians was into, what do
you call it, corporal punishment, if you didn't
do it right, he had a switch in
his pocket and he hit you in the
head with it real hard, I said if
he does that with me, I'm gonna kill
him, but he didn't, and I said, you
know, I could do this, I said no,
you can't, we got a five-year apprenticeship,
you know, you wanna do that?
I'm like, nah, nah, fuck it, I'm gonna
do it right now, so I started taking
stuff home and restoring models and bringing it
in, and then they bump you up to
$25 an hour.
Half the people there hated me, because they
were doing the five-year apprenticeship, because it's
also merit, it's not like in Japan, where
you have to torture the apprentices, like if
you're an apprentice in Japan, they like inflicting
pain on you too, by the way, you
know, like in the movie Jiro's Sushi, you
know, Jiro Uno's Sushi, the apprentices, you know
how you go to have sushi and they
give you a hot towel, right?
The messed up stuff like they show you
in the Kill Bill movies, where he pays
homage to a lot of that cinema, and
he does the whole thing with training the
girl, and he has to eat the rice
every single day, and he smacks her when
she doesn't eat the rice properly.
Or just making the way you're giving them
to do harder, like getting the sushi guys,
you know, what they do is they make
the, instead of the water just being hot,
it's like boiling hot, and the apprentice can't
wring it out, he's a weenie, so they
just inflict pain.
But I didn't go through that, and it
was good, and then after this company stopped
doing what they were doing, I got into
it like a wildcat decorative plasterer, and I
mean, then you're making $1,000 a day,
I didn't know what they were billing us.
So that's the thing, that $25 an hour
was nothing compared to what they were taking
in.
Oh, they were billing us out at $1
,000 to $1,500.
Look, when the company went under, we organized
a couple of people there, and I went
to go bid on a job, and I
was afraid to give them a price for
$1,500, it was a couple of feet
of molding that was missing plaster, and they
were like, come on, give me a price,
give me a price, and I didn't have
the balls to tell them $1,500, every
day was a day, two days work, three
days, you know, touch it up, $500 a
day was good, just talking about 1986.
Yeah, so that's a lot of money still,
yeah.
Yeah, people, you know, I mean, Union Carboners
are basically making at the top end $100
a day, right?
So anyway, I didn't have the, you know,
the gumption to tell them such a high
price, because I thought it should be priced
higher than normal labor.
They said, listen, if you could do it
for less than five grand, you got it,
and I'm like, oh my God, oh my
God.
I'm like, what the hell, you know, and
I was like, what, okay, Joe, you're pressing
me, I can do it for five.
I walked out, and I was like, walking
on air, I'm like, this is a day's
work, I'm getting five grand for that, you
gotta be kidding, and then I got in
touch with the people that worked them, like,
oh yeah, you thought you were making good
money, but they were billing you out for
$1,500 a day, I was like, oh
my gosh, and they were giving me $250,
I was getting ripped off.
Yeah, right, you're getting paid maximum $400, and
they're walking away with, you know, $1,200,
$1,800.
$1,000 a day, so I said, every
time they had a guy on the crew
there, just count the heads, that's $1,000
in the company's pocket for each person that
showed up to work, I was like, oh
man, no wonder they shut it down and
left.
So yeah, so I did this for a
little while, and it was great, because I
was bike racing and all that, and I,
you know, back then, a high-end bike
was $3,000, $4,000, now they're $20
,000, and I was like, oh yeah, just
give me the KPC record, give me the
Mozzy frame, give me the wheels, the guys,
ooh, what the hell is this guy, you
know, I'm like, guys, I remember, you're a
bike messenger, how are you affording this, I
don't do that anymore.
I got my own company doing restoration work,
and what was cool, and I still used
to do it, even in Tucson, you go
in the yellow pages for construction, you find
thousands of plumbers, carpenters, cement people, whatever, right?
Ornamental plasters, there's two in New York City,
and you call them up, and they're like,
oh yeah, we have a waiting list for
nine months, right?
What are you gonna do?
Because these construction companies, when they finish the
job, they have a retainer, and they don't
get paid the last 15% until the
job is completely done, and you had these
Park Avenue apartments with pieces, you know, that
were just unfinished.
So word got out that I was doing
it, and a couple of other people I
encouraged to do it, we were hitting all
these projects, and I still did it, even
today, sometimes, you know, I would, I mean,
recent years, like 10, 20 years, when I'd
get a call, I'd say, yeah, we have
a, you know, if it's May, I'll say,
I can't get out there till July, and
they're like, oh man, blah, blah, blah.
So now you can really gouge, right?
Well, you know, we have a service for
where, you know, you have a contractor, an
architect involved, and there's a retainer payment, we
can expedite, we can front-end expedite.
How much is that more?
You know, we double the price.
So it was like two of us basically
doing $20,000 or $30,000 a month
with two people and a laborer.
Look, when we hired laborers, we just, we're
talking about someone who just pushes a broom,
fills up buckets, cleans the tools, right, goes
get coffee.
We're not talking about someone that's required to
do skilled work, right?
But they have to be there, and they
have to be willing to do what we
need, right?
We started them off at $25 an hour.
Do you know the, you know, because the
laborers then were like six, seven bucks an
hour, maybe minimum wage even, and you wouldn't
believe the reputation, you know, it's like, oh,
go work for these guys, push a broom,
get $25,000, we're talking 1986.
Yeah, right.
No, I would have been glad to get
five bucks to do that back then, even
though I was a kid.
So we took care of, whoever worked us,
we took care of them, Paradigm Restoration.
That's one of the best times in my
life.
We're looking for a studio space, couldn't find
it, and this opera singer, Don Ewell, ran
into it.
It was Jay Adams.
His wife was an artist in New York,
famous sort of, and he says, listen, I
bought this warehouse building on Underhill Road and
Vanderbilt Avenue, and I need somebody in there
because they're going to burn it down, you
know, because it's a really rough neighborhood.
And I was like, all right.
So he basically got a 2,000 square
foot loft on the second floor for free
just to occupy it because, you know, they
find out there's a white landlord there.
We're talking the 80s.
A white landlord, he's not there.
I'd burn the fucker down, right?
You know?
Yeah, so at least there's somebody there that
can't go in there and screw around with
the Yeah, it was great.
And he called a plumber.
I remember he dropped, like, five grand to
install a new gas line on one of
those forced air heaters.
He treated us great.
Right.
So here's the thing.
We're waking in the high end of construction,
you know, for two people and free rent
and this.
It was just like, this is like, what's
going on here?
What's going on?
You know, this is life was different, but
it was, you know, doing that kind of
work in New York.
First of all, you can't park anywhere, right?
Right.
You have to pay off the meter maids.
I remember a Verderami construction.
They parked anywhere.
And I was like, how do you guys
do this?
Oh, yeah.
Verderami construction.
OK.
Gambino, whatever family.
And it was the female side of the
Gambino.
Anyway, all the meter maids walked by, you
know, double parked.
Didn't matter.
I was like, I got to get privileges
like this.
I never quite got them.
So we would just hire people instead of
having our own truck.
It was cheaper in the long run.
There were trucks for hire by the hour.
Hey, you know, hey, we got to know
them.
Go pick up this material.
Bring it here.
Bye.
No parking.
We never have to change the oil.
Pay the insurance.
Right.
And if we wanted to needed a bigger
truck, we found something, you know, his brother
had a bigger truck.
So we found out renting like, you know,
it's cheaper to use a cab in New
York than own a car.
Right.
Yeah.
Of course.
I look at New York City.
You'd be better off going to, like, say,
Home Depot.
Right.
And you get the van for a couple
of hours.
You make a couple of runs back and
forth to the store.
And then that's the end of it.
Drop it off and take a cab back
to the.
No, we didn't even do that.
This came with the driver.
There was a paper called the Village Voice.
Yeah.
No, I know the Village Voice.
You can hire anybody to do anything just
about because there was always.
Yeah.
And literally the massage parlor section.
Oh, yeah.
No, no.
Everything from escorts to paint my ceiling.
Yeah.
No, whatever you needed.
You could hire somebody.
Always.
Yeah.
So this just gave you a slice of
the 80s.
And do you believe that's 40 years ago?
I mean, not exactly.
But, yeah, 40 years ago, the 80s were
in the mid 2020s.
So 40.
Right.
Yeah.
No, I can't believe how clear I remember
the 80s, you know, and it's like 40
years ago.
Wow.
I can't believe I say something like that
now for decades, which is which is a
legitimate generation.
Yeah.
Forty years is a generation, you know, biblically
and otherwise.
So and you know what?
Not much has changed.
My advice to young people is that your
your 20s and 30s are your best years.
But it doesn't mean that the years after
that are not your best years.
But you're really an adult.
You're free to function.
You're still viewed as not really the youth,
but young and you'll have the most energy
and recovery.
Like, you know, you could work 20 hours
a day for a week in a row,
sleep on a slate on a Saturday and
you're fine.
You can't do that when you're 60.
You need to get enough to sleep for
three days to recover.
Yeah.
So but your debt, your best days are
in your I've even told someone recently, you
know, it was like 20 something.
I said, these are best years of your
life.
Take advantage of the the energy that you
have and it doesn't mean the other years
won't be good.
It's just that your your recovery powers are
the greatest.
Right.
You can recover.
You could take a hit and bounce back.
Absolutely.
And also, you're young and beautiful.
If you're not sorry, if you're not young
and beautiful in your 20s and 30s, it
ain't going to get better.
That's the truth.
Anyway.
So what do you got?
I mean, that was my that's kind of
personal.
But I think that whole thing I went
over just now, but it gives a little
bit more light into how anyone could view
their lives now and right now, no matter
how I look, let me just say this.
The political environment, because of the media, we
got media, more media now than we did
back then.
Right.
I mean, back then, the most technology you
had, there were computers, but the Internet was
not prevalent.
There was an Internet.
But the most information you got back then
were billboards, TV, movies, newspapers were still important.
And if you answering machines were pretty common,
but if you had a fax machine, wow,
you got a fax machine, you know.
Right.
So so that was it.
But now, because the bombardment, the political situation
now, people let the young people let themselves
bring them down and don't because the political
situation back then was World War Three and
a mutual destruction with the Russians.
Right.
So, yeah, I think the political situation was
worse in the 80s.
And it is now very similar.
It's very similar with inflation on a global
scale.
You know, yes.
But quite honestly, I don't know.
It just seems like people were freer that
you know what I mean?
They were free, like to not be at
war with everybody around you all the time,
unless you were in the wrong neighborhood.
You know what I'm saying?
Well, not only that, there was a lot
of animosity with the yuppies, the young up
and cut the Wall Street.
Yeah, right.
People was a lot of animosity for gentrification,
like classic neighborhoods being turned over and flipped.
You know, the traditional people moved out and
flipped over for this gentrified, you know, the
big box thing was becoming a problem a
little bit, you know, like Avenue A.
I mean, right now I look at walking
videos through the village and Avenue A.
I mean, that's Avenue A.
So that was like Lafayette Street or Broadway.
What the hell?
Yeah, totally different.
It does not look like the Alphabet City
of old.
Oh, you can smell the piss, urine and
vomit and heroin from Thompson Square Park before
you got to Avenue A, you know?
Oh, absolutely.
Yeah.
And oh, my gosh.
Hey, look, I lived on East 9th Street
between what was it, A and 1st, right?
So, yeah, OK.
I lived on 11th between 2nd and 3rd.
Dori Ashton was my landlady.
And I didn't well, I knew at the
time in a little shed about 50 million
dollars worth of artwork hanging on our walls
because she was one of the most prestigious
art critics in New York.
She had all kinds of stuff.
And I would go to her parties occasionally.
But, yeah, 11th Street between 2nd and 3rd,
right, right down from the St. Mark's Church.
You were between 9th and 1st.
So you're down you're out of near Venero's
Bakery.
Yeah, well, the pizza joint, Doc Holidays.
The right was on the corner there.
I could I could step out onto my
stoop.
I could throw a rock to the left
and land it in Tompkins Square Park.
That's that's right.
Yeah, right.
So what a park I never considered.
But that's where I first learned about vegan
food.
And boy, was it delicious.
And then these other people trying to pawn
off the crap they cook is vegan.
It doesn't taste good because it's vegan.
I said, you got something wrong because they
do the free food.
Those guys show up in their school buses,
remember?
And they come out with chanting with their
little finger symbols.
Yep.
And they give out food on Thompson Square
Park on the weekends.
Yep, exactly.
No, I love that.
That was that was great.
And it was delicious.
You get these white people try to say
it doesn't taste like that because it's vegan.
So what are you talking about?
Vegan food is like super delicious.
If you know what you're doing.
Yeah, you better know what you're doing.
Exactly.
So, OK, I got a question.
Is there any literature out there or resources
where I can look more into the concept
of induction and things being replicated by the
body instead of absorbed?
Which is obviously wrong.
Sure.
Such a fascinating concept.
But yeah, they want to see if there's
reference material.
Well, right.
I haven't looked at Lewis Kevran.
K-E-V-R-A-N.
Lewis Kevran.
He was buddies with Michio Kushi and George
Asawa and all these other guys into transmutation.
Other people.
OK.
Lewis Kevran.
He, I think, does use absorption term.
So, no, there is no place.
But biological transmutation would be Lewis Kevran is
a good place to start.
Unfortunately, OK, this is like, let me just
segue.
The water device that I use uses a
magnet magnetic reactor.
It's actually a nuclear reactor, but magnetic reactor.
But it doesn't use the North or South
Pole, the magnets.
Matter of fact, if you if you apply
that, it shuts down the device.
I'm using what's called the block wall.
Right.
And I was speaking to an engineer, which
I'm speaking to often because we're in negotiations
for a lab and all this other stuff.
And I said, you know, the last time
a white paper was written on the block
wall was by Felix Bloch in 1946.
How easy is it to pick up something
that was last written about just two pages
in 1946 and continue that research?
How easy would that be?
It's pretty damn easy because no one's looking
at it.
Right.
So any research you do is the research
is the looking up.
You're going to have to do it.
The best place to start is put your
put your cheaters on and don't be cheated.
You know, cheaters like reading glasses go look
at cross sections of the lungs, the skin,
even microscopic illustrations are good of the intestines.
Any nothing goes through any of that tissue
at all at all.
There are glands that have I forgot what
they're it's like an opening sometimes, but those
are highly controlled.
And but nothing goes through that.
So now start formulating what's going on by
going into the chemistry and the physicality.
Now, they're they're covering this just like, can
you go to the library and look up
how to build a nuclear device?
No, you'll see a general sketch and they'll
lie to you about it.
Right.
So well, once you understand the concept, right,
you'll find out you can't do it.
Right.
Because it's just like it's just like printing
money.
You need a special printer.
Right.
You just don't need government special engraving.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
And by the way, when they tell you
anybody's building them, it's not accurate at all.
They at least they stop scaring people about
it recently.
So.
Fair enough.
So there was also this discussion in the
chat about noises and somebody hearing a bunch
of noise in the kitchen and a voice
coming together, calling out their name.
Yeah, that's common.
I've had a cat had to be put
down and I hear him meowing occasionally because,
you know, they all have different specific voices.
And, you know, this is in the echoes
in the field and that's being taken advantage
of.
I put I posted Lookout for Charlie.
Look at F.A. Charlie, the YouTube channel,
because he's an audio guy.
But what he does, he's just not telling
you he's showing you.
Right.
So that's a good place to start.
If you understand the stuff I've been speaking
of for all these decades now, put that
together with this and make your own hypothesis.
You know what?
Yeah.
But you don't hear with your ears, right?
You hear with your brain.
So you can affect someone's brain and have
them think.
Right.
Yeah.
Well, I was going to ask you about
that because, you know, I went on that
channel and started listening and paying attention.
He was doing the thing on Waco.
Did you did you check out that one
yet?
No, I'm going backwards.
In other words, I'm going from his oldest
to his newest to see how it develops.
OK, I picked it random.
Right.
And went through a couple of different things
in the Waco thing stood out.
But I start listening to this and everything
that he's hearing and saying that is being
said, I'm hearing exactly different things.
And I mean, repetitively, and I'm trying to
hear what he's saying is being said.
Right.
I picked that up on one of the
videos about the haunted house.
But the good one is the one he
does.
Well, this is his own house.
Well, this is him pulling apart the 30
seconds of the audio from Waco.
And he's saying that hidden within there are
all these different voices and things they're trying
to say to people.
And I'm hearing different things from what this
I mean, clearly.
Well, you're hearing things to that.
Yeah.
I'm just joking.
But what I'm saying is if you go
to most of his stuff, most of his
stuff is right on the money.
OK.
You know, I haven't heard that one, but
I wouldn't hang on one thing.
It seems like it was obscure because he's
picking up the recording also from some media.
Right.
Well, so but if you go look at
when you record ambient quietness at night, you
know, there are voices in that.
Yeah.
But have you watched that?
What's funny is, is I've gone through a
bunch of his stuff.
But the Waco one I stood at for
a while going back and forth over it
because he was saying it's so obvious, it's
so obvious.
And I'm like, it's not obvious to me.
I'm hearing different stuff and I hear different
things than what he's doing.
Well, look, yeah, in his defense, not that
he needs it.
I go out and talk about stuff and
people don't understand it.
And it's really obvious to most and to
some.
So it's subjective also.
But I understand what he's saying.
And I'm sure that he's right, that there
are these hidden, you know, that there are.
Well, they're not hidden.
I mean, they're they're masked.
They're masked.
They were hidden.
You know, they're there.
They're there.
They're just very subtle.
Yeah.
But but it's beyond that.
What I what my focus is on is
your own inner voice that you think is
you that you actually you know, when you
when you hear a voice in your head,
meaning your your thought, your simple thinking patterns.
Right.
And that you hear yourself, you know, thinking.
And it's usually in your own voice.
And I'm telling you, that's not you.
Right.
That's another thing.
So and now, look, I have no problem.
There's an A.I. that runs everything.
Breshears is into it.
Much of the people I talked about that
long time ago.
But there's no reason to stress it because
you can't do anything about it.
One thing you'll notice, what I always discuss,
oh, not always, but mostly is things you
could do something about.
Like you got B.O. in your laundry.
It's because you're using the same laundry.
So there's no one online that's going to
give you.
I shouldn't brag like that.
So many practical things that you can actually
do something about over so many different fields,
over 20 different subject matters, at least that
you can actually listen to the sonic and
go do it right away.
So that's why I posted the Charlie stuff,
because.
If you if you're savvy enough, you can
download what is it, audacity, and you could
put a recorder, a non digital, preferably, which
is an old camcorder would probably be the
best.
And you can find them at Goodwill still
functioning for like five bucks, right?
Well, I got a cassette boombox, actually, that
that's that's even better.
Yeah.
Nothing digital.
Not like a smartphone.
Now there are there are better digital ones,
but why not digital?
I don't know.
Can't trust it.
Right.
Like Public Enemy says, can't trust it.
But and now you've got the background noise
of your street or the country or whatever.
And if you got audacity and you know
how to use, you know, different frequency bands,
you could reduce it.
You could hear stuff in there.
And he showed that.
Yeah.
And that's important because he's not talking about
like most of the stuff like you don't
hear with your ears, hear with your brain.
You don't see with your eyes, hear with
your brain.
They're not talking about anything exotic.
He's saying that it's actually in the sound
field versus microwaves that could make you think
you're hearing something.
Right.
But he says that it seems to me
he's saying that both exist, but he's trying
to show you the one that he can
reproduce.
Yeah, it's plain audio.
It's not microwaves.
Yeah, I know you could post microwaves that'll
make people feel like their head's going to
explode.
Micro is unnecessarily make you feel just like
you can.
You can also send these very narrow sound
waves that are only say, you know, like
present in one foot of space.
And if you stand in that one foot,
that one square foot, you'll hear it.
You see you step out of it and
it's no longer audible to you.
It's no longer being like shoved into your
head.
I understand all this stuff.
And I understand what you're saying about the
inner voice.
What I'm telling you is that apparently my
brain is picking up a different frequency.
Oh, yeah, it should.
It should, because you got the the reason
I'm saying it is not for nothing.
You have an eye disability, right?
So when that goes, the other ones tend
to unfilter less, meaning they're more open.
Well, and my eyes actually see different spectrums
of light already.
So I'm thinking that my brain is just
trained to pick up different frequencies anyway, because
like, for example, with food and cooking, people
that are very finicky about their food and
they can't find good food to eat.
Those are the people you want to make
prepare your food because they're hypersensitive to that.
Right.
So it's it's about sensitivity.
Anyway, enough about that, because that subject goes
on forever.
The most important thing we've discussed tonight is
how do you learn about induction?
And I don't know.
I don't know.
You're going to have to piece it together
yourself, like 99 percent of the stuff I
talk about and start off with your visual
cues, like when you're looking at something.
That's why when I go back to the
induction, I always say to a cross-section
of the intestines, do a split screen and
get an image of a cross-section of
a steel belted tire.
Look at them.
They're the same thing.
Pressure difference, very robust construction and nothing in
the design or the engineering allows for anything
to penetrate through the wall.
It's a failure if it does.
So all of it, everything is like that,
how the induction works.
Look, I wanted to look.
I can't even get a food seminar together
that I wanted to by now.
I want to get more into the human
body with some simple experiments to show how
all this stuff works by midsummer.
I said, I don't know if I'm going
to be able to do it, but it
doesn't mean I can't talk about it and
get other people to do it.
And that's the whole thing.
I've always been trying to get other people
to just.
I don't know.
I want to get a band together.
Does that make any sense?
No, you know, I need it.
I need to draw.
OK, I need a drummer.
I need a guitarist.
I need a vocalist.
Does that make any sense?
Yes, it does.
And you're starting to get people interested in
at least learning how to play an instrument,
which is good, because eventually you're going to
come across somebody who's a decent enough drummer.
You want to work with them.
I mean, that was my experience from trying
to build it from scratch.
Yeah, and all these subjects I require with
the financial stuff.
And I don't know.
I mean, I'm just sitting back and watch.
Look, look, I'm not supposed to be here.
So why am I going to act like
I am?
Right.
But at the same time, you know, you
make an effort.
You see how it goes.
Whatever.
OK, what else?
You got any other questions?
Yeah, I got a few.
What are the Greeks thoughts on aromatherapy?
Any suggestion for some way to bring scent
into the equation to make a day more
productive, relaxing, et cetera?
Should I open a day with certain things
or close a day with certain things?
These are all questions.
Yeah, but don't get OK.
The problem when you bring up aromatherapy right
away, everyone's mind goes to the marketing side,
which is all these essential oils.
Most essential oils that out there can actually
do more harm than good because of their
natural solvents like tea tree oil will dissolve
plastic.
Any plastic tea tree oil is pretty, yeah,
pretty rough.
I mean, actually, like, you know, you get
a bottle of acetone in plastic and that's
pretty aggressive.
Good for tea tree oil.
They come back a week later and let
me know how it's like chewing gum now.
Right.
Tea tree oil.
So so right.
So the thing it's just like vegan people.
Everything's got to have jackfruit.
I'm like, oh, what's wrong with you?
So what I'm saying is when aromatherapy is
brought up because of the propaganda, everyone's going
to run and buy someone's essential oil for
some reason.
That's not what aromatherapy is about.
Right.
It's it's more like this.
Remember the scratch and sniff stickers again in
the 80s or 70s?
Right.
That's when that aromatherapy started.
Otherwise, why do a scratch and sniff?
Any other is they do anymore?
No, there's no more scratches.
I haven't seen those in years.
Yeah.
Long, long time.
I don't know.
Somebody.
And if you went to eBay and bought
one new old stock, guess what?
It probably doesn't have any more sniff to
it.
Right.
I don't know.
It's probably stale.
Yeah.
So anyway, never seen him get that old.
Happens.
The smell of clean is the best you
can have.
Clean doesn't mean Dow Corning and Johnson and
Johnson cleaners.
Clean means water and rinsing.
And if you need an oxidizer, use hydrogen
peroxide with a spray bottle on it.
By the way, never dilute hydrogen peroxide and
never expose hydrogen peroxide to light.
That's why it always comes in the dark
brown bottle.
It will.
It'll do, which I want to when I
start talking about water again, the most important
thing for water is away from light.
And I've been doing experiments with that.
And the fastest way to degrade water is
to subject it to light.
People say, well, I went to a beautiful
lake and whatever.
It was in the sunshine.
No, you know, we're talking about maintaining water
quality.
So keep it absent from light.
Now, aromatherapy, get it where you can.
You know, if it smells good, eat it.
It was a bumper sticker like that in
the 70s.
That was next to the one that said,
no, no cashews, ass or grass or no
ass without gas, grass or something.
Or no, no ride without cash, grass or
ass.
Yeah.
And next to it was if it smells
good, eat it and whatever.
And smile.
Yeah.
OK, so aromatherapy is not what the people
that are getting into it now in the
past 10, 15 years is.
It's good stimulation.
The best kind of clean is the good
kind of clean.
I use that term all the time is
keeping things clean.
Doesn't mean using soaps and chemicals unless they're
homemade soaps or, you know, organic soaps.
But the best aromatherapy is actually fragrance and
fragrance free pheromones that attract humans are actually
sent.
They cannot be detected.
Right.
It's like, you know, when you get a
hearing test and it goes above your ear,
you don't raise your hand.
But there is a frequency being there.
But they're so the the best aromatherapy are
the ones that you don't pick up as
having an aroma, believe it or not.
And then it goes down to fresh things
like when you go to, you know, when
you walk into a really good organic market
on the vegetable side.
Right.
Smells really good.
And then the meat side smells like meat.
And then you go to the cleaner side.
That's not toxic.
It just, you know.
All right.
So if you get used to walking around
like a natural market, I would say whole
foods, but I don't know how good natural
market is.
Aromatherapy.
Right.
And you start tuning yourself, but don't don't
please.
I'm not saying don't buy essential oils, but
don't fall for that trap because they do
have aromatherapy kits and it's 50 bucks.
And guess what?
All these little bottles of what?
Essential oils.
And most of them are toxic.
If you use them the way that they
they have to be diluted.
They're natural solvents.
No different than getting some petrol or gasoline
or WD-40.
No different.
Right.
So, you know, you're not for the using
the melts and all that kind of stuff.
No, no, especially no heat changes it.
When you get more into the induction, you'll
understand.
Most of them will become toxic to you.
You might get.
Oh, yeah.
Smell that cinnamon.
Yeah.
Oh, smell that geranium.
It smells nice for a minute.
Yeah, it's toxic.
It's going to end up being toxic to
you.
And it's going to be another fad that
you pass through your life.
Don't fall for that is what I'm trying
to say.
Fair enough.
So they have another question here, and I'm
going to boil it down real fast about
marriage.
OK, so they note that you're married, but
also you're not having children.
You're not procreating.
But you also recently mentioned that the whole
purpose of, you know, sex is procreation.
That's all.
What if you hold on in terms of
purpose?
You got anything else?
Let me know in terms of purpose.
Well, what that word means.
Ultimately, the question is, what is the purpose
of a marriage if you're not procreating?
Well, it's supposed to be partnership coupling.
You know, there are certain animals that that
what are they?
What are they called?
Couple for life.
I think doves do that.
Right.
Who knows?
I mean, dolphins, I think they say.
Yeah, we have to trust what they tell
us to a degree.
But the idea is cute to think about
the idea.
It's not for everyone.
I think it's it's it's a matter of,
you know, that term I got you, right?
You know, you know, you got somebody got
got your back.
But, you know, what's the interesting thing in
Western society, especially American, the most horrific stories
of betrayal come from what?
Oh, yeah.
People that have been married.
People that are married are the worst.
So you could scratch what I said right
there.
If you feel like you're in that category,
it's a tough one.
If I had to do it all over
again, yeah, I'd do it.
That's why I keep saying being here is
a complete waste of time.
How many times you heard someone, you know,
they're in prison?
Would you regret it?
No, I don't regret it.
You know, or, you know, I lost everything
in a bad business deal.
I don't regret it.
I would do it.
Yeah, I understand.
If you lived in a real world, there
would be very clear demarcations about, oh, no,
I would never do that again instead of
most of the time.
Oh, yeah, I understand why.
Yeah, I would do it again, you know,
wherever I would.
That it was not it wouldn't be this
wishy washy.
You'd have more black and white, very clear
yeses and no's.
Well, we don't live in a real world
because we're here to waste our time.
So if you're wasting your time alone or
with a marriage or in prison or out
in the world, it doesn't fucking matter because
it's everything here is a waste of time.
It's just passing the time.
Fair.
Right.
So how do you want to pass your
time?
Well, there is no specific instruction to marriage
other than if you want a specific instruction
on marriage, read the old test.
Yeah.
Fair enough.
But that's that's why they were asking, though,
because it just seems like procreation is one
of the keys to marriage.
But, you know, but if you're not doing
that, why be married is the question.
Anyway, forget it.
That's that's all good.
And we're here to waste time.
But last question is that they've always felt
that music definitely has a spiritual element to
it and all that.
But the question for you is, does it
is it a useful tool when it comes
to emo work music?
Of course.
So well, again, we go back to the
sound, which is a very broad topic.
Let me just say this.
Your survival is not based on your sight,
right?
You're in a dark forest, can't see we're
in a cave.
Your height, your survival and your defensibility and
all that depends on location, on sound.
Sound is so important.
Right.
And half of the time that you're breathing,
you have to rely on sound if you're
in a natural world, because guess what?
It's dark.
Your sound is underrated.
That's why one of the things is wherever
you go is crappy sound, whether, you know,
wherever you go, everything sounds terrible.
We have a fix for that, by the
way.
But it's not you're not going to get
it unless you get it from me or
anyone that's I'm working with a fully coherent
sound.
It's a very simple fix, very inexpensive.
It could be put into production very easily.
But you don't get this stuff, just like
you get toxic food and all that.
But music, music is people ask me what
kind of music you like.
It's like asking me what kind of food
do I like?
You mean like salty, savory, sweet?
What?
There's no such thing as what what sound.
If it sounds good, if it's well done
to you.
Right.
Like, for example, you know, the mosh pit
songs, you know, that call when I walk
in a place of playing that heavy metal.
Sure.
I'm like, oh, you're playing love songs.
Right.
And I could see how I don't like
that, but I could see how I could
get into it because I recently was somewhere
waiting and I heard the whole song.
It was like some band out of Sweden.
Right.
And heavy, very heavy.
And I was like, I get it, I
get it there, you know, but it's not
my type of music.
Right.
You see, like I met someone recently who
were like, oh, I don't like jazz music.
I mean, how can you say that?
How can you say I don't like jazz
music?
That's stupid.
You know, keep your mouth shut, you know,
because you sound dumb.
Now, when it comes to music, look, I
like some things.
I don't like some others.
And you know what?
It changes over time.
And my mood changes.
I might be more happy.
And also what's being delivered.
Like somebody, I don't like Chinese food.
How can you say that?
I mean, how do you know?
I mean, you know, it's always different.
And at what level, you know, are you
operating on, you know?
So, yeah, the music is extremely important.
As a matter of fact, I for when
I'm having, let's say, a challenge, challenges in
my life.
And I know I need to sleep well.
I put some music on in the background.
Right.
And what I do is I go to
Nemo's dreamscapes and he it sounds like 1930s
old.
He's playing in the background with rain.
All right.
So YouTube channel and yeah.
Antique radio playing music in the background in
another room.
Right.
Cool.
And that'll just lull you away.
Who knows what kind of subliminal crap is
in there, too.
But that really helps.
And yeah, you will you will find if
you integrate music into your life properly.
The only thing is.
I've seen people that can't afford a system
or have roommates where they get headphones, don't
don't get stuck on the headphones because music
is tactile.
You get more information through your skin when
you're relaxing with music and not listening to
it directly than you do through your ears.