She plum so all right. I'll just lead ahead. I'll just just sit back. Yeah. Well, it won't be a long one
I might read a little bit from a thing that Michio Kushi wrote in the 1950s
so
Okay, fair enough. This is really it's really important be able to diagnose and analyze so
Okay. Yeah, excellent. All right. I'll get us rolling
The
Sonic event 73 and here we are now. We might have seen a few things in the chat room, but not much new
I know you got a couple of contacts here and there and you might want to address those to start with Greek
But sure also go into I don't know the further study of how things really work to after all
It's interesting to break it down and explain the process of just about anything. So where should we begin?
Well, we mentioned in the past we spoke about intuition thought action and
That would suggest
Is there a method, you know, I mean, how would you say it?
When you standardize stuff, you know
Like you can have someone who builds things right like sheds and houses and all that, right? They don't need blueprints, right?
but
Our blueprints bad. No, not at all. All right, they're actually necessary. So there's a there's a
When you study a blueprint, there's a test. It's almost another language
It's not difficult to learn but it's fairly a standardized process
so I've been bringing up the yin and the yang a lot lately because I can't find anything else that
Shows how one can determine and make accurate predictions other than those who are good at doing that. Should I say naturally?
Right. So it's basically teaching a method in a way
Yeah, if you understand the process how something happens in the first place, right?
Then it gives you the ability to understand how something might happen in the next place, right or well
It it's well, here's the thing ready. It's it's how things are always happening
Happened and are going to happen. There you go even better
It's really the structure
There's a there's there's not much on me to kushama. There's a bunch of books
I used to have them and they're kind of an okay read but you don't leave with much
His stuff isn't very good
There's a couple of books out there maybe four or five books on macrobiotics that there's one the writings of Michio Kushi
I think how old are those books? I just balanced this back out by the way, I think 60s 70s 80s
Okay, 60 70s 80s. So that's relatively new information that you're saying is useful. That's kind of
well, he's gathered and stuff from
from
Taoist thinking basically Buddhist Taoist actually all of the real ancient
Quote-unquote religions before they became staunch control mechanisms 500 years ago
Were a matter of you, you know, you go to the temple. That was your university. That was your court building, right?
it was your
hospital
Sort of like a little house on the prairie, right? The church was the school. It was also the meeting place
It was also the yeah, but also in a big urban environment
It's just it's just bifurcated into well trifurcated whatever into many different other things
so well because the control mechanism has to
Do what do you call it when you separate people right and you make them focus on one thing, right?
So compartmental you know, she's right and I was in the compartmental eyes. Yeah, so
Excuse me. What I would suggest is
I've had some messages about people listening and re-listening to what I gave yesterday
and it basically was a follow-through if this then that and if that then this and then
That than this and it just keeps folding over, you know
Kind of like a young child and tell him something and he's and he goes why?
Can you tell him why and it is but why but why right so it keeps on going, right?
Yeah, you could always ask why so this is the answer to the why anyway
You can always ask why and you can always ask what's next because after well then what's after and what's after sure?
That's another endless questions, isn't it?
Yes, but it's about
Tendencies, right? We talk about tendencies all the time, right?
like when you look at a cat you might expect different reaction than if you look at a dog, you know, if you're antagonized the
animal and
Because of its properties, right?
How they react to a loud noise for instance, right like, you know
Oh, or if you're if they get aggressive while you're holding them, right? Okay, the cats got sharp claws and all and if you understand
Yin and yang you could predict that without even ever
Like you'd see a cat and say, oh that probably that animal probably has sharp claws
And if you look at a dog, you'll say it probably doesn't right
if you understand the concepts of
Let's just say yin and yang which I don't want to keep
Leaning on too much that if anyone I brought this up has any other solutions on how to describe it expensive contractive or what?
Have you?
Let's use it
But because when you keep saying yin and yang it sounds like you've just done some kind of modified Asian philosophy, right?
Yes
You know, most people have heard of it
Very few people know how to use it what very few people most people still know a little bit about it
But very few people know how to use it and it is the basis of how things work here. Oh, there's um
they don't like using the colors either because people used to say well, there's a matter of black and white right and
Black and white or two modes as opposed to being colors and they're very
Opposite in their way, right one reflects everything one sucks everything in and they seem to be these opposing and balancing forces
One way or another that could equally appear in almost anything light
They're not no, they're not balancing here. This is the other thing. This is a little Greek speak mixed in
You know, let's say you have a scales and they're bouncing up and down right, you know, if the old-fashioned scales left and right
Oh, yeah scale with a fulcrum in the middle. What happens when they're balanced?
There's no more movement
Right, so that means stagnation. So what happens is when you you never truly achieve balance
It's slightly lean one way slightly more than the other to maintain movement
Because quote-unquote use this term loosely the construct the universe
The relationship that we have with our perception to what we consider real, right?
Always has some kind of motion or change, you know, like the half-life of elements, right?
For example, which takes a long time. Okay, listen, I'll go over this
This is a I'm reading off of a PDF if you just search Michio Kushi in folios
I n f o l i o s in folios. It's not a Rex research.com site
Rex research has a lot of stuff on inventions and all that other stuff speaking of inventions before I get started
I got an email about some
question about cars and it's from down under and
My response was I'll get into it a little bit
But I just wanted my response was
Spark plugs and throttle body if you can rework the throttle body and the spark plugs you're on your way
That's the two things that have been ignored in the automotive industry and I have two techniques
The spark plug technique and the throttle body technique are both modified techniques
But I've optimized them so and I gave the initial
Basically, you just drill a hole on the J strap, you know a strap at the end of the
Spark plug so the when the combustion or the spark occurs
The hole looks it's an aperture acts like a port in the rest of the bore
The piston sees the spark instead of being completely blocked. And the other one is there's something called the gadget man groove
What was his name
Ron Hatton
Kind of took his own life after a car accident, but a couple of years ago
He's one of these guys that says we need to do this to make the world a better place
And I always told him don't say that I've had personal calls with him for since 2013
And actually performed that
Service but on my own it's modified
There's plenty of videos on it
And you can do it yourself if you study it, but you know, it's kind of like if you get a recipe
You know you modify it, right? Usually if you're into cooking, right?
so these things
Have been around but they're not popular. But those two things will give you a lot more power and a lot better efficiency
I just wanted to bring that up. There's a well used to be known actually right now
So there's a sub or two that I work with their cars and they're always amazed by the results
on what I do with the throttle body and the
Spark plugs. So I just wanted to bring that up and the water device
I just mentioned if you've been around and gotten Sonics, I've brought up pretty much the crux of the matter
I am working an industry right now and part of it is they want to keep some of the developments because it's constantly being developed
A little hush and I said well for how long well just for a little while
so we'll see, you know how that goes, but essentially what was been put out on the
Let's say five six months ago
On Sonics and in the chat regarding the water device is pretty much the the crux of the matter if you do that
You got you got it, right?
So yeah, so anyway, I want to get into
Because the last Sonic was about addressing
Several things even to the point of carbonizing cockroaches, right? Right. I think people got that and they and the logic behind that, right?
Yeah, so I want to spring up some points because
Macrobiotics again when you say that it sounds medical it sounds
Macrobiotics isn't so just macro means big and biotics means life, right?
So it yeah again and if you look at macrobiotics, it's what is it if you study it
It's and you end up doing a modified Japanese diet or a Japanese diet pretty much and modified
You know, which is leaning on whole grains and legumes and vegetables, let's say and
You you really it turns off a lot of people when you get into condiments
Which I did get into how condiments affect you also on the last one
It's the first thing that comes out
Because it was the last thing that went in right? So in a way in terms of the way the body sees it
What I would say is
When you get into microbiotics and you look at the condiments they use they're strictly Japanese condiments and you're like, oh man
This is kind of a turn-off to someone who is like
Would say Western or just Western, right? So
yeah, modifying these things because you'll notice eventually that it's about
Original Greek speak where I went into regarding in food intake and living
Across latitude living and eating right wherever you are in the earth. You have temp we have northern and southern polar zones cold
You've got temperate
Zones both northern southern hemisphere and you have the equatorial and those three areas that I just mentioned are very different
And whether what things grow, right?
traditional
Ways of living and if you just follow that right it just to recap
if you're in New York City, and it's cold outside and you drink orange juice any tropical fruit and
Sugars where sugar comes from right tropical
your body is going to be adjusted to a
That climate even though you're living in the in the winter a lot different latitude
You will lose biological vacuum and to compensate for that. The body produces mucus. That's all it is now, by the way
from the
Laboratory clinical perspective they will say it's bacteria. Yeah, there is bacteria and quote-unquote things in there that the body produced
It's not like you contained
Contagious
Contracted bacteria that made you sick. It's backwards. You see so your body your body becomes a petri dish, which is possible, right?
It's not the intake of the bacteria. It's the growing of the bacteria internally
from the loss of vacuum
Increase of mucus. Yeah mucus whenever there's mucus, by the way
That is your first sign that you're losing biological vacuum
And this by the way is not in any of the macrobiotic writings at all
This is not addressed and one thing that's a turn-off for me personally about Michio Kushi big-time is his belief in
The viral theory and AIDS is a real disease. He didn't know how can someone so quote-unquote smart and wise
Fall for that, right? I think we've gone over that several times. There is no AIDS disease
It's it's a cycle. It's a psyop a very dangerous psyop right and just to recap
They have a bullshit test recently there was a lab
There's an article that got 1,500 samples by the way COVID samples that were positive and they reviewed them like an audit
There was not none of the 1,500 positive samples had any virus of any kind in it or you know what they're saying, right?
And he says they didn't even they didn't bother using the bullshit PCR test actually wrote bullshit in the lab report, right?
That's how bad it is
So it's a test for nothing really I will do it basically test how much puss is in the blood so
Quickly, how do you spell?
Kushi's name by the way, I just say
Okay with a K and the rest of how it sounds you s hi. Okay. Okay, Michio. Yeah
Okay, no problem, which is a very common name like Bill or Bob or John in Japan. Yeah
No, I know it but I just wanted to check the last name. That's all. Thank you
Yeah, fine
The family name in Japan they do it backwards by the way, your family name comes first, so when you
Say Jing ping in China. Also, there's it's ping ZG. It's right. They do the last name first
There's you know, so it's like Kim Jong-un Kim Jong soon. The reason is because Kim is the family name
Yeah, yeah, exactly. But yeah, right. It's not like yeah, right, right
Wait Westerners kind of do that when they when it's abbreviated, but you know, even in a non abbreviated they do it backwards last name first
In Asia, so yeah, cool
So he fell for that but but just to recap on the AIDS they they have this test that basically is
Statistically impossible and impossible and they just send out letters that let's prank this guy or that could be dumped and pulling out of a hat
And that's positive and then they follow up because they have your contact information, right?
on oh
You know, you were possibly tested maybe positive for a very serious illness, right?
That could be a service never that it is a serial
So you should consider treatment possibly and they keep sending and then people are gullible
They don't say that you have it. They say you've been in contact with it, right?
No, you've been you've been maybe tested positive for a potentially positive
For potentially a hazardous disease or dangerous disease potentially
I thought it was they they say you tested positive for exposure to
Dangerous they could they could use all kinds of language because they have to consult the creative writing department at the medical department
Oh, yes. Okay. Yeah, and they say you're writing the person goes for treatment and we know what happens
They look like crap and they feel like crap and they die and they say well, we have records that they had AIDS
Oh, yeah, everybody's like, oh my gosh AIDS is killing so many people. It's people are really
Right stupid when it comes to this stuff because they're stuck. Here's the thing
What does that basically say is that if people really tightened up their psychology?
Let's say their mind. They would be less gullible if they're less gullible. There'd be no AIDS
Right, there'd be little fewer financial troubles, right? Just ask the bank week
You loan I never got a loan. How can you give a loan? There's no money, you know? Yeah, well show me the loan
Yeah, it's kind of hard to think if people weren't stupid. They wouldn't be poor, you know
Yeah, right, but but yeah, all this stuff is cut if everybody's doing a cutout. This is a cutout operation
Right. So how much choice do they have a lot of choice, but I don't know
I don't know about that lately. I've been speaking to people
Inventors and you and they're not smart at all. I mean, oh my gosh. How did this person get there?
It's like well my gosh talk about like
Floating through life, you know
It's very easy. By the way, you can go, you know, what depends on the University
You can go to university and get a degree pretty much anything and just graduate with low marks
They'll still give you the degree right and then you have social rank, right?
Jeez it's pretty
It was pretty spooky pretty spooky
House, how ridiculous I'm not about professional people, you know, oh my gosh scary. Anyway doctor really from this. Yeah
Oh my gosh, you know, there are no there are no doctors anymore there. There haven't been
long time
You know, by the way, I've never gotten a shot. I think I'm gonna bring this story up to show you how everything's cut out
In
1970 or so in order to go to school
Had to have they had these green or blue cards was a kind of cardboard index card
Yeah, it was a vaccine card. He wrote down what vaccines you got, right? That's right. And
I was at a doctor's office, which was in the front of his house back then
The doctors operate a lot of them operated, you know out of their homes. The living room was converted into
They put up partitions and a little waiting area in the living room right and side rooms built in receptionist, right?
Yeah, and they some gaze examination rooms
They called them examination right in some cases the front of the house was the doctor's office and then just passed a certain point
Where the bathroom is usually boom past that bathroom is the living space. Yeah. Mm-hmm
They did that in Jersey to you
so I remember I was a tall guy bald head big head bald and
It was snowing outside I was there with the siblings or waiting quite a while with the moms and
Hand but with the cards to get stamped after you get the shot
The receptionist his wife goes in there. She kind of
Yells and tells everybody be calm because he died. He fell over and had a heart attack and passed out
I don't I think he died
Yeah, so I looked through the door being curious child. You see this really tall man in a white robe with
Gray pants flannel pants and very polished shoes laying down sight with his head sideways in his mouth open
first time I saw someone you know, but that and
She went around to the people who were waiting and it was a snowy day
So it was just us in another group another lady and maybe man. So what are you here for?
and she said here go here, you know and
They came to us and they said what are you here for?
Showed the cards and she just takes the cards and stamps and stamps and stamps them by you got it
There you go. Never got the right never got any of those polio's measles, whatever. They were jacking people up with
Right. So now think about that. What are the chances of that, right?
Well, there you go. Those are the chances
Back then so, you know something unusual
Right because typically they would say go somewhere else and get the shot she but she felt that it was
Okay to just right. In other words, let's look at it this way. She knew it's bullshit
You don't need the shots, right? You just need the stamp on the card, right?
Apparently because otherwise she would have said oh no what I'm gonna do is send you somewhere else
Somebody else can give it to you or maybe she could have given it to you. She was a good enough nurse, right?
Oh, look, I'll do it because yeah
If it was what they said it was she would make sure that we got him just like she sent the other people to another
Office, but even then it was known. It was bullshit couldn't have been that big of a deal
Yeah 19th and that's funny because that's like a 70 we're talking
Black and white TV in the living room and there was moon landing and there was some people there and they were saying this is a
fraud
Hmm
Adults and the family friends
Okay, while it was going on. I remember it was late at night when it was happening was 10 ish 11 ish
Eastern time live or whatever. This is this is a total fraud and I looked at him and I looked at TSA
Yeah, it looks kind of fake
I gotta say that's the first time I've ever heard somebody say right away on that day when it was being because that was a big
Deal watching that live on the black and white. Yeah
Someone is standing right where they were sitting and standing and they're like, this is a fraud
That's the first time a lot in real time. Yeah. Yeah, that's the first time I've heard of a group of people doing that in
Real time. Yeah, that's a very awake group of people. It is the early early truthers. I was around
I wonder if you that that has a great deal of influence over who it is. You have to yeah, it has to think about it
Yeah, sorry. Yeah, just a little mental aside my apologies. No, no, that's true
Figure I'd share that because I think both not getting the shot of being around people like that, you know, which we're not relatives
They were just friends. It doesn't matter. You know how they say
It's a village. It's not the families are supposed to just provide food clothing and shelter
the rest of it's supposed to be the acquaintances and associates of the family the education and all that right psychologically and
Culturally and all that. It's absolutely true. You can't do it with just the two parents and
siblings, that's impossible
You need more than that to add to create a culture you don't have a culture out of two people, right?
yeah, and one of the things I was always very suspect with chicken because similar people like that would
Be a ghast if you were serving chicken because they come back from Vietnam
So when they would go into a village, it would be all the chickens that were left alive. We're eating the humans, right?
people are not aware of how
Natural tendencies that say they eat each other to by the way if a chicken dies in the pen
They'll come, you know
Remove it. It'll be eaten by the other chickens. Oh, yeah, absolutely. If you don't they'll go they'll eat it
Yeah, which is I could see what's going on there
But anyway, that was yeah
So another lots of little things that came across as a young person because you imagine being that young and someone's oh no
Chicken, that's disgusting. It kind of gets stuck. You know, even if you ask why you know, you guys right?
You see the chicken McNuggets growing up in a totally different way, right?
So they can see a lot of things in a different way if you're accustomed to seeing something in you know
Well, you've been influenced just by someone saying in an adult, right? That's that's how we've brought up before
Often people say well, I'm not technical. I'm not good at that
I said, you know, I could see where that comes from because we all have the same capability
Because as they were young they heard someone influential or it was accepted to say so and they said oh I could say
I'm not good at math and not have to do the work to learn it and I'll be fine
Just like they were I'll do that
right
You see and they copy and emulate
How many times you've been in public and seen see young children speak like the Marvel stuff or the cartoons that you see on TV?
They write they emulate that in their speech
Emulation exactly. So whether it's choosing to eat or not eat a food or it's choosing to use certain words or certain phrases or whatever
It's all based on this external input that you're yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that's why I say get him while they're young, right?
Get him while they're young
Whatever in terms of influence. Okay, so the way to read off of this because this is a very comprehensive
it's about a dozen or so things and I'll throw my my
Three cents into it. So he's got a on the left column stuff like tendency position structure direction color temperature weight catalyst atomic
Elements construction of vibration and then he has a column in the middle for you
column on the right is young and I'll just go through each one and it's it'll be very basic and
maybe I'll throw something else and so in terms of
Tendency, I'm gonna go through these first and and then I'll read some principles here and some unified theorem
Okay, so for a tendency yin is expansion. Yang is contraction
For position yin is outward yang is inward
Okay in terms of structure
he says yin is space and time is young which I disagree because there's time is just a
Measurement. So time is distance by the way with no distance. There's no time, right? Well something changes. There's a distance, right?
Yeah, but you don't object to the expansion and contraction. I know no, but I think that one should be left out
Okay, I just I'm putting that shit. Yeah, I'm not gonna leave anything
Listen, I'll tell you how to look at it in a way that you can consider
You could say that time is young and believe that there is such a thing as time. I'm telling you there isn't
It's merely the measurement of distance, right?
So because even measuring distance takes time. Haha. No pun intended
Yeah, so yeah, and then direction. I'll actually direction up is
Yin, and just you know ascent is yin and descent is young down. It's young color
Purple is yin red is young
Temperature cold is yin
Hot is young
And just to go on that when you have a lot of cold it makes things hard like water and other things, right?
Which are young?
Okay, so if cold is yin if you affect something like water with a lot of cold or a banana or whatever
With a lot of cold what happens it gets harder and harder, but wait a second. I thought cold was yin
Yeah, it makes things the opposite
The antagonistic heart, right?
Okay, give an example on that because it's very explain you ever see where they have liquid nitrogen, which is minus 100 and whatever below
Okay, they dip they have a nail on a board and they dip a hammer in
It and they try to drive the nail and the nail the hammer shatters like glass
Of course, then they dip they dip a banana, but you can drive the nail with a banana
Why and it doesn't shatter
Why because the the hammer is already very young and you tip it over comes too young and it can't hold its young anymore
But the banana started off being yin and you made it really young and it's gonna hold its it can hold that
You see that didn't shatter
Okay in terms of weight lightweight is yin and heavyweight is young
in terms of catalysts
Water is yin and fire is yang in an atomic
Structure yin would be an electron a proton would be young
He's got elements. Yeah, that's a strange thing about fire and water though
because it almost I
Don't know why but my impression is that fire would be more of a transient thing
Water is more of a solid thing
Well, hold on water is an exception because if you start compressing water
You think it would become more yin like compressing a banana, right which is young
But it actually becomes more young than what you're compressing it with
So what this one thing meets your cushy did not appreciate water. You could not get into the talking about it
Hmm, which is by the way water is a lifelong pursuit
No, just studying water. Absolutely. I'm just thinking in a pure physical sense though that one is more substantive than the other
Now fire by the way fire is oxidation. Yeah
But that fires oxidation, but you can't have fire without oxygen and that's a different type of fire strange fire
If you want to go that way
Well, but see there you go
Is that you know fire requires other things to feed it and it also in and of itself is not really an object
It's more of an action water is
objectively
Something well, so the category was under catalyst
You know, let's go under catalyst. Okay, that's why I'll skip the elements because he's got elements of various things like potassium oxygen
Calcium or yin and yang would be hydrogen arsenic chlorine sodium in terms of construction
The surface of something is yin, but the inside is the young part
Vibration shortwave is yin and yang is longwave just like the colors. Let's say in terms of expression work
Psychological work is yin physical work is young
In terms of attitude gentle or negative is yin active and positive is
Young or forceful, right and biology vegetables are typically yin and animals are typically young
But I've gotten into and I'll read some of the principles anything nutritive is yin
Because right because young is the protection element
Usually and that's more advanced
But I don't mind throwing the advanced part in first because when you throw the advanced in part first what you're going to learn anyway
It set tends to be more self-corrected the system, right?
If you have more advanced knowledge on something you're less likely to make a mistake as a beginner, by the way
That's a philosophy. Maybe I find that to be true in many cases, right?
so
Okay in terms of gender or sex yin is
Female male is young
That which that should be a major example, right? That's pretty simple there, right?
And then in terms of nerve we have ortho sympathetic or parasympathetic. Oh, what the hell is that?
Okay, so ortho sympathetic is yin ortho sympathetic is where you get a nerve impulse and parasympathetic is young
That's where the body
Relaxes right actually it's in reverse there but in terms of
This is kind of then he has the cold season is yin
Hot season is yang
Right, but what's interesting in the cold season things that are affected by the cold season become hard
right and yang and
And the heat season for the hot season things become yin when you look I love melting right so hot, right?
What's melting? Is that yin or yang? It's yin. See that's a good
Way to see the antagonism, it's calls a polarity
I don't believe in polarity and opposites attract and things there's no attraction there get into that
Then basically tastes hot sour sweet is yin
Salty and bitter is yang
Tropical climate would be yin a cold climate is yang and summer is yin winter is yang
We'll stop right there because then he gets into other things that are more technical or chemical
so here's a
Seven principles of the order of the universe. This is Michio Kushi
Influenced by George Osawa also
I mean sounds like an Asian filed modified Asian philosophy here very much and the thing is this needs to be redone
More on the western side, you know
well, I
Shouldn't say needs to be redone. But the whole thing has died away, you know, you don't hear about it anymore, you know very much
so
I'm gonna take this with a grain of salt
So number one, he has seven principles of the order of the universe. All things are differentiated an apparatus of one infinity
Everything changes is number two. Number three all antagonisms are complementary
Tell that to your wife the next time she wants to
You want to have an argument? Actually, they want to set the argument anyway
For there's nothing nothing is identical
Five what has a front has a back six the bigger the front the bigger the back
Seven what has a beginning has an end?
Now the bigger the front the bigger the back was a classic if you hang around macro neurotics, I mean macrobiotics
When you give something good what it does it's a very leveling mood leveling or thought leveling
Way to think
The bigger the front the bigger the backs when someone's got really good news or or you know, really good
Let's say proposal even what what's the catch? What's the backside right? Right and that always goes together
So people that are in the macro biotic stuff when you give them something really good. Well, what's the backs? What's the counter?
You know, what's what what's the backside right?
So so that can actually drive people to seem pessimistic or not really grasp the opportunity
I should say take advantage of an opportunity
So anyway
Well to adjust that with attitude. It's what you know, the greater the risk or the greater the
Investment the greater the return right the great
Not always a lot of people have made great risks and lost everything and end up sleeping on a park bench
No, but the only way to achieve the great return is to take the great risk, you know that not not
Yeah, that's a saying not true either. I'm not saying it's true. I'm just applying it
Yeah in a world when you figure out it's cut out
Most of these people I've been around people very wealthy and said tell me how you got there or forget. Well, I'd be go read
How these wealthy people you could access online or whatever pick one and look at their bio and their history doesn't add up
Doesn't make sense never does
Right. It's a cut out. Yeah
right, so
to go on a certain theorems here
Infinity differentiates itself into yin and yang which are the poles that become into operation when the infinite
centrifugal
Arrives to the geometric point of bifurcation
Okay, so basically you just described the shape of the galaxy right when you see the swirling pattern in a galaxy
Yin and yang continuously form from infant centrifugal this
centrifugality
so
basically
Both yin and yang come from the expansion of the universe. So this is Big Bang Theory, which I'm not into either
Yin is centrifugal yang is centripetal
Yin, and yang together produce energy and all phenomena both material and energetically
Yin attracts yang and yang attracts yin
You don't agree because you'll see why here in a moment
Yin repels yin yang repels yang
The force of attraction and repulsion is proportional to the difference of yin and yang
Components yin and yang combined in varying proportions produce energy and all phenomena again
phenomena, by the way, if
Is material also because you know as they the quacky scientists tell you which is correct and to some degree when they look at an atom
Let's say a very dense material
It's atomic structure. Well, you know the best they can measure the closer they look there's nothing there
But once they get down to the electron proton
Right
Level the the distance between the electron and the proton that makes supposedly the solid atom is so great
That you could say the atom is 98% empty space if not more, right?
So that makes material a phenomenon
Because how does it feel so solid when there's nothing there versus nom noumenon?
The majority of anything that you encounter as a solid object is actually composed of empty space. Yeah
So so that means that anything material is actually a phenomenon once you start viewing it as such then you can get into the
transmutation aspect of things
And by the way from a spiritual point of view, the highest level of transmutation is to transmute yourself, by the way, right?
so into a higher being
Well, that's the catch
okay, nothing is yin solely or nothing is solely young and
There's nothing neuter. It's either yin or yang in
Excess in every occurrence says here large yin. Here we go
Large yin attracts small yin and large yang attracts small yang
This is this is the idea of the ether that the potential goes from low to high. It's not attraction
It's that the lower potential the small yin will go to the larger
Right. This is yeah
So all extremes, okay yin produces yang in extreme situations and yang produces yin
Give an example like you have a grenade in your hand
Military, you know, I'm the grenade grenade and it's young it's small. It's very dense
It's hard right focused, right? Right when you pull the pin what happens immediate expansion, which is yin and
pulling the pin is so extreme that the
grenade ceases to be
That would be an extreme action when something ceases to be right
So the same with the hammer, which the iron is already very young
but if you make it more young with the being of the cold it gets
So brittle which what is something brittle when it breaks yin spreads out everywhere, right?
Where the banana was or yin it could take the the yang reaction from the yin cold
So it's a flipping process
You're subjected to something that has a yin component and he's that mostly yin components and he's subjected to some young
Then you can predict what the reaction will be
Right, and then if you have something with many yin components and predict subjected to the more yin
You can predict what it will be but in the process
There's a relative scale though, because look if you put a hammer in a refrigerator, it's not going to shatter
It's not producing enough yin
Too much of one flips and become its opposite, right?
So for example when someone is going on an angry tirade and they're done with their tirade
Which is very forceful noisy very young
When they're done with their tirade what results they fall down and go to sleep
Which is Yin. Yeah, so this you can apply this to everything in anything even color theory, by the way
Anything and everything but again
It sounds like the Greek is some kind of Asian file, you know using some modified to Asian philosophy and if we can find a
Basis in Western quote-unquote philosophy or methodology. I'd be willing to adapt it a little bit more because guess what?
We speak a Western tongue
It's a Western culture usually, you know
And all that it'd be good to develop something like that after we develop a b c d e f and geos also
No, absolutely
the only the only thing that stands outside of this of course is the
I heard this once and I don't remember exactly what the context was
But you can't get everything from nothing and you also can't get nothing from everything
So yeah at the most extreme points
it's
Not, you know
In other words, there has to be something in order for it to become everything there has to be nothing in order for it to
Be nothing, you know what I mean?
so
There is there is an extreme point on the scale where this does fall off
But only at the most extreme point. Yeah, but here's one way to use it lately
I've been working lately past six nine months or something on developing things
Technical devices and when I get to a point I want to make an improvement or I know there's something else
That's let's say hasn't come into fruition. I use the yin and yang principle
And so when you're thinking about something and you're asking, you know internally out loud even and
You're thinking about it for hours and days and weeks on on on and you're not getting any any development at all
It gets kind of tired, right? It's like I'm not getting it. I mean, come on throw me a bone, right?
I'm not getting any develop nothing. I'm thinking about it. What right thinking thinking thinking thinking thinking nothing
Doesn't mean stop thinking keep it going keep thinking thinking thinking thinking and what happens you get a little tired
And it's like seems played out to be asking those questions still
How can we make this better right and it gets more played out and it kind of wears you out a little you get tired
Right, you keep doing it and you're like more almost like OCD. I guess might be the
Application here. It's like he's guy still talking about or thinking about this for weeks and he's got no headway keep doing it
To the point where you become so Ying
From it so expansive seemingly most people would give up way before
Nothing's coming to them right and he's still doing it what happens suddenly like a bolt of lightning BAM
What happens young the idea comes and hits you like a bolt of lightning out of nowhere very sharp very focused
Right write it down
Actually, sometimes it's so sharp and focused. You don't have to write it down
It's like a 3d image in your brain. You can touch it feel it smell it, right?
So in other words
persisting
right
It's in thought I find that to be a formula that works for me when there's no solution for something hold on to that idea
Even though you're not making any headway so long just keep something
Even in the biblical text keep knocking keep asking right and errors
Just keep it going and then it comes like a shot like a shot
Right so that actually works for me and ever and sometimes when I don't have an answer for something
I'll just persistently
Keep that question and try to look at it from sideways up down right and it does the answers always do come like a shot
But you have to keep expanding you can't just do right with repetition though, right? I mean exactly. Yeah
It's like almost imagine you're traveling in a desert for days and weeks and you just see the horizon or in the ocean
You're on a boat and you're just days and weeks. It's like I don't see any land
Just keep going and then you'll see what you'll see a very sharp focused little island young, right?
It's typically the story but to make the story work the way I'm saying that is counterproductive
If you walk for weeks in a giant circle
You're gonna accomplish nothing because you're covering the same ground over and over again
You will you will because you'll notice the center of the circle the young part that you're walking in a circle and you should maybe
stop
The moment you realize you're walking in a circle is when the yin and the yang come together