86 best I can figure it out looks like we're at that sonic event you know the
first thing that comes to mind the phrase 86 you throw something away you toss it you
eliminate it are you for 86 that was the abortion pill kind of ironic a lot of things we could
tie to just the number but let's get on to the words how you doing tonight Greek sleepy
but doing okay I think I might have heard your neighbor's dog bark on cue there right
when I said it and it was turning to you did you hear that no I didn't know it's there's no
neighbor's dog anymore no kidding the ghost hitting the ghost dog in the machine so the
throwaway episode also worried speaking of throwing away a year where this is about a
year also pretty close within a week okay so here we go with this the counting of time now
becomes almost irrelevant you know but nobody knows what time it is anyway and if they do they
don't know yeah yeah but it's about a year and this was actually a very slow year for me this
past year albeit time speeding up as you get older so yeah so yeah something you mentioned
someone messaged about the scalarator and possibly getting into monatomic elements I got a lot to say
about that okay so yeah then there was one other contact which I didn't show you but I figured
I'll relate it to you I'll save you time here I go saving you time and stitch in nine and all that
but 89 will be the next episode anyway either ladies 87 oh 87 87 right it'll be a couple episode
look at me I'm screwing up what I'm trying to say well what else is new funny thing this email
starts off kind of insulting me a little bit that I'm like I wonder why well cuz according to them
I'm kind of like your retarded pet apparently during these Sonics that we do together which
I know I'm the pet Greek you got it I got that spot already but that's it but I'm the retarded
I'm the retarded one you're dragging along going look this is a pony Chucky yeah that's kind of
what you're doing but anyway then he gets he gets a little nicer and kind of sideways insults you a
little bit but none of that's relevant really because I just want to give you the attitude
setting that we go into here many times he says that you mentioned that everything this world is
yeah well of course we're in a simulation now putting that together biological all right let's
let's go because I get thrown off on tangency it's a biological one because if people keep
thinking of the matrix and these computers and things like that then then that makes us robots
and we're not robots but we are biological machines it is a biological simulation of
that is more real and all this by the way started with Plato right you know like if you think of the
color white although all these different whites which one is white well there's a true white
somewhere in a in a better realm right so whether you're looking at the low-grade religion is
religious promises or any form of analytics you'll see that there's no real reality here
but it is biological yeah not to discount it no not at all and look there is the matter of
containment versus you know what is entertainment literally because when you think of Plato you
obviously got to go to the projections on the cave wall and the concept of the cave and do
you know about anything outside of that cave do you need to know about it well no because you're
in the cave at the moment now when the moment comes that you're outside of that cave you might
want to know what's going on maybe maybe not but anyway back to the simulation and it is
relevant just hold on I won't go too far on this thing is if we're in a simulation and you accept
that the gods are real and we are real but yet we're in a simulation what's to say that this
is not a fully fleshed out parallel of what the gods would do they wouldn't bother to interact
with us directly they might let us be the NPCs so to speak in their own game where it's kind of
not relevant we're just part of their video game so to speak yeah I don't know what kind of
agreements they have behind the scenes they don't always share everything but it's there it's okay
they do put it out but it's not in a form that we recognize right the reasons for these things you
know the money okay they always get into the money system like there's hardly anyone that knows how
the money system works because he because it's actually accessible you know it's it's kind of
convoluted but once you you follow down the road before they got into this convoluted system with
the money they had to give you a remedy which is you know the law you know redeeming awful money
every country has something similar to that and no one uses it so the the story of the gods and
humans and the gods of the gods and on and on and on is all the same these remedies are put out like
if you really want to if you're having a hard time here you want to find out why you're having a hard
time I assure you the reasons are given we just don't know where they are and I'm talking just
literary ones so information all right go ahead yeah but overall the question boils down to this
isn't it more likely that the reason why this is set up is not for this nefarious oh they're seeking
to control us and the people are hijacking and all of that that is all secondary the reality is
that if the gods were to say communicate with us directly because several times we've gone over how
you're communicated to by other entities other middlemen one way or another other facilities
one way or another there's a middleman there's a middle part of the process etc it's because in a
direct fashion based on our construction our limitation we would not be able to interact
with them directly so everything boils down to how good your middleman is how good your instruction
book is how good the part of the simulation the programming is in your part of the simulation
all of it comes down to you're dealing with some sort of middleman because to be in direct contact
with the gods we would not be able to have the story typically go but if you were you then it
would be in such a different framework that it would be difficult to communicate to the others
and then you'd be thrown in an insane asylum and it would be just as bad right well even if you get
close to it that happens but in a real direct sense what what he was saying is isn't it true
that basically we cannot interact directly we know it interrupts a certain part of the show
like what I mean sure I mean like you have acts and then you have scenes within there so these
things have to be played out it seems mm-hmm right so yeah the overall question once again
is just simply isn't it just based on the fact that we are incapable of doing it though because
we don't have you know the old idea that why does why do angels speak to people instead of God
directly a lot of this we're completely incapable the situation doesn't permit it the situate right
every aspect of it yeah and you could still see even now people's lack of ability to communicate
clearly I mean just with you know with their mouth let's say for freedom that's what you're
all writing or whatever yeah and that's still like a leftover hindrance that was put on humans a long
time ago unless humans just started out as really dumb creatures that were genetically modified to
be what we consider now but that doesn't make sense of how much degradation has been taking
place over the centuries so either way either way it's fine I think next week I'll bring up I
found a book that was online about 1749 someone I think I had this book at one point and it was
about meteors anomalies and things that in the world world history and chronology I don't have
the title with me right now I'll put it up in the chat or in the next sonic so it's a good one it's
got some interesting stuff because it gets into medical remedies towards the end of the book so
pretty interesting no definitely I look it's all fascinating to me that's for sure but people often
ask about the biblical stuff and they never really have a direct question but he wanted to
get into more about how it's the best way to look at it is that it's always about middlemen one way
or another there's always gonna be it is you know so direct interaction even though people talk all
the time about being I was touched by God I was you know God spoke to me you know all of those and
by the way I'm using all these different phrases and things that I know are absolutely not part
of Greek speak at all I'm just trying to give you the most relatable bits of it to make it understood
and this is what he did in a very long rambling thing that would have taken me longer that's okay
so let's just stop it right here and we'll be able to pick it up again or just dismiss it right because
I get a lot of long rambling emails as well some of them are enjoyable some of them are not and
usually if you do send long emails if I if I do enjoy them I usually respond back that I enjoy
you writing to me so it's yeah it's not something that I don't enjoy and and so people who do send
me very long emails when I give that response well you know it's a thumbs up so yeah and I
particularly don't mind when some people do it like you same thing I'll call I'll call one out
by name you know Meg Z when she sends me something I enjoy it I always enjoy it it's even if she's
telling me you know things that maybe are you know outside of where I thought the conversation
was going it's always enjoyable just to I don't know read her stuff it's just enjoyable anyway I
keep using that word forget it point is if anybody else wants us to pick up on this idea about the
middleman and how that works or that system I think people would be interested in it but let
us know because if I don't hear from you I don't know what's in your heads I'm not that kind of
guy anyway moving forward or maybe backward depending on how you want to look at it yeah
I did send this thing along about the scalerator and I got to admit I'm finding it interesting as
sort of an observer who you know straight out I'm not going to try and build any of this or anything
else but watching the process and learning a great deal of things along the way just about
the nature of certain things how things are handled and how it is we've been given to understand they
should be handled all the way down to the very basics of water it's fascinating to watch people
who are actually trying to accomplish something accomplish it and it's been very interesting that
Skype group you said it's coming to an end soon yeah it's done already and in the next what they
call Thursday I don't know what's today the 7th or the 6th the 6th of February so the 8th of the
morning of the 8th it'll we're gonna nuke it so it's not a public thing so anything well you know
what I say anything you put on the internet is like taking your garbage can out to the curb right
you can't get upset for people using it so your point of reference is you'll see a date on this
but the thing is I'm gonna put it out on what they call a Wednesday so when you see that
or even sooner might do a surprise and pull it sooner or later I don't know but I've been putting
things up there and we'll just see what happens because the whole thing is I wanted to see who
else is interested and really it's getting to the point well who can really do it you know yeah
that's all I have to say about that but one of the messages you got pertains to it regarding
or where's the material going right stuff like that well that is one of the questions that I kind
of had way back and I've sort of gotten lost just sort of observing this and you know I would
suggest if you are in on that group and a lot of people that do listen to rated wire in on that
group I would say you know collect your stuff up and hang on to it so you can go back over it
because I'm gonna and I think it'll be an opportunity to have a point of reference for
whatever was going on a couple of people have actually done some work and I think that's a you
know that that's something that should be you know what would you say commended you know for
actually taking action but one of the big questions I had from the beginning is okay
it's not a filter it doesn't take stuff and collect it in you know a mesh screen or a coffee
filter ends up really dirty because it collected up oil you know this kind of thing where does
stuff go because you would think okay even with things being moved or things being trained yeah
that's there's a question of the nature of stuff yeah like anything okay go back to Plato it's all
shadows on the wall if you look at just to jump in hard and fast on this the the scientists that
are looking they're using some kind of scattering technology to show you an image of an atom which
is total bullshit right but they will tell you that there's nothing really there you know when
that in other words is that closer they look at the densest material the less dense it becomes right
right right but you look at a mud puddle let's go back to the you know basic and third grade
science even in you know what they call schools you know same thing they call fish that just
happen to be swimming in a clump but anyway yeah so you take a look at a puddle of water that's
you want to take the mud out of the water because you want to be able to use the water without the
mud you don't want to well hold on this is going to get interesting here and confusing maybe there's
another device that does that the scale orators purpose was to increase water quality yeah it
does remove a lot of stuff out of the water meaning hard minerals yeah it drops the TDS
which is told dissolved solids which measures TDS measures total dissolved solids it's an
acronym for that right so usually we get when it's properly set up the higher the solids are
the more reduction up to 50% I've seen 80% reduction right okay and and when you see an
80% reduction it means that 80% of the material that was dissolved in the water is now gone right
so but there is another device I call it the turbid orator that may never see the light of day
it's for several reasons in order to do proper research on it I need turbid water so I'm not
going to keep harvesting pond water from a local park or golf course and very few people actually
have a turbidity water problem but this device also not the scale orator it's her bitterator
it does something very very very very very unusual and it has again magnetic reactors they're not
there employs magnets but it doesn't use it uses magnetism but in a completely different way I've
shown this and explained it to several people that have like nuclear engineering background and
they were they were like oh my gosh you'd really do you see the potential and they went down a list
of things that could be done with it I'm like yeah but it's not going to really help anyone
you know at this point it's very specific and it's very intense but yeah well I mean off the top of
my head just really fast off the top of my head I mean one of the instant things that jumps to my
mind is how about desalinization that's always been sure a grand idea it's not really for that
but it is going in that direction yeah because it's her bitterator is about three or four times
more powerful in the scale orator in its application maybe more and it actually does
have a scale orator in the center of it it's a it's it's minimum three come three separate
components working together in unison yeah this is really cool and I think people that have known
me for over a decade or so know that I've always worked on water and I've said that you know what's
possible you can make just a pipe nothing in the gut and put dirty water through that pipe and on
the other end clean water comes out right oh yeah I've been telling people this for a long time you
have and one of the like I said a key use would be I mean just the very simple I mean even a monkey
can figure out look the planet has plenty of this salt water all over the place well that's too much
you don't know well actually there's more freshwater than salt water it's just not available it's
underground well and the difficulty is the location the ability to harvest it no no there's
no difficulty the difficulty is the perception of it there's plenty of equipment there's lots of
equipment and lots of where with all the knowledge and how to get water where you can just make one
hole in the ground it'll feed an entire city and you don't even have to pump it up of pure clean
water but it's not it's not for this group of people here so but anyway let's let's get back
to the topic and hand the person brought up monoatomic elements and when you bring it when
you hear that and you speak to orthodox conventional people in science they're gonna think you're
referring to like the noble gases right no things that don't they're also called monoatomic meaning
they don't combine with any other element but just to the long and the short of it I do have
monoatomic rhodium and gold and in its purest form made by date the David Hudson crew group they're up
a hundred miles north of me so and these are the originators of the process let's say modern day
what I would suggest it is it's not necessarily going to monoatomic but it is in a way what the
scalarator does how else would you say it it's a quality issue with the scalarator where monatomics
that I wanted to get into a little bit is not necessarily monoatomic it's just a state of
matter and they will tell you this when you get into you know the airy fairy or miss stuff it's a
state of matter so just like you have a plasma state it's like that it's if you we would go back
and you know you're gonna hear a lot about yin and yang with Greek speak unless we come up with
another way to explain it when you say monoatomic gold or any other element that is in its most
young state its most contractive state and because it is such an extremely contractive state that it
appears to be very light because each aspect of it contracts into a tiny tiny particle very light
in color and fluffy like a very light powder like the finest dust you can imagine right and it's
because it's extremely young now metallic gold the heavy bar of gold that shiny yellow orange
color that is a much more yin state like for example the last young element on the periodic
table would be platinum anything beyond platinum larger than platinum is yin I mean it starts to
expand right so if you want to turn more base metals which would be more young than platinum
into gold you have to learn how to make them more yin so what do you know about making things yin
consequently when monoatomic elements are found or identified by whoever not the noble gases that
orthodox sciences but the ones that the airy fairies talk about the white powders that is just
an extremely young state so how do you get things to be into a very young state now tie it back to
the scalarator what it's doing the scalarator is it's allowing the dielectric inertial plane
more like Ken Wheeler talk but that's what it is it's actually referred to as the inertial plane
to affect the center flow of the water and the water is just as magical as using the inertial
plane of the magnet which is the part of the magnet that no one uses at all now we're running
an incredibly sophisticated element or water is an element it's not a compound don't be fooled
by them telling you it's hydrogen and oxygen so you put hydrogen oxygen together you will get some
water but if you cannot take water and turn it into hydrogen oxygen completely so you have this
magical thing let's just use that phrase loosely known as water going around the most magical part
of the magnet which is not considered magnetic at all incredible things are going to happen right
and and I'm the only one that's doing this publicly and I've been looking at this for a
while and the only one still pushing on it I've spoken to academics physicists engineers all kinds
of people and they have no input at all nothing zero nada because they're hampered by their you
know background right and then of course that's when I talk to people that are physicists and
engineers I said I kind of like don't impose but I do to some to some of them I'm look I'm not
looking for an academic or an engineer looking for someone who is very what intuitive right you may
not even know how to read and write I would even prefer that but if you're intuitive and you get
the concept can we can we brainstorm even just to get figured between myself and somebody else
we'd have at least a half a dozen brain cells that work so we can brainstorm and come up with a
better solution now the reason this is from a managerial point of view see managers if you
can't measure you can't manage it so from a managerial point of view the more understanding
we have the more better we can manage it and advance it right now it's hard to advance it
because we really don't know what's going on so what what part of it do you advance right you might
actually think you're making it better and you're actually making it worse right because you don't
comprehend it but what we do comprehend and have realized is that what is considered as raw bulk
matter brutal matter is disappearing before our eyes when it runs through this device as long as
that matter is in water and it's consistent and they're the one that I've been showing in public
you know this is turning into a call about the scalarator it seems or a sonic event the one
that I keep showing is the most dumbed-down version there are other versions like the super
scalarator I call it the 700 I did post a picture of that it's the one that goes into the condo with
more wraparound other people experimenting but if you don't know more exactly what mechanism or see
if it's not if it's not material how can you call it a mechanism the effect the true effect the
basis of it we can't go any further so I am just always just showing the most dumbed-down which is
it's a very elegant it's a very simple spool one bend around you know magnetic core you notice that
it's not met we're not using the magnet or using the right the magnetic fields we're using the
magnetic fields where it's null and it's just a single loop very precisely made and that's it
there are other versions that are actually more intense and do a little bit more but it's not
necessary to put that out because you got to start somewhere right well and the issue is that it's
it's rather difficult to relate any of this to somebody if they don't have a standard by which
to measure it and the standard to measure it doesn't work because well we measure it by outcome
just like you'd measure heat or anything else yeah right well this is this is like the weather
work by the way we don't know when I work with the weather we talk about working with the ether I
don't know exactly what the ether is but I know if I do this then this it will do that right same
thing with this this is okay another way to look at it it's ethereal and going back to the mono
atomic elements you know the white powders from you know the or miss and all that one thing you
could nail down on that is that is the most young state of whatever material and as the material
gets heavier and shinier and more metallic you know keep going down the periodic table as the
numbers get larger it's becoming more and more yin so it's actually a very simple concept someone
did put in the chat on the last sonic I mentioned the internet is spreading and spreading and
spreading and spreading and spreading and spreading and spreading to the 10th power what is that
that's yin so the counter reaction would be an extremely young reaction an extremely young
reaction is something very focused and it would be very small all over the place like pores on your
skin under a microscope would be the young aspect you know the skin is very yin covers the whole
body and well some people you can see the pores on them without a microscope but and if you look
within the pore there are these tiny hairs like the peach fuzz aspect of hair right not long hairs
and dark hairs or pubic hairs but very thin hairs that grow between the hairs those are young
manifestations so what what I'm trying to say here this person liked the analogy that the internet
is as something keeps spreading its opposites gonna have to manifest something that's very
contractive that's why for example I gave the analogy tied laundry detergent they spend a
hundred million a year on advertising and no one's clicking on their ads no one at all I mean well you
know no one you know for a hundred million dollars worth right so everyone's clicking on what all the
little micro companies that plant-based this we're a local Colorado soap company we're like this weird
you know make using frog eyeballs you know whatever you know I mean all the really tiny
little craft soaps and all that everyone's clicking on all of those and there are thousands of those
other companies but no one's clicking on big companies anymore so so this is again ye applying
yin and yang so you can apply this yin and yang principle to everything and it always works and
that's going back to the simulation well there's one other principle hacking the simulation yeah
there's one other principle here that needs to be recognized and that is that look from a
standardized you know the academic the sort of normie world of things right the fact that it's
not visible to them the fact that it's not observable by them with the tools they have
that's where that's where the breach is see well hold on the academics every academic anyone that's
gone past the eighth grade and especially that's taken a career with college and university and
continue those studies yeah is an actor yeah is a player is a chump in other words they know down
in their heart that if they don't do what they're told right by the administration or the trustees
they are out of there right so to me they're chumps are they offering a service perceptively
to the ignorant public the ones that watch the Super Bowl right for them they offering a service
of distraction but for people like myself or other people trying to advance anything no they
have absolutely they could stand by the door and hold the door open they have absolutely no use
at all for me or anyone that's working on stuff that you know requires realism right but here's
the thing what what occurs here is that the reason okay this is gonna be a little hard for me to
explain bear with me just a minute the thing is that even though things are happening and they
are very significant because they are not visible to what they used to call the naked eye right
there were people that would say that those things simply do not exist because they're not able to
observe them in the standard way that they understand they should be able to observe things
so here's the thing does it matter if you can't see it on a microscopic level because there's the
fractal nature of things right of course you'll see it in a large like if you have very tiny
nanoparticles and you blow them through a fan in the parking lot and they make a dust cloud
they're actually going to form a similar geometric shape to what one particle would
look like under a microscope it's kind of it's called chaos theory right well it's a way to
demonstrate it but the point I'm trying to make here is is is pretty interesting I think in that
if it is not observable right there are like okay with the scalarator right if it's not observable
you need intuition right and you're using so you need intuition to get there but then you have the
end result which is demonstrable demonstrable right that's right and that's how you measure
the the the gains of the work that you've done right so if you've done all this work using
intuition and nothing gets better nothing changes or you haven't met any perceptible goal
you have no gains and now you might want to stop take a break yeah now smoke and a coffee and
reassess and not going down that direction right now anymore it's not giving you any benefit so
the only problem that really you have here but like release this to the world and the whole
world would use it is that you don't have to say never do that no especially now we're in extremely
this is where the spiral expands divergent this is where society is ready to disassociate of course
and you do not want to if you try to address the entire society the whole world you just
f yourself big time yeah of course uh yeah what you want to address is a small group of people
that might take interest and those that you've gotten the attention that might take interest
satisfy those that do have the interest so right with anything that you do by the way I see so you're
utilizing that as the step in between because you don't have the measurement the tools for
measurement capable of showing them the process what I just said has nothing to do with the
measurement it has to do with the state of the world yeah no I guess if you lived on the planet
where there are like a hundred thousand people and maybe a few thousand little tribal villages
with 50 people each yeah you could probably get your what you're doing to each one through your
lifetime you travel yeah right and you might go to each village right but this is too spread out
and too divergent and it's it's too degraded and but within those pockets there are people that
are interested right just it's all right more specific the scale rater is who is the client
someone who's interested into water in in water quality and well handcrafted artistically crafted
devices no different than someone who likes fine watches you really you know think about these
mechanical watches that cost tens of thousands right why you can get something with a little
battery in it that's just as accurate really you know that costs like less than 100 bucks but
there's an appreciation that something mechanical can achieve such accuracy in time they're not that
accurate by the way uh in time you know time keeping right but but it's just an appreciation
so this is strictly for someone as an appreciation and this goes for anything if you're an author
i hang out with authors in town and and you know i'll sit down with them and these are like ones
this one's a completely unrelated fields and uh they they have more personal concerns about what
they're doing meaning you know how to get their book going but uh it's really hard to convey to
them that you should never look for a big market always a very very small specific market and if
you go here here's another thing if you try to market to the whole world and everyone you will
no one will listen but if you market to a small group of people highly specialized
other people around them will find out about it and you'll get more play you'll get the better
chances of the whole world finding out about what you're doing that way and going directly trying
to market to the whole world well that's why the same thing goes with information they always select
a demographic they target it they narrow their scope so that they have a particular uh type of
people that have certain things it's beyond demographics it's like uh seth godin says
psychographics well that's why i said a scope within you know yeah it's like psychograph it's
this it's the mental you're looking for no longer is it okay you know spinning rims you know in the
ghetto you buy a car a toyota for two thousand dollars but you spend eight thousand on wheels
yeah right what kind of demographic is that if i if you were developing a company that sold wheels
for eight thousand dollars all for a set you would never think of some you know 18 year old with a
two thousand dollar busted corolla never but that's who's buying them i'm talking about you
know what was the fad that was going on two decades well that's why you gotta know what
your niche market it's a psychographic yeah in other words it's it's something based on the
the mental perception the mental state of of who you know uh would would get the product yeah like
i said no one's clicking on tide soap ads no one's clicking on ivory soap you know no one's clicking
on microsoft ads no one but thousands of people go to the michigan soap company that says they
have the most natural soap flakes you know that they hand make yeah what are the little because
you have to understand the union we are in the outward divergent spiral everything is in
dissolution right it's going into dissolution dissolution into the ether dissolving there
there's no more great people there are no more great things being done that affect them other
than a big-ass war which believe it or not is going to be really hard to do anyway it's always
from now on it's going to be a whole bunch of little wars until the big cosmic world comes
right right and we see that starting to unfold actually now a bit yeah they can't even get a
world war going right i'm serious bring it they keep they've been threatening it since uh people
don't know but they've been threatening since 2016 with the or 2014 with the first ukraine debacle
yeah right exactly yeah so they can't even get a world war going so because it's not about the
met it's not about doing it on a global level but for humans it's going to be on another