78 is the sonic event we're on right now, Ocelli in the Greek rated Y, so a couple things
in the chat, or one thing in the chat really, and you put a few pictures in there, but first
off how you doing?
I'm doing good, feeling spicy, so this should be a good one.
Little bit, little bit, I'll tell you, you know sometimes I try to hit the button a little
early sometimes.
Come on, hit the button, let's go, come on, let's get this road on the show, come on.
That too, he's anxious, anxious to talk tonight, okay, good.
Well, yeah, okay, we could, no, no, no, no, no, not like that, it's different.
It sounds like it, I gotta tell you, all right, hey look, I am willing to accept that I am
possibly wrong about every single thing, it's fine, and I have the flexibility to try and
learn.
That's going to require a lot of apologetics, because we've been doing this for a long time,
you shouldn't say that.
Well, I don't need to apologize, hey.
Well, you know what, I mean the real meaning of apologize, like the real meaning of the
word nice, you know, it means to defend something.
Yes, I understand, I was making a joke, but it didn't land.
All right, anyway, it's okay, I'm not a comedian either, but let's get back to it.
You just look like one.
No, look, looks aren't, I'm not funny, but looks aren't everything, right?
Anyhow, they can be, though, as long as you're smarter than you look, that's what counts
in tough people.
And if you don't have either, then what, right, you just got a face for radio, and you got
to hope your voice will pull you through.
That's right.
Don't push.
If you don't, bang the table, bang the juror, right?
All right, anyways.
Yeah, let's get to the chat, okay, before we get to the chat, if you get to the chat,
I put up some more pics on the Scalarator Mark 1.
This one was one that's got, I call it the 700, but it's really five, someone pointed
out, it's really 540 degrees wraparound, not 700.
But the reason I call it a 700 is because the straight pieces count as part of the circle,
because whenever you're using circles, you will, and let's say you have like the letter
Q, or the letter P, which is a semi circle or full circle with an appendage, right?
You should always count the straight part as part of the length of the circle, even
though it's straight.
Now, why?
This is another discussion.
But on the Mark 1, the water devices, they have like two straight legs, right?
Usually in a line.
I count that length as part of the circular degrees, right?
So even though it's a 360 going around, it's right.
So anyway, I call it the 700.
The purpose of building it this way is to show people that you can overlap the pipe.
It actually works a little bit better.
Every little small thing, improvement that you make, if you notice you get an improvement
in the water quality, it should be noted, right?
You know how it's just each little increment, is it worth it to do it every time?
No.
It's not that much of an improvement.
Did you discover this incrementally or did you just keep kind of tweaking it to improve
it?
Constantly.
Well, these are downloads that I get, their inspiration, gut feelings, mistakes that I've
made.
Okay.
Something doesn't come out right.
So let's make tests.
Let's make tests.
Right.
I learned it from a Russian.
Anyway, guy at the mines, whenever something is like, wait, wait, wait, wait, don't, don't
do that.
Make tests first.
Okay.
So let's make tests anyway.
And I noticed that the extra wraparound, you got to keep it away from the faces of the magnet,
right?
You want to use that block wall.
This is situated this way.
I even put plastic threads, male threads, cause it's going to get flex connectors.
We only have about six inches of water main we can get to.
Now we can't mess it up.
It's only like imagine six inches access to the water main.
That's it.
So if you mess it up, it's like you just asked yourself pretty good.
So what we're going to do is going to cut into it, put two 90 degree elbows to come
out of that little six inch zone.
So we could put some flex connectors and have this in line.
And I just wanted to show this because it's like, I promised I'll keep people updated.
And then I have the net, the newer versions and the upgrades are going to have flow forms
built into the pipes, like the Shaw burger stuff.
And I have even a pipe cut open and these flow forms are molded into the plastic.
And like I said, I'll keep updating.
Now, a few months ago, I said about the water tech, speaking to some people in the corporate
and they wanted in order to honestly, would you keep it hush hush for a while?
And I said, yes.
So in order to honor that, I told everyone, look, I got to keep things hush hush for a
little while.
But that little while is over now.
Nothing much has come.
I don't think much will come because there's a lack of maturity.
So the next thing here is to keep spreading this out.
And what I want to do is a quote unquote seminar on Skype.
Anybody in the chat, you could reach out in the chat.
You could reach out through the email, Uncommon Sense, radio one at Gmail dot com.
It's number one.
Right.
And let me know you want to be a part of it.
If I get three, four, five, six, seven, eight people, we'll do a Skype date.
I'll message everyone back when it is.
It'll be on Skype.
No, I don't do Zoom.
I don't follow the collective.
And Skype is way better or anybody else has something as good as Skype or whatever.
We'll have it there.
And what I'll do is, well, it'll be an open time or however long it takes.
I estimate an hour to two hours.
I'll do a slide show that I'll post images, tech documents, whatever, history, installations,
all that stuff, things that I've discovered, things that directions it could go and what
it could do.
There'll be a physicist present who's on staff, by the way.
Yes.
A fizzy, not a physicist, but a physicist, however you want to spell it anyway.
So yeah.
So I just want to put that out.
I just want to, because I said a while back, I got to keep tight lipped because some dealings,
those dealings are now done.
And I think it's, you know, I got to live up to what I say.
Right.
Of course.
Well, you know, and there's a there's an interesting thing because I actually got an email this
week about the old water episode that you and I did a few years back.
And somebody was saying that they were looking for it and they wanted to know if it was going
to be part of Rated Y.
But this is this is different.
This is specifically on this device and similar devices.
No, I get it.
But you mentioned the form.
And I was thinking to myself, well, I wonder if that has anything to do with like what you
mentioned in that one about the shape of the container and how this is completely.
This is a new.
This is actually if anyone's got more than two sharpened pencils in their pocket, they're
going to realize this has nothing to do with water.
This is actually a leap in physics.
This is something that the current physics is not acknowledging.
And without getting into it here on this sonic, they got the poles right of the magnet.
And then they this thing they call the block wall or the Neal wall.
And they dismiss the whole thing.
They acknowledge it.
Then they got dynamic formulas.
They tell you it's a thousand angstroms wide.
Right.
Which is ridiculous.
You know, hydrogen atoms like eight thousand angstroms wide.
So it's just a typical physicist stuff.
Right.
Bullshit.
But just to keep you away, I'm sure it's being used, but not in the public.
So now we've found and show that there are dynamic results by using that.
There's many, many applications.
We could talk a little bit about that.
But this is not the water business.
This is the physics business, which is we do not want to get into anything that crosses
lines with academia and industry, because they will hound you to the grave.
And after you're dead and they make sure you're done and forgot it, they pick it up and take
it and carry it as if it's theirs.
Of course.
So they can go eat a dick.
They can eat two dicks.
As a matter of fact, the academics and the establishment and what did I just say that?
Yeah, anyway.
And it is.
Yeah.
So I'm not interested in that.
So the thing is to get it out on the I don't say grass level roots.
I don't believe in that either.
People you people who are good with working and building stuff.
Right.
Like sometimes I've talked to someone about building this and are like, oh, yeah, we need
all this.
And so I'm like, are you joking?
Look at it.
My two neighbors down two houses down.
They have a daughter that's just started high school and her eight year old brother can make
it.
What do you mean?
You're going to meet with a bunch of engineers and spend a hundred.
Are you joking?
No.
Get out of here.
You know, all you need is a guy with a shed and fair enough tools who can eyeball something
and go, OK, I know how to do.
Yeah.
Who's that?
Who's has tactile control?
You know, like baseball is tactile control.
You know, you have control of everything in your eyes, coordinate in your ears and everything
coordinates right in your body.
So, yeah, it's it's sad.
It's it's it's always been sad.
Like, you know, anyway.
Of course.
So if people are interested, this is not water a meeting I want to have.
It's strictly on developing this building through the council of the multitude comes
wisdom.
There's a certain aspect that I believe that if you get enough people involved, that someone's
going to come up with something, no matter how long it takes, there's always a slight
improvement.
All that's welcome.
Yeah.
So what were you going to talk about?
Oh, yeah.
Well, in the chat posted something about three dimensional thinking.
And my response to that was, I may not say what you want to hear now.
It's weird because I saw it differently.
They seem to imply to me almost like they want the Greek speak version of feng shui,
which is an interesting term that has, you know, gained popularity in the past.
I don't know.
Two decades or so.
You know, this Asian concept of moving things around in a room, arranging it so that energy
is directed through that room in a certain way, the furnishings, the decoration, etc.
You know.
And that's about all I know about it.
OK.
OK, good.
So let's stop right there.
Let's let's circle back to the direct question of three dimensional thinking and we'll finish
off with the part you don't want to hear.
Let's get into the feng shui, feng shui, feng shui.
If you're speaking another dialect, which means water, wind, basically now.
Real simple.
Don't start with that.
You want to get a preliminary idea of how you fit in it as an individual.
You got to look up something called nine star key.
And the key is with a K.I.
As a very watered down subject, again, Michio Kushi revived that a while back.
Now, what nine star key is, it's like horoscopes, but it's not like horoscopes because horoscopes
are just plain dumb.
Nine star key was based on over 4000 years of surveying people and keeping information.
So what does that mean?
I'll give you an example.
There's a village, let's say 4000 years ago, and they got a summary of the village who
did what when they were born, right?
What they looked like, like beauty marks, you know, high facial structure, everything.
Right.
OK, so let's say they went back and reviewed a town and every time this person started
business, it failed.
And every time this other person started a business, it succeeded.
So they studied the person whose businesses failed consistently, everything, beauty marks,
when they were born, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
And then they studied the person whose business succeeded, their height, their size, their
beauty marks, facial stuff, all that kind, right?
When they were born and they made a record.
Well, eventually they found out that all the people who started businesses and failed
had similar beauty marks, similar days when they were born through the year.
Right. And then they noticed the people who were successful starting.
I'm just using this as a model, by the way.
There is no category for who looks, you know, successful, but who doesn't.
But no, but this is an interesting thing, because, you know, throughout mankind's
existence, it seems to me as though people have attempted to come up with a way to
draw a map.
Basically, but this is done not because what's in the stars at all.
A little bit. Well, a little bit.
Because the horoscopes are made up, by the way.
But when they were born, I got you.
But when they were born and all that, that's your horoscope part.
But sometimes they say, oh, but people that have certain personality traits, you know,
certain this or that trait or whatever, this is what they're meant to do.
Right. Yeah, but this is far more specific.
And so the people that were successful, they also found had similar things in common.
And they started grouping this into a study, a statistical science.
All right. So what's more important is there's a wheel, the five or the nine star
key, the various elements.
Give me an example. Like I'm the element that I am is earth.
And there's a wheel where earth is.
It goes fire, earth, metal, water, wood.
Right. And back around.
So when you go in one direction, one element feeds the other.
And across other elements, if you go backwards, destroy.
One destroys the other. Right.
Right. If you go backwards.
Right. So like, right.
OK. So and then they go across.
I give you an example. The wife is a tree or wood.
And I'm earth. So I feed the tree requires that I feed her, build her.
But she breaks me. Right.
The roots go through it. Right. So.
Right. The roots. So you can dig in the earth.
So it's not a good. OK.
It is to nine star key that would not be considered mutually.
Mutually beneficial. Right.
Mutually, but not beneficial for one, not the other.
In one direction, it works in the direction it does not.
Because, yeah, OK, gotcha. Right.
See, the tree roots break the earth. Right. OK.
And then you get more specific.
Are you black earth? You know, black soil, yellow soil, brown soil.
OK, so then if you there's a later on, I'll post it in the chat.
And that is a very simple, comprehensive wheel to look at.
Right. And that is significant.
The type of soil it is, because, look, different types of soil are good
for different things. Some things are well for you.
Go ahead. Well, the important this would be in your young.
So the light colored soils are more young and the dark colored soils are more yin.
OK. Right. OK.
So that's why I like what color is really good.
Topsoil, black, black, black coffee grinds almost.
Right. Use coffee grounds. Right. OK.
So and light colored soil is usually considered star.
You know, you can't grow anything.
Maybe, you know, maybe sweet potatoes, red fruit or sandy.
Sand or sandy soil.
OK, so nine star key.
Start off with that.
And then you get into other aspects that nine star key will introduce you.
This is not horoscopes, by the way.
It's horoscopes is like, oh, my gosh, the Mickey Mouse version of it.
Horoscopes came about not even a few hundred, not even.
I don't even think it was 100 years ago, the way we use them now.
But it's a Greek invention.
Yeah, it's no, it's less than 100 years ago, the way that they use them now.
The truth is, and also this is none of the star horoscopes horoscopes, by the way,
the way they exist currently are almost like the three little pigs version
of trying to teach morality. Right.
Where it's it's like it's one of those things
where they boiled it down to a children's story.
And here you go. There's your there's your lesson.
So you could take something out.
By the way, you can't teach morality.
You can only make people aware of it.
We're going to get into that to understand.
But the purpose is supposed to be a morality lesson. Right.
You know, if you learn this, then what does it tell you?
Make sure you're careful with strangers.
You know, whatever. OK.
But that's the thing.
It's it's this convoluted way of teaching a lesson
that doesn't actually get to the root of the thing or to a scientific basis.
Yeah. What's the one where there are tales where if you do this,
you become something bad?
I forgot there's a term for that.
Those tales. Oh, Aesop's Fables.
No, no. Actually, most young people have never heard of Aesop's Fables.
Those are actually good little lessons.
But there's another cautious, cautious tales are cautious.
Oh, OK. Yeah, yeah, yeah. All right. All right.
Yeah. Don't you know, don't if you make a funny face, it might stay that way.
A cautionary tale mixed with cautionary tale.
Thank you. Yeah, it's different. Right.
Gotcha. OK. Morality could go down that road because, in other words,
people that had immoral thoughts where it would punish themselves,
like cut off their genitalia and all that.
You know, you've heard of stories like that and stuff like that where they.
Yeah, very, very Christian.
You know, if you think terrible, they got their eyes right.
If you think terrible things about other people,
terrible things are going to come to you because blah, blah, blah.
And they attach that to karma, which is another bastardization.
Yeah, that's that's the that's the you do stuff like that.
And you end up with what you got today. Right.
Well, that's that's what I'm saying, is that when you when you work
with convoluted to begin with, you're going to end up with convoluted at the end.
Yeah, it's a it's a control mechanism.
But it's psychology.
I took it once in a college course and they handed out the issue.
The professor asked for everyone's specifics.
And she's she put it at the beginning of the next class.
She went through all the sheets, everybody's name
and handed each one a very specific horoscope.
Right. It was specifically done for us.
And I read it, read it.
Who feels like it pertains to them?
Everybody raised their hand.
OK, now I want you to exchange whoever you're sitting next to.
It was everybody got the same thing.
Right. So that's what I mean.
That's exactly like the thing.
Not to mention names like Cliff High, but people that sound smart who are not.
Sorry. Right.
Please don't send me links to the clinic.
Hi, anybody, please.
I'm just laughing because it's like the second time.
Yeah, maybe the fifth time.
So it's not enough to disparage him.
I don't know the guy.
But to tell people, please don't, you know, don't fall for it.
If you fall for that, please.
You're not going to understand anything I'm saying because there's no substance there.
And there's no point in disparaging, you know, an idiot.
No, I don't know.
I mean, I might say that I might see a man who might have,
you know, hang out a bar and have a good time.
Listen, I can shoot pool with with the worst people on the planet
and have a really great time because it's fun to shoot pool.
No, not even. I wouldn't even go that far.
I don't think you would be there.
I'm just saying to don't.
Well, you could say that I'm not getting it.
You're not getting where I'm going.
I mean, it's like, oh, my gosh.
But thanks for the thanks for the whatever subscription a month.
You know, whatever.
Thank you for supporting me that way.
But please listen.
Anyway, that's another thing I want to lead into before PhDs
and graduate study people, right?
They have learning problems, right?
Because the material they put in front of you and all academia is contradictory.
So if you say you've gotten one of these degrees here, you have a learning problem,
dude, because you're not paying attention to what you're, quote, unquote, learning
because all that stuff is contradictory.
And some of the stuff that the academia puts out in every field is just downright
alarming. How can you say this on this chapter
and then say that on the next chapter?
The what?
And any field, any field, medical, science, political, anything.
It's like, oh, you got learning problems if you went beyond the eighth grade,
by the way, and believed any of it.
Now, I'm not saying that you can't learn stuff.
Look, when I was in school, I went to a technical school.
You had to you had to test to get in.
And that was the time when the T.I.
Texas T.I.
90 or something was the first scientific calculator come out on the market,
which is one hundred and twenty five bucks back in 1980.
Right. Today's money.
That would be like a four hundred dollar calculator, right?
Five hundred, maybe more.
That's when Texas instruments dominated the market.
Yeah, that's when it first came out.
We're supposed to get that.
But when I got into technical school, we're using slide rules
and we're transitioning.
What the hell is a slide rule to paint stirrer?
Right. Was that it?
That's a funky looking paint stirrer. Right.
You know. So anyway, I use this, you know, give a slide rule
to someone under 30 and videotape it.
It'd be funnier than a monkey trying to fuck a football. Right.
But anyway, a slide rule and an abacus.
I mean, they think, oh, what do you give me? Baby toys. OK.
No, actually not. But yeah.
Anyway. So yeah. So so the technical aspects.
Yes. But then the technical aspects are so linear, put you in a box.
That's why everyone's trying to think out of the box
because they put you in a box. No one put you in a box.
I mean, no one puts themselves in a box.
You've been put in a box.
That's why everyone says you got to think outside of the box.
Why don't you just walk out of the box? Just put it in its place.
Put your education where you think it should be
and then find out where it really should be and then mitigate it. Right.
Because some people let me say that again.
Put your education where you think it should be
and then find out where it really should be.
The big difference.
Because some people hang everything on what they think it is.
And it's really not that at all. Right. It's a rite of passage.
It's a fool's game. It's this and that. So anyway.
So let's get into a little more of the nine star key.
Let's not actually let's just we just introduced this. Right.
Yeah. Well, so still we're looking at now.
Key. Now, look, key to me is if you think about it.
Yeah. Well, I was just going to go back to a martial arts class.
You know, when I was a kid,
you know, the idea is that your key was it was about your energetic.
You're you're you're sourcing your energy, right?
You're you're you're gathering it together and you're focusing energy.
That was your key when it came to martial arts.
So it doesn't have anything to do with that sort of thinking where it's.
Yeah, it's a trauma in India.
Like, for example, if if I were doing a presentation
with weather devices in front of people in Bangladesh,
I would show the device and say this is a device to guide Prana
and they would understand completely everything that else
I have to say and how it functions and what's its intent is. Right.
Or if I went to do a presentation on weather devices
in Japan or China and Japan, I would say this is a key device.
Or in China, the same term is Chi.
This is to channel Chi and everyone would know exactly what the intent is.
No problem. Right.
Now, here you would say energy, but that's really still up for grabs
because energy, they think the socket in the wall, which is,
you know, pressurized magnetic electricity. No, not that.
Anyway, the nine star key is based on study.
It's not. Don't confuse it with the horoscope garbage at all.
Now, I'm not saying it's, you know, rock solid.
I wouldn't really lean on it too much.
You could lean on it enough to see if it works for you,
because it is information to work with.
Now, an easy way to figure out what you are.
There's many ways you add up the if you were born between 1902 and 2001.
All you got to do is take the last two numbers of the year
and add them together and subtract it from 11. That's your number.
So if you're born in 63,
six and three is nine minus 11 is two.
So you're number two.
All right. There's other formulas.
There's charts. You can look it up online.
Some of the conflict, some of them are conflicting because, OK,
once you find the year that you were born, then you got to find out the month.
By the way, nine star key, the month starts in February.
The year starts around February.
So if you're born in January, it's the year before.
So if you're born in January of 1963.
Well, let's do mine. Let's do mine real quick.
OK, so I'm born. OK, well, I'm not I'm not in front of a computer.
So go ahead. Well, I'll do my best.
Yeah, no, I think you'll be fine without the computer.
So I'm born in 1972.
So I take the last two numbers, which is the seven and a two.
I've got a nine.
I take that nine and I subtract it from 11.
It's a two and it's a two. All right.
So what does that mean?
But but you were what month were you born?
Oh, sorry. April.
All right. Well, that's in that year.
But if you were born in January, you'd be counted as the year before.
Seventy one, right?
Well, yeah, because the year doesn't begin to February.
So if it was January, then we start with seven.
Now, some computers are different.
Like, OK, OK, let me just continue on the thought.
Yeah. Then you have the month number and the week month and day number,
which actually shows your tendencies up until you're mature.
So it's so much more complicated.
This can be perceptively to Western to the horoscope.
You have to also find what month and day you were born
or what part of the month.
Right. First half less.
And then that shows you how you what your tendencies were
up until your 18, 19, 20th year.
And then it shows how you can revert back to those years.
Right. It gets a little more.
Well, we'll explain.
It's like, you know, this union young and health.
I've been getting into it.
You can't just do that in 15 minutes.
No, no, not at all.
But, you know, what's funny is that you're describing part of the process
that people do these personalized charts with actually sometimes not the
not the crazy one, like you said, where they did it among the whole class.
And oh, no, I know what you're saying.
Those are the ones. Yeah.
But those are still just based on where the stars are.
Most has nothing to do with that at all.
This has to do with studies that have been done with boots on the ground,
taking notes of people for thousands of years.
These are records.
It is, by the way, it is based on stereotypes.
And these are more anthropological.
Yeah, but we got into what a stereotype actually is.
A couple of sonics ago. Right.
So this is based on stereotypes.
So if you don't like stereotypes and music like that, you got to go somewhere else.
Right. Got you.
With a set of nine star kids based on stereotypes.
Stereotypes are used in cartoons when you see the the block face,
the block head with the brow bone, with the the gray shade and the cartoon.
That's usually a thug or a criminal in the cartoon, right?
Oh, yeah, of course.
When they show a vertical, narrow face with glasses, that's usually the professor.
But you're right.
And they put the five o'clock shadow on the guy who was.
Yeah, it was kind of the dog.
Yeah. Yeah.
But he's not a smart thug.
He's the there.
And most of the people that do look like that are not that smart.
That's true.
You know, like strong, like both smart, like Gorilla.
OK, so. All right.
So anyway.
We're bringing a little Russian flavor tonight.
Why not? I guess.
Yeah, that's more of the north north
western part of Russia.
But cool. OK, so anyway.
So I start to look into it.
We'll get into it further if there's any more requests.
Some of you might know about it already.
I know some of you do from based on your backgrounds.
Let's continue.
Fongsoi, Fongsoi, Fongsoi, Fongsoi, right.
What's a funky way?
I heard it once said it was really funny.
Oh, Fongsoi is the text.
OK, Fongsoi. Yeah.
So anyway, Hong Kong, what that is, that is also energy movement.
Right. Like very simple.
You know, energy movement that you that everyone knows,
like if you walk into a house that doesn't feel welcoming.
Right. Whether you're when you're inside,
it's probably because the entrance door is in the middle of the house.
Right. That's why you build vestibules.
A lot of it is very commonly understood intuitively by human.
Should I say nature?
Well, and some of these things are developed structurally
due to the fact that they're more practical.
Right. I mean, look, the fact is that when you have a you have a chest of drawers
or you have a piece of furniture with drawers that come out,
it is wise to give enough space in between that and the next object.
Yeah. And also, you know, things like bathroom locations,
things that make smells.
So we can get into that.
But let's let's let's do let's, you know, remember the thing.
If we run out of time, give the most important stuff.
Some things are mechanically significant, though,
and therefore make more sense, you know, to have doors swing.
Yeah. Every culture uses it.
Actually, there's a lot of Fongsoi built into.
I use the Chinese way of saying Fongsoi
or Geomancy, which is measuring the earth,
is used in many of the codes, by the way, you know, the building codes anyway.
Well, I was just thinking of building codes, because if you take a look at,
you know, the way places are built based on different time periods,
you can see that some of them are more adapting to the environment,
whereas others really take hold of the environment and sort of redo it.
And others will create an entirely artificial situation.
Again, thinking about the different types of earth that one could place.
But it's also power structure.
So let's get the most important part first, you know.
All right. Give me more advance, because I studied this back in the 80s
when it was just beginning popular.
It was more for the rich folk, right?
When it was really deeply trendy for those who really wanted to spend money
and somebody would pay a couple of grand for somebody to come in
and rearrange their living rooms.
Believe it or not, that was a real thing.
So go ahead. Yeah.
Capitals, important cities, important corporate buildings.
They hire geomancers, which is someone who practices feng shui.
Well, there they want to set up their waiting rooms.
And, you know, their lobby area is on the map, right?
So you always want mountains to the north of you, a lake or a body of water
to the south. Right.
The west is your main entry and egress, your highway and roads.
And on the east is a river.
That's your typical setup.
You'll see Tokyo, major cities in Asia always set up.
Right. And that's the way that they develop, you know, say the way
they're going to lay out the buildings, the actual engineering of that.
Right. The way that they're going.
Well, that was the layout of the city.
Then the building would be something.
Let's just take something very common.
Like you don't want bedrooms facing the east because.
Right. You're going to be waking up with the sun or you need some heavy shades.
Right. That's very common.
You're going to get the sun pounding down again.
Common. Here we go.
And you don't want them really on the west because you're going to get the
they're going to get heated or you might have them on the northwest.
That's the most power position.
So we can get into that.
But these are practical considerations again.
Right. You know, just like before we transition.
Yeah. You make a bed of certain details.
You make a big of the.
So let me. All right.
I was just trying to say you make a bed a certain height in order that
you have a certain quality of air at a certain level
and a certain quality of air at another level.
You know, well, that yin and yang again, yin and yang.
So someone who's very yin.
Right. Right.
Would need a young bed to balance them out.
So young bed would be very high. Right.
Someone who is very young.
You would want a low bed to balance them out.
So generally, like people in Japan are far more young than people in Western.
Where do they sleep on the floor?
And that's why they also sit on the floor.
We and if you go to places where people are very, very yin.
In the tropics, you sleep high up in a like in a hammock or, you know,
yeah, and you might say it's to keep the bugs away or whatever,
but they just find natural comfort zones.
So here. Yeah. The front of the body is young.
The back is yin.
So where does the young energy on the body run up the back?
The yin side.
And where does the yin energy run down the front?
So if you tell someone Western thinking doesn't understand
yin and yang at the front of the body is young and the back is yin.
They're going to approach it like the battery.
Right. Positive with positive. Negative with negative.
Right. When you hook up a battery.
No, the front of the body is young.
So they're going to tell you the young energy runs up the front.
No, it runs up the back, the inside.
So you always got to remember that throughout that flip the antagonisms.
Well, just just like the look of the black and white symbol is that you got to see
that the curve flows against the other curve exactly the same.
No, that's not where I'm going at.
You got to look at the flip.
You got not the black and white simple symbol, but like the black and white tile
that the Freemasons like.
OK, every every black tile is surrounded with white tile
and every white tile is surrounded with black tile.
Think about it. Think about a black checkerboard, white checkerboard,
black and white checkerboard.
You notice that every white tile
only on its corners does it see another white tile,
but its main line see the opposite color. Right.
That's the yin and yang symbol.
By the way, Western interpretation is trying to communicate something.
So again, the checkerboard.
Yes. In other words, they have things that shouldn't be secret.
That's why they keep them secret.
That's what right. You see how it works anyway.
We need to get into more of the methodology, which is what the part
that you don't want to hear.
Let me let me. But let me.
All right. This is the third time I'm doing it.
Third time you're coming up to the cliff and not getting there. Right.
Yeah. This is I want to give how esoteric this can get.
The this is the end.
Like, let's say we did four sonics on four sonics and each one progressed,
you know, from kindergarten, grade school, high school, graduate level.
Let's just give the end of the graduate class right now.
This is the spot in the cell phone conversation where you get.
Yeah, you get the most important.
It's actually the least important if you don't get it.
But I'll give it in a way that hopefully you can get it,
because I've been told I can communicate these things well.
So let's give it a try. Cool.
OK, one guy was.
Why, gentlemen, sir, this is in the 70s.
He was consulting his father, consulted with this father of this family.
It was multi generational.
So this multi generational wealthy family had a multi generational geomancers.
So they all knew each other very well or whatever.
And they had a duty. Right.
So they he watched this one's family wealth go down and down and down.
And they they tried him.
He couldn't figure it out at the time.
And they hired other geomancers.
They couldn't do better.
So he finally resulted to say,
because this is sympathetic magic in a way. Right.
Because we've tried everything except for the ancestral worship,
respecting your ancestors, we're going to try that now. OK.
So what he did was he imagined that the family being powerful
and wealthy had powerful, wealthy enemies that hired a smart geomancer
to do something to hex the family.
And they tried to mitigate it every way and didn't work.
So he says, ah, one thing we didn't try.
Is that let's suppose the enemies of this family hired a geomancer, right, to
do something to hurt the graves of where the ancestors were buried.
And because of that object
that is putting that negative energy towards their graves,
they're experiencing financial misfortune.
So he said, let's say
that what they did was they took a statue of the antagonist,
took a statue of an archer, a small statue.
It doesn't matter if it's 10 feet tall or or a one inch tall statue
and found out where these ancestors were buried.
And he placed that statue with the archer drawing the bow opposite the graves.
So the energy of an archer drawing his bow in full tension
before release, pointing at the graves is what's causing their misfortune.
Did he imagine?
So let's mitigate that. How would we mitigate it?
We're going to go and get lots of little statuettes of rabbits
and place them all around the grave
in a way that people don't have to see the statues.
Could be 10 feet tall or half an inch tall.
They could be the size of army men.
You're even smaller.
It could be microscopic.
OK, point. Right.
It's because it's sympathetic magic.
Well, what the when they placed like the Otis's rabbit doesn't matter, right?
Yes. Yeah. Well, in this case, no, it is sympathetic magic.
When they placed these statues
almost immediately within days, the fortune started recovering
and they grew and grew and grew.
Now, is this simply because they're given the rabbits?
You know, the rabbits are now the reason for the OK.
The reason his logic was about putting the rabbits around the graves
was now that the archers arrow would hit the rabbit
instead of the grave of the ancestors.
Well, let me just say as a target, not not not.
No, wait, hold on. As it turns out, it didn't have to be a rabbit.
Any other prey animal would have been fine.
Game animal would have been fine.
It could have been antelope or whatever.
But basically, well, I think the rabbit was to symbolize the prey
to take the arrow away. Right.
Well, I think I have another question here, like as opposed to giving
the archers another target.
What about putting a wall around the ancestors grave
so that there is something that the archers cannot penetrate?
Right. Put a put a dome over.
Yeah, you could do that, but I wouldn't do that.
You wouldn't. I would fire you and hire someone who had a different
different solution because a wall is an obstruction.
Remember? Well, yeah, of course, it's an obstruction.
But the thing is, if you direct the obstruction, now you have your your choices
as to where there is an ability where it would deflect.
The arrow could bounce off the wall and hit someone else's grave.
Well, this is true.
But you want to use a but no one really aims.
And it also has to make sense in sympathetic magic.
No one aims an arrow at a wall.
You might aim the arrow at someone on over a wall or at.
But we still need something to aim at.
It has to be in accordance with the way that things are living.
Not you see, not body armor because body armor is not living. Right.
Right. No one aims.
People wear body armor, but no one aims at the body armor.
As a matter of fact, you want to hit them where they don't have body armor.
Well, right. Of course, somebody's got to confess.
So anyway, this is the this is an example of how esoteric it can get.
OK. All right. Now, rearranging furniture in this sense.
OK, the question that's answered there is that if the most basic instruction
let's go back to what I said earlier, that academics have people with PhDs,
doctorates, master's degree, even bachelor's degree,
they have those people that tout that they have those degrees.
Right. They have learning problems
because, OK, there's a difference between learning. OK.
You. A more accurate way to say something
is to you are familiar with something.
You can accommodate a thought or a subject
based on being familiar, right, or being acquainted.
Right. And that's called learning.
Right. You really can't learn because, OK,
when you have learned in something, you are acquainted with the subject.
You're familiar with the subject.
You can discuss the subject.
You have working ability and talent in that subject. Right.
Right. So you called your learned in that subject because of those other traits.
So what they call learning in these academic
this has been going on for a long time is memorization.
So on one page of a textbook, they'll give a whatever.
And then on the next textbook, it's totally contrary.
But if you memorize the two contrary things and repeat them, they'll give you an A.
It's called regurgitation. Yeah.
But if you are a comedy, if you are becoming familiar,
acquainted and knowing of the subject and using reason,
you'll say, wait a second, the stuff you want me to learn
ain't worth learning because it's contradictory.
So the people with these degrees are learned because they memorize,
not because they're familiar with the subject.
Here, perfect example.
Try to have a conversation with anyone with a graduate degree
about any subject. They cannot hold it very long.
After about a minute or two or three or four,
they're going to sound like they're speaking from memorization
and they cannot take questions that they have never heard before ever.
This happens every time.
These are the ones that believe in that they they've learned something there.
Right. Get it right. It's very easy.
I don't need to give any examples at this point.
If you're listening to Greek speak.
Exactly. And I've spoken to plenty of historians.
And you can, you know, definitely get a sense of what it is they've memorized.
But they have no clue.
Majority of them, any which way to study it.
Like if you give them a historical subject, OK, let's just say
they're all about the 20th century.
OK, fine. They got plenty of memorization there for you.
But you say, OK, well, you're a historian, correct? All right.
So what about the historical?
And you take them just a century or two in another direction.
They can't even begin to reason because.
Well, no. Well, yeah, because this is OK.
But like if 80 percent or 90 percent of the casualties of World War
II were civilians,
the military is not that bad that they can miss their target that bad.
So the purpose of World War II is to kill civilians.
I mean, you might have some people that are bad shots,
but not for four years consistently. Right.
They're not with 40 million, 50 million, really 100 million people.
Well, that's always so they can't come out and say
World War II in summary was to get us rid of civilians,
even though they know 90 percent of the casualties were civilians.
They just say, oh, was this battle, this ally, that bullshit.
No, but they'll just fire it back at you that, no, that is not the purpose of
because they're just repeating the corporate line.
And why is there three banks that supplied everyone with the credit that they needed?
No, that's not right, because they're not looking at the actual
because they're not objectively examining the situation and saying, well,
if you have this consistent,
you know, achievement here, that obviously is the
desired result that you're reaching for.
Yeah, but it's any subject.
How can they show you the lumina cross section of the intestine and anatomy
and then tell you that you're absorbing?
And by the way, in medical, what they're doing is they're forcing you now
to memorize all these chemical reactions in the cells, which are totally.
I see this textbook, $400 textbook, all about these chemical reactions in cells.
And I'm like, how did they find out what chemical is in the cell?
They they they they crush it, centrifuge it and then burn it. Right.
This doesn't even resemble it.
No, because what does that have to do with any of the stuff that's
that that shows you nothing about what it's like if I have a Webster's
dictionary and I and I should put it in the shredder and then burn it and analyze it.
It's it's so far from Webster's dictionary.
I could do that with anything.
If you want to eat your dictionary, you can.
It doesn't mean you picked up any of the words from eating it.
OK, it's just that's what they believe you can.
But here's the thing.
How can they show you that you have?
Where's the what's the people talk to me about even recently
about diseases and nutrition, like what's the mechanism for that?
Well, you absorb these vitamins.
What's the just a simple what's the mechanism for absorption?
But, you know, they studied this is what that was taught.
Yeah. Oh, no, no, no. I'm not asking you to.
I know you were taught. What's the like?
You're right. I don't know what the mechanism is for the.
You see, it's like, oh, my gosh, you should have asked that while you're in class.
Yeah. And you know, but no, you're too busy memorizing because here's the thing.
Again, when you take a look at the medical industry.
Right. And you say, well, look, how many people did they cure
and how many people did they kill?
Now, if you see consistently that they're taking something like medication
and constantly killing people with it, you kind of start to say to yourself,
well, it appears as though it works out.
But hold on. It's that's outside of the medical industry.
OK, for example, you like attorneys don't know any law.
Judges don't know any law. They tell you that.
By the way, I've seen in a federal courtroom was a financial thing.
What person brought up the law?
And the judge got very upset that the defendant said, you cannot bring law
into this courtroom.
I'm like, whoa, you know, this is exactly right.
So it doesn't matter.
But, you know, OK, look, it's interesting.
Yeah. Yeah. You can see this repeat.
No, it's what's what's going on is what's socially accepted.
Right. And so it's social rank.
OK, let's get into the part people don't want to hear.
Yes. Dimensional, dimensional thinking and all that.
OK, first of all, the problem word there is thinking.
First of all, when that term comes up, you are presuming
person can't think.
We described a few mechanisms here tonight
indirectly that refer to this. Right.
Second thing is, does the person want to?
Now, there's a difference between someone saying they want to
and really wanting to. Right.
OK. Now, the other part is
when you see there's something lacking in someone
within two minutes, if you don't see any progress
and I'm not talking about a baby that's still crawling
and hasn't woken an adult, you're probably not going to get any.
Sorry at all.
So what you do, because you can do it,
you step in and that's your job when you're around that person,
almost as if to the point you're around a handicapped person.
You actually view them not being able to know as a handicap,
like someone in a wheelchair can't reach something.
You don't figure out how to get them out of the wheelchair at the moment.
You reach and accommodate their condition.
So right now, this is right now, meaning this year,
last year, the past 50 years and probably the next 10 years.
The situation humanity is in, we have to accommodate each other.
If someone doesn't get anything or something, leave it alone.
If you get it, it's a blessing because there's someone in the room.
I can figure it out.
But teaching other people at this point, quote unquote,
I'm using the term loosely if they are exposed to it.
And if a hint is brought up and a very small edifying comment
does not show result within two minutes, two minutes and 30 seconds,
leave it alone. Drop it.
Forget it. Because you are bringing up the question,
how do you show someone this type of thinking?
It's OK. So just simply how would you do it?
There is no magic way to teach anything.
It's the only thing I could say.
And now that we're looking for magic and bring up the concept,
try to be a good communicator, communicate your thought clearly,
concisely, simply as if, you know, not juvenile, but childlike.
There's a difference between juvenile and childlike.
Childlike means simple and gentle.
Juvenile means simple and gentle, but so narrow and inexperienced.
Try to bring whatever you can.
If the person cannot grasp it at the moment, they probably won't.
That now it might seem like they are 20 years later, five years later,
but they still won't.
This is the sad part about understanding humanity.
Now, this is another aspect I want to throw in.
Recently, I've been looking at, not studying, looking at the work of John Mace.
Mace, just like the mace, the spray mace that you spray pepper spray,
Mace, M-A-C-E, psychology.
Basically, it's very, very much like Greek speak.
But I like how, you know, very often I say you could do things very rapidly.
This is all tied together, by the way, it's not a tangent.
He basically can help people psychologically
with people like rape victims and how to whatever.
In two sessions, almost immediately, because he says that the mind stores only images.
We create identity around these images and then we attach identities like that was traumatic.
The brain, the mind does not know is traumatic.
We call it traumatic.
So he has you recall the event.
You don't have to share what the event is at all.
He just asks you to whatever is bothering you.
Do you get an image and you say yes.
So it basically tells you is the image getting bigger and you say, yes, yes, yes.
Tell me when it stops getting bigger.
And then after a while, the patient or someone will say, OK, no, not getting any bigger.
How big is it? It's as big as Queen Mary is like, OK, now look at it.
I want you to shrink it down to nothing. Is it shrinking?
Yes, it's shrinking, shrinking down to nothing deleted.
Now it's gone and the traumas go away. It's very interesting.
All right. But he also states that everything is emo.
Everything is emotional.
Oh, my gosh. Where have you heard that before?
Well, this is almost like writing something down on a piece of paper.
Burn that piece of paper.
Now consider that exactly. Yeah, exactly the same.
But it's that's considered more sympathetic magic.
But in this case, it would be representation of that.
You don't even have to go that far. You have to waste paper.
There's some interviews with him.
John Mase, you can just search around.
I don't have any access to that right now.
Maybe there's people that are really good at the keyboard.
You'll pull something up, look at it.
They're very secretive because they're there.
They're actually they think that because they have a new technique of doing
something, Scalarator, that they're going to be wealthy
because they have a new way that's 100 times better than normal psychology.
They're going to be stupid.
If you think you're going to be wealthy,
if you are not part of this, then you don't. Right.
OK, so example, in other words, what they're doing
is holding back a lot of the critical information.
But if you read the book,
you'll get 90 percent or let's say 75 percent, which is enough
to do the therapy they talk about.
But their whole you have to pay them a whole bunch of money
to get the last 10 percent or 25 percent because they think
because they bested psychology, by the way, which is true.
Freudian stuff is ridiculous.
You know, Freud was
recorded on saying on his way over to America
that we're bringing the plague over to the to America right now.
He didn't mean the playmen, you know, psychology that he does.
So it's going to really screw everybody up.
So anyway, the only thing that, you know, they, you know, anyway, whatever.
But you'll get his it is valid.
His technology is valid.
Sounds a lot. If you're familiar with Greek speak, you'll get it right away.
I just was made aware of him.
I would suggest to the listener, actually, that you could probably find that
on the Internet archive if you look in the right spots, this kind of stuff.
But go ahead. Yeah.
So anyway, tie that all together.
Images, images, images, emo, emo, emo.
You know, the structure builds that way, the structure of the mind, the learning,
becoming familiar with something right that you can have a working knowledge
and something we call that learned, you know, someone he's learned and whatever.
It's because he's familiar with the subject is a working knowledge.
Right. But what most people are
that they've learned something is not learning.
Just again, any academic, any subject, they have just memorized things.
They cannot follow logic and reason.
I speak to people who have graduate degrees in various fields,
and they do get them in a personal situation, never in front of others.
They will admit that everything they learned is pretty much bullshit
or some of it's useful.
But most of it is bullshit.
But they have to retain.
It's kind of like a colonel in the army.
Basically, you know, you're a colonel.
It doesn't mean that much other than the uniform.
Yeah, I know. But don't tell him, you know, we don't want everybody to think that.
Right. Because then the structure falls apart.
Right. The structure is in between your ears.
Everyone's here.