This is Sonic Event 93, Ocelli in the Greek rated Y, how you doing, Greek, what's going
on?
Okay, good, it seems I got my voice back, or a voice, and yeah, let's see what we could
talk about today.
Well, it sounds really strong.
What are we up to, 93 or something?
Yeah, 93, 93.
It sounds really strong.
I mean, we've been pretty regular.
We took a little break this week because, you know, your voice was out for a bit, as
you told them in the chat.
If you guys aren't looking at the chat, we do have a chatango, which we mentioned before.
Let's see, the exact address, let me pull that up real fast, just to make sure I got
it right.
And it's, yeah, ocelliinthegreek.chatango.com.
It's the old basic chat room.
You don't even have to sign into it if you don't want to, you can go in there anonymously
and all that good stuff, and put some feedback in there.
There's other discussions going on between listeners and so on and so forth.
Okay, so with that having been said, but you did mention in there that your voice was down.
Your voice sounds really good, actually.
It doesn't sound like mine does.
Usually when mine recovers, it's still weak for a little bit.
Yeah, I did some sleep therapy and did some different stuff and actually got out and about
more than I usually do and didn't behave like I normally do, which is engage people.
I usually engage people and when I'm out in public, I start making Greek-speak comments
and typically I'm at a place like Home Depot or the grocery store or whatever, and people
start gathering.
Hey, why don't you write a book, and I give them the answer, right, and all that.
So, public speaking, and I didn't do any of that.
I just was very, I didn't yell at the cats or do anything like that either.
I actually just babied the voice, but it works.
I know, it's working good.
I mean, me, if I sleep, it gets worse because I'm one of these open-mouthed sleepers, you
know, I snore and all that.
Yeah, there's remedies for that.
You could do the yin and yang on that.
You know, that's yin manifestation.
People that clench their teeth would be yang manifestation, so a very slight bit of adjustment
before you go to sleep, you know.
And by the way, when you say yin and yang, a lot of people consider it to be, the easiest
approach is chemical.
Again, you know how we always harp on the pharmaceuticals because they just use chemicals,
right?
Right.
But yin and yang can be that way as well, so if you want to displace the yin, take something
a little salty, and if you want to displace the yang, take something a little bit sweet,
right?
Okay.
So, yeah.
In other words, balance it out, cancel it out, right?
If something's hot, you put cold, if it's cold, you put hot, same thing, yin and yang.
Yeah, these little tiny remedies, you know, I've walked this earth now for, I mean, my
sixth decade, almost going to my seventh decade in another year or two, and I've always just
tried to share little snippets, I guess they call them, you know, of information to people.
And you know, if they can't take a quick explanation without getting cross-eyed, right, you bring
up why someone should do, you know, what someone can do and why and how, they go cross-eyed
because they're not used to getting that kind of information, they're used to being raised
in a society where this is the way it is, don't ask any questions, right?
So they're not used to it.
So, yeah, I've been applying this kind of remedies to people around me, and I always ask, you
know, let me know, let me know how it works out.
If I don't see you again, here's my phone number, call me, right?
Because you need feedback, right?
Anybody can say anything, yeah.
Well, always, and I'll tell you, it's strange, occasionally, if you hand somebody a tidbit
like that, it might take a little while, especially if you live in a, well, I mean, you live in
a, you've been in the same town now for quite a while, right?
25 years plus, yeah.
Yeah, so, I mean, eventually, you might run back into somebody, even a couple years later,
and even if they didn't call you back, they might say to you something, hey, you know,
I saw you a few years ago, you ever have that happen?
Yeah, yeah, I've had people in checkout come out of line and come up to me and say, hey,
I remember, remember you were talking to us a few years ago at blah, blah, blah, you know,
at this place?
And I was like, no, I don't remember, but what did I say?
Typical Greek-speak recall, which, by the way, the typical, the basis for the Greek-speak
is when you hear something, a new idea, a piece of knowledge, something you're not aware
of, first thing, the thing is, what's your source for that, right?
What's your source?
And then, when someone gives you the source, it tells you a lot, right?
Let's say someone brings up a little snippet, and they say, of information or something,
dialogue, what's your source?
New York Times, wow, that tells you a lot, right?
Or if they say the Bible, or college, I learned that in college, and I usually, when they
say college, they say what year, which year, right, because I'm curious.
So you get to go, right, so we know what they're doing in college, we know what the New York
Times is doing, right?
And when they say the Bible, are you reading an English version, are you reading a version,
or did you get into the original languages?
That tells you a lot right away there, too, right?
A lot.
And another point of reference could be, look, from experience, I know this, right?
I always take a piece of information a lot more serious when they say, look, I've done
this.
And it works.
Yeah, and from experience, I, again, ask, how did you get there?
In other words, did you experience it because you were instructed, or it just so happened
that you observed it, right?
But the problem is, again, most people can't communicate.
They're not good at stringing words together, first of all.
Well, and here's the other thing, do they have recall of where they got the information
from?
That's another part of it, because I often have ended up in conversations with people
where I want to know where they got the information from, too.
Well, yeah.
Well, if they don't have recall, then you take the information.
And you know, I was talking to someone the other day who wanted a water device.
He owns a shop and a grocery store, actually, a health food store.
And basically, I said, you know, I've been using this stupid rectangle only for a few
months now.
And he says, yeah, you could find out anything on there.
And I'm like, yeah, maybe anything.
Yeah, but not everything.
Anything.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah.
I said, yeah, I'd catch myself there, right?
So he's, you know, very impressed.
But he knows sort of what's going on, but not really.
I didn't lay into him too hard.
But in other words, you have these devices, they're cameras that happen to be able to access
the Internet, right?
And used as a telephone, right?
That's the primary function is a camera, right?
At this point, it's a camera now.
It's a camera that happens to also be able to make phone calls.
What's great about that, though, is, you know, much like, look, neither one of us is a fan
of YouTube.
But we see.
Oh, by the way, I got to say something about that.
Yeah, go ahead.
Sam or Archon from Greek speak, decided to do YouTube, go up on YouTube for whatever
reason.
And I don't endorse that.
I'm not saying it's OK.
And I'm not really completely against it where I'm like, go, you know, take it down.
Right.
He made a an executive decision on that.
And that's I'm I'm I'm I fine with it.
Let's just say I'm going to be neutral with it.
But I would never personally do it.
And when I say, look, let's say you wanted to put all this stuff on YouTube in the future
or whatever.
Right.
I wouldn't get on the I wouldn't get on the horn and lay into you for doing that.
Or anyone at all.
Really.
Just when I when I express my wish to say dissatisfaction with YouTube, it's a mild
way to put it.
It's personal.
Like, I won't do it.
You know, I'm never going to say, you know, I'm never going to consider it an option.
But you don't consider it an option.
But you do see that there can be a practical use for it in a way, because I personally
didn't do that.
See, I would go the other way personally.
But if yourself or anyone else that I'm working with on this or is working with me or whatever
wants to do it, if you know, go ahead.
But I don't.
I will not.
Because not not not not for the point of creating content.
What I'm saying is, is that you do find a use for the platform in that you've told me
before.
Look, you can go on YouTube and see how to do something and watch a step.
Oh, yeah.
I think from as a creator, as input for output, in other words, I would never upload anything
right to YouTube.
No, no.
I get that part.
What I'm saying is even even even let's say on the business end with the water device
and it's not really a business, it's I want to talk a little bit about that from a perspective
that I've never discussed publicly either.
But I would not do it as a primary either.
I would go to one another.
Look, and if we say there's other ones, Vimeo, whatever you can name, they're just as you
know, they they use they use what you call YouTube as their benchmark.
Right.
Remember, those people that left YouTube because of censorship.
They went to the and then they got dropped and they got censored on there also.
Right.
You've heard of that.
Or am I just.
No, that happened.
There was a bunch of video platforms.
Some of them folded up, went away.
You know, a couple other ones are still around.
They're still, you know, presenting themselves as the option to YouTube.
But again, they're still using YouTube as the benchmark, like you said.
Right.
So if they see YouTube going on a censoring binge or whatever, they do it also.
So they're not much better.
So but I want to bring up something just a little segue regarding like what I'm doing
with the scale rater and the water devices.
The primary thing is I consider it Magnus Magnum Opus my greatest work ever to make.
And it's the dumbed down version that I've been presenting.
There's another version that's far more complicated, not the double one, the gen two, but it's
a triple component.
I call it a terbit error.
That's where you put water that is not clear, like looks like tea or light coffee and it
comes out clear through the device.
It's insane.
It's it's.
Yeah.
And I have not presented that.
Right.
And that might be presented maybe in a year or two or less.
I don't know.
But what I want to say is I want to get this out to people, right, and have them use it
because when I first put this together, I was having a conversation with someone here
who has a if you put in structured water, Tucson, she's the first Web site on top of
the Google search.
Right.
And I remember the earth's air, water or whatever is a Web something.
Anyway, I mentioned to her that you don't need many of these devices if they're built
well to basically clean up all the water in an entire state.
Why? Because, you know, when you hook up when you put this in line and, you know, when a
water main, let's say, or any device flow through or not flow through, you expect all the
water that's upstream to be your control.
And there's and when it goes through whatever device you're using, this or any device
filters, whatever, that there's a change in the water downstream.
Right. Because it went through the device.
Right. Right.
Well, when you connect this device into the water main, it starts changing the water
upstream. Before the water even runs through, it starts changing, doesn't make any sense.
Right. Well, you know what it does on an induction level.
Right. Well, I was going to ask the reverse question, which is even though it's been
treated now, it continues on down the line and further on down the line.
There's a problem. Couldn't it reacquire problems?
You know, unless it go with this for a while, for a minute.
Yeah. Walk with me on this.
All right. So when you attach this to a line and it's sitting there day after day, it
starts cleaning up the water that has not gone through it yet.
Upstream. You know what I mean by upstream?
Upstream is prior.
It's called the influent and affluent is what comes out.
OK. Right. So it's kind of like I've given this analogy before when there's a down
power line. Right.
Right. You don't have to go to the end where it's broken to touch it, to get hit with a
current. Right. You can grab it further up.
Right. Or either side.
Right. Right. It's kind of like a wire with no insulation.
Doesn't matter where you grab it.
Right. It's kind of like this takes care of what's called Faraday's paradox a little bit,
which is not a paradox when you talk about induction.
But my reason for getting this out to the public is.
It's one way of kicking the establishment in the shins before you go, because I remember
being in the labs with Halliburton back in 2012 and I was talking about inline devices
with no consumables, no consumables, which means you don't have to buy anything once you
put the thing in. There's nothing to replace.
Nothing wears out. Right.
Right. And they looked at me very angrily, the senior engineer.
And he says, no, if people want clean water, they have to pay for it.
Right. And that really let me know earlier on or 10.
That's not really that early, but still 12 years ago, what kind of a rotten, you know,
establishment it is.
Right. Well, it's typical because like every other business model, like medicine or
whatever, it's not about curing something.
It's about giving you a treatment to mask things so that they continue having what a
customer or repeat customers, what they're building.
So what I want to do is because I was thinking doing video website, wherever there might
be a small website, but it's got to look.
Not whenever I speak to someone regarding this and a buyer seller relations conversation
starts happening, I cut the conversation short, you know what I mean?
Like I'm selling and they're buying, you know, you know, if you listen to a buyer seller
conversation, doesn't matter what it is.
You could tell who's selling and who's buying.
Right. Oh, yeah. If you were to eavesdrop or listen to what we did.
OK, we're transcript or whatever.
Soon as I start noticing that kind of language happening, I say, OK, I got to go.
We'll get in touch another time because it's not what it's about.
Right. It's it has a different purpose.
So when I were to do anything online, like a website or video or whatever, it has to
look like someone is on the receiving end of this device, not on the selling or
creating. And he's got this device magically fell out of the air or the stork brought it
to tell little children where the babies come from.
Right. And right.
Stork brought this thing.
I was in it. I opened the door as a basket and I hooked it up and it's cleaning up the
water. That's it. That's that's as far as the information, you know, the packet of
information that goes out to the world is, look, there's this thing and, you know, the
thing is this thing and it does this.
That's it. Right.
So this is very contrary.
Why am I bringing this up?
Because in the past month, I've been speaking to people that are into marketing,
advertising, website building, blah, blah, blah.
You get it, right? Yeah, of course.
And they're all like, oh, you got to market this and you take it to markets.
I'm not taking it to market.
There's no market. They're like, oh, yeah.
The minute you sell it, someone I've never there's never not selling them.
Right. Someone asked me, how many of you sold none?
Right. You know why?
Right. Right. Well, you went over the contract.
You know, it's a 90 year lease, one time settlement.
Right. So. So these people don't get it.
What do you mean by these people?
Who are you calling these people?
Right. Yeah, yeah, exactly.
This is so different.
Yes, Ivan.
It's so different. You see what you say.
So it's in line with what I've been talking about, isn't it?
So I'm just trying to share that Greek speak is also walking your talk and
talking your walk, if you know it.
By the way, I can read along.
Maybe I could read an abridged one from someone who has built.
Let me just do this.
And I don't want to make this about the scale or whatever, but.
I'm going to read a message that I got from someone.
That. Built one, OK, and
OK, you had some I'll just read the whole thing.
And they're a sub, I think, because they're well, yeah, they were in the
seminar. OK, this is a text that they sent me through the phone.
OK. Had some positive results Thursday, 40 p.m.
went down to about twenty nine p.m.
parts per million. Right.
So about a twenty five percent reduction.
I'll be testing again today with some adjustments.
Are you getting over 50 percent reduction consistently?
Oh, and the kitchen sink went from 40 p.m.
to 30 p.m. even with the phone.
Even though even though the scale rater was hooked up to a garden hose outside.
So I can confirm what you said about upstream quality also improving.
Took a few hours after unhooking it for the kitchen to go back up to 40.
There was a lingering effect and and it keeps going on.
Then I made a couple of comments.
And I've been listening to for years.
There's all again. But seeing the results of my own handiwork is something else.
It's an incredible invention you come up with.
Anyway, so I constantly have people see if you test it like I've had people that had
labs. There's no lab that will test this like this, by the way, because it goes
contrary. Right. Right.
To what they're used to doing.
You just do labs.
You give them a water sample.
You don't give them a device, you know, because it's going to cut into their lunch
hour. So what I'm trying to say is that
the only way to really see what's going on is to what do it right or have one.
I think I've mentioned before people that have gotten one are very skeptical.
And they're like, you know, when this is connected, I'm going to take a water sample
to the lab to find out what it's really doing.
And the moment I was like, fine, the moment it's connected, I said, take a drink of
the tap water, take a taste of it now.
Oh, no, no way.
I would never drink that. So we're just just taste it.
And they taste it, their eyes open up.
I'm like, you still want a lab sample tested.
They're like, no, that won't be necessary.
My gosh, what could change?
How drastic. Right.
You see what I mean? So it's it's the paraphrasing, the typical.
OK, so you can do a YouTube video or website and try to explain this to someone.
Good luck. Not going to happen.
Well, people have to experience it.
Yeah. Well, first of all, it doesn't make sense that you're telling me the upstream
water has changed because it hasn't been affected by the device.
That's the way most people would think about it.
Right. So since that water hasn't been affected yet, it can't possibly have changed.
Well, it has been affected because what's going on is an induction.
It's like Faraday's paradox.
And if you're familiar with it, you can rotate the magnet.
In other words, anyway, look, you can look up.
There's probably YouTube videos on Faraday's paradox.
And if you listening to Greek speak, you'll see it's not a paradox at all.
It's just a failure.
Of the physics that they're teaching.
Right. Because they write, they're talking about electrons flowing.
There's no there's no electron.
It's just pressurizing.
Right. By the ether that's around everything.
They don't know that there's no empty space.
Right. Yeah. Well, go ahead and if we really had empty space around that, we would not be
able to quote unquote generate electricity at all.
Right. So, you know, the analog of electricity and water.
Right. So where it's like fish.
You know, there's a crazy philosopher fish, you know, and he's trying to tell the other
fish, you know, there's a possibility that we're all underwater, right?
We're all in water. And they're like, this guy's crazy.
What he's talking about. Right.
But they all. One thing that I used to say is perhaps the last thing a fish realizes
when he's dying is that he's in water.
Right. Well, yeah.
I mean, again, if people have presented this concept of, you know, the fluidic other
universe, whatever.
And I say, well, what what is it that, you know.
Yeah, we are in a fluid.
If you are fluid in it, if you exist, it's not liquid.
It's not going to seem that way.
But to someone else where it's a lot thinner somehow, it might seem that way.
You know, so density again, density, pressure, direction.
Right. Ken Wheeler gets into that a lot.
But if you could. Ken Wheeler is pretty good.
My critique on him is he's not an idiot.
He's not a moron. He's actually smart.
But he has very little wisdom and he touts himself for having a lot of wisdom.
So, you know, it's it's kind of like a loss there.
I'm a little lost. I'm not knocking him, but he's he's an OK.
Listen, once in a while, you know, again, the biggest.
OK. You know, very part of the Greek speak thing also is what I talk about a bit
more. You know, when I meet people, I said, you know, because you're having this
problem because everyone, you know, is a freaking moron.
Right. And I tell him when I tell people, you know, no one has ever turned around
and said to me, oh, how could you say that?
I know plenty of people are not morons.
No one. No one. Everyone's like, yeah, they all agree.
When I tell people they're surrounded by idiots and morons, everyone's like, yeah.
I'm like, oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh.
That's bad. You can't, you know.
So anyway, I get no what do you call a blowback when I get with those comments?
It's amazing because somebody that wants to engage with something other and is not
just willing to accept things on face value and on the value that they've been
given to accept them on might have the idea that they're not dealing with a
super intelligent population.
Well, no intelligence.
Well, you know, intelligence is a word that's constantly being overused.
OK. One of the earlier definitions is, you know, intelligence is measured by how
adaptable someone is.
Like if you put someone in a new environment like these intelligence IQ quotient
tests and all that, that's what it is.
You're taking someone from their everyday life and they agree to go into a new
environment, which is the IQ test and see how they can adapt to the questions.
Right. And how well they perform in adapting.
Because if you let's say you take an IQ test and if you fully adapt to it, you get
everything done very quickly.
Right. And you score very, very high.
If you don't adapt very well.
Right. You score very low.
It doesn't mean you're not intelligent, just that you're not adapting to the IQ test,
you see. And yeah, it's a whole thing.
It's about adaptation.
We used to call it improvising back in the day, you know, common sense,
improvising. Right.
So, you know, I always heard the phrase adapt and overcome because that's what you
have to do when you're faced with something.
Yeah. Well, OK.
I'm not trying to I'm trying to go with the marine thing here, but but that's what
it means. Yeah. But yeah, I get it.
Yeah. That's where intelligence is.
So, yeah, that's a that's a sticky surface, a sticky thing to deal with.
Intelligence. It's really I look for it.
Well, what I suggest is to look for adaptability, right, to a new environment, new
reset experiences, earlier situations.
And why would you adapt to what to prevail for yourself, for the benefit of yourself
and others? Yeah.
Generally, I mean, that's that's why you have to have some level of flexibility,
because I mean, look again, without direct experience, a lot of times you end up
taking the word of somebody like we were talking about before.
And where does it where did they get that information from?
Sometimes they don't know.
And that's the funny thing.
It doesn't mean that it's unreliable.
It just means.
Yeah, well, that's the normies are totally engrossed in what's called opinion.
Right. There's no truth with the normies at all.
So there's no circumstance or reference or baseline or references.
It's all opinion. Everything is all opinion.
And that's how they that's how they roll.
And that's fine because, you know, their background, you know, that's their part of
the background.
Yeah, and that's what makes it so it separates, you know, all these different
things. And that is the funny part, too, is when you do try to say, look,
empirically, here's what, you know, based on this, that third thing, you can say,
look, I've tested this myself.
I've read this. This is what has been said.
This is what appears to be.
And do you have any something that, you know, to the contrary?
And sometimes they'll just come out and say, well, I just feel like that's not
right. You know?
Well, yeah. And also when they say it appears to be, it's what appears to be
appearing to be meaning it's not at all.
And they're not interested. But that's OK.
We don't want to get into an NPC or that was like maybe a year or two ago or
harping on PCs. And that's part of the norm.
I've always brought up comments from old philosophers.
By the way, Plato was an asshole, by the way.
A lot of people that hold him up.
He's not really. Anyway, what Creek, why would you make a comment like that?
Just out of the blue like this sounds like Tourette's syndrome or something.
But yeah, but some of the better philosophers, the ones that are lesser known are
way better. If you read a lot of their comments and just strike them as
a quote and show them to someone today and say, when was this written?
And they'll say, this is about the people here today.
And like, no, this was written twenty five hundred years ago or two thousand years
ago. It's the same. So there's no reason to harp on the NPCs.
Right. Because they're always going to be here.
I mean, as long as the society has this type of framework.
Right. But again, what we got into the last time we spoke in terms of
framework is the I think in just a pair without paraphrasing
and adding something to it.
Remember Eisenhower's speech about the military industrial complex?
Of course. Yeah. And we were talking about the purpose of industry.
Right. And what's the techno feudalism and all that on the last sonic, I believe.
Right. Memory serves her well.
Yep. The military industrial complex, when he was talking about industrial,
he was not talking about the purpose fullness
of industry as we use it now, like factories making things
for people to buy. Right.
Or war. But it was locking in
production and the fiat currency together.
So the way it would overtake humanity
is by convincing humanity that they need a currency
to get anything and everything that they cannot.
Right. You see what I mean?
That you write. That was never.
And also we talked about there were no jobs prior to 1720 or 1700.
No such thing. You did what you know.
And you and you may do with it.
Right. Even you could be wealthy also.
But what industry's purpose was, was to show
or create a model for society that they were.
Everybody wants money to get stuff instead of if you want stuff, wanting the stuff.
That's why all these things about like law of attraction don't work
because people just say they want money.
How can you go into, quote unquote, a universal field asking for something
that is a complete lie?
The current current credit system breaks, which works on increasing
the money supply through lending, which means when someone borrows money,
they draw it off their signature and the money to pay it back doesn't exist.
Right. So it's constantly diluting.
It's a constant struggle.
It's in constant turmoil.
That's why whoever is in the future, watch the financial system.
People like the Basel people, you know, out of Sweden that do all the
the the theory behind it and all that.
They never put out real people.
They always put puppets out like Legrand or, you know, these
IMF people, none of them know anything about economics or puppets
because they can't put out the people that know what's going on
because they're going to have too many Freudian slips
and they're going to show that.
Why is this person look so terrible?
I mean, like they're in a panic all the time, right?
Because the system doesn't work.
But what it did do industry was it created a baseline
where people now still believe it or not, and will consider
that if they want something, they have to have money to get it.
Big mistake. Big, big, big, big mistake.
I assure you that if you want a car, a house, a wife or whatever,
and you think you have to just focus on getting money to get those things,
you're probably not going to get them.
But if you focus on wanting
and you want to, let's say, acquire a car, a house or a wife and just focus on that,
then you the money will appear to get those things.
You see the difference? Don't you see?
You see the so that's what the purpose of the military industrial
when he says industrial.
It was the bankers he was talking about.
And I have a lot to back this up.
I remember years ago, I did research with a bunch of guys back in the
between like oh three and oh five or six before the crash.
And I kept telling people the crash was going to happen in oh six.
It didn't happen in no way.
Just like I talked about, the pandemic would happen right before it did.
But it was I was I was thinking it would be
a before Trump actually came into office.
So with Obama. Right.
But anyway, these things, you can smell it in the air. Right.
But the research from back then was we were told that the economy grew
and all that stuff. Right. Right.
After postwar and all that. No, no.
It was trained. It was a training regimen.
It was to get people high and confident on liquidity.
Of money and products available and all that stuff
to trap them into what we now call the money system. Right.
And they're young children that just want money.
They don't know what they want. They just want money.
Yeah, I've heard even older people say, I like money.
I mean, idiocracy. I love money. Right. Right.
So, yeah. So this whole thing now
is, in other words, the ability to appreciate material goods,
even good food and good clothing has gone away.
Right. If you look at, for example, sometimes I go on YouTube
and they'll pull up like a fabric, whatever conversation we're having.
By the way, if I go on YouTube after we hang up, let's say. Right.
Actually, we shouldn't call it hang up anymore because we don't hang.
You remember the phone hit the red button, let's say. Right.
There will be suggestions based on all the various subjects
we talk about on YouTube videos. Yes, it will.
Yeah. How can it be?
Because I'm going to be going on a Lenovo
Windows based laptop where right now I'm speaking on an Apple iPhone.
How do they write? How do they cross it? Right.
You see. So Apple versus Microsoft.
I don't think so. Right.
So the other thing was the just to recap is the techno feudalism.
I don't know if I've said this before, but, you know, the Tesla cars. Yeah.
If OK, if they gave you a Tesla car for free and paid you
every time you got into it, they would still make money on them.
Why? Because we're Tesla's making their money.
You know what?
They were enriching themselves is every time you get into the car,
it goes up to the cloud.
What song you're listening to, what time you got into the cloud,
where you're going ties into all of your, you know, what you bought
and all that information, all that data, what do they call it?
Metadata is stored and sold by them, but not actually not by them.
If you do an audit on that, you'll see that there is a string of hundreds
of companies that relying on that data from Tesla cars.
So all of the whatever you paid to buy a Tesla,
they're making back several times every year.
What a scam. That's why when you see like Tesla didn't earn any,
didn't make any profit or they're losing money.
You hear that.
I don't know if that's still the situation, but a few years ago,
it's like don't invest in Tesla because their company is losing money
on the production of the cars.
Yeah, but they're super, super ahead on the.
Does that make sense to you?
Yeah. Just like these phones. Yeah.
Well, Netflix, same thing, actually, because Netflix
was hemorrhaging money for about a decade.
And during that hemorrhaging, they somehow financed
a whole bunch of shows and this and that.
And they continued to be one of the top, you know, right.
Streamers, you're probably probably going to stream.
I think you could still get the old DVD in the mail from Netflix, too.
I don't think they've abandoned that service.
In most places, you still can sign up to Netflix
and they will send you a DVD in the mail like back in the early 2000s.
Well, I got to say, I don't know anybody who's done it in probably 15 years.
But but yeah, I heard it's still available, though.
But that was the source was someone that was talking about Netflix
financials like you just brought up.
But they're the same thing, because if you're watching Netflix,
you're probably on a smart device or a smart TV again or a Roku box,
which goes back and forth.
Yeah. Yeah. I just noticed the HDMI cables,
you know, that you hook up video and audio with one cable
that work both ways in two directions of you. Right.
Yes, it's quite interesting. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I wasn't I had I was suspect to that,
but I wasn't sure until recently that they communicate back and forth.
Oh, my gosh. Right.
So everything's right.
This is going up to the cloud.
Well, I've done stuff on this on my show where, you know, look,
even your appliances that don't appear, you know,
that you don't even think of them as having computer chips are communicating
on a different part of the Web.
Indeed, you know, not not one that's even visual that you can watch yourself.
Yeah. Yeah. And it's all.
In other words, it's in the it's it's built in. Right.
It doesn't have to be programmed like your refrigerator
literally has a computer chip in it that communicates your your air conditioner.
You're I mean, I'm talking all the appliances
that you can name around the house communicate on on this on that Cisco system.
Yeah, I kind of I have a mini split.
I installed a Mr.
Cool and you could do an Internet hookup so I could be away from the house
and turn the heat on or on or off. Right.
Yeah, I kind of like that idea.
It's kind of like I worked with someone who was a trustee of the John Arava's
trust. I don't most here's a name that people don't know.
John Arava, he there might be actually YouTube video
that's like 12 years old or 15 years old of him talking about magnetite and
or AVA.
He came up with the smart home designs in the 1960s. Right.
And also stealth paint,
which I do have here, by the way, and the formula and all the stuff to make it.
That's why, if you remember back in the early 2000s,
Israel was not concerned about getting stealth planes in the late 90s
because they had this paint.
They could just paint the old F-14s and F-16s,
and they were just as stealthy as the cell. Right.
So that came from him.
Anyway, there's a name that no one hears about.
And on Arava. That's true.
But that feature that you that you can access is one thing.
But it but through the features like that, I'm telling you,
they have secret features that literally could tell
like everything you put in the refrigerator.
It can scan all the barcodes.
Sure. I think that has to be a smart.
Like if I have a fridge, it's 25 years old.
Probably not. Maybe.
Maybe because much like it does have a chip in it, though.
Yeah. Like much like I learned about the cars that, you know, like I didn't realize.
And I found out about this from a mechanic who pulled one out one time
is that, you know, cars in the 70s, some of them had those chips in them already
that today, you know, like they have the integrated computer.
Everybody knows all the cars have a computer in them, all of that.
But in the 70s, they had them and they just weren't as sophisticated.
But you could have like a Le Mans from 78 or whatever.
And which they don't make those cars.
So it's trackable. Yeah.
But it's always it's always been trackable, which is funny.
Because cars that you that you buy at the used car lots on,
you know, no credit check or whatever,
they find they always find you because they've got the chips in them. Right.
Right. Exactly.
And that's that's the funny part about it.
But but they track everything, though.
They know how much you you use your your air conditioning.
They know how often it's on. They know how.
Sure. Well, it doesn't matter if they know what they want to know
is how much data they can gather and how can they sell it?
Well, all of those data types.
Yeah. Good.
I want to tie this back to the industry thing, because people don't see that
as substance, what they don't see their behavior and everything that they say
and do and interact with is being is being used as currency.
They don't know that most most people are aware of something like that,
but they don't understand the value of because there was a
there was a person to help you say this. Maybe we'll end it here.
There was a
interview that I watched late night on cable back in the 90s.
One of the top credit card guys like let's just give a like the CEO
of MasterCard. Right.
And he and he's like, you know, most people who use credit cards
don't know how they work at all.
But if you know how it works and you're still using a credit card, you're an idiot.
And this is coming from the top.
That's kind of like the CEO of McDonald's.
You know, I don't eat McDonald's.
I eat that crap. Right.
Which I think happened at one point, too, by the way.
One of those. Yeah.
He got his order for his stocks dropped a couple of points when he said that.
Right. That's when the guy some guy did a documentary
about eating McDonald's only for a month or two.
And he went he kept getting medical checkups and his health was dwindling.
Oh, it was a supersize supersize me.
Yeah. Spurlock.
Yeah. That was a while back, too.
So, yeah, people don't know.
I don't think they care enough.
But if they just cared a little bit and made some changes, just lasting
changes that went through some personal austerity just for three days,
didn't use these things.
It would it would be enough to shake the system to its core.
Oh, yeah. Much like that whole you've heard it over and over again
over the years about don't buy gas on this particular day. Right.
Yeah, that's it.
It never works.
But if people did it for like a couple of days and also did.
Oh, massive.
They don't understand the power that they have. Yeah. Right.
Because that's the thing.
And that's the thing about this information, I think, is it's about the flow
of the information more than it is the information itself,
because it was about maybe seven, eight years ago.
They had one of those massive, you know, economic forums.
And the main speaker came out and said, you know what?
We don't need to worry about oil anymore.
Oil is not the big moneymaker.
The new oil is information. It's data.
Yeah, it's data, not even information, just data.
I think there's a difference.
Yeah, I think there is, too.
But that's the way he presented it at that forum or whatever.
You know, he said it's the information economy.
I think they called it or something like that.
And and then he led into it.
But the main thing was, yeah, the key was data.