The Sonic Event 27, Ocelli in the Greek, rated Y.
And, you know, we were starting to have a conversation and Greek says to me, look, hit
record.
So, so here we are.
I'll begin this time, actually, but Greek, before I begin, how are you doing tonight?
I'm doing OK.
I mean, I said hit record because this Internet stuff, the people, these kids, right, they
call it content, content, content, content, those kids, those kids, they got, they got
this newfangled Internet stuff and, yeah, they call it content.
I mean, contents may settle, right?
That's where I come more, I'm more from contents may settle, right?
Right.
Cereal box generation.
I used to say that.
As a matter of fact, I used to put that on chip bags, too, I used to say that a lot.
Right.
Contents may settle in shipment or whatever, because I'd always ask the question, why the
hell is the bag half empty, right?
So all the lawsuits in the 80s, so remember the quarter pounder wasn't a quarter pounder
and then the Stella who dropped the hot coffee and McDonald's, and that was the legal community
telling you we're taking over.
Yeah.
So we're, you know, we're talking about.
So yeah, what we were talking about off air.
You want me to set up or you want to set up?
Real quick.
Sure.
You hear a lot of times people talking about, let's say, controversial stuff and the lines
get cut off Skype phone or whatever.
Oh, they don't want us to say that, you know, and then go ahead.
Yeah.
No, the call drops or, you know, you get some weird kind of thing happens.
You and I have had this happen a couple of weird times where I had a thing happen the
other day with you where I said it sounds like a European fire alarm.
And I don't know if anybody who's listening to us has heard some of these fire alarms
that used to.
I mean, I haven't been to Europe since the 80s, but they used to have different sounding
fire alarms and we have on, off, on, off, on, off, on, off, almost like the ambulances
that sounded that way.
Right.
Okay.
Yeah.
So like, like, you know, Harley Davidson's potato, potato, potato, potato, potato.
Right.
Anyway, there you go.
Exactly.
So but anyway, the screeching weird noise came across.
I'm like, what the hell is that?
And he's like, what?
I said, there's this.
I hear like a fire alarm.
No, I didn't know how to describe it.
So we had that.
We've had other times where like the call seems to drop on one end, but it's still connected
or it does disconnect.
Weird stuff.
You know, Greeks going, why are you echoing?
I'm like, echoing.
I'm set up specifically not to echo.
Everything is intentionally done with my machine.
Well, look, the most hardcore, by the way, is when we're on this certain matters, you
and I and recorded just like this.
And the screen goes trying to reconnect.
And I hear the Skype calling really loud in the headphones.
And I'm like, Chuck, can you hear me?
And then I hang up or whatever.
You're like, I heard you just fine.
Yeah.
Well, that's the other thing is he's sitting there going, I don't know what's going on
here.
There's something going on.
It's disconnect.
I don't hear none of this.
He's talking to me.
To me, Skype is indicating me.
It dropped the call.
It's calling you back.
That's all I see.
Right.
And it's happened several times.
So anyway, the default thing is when anything goes wrong with with connections, right.
Anybody in media especially has always been like, oh, the CIA is listening.
The NSA is listening.
Now, sometimes they are.
But I mean, generally speaking, and of course, everything is a database and recorded and
blah, blah, blah.
And that's something that they do use the so-called A.I. to do is to quickly do this,
that kind of work so that it is database and stored.
That's true.
And we've known about that for, what, 30 years.
You know, I didn't need Edward Snowden to tell me about it.
We knew about the but what did they used to call that?
The yeah, the echelon system and all that.
You know, these names are known now.
But anyway, whatever.
Who cares?
All right.
So during certain topics with the Greek, when he brings up certain technological issues,
these things tend to happen more often.
I've had it happen.
And I say, look, on occasion that happens because, yeah, you struck the wrong nerve.
And it may indeed be something that is being listened to by an intelligence agency or whatever.
And I've had that happen.
And a good, for instance, is all of a sudden weird crap started to happen when a couple
of months back I found out and a few other people found out that the CIA had went and
briefed media assets ahead of the files coming out, the JFK files that they've they've hushed
up a lot.
And they went to the news media people and started telling them, look, we're going to
tell you what's coming out in these files ahead of time, even though the world is allegedly
not seeing these except the restricted group and blah, blah, blah.
You know, but we're going to tell you what's in them because you guys are so young, you
don't understand any of this stuff and you're not researchers.
Only researchers who have had their heads buried in this for the past 20 years even understand
what the hell this is.
So we're going to help you.
And but the researchers saw it as being a nothing burger anyway, right?
Well, not entirely.
Not entirely, because we did learn they did preserve some things accidentally, I think.
As a matter of fact, it took us a while to dig it up.
But now we have absolute proof that they destroyed a bunch of evidence which has not been in
the public's hands before.
And we can prove that.
But it's a long winding road to get to somebody.
So it takes.
Right.
But hold on.
You know, I have no sympathy about JFK getting, you know, whacked, right?
Yeah.
You know why?
If I was alive back then and even not into Greeks, because first of all, what are we doing
with a Catholic president?
Because if you pledge to be Catholic, your allegiance is to the pope, not the laws of
the U.S.
Right.
Yeah.
But I'm a drug.
Well, whatever runner, not drug, whatever runner family.
Right.
Well, it's very well known that the election was rigged, by the way.
So there are many questions, many questions about it.
I'm not going to say that you're absolutely correct.
I'm going to say that there are many legitimate questions regarding all those things.
And I'm not one of these guys who like worships Kennedy either.
But but realistically, I do feel as though there was a wrong thing that happened there.
And it needs to be understood by a lot of people did not like them.
And those that liked them had a picture in their house in an altar kind of setting.
Yeah.
No.
Well, he was alive.
This idea about he was Catholic to the other thing is how Catholic was he?
Right.
You know, he wasn't entirely devoted to that.
But anyway, forget all that.
Sometimes it's just just just saying if you don't renounce it, you're it.
That's why I tell people, you know, you know, the like not to divert, but you have some
being an alternative media and he talks, he's 10 year in this and this and he hasn't renounced
that shit.
He's coming on with credentials as academic and these morons that are listening to this
alternative media actually think he's got anything valid to say.
Yeah.
Well, you notice there's not too many professors come on my show.
And I often point out, look, I got a high school education and that's fine for me learning
too much.
Yeah.
You already got fucked up.
I know.
Eighth grade is the point where if you go past eighth grade, they got you.
But I always point out, you know what I know?
I know.
But I point out that, look, regardless, that's as far as I went because I was dumb enough
to go there.
But the thing is, it was what it was.
And it's really my street knowledge that has ever been useful.
So that's all there is to it.
And that's stuff I learned by doing.
Very simple.
Mm hmm.
Yeah, it was.
It was.
I understand.
Yeah, but street knowledge, you don't need to go right to the books.
You go right.
You go right to the library.
Not the textbooks.
Not what the idiot professor is teaching.
You go right to the library, right to the library and you learn from there.
And not not the library that they're telling you to go to or the part of the library where
they have to use textbooks.
Textbooks are garbage.
Right.
So let's go back to the.
Well, you don't object.
Hey, listen, you don't object to apprenticeships, though, because basically because of my visual
problem, I couldn't read a lot of those books because the print was small.
So quite frankly, I went and learned from people who were doing it already.
OK, how do I do this?
Show me.
All right.
Instead of reading.
Yeah, well, that's that's that's the way to do it.
But we look here.
The show me thing today.
If they're not doing it, you have to know that if they're doing it right or not.
That's why we're doing it.
We're one of the things we're going to talk about.
Mm hmm.
So we'll get there.
But let's OK.
Yeah.
Let's finish with the censorship issue, because this is important.
The thing is that as soon as we knew about that and we knew about activities we weren't
supposed to know about, all of a sudden people had troubles with their communications.
You know, it's like somebody's waiting for a call.
You're calling them.
You swear you're calling them and the phone's not ringing.
Things like that go on all the time.
And then you're all done.
Yeah.
I see it as if they're detecting your voice to prompt the device.
That already is read.
That already gets flagged, just like, you know, if you if you have an email with certain
words, it gets stored, put aside for later, they say.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
So, yeah.
So, no, here's the thing.
I don't mind.
Recently, I was in a conversation with someone in a certain business and I was talking about
certain technology that could that's way ahead of what the industry has.
Phone gets cut off.
And I'm thinking their battery died because I tried calling them back and went right
to voicemail.
Turns out they were doing the same with me.
They thought my battery died.
So we could not communicate for a good 20 minutes and then we went back and it happened
again.
Mm hmm.
Right.
So I said, this is fine.
And neither one of us really brought up what we're bringing up right now because we're
beyond that.
But I think bringing it up in a more cogent way where instead of people on the you know,
you hear an interview and they get cut off.
They don't like what we're talking about.
Usually ends there.
They don't really talk about it like we are right now.
Right.
So but that's the thing.
Now, on the other hand, I do see that occasionally there are valid disruptions that are put in
place and indeed it spooks some people and all that.
But on the other hand, I think on occasion you can also get sort of censored, you know,
in electromagnetic frequency, which is one of these things that is essential in almost
any communication at this point in the, quote, modern world.
Right.
Can be disrupted on another level.
And I think sometimes it comes from the spiritual side of things.
Right.
And that's, you know, so and I try and explain this and they go, no, no, it's the CIA, it's
the NSA.
And I'm like, but the NSA doesn't care.
Hold on.
Let me just interject.
You know, I brought up biogeometry, biosignatures, Ibrahim, Karim, right, right.
I discovered him because I was doing research on the Internet for a while about what entities
were in charge of electricity in the ancient world.
And when he first came out on the Internet more than 10 years ago, he was talking about
and he had written a little article that the ancient Egyptians knew about electricity,
but they didn't want to bring it out because it would evoke this particular demon.
And he gave the name of it.
And you'll find this in various literature.
Steiner talks about it.
I like Steiner's stuff, but he's too fruitcake-y for me.
You know, I don't know if you're familiar with Rudolf Steiner, so is Walter Russell.
They have valid stuff, but I think some of the people that are out right now talking
about similar things are far ahead of those guys, even Tesla, believe it or not.
So I was, it was part of the research of how everything that we have now was known.
You've heard me say electricity was always known, always.
Don't believe in the people thought that if they sail to the edge of the Earth, they
fall off, right?
That's what they thought.
Yeah, all that nonsense.
Never.
Yeah, they knew that the Earth was both flat and round, and you got lost.
Like, in other words, if you're going to travel on the planet or the Earth or the world to
see its limits, it's going to take advantage of how you perceive it and make it a nightmare
for you.
So if you think it's round, it'll make it a round nightmare.
If you think it's flat, it'll make it a flat nightmare because you're poking the bear, right?
Right.
You're not supposed to do these kinds of things here.
Same with any subject, right?
Researchers know that.
How many researchers have ended up in a fiery mess, right?
A fire, car accident.
Right.
What?
Fire, car accident, you know, suicide, shoots himself in the head twice, you know, this
kind of thing.
Right, right.
Of course.
No, but sometimes it is purely a spiritual thing, and sometimes, you know, through a
spiritual entity, what do they do?
Well, sometimes they might use somebody who is already in their system, right?
Why not?
You've already got somebody on the table.
By the way, the intelligence agencies, you know, it's an oxymoron, right?
Of course.
They're panty sniffers now, and people may not know.
Panty sniffer is like back in the day, you got, you're a young man, you're living on
your own, you live with your girlfriend, and you know this guy, and he doesn't have a girlfriend,
and he always, you know, he's like hard up for, you know, whatever.
Can I use your bathroom?
And the door is slightly open, and you see him going through your girlfriend's laundry
sniffing her panties, just because he never, you know, he can't get any, right?
He's never been there, and so he just wants to get a whiff.
Yeah, yeah.
So, I mean, it sounds kind of disgusting and lascivious, but it's like a low brand type
individual, and yeah, and you'll see this common mentality through all of them, yeah.
And they're very, very heavily manipulated, and the ones that you hear speaking in public
are allowed to do so because they sound like they have their shit together, right?
But none of them do.
But, okay, so let's go ahead.
No, exactly.
None of them have their shit together.
Yeah, but sometimes those guys are real useful, not only to the people in charge, but maybe
to the entities in charge, right?
Right.
Well, the entities look around.
They're not, the entities are not dumb, although, albeit, believe it or not, I've gone through
many, many years of discussing peripheral and depth.
Well, somewhere in the hierarchy, there's probably some idiots.
Most of them are dummies.
Yeah, no, that's what I was going to say is that somewhere in the hierarchy, there's got
to be a class of idiots, right?
Well, it's like humans.
Like, today, I put in a phone order with an industrial supply, and the woman was so well
spoken, I thought it was a robot.
I said, are you human or are you a computer?
She goes, I'm human.
I'm like, wow, you're so well spoken, and the timing between your words was spaced almost
mathematically.
It sounded like you were, right?
Right.
So, and she says, oh, okay.
I said, do you get that a lot?
She goes, no.
I said, well, I'm just visiting here.
Have you been on Earth for more than 15 minutes?
She goes, yeah.
I said, so you know what's going on here, right?
I didn't get into the whole morons thing.
Right.
But I let people know right off the bat what I'm thinking in a very short period of time,
like 15 minutes, right?
Just, I mean, not 15 minutes, but just asking if you've been here for more than 15 minutes.
But no, what I, my point here is that, you know, I'm not saying that you should be here
for more than 15 minutes, but I'm not saying that you should be here for more than 15 minutes.
So, you know, these entities are dumb.
Most of them are idiotic, just like people are, the great majority.
And there are a certain, that's why when you are an advanced human, in other words, the blood that flows through your veins is generally the same quality as other people.
Well, not really, and I can get into that too.
But your actions, the way you behave, what you express and manifest, if it's superior, you're going to get attention.
And the dummies are going to be, what do we do with this one?
I don't know.
Let's ask the Sarge.
Well, Sarge says, I don't know what to do with that.
You know, the next guy up, right?
And the Sarge says, oh, let's ask the Colonel.
I don't know.
So they get really, so the problem with being an advanced human in your ways is you're going to start attracting higher up and higher up.
Attention.
Demonic entities' attention, yeah.
Yeah, so it works.
You know, people think of it on the positive side of things, right?
You're going to get the attention of the good ones, but that's not really the way it works.
And you know what?
Here's the thing.
That's an interesting thing, because if you actually look at what's been memorialized as some of the worst shit that's ever happened to people
and who actually put it on them, it was the good guys.
When you read, let's say, Book of Revelation, Apocalypse, who's doing all the wrecking?
The good guys, right?
So, yeah, so it's, again, it's backwards.
That's why, you know, people listen to me, and they say, oh, yeah, I shared it with someone.
They think you're angry or upset or whatever.
I say, no, because they don't know how to listen.
They're not hearing what I'm saying.
I'm actually, I'll put it in air quotes, I probably have the most hopeful message that exists out there.
The reason why is because it's so efficient.
What I'm saying is operating at such a high efficiency level is just don't even bother fixing it.
It needs to be blown up and started over.
There's no way you could fix this.
I'm telling you, right?
And that's it.
That's very hopeful, a hell of a lot more hopeful than, oh, we'll just fix this and we'll be happy.
I just said, no, that's not going to work, and I could show you a thousand ways why it won't.
And no, you can't show me any ways how it will.
So leave it alone, blow it up, and start over.
You see, I don't look at you as either optimistic or pessimistic.
I think just fairly pragmatic most of the time.
Yeah, you can't fix it.
And, you know, this can't fix it stuff started a long time ago, which shows it's a testament for the human durability.
Humans could take a lot of punishment.
And still, you know, look at the medical industry.
There's like nothing I've seen the medical industry do, and I've said trauma, right?
You need them for trauma.
Not even that.
They have you sitting there for an hour unless your guts are falling out and they need a bucket.
Even then they don't really know what to do.
They just put you together just good enough, and they, yeah, they're very.
Here's the thing.
If you're a good medical technician, a.k.a. doctor or whatever, you're not going to last long.
Because you're going to look at everyone around you and say, what the hell is going on here?
I'm going nuts.
You're not going to last, right?
And this is with anything, even the intelligence agencies, quote, unquote, same thing.
And you're also made fun of if you go by the book, which is one of the things I want to talk about.
But the censorship thing is it has a spiritual component, but what doesn't?
But to bring up the spiritual component is something that no one does.
They think it's all a bunch of panty sniffers pushing buttons, you know, or AI.
Because that is present, but it doesn't mean that's the whole thing.
And the panty sniffers get their inspiration from the spirits.
Also, they don't know it, you know.
What's that?
There was a film.
The first thing the devil was to make people believe he doesn't exist, right?
Oh, yeah.
What was it?
The greatest trick in the world was ever pulled off is that the devil got people to believe he didn't exist.
Right.
Something like that.
Yeah, very good.
Okay, yeah.
That's how most people operate anyway.
But I think the censorship is real, and it happens along, I believe,
and from my, let's say, reason and logic, along the lines of voice recognition.
Because if you're talking to the device and it recognizes context and syntax and all that to do what you're telling it,
it could sort out anything and everything else backdoor style, you know what I mean?
Right.
It could sort it all out immediately.
I put out a challenge on Twitter, and I haven't checked to see if anybody is answering it,
but something strange happened to me when it comes to recognition.
It's not just the voice.
It recognizes all kinds of things.
Sure.
I realized that I shook a bottle of something that is like an over-the-counter kind of, you know,
just thing that you might buy in a grocery store or a pharmacy.
With a ball bearing in it?
Tick, tick, tick thing?
Well, not a ball bearing in it, but it had some alleged medication in it, right?
So I do take something for headaches, all right?
I don't know what you think of that, but it does work.
I do, too.
Look, when I'm doing what I'm doing, especially lately, you know, I could do a fistful of ibuprofen.
Okay.
Fair enough.
So if I rattle a bottle of something like that anywhere near one of these connected devices,
even if I'm not using it for anything, but it's just turned on, if I go and surf the Internet later,
I'll find that they're advertising a bottle of something similar.
Yeah.
Yeah, they're reading.
They could read this.
They're using radionics, which is, you know, sympathetic vibration, which is vibration, not frequencies, yes.
Okay.
In other words, you can have vibrations that are not a function of time, right?
And that means they can detect anything anywhere in the universe at any time in the universe,
because they're not a function of time, right?
So that's why you focus more on vibration than frequency,
because there are elements of things like thought and will and things, emotions, the emo, that we've talked about,
how to imply and manifest.
That is independent of time and location, right?
But it has a function, meaning because it's a vibration, we always, when you go to the academic side,
it has to have a function in time, you know, how many per second or for how long,
and I'm telling you it doesn't, because your thought, your consciousness is beyond time if you allow it to be, right?
So don't be conscious of time.
A perfect example is when you're falling or in an accident, you notice how time slows down.
It seems like it took forever for that other car to finally crunch the front of the car you're in.
Right.
Right?
But if you saw a videotape of it, it's almost instant, right?
Right.
It's a good example.
It happens so fast, you have no idea exactly, you know, the order in which things happen.
People ask you later, well, did this happen first or that happen first?
In reality, if you're in the midst of it, you know.
It's slow.
It's slow, but you can't do it, you're disabled because you're not, that's what the martial artists and the Qigong do,
is how to move within the frames, within the, you know, like in a film, how many frames per second?
It's not the frames per second, it's how many non-frames in between the non-seconds, what you do there, right?
That's what that's about.
Yeah, that's kind of what, believe it or not, Richard Allen Miller was trying to explain that on my show once.
Oh, my gosh.
Yeah.
I want to listen to him.
This is not a negative criticism.
I want him to provide stuff that is good.
He just doesn't.
I mean, I don't know.
I could tell you why and there's no reason for it, but yeah.
So, yeah, the whole thing is, you know, the old saying, it's the space between the notes that makes the music, right?
Or the space between the bars that keeps the tiger in the cage.
The notes you don't play are the ones that are most important for World War II, yeah.
Right, yeah.
Those are non-time functions that are very evident in our existence, meaning,
and that's where you want to jump, dancing between the raindrops, right?
Right.
So, it's called scalar function.
It means it's everywhere all the time and it doesn't have a time function.
Oh, yeah, that's why they say scalar waves.
What are scalar waves?
That doesn't make any sense.
So, learning to operate in those places, but yeah.
So, what do you think about the censorship stuff?
It exists, yes or no?
Oh, absolutely it does, but I think it's misunderstood by the people that, you know,
they think of it on one level.
But it does seem to have changed in recent times to me.
I don't know how to explain the change, but it does seem to be changing.
Of course, it's reality changes.
But here, could we call the spiritual side cosmic censorship?
Could we call it that?
Also cosmic censorship.
Have you heard that term before?
I have, indeed.
Yeah, it's come around a few times.
Yeah.
You notice I haven't been talking about dummy loads, cosmic censorship, space heaters,
and all the stuff that I used to back in the day, so to speak,
because it's move ahead and get more casual about things in a more functional way.
But, yeah.
No, and I appreciate that.
And we have looked in the chat recently.
You know, people are obviously hearing part of what you're saying about the water.
Yeah, that's by the way.
I like to put – there's more stuff I could put out regarding other things.
But what's interesting is a couple of people have caught on,
but no one has caught on who's enterprising who says,
do you know, Greek, this is like telling people that you got bitcoin for 20 cents
and they should get it, right?
So no one's really picked up on it like that yet, which is fine, because it should –
and I'm not saying it's a commercial thing either, you know, whatever.
But if you're an – put it this way.
If you're an enterprising individual, you see this, you're going to be, oh, my gosh, okay?
It's kind of like when you meet a cold-blooded killer in a crowd.
When you present something to a group of people and someone asks questions like –
let's say you present weather work to people that you can make rain or stop rain or stop hurricanes.
And, oh, wow, can you do this?
But if someone comes up to you and says, okay, you said you could stop hurricanes,
but can you make them, right?
That's a cold-blooded killer type.
You know what I mean?
That's like the kind of people that are – that other groups want behind the scenes,
to see that kind of – ask those questions right away, right?
So anyway.
But, yeah, the chat.
Let's go back to – nothing much in there.
There's – someone put in some interesting stuff about origins of Greece and things like that.
Actually, he did an informal but serious invitation.
If he wants to drop stuff like that, said, let us know, tell us more, come on to Sonic.
It will be a first time.
I think once we had the little Buddhist girl that you brought on that was kind of ridiculous.
Yeah.
But we could bring on – I don't mind.
By the way, if you've got something to say and you have to say something that's, you know,
very pertinent and can move things along, whatever those things might be, yeah, we'll bring you on.
I've had some people send emails that said, hey, look, I love reading your messages
and maybe come on with Chuck or whatever.
Sometimes it works, sometimes it doesn't.
Obviously, we haven't had anyone on yet.
But that's an open invitation.
This is Skype, by the way, right?
I don't do the Zoom.
You know why I don't do the Zoom?
Just for the – I haven't even looked into it.
For the very premise that it became the Hockney thing, that's why I don't want to do it.
Just for that reason alone is good enough.
And you know what?
That's a pretty good reason.
You know, that's one of those weird things you and I have in common.
Like the moment that something becomes popular, I automatically reject it.
Yep, automatically, yeah.
You know, even if it's a movie.
Somebody goes, this is a great movie.
Everybody loves this movie.
I go, yeah, that's why I'm not going to see it.
Like right away.
That's always my reaction.
Yeah, I learned that when Foreplay became popular anyway.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, oh, okay.
So, yeah, so this is an indirect but serious open invite.
Well, not really an invite, but an open, yeah, come on.
If you got something, I want to hear it.
And everyone else should too.
Yeah, by all means, we can arrange that.
Easy, yeah, that's why I said Skype.
Just get Skype, you're ready to go.
Exactly.
Look, I give out my Skype all the time.
I'm Charles.Ocelli on Skype.
If you want to reach out to me, send me a message, you want to come on, just, you know,
do that thing where you try and friend me on Skype.
And for me, it's the same as the e-mail,
UncommonSenseRadio1 at gmail.com, and it's numeric one.
There you go.
So you can reach us real easy there.
Do I give the password out too?
No, I'm sorry, I'm just joking.
I wouldn't do that.
I had guys on my show one time just sitting there giving out their social security numbers.
I thought that was funny.
That's fine.
It's not your number anyway.
That's what they were saying.
By the way, here's the thing.
If anybody asks you or any institution asks you for a social security number, they're not government.
No.
Proof of that is if you deal with the State Department, passports and all that, it's optional.
But anything else to ask for a social security number, it's not government.
It's sort of optional with doctors and things like that.
By the way, I've kind of brought this in passing.
The social security number back in the days was called the exemption.
That's it.
It was the exemption.
What?
Exemption from what?
The bankruptcy.
In other words, what you call parts of the government, especially the Congress,
if you talk to the IRS and say, well, don't complain to us.
It's your Congress that enacted us.
That's the same with the Federal Reserve.
Don't tell us what we're doing is wrong.
It's your Congress, right?
So they rub the Congress in your face.
Okay, what they did was they did some dealings with some private bankers,
and the bankers set it up and the government became a corporation,
and that corporation went bankrupt, right?
And it's insolvent, and it cannot get out of that bankruptcy.
But you didn't know about it, meaning the general public, and you didn't cause it.
So you get an exemption number, meaning when it comes to money,
you use that number and you get what you want, and it's generated from your signature, right?
So that's why some people say, I'm so thankful I got a federal grant.
I said, what do you mean?
The government's got no money to give you a grant?
They took your signature and ran it through the Fed window, right?
So they're talking about all this stuff.
So it's called an exemption, by the way, but they don't use that anymore because it's –
let's just put it this way.
The rational, quote, unquote, real academic side
and the real lawful side of what this is was washed away a long time ago.
Even judges don't even know if you – I even brought this up to a judge once.
I said, what about the – you guys are using the exemption.
You see, you mean you're trying to say that they're exceptional?
I said, no, the exemption.
And he was – I thought he was playing dumb, but he really is dumb.
Anyway, that's all that is, social security.
It's not your number.
It can't be used as ID and all that.
And, by the way, there are codes that if they demand –
someone demands that number to do business with you, like a job application.
You know what that – that goes under RICO statutes.
And if you could get them – usually if you ask them,
you want the social security number or you won't give me this or do that,
give me that in writing.
They say never.
But if they do, that's 30 grand for you right away.
Probably if you're applying for a job, you could sue them for treble damages
so you don't go by the hour and say what your yearly salary was,
three times your yearly salary.
Yeah, you could make a living doing that, just applying.
But it will take a while to – and they usually settle out of court.
There's no judge that will take this, by the way.
Closed case, sealed case are open, right?
And how do I know this?
But anyway, yeah, so where were we?
We talked about social security number, passwords being put up.
Yeah, well, you got my head spinning there for a second.
So, okay.
Yeah, well, you also mentioned by the book
and how people don't go by the book or do they go by the book
and how they get treated if they're by the book.
I mean, you know, there's an interesting phrase.
That's a term that you'll see that certain authorities use.
Oh, he goes by the book, right, or whatever, right?
Because remember, this isn't as seen on TV society, right?
Before that, it would be as heard in church society, right?
Or as you heard it on the radio.
I was watching a film once.
It was done in the 70s.
I don't know if it was Sean Cassidy and Sundance Kid or something like that.
It was filmed in the 70s.
It was supposed to be about the 30s,
and some guy's whistling a jingle that was on the radio.
You see, that's pretty common, right?
Like someone uses jingles that they see on commercials now, right, on TV or whatever,
or the Internet.
And I pointed it out to someone.
I said, look, you see how it affects the culture?
This movie's supposed to be in the 30s.
They're whistling a jingle.
Perfect.
You see how this isn't as seen on TV.
What I mean by the book, let's say you go, there's a book called the Bible.
They say, swear on it.
And you say, well, look, the contents of the Bible,
you mean what's written on the Bible is what makes it the Bible?
And they'll say yes.
They'll say, well, I have all those words downloaded on my phone.
Can I swear on my phone?
No, no, no.
You see what's going on?
It's all direction to make things that are not important important, right?
Because the book known as the Bible has no value at all in its mass form.
You know what I mean?
It's mass, whether it's a big Bible, small Bible, whatever.
It's what's being communicated.
And now it doesn't have to be a book.
It can be digital.
It could be audio, right?
So that's where when I've used to do some Skype calls years ago
and where comrades go and say, oh, I don't know about the Greek.
He relies on information from books.
And I was like, oh, my gosh, oh, my gosh.
It doesn't have to be a book, right?
As a matter of fact, Homer's Iliad and Odyssey,
most of it was written to be done in iambic pentameter to be oral,
to be remembered oral around a campfire story, right?
Right.
So it's just information that's been memorialized and undistorted,
uncorrupted on any subject.
And that was the thought.
So let's use an example again about the Bible.
People think I'm religious or some people think I'm Jewish.
No one thinks I'm Christian, thankfully, thankfully, whatever.
Look, I don't believe in any of it, right?
I'm not religious as most people that are connected to things
that say they're part of the Bible.
What I've done with the Bible,
and this is a little personal too over anything else,
I see that it's thrust by the –
it's allowed by most of the powers that be
to be a reference about morality and all these other things.
So, all right, so that means the Bible is important.
The Bible is important, not what people say about it.
So go read the Bible and you'll find out what people think is in there
is not in there at all, right?
And the religions or the institutions built around it
aren't doing anything at all that's in there.
So now you have a choice.
Well, the first thing is if you have two dissimilar stories
and they're both telling you it's the truth but they're dissimilar,
well, only two things can be true.
Either they're both wrong or one is right.
They both can't be right, you see.
So that's what you do with all the information.
That's what I do.
So when I look at the Bible, I'm like,
hmm, is this something I want to incorporate in my behavior,
my ideology, my ideas, the way I think about the way I want to live?
And I thought about it for a while and I said, sure.
So that's where I'm at, right?
No more than, for example, I have a manual for Chrysler cars
and you have to use certain fluids, right?
And I mean they're Chrysler fluids, right?
And so, yeah, so do I just go get what transmission fluid, right?
Because no, no.
You've got to put a certain kind of coolant into an engine
because if you put the wrong stuff in there.
The manufacturer, the alloys, right?
They're going to be the metal alloys against that chemical, right?
So it's just a basic aspect of that.
So the same with quote-unquote science.
Recently with the pandemic, trust the science, but it's all hearsay.
I didn't hear any science at all whatsoever
because you go look at the science, if you can find it online anymore, which you can't.
Well, that was the funny thing is that they memorialize some things scientifically
and then that's not what is being put out as, well, look, we've got the papers here.
We're going to tell you what's in it.
And they tell you things like, you know, I went over this with you.
You know, oh, this is going to stop the spread.
That's not what it says.
You know, even the people that made it didn't say that about it.
You know, well, a little.
So that's where you make the decision.
You're going to go along with the collective believing what they're being told, even though it's right.
It's actually a mockery.
I kept saying for many years that you're being mocked.
Like by who?
I'm like, oh, my gosh.
I get a lot of questions like that.
By who?
Who's they?
I'm like, oh, my gosh.
You know what happens when you show up to class without doing your homework?
You look stupid, right?
Oh, wait a second.
But even if you did your homework, you'd be stupid.
Anyway, that's another whole other thing.
So it gets, I mean, it's that bad.
Well, look at it this way.
If you're a five-year-old and you go to school and, you know, there isn't much homework still,
but, you know, everybody else believes in Santa Claus and you don't, you look stupid, right?
But if you believe in Santa Claus, you're stupid, right?
Right.
That's why I have no problem with them doing History Channel documentaries on, you know,
Where was I somewhere recently?
There was some History Channel about a Paleolithic man, like, you know, and the dinosaurs millions of years ago.
I said, yeah, this was done by the same people that are going to show you Santa Claus' toy factory in North Pole.
It's the same, you know, category of truth there, right?
And by the way, here's the thing.
There might really be a Santa Claus with a toy factory in North Pole for reals.
There might be, right?
But I'm just saying that is, when you use that as a metaphor, it's categorized as fiction.
Well, I know this.
No fat man in a suit was showing up to drop off toys when I was a kid.
I mean, that didn't happen.
Oh, that aspect, yes.
If we lump it together, it's all stupid, yeah.
Yeah.
So, but this is what they do.
And they've been bred this way and groomed this way.
Now, the breeding is through chemicals and dumb people should have, are encouraged to have babies
and people, not necessarily smart, but people that are, quote, unquote, more better in their ways are disencouraged to have,
and that disencouragement is self-disencouragement.
It's like, why would you bring a child into this world, right?
And I'm saying this even 100 years ago.
Why would you bring a child into this world?
By the way, because the 1920s and the 20s that we have now are very, very similar, right?
If you look at what was offered in the 1920s in society, technologically, it was way ahead what it was in the 1890s,
even though everything that could have been known was already known by the 1890s, right?
Well, there's all kinds of weird stuff that people don't seem to realize.
I'll bring up one of the odd technological things since we were talking about Skype earlier.
It's something I was looking at is, you know, on the Jetsons, right?
You remember the cartoon, the Jetsons, and it was a big deal.
Oh, look, you know, they have these telephones.
They could put it on their TV, so you got a TV screen to watch people and this and that.
Oh, well, that's something we're going to have in the future.
1920s.
Futurists in the 1920s had that.
Well, see, I found it in the 30s, but either way, I found it in the 30s in Germany.
It was actually something that the public even had access to,
where you could make these video phone calls, basically, in real time.
It's just too much infrastructure.
It's all about infrastructure.
But they did have it.
They actually had it, though, for a bit.
Well, look, this is a broad brush coverage of the subject.
Sure.
Anti-gravity technology exists.
There's 1,000 different ways to do it, what you call anti-levitation.
Easy.
It could be put out to the public.
What's it going to do to the infrastructure?
Which lane are you driving in?
Yeah, right.
It'll make it very difficult because now you're going to have to have air traffic control, basically.
Completely different concept.
Yeah, and even if you made the things so they can't collide would be chaotic even then, right?
So it's all infrastructure.
Yes, most of it is infrastructure to be built.
Not necessarily that, but what kind of infrastructure,
how will the infrastructure behave once it's put in place with the mindset of the people that are here now?
It won't work.
I would think that you could automate it so that, you know, look,
certain people at a certain height would only go here, here, here.
You know what I mean?
Like you could control things by height and basically the vehicles, much like the self-driving,
you could probably set it up so that they can't collide with each other, like you were saying.
I mean, obviously, things will go wrong now and then, but I mean, I think it could be done.
It's just that it would require, again,
It's the mindset of the people won't work, right, with the people that are here now.
You see, that's the ultimate problem, is at the end of the day,
even though it could be made sense of, you know,
very much like when people talk about competing for resources on the planet,
they go, oh, there's not enough resources on the planet, and I go, that's not true.
The problem is the distribution of it, and if somebody very pragmatically distributed this stuff
and there was no cause for withholding it from anybody else,
everybody would have everything they needed, and it would not be a problem.
Well, yeah, but the people in charge, who are not really people of the planet,
hate the people, not for their behavior.
I'll be honest, I hate most people, not because they're people or human,
but because of the way they behave, and they won't change.
Here's the thing, they're amoral, they're apathetic, and they're beyond immoral.
Amoral means, you know, not only...
Amoral means you know the difference between right and wrong, you don't give a shit,
but the reason why I say they're amoral is because they have access.
Perhaps I'm misinforming, because when I hear amoral, I think to myself,
there is a lack of moral direction.
That as well, right, but they do have access to gain the knowledge,
but they don't want to, and they're apathetic and all this.
See, I would make that more akin to apathy,
where you just don't care what direction it goes in at all,
because to be amoral, a lot of people confuse it with, to me,
to be just very nasty and negative morally,
and I'm thinking to myself, no, that's not true,
because if you're amoral, it's, you know, when you A something,
it's absent, basically, right?
In essence, it's kind of like that old Christian maxim,
it says, I hate the sin, not the sinner, right?
Because ultimately, it's the behavior of the person.
You know, someone, however they look, or even smell,
it doesn't really, it's not going to affect the overall group
as much as how they behave, and that it means speech, action,
and all that, right?
That's enough to actually have people condemned.
It's your behavior.
I mean, why is a guy on death row, and someone is sitting at a desk job?
Well, because the death row difference is behavior.
You see, so, and by the way, humanity is on death row.
They don't know it, though, I mean, but not naturally.
I mean, it's going to be like mop-up crew type stuff, death row, right?
And it won't show well in history because it'll look like,
well, it'll be more honest, hopefully, in the future.
It won't show like, oh, all these innocent people got wiped out.
No, and you'll have to redefine what makes one guilty, right?
Because your model citizen and model human, right,
that was pretty bad.
You know, what they're showing you as a model is not good at all
because of what they support, what they're doing, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
It's a long story, and I've gone over this many, many times.
You know, that's where I bring up the subject or the phrase,
have you been on this planet for more than 15 minutes?
Oh, yeah, so you know what's going on here, right?
Yeah, but it did take me several years, to be honest with you,
to make peace with the idea that quite often the people that are on the surface,
you know, like what is the weirdest thing, right, is the Dennis Raiders,
you know, the BTK killer type guys, the this, the that, the third thing,
are often conducting themselves perfectly fine throughout a lot of other society.
You know what I'm saying?
It's not like they're sticking out as a sore thumb constantly
and calling attention to themselves.
They actually are, you know what, they're your church leader.
They're your, you know.
Oh, yeah, but all that stuff is so twisted and backwards, right?
Yeah.
It's all backwards.
I think, where was we?
We were speaking, I said, what do you mean about just look at it 180 degrees?
Well, it doesn't mean you get everything if you flip what they're telling you
regarding anything, really, 180 degrees.
It's true because how are you going to get the information reversed, right?
Right.
What if they tell you a building and 180 degrees is no building?
No, no.
What I mean is if the overall subject matter, if they tell you it's terrorism,
that means it's not terrorism.
But if they tell you it's a exercise, it was probably terrorism, you know, most likely.
And I use that as an example, and I can't really talk about it,
but how many times have you heard of the reporting,
downtown L.A. there are Black Hawk helicopters flying low for the past three hours
and no one's telling us why, and the next day the Pentagon says,
it was an exercise, right?
Bullshit, right?
That goes back to what's the, you know,
what the difference between genius and stupidity is, right?
So these people have no limits.
I mean, in other words, genius has limits and stupidity doesn't.
So there's plenty of people like that internationally and nationally
that try to do dumb things that are found out,
and then it's like we don't really care what they do, you know, to the public,
but it'll make us look bad, so let's try to stop it.
And they usually do.
The only weird exception to that over the past, like, say, 20 years that I've seen
is the Boston bombing situation where that was wild.
Yeah, the smoke bomb that they blew off and the guy with the legs already.
Yeah, that was about Kennedy Library getting a fire, wasn't it?
Well, that was part of what went on, but then the strangest thing was,
you know, they're going, okay, this is terrorism,
and they basically locked down not just the city of Boston,
but, I mean, the whole, like, half of the state they locked down.
Yeah.
And then every time they encountered these guys,
it turned into, like, you know, this crazy shootout.
And allegedly they had done this with pressure cooker.
I mean, the whole thing.
Oh, yeah.
I saw it.
I was in a Vietnamese restaurant when it happened, and there were some military people.
I said, look, that's a smoke bomb.
It's just a pressure, not a pressure cooker,
but one of these concussion bombs that they use in training.
Yeah.
It doesn't hurt anyone.
And they were like, yeah, it is.
And then I said, well, they're talking about,
they're pulling something else is going on, something else is going on.
The 9-11 is an interesting one because even the Boston bombing and all these things,
they usually have Muppets go and do the job because anyone that's in the intelligence agency
or they hire, they're going to say, oh, man, this is going to be on TV,
and it's going to be used, so I don't want to do it, send whatever.
So they usually end up having a bunch of Muppets,
like the worst people in their groups, like they did 9-11,
what you saw on TV, even the airplanes and all that, the Boston bombing,
even the Kennedy thing, the way they botched that evidence and all that.
They didn't send, I think, their best guys to run that operation,
but the best guys were on standby, you know what I mean?
Of course.
Yeah.
Well, that's the unique thing about that.
A lot of people think that they send in the elite team first.
No, they send in a functional team, and the elite team is the one that backs up the functional team.
They're just good enough to 90% get the job done.
It won't look pretty, but it's enough for the public to buy it.
Right, and it's messy enough that it doesn't look like a well-oiled machine,
and it's purposely that way,
but you've got guys who can actually get things done really efficiently behind them
so that in case anything goes that hand wrong, that's who cleans it up.
I brought up 9-11 because that was a real screw-up, and it's hard to discuss this unless you know.
They blew the North Tower out first.
They said, well, there's no plane or missiles or anything,
but they blew the side of the building out first.
That was a big screw-up because then you can't, if they were to pull that building,
well, if it was supposedly due to fire, it's a function of time,
so the one that burned longer should come down first, right?
Yeah.
So they should have blown the South Tower first, right,
because that's the one that came down first, the one that got hit with the plane second.
They could not bring down the North Tower first because it got hit first
because then it could damage the delivery tunnel for the nuke in the second building
because these are, you know, and also they're a drive-by-wire that's not radio-controlled.
It's a 2959 zero time.
The device, I said nuke, it's called a zero box,
and the time for civil, these devices that are made for civilian use and demolitions,
it's a zero time, it's 2959, 29 minutes, 59 seconds, zero time, which is exactly 30,
and the area where they go off and they detonate is called ground zero,
so the zeros in the name, so they really, really mucked that one up really bad,
but guess what?
They still pulled it off big time.
You'll never hear what I just said.
Dmitry Kaluzov will say it.
One thing Dmitry has never really brought up that I've mentioned to him more than one occasion is the smell.
Is he still doing stuff?
Yeah, he is, but in Russian.
He's, I think, riding the Ukraine-Russian wave and commenting on that,
but I think the 9-11 thing, it's very limited.
It's a limited thing, and I don't think he could expand on more than that.
You can.
You can actually do a lot more with the 9-11, but it doesn't matter at this point.
You know what I say?
The main purpose of 9-11, yeah, they absconded with gold.
Yes, they did.
They wanted to bring in the Homeland Security, which was drafted in 1992 by Hugo Ballestieri, right, in Italy,
and then after he drafted that, they arrested him.
Right.
Anyway.
You're talking about the basics for the Patriot Act is what you're talking about, right?
Right, yeah.
It was done by the Italian, the guys like the, what was the Italian underground there?
They were blowing up buildings all the time in Italy.
There was a group in Italy.
Oh, yeah.
You're talking about, it was a stay-behind thing for the UN.
What is the name of that organization?
Yeah, it was an organization.
Yeah.
Yeah, that group.
So, anyway, so they brought all this stuff.
That's not why they did it.
What they did was to give you a very clear message, you, the American people and the world,
that the U.S. military will do absolutely nothing to protect the territory known as the United States of America.
That's it.
That's the main message, right, internally.
You know, in other words, do you get it?
It's like a joke might be about a certain guy who walks into a bar and says,
has nothing to do with being in a bar.
The punchline is usually a punchline on its own, right?
You know, a monkey walks into a bar and says, I want whatever.
It has nothing to do about being in a bar.
The bar is just the setup.
The setup was what they showed people.
But the main point, the underlying point is that the U.S. military is not here to protect the U.S., let's say, of America at all.
And I made this point earlier on.
I said, if the people had any modicum of reason after 9-11,
they'd say, okay, what we have to do is completely disband the military,
and if we have allies, and since we have allies, quote-unquote, narrow quotes,
bring them in as an interim military temporarily, right, to protect the country,
because obviously the one we have can't do shit, right, and then redo the military.
Was that done?
No.
It went the opposite way.
It, you know, venerated the military.
It was like, oh, my gosh, these people are going the wrong way.
Oh, wait a second.
You know, that's what you figure out when you've been on this planet for 16 minutes, not 15 minutes, right?
You need an extra minute for that?
An extra minute to figure that one out.
Oh, my gosh.
It's so ridiculous at this point.
Wait, didn't I, you've heard me discuss time ended in 1998, right, so we're in the credits, right?
Yeah.
Credits don't have to make sense.
No, not at all.
They just have to note what.
In alphabetical order.
Right.
And Gladio is the name you were thinking of before.
Gladio, yes.
It's the Gladio group.
Yeah, which is part of another big group that comes out of Belgium and Sweden and Switzerland, and they're all.
It's like the Masons.
Yeah, but Gladio was directly tied to Bologna, Italy, the train station and all that.
That's why you brought it up.
In 1980.
Gladio is the group, yeah, that was the notorious Italian group.
Gladio, yeah.
But that was the thing going on since post-World War II.
Yeah, and they were supposedly rebelling because it was illegal to have secret societies, and even though they're all part, you know.
Right, and they were allegedly the communist terrorists, right?
Yeah.
So, yeah.
Oh, my gosh.
But that was.
Such a mess.
B.S., but yeah.
Such a big mess, a very big mess.
So the whole point of Greek speak essentially is when you come across something, whatever that something might be, ask yourself, when did this something come into being?
Is there anything about it?
Is there anything more about it that I can learn?
And you'll have all the people, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Hold on, stop your yap.
Can I find what you just told me in the reference books about what's been written and held in Time Memorial?
Will I find what you just said in there and where?
Right?
Then you can listen to their blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, right?
You see what I mean?
No, I always.
Yeah, whenever somebody starts talking about these things, even when they talk about Gladio, right?
Gladio has turned into now people have applied it to other things and stuff like that.
And they say, oh, it's actually Gladio II, Gladio III, Gladio.
I'm like, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You know, you're putting numbers on this.
What are we talking about here?
Give me a reference, a point at which.
Or let's go back to the religions, right?
Yeah.
You know, I talked to a very religious Orthodox Jewish guy.
He goes to the temple every morning.
And I try to have a talk about prophecy.
And he says, oh, yeah, well, Elijah is going to come down from heaven with the temple.
You know, and I said the stone temple made of stone.
And heaven is going to descend.
Yeah, yeah.
And then I was like, where do you get that?
Where do you get that from?
Where does it say?
In your book.
Where do you get that?
Because literally you're talking about a guy showing up with a giant building, right?
I'm like, okay, okay, that's fine.
I mean, look, it's possible, right?
Anything's possible.
But where do you get that?
Right.
Well, where is this idea that is fairly elaborate?
Yeah.
He says, yeah, I'll show you on Yahoo.
And I say, I'm like, not really.
There's some reference to some things coming down, but not like that.
Oh, my gosh.
Or the virus thing, you know.
There's a guy that did a hit piece on Ken Wheeler with magnetism.
I researched Ken Wheeler, see what he was up to recently.
Some academic did a hit piece, and he had magnetism.
He says, well, here's some magnetism, and he showed multiple poles.
This is a nano thing, and it's very expensive to get this picture.
I'm like, oh, it's just as expensive as the cartoons of viruses, I guess, right?
I mean, these people are so ridiculous.
Well, you do have to pay an artist to render something, don't you?
Yeah, yeah.
Creative bullshit.
So the whole thing is it's very, very, very simple.
It doesn't mean you have to be, what do you call it, when you really get into a subject, not a researcher.
A fictionato.
You know, when you really get into something.
Anyways, a couple of terms for it, I guess.
Well, you have expertise.
You're someone who is a...
Yeah, you delve into it in a more than normal, right?
I could make a lascivious comment about that, too, but I won't.
So the idea here is that people will criticize that because, remember, you live in a society,
whoever you is, that hates intelligent people.
And proof of that is Hollywood and your government are the same thing.
How are, quote-unquote, people that are well-studied portrayed in Hollywood?
Nerds, bookworms, the guy you kick in the groin, right?
The jock is the good guy, right?
Unless you want to make a comedy, and then you make revenge of the nerds, right?
Yeah.
So you're always being shown, portrayed as being negative, but they tell you to get a college degree.
I recently, even an academic, I usually set them up because their whole life is about being set up, right?
So I set them up.
I said, you know, the education system is faltering.
They're like, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So as a matter of fact, it's more than faltering.
I think it's a disaster.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And it's such a bad disaster that I think it actually does irreparable damage beyond the eighth grade.
Yes, it does.
So I said, all right, so you're a doctorate, and you're going to be teaching at the university.
So when you showed up at university, they put some kind of pixie dust on you to remedy that damage that you get after the eighth grade?
How dare you talk to an academic that way?
So it's like, oh, my gosh.
So you know what you're doing at the university, right?
It's psychological terrorism on the public, right?
Well, you can't tell a tenured person that, right?
That's a protection when you can't be fired now because you've been tenured.
I never understood that.
If you actually read a degree diploma, have you ever read it?
It's all presumptive.
It says the trustees of the university believe that this person has enough credits to earn this degree.
It's like, what?
It's all presumption.
There's nothing there, dude.
Credit.
Oh, my gosh.
You're granted a title.
Well, it's even they believe the trustees of the university believe.
In the word, it changes somewhat.
But it's all presumptive.
Oh, the other thing is how many PhDs, professors, doctors, or whatever, when the Soviet Union came down, came to the U.S.,
could not use their PhD and they worked at the baggage checkout at Safeway or something.
A lot.
I ran into some of them, by the way.
This Polish guy says he was a doctor back there in Poland.
I don't believe him because he's the baggage checkout at the supermarket.
I said, yeah, he is because when the government goes down, your degree goes down means nothing because it's attached to the state.
Oh, yeah.
I had a couple of guys from Pakistan that were working with me, right, in the 90s.
Just before 9-11, they had gotten out and all that.
Yeah, I gave them jobs as guest attendants.
Yeah, because people don't understand that your degree is a function of the state.
When the state goes down, so does your degree.
It means nothing.
It's almost like the same thing happened to the military in the Soviet Union.
If you were a ranking officer or whatever and it goes away, you no longer exist.
You mean those benefits and all those things don't exist.
They go with it.
It's amazing.
A lot of people thought that was like Cold War prejudice with the Soviets.
That's why I bring up the Pakistanis because it was interesting.
At the time, I'm talking about, if you remember, there was the military overthrow of the government.
Well, Pakistan is one of those weird places in between.
It's an artificial, like where they all are, but anyway.
Yeah, but the thing is, if you remember, Musharraf there, he had taken over the government.
As soon as that happened, all of these people that had these degrees and whatever,
if they weren't recertified by him because he took over the government, you had nothing.
Right, you got annulled.
It's known that internationally as well.
Automatically, it's just like when a country loses a war, its currency goes to zero.
One of the guys, actually, who was pumping gas for me noticed my daughter was sick.
She was with me at the time.
My then wife comes to pick me up at work.
There you go.
I'm like, well, yeah, baby's a little sick.
I don't know.
I haven't looked at her yet.
He's like, well, can I?
I said, well, wait.
I know you were a doctor, but he's like, yeah, I was a pediatrician, actually.
Okay, go ahead and take a look at her.
He probably could, probably better than the ones over here.
Actually, yeah, exactly.
He was better than the person I had already taken her to, and she was still sick.
He goes, look, all you got to do is this and this, and it'll clear up.
Two days.
I said, okay, and I followed his directions.
Yeah, my daughter was fine.
But I bet he didn't know about the biological vacuum, though.
I don't know.
I didn't get that far.
I know.
I'm just being facetious.
Of course, he didn't know.
Well, no, but the other doctors are telling me about, well, she needs antibiotics.
She's got ear infection, all this other crap.
I'm like, yeah, they're not doctors.
They suck.
They see redness in the ear because they look in with the little light.
I don't know if you've ever seen a baby when they go to a doctor because they can't talk.
So the doctor's got to actually, you know, look at things.
They're idiots, though, the medical people here.
I mean, you really have to know what you're doing on your own.
And the reason you go to them is because it's something that you can't do.
But if you ask them for, like, if you know nothing about what's going on, you're at their mercy.
And it's, yeah, you might be good at that.
If you're good at Vegas, like rolling dice and stuff, it might work well for you.
Yeah, but see, in 1999, okay, my daughter couldn't speak yet.
And I'm just like, okay, I don't know what to do with her because clearly she's ill.
You know, so I take her to a doctor, and the doctor's, like, giving me stuff to give to her.
And I'm like, ah, crap.
And then meanwhile, the guy who was pumping gas for me gave me exactly what to do, and he took care of it.
Yeah, there's a lot of remedies.
But here, you don't mind going a little bit more.
Was she breastfed?
No, she wasn't.
Okay, all right, that makes sense.
Was it the left ear or the right ear?
It would be both most of the time.
But mostly, it would be the right ear, mostly.
Oh, really?
Okay.
So it was a blockage from the energy going up into the body.
Yeah, interesting.
By the way, one day I'll get into it more.
The left side of the body, the energy goes down.
The right side of the body, the energy goes up, both men and women.
The only difference is the way it spirals.
On the man, viewed from the top down, the energy spirals clockwise.
And on the woman, it would be counterclockwise, viewing from the crown of the head.
If you're standing on a balcony looking down at someone, that way.
It's the only energetic difference.
And there's more energetic difference below the waist, the way it goes down once it leaves the body.
But generally, the left side of the body in any manifestation is energies moving downward.
The right side of the body is energies moving upward, either deficiencies or too much.
And they're either deficiencies, the manifestations, you know, the sicknesses or whatever.
When I say manifestations, isn't that part of the body?
Or the body's creating a block because there's too much.
Let's say you have too much energy going up that it could harm the body if it discharges it.
It will put a block there.
So it's stopping.
That block could be a sore.
It could be internal.
It could be a tumor.
It could be external.
Right?
Or it could be a deficiency, so you have to know how to read both.
The interesting thing about this is you learn about this by watching everything around you.
You know how the trees and the things were plants and stuff were made before man, right?
Right.
And then the animals and all this, right?
Well, according to every story, that's the way it was, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
So that actually can be taken as an archetype.
In other words, the same – it's kind of like – in other words, the same, not blueprint, but the archetypes.
The way things move, grow, die, maintain strength or weakness can be seen in the plant and animal world.
Those same energies are in the human body, right?
Give an example real quick.
You have a tree that comes out of the ground, a plant that comes out of the ground, right?
Certain times of year, not counting perennials and evergreens and things like that.
Those have a different energy.
They come out of the ground at a certain time of year, and they pump all this material.
They form all this material up into the sky, right?
And they rely on energy from the sky also.
So let's take a fruit tree real quick, and this will tie it all together about energies going up and down in blockages.
So that's energy coming out of the earth manifesting into a physical form known as a fruit, an apple tree, let's say, right?
But what's interesting, the food that we use from the tree, the apple, it's all manifestation.
It manifests physically from all these manifestations driving from the earth, you know, up, upward energy.
But what's interesting, when the fruit grows, right after the blossom forms, it's going on its way where?
Down, right?
You notice as the blossom falls off and the fruit forms, it's going down.
It forms downward.
As the apple gets larger, it keeps forming in the downward direction, right?
As a matter of fact, too many apples on the tree, the tree kind of sags down, right?
Right.
And then eventually when the fruit ripens, what happens?
Where does the apple go?
Does it go up or down?
It's Newton on the head, doesn't it?
It goes down, yeah.
Right.
Well, you know, an interesting, look, a little punch line on that story with my daughter and the Pakistani guy is this.
You know, come to think of it, that's the first guy I remember saying, basically, eat seasonally,
because that's part of what he told me to do, which was to feed her something that was seasonally available.
Oh, that's a big deal.
But that's common.
That's a common big deal, just like keeping lawful time was a common big deal.
Yeah, but no American doctor would ever bother to say that.
Well, that's because the Americans don't bother.
Right.
The doctors, remember, are accommodating the people, right?
Give me an example.
If you've got a witch doctor, let's use a cartoon, Bugs Bunny cartoon,
witch doctor with the bone in their nose and their faces painted with a spear and monkey skulls hanging from his waist,
and you brought him, you know, the American goes to the doctor.
The doctor will see you now, and the American goes in there, or the Canadian or a Westerner or whatever,
and he sees a doctor like that, they're going to freak out and run.
They're not going to listen to anything he has to say.
Right.
Because the way he looks does not accommodate the American mindset.
It accommodates wherever.
Another culture, you see, I'm using that as an extreme example, right?
Right, right.
So what they do is no matter what these, quote-unquote, medical technicians,
they're calling them doctors way over-gratiating them.
Okay, let's just say doctors.
They're simply accommodating.
The people are totally happy.
The guy doesn't know anything.
He's just, I'm going to give you what they call script, right?
Here you go, a script prescription.
And the people are so, oh, we're so glad we saw the doctor who gave us this prescription.
They're so happy.
Everybody's happy.
The doctor's happy for not having to do anything.
He's lazy, but they make him work a lot anyway if you're in a hospital.
And the people are lazy, but everybody's happy, right?
But they're happily in misery.
Their quality of life goes down and down and down,
and they blame it on something else, something else, right?
Right.
But it was just interesting to me that that was one of the solutions
that was presented to me from a guy who just had some knowledge,
took a look at the situation, and said, well, here's what's going wrong.
And that's what he told me to do.
Yeah.
There was something else, too, to it, but it was about, you know,
like allowing a certain amount of air or whatever.
I mean, you know, stuff like this.
But it was all this really, again, stuff that I would have never heard from, you know,
an Americanized medical person.
Because, yeah, it's, you know, the U.S.
Here's the thing about the American Revolution,
which is the revolution that really wasn't, but it was.
It's kind of like saying the Iraq War was not really a war, but it was, right?
Or this Ukraine War with Russia is not really a war, but it is, you see?
So you've got to look at it that way.
It was to set up things a certain way,
so because the people who were involved behind that idea,
they had long-term visions, you know?
Academics like to say that a lot, by the way.
They have their catchphrases.
Oh, this program has a long-term vision.
By the way, if you know any academic idiots,
they use that word a lot, vision and all that.
So, yeah.
So, yeah, this is a big, big, big stage play,
and the thing is, fortunately, here's the fortunate part,
that your life is too short to enjoy enough misery to see it clearly.
Enjoy it, because it's designed and made to be miserable.
I actually put in the chat,
if you know you're here because you stepped in some cosmic shit
or stepped in shit, that's why you're here,
well, Greek-speak has a lot to offer to you, right?
There you go.
Basically, cosmically, if you're here on Earth,
you stepped in shit, cosmically, like big deal.
It's a big deal.
Later on, if you get out there, wherever there is,
and you say you were born and lived and died on Earth,
they're going to be like, oh, my gosh.
Half the people in the bar or wherever you are
are going to laugh their ass off,
and amongst the group say,
what the hell did you do to screw up so bad?
They sent you there, or you went there,
and the other half of the group will be like, tell us about it.
That place is notorious in a very subtle way, right?
It's like death by a thousand cuts.
It's not like a deliberate hell planet
where you're standing in molten rock and not dying,
molten lava and torture.
But it is, actually, in small ways.
So the whole thing is also brought up while there's no free will.
And I say that just to get a very well-grounded point
on how they tell you you have rights and you're in a free country
and all this.
None of that is true.
None of that is even actual,
because it's all programming.
The worst slave is the one that's told that he's not a slave, right?
But there is free will when you learn to dance between the raindrops.
There is free will when you see that it's all about programming.
And once you know it's all about programming,
well, then what do you look for?
The part where you can exercise whatever free will you have.
You see?