146 the sonic event rated Y and Greek. How are you tonight?
I'm doing well. I was thinking about what we did on the last podcast. And what do you mean we don't burn calories?
I want to start off with that. Well, and I want you to go over. This is important. This is very important because I've been watching this for decades.
Now has to do with communication. So I want you to go ahead because you got you started saying what your stance or what you take your take on it is.
And I stepped on. I said, no, no, no, don't. And I have to correct. I have to expand on that because I think it's going to help other people.
So I want you to start from the beginning. So what do you think about calories, Chuck?
Yeah, well, the thing is, I tried to explain to somebody, listen, they tell you, you burn these things. Right.
So you know what the meaning of word of the word burn is. Now, where in your body are you burning something?
You know, you got fire on your body. You got a problem. So you're not burning anything. That's a you know, that's a ridiculous term.
So think about it. And that's what calories are based on is when you burn something. Right.
It gets reduced down to this thing that they count up and then they say, oh, because this is what remains.
This is the count for burning. And where are you burning things in your body? You're not.
So let me interject. OK. Is that pretty much what you bring forward?
OK, that's pretty much what everybody knows. Everybody knows we're not burning.
Everybody knows we're biological beings. They're they're they're scientists and they're professionals.
And they know a lot more than we do. They've been researching it for a long time.
But that's so maybe we could overlook the burning part.
But it makes no sense, though, because if I told you, listen, if you're flying, you're flying.
Look, you you can't hold on.
It doesn't make any sense to you because you're not a scientist.
They know they know. Do you see where I'm going with this?
OK, sure. You're going to be OK. I want to just bring this up to people.
I'm using I'm not using Chuck as a punching bag. I will later.
I just want to show what's going on. I've been watching this for a long time, especially people that listen to stuff that I've brought forward.
The same thing happens with the anti-vax people. They always get defeated.
But when I go there, they pack up and leave. Right.
Why? What's the difference? I'll show you the difference.
So so with the calorie thing, what you just said, everybody knows we're not burning.
Right. Because we you know, there's spontaneous combustion is an exception.
You always bring up the facts. And so we're not burning.
But, you know, they know they know they know that calories do apply, even though we kind of jokingly say it's burning.
So calories are valid. So. So you know what? Fuck off. Right.
And that's what ends up happening. I hear people doing this all the time.
I've been on in person and on Skype calls, people trying to explain something.
And the person's like, no, that stuff you got from the Greek doesn't make any sense.
Does it work? Sorry. And I watch this all the time.
OK, so this is what's going on. This is an example.
This is not only the calories, people. So. The fact stick to the fact they will agree.
OK, how are calories? Calories are measured by it's a unit of measurement where something is measured to how much if when it's completely burned,
how much it raises the temperature of water, you know, one gram of water, one degree Celsius or cubic centimeter water.
One degree. That's a fact. OK, so, yes. No, everybody knows we're not burning.
That's right. So this is where you get them. This is how you get them.
So if you've ever seen a caloric experiment or data retrieved, it's a glass tube.
They put whatever they want to test the calorie for and they put oxygen in there.
You don't have to say all this. The punch line is coming.
And there's something that looks like a spark plug and they purge it with oxygen and they hit the spark and it goes, boom, and everything in there turns to carbon.
And that vessel is underwater, which then in turn heats the water and they measure how much water is in there and the temperature.
And that's how many calories they have. So the issue is not whether you're burning anything they're burning.
The very intelligent scientists are burning it. The issue is, are you pooping carbon?
Because your poop can be put into that. Let's say a banana has 60 calories and you poop that banana.
Can you put that in, burn it and continue? Of course.
So unless you're pooping carbon, calories are not relevant because nobody's poop is carbon.
Now, there might be. Look, I haven't met everyone. I don't want to meet everyone, but maybe there is someone who poops charcoal briquettes.
Maybe, maybe. And then calories might apply to them. But we know that no one poops the charcoal.
So the outcome of the experiment, the resultant data is formed on the fact of the resultant being carbonized product.
And when we pass food that we've eaten based on what they say is caloric intake, we don't not pass that product.
We don't pass carbon. OK, you see. So it has to do with biocompatibility. Right.
So that's why you're the one with the vaccine. Maybe I'm wrong, but it seems to me like that's a long way around.
No, no, you're not. Well, I did. This is the way I would do it.
Yeah. Calories count. Unless you're pooping carbon.
Look, my cell phone might die in five seconds, right? Right.
Unless you're pooping carbon, calories have nothing to do with any human consumption of food, any rating of food at all.
Now, when I'm speaking to a multiple group of people and depending on their exposure to this scientific experiment or procedure,
half of them will say, holy, I don't have to explain it because they're like, oh, yeah.
But the other half don't know what how calories are obtained. So I'd say, yeah, you know, they burn it until it turns to carbon.
So your poop can still burn. Right. So there's no. Oh, then the rest get it.
Because most people don't know how a carb, a calorie test, a calorimeter works.
They don't know. But some people do. So all you got to say is calories don't apply because we don't poop charcoal.
And depending on the level of exposure or how well read they are, I'm not going to say educated.
But, yeah, you might I may be speaking to, let's say, 20 people and they all get it.
So all I have to say is they don't poop carbon and they don't get it because, you know.
Oh, are you familiar with or I might say another way to do it in less than 10 seconds is we don't poop carbon.
Are you familiar with the calorimeter test? They're like, oh, yeah. So, you know, I'm talking about.
Oh, yeah. We don't. Yeah, I get it. But if you familiar with a calorimeter.
No. You know, they burn it till it turns to carbon. Oh, now I see.
So you don't have to get into explaining over and over and over and over and over.
Now, here's the thing. I've been around some anti-vax people. Right.
Because I won't hang around with anyone that's vax. I mean, whatever. I mean, they just don't.
It just doesn't work out. Right. And they always when the VAX tables are out during the flu season every year.
I'm not just talking about the pandemic. They go in to give these people a hard time.
And they all the people that are ready to give the nurses, whatever the administrators, they laugh at them.
Here's an anti-vaxxer. I said, I knew this because look at the argument. They're not thinking.
They're not thinking. They're just OK with calories of actually what you're doing is you heard something that rang true,
but you can't communicate it in a way will be effective. Right. Right.
It's kind of like the thing with the broken glass. You know, they had a psychology experiment.
Five people watch a car accident, a red car and a white car. They separated them.
They watched it all together and then they asked questions. And and they asked each one, you know, a series of questions.
One of the questions was, what did you see? Broken glass. And everyone said yes.
But then they went back and played the film and there was no broken glass.
No, none of the windows are broken. Right. So why do people say that?
Because they're a car accident. Of course, they expect to see what there isn't.
They expect to see it. Now, this is a lot of things that I say are the antithesis.
They don't expect to hear what. OK, let's go back to the anti-vaxxers.
Remember the the broken glass and the calorie burning thing?
The anti-vaxxers, they get laughed at. I've seen them. I've seen them.
They get laughed at. And the people around them get laughed. Laugh at them, too.
Now, I go up to them and I say, are you taking you're giving out vaccine for what?
OK, and I give them the whatever given the scientific name because the flu is a certain type of thing.
Right. It's an influenza streptococci or this or that or whatever. Right.
So it's whatever, whatever. Yeah. Which one is it? Which strain are you going for?
And they're like, OK, all right. It's like when I used to go and question rabbis.
I know Hebrew. You know, they're not going to talk to you if you don't at least have past the bar mitzvah.
Right. Yeah. So you have to do you have to be able to. All right.
So I say, OK, so you're doing this strain for this vaccine or whatever. Right. Right.
But yeah, I said, are you taking into account the dosage taking each dosage
or the dosage is taking account for the person's body weight, blood type, age, sex and race?
Because usually there might be someone there that knows the vaccine studies.
And that's if you look at the NIH studies, which, by the way, none of them are online anymore.
When they did the tests and controls, those are all the things that they looked at to structure the injection.
Right. Now, if there's an old head there. Yeah. If there's an old head there.
Actually, those experiments are pretty good. I got more to tell you about how they structure those things.
But that's another sonic entirely. Remember, I've been looking at this since the 1980s and it hasn't changed.
It's just that it's not available. But soon as they hear me say that, they pack up and leave.
They pack up. They pack. You know, they have these folding tables, picnic tables.
Right. They pack everything up and go away. Or like if you're inside a Walgreens or so, they all go back to the they leave.
They leave everything and they go all the way back into the employer and sit there until I leave.
I've watched this. And when they go every time, not sometimes, every time.
But every time I'm with an anti-vaxxer that's giving off the Alex Jones or what they heard, they're getting laughed at.
Why is that? Why is that? There's a big difference. It has to do with communicating a certain amount of facts.
And don't get into something that you don't know. Right. Because eventually someone will know that you don't know and you get laughed at.
Right. Of course. Now, I know you knew the part about not pooping carbon, but you didn't bring it up. Right.
So there's a certain amount of mental laziness there. So what I'm saying is like one of the things in martial arts is laziness is not in your vocabulary.
At three o'clock in the morning, you can get up and perform. Right.
Because that's that's the discipline. Right. Discipline doesn't mean unpleasant.
Well, I'm so lazy. I'm stressing what I think is the most simple and striking part.
But it won't. That's all. What you're doing is stressing that. Yeah.
Well, it doesn't work. Well, it doesn't work. But it has been effective to get people to go.
Wait a minute. You know, I'm they're thinking to themselves, where is the burning in the process?
And you even mention it where it's like unless you're burning, you know, see burning.
But the result is the result. You must have the result that's done.
In other words, the conclusion, because you know how we had Dimitri on it is ground zero has been used for many things like they talked about recently.
I saw. Oh, the wood. They're not going to do another Woodstock anniversary, even though it was the ground zero for the hero hippie movement.
Right. They're using it for other things. Yeah. I'm saying you can get away with it, but it's not rock solid.
And I hear this very often. I've had many people through the years have discussed.
Yeah. My girlfriend's a Ph.D. and whatever. And I brought up some stuff and she laughed at it.
And I'm like, well, how did you what did you say? And I started laughing as I'm laughing at you.
Don't don't try it. How many times have we had a sonic? And I say, don't do what I would do.
You're going to fall on it. Now, it doesn't mean you can't. It is a discipline there.
And the discipline is there. You have to hear it and visualize it and then be able to communicate it.
So I just want to bring that up because you mentioned the burning last night.
That doesn't get any because like the word grounds here, everyone's using it. Right.
You have to stress that it's a technique only. Right. So the definition of a calorie is carbon.
Let's let's go back to the cat for a second. You have a calorimeter and we put a banana.
That's a calorie. OK, so we purge it with oxygen. Everything gets sealed and it goes.
It burns and it goes boom. Now we open the calorimeter, but there's still banana in there.
It didn't turn to carbon. Guess what? That cannot be counted. Right. Right.
You see, cannot be counted back to the vaccines. The same thing.
The other thing with the vaccines is there is no regardless of how harmful it is.
There is no such thing as a one size fits all. Even when you look at something like pain pills for children,
they say half a tablet. Right. Depending on body or or if you have a 350 pound, you know, Greek guy,
he's going to need four ibuprofen. Right. Maybe so. Yeah. Right.
So it goes by weight. Everything goes by weight. Right. Children get very small doses.
Right. If you're distributing a chemical and the idea is to distribute a chemical throughout the body, then, yeah,
you have to take into account what the size of the body, the amount of stuff that you got to do because it's based on dilution.
Now, the other thing is there are other things that are based on dilution before they're taken in the body.
It's the opposite. The less of it you have.
A 90 pound, a 90 pound woman, you know, who is perfectly healthy, has a headache.
I'm 230 pounds. I have a headache. You know what, though?
We're going to distribute this chemical throughout the body. We're going to need two different levels here.
It's just that simple. I mean, because I'm I'm more than double her.
You know, it wouldn't wouldn't that make sense or no. Right.
Because you got to do that. You know, the chemical never gets into never passes the intestine.
Well, when you take more of it, because the induction that happens in the body is proportionate.
Well, to encourage that induction. Right. That's right. It's proportional.
So, you know, if you have just a drop of this versus, you know, a whole eyedropper full,
it's going to be a different proportion that you're introducing for induction.
That's yes. That's why in homeopathics, you can have an angstrom, which is the smallest smaller than nano.
Right. Angstroms are what the width of supposedly atoms are even smaller than light waves.
You can have angstroms of it of it in a gallon of water and give the small lady and the 230 pound man a glass of water and it will work the same.
OK. Right. That's the beauty of homeopathics, because, you know, homeopathics, there used to be a state.
OK. The situation that we're in is never going to be able to recall what I'm about to say.
Like, you know, you have psychologists where you get to the questions. I'll make this short.
Years ago, before psychology, psychology is a new thing.
Didn't come out till the 20s or teens, let's say of the 20th century.
Before that, you were known as a master of lunacy.
And it was right to see if to judge if someone was competent, mentally competent.
Right. Until they started to codify the schools of thought or so somewhere around the turn of that century.
Yeah. They were called master of lunacy before they had psychologists.
And then you had state certified herbalists.
You had state certified homeopathic. Right. Right. All that.
Where did all that go? You know, they can't say that the people say the government doesn't want.
No, no. The government had a lot of stuff.
There was even legitimately an agency to hunt vampires during the time of Lincoln.
Probably. Yeah. It's not famous, but you can look it up.
Yeah. All these things.
So it was quite interesting when you live in a more of a real, really proportioned society.
We're now we're very disproportioned. You know, it's where everyone's been enslaved.
So let's I'll stop right here. And why don't we get to the questions that you said you messaged?
There's a very lengthy one. Maybe we leave that out or abridged or let's let's get going on the questions.
I'll actually cherry pick off of it and see how that goes, because there's a bunch of explanation in there.
And I don't think it's entirely necessary, but. Oh, OK.
Hold on. Before I went, I got into the spirit and the soul last week. Yes.
And I gave my own. OK. In the Hebrew, by the way, just so as I remember, there's something called the rule of Kodesh,
which is the set apart spirit. But when you get to the Holy Spirit, it's the set apart soul.
When you get to Hellenic, they switch it. But either one would be correct.
But it would not be referring to the same thing. So I just wanted to bring that up.
And there's one day we'll do I think one of the early rated wise who got into the soul and the spirit again.
Yes. And maybe we'll do it again because it's one of the.
But if you don't know that you are made up of a physical living metabolism that is transferable and a spirit,
a mind that is also transferable and a body that relies on the metabolism, because you can have a body without a spirit,
by the way, just needs the metabolism. Someone in a coma. Right.
Right. Can be wandering around the whole universe or the whole city, whether bodies still pumping and beating.
And right. Right. So the body and the soul go together. Metabolism of the spirit.
But all three of them can be separated. I mean, the spirit and the soul, the soul and the body have to stay together.
Otherwise, the body dies. So that's again, I mean, there's so much once.
OK, I'm bringing this up again, because once you understand that firmly now, you know what what you're working with and how to work with it.
Right. You know, you can work with it and go on to other things that we have. OK, the questions.
OK, so since we ended off on that part, I'll go to the questions from Eddie, which are two short ones.
Questions are the wicked in Proverbs 16 for referring to NPCs.
Probably not. I have to go look at it because the word there's several words for wicked.
As a matter of fact, sometimes the word unclean to me is is is translated as wicked.
I don't know what the word is. I'd have to go look it up and see which, you know, the translation is, I'd say, a 40 percent.
Right. Correct. At best. So I don't know which word they're using in the words would mean different.
So an NPC is I don't know. No, I wouldn't know how to answer that anyway, because the NPC, I think, would be generally innocent because they're a tool.
An NPC is a tool that's been it's a throwaway. It's a throwaway.
Like, you know, those paper plates and it's not acting under its own its own will, so to speak, its own.
Yeah. Right. So therefore, it's really not. It's a throwaway.
So whether they're working, let's say, for the dark side or the light side, it doesn't matter.
There are throwaways. And remember, the dark side follows what the light side has outlined.
Yeah. Right. Remember in Job, you know, Satan is walking around. Hey, what are you doing? Walking around.
I want you to go and bother this guy. So the NPC is inconsequential.
It sucks when you find out, you know, your your family is our NPCs or your best friends are NPCs when you wake up to that fact.
Right. It sucks. But it's true. This is the way. Right. But I want to throw in something.
Right. I was just going to say it's as responsible, though, as like, you know, say a cave collapses and crushes, you know, 100 people and kills them.
The cave is not evil. It's just simply, you know, doing a fun.
Well, evil has affected. Yeah. Evil has happened to them. But the cave is not.
The cave is not right. That's what I'm saying. It's an evil.
It's like when I do weather work in a trailer park, it's washed out.
You know, I just tell myself, oh, they shouldn't have been there. They should have picked another spot.
Well, you weren't seeking. It wasn't your volition that you weren't under the idea.
Look, I'm going to destroy these people's place to live. I'm not going to destroy them.
You didn't intentionally do that, but you did take an action and something bad happened to them.
Not that time. Those are the things that I intentionally did. I got really close.
Maybe. But I'm just saying in that instance that you brought up, you're not evil in that case.
You just did something that. Yeah, you did evil.
Evil is a is a is connected to an adverb.
But that's like an adjective. An NPC is even less responsible because they've got no will involved there. It's not them.
Yeah. Like like here's the another tangent to the NPC thing.
I don't know if you guys remember there was an article.
Well, you know, the if you want to know what the federal government's doing, they have a monthly register.
Now it's quarterly because no one reads it. Right. Not Fox News, not the news.
You want to know what the federal government's up to. They put it in the register, federal register.
Look it up. The U.N. has a register also. And again, I think they used to be bimonthly.
Now it's like quarterly because no one reads it. I don't know if you guys remember.
I think it's about two decades ago. They listed the they did went through all the countries and classified them.
And the United States of America was classified as nomadic because most of the people are classified as residents.
So I saw that they called it oligarchy as opposed to, you know, when they were trying to classify us as, you know, either a democracy.
Yeah. But the oligarchy also applies to them. But what I mean is that no one lives here.
No one lives in the U.S. I mean, no one lives in this kind of most countries because they go on the street and ask, are you a resident?
They'll say, yeah, yeah. So where do you live? Because you only be a resident when you're either traveling or on vacation.
Right. Or for business. Where do you live? Oh, well, I live here, too.
So. Oh, so now you're not only a vagabond, you're also insane.
Because how could you be a resident and be an inhabitant at the same place? Why would you say so?
They're also insane. That's why, again, I don't know if you guys remember the psychiatry society a few years ago, again, with some outrage.
Maybe around the time of Obama, they put out an article saying 70 percent of the Americans have mental health problems or 78 percent.
Remember something? Do you remember that a decade ago? Yeah, absolutely.
Yeah. Well, that's OK. So that's when you say NPCs. I mean, it's a serious, you know, you know, where are they? Who are they?
You know, I mean, yeah, they're everywhere. You're just like when I say there's a lot of evil people in the world.
Everyone shakes their head. Yes. But it's never them or never their family.
You ever notice that? So then where are they? Of course, even, you know, like the hypocrite, the most evil thing you ever see, their hero in their own story, you know?
Yeah. So, you know. So anyway, that's the side note on the NPCs.
It's not just this. And there's no strict definition because it's I just gave you the examples with the U.N. and the SEC.
They're basically telling you you're all crazy and you're all vagabonds.
And yeah, OK, but there's some outrage. But OK, next question. Sure. This one's about food, actually.
Let's see. And let's see a question about an older said around 100 or so.
I mastered the carrot and the onion sticks with sesame oil and sesame seeds with organic brown rice and up the intake of cauliflower for the whole family.
All that. OK. My language skills are not good enough to take a picture of my head.
How to cut the broccoli. OK. How to cut the broccoli or the cabbage for the cabbage steak.
Listen to that episode several times. So do you have some advice?
Oh, yeah. Yeah. As large as possible. You want it. You want it just like you would.
What's the difference between like a roast when you do a roll?
Cabbage roast. I'm sorry. Is it the cauliflower cabbage on my mind went to the cabbage.
Sorry. Repeat that broccoli and how to call it broccoli or the cabbage for the cabbage steak.
Large head, a large head, twice the size of your fist would be good.
OK, so you cut the stem off. By the way, you know how the stems are thick on those types of veggies and the skin is very thick and chewy.
Use a peeler and just peel the stems. If the stem is thicker than your smallest finger, peel it.
Use a peeler and peel the skin off. And it's just as tender as tender can be.
So you don't waste product. By the way, when I buy broccoli or cauliflower by the pound, I break off the stem and I leave it for the grocer.
Right. Because it's good. Right. You don't need to buy the stem. You're going to break off anyway. Right.
So just to be clear, her her first language is not English.
And she that's fine, partially because of that. But that's the most simple way you could explain that.
But she got through the to the food instruction. Now, the thing is, the beginning, the master, the the onion and the carrot stick.
If you can get some gobu or burdock root to go with that, then you have what's called a full like Kempira, full balanced, very OK.
She didn't mention burdock, but if she can get her hands on some burdock root, B-U-R-D-O-C-K, which is a thistle plant.
When you add that to that veggie mix, it's like eating steak. It's like eating meat.
It has the same amount of energy. That's very important.
If you can't get the burdock root, get some kind of the next.
You can go laterally and use some kind of a radish, like a parsnip with the carrot also.
But I would say just have more grain. But the burdock root is essential.
And I sent someone an email. They didn't respond. About how burdock root and whole grain we were.
We developed on that. And they might think like, you know, from developing, you know, like the uniformitarian model where we did evolve for millions of years and hundreds of thousands of years.
That's not what I mean when I say we developed. What I mean by developed is, you know, that between 1950 and 1958, the average height of Korean children was more than two inches, grew more than two inches because they introduced dairy, commercial dairy in South Korea.
So just drinking milk, the average height went up one and a half to two inches in eight years of studying this. Right.
Which is very short. So they develop. You see what I mean? Development can be very quick.
There's something about the thistle root or the burdock that's essential if you're going to be veggie to incorporate that.
And if you read the chat back in the day, I brought up burdock root. People were using it.
And they were like, yeah, just like Greek said, it's like eating steak or a good hamburger. You get that kind of energy from it.
You won't get that energy from eating other vegetables that I know of. Yeah.
And that I know of, actually. No, not at all. You can create that energy in like a ratatouille, which is lots of vegetables sauteed and caramelized.
And we'll get into how to do that maybe. But no, the cabbage, the cauliflower and the broccoli, even a big head is fine, depending on people.
When I do that here, I call it broccoli steak. I put the whole head of broccoli and that's all we eat.
I might do like a sour cream blue cheese dressing or I might do a miso garlic.
And you can have that with some fresh baked bread if you do that sort of thing or some beans, lentils.
And it's a complete meal. And it's just as satisfying as cutting into a roast. Right.
And and I think I explained how I did it. So and she says she's mastered it. So that's good.
OK, excellent. So and by the way, just there was a couple of loose comments, which I'll just bundle together here.
There's a few people asking if you could do another food episode soon.
Yeah, I will. And OK, so on the yin and yang. OK, a couple of bits of feedback here.
These aren't questions, but just want to offer them to you because they're very short.
Yin I call discharge and yang is charge. Positive or negative are another way to discuss polarity and duality.
This is Patrick said that another yin and yang is yin as will. Yang is yang is power.
That's correct. Yeah, those are correct. But do they do they help in the descriptor? I'm not sure.
No, no. No, because what happens is I was I woke up this morning and I was barely awake and I had a metaphor running through my head at like 80 miles per hour.
And I'll use that for yin and yang. OK, anything else on the yin and yang?
And I'll show you what I know. No, no, that was just that was just the specifics on those people.
OK, that has feedback. Yeah, that's the most cursory. Even if you get books, the most cursory stuff, the quick things you'll learn about yin and yang is yin is soft, dark, flowing, cold.
And yang is hard, sharp, bright, hard, hot.
OK, when you get to a level where you're working it to diagnose things and not just people diagnose any situation.
Yeah, you what you'll find out is that the yang protects the yin. It's not polarity anymore.
It's it's beyond that. It's not. Even if you listen to that, Uncle Fester guy, what's his name with the tattoos?
The monkey guy called is a monkey. I forgot. Oh, Ken Wheeler, the magnet guy.
OK, yeah. Whatever he doesn't know about magnets, I know. And whatever I don't know about magnets, he knows.
OK, remember that? And that was from War of the Worlds with Tom Cruise.
They asked me a question. Oh, my brother knows that one, right? Yeah, fair enough.
And between me and my brother, we know everything. So if someone asks you a question you don't know, my brother knows that one, right?
So you look flawless, but even he says there's no polarity.
And I agree. That's a that's a very Walter Russell thing. He got stuck on that. It's not bad.
But Ying, let's say let's stick with the body. And then I want to use the metaphor of a can of beans in the human body and in the animal body and in the plant kingdom, let's say, and all that.
And even to the mineral kingdom and metal, the yin is the nourishment and the yang protects that nourishment.
So the let's let's say you have a protein drink as your nourishment, the container, that's yin.
And the container that it's in is the yang part of the whole of the whole system.
But within the nourishment drink itself, without the yang, there's another yin and yang in there, right?
The salt in the drink itself would be the yang and the water would be the yin.
So it keeps going into many directions. So this I want to give a can of beans is in the metaphor.
So I woke up thinking about so we'll use a can of beans. It's pretty typical metaphor.
So you have a can of beans, a can of beans. So let's it's a metal can use a can opener, right?
With a label paper label on it. The can is yang and all the beans inside are yin.
So let's go inside the beans. Now we take the beans out of the can, which are yin.
But when they're coming out of the can, that's a very yang motion, right?
Now they land in another yang container in a yin way because they spread out when they hit the other container.
They land in the bowl, they spread out, but they're kind of like soft, but they have a harder outer shell.
So there you have another level, right? They have a harder outer shell.
Look at the beans and they're preserved with some salt, which is yang.
And there's also water, which is yin. Now the bean itself has a skin on it, which is yang.
It has the starchy element on the inside, which is yin.
That's what I meant.
It also has a sweetness to it, which is yin. And the pithy part is more yang.
And when you get to the center of the bean where there's the kernel, that's yang.
But inside the kernel is a very sweet part, which becomes yin.
So it's always flipping, yin and yang. It's always flipping, right?
So now let's go to the can.
So the can itself, when the beans are dumped out, it becomes yin because it was full before, right?
It was full, now it's empty, so it's yin.
The inside of the can is yin, more than it was with the beans in it.
Now if we look at the can itself, before it was opened it was all very tight, compact, and hard.
Now that the lid popped open, that was a very yin action.
But to cut the lid is a very yang motion.
Remember yang is sharp and pointy.
We need a sharp pointy, right, to cut the can, right?
So now the can itself, the surface area of the can is very yin, it's spread out.
And then it goes to the edges which are yang, pointy.
There's a label on the can which goes all the way around, which is very yin.
But it's very thin paper, which is yang in that dimension.
It's also stuck on with some glue, which is very yin, it goes all the way around.
But that glue is very hard, which makes it yang again.
But it had to be yin to be applied as a liquid, right?
Because you can't apply hot, hard glue.
So you see how the yin and yang is constantly flipping.
As a matter of fact, when you look at the atomic scientists,
they say everything is frequency and oscillation.
You know, like they'll say this is a vibratory,
sympathetic vibratory physics, right, John Kealy.
You just demonstrated the oscillation.
That's right, the oscillation is between yin and yang.
So what happens is the oscillation, whether you look at it one way
and then there's these different ways of seeing, like one of the things,
when you understand phasing and different types of pulsations
and the way things work, like if you walk into a room
and you turn the light switch on and then you turn it off
and you're on and off, on and off, not enough.
But you come in and you go off and on.
It looks, right, so you turning the switch off, on, off, on,
I'm going on, off, on, off, same switch, same motion, but different.
But it's the same. No, it's not.
Because, OK, pulse width modulation, when you get into
certain electronic theories with imaginary numbers,
that takes into account.
So the direction of things are always switching between
yin and yang, yin and yang, yin and yang, and building on each other.
That's the vibratory resonance of atomic things, you know.
So once you understand this, for example,
you can get more into transmutation.
Like, for example, hydrogen would be the most yang element
and then going down to the radioactive ones is the most yin.
So if someone is very yin, you would want them to take hydrogen,
which is what this guy with Eagle Research, I forgot his name,
he's been telling people to breathe that.
That's good, but he's not really breathing hydrogen.
But the idea is there when you bubble from an electrolytic cell.
So, you know, when you see people walking around,
old people with those oxygen tanks, that creates,
they all die of pneumonia, by the way.
If you stay on that oxygen tank, you know, the thing they carry around,
you're going to die, I tell people, you're going to die of pneumonia.
And I have people that I've known who knew someone,
oh, she saw that oxygen and goes, no, I said she died of pneumonia, right?
Yeah, how do you know? I mean, everybody dies of pneumonia.
Yeah, it's either that or they call it COPD, but it ends up...
Yeah, that's the banker's terms.
So you should be doing hydrogen.
But anyway, the body can turn it into whatever it wants.
So the yin and yang again, and I brought up hydrogen because it's the most yang,
and everything down from that starts to become yin.
But as you're moving down the chain, how does it become more yin, right?
You need to apply yang to it, right?
So this yin and yang thing is a constant flipping.
Like we got into a little bit with the food before.
When you take sweets into the body, oils, sugars, things like that,
when the body induces them into the bloodstream,
the energy of those things tends to go to the upper part of the body,
right or left depending on if it's moving up or moving down.
When you take salts, minerals, and animal, that goes to the lower part of the body.
When I say lower, meaning the navel's down, right?
The center is the navel, so it goes down.
So when you hear about people having gout,
you hear people about having, what are all those diseases near reproductive organs
and all that stuff below the navel, all these organs, colon and all that,
that's animal and salt, and bad salts like that,
you know, the toxic salts that they use from industry in your food and all that,
and animal products that have been steroided and antibiotics and all that,
or too much unbalanced animal.
I was just watching someone have a steak dinner, and how unbalanced it is.
They have a steak dinner that the steak is broiled in butter, which is fat,
and for a side dish they have creamed spinach,
which is basically butter and fat and cheese in there,
and they have bread and butter, which is again fat.
There's nothing there to balance the fat.
It's fat and fat and fat and fat.
If you go to an Asian country, for example,
and again, this sounds like I'm modifying an Asian culture or diet.
I'm not.
But if you go to, I mean, I might sound like I am, but disqualify the thought.
If you have a bowl of like a beef broth or beef stew in an Asian country,
you also have daikon, which is a radish.
What does that radish do? It cuts the fat.
You have some type of horseradish, cuts the fat.
Some type of a soy sauce or acid that cuts the fat.
If you go to, for example, to a Greek country,
a Greek country, there's only one Greek country, right?
Okay.
But Middle Eastern, when you have a roast of meat, fatty meat,
what do they serve with it? Lemon.
What does lemon do? Cuts the fat.
It's another acid to cut the fat, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, and other things that cut the fat.
You're going to have greens that are steamed greens with olive oil,
which cuts the fat.
By the way, olive oil cuts fat because of its acidity also,
not more than just the acidity.
So the American diet is completely out of balance
because you're sitting with a meal that's fat balanced with fat,
balanced with fat. It's not balanced.
So when you have fat, you have something that cuts the fat
and then back and forth.
Okay, let's just finish off this way,
how horrifying it is when you understand this.
You're going to get a hamburger with cheese and mayonnaise
and all that other fatty stuff, hamburger, cheeseburger, right?
And you're going to have that with  it's fatty.
And then you're going to have that with French fries.
And you're going to have that with a milkshake.
More fat and even fattier.
There's more fat in the milkshake than there is in the French fries.
Now, people that are addicted to fried foods, you know what I used to do?
You know the old orange presses?
There's a die-cast metal.
You've got a lot of leverage, the ones that have like a foot-long lever.
They use that orange whatever.
I used to put a donut in there or go get some McDonald's fries.
And you press it down. You get a teaspoon of oil.
You smell that.
Absolutely.
Yeah, yeah.
So that kind of stuff I would get people to  addicted to donuts and all that stuff.
So that's what the yin and yang balance is.
So when you see a society like the American society, the way they eat
now the British to some extent are very similar.
That's why you'll never  you might see American restaurants because it's fat.
You'll never see a British restaurant.
Never, ever, ever, ever, ever anywhere.
Even in England they don't  they have pubs that serve their food,
but the most popular food in England is an Indian.
I think the national dish is chicken tiki marsala, right?
Something like that, yeah.
So yeah, I can have an Indian.
I can just mad at one right now.
So anyway, balance is the yin and yang.
And when you have the full-fat meal, like I mentioned,
the steak with the cream spinach and the butter and this and that,
there's still yin and yang within each one,
but it's all going in one direction against you, right?
So you can predict  you can make predictions about outcomes
by understanding the yin and yang.
When there's no  it doesn't mean when there's balance
you won't have a degrading situation because that's how the art of war works, right?
The art of war, like one of the biggest things in the art of war
is when you have the ability to completely surround your enemy with four corners,
you always give one of the corners  you gild it with gold for them to leave.
Yeah.
Right?
You give them a way out.
And not only  you gild it with gold so they enjoy it, leaving.
That's what the Germans did in Dunkirk and the Americans and the British
because Hitler said these are Aryans, let's let them go.
They let 100,000 troops get away, and the Americans don't know that.
Gave them an escape route.
Yeah, yeah.
So that's yin and yang also to be in balance.
So it works in every combination of things,
but it doesn't mean you won't have degradation because that's still
but you'll be in more control.
Fair enough.
All right, so moving on.
This one is, again, a different area.
And let's see, Franklin, thanks for the back catalog.
Okay, a question about the economy.
If we exist in a credit-based economy, i.e. your signature is your money,
but the people don't know this,
why are they changing to the blockchain tracking technology, question mark?
Distraction.
Well, there's a follow-on to this.
Is a higher force involved in making the economy more lawful, question mark?
He somehow thinks that blockchain is more lawful
because Greek had mentioned that this time, quote, they, end quote,
are allowing more, quote, people to live, end quote,
instead of being wiped out like Canaan, question mark.
So I'm wondering if this is the method,
is a way to correct or corral the people as a whole.
Yeah, I don't think it's going to work.
Weren't there others like the BRICS thing?
Yeah.
That was supposed to take over.
There was all these other things.
That was the opposition to the American hegemony
where we're using the dollar, the oil, you know, the petrodollar.
Yeah, that's not, it's because there is no,
Americans don't have a currency, which is not money.
What people should focus on and watch, these are all distractions,
is that the U.S. government and every government in the world
lost their own countries in a card game, literally,
in a card game with the bankers, and they didn't tell the people.
So what they did was they structured the laws
that if anybody needs anything or falls into a debt,
the government will satisfy that debt.
That's what's called full faith and credit.
And you're given a social security number, that's your,
but they never tell you how to access it properly.
Now, you can do it through a 1099-A.
I've seen where there's been a forensic audit
and someone bought a house, and this is through Rod Klassen,
this guy named Raja, who was an accountant,
and his, it was a $400,000 mortgage,
but they got the money through his trust fund
with a 1099-A using the social security number, right?
And they kept doing it.
Every year they pulled $400,000 up because the government won't say no.
You know, there's no government, but, you know, that's the,
they create it out of thin air based on your full faith and credit.
So once your full faith and credit goes down,
it goes towards a blockchain,
that's going to take a pressure off of people
demanding what I just said,
going and using the social security number as a credit card.
By the way, if you, you know how there's a thing about,
oh, the Nazis were so, you know, Nazis were so bad,
they tattooed the numbers on the people's arms?
That was a fashion in the time.
If you go on an internet search, by the way,
social security numbers tattooed on people's arms,
I think one of the sites would be the New York Historical Society.
And it tells you there,
all the tattoo shops were offering that, right?
To put your number so you never lose it on your arm, on your forearm.
Right? So this was a very common and popular thing
because back in those days,
the soup kitchens were not just soup kitchens.
Just like, for example, today they have these gospel rescue
or something, people that are homeless,
you go into town and they take care of you.
It's like a soup kitchen, they give you a cot.
They won't take you unless you have a social security number
and a birth certificate and all that because they're tapping, right?
Same if you spend the night in jail,
they have to get a social security number from you
because they get $700 per person per day from your,
you know, it could be more like $3,700.
Whatever it is, they're going to get it, right?
So everyone is using that except for you.
And the people are finding out that it exists.
There's people buying cars with 1099As and all, it takes 45 days.
But anyway, people that are using it.
So when you start changing people's opinion or,
I mean, not even opinion, opinion actually, yeah,
because they have no knowledge about it.
Opinion means decision or judgment with no knowledge.
And when you change their focus to something,
oh, let's get Bitcoin, all this other stuff,
which is an intelligence agency operation,
100% is going to alleviate some of that trust.
But yeah, that's why these things don't go anywhere.
They're what's called, when it's not mainstream,
what's it called? Help me here.
Fringe or something. Alternative or fringe.
It's always going to be fringe. It's always going to be alternative.
They're going to have a very hard time going 100% digital and everything
for the very fact that there's still too many people
betting and shooting pool.
And there's something called the Mexican drug cartel.
They're not going to use digital currency.
You know, have you ever seen pictures online where pallets
have pallets of $100 bills in these mansions in Mexico?
Pallets, right? A billion dollars.
They have figured out ways to corral the digital currency now, though.
That's starting to happen.
To be seen. To be seen. I doubt it.
I wouldn't say no and have egg on my face, but I don't see it.
I don't see it. Not ever happening.
I think when you get into the point where Breshears of Archaics
talks about the dark satellite where these beings disembark
and liberty is taken from the earth.
They can install a system like that because anyone who doesn't go with it
will be eliminated.
Yeah, but somebody already figured out how to corral a lot of that stuff.
If you have, look, all you got to do is have an authorization number to collect
and you can collect things and it looks like it's nothing.
You know, that's why they started up all these things
like where they were saying, hey, look, you can just take care of little debts
between you and your friends with this or that.
So they created these other little things that are almost like debit cards.
Well, PayPal. PayPal will do that.
Like PayPal.
But more. They got more stuff so that you have a card also.
And it's meant directly to exchange
just between people.
Like, OK, you guys decide to go out to dinner or whatever.
He pays for the whole thing. You can pay him back with this.
So it's more of a loose thing where you're exchanging with your friends.
They would have to be very loose. And you also have no regulation.
And because, you know, the more regulation
the so-called government puts on, the more the black market grows.
The less regulation, the more the black market goes away.
That's the thing they've been fighting over.
You've heard about this where they're fighting over the regulation.
OK, if you make over if this amount goes through an account,
then you're then they're supposed to report it.
That business is supposed to report it and so on and so forth.
Some of them are resisting it.
That's because you're doing blank endorsements.
If everything you do writes lawful money only, 12 U.S.C. 411.
And you could also use it in other countries and argue it
because of what's called reciprocation.
Because it's money.
In other words, if you go to E.U.
and you have, let's say, a Georgia state of Georgia driver's license,
it's usually honored.
But they give you a residency of like 30 days.
They don't make you go get an E.U. driver's license.
They'll say, OK, it's reciprocated.
The passport is reciprocated.
So you can, by the laws of reciprocation,
and also that I found in about 12 countries
they have laws where you're allowed to make a conditional endorsement.
So when you do a conditional endorsement
and it's over $10,000,
it doesn't apply.
I would be confident with a million dollars in cash
going through the airport.
They're going to want to take it.
I'm like, all these serial numbers are recorded
and they're making a demand for lawful money.
Yeah, they'll laugh.
But once their superiors get a hold of that,
I said call the A.G. or Secretary of State.
They're going to say, oh shit, we've got to let them go.
They don't know. The people are savages.
I think I once got into a Skype.
Myself and one guy were going to go down at the border.
Homeland Security seizes stuff like speedboats and cash
and they have to post it before they auction it off at the Treasury.
So we went down there.
Actually, I didn't, but I was part of it.
And we called Homeland Security and Attorney General down there
and I said, I want to come down and I want to see the stash of cash,
all the cash you have. Why?
Because I want to record all the serial numbers on there and claim it.
And they were like, no, you can't do that.
I said, of course I can. Under law, I can do it.
Because you say it's abandoned, right?
Just like, for example, the reason they post it for 30 days is it was a claim.
And they say, well, you're not doing anything illegal.
We're just not going to let you do it.
There's the problem, because if it's been abandoned,
then it is legally open for you to do that.
I can't go claim the cash, but if I take all the serial numbers
and do a conditional endorsement and make a ledger to the Treasury,
those are my notes.
Those are yours.
And it's so funny to watch how it's not the government, it's the people.
When people say the government does this, you know who really fucked you up?
Your parents. Your parents are the ones who went and filed and made you do all this stuff.
They're the ones that report you first when you're born.
That's what they do. They report you as an informant.
And that's your mother, is your informant.
So it's your parents.
And by the way, if you are a government or a propaganda machine that runs the government,
you don't go after the people, you go after the parents.
Because if you get the parents, you get the rest of them that are in that unit.
You see how it works?
So yeah, it's your parents that screwed you up, not the government.
And no one put a gun to their head.
They think it's an imaginary one.
But that's why people, you know, sometimes they'd be on private calls
where people are all mad at this political situation.
I said, so which one was the bigger asshole, your mom or your dad?
And they're like, excuse me?
It's not the government, it's your parents.
They got you in this.
So anyway, Jimmy should wear a hat next time.
That's funny.
They thought that they were doing exactly what they had to do.
But they were actually volunteering a bunch of things before you could even see.
Anyway, there was a few other comments that I'll just bundle together again.
Because apparently you mentioned something about doing a seminar on water on Skype or something.
Weather, weather.
Well, they said water.
Water is not necessary, but we could do that.
It's not necessary, meaning that could be bundled up, like you said, in 10 minutes within another seminar.
But I was thinking of weather.
Well, weather was another thing.
I think that was brought up in chat.
But this is from a separate contact I have where a couple of people had asked about doing a water Skype.
And they thought you would do that.
You had mentioned it.
Yeah, simple.
That's real simple.
I've got that since the Scalarator was developed.
I've got that even so short.
You could charge $50,000 for a water seminar that's 20 minutes.
And you'll walk out of 20 minutes.
And was it worth it?
And you'll say, yeah, it was worth the 50 grand.
I mean, that's how simple and how pertinent it is.
We could do that with any seminar.
Well, sure.
But there's a lady that's a newcomer on the chat.
I think I've spoken with her before.
And very pleasant.
And she's interested in the weather stuff.
And what I want to do is put out now, if you have the email for the Greek, UncommonSenseRadio1 at Gmail.com, the numeric one.
Send me an email as a request that you want to do the weather seminar.
But also give me a short blurb why you want to do it.
Because when people  even if it's any seminar from now on, it's like, why do you want to come to this seminar?
Just in a few words, tell me.
I like it when people say, in your words.
Well, if you're not going to use your words, whose words are you using, right?
But anyway, in a few words, why you want to come to the weather seminar.
And be frank.
Because that lets me structure.
Like if  let's say I have 20 people come and half of them have the same reason.
Well, now I know what to focus on, right?
And you could say, because I'm mad as hell and I want to start taking cities out with hurricanes.
That's fine.
Come on.
I just want to know why.
Give me a short reason why.
Because that allows the narrative to be steered in the direction to satisfy the desire, right?
Hey, look.
You can make it more applicable to what people want considering what it is they're looking to do.
I think that's fairly logical.
OK.
So that was in there.
And just for the record here, I have pointed a few people to the Chatango that didn't know about that.
But also if you're on the Patreon, there's that separate chat there, which you guys are using to chat back and forth.
But it was meant to be an announcement board.
I don't care.
You guys are communicating with it.
You're using it.
I put it out there for you to use.
It's fine.
And you can post
You mean you don't mind?
Yeah.
I don't mind what you use it for.
It's fine.
Because you're communicating a bunch of things and obviously paying attention and listening.
So this is good by me.
Anyway.
There's a lot of stuff that I can get into, but I'm afraid
See, I have to get feedback.
I'm always asking for feedback.
I'm afraid that it's going to get a little technical because I'm working on several counter-space projects, which is anti-space.
Yeah, it's anti-space versus space, which
Space doesn't exist, so how can you go to anti-space?
But yeah, and it's very simple.
But I have to  I don't know the terminology, what terminology to use because it doesn't exist,
and how this can be applied to many things.
And, of course, there's the water, the food, and the weather.
Right.
And the health things for DIY.
The first DIY probably you put out a DIY vasectomy kit, and you get to keep all your parts.
Okay.
But anyway.
Yeah.
But anyway, a lot of these people are catching up because they're new, and they're back on Sonic 20.
They're back on Sonic 30, and they're listening to them in order.
So they're coming up with different things.
That's why we're hearing about the food, which was many Sonics ago and stuff like that.
But anyway, this one's a little more complex, but I'm going to cherry-pick from it a bit.
And this is from Shadow, and you need to cut it down.
I would appreciate it if you're a little more concise when you want to ask
Well, you can just keep it anonymous.
You don't have to give names either.
Well, yeah, but I want to be specific to tell a guy to cut it back because he's doing this publicly anyway,
like as far as the other listeners can see this too.
So that's why I'm doing it.
Is this the really long?
Yes.
So what's the gist?
If you've read it, what would be the cliff notes?
I'm going to it.
Now the topic, which distinguishes
I'm fascinated by the complex scientific and philosophical topics, okay?
He says it in certain places here.
He also wants to know, let's see, in the banking, all right?
Interesting.
Okay, the intersection of law and finance, okay?
You'd love to hear an episode dedicated to the concept of legal fictions in banking.
All right, stop right there.
Yes.
Finance is not lawful.
It never is because in law you have money.
Finance is not law.
If finance is legal, it's all contracts.
So let me just  this is very important.
That's why you hear me say  let's say someone wants to send me quote-unquote money.
I said, all right, send the credits here.
You never say send me money.
Actually, there have been people who have sent me silver and gold.
Yes.
And thank you for them, right?
But I would say that finance is never lawful.
It's private and it's contractually legal.
In law, you have the right to make contract.
In law, it's actually a contract.
You go to the Bible.
You see if you do these things, you'll be my people.
And if you say you do them and you don't do them, this is what's going to happen to you.
It's all by contract.
But what I'm trying to say here is finance is never lawful.
It's always legal and it's always private.
Here's the thing that people don't understand.
They've been brainwashed by like SEC and IRS and all these regulations and all that.
Any financial system or agency can ask you for finances.
You could tell them to F off.
But people never do because they have accountants and attorneys.
Oh, you have to give it to them.
No, you don't.
It's all private.
It's all you have statutory and constitutional rights to your papers, right?
And not to quarter troops, you know, and all that stuff.
But there's also statutes.
All of it is private.
Yeah.
And you know how they get away with it?
For example, when people were fighting mortgages and, you know, you have to show that you have the note to have a claim.
And they were just telling, just say you lost the note.
That's good enough.
You can't bring it to tell the bank, oh, we lost the note.
So you just tell them, you know, anybody wants financial, we lost it.
We lost it.
You don't have to say how.
And that's another way of saying it's private.
But they don't say that.
Right.
So none of it is lawful because it's not money.
So the way you do you stay in law is by demanding lawful money or conditional endorsement.
And the best place to go for that is there's a YouTube channel, Lawful Money Trust, David Merrill.
And David Merrill's YouTube 1913 Federal Reserve Remedy.
I think we posted that once before.
If you 1913 Federal Reserve Remedy, David Merrill, double R double L Merrill.
And he gives a 20 minute recitation that's on a PhD level.
But could understand if you have an eighth grade, you could understand it.
Education.
So he's the only one that's purporting this.
I have seen it by others, but he's the one that's put it together really well.
It's very tight.
And I heard he's doing really well.
He's got over 200 people at 5000 bucks each per year.
So do the math.
Finally, you know, he's doing well with it.
Absolutely.
But as a subscription thing to, you know, for building trusts and consulting and all that.
Yeah.
So basically, OK, continue.
But finance and law do not go together.
It's a private legal contract.
Right.
Now, this is the reason why I'm presenting these questions as a written, because this helps you take it and go.
No, wait, I got to split it apart.
I'm doing that on purpose, guys.
That's fine, because the thing is, I'm spending on it.
Yes.
To help others.
Exactly.
But that's why I'm posing these questions that immediately he's cutting apart.
OK, because that's the purpose of this.
OK.
Last part of this that I think is relevant is and I want you to let me finish this statement.
OK, because it's going to it's going to twist a little bit on you.
Probably.
I want a sonic that basically wants a sonic.
I'm not telling you how this is written.
How the law distinguishes between corporate entities and private individuals in the banking sector seems to align well with your series on legal complexities in modern economies.
That's how he worded it.
OK, that's fine.
But I get what he's trying to say.
Yes.
The whole system of finance, which we're in right now.
OK.
The last time there was any law with this was watching a cowboy movie.
And they say, I got a score to settle.
When you hear a score to settle, score is 20 and 20 is what's written on a gold piece.
Gold piece.
OK.
Anything after that is financing.
That's all you're going to hear in law about settling a score.
So so everything else, their fiction, everything they do is a fiction.
If you put in legal fiction, even Wikipedia or whatever will tell you everything in legal is a fiction.
It's all presumption.
OK, so when you're dealing with legal fiction in the post 1930s era, which we're in post 1930s, they're not talking to you.
They're talking to the trust because they know that, you know, they know that you don't know that you have infinite access to money.
Everyone does. Everyone's a millionaire, you could say, or a billionaire or whatever.
There's no limit. But they know that you don't know that.
Right. So it's like, how do you let's say, you know, this is what's going on.
Give a metaphor. You there's a rumor that the house across the street in the backyard where the old lady lives, there is a bunch of gold bars buried in there.
And, you know, you know it for sure. Right.
Your friend has access to the satellite and they did ground penetrating radar.
And they just you want to get to it for the government does. Right.
The old lady dies and the house is sold.
You didn't make it while the house lady died. You didn't get back in there to dig the gold bars out.
Well, no one was there. Now the new people moved in.
So what do you do? You go to the new people and say, hey, there's a hundred million in gold bars in your backyard.
Let me dig it out and split it. They'll say, screw you.
It's my backyard. Right. Thanks for telling me. Screw yourself. Right.
Whatever. Yep. Or you see. Or do you want to go take it all yourself?
That's what's going on with these social security number. Right.
So everything in finance is they know. But here, let's say a credit card company or a bank or a government agency, their co-franchise boards is asking you for money.
We're using the slave term. It's not money finances or to settle something.
Yes. The people that are calling you, even attorneys don't know what I just said.
They don't know it because especially since 9-11, it's very important that anyone that deals with the public doesn't know anything at all.
Right. Even if you go to a government, if you go even I've heard even the vice counselors in embassies are dumber than rocks.
They don't know anything at all. They're like so dumb. It's scary.
No one knows anything since 9-11. It's been over 23 years.
They have plenty of time to filter out. If you want to get a government job or something like that and you know anything about government or law or anything, you will not get hired at all.
At all. You will never, never approach the place. So when you're getting the same with debt collectors, they don't know anything.
So you're going to have to address the CEO of the company if you're going to start doing correspondence or litigation.
So if you have a problem, let's say with Amex, like Brandon Joe Williams is dealing with that, everything you sent to American Express is to the CEO.
Find out who it is. That's public information. Right. If you're dealing with the city, you go to the city manager.
If it's the state, you go to the comptroller of currency or the governor. That's all you address.
And they're not going to open it. They're going to kick it to the side.
So, you know, then you go get into what's called conditional acceptances.
There's a bunch of stuff of conditional acceptances online. They're all very lengthy and complicated.
I have a way of doing in just one paragraph. No, do not ask me how to write you one or two paragraphs.
But if you listen to enough of the sonics, you'll be able to get to the point.
Just like the calories and the vaccines. Right. You got to make it short to the point.
And no wiggle room at all. Remember, unlike Sun Tzu, where you give the enemy, you surround them on three sides.
You give them one side to leave. In fiction, you don't have to. You can surround them completely.
In fiction, you want to completely devastate them. You want to surround them on four sides, suffocate them and burn them completely.
Because it's fiction, just like in a video game. Right. In a video game.
Are you like, oh, I'm going to let these things go right here or are you just going to annihilate everything in the video game?
Right. That's the thing about fiction. Take full advantage. You know, I watched it.
You know, they go in against an unarmed, you know, an unarmed NPC.
They go in there with a with a Gatling gun and shred the thing, even though it's got nothing.
It doesn't matter because it's fictional. Yeah. You always devastate 100 percent.
That's why it was very important to bring up the art of noise, the art of war earlier.
And in real life, you give a way out. But in fiction, you don't.
The art of noise was interesting, though. Go ahead. Sorry.
Yeah, I've been using that actually developing loudspeakers and I'm using the piano piece in Diversion One.
It's one of the greatest piano recordings ever, I think. Sure, it's only about 30 seconds, but that's all I need.
So, oh, by the way, if anyone's interested in some super high end loudspeakers,
I have a small loudspeakers like nine inches by 10 inches by 10 inches.
And it goes down to 25 cycles, extremely fast impulse response.
So it sounds like speakers that are as tall as you are and they fit under your arm.
So dynamics, it's breaking every law of physics with it because I developed them using what's called steady state physics,
not the physics that are currently being used. That's very neat.
Anyway, though, because the majority of people, it seems to me, no longer have stereos or anything.
That's like an audio device in their house to like just listen to music.
You notice that I would be geared more towards the audio house.
Towards the audio house, like the people who buy.
You cut out there for a second. You're back.
Yeah.
Okay, you cut out for a second. Sorry.
My clients would be people who buy, you know, 200.
My clients would be people who buy like Fazioli pianos for 200,000 or Ferraris for 400,000 or just someone who's interested in reproducing music in a lively way.
It sounds like real life.
But it used to be very common. Like almost everybody had a stereo and a stereo system in their house and a portable stereo.
And those things are not commonplace anymore.
Then there was the home theater and then everything's gone away now.
Yeah, pretty much. Like nobody has any of that stuff. Everything's on a phone or a device and that's it.
It's on a rectangle of some kind and that's it.
And they don't actually have a sound device in their house. You know what I mean?
It's just not one of those things. They don't carry nothing.
Yeah, but what I'm bringing up is I'm going against physics completely and proving it that the physics is wrong.
And this is kind of like what I'm doing is, I don't know if you remember the first men in black when it was choose your weapon and they give him this little thing called a cricket.
He's like, oh, why do I get the little one? Right?
Yeah. And the joke is, whoa, whoa, hey, don't point that thing at me.
You know, he's got the big giant gun. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But it's got the most potency. Yeah.
And I have people that know music that have heard it and they're like, this is incredible.
And one person who came from cross country over about a month ago still messages me.
He's like, I wasn't expecting that. He's still thinking about it.
You know what you heard, right? Which is which is I go through that every day.
It's like this is this shouldn't be happening.
So, yeah, I'm not going to mention a price or anything, but there are about five thousand a pair if somebody wants them.
So I know. Fair enough. I'm just saying that in general, though, people used to I miss that, though.
Honestly, I went to even, you know, see inquire how much it would cost me to get like, you know, a stereo back in my house, just something.
And really, that equipment is not the common stuff is not available like it used to be at all anymore.
Well, you have to it's a system. You have to know what you're getting.
There's nothing put to bundled up and put together for you like it used to be in the 80s.
Well, 60s, 70s and 80s. But it depends. It's not for everyone.
Here's the idea is if you have a stereo, like you say, and you play a piano music piece on it and it doesn't sound like a piano, it's distortion.
So let's say you go out and get a high, high quality, small pair of speakers that, you know, whatever.
If you play an orchestra and it doesn't sound like an orchestra, it's distortion.
And when you say distortion, most people think it's a crackle sound.
No, if someone's playing guitar on the program material and you're playing it through whatever you're playing it through, and it doesn't sound like a guitar, it's distortion.
Yeah, I mean, it's not. Right. If you play piano music and it sounds like a little toy piano, that's distortion.
So what I'm able to do in a very small package device, have the full weight of a grand piano, which is not possible in physics.
You need very large systems to do that. And I'm able to do that with a very small system because I'm not when people think of transducers, things moving like speakers and all that.
They're basing it on pressure equations. And I'm telling you, there's no pressure. It's all based on steady state.
So when a speaker moves out a cone, people say, yeah, even I spoke to speaker designers, they think a pressure builds up on the code.
No, it's in a steady state. Actually, it's the opposite that happens.
The air moves out of the way just before the cone moves and there's a vacuum on the surface and there's mass to prove it.
And there's people that can measure it, but no one wants to hear that.
So that means that no one in the loudspeaker industry is designing things properly at all. And I could prove that.
I have the receipts because I have got even there's a guy that made a speaker company that made a YouTube video on what I said to him.
He's calling it some quantum whatever. And it worked. It worked. And then he took the YouTube off the thing.
So anyway, I have the receipts in terms of dealing with engineers. They just don't want to do it.
It's kind of like imagine saying you can do weather work. Right. Right. And going immediate meteorologist.
What is he going to say? He's classically trained, which means shit. Right.
So exactly. Yeah. So this has been a long sonic longer than normal. Right.
But that's OK. Maybe to help welcome some people and see there's more stuff going on.
And I've mentioned, I think, to TXPS known as Bruce there. He's interested in the loudspeaker technology.
I might do a seminar on the steady state acoustic counter space and show how these things.
Yeah. And how you could build these things yourself. But, yeah, if there are any audiophiles out there, get in touch with me.
There you go. So because I've got something for you that you will. Yeah. OK.
There you go. Fair enough. And so, look, if anybody knows a little bit information about a good place to go economically,
where it's not going to cost, you know, a huge amount to get something, you know, decent as far as a home stereo or.
Oh, Craigslist. I can answer that Craigslist all the time.
Not in Georgia. I'm telling you, it sucks here. People don't have crap on Craigslist here.
I used to. They told me that about Tucson 26 years ago before I moved here. And it's better than New York.
Well, maybe, but but not here. It's it's all it's the way you look at it.
OK, well, if somebody has a good way for me to search it, I don't know anything.
If you can find me something and you have a good shortcut, you got Facebook marketplace, TikTok marketplace.
And if you whenever you go to a store, I think when your computer broke, I said, I said, I'm not talking to a child anymore,
because when you go to buy something from a store, you have to pay the rent, insurance and salaries, never buy anything.
In other words, in the day and age right now, just like people don't send letters, they send an email.
You don't buy anything from a retail store. Well, I got two things because you're paying for their.
So if you wanted to get a stereo, you could go on Craigslist or Facebook or TikTok for three to four hundred bucks.
And the same stuff at a used therapy should be two thousand. Right. Because that's how they roll.
So that's foolish. Now you have to buy. In other words, you're living in the age right now where you must buy private party.
The only reason you buy from a shop is because you want their service.
Now, maybe I'm speaking for you. Maybe you want the service.
Maybe you want the service and you're going to pay four times more than what you can.
If you know, I threw away two hundred dollars getting two different computers that were useless from from local people because they have garbage here.
I'm telling you, these people have garbage. It's an attitude. It's an attitude thing.
Yeah, I learned that. I learned that 26 years ago.
I was told by everyone in Brooklyn and everyone in Manhattan that I knew I was moving to Tucson.
It's horrible there. You won't get it's great. I'm actually having in many cases, it's easier to.