The sonic entity known as Ocelli and the Greek
Greek, you know where I'm going with this, don't you?
Israel, okay, and the use of the word war, even coming from the prime minister,
people talking about it, there's clearly something happening there.
So the instant question that I got about five or six times already,
is this what the Greek was talking about yet?
No, but it's letting you know.
Go ahead. Do you remember, was it a few months ago you were bringing up something
and I said it was a nothing burger. Do you remember that?
Yeah, it was it was about a month and a half ago.
And what I was talking about is the the whole thing with the military
and people didn't want to serve because they didn't like that.
You know, the the leadership and there was a problem with the courts.
And I said, it looks like there's some unrest because there was some civil,
you know, unrest that was being broadcast. Right.
People were resisting. And of course, that society is interwoven.
The military, the civil part of it, the religious part of it is all
very intensely connected as far as I can observe from a distance
because I haven't been to Israel. Have you ever been to Israel?
No, but I just communicated with someone recently who spent about a month there
just recently. OK, fair enough.
Their comments to me was thanks for all your prognostication,
everything you've been saying. I saw personally when he was there.
And what that really was, was the military is in disarray,
the disenchantment of the people and how things are not the way
they are told. Right. And yeah, what I'm talking about is the
is the World War three kind of scenario that people are talking.
By the way, World War three is not going to be at all like World War two.
It'll be a series of events that will just be a blanket over society.
But there's no such thing as nuclear war, by the way.
It's already been decided. When you say World War three,
you think of nukes. Right. But a lot of that's not a tangent.
Yeah, but yeah, that's not you can't you can fire off more than one nuke
at a time, guys within range. You know, it's not like the Terminator
where you see nuke going off and nuke going off or Battlestar Galactico
or Armageddon. You fire one nuke and the next nuke, you have to wait
quite a bit, at least a half an hour. Right. So anyway,
and they don't really work well. They just make a really bad hotspot
and you rely on a radius and there's a lot better ways to kill people.
And the best way to get people to kill the best way to kill people is
having volunteer. Well, I've always said, you know, even when people
were talking about they're going to round us up, they're going to.
And I would always shake my head at that. That's nonsense.
It's a waste of time and effort and energy.
You can just get people to kill each other right where they are.
They don't got to be around injections. It's called pharmaceuticals.
It's called by, you know, your food. It's slow.
All that slow. It's more manageable when it's slow.
All that. Plus, if you need something done a little quicker,
you just turn people against one another and they'll do it for you.
You know, that's that's the thing. You don't have to make the effort.
If you're the big controller, if you're the guy looking at this as a chessboard,
what is the best thing to do? Not to go and attack the other chess pieces,
but to put them in a position so that they have no other choice
but to offer themselves up for sacrifice. I mean, that's the way I play chess.
Yeah. But by the way, for nuclear, they've already did the nuclear prototype,
you know, front lines engaged with nukes.
That was in sixty nine. Seventy was the Sino-Soviet war
where the Chinese were fighting the Soviets over the border.
And it's also classified. If you go to State Department,
they do listings of battles and things that they've sent monitors to to watch.
And it's also classified because they did a nuclear exchange back and forth,
like, you know, tactical linebreaker type nukes. Right.
OK, it did work. And you could also it was also very well proven at that time.
You know, everything downwind, all the lung cancer people were getting in the U.S.
right from cigarette smokes. Ha ha ha. Yeah, it wasn't from that at all.
It was from the ionized particles in the air. But from that war,
you could look up the Sino-Soviet war.
Sixty nine. Seventy is very little information, even though there was three million
people involved fighting or two million on each side.
Yeah. And forget about smoking. You can take a look up at the even just,
you know, out there publicly, the downwind babies. OK, because all the testing.
Right. They said, yeah, downwind cancer in different places.
Even John Wayne, you know, the whole thing with John Wayne. Right.
Like he died of cancer. And the whole thing was that that one movie he filmed
was right there on one of the one of the testing sites.
So it's like, yeah, of course, it's right downwind from the testing site.
So him and I don't know, everybody that worked on that production pretty much
if it was active, here's the thing. They got everyone so afraid of it.
The way you get cancer from nuclear stuff is when you breathe in the ionized
particles and they're stuck in lung tissue, let's say, or ear to ear canals
or places, you know, where they irradiate you night and day for a few days
or weeks, not not being around a sun lamp.
You know, I mean, you get a low rentage and count on a high UV situation.
But anyway, all that stuff is never going to be.
So not going on a tangent about Israel.
I have not looked at the news at all.
I actually just went into the room to get some coffee ready.
And I put on the last YouTube posted about Israel and I walked out of the room.
So I just to see what was going on.
So I literally still don't know what's going on other than what's been posted
in the chat and what I've gotten two or three mass private messages
with headlines, which I didn't click on. So I really don't know what's going on.
The last thing I saw was like 300 rockets and all that.
So it's the same stuff. Hamas, the terrorist, whatever.
Yeah, that was that was about yesterday at daylight is when that started.
And daylight is about to come back around to that area again as we speak.
So I'm assuming, you know, I mean, look, it's it's easier to shoot things
in the daylight than it is at night.
I know night vision, blah, blah, blah.
But just saying it's simpler to do stuff in the daylight, isn't it?
Yeah. Daylight creatures. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I would suggest that.
Yeah, this is the beginning of what I kind of know.
Breaking down period. Right. Fall. Right.
I did bring this up before the year is out.
And by the way, it is another thing.
The quote unquote Jewish calendar is very close to the lawful calendar,
except they're doing dark moon.
Because I noticed when was the Jewish New Year this year?
It was already in September, which is the seventh month, which is proper.
Right. They still don't have the right. It's not lawful.
It can't be. They can't do that.
Because what happens when you instruct people lawfully,
it opens them up to so many other things.
And how are you going to. Right.
You know, it's a consciousness change. Right.
Yes. Well, that was the thing I told you about.
Just recognizing that the day begins at, you know, the solar noon.
Even that is a consciousness change for me.
And I didn't make a lot of changes.
I just allowed that to seep in as a.
I mean, I'm using a personal experience.
But I assure you that if you do something as simple as that,
it will make a change in the consciousness.
Sure. A higher consciousness can always contain a lower consciousness.
Right. So when you're caught, that's a much higher form of consciousness.
When you go to understand these things.
And then when you go back and look at the concept of midnight,
that's obviously a much lower form designed to be, by the way,
a lower form because it's contradictory and all that.
And it's antithetical to the way we live. Right.
And so on and so forth. And also the people that put it out.
Right. What they intended to do with that.
Right. So you contain that and you see that and you say, oh, yeah, I was I was there once.
Right. And you move forward and you're at a much at a higher place.
Yes. Qualitatively higher. Right.
But anyway, going back to it, I did mention a lot of this stuff this year that.
And it's going to be it's going to be like the gang of Israel, the army.
What would I like to stress more? Because these things happen often.
Right. Every you could count on one of these things happening every five years.
You know where they lob a bunch of rockets over. Right.
Well, see, this happens often. But if you track it, it's this is different.
I can tell that already.
I feel I'll tell you without looking at anything or fielding any of the stuff they're putting out.
It's so it's it seems when the media grabs onto something like this, it's preplanned. Right.
The script is written. Sometimes, you know, they give the script out before the event happens. Right.
Yeah. No, I get that part. But there's something else happening here.
I don't know how to explain that. I have this feeling that this is different.
Not, you know, and I've seen it before. And look over the past.
You can track it. You know, you can take a look at the casualties,
exactly what happened on one side or the other in the occupied territory.
You can go through this all different ways that that information is all out there.
No. Yeah. It's information that can't be trusted, by the way.
Sure. Yeah. But you have to reckon what how are they showing it to you?
Yeah. What they're saying and how they're saying it. That's anything you see.
So it's this is this has got all the tales of a preplanned event.
Mm hmm. Both in other words. OK, what does he mean?
The Israelis knew this is not a surprise. Here's the thing.
Remember a few months ago, I said first reaction, by the way, that's the weirdest thing is that was my first reaction,
because the big headline initially was big surprise.
Nobody knew this was coming. This is it. And I went, oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Because then I heard and I knew I was going to hear it before they started saying it.
It's a failure of intelligence, Greg. Yeah, of course.
Yeah. Right. Which means it's an intelligence success. Yeah. Right.
So please continue. Well, one of the things that I mentioned to look for,
one of the tells may or may not, but look for anyway,
is how many dignitaries would have been out of the country when this begins.
Now, that's something that that the current news reporting is muddied up.
In other words, if you search how many Israeli dignitaries left like the past few days or a week ago,
it's very muddied up. You're not going to get that information.
You know what I mean? Well, right. Well, unless you know someone that, you know,
has got their finger on that pulse, you know.
But I would suggest that anybody who's anyone knew about this
and suddenly had to go vacation that I was going to say Morocco, but maybe not.
But you know what I mean? They're out of the country or, you know, they're in a safe place.
Where does Hamas get all this ordinance? Right. Same place Israel does. Right.
Well, that's another funny thing, because, you know, allegedly this strip is blockaded.
And of course, it's surrounded on all three sides.
If you take a look by people that are not exactly going to be friendly to them,
importing anything and you have a blockade on the water.
How is it you get, you know, the first claim dozens.
Then they said hundreds of rockets, which is a lot as opposed to just.
Yeah. But I said they're not improvised devices. Right.
No, no, no, no. These are, you know, and they're even trying to say already that the technology is.
But, you know, so, again, I'm looking at what they're saying, not trusting it,
but understanding that it can be revelatory anyway. Right.
Yeah. What form of should show it is, you know, is it going to win an Oscar?
How many rotten tomatoes does this one get? Right. Oh, yeah. Right.
Is it just going to be something to fill time on the weekends?
You know, is it just part of the Saturday cartoon run or is it going to be primetime?
Yeah. Let me just read. Well, let me just reiterate primetime or not.
I think this will be primetime. What I'm going to say.
We're looking at casualties on the Palestinian side in the tens of thousands, not a few hundred.
That's the what that's the event that I'm talking about.
Yeah, well, that's the tens, tens of thousands, not a thousand, not two thousand, not not nine thousand nine hundred ninety nine,
but over ten thousand plus many times.
That's the event that I was talking about that would change the, you know, the entire scenario.
I don't think this is it. You're talking about in one day, in one action or you say it within one, let's say, campaign, like within a few weeks.
Well, depending on how possible, depending on how they would considering that they have declared that they're they're at war
and they are looking for vengeance and they are looking to strike and they're doing all these things and talking about wiping.
Yeah, the first words. Yeah, we've all heard them.
Yes. But we haven't heard these in a while from there. Exactly.
It's usually, look, we're going to defend ourselves. We're going to protect ourselves.
We deserve to protect ourselves. We deserve to exist. And we're going to do so.
That's usually the rhetoric. This rhetoric is a little different.
Yeah, I know. This one's more like we're going to fight for the sake of fighting now.
It seems like it seems like. Yeah. I mean, look, I'm just presenting.
Yeah, I don't know. It might be. It may not be. You know, here's the thing.
I wish the best to everyone. It's sad when these things happen.
But, you know, the sooner these things take place and are gone, the sooner we get maybe our ticket out of this place.
But but anyway, that's another discussion. Here's the thing that I've always brought up.
What you're going to be looking for is a conflict that's going to be so bad between the Palestinians and Israel that it's going to change the the map literally.
And it's going to result in a very strong alliance. Is this it?
I don't know. Let's just sit back and watch. But thanks for giving me some credit on a heads up on this, because I sense that from all the private messages that I've gotten.
I'm the only one really talking about more specifics, because if you tell anyone the Palestinians and Israelis are going to go into a war.
Well, the bear shit in the woods. Right. Yeah.
But giving specifics about how the Israeli army has been downgraded internally, what you'll hear, I assure you, is the Israeli army or IDF.
I think it's Israel Defense League, the Israeli Defense Force.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, you'll hear later, as we were given these bizarre, nonsensical orders.
Right. You know, maneuvers and things. And we were like, well, who said this?
Right. And they either will not follow them because they're just bizarre or no orders or a mutiny or, you know, in disarray.
You know, what's a what do you call a military in disarray?
You know, basically, is what you will see on the Israeli side, not this precision strike and these, quote, unquote, miraculous battle outcomes that you saw in the previous wars in the 60s.
You know, where, you know, two Israeli tanks defeat 100 Syrian tanks.
You know, you know, you've heard those right.
The crazy six day war thing where we're with nothing.
They took down entire. Yeah, right. OK.
Yeah. You know, nothing like this is the opposite. This is where the they all got the thumbs up their ass and it's the gang that couldn't shoot straight.
You know, we had rubber bullets, you know, just, you know, we're giving an order to do this, which is stupid.
You know, yeah. Yeah. Nothing's going to make any sense.
The kind of thing where they're going to get beat with slingshots, even though they've got, you know, state of the art infantry weapons, this kind of thing.
Yeah. Kind of like what they did on 9-11 when they wanted to deploy jets.
And the reason they didn't deploy jets is because there was no jets to deploy to chase.
Right. So the fewer people you do that.
So anyway, I mean, there were jets, but not they all were going to what's that airfield in Massachusetts, Westover.
Yeah. Right. So, yeah, you're not going to deploy jets to intercept commercial airliners that are already scheduled to land at a military base flying at an altitude of 400 feet.
You don't do that. Right. So it's going to be along those ridiculous lines. Right.
Why are we letting that. Right. So, yeah, it's all ridiculous.
But the one that again, the one that I'm talking about is going to be very, very dark day for both.
Both a lot. We're talking about casualties, you know, maybe a hundred thousand even.
Well, I'm curious about this because I have seen some reports and then they seem to stop about the possibility of this.
This is the first time I've ever seen this, actually. Maybe they'll actually use the nukes, which you brought up to begin with.
No one. Well, they're tactical. If they use if anything is ever used here, just interrupt for a moment.
Well, it would be stupid to use anything else larger than that on the Gaza Strip just based on geography.
It's not it's already been determined since the 1980s to not use these atmospherically.
Right. But I'm just saying because of the moral consequences that people have.
But you couldn't use anything of any substantial size in Gaza unless you're going to destroy things outside.
It'll cover Gaza. Well, the way they have been.
You know, if I told you a thousand nukes have been fired off since the 1980s, but no one knows it because they're classified as car bombs.
OK. Right. And they're not in the car. They're underneath the car, in the ground, in the sewer or buried the day before.
Right. So I would suggest, yes, a thousand nukes could be used in this conflict, but not atmospheric.
Well, that's how you get a 10 foot deep crater under a car that really just lost the bottom of it.
You know, it's like, wait a minute. The only car is gone.
But if you do the math, it needed it was 10 tons of dynamite.
You know, so which you remember, you need a freight train to carry that.
Yeah. So thousands of nukes have been maybe in the thousands, but definitely over a thousand nukes have been used in the past 40 years.
Touted as car bombs and terrorist bombings and things like that.
And they're always non atmospheric, meaning they just have to be covered under the ground or inside something.
So the initial flash is not seen because remember, nukes do not explode.
They detonate and the reaction is based on the environment.
Right. So Fukushima, Three Mile Island.
What's the one Chernobyl? All those are little micro nukes.
Right. So all those things that you see, these car bombs, you know, that leave these 30 foot craters, these assassinations, these buildings during even during wartime, you know, say, oh, my gosh, that was a big blast.
And there's quite a few of them on YouTube from the Iraq War still.
Right. You know, they're never atmospheric.
They could be. I'm sure they have a containment system where, in other words, the actual bomb, the weapon casing itself can shield some of that initial reaction.
I doubt it, but possible. So they're going to be used as, you know, you know, whatever.
Use your imagination. But what I'm talking about is something that will change the relationship for indefinitely between those two countries or peoples and bring them close together with mass casualties, mostly on the Palestinian side.
And, of course, is, you know, here, if you're killing 10,000, 20,000, 30,000 Palestinians while that killing is going on, there's it's going to retaliate into the hundreds, tens of hundreds and maybe even thousands of Israelis as well.
They're not going to sit there and say, shoot us. Right. Right. So it's going to result in casualties on both sides, but mostly heavy on the Palestinians.
And that's what I've been talking about for the past 20 years, not and specifically decade is what you will see.
But what what brought this on this year is looking at this, the timing that it's time for this conflict to somehow begin or made foreshadowed.
So is this it? I don't know. I don't I'm not sensing it, but it is.
It has all the marks of a modern media production, though, produced for the media.
And, of course, someone will say, Greek, what an asshole, man.
They kill 500 people or we mean media production.
Yeah. Yeah. You know, 500 people killed or a thousand people killed for a media production is nothing, you know.
Right. Well, and the other thing is that it resonates.
Right. Because then people that are sympathetic or people that are related to some of those people that wind up dying that are living elsewhere.
Well, they might just take a little bit of issue with it. And therefore, see, that's the thing that that's why I want to get to the final question on this.
And then I'll shut up, which is and these are all based on your guys messages and questions.
So I appreciate it. And I put them together here.
You know, the Middle East Union, which you have brought up previously on other Sonics, we haven't really discussed it on Rated Y.
But of course, this started those questions.
Is this one of the and what I what I would think immediately, and I'm not sure if you believe this and I'm putting it to you.
Is this kind of like the the pre show?
I would say I would say at least, yeah, the pre show.
In other words, to soften people's minds that because of an event, other countries start being allies or what have you support group rights to support.
And they stay supportive even after the battle is gone.
And when I say Middle East Union, remember, I always qualify.
It'll be a loose Confederacy, not like the EU.
Right. It's not like we have a parliament and everyone, all the member states and nothing like that.
It'll be a loose Confederacy. In other words, they're working together loosely.
But they in fact, they work together in practice so well that might as well be a union.
But it will be a Middle East Union in that way. Yeah.
OK, well, imagine a formal union politically like having you and all the countries don't work together.
Right. Ineffective. It is effective because it's overarching political scheme.
But in this case, it'll be a loose Confederacy.
Right. But there they will start uniting and things will start centering around there.
So we'll see. I'm actually looking at everything and other input that I'm getting.
So I'll be ready to talk more about that in the near future.
Not not tonight or even next week or next month, because I'm rehashing things from other inputs.
And, you know, I'm if you're a seeker of knowledge, you're a seeker of knowledge.
Right. It's not a seeker. It's not you don't have to necessarily defend things you've said or be apologetic.
You can change your perspective because if you're a seeker of knowledge and you want to share it with other people,
you want to be what as accurate as possible. And, you know, so that's the phase that I'm going through right now.
Right. And legitimately, look, time goes on. New events occur, which add to what is happening.
And there are choices that can be made along the way. Sometimes there's a bit of a multiple choice about it.
Right. So it's based on input, you know, because of the input that I've gotten on what I've been talking about for the past two decades
is rather minimal when you compare it just to what's in the biblical text.
But when you start to look at more world, a broader viewpoint of what we should be expecting in these, quote unquote, times,
it starts I start to want to make some adjustments. So I'll be talking about that.
So fair enough. Plus, you know, new terminology, new emerging individuals could be there.
I mean, people that weren't even born at the time.
Yeah, but the terminology, look, but rose by any other name is still a rose.
So we want to keep state to the subject matter more than the terminology.
But, yeah, I get what you're saying. OK, fair enough.
So with that, I mean, is there anything else that we should be looking at?
I mean, would you suggest that anybody keeps an eye on anything in particular?
If we're still here next week or the next time we record. Right. You always got to say that.
Fair enough. So we don't we don't want to seem like we take things for granted, right?
No, anything. Look, whether it's, you know, the the mop up crew comes through or I get hit by.
Well, we get surely those that are deserving will have their fair share of information for when that's going to happen.
They won't happen now. But but yeah, let's say what I'll do.
I have not even spend one stitch or five seconds looking at anything by the next recording.
What I'll do is I'll review what has transpired and in the next few days and I'll give more of an overview review of what I think,
you know, this is my assessment of what's going on over the next few days.
How's that? That's quite fair. Thank you. And point out whatever I think should be pointed out.
Appreciate it. I do. And I'm sure that some people that are paying attention to the Sonics will appreciate it as well.
Yeah. So with that, what else is on your mind? I mean, because this wasn't really on your mind.
Maybe you have something else you want to go into here.
You know, yeah, some interactions I've had this week made me realize that one of the I would say the slogan of rated Y, which is the on culting of humanity.
Right. And how do you know you're in a cult? Right. I mean, there's a lot of stuff online, you know, I think before we started recording, I said, hey, you know, you know, Chuck,
everybody's in a cult. But if everybody's in a cult, it doesn't seem like they're in a cult because everybody's in a cult. Right.
So you hear you've heard parents say, oh, my daughter, she's in this cult. She's throwing her life away. Right.
Oh, my son is in the cult. I got to get him out of it. It's really bad for him. Right.
Well, what if the entire human population is in a cult?
That's the trouble, because, look, it's counterintuitive to say everybody's in a cult, because why?
Well, as far as I've always been taught, you know, the only difference between a cult and a, you know, organized religion is usually the numbers.
If it's small, they call it a cult. If it gets large enough, then they stop calling it a cult.
So, I mean, maybe I'm crazy, maybe I'm wrong, but that seems to me to be the only real difference between a cult and a so-called religion, according to the nomenclature.
I mean, isn't cult short for culture?
It sure is to my mind.
Yeah, I'm not like con man is short for confidence, man.
I'm not sure. Someone once told me cult is short for C-U-N-T. And I was like, no, that doesn't make any sense.
No, unless, you know, I mean, look, your experiences may vary. Of course, you out there.
I mean, it's possible, I guess, if you have an all-female. And anyway, I'm joking.
No, it doesn't make any sense. You know, you could call a C-U-N-T in England. It's a popular term for someone who's annoying.
Well, yeah, exactly. They are funny with that word.
It doesn't have to be gender-related.
That word flies out of their mouths so easily. I mean, it cracks me up, actually.
Anytime I talk to somebody from over there, it's hilarious to me with how easily they...
Yeah, we use the other terms.
Yeah, that and taking a piss are two very funny things that they just flip out there as quickly as, you know,
you and I might, you know, on a very, very rudimentary street level, might just drop the f-word.
Yeah, and we don't make those associations with those words. So, yeah, they have a different association.
But anyway, cult. What if the entire population at large, let's say, with a few exceptions, is now part of this cult,
you know, as the human cult, which varies, right, by continent, by geographically, and socially, meaning the culture, right, varies.
So what happens? How do we examine this? If you start, like I said, this week, experiences interacting with people,
several subjects, medical, food, politics, money, and all of the inquiry discussion from their side was all cultish in nature.
There was no reason behind it. It was like they were parroting something that they seen as, you know,
I said most people, when you hear them speaking, especially when you think they're going to get more meaningful,
it's still as seen on TV language, right? They can't escape that, right? Because most people were raised by that, right?
And you're exactly right. It is all based on a culture. And by the way, if you take a look at even the language these people use,
they'll say that there is a corporate culture. There is a culture in the monetary system.
There is a culture in this group, that group. Every group has a culture, so to speak.
So, yeah, it seems like a lot of little cults come together to make one big cult, if you subscribe to a bunch of them.
Is that not accurate, or what?
Yeah, but the main franchise is the same. In other words, there is a force behind it.
You have both the detractors and the benefactors. You have both.
But it's mostly detractor. Mostly detractor.
Because very, by the way, it's very easy to turn the entire, all the cultures.
Let's just say the Western world is the most screwed up, and then you would say most of the Eastern world is screwed up.
And here's the thing. I've left most of the African continent, 36 or 38 countries there, out of it.
Because they just seem to be going on along their merry way.
And they pretty much do, right? And also, by the way, that's no song and dance either.
Cannibalism is not as, see, there's a lot of cannibalism everywhere.
By the way, I think I'm going to reiterate.
If you eat pork products, pork on your fork, and it's processed pork, 10% of it, I'd say more, but 10% for sure is human DNA.
So use your noggin. When I say 10% of it is human DNA, what am I saying?
It's people, right? It's people. Rhymer, Soylent Green. What's Soylent Green? It's people.
So, yeah, and you want to hear something even weirder is the, if you like those processed pork products,
any pork taster, pork sommelier, will tell you, blindfolded, that the one with human meat will always taste better than the one with just pure swine.
So go figure. Yeah.
I was going to actually ask you about that real quick, because some people might just get the muscle.
You know how we were talking about with muscle and organ meat?
Yeah. With beef, you know, muscle and organ product.
OK, well, what about the muscle product of pork that is out there?
Do you think that that also contains?
No, that's mostly mostly the muscle. They would put the human muscle in there.
Yeah. OK, just I'm surprised if they would do skin, but the fat content would change.
This is part of the pranking. This is fun.
This is like, you know, you got a guy flipping burgers in McDonald's and his brother was just arrested.
So here come the pigs. I mean, the cops at the drive through and he spits in their burger.
Right. You heard that, right? Sure.
Of course. Yeah. So it's got that's what they're doing there.
They're just sad at the people, not happy at the people.
And they say, let's grind up some of their babies, which were killing anyway, and put it in there.
And we'll just enjoy knowing that they're eating their own kind, which is a common thing.
Most of the world, by the way, it's just it's openly known in many parts of the world, especially the African continent.
But here it's not here. It's very hush hush.
And it's so hush hush that it's deafening.
So anyway, I left back back to the I left them out.
But basically, it's very easy to fix the Western world because all the ways to fix the Western world,
financially, medically, culturally, religiously, whatever, has already been disclosed.
So this is how bad the cult is.
People are having financial problems.
Well, have you gone and studied the codes, statutes, rules, whatever laws that pertain to finance?
No, I don't have time for that. But I have time to worry about it.
Right. If you study those codes and you learn how to do restricted endorsements and ask the right questions, you may not be in financial trouble.
I'm not saying you're going to make money and be wealthy, but you won't be bleeding funny, funny money as money as you are.
Right. With the medical stuff, have you gone and.
Oh, this is OK. Medical. I'm going to bounce around between medical, religious and money here.
And then law a little bit with the medical stuff.
Do you know that no doctor in the U.S. has ever told anyone that they have any disease at all?
Ever. I mean, in the past, let's say 75 years, 50 years for sure.
What the doctors say is that you've been diagnosed with.
Well, we have a lab test showing that you might have.
But the people walk away saying, oh, I have a doctor ever said you had that.
He said you were diagnosed or the lab test results came back and it shows that you might have.
It's all presumption, but you say you have diabetes, you say you have AIDS, you say you've got whatever, whatever, whatever.
But no medical technician, professional doctor has ever said anyone has ever had anything.
You are diagnosed with the symptoms of. Right.
You see how that works? Yes.
There is no certified disease ailment, anything that the medical community has put out in decades.
But yet you have all these people crying that I got this, I got that.
I got no. Well, who told you that? No, I didn't. Go look very carefully.
Why are they saying it that way? Because it's all presumption. It's all commerce.
It's all the basic by the basic bodily functions are completely ignored.
Here's the most frustrating thing that I've ever contemplated in my in recent decades.
Why am I the only one discussing the biological vacuum in the human body?
Why seriously? You won't find anything.
But all of the studies, anatomy function scream.
That's the conclusion. Right.
So there's something going on where you just have to sit back and say things the way they are and then sit back and see who takes.
And by the way, this is no fault to anyone.
I don't see anyone ever listening to what I'm saying, taking the work and carrying it on on the medical side.
And I'm not talking about just regular subs or whatever. I'm talking about people in the medical community.
Yes, I have told many people in the medical community scores.
How many of them are right forming an alternative movement? None.
I don't see any. There's something going on, something very wrong.
I will take my time. I will go out of my way and take any amount of time necessary.
That's that can be given to speak to someone who's working in the medical field about what you know about the stuff that I talk about and show it and prove it and how it can be addressed.
And I have. And how many of them are doing anything? Nobody, none online or anywhere.
So what the hell is going on now?
Isn't that sound a lot similar to like if you spoke to someone that was deeply ingrained in some kind of cult philosophy?
What? Go ahead and try to talk them out of it. Good luck. It can happen.
Oh, yeah. It doesn't matter. I mean, trying to trying to explain to somebody that, you know, whatever.
Someone who's in a cult, go tell them that what a cult isn't good for them or what they're telling you is the antithesis of what can be shown.
Yeah, it really is. And what are they going to say? Thank you very much. I'll get on it right away or get out of here, man.
All right. When they decide that they have a messiah who is, you know, God, God's power within them.
That's the end of it. You know, it's like I can't, you know, you go like, look, OK, so by what proof do you have that this is well, this is what I know.
Well, but how do you know it? Tell me how you know it. And I'll tell you how it's wrong. It doesn't work here.
Let me help you now. They don't want it. They don't want it. It's it's real.
Because they're they're in a cult and severely, severely indoctrinated.
Same same thing with political discussions over the past few years, especially the same with financial.
Same with financial. Henry Ford's, you know, famous quote about if the people found out how the banking system works,
it'd be blood in the streets in 24 hours or something. 72 hours or something like that.
Ain't going to happen. Why? Because they're all, you know, whatever about it. Right.
The same with religious stuff. The best thing that's happened to the quote unquote religious people is the Mandela effect changes in the Bible, like it or not.
There are institutions with sculptures and signage and illustrations of the lion laying down with the lamb.
Right. Everyone's heard it. Lion and the lamb ministries. Right. You've heard of that.
But it's not the lion and the lamb never was, according to any Bible. It's the wolf and the lamb.
So all these lion and the lamb sculptures and paintings and illustrations should have never happened in the book of Isaiah.
Right. On and on and on. Right. So I love that these things change out of the blue.
By the way, I've been directly Mandela affected directly, like actually I engineered something and I needed two of them because they were the same.
So I built two. And the next day I went to fit them and one of them was the opposite.
It was it was flipped and I knew I had cut them from the same template.
There is no way I would have cut one this way and one that way because they were cut through and through the same way.
And I was like, oh, my gosh, I ruined my next day. I sit back and meditate on exactly every step that I did.
And I did it. Correct. But something happened where it didn't fit the next day. Right.
So that's my own personal thing. You know what I mean? It's kind of it's almost as bad as imagine you you try to go home and the keys don't work.
And like who changed the locks? No one changed the locks. Your keys always work.
No, they don't work. And you get a locksmith says, yeah, it's the wrong key.
But it worked yesterday. Who changed the locks? Nobody did. You see what I mean?
It's that in your face. You know what I mean? I have had that happen.
But oddly, I had not thought about that. And you just reminded me that that happened to me with a key.
It made no sense. She was just tired of you and she changed the locks.
No. Listen, this is a weird situation. I actually wasn't living with anybody else.
This was a weird deal where I was like, I've been here for two years. I've been using this key.
You couldn't have. It's not the right key. And I didn't know it was the right key.
It's not fluid reality. It's I think these things are changing. So we take notice.
Right. Weird stuff. I mean, I was, you know, what are you going to do except, OK, fine, give me the key that works.
But I mean, you know. Yeah. And the whole bit. Here's the interesting thing.
There was someone I've researched this about a year ago about the no crucifixion thing.
By the way, you know, when someone gives a parable or a story and you you resolve the outcome based on how the story is told.
Right. Instead of telling you this directly. Right. That's how the New Testament is about how the Christ was executed.
And it's not a Roman cross. Right. It's by the actions of Pontius Pilate.
So. But I did find an article written in the late 90s, and it was by a Greek, by the way, a Greek scholar that talked about the whole world's got it wrong.
It did get press. It did get some press. You'll find the press that there is no crucifixion, according to the Bible.
OK. So where's everybody been for the past 1500 years or so?
You know, let's say you really haven't had access. Most people haven't had access to the Bible for at least 300 years or less.
Really? Yeah. Because King James right before that, it was you had no access in the Catholic Church would put you to death.
You know, actually, the an excuse for the Catholic Church to attack a town or a village in Europe was when the Protestants came through and handed out Bibles to that whole village or town.
That was an excuse enough for the Catholic Church to send military and kill everyone.
By the way, this is let me just say this. This is harsh with the type of morality that's accessible information that's accessible and weaponry that we have.
Why is the Vatican still there? If someone set up a big palatial Nazi thing with the SWAT stickers and everything out there, what don't you think that would be bombed by F-16s in like a week?
You know, you would have thought so. And the odd question there, the real odd question is they don't actually possess the military that we can see that would repel a serious attack.
If somebody really wanted to just, you know, finish that and take it. Why hasn't that happened? That that is a very good question.
They are a thousand times worse than any regime. Well, you know what the actual worst regime ever political regime is, is was FDR. Why?
Franklin Delano Roosevelt did what no dictator, no monarch, no parliamentarian, no form of political government in history has ever done in the history of mankind.
What was that? The gold confiscation clause. There is no dictator, no matter how good or how bad or system or type of government in the history of man that ever told the people that their gold will be confiscated or there will be a year in prison and $10,000 fine.
No, that is absolutely the worst thing that has ever been done, you know, in terms of a policy. Right. And then you could see then, of course, you could say there's the genocidal policies of certain regimes, but those were specifically targeting certain groups.
I'm talking about the nation at large. No regime has ever done that. So the hands down in terms of a general order, it's not actually just executive order, but people take it as a general order anyway.
They see the Bar Association will construe that executive orders apply to people where they don't only general orders do. And in the US, the last general order was General Order 100 in the 1860s. It was the Lieber code. All the rest have been executive orders.
Right. So anyway, are you familiar that there was a letter where Lincoln bequeathed all titles that the United States held any land monies or whatever bequeathed and given and put under the Navy's control? Because if if the union lost, you know, yeah, the Navy would have control over it. And they never that was never changed. Never rescinded. Right. Yeah. So anyway, Lieber code. So there. Yeah. So but anyway, the Bar Association talk about those grasshoppers. I don't even know why they exist, by the way.
I remember someone going into some place and talking to these attorneys about what they're doing is unlawful is about a decade ago. And the first thing they said is, are you trying to say we shouldn't exist? And he kind of shut up and would have taken a lot of balls. But it should have been said, Yeah, no, you should not exist in the capacity that you are. You could exist as some cult off to the side doing what you're doing. Yeah, sure. But not as the mainstay for what people consider to be law. No, you should not exist in that capacity would have been the right thing to have said.
So you have all these things working together, because in a cult, that's what that's what happens, right? So yeah, it's these. In other words, if anyone comes and examines the human society, especially in the Western world, nothing should be the way it is. But it just happens to be it's kind of like that. Who's that philosopher that contemporary foster so that everything in the everything in the whole world is wrong, and everybody knows it, right? So and they're letting it go.
I forget. So that's pretty much.
No, that's nonsense. That's just people not that was something I thought it was five, two in the front and three in the back. No, because wasn't there wasn't there a Secret Service guy hanging off the back?
No, he doesn't. He comes from another car jumped on. I mean, that's okay. I'm not going to go ahead. No, but I've heard that one before. I've heard lots of these. I've heard them all everything from the hyphen and the KitKat to the you know, you name it. Okay. But anyway, weird thing happened to me. And I was wondering because this might be something that touched you. And I was just curious. Okay, just off the top of your head. Don't look at anything or anything. But how would you spell the word antenna?
With a double N, just like it sounds.
Okay. Now what's weird to me is I don't ever recall there being a double in there. And I used to work with antennas. And I used to use antennas. And I would get them from I was one of those guys that went to Radio Shack, right? I was one of those dudes who did that kind of stuff.
All right, hold on. How about biology? Because they antenna are also for insects. Is it also spelled with a single N?
I do not recall.
A double N.
That is a that is a that they spell it with an AE sometimes with the insects, right?
Yeah.
Yes.
Are you trying to make it a double N or a single N, right?
Exactly. I recall the AE as in an antenna, like a single one, I think is the way that would be used, right?
Antenna. Yeah. Yeah.
Okay. But antenna, which is also could be a singular. Okay. Or whatever.
It seems weird with one. Are you trying to say that's one N now?
No, I'm saying it is two N's right now. And I recall one N.
Oh, I recall two N's.
Yeah. Okay.
That's the problem with with this effect. It's it's based on memory. But I have always harped on people that you've got to improve your memory and everything else will improve.
No, certainly. I agree. But it's just and it's look, it's not a major thing. It doesn't shake the world. I'm just saying it's one of those things that absolutely sticks in me the wrong way.
It just there was not two N's on there. I know there wasn't. I remember looking at packages. I remember looking at, I mean, seriously, everything.
Really? Okay. Yeah. Because antenna with one N sounds kind of Latin. It would read like a Latin word, but that's fine.
Yes.
You know, like when you speak to someone in Italy, Italia.
Yeah.
They don't say Amazon. They say Amazon.
Amazon. Yeah, right. Exactly.
Because in Italian, the second vowel is emphasized typically.
Right.
Right. So it doesn't change the spelling. So antenna spell change still sounds like antenna.
That's the one thing I do about language is if it sounds right, tomato, tomato, you spell it the same way, potato, potato. And it sounds different.
I think if it sounds the same, the spelling, you know, you've gotten private messages from me.
You know, I'd like to misspell words like time with a Y and public with a K.
Right.
Oh, yeah. Sure.
Yeah. I like to do that just to show that how well, you know, the language is not a factor of what's being written. It's how it sounds.
No, look, and I'm all for that. And I get that it sounds proper. I'm not trying to make a big issue out of it.
I'm just saying.
No, no, no. But that is all effect is about these little innocuous, harmless changes to get to get us to those who are ready to to pay attention to start paying attention.
Right. So something is weird here, because I'm telling you now, most of this stuff I have.
You could bring up a hundred of these things and I'll go, look, man, come on.
I understand even why people are misremembering.
OK, in cases like with the JFK thing, I get it.
They're they're turning around and forgetting that, you know, John Connolly was wounded.
It's OK, because hardly anybody talks about Connolly getting wounded.
But he was. Yeah, right. So you just you know, he was the governor of Louisiana or something like that.
The governor of Texas, the governor of Texas, governor of Texas.
And his wife is sitting next to him. So there's two people.
And then you got John and his wife. That's two more people.
And then you got two Secret Service agents in the front. That's six.
That's the way it's always been the way I know it. Now, people.
This is a pruder show that. Yes, yes, absolutely.
And it always. And but that's the thing is I studied this long time and I don't remember any change.
You know what I'm saying? But this was weird to me because I'm telling you, I remember looking at boxes with the big word antenna,
the small word antenna. I remember buying antennas. I remember vaguely, vaguely, vaguely.
I could see one. And, you know, and I think here's the thing.
It's not static. There's a lot that's going to change and keep changing.
Some things might change back. Maybe so. And maybe this has nothing to do with anything.
And it's just me being weird. But I'm just saying it's just weird.
Well, I don't know. Weird. Maybe other things, but not weird.
I might be odd a little bit. But the thing is, it's just weird thing like that to me.
It's just kind of like for some reason, this sticks out to me.
And I don't know why I'm going, you know, doesn't even make sense as to why this is a big deal.
But I tweeted about it. I was like, does anybody else remember this?
And nobody said anything. That's fine. But look, let's just go back to the cult real quick.
It'll wrap this up. Please do. When when you're looking for a cult to disband or change or improve or whatever.
So it's not a cult. It's not going to happen by its followers.
Is what it was. What was the thought that I wanted to really instill?
No, it never does. Well, it never does. If you look at any cult that is ever disbanded, broken in any way, shape or form.
How does it happen? How about the top down? Yeah, top down.
There you go. So that's the only way this will happen then. Right.
Yep. From the top down. Yep.