Sonic Event 36, Ocelli in the Greek rated Y, and why oh why does your computer work the
way it does?
Maybe we'll get into that.
Maybe we'll talk about the intrusive nature of the intrusive things that are, can I say
intrusive again?
No, I'm not going to keep repeating myself because I'm not going to talk that much.
I'm going to talk with the Greek and that's what you're here for, the conversation that
ensues.
How are you doing tonight?
I'm doing, doing as I always do.
We spoke earlier.
Maybe we'll talk about the news.
I'm like, oh, I can't do that.
Anything.
Oh my gosh.
You said it's comedy.
Yeah, it's comedy, but it's just there's an underlying something there that I don't know.
You know, I did an interview recently with the guys at Forbidden Knowledge News.
This is really a mellow cat.
Chris I think is his name.
And it's interesting that, you know, it's a totally new group, new person, let's say.
And I come out now, let's say speaking someone for the first time, new group, new audience.
It's very different than it was 10 years ago, bringing up, just showing people a lot of
stuff that they've been missing because that lot of stuff is a list of 5,000 things, right?
They've missed out on that's in front that they should know or be aware of or have passed
through the gray matter.
And I didn't quite do that.
I just sat back and try to address his questions in a Greek speak kind of way, in a way that,
you know, no one would, you know, no one else does.
So so yeah, being it's not not for the sake of being different.
You know, some people want to be different, right?
For the sake of being different, you know, you know, this is different considering your
normal patterns.
I mean, lately, a theme between you and I privately, especially is breaking the patterns.
Right.
Which is a good thing to do in general.
And you've been doing that personally, it seems like.
So, you know, the fact that you conducted yourself differently in that interview, I did one on
the infinite fringe recently, which was a repeat because apparently he had problems with
his recording device the last time that we sat down.
And and I noted how different things were, you know, as far as information gathering and
stuff.
There's a theme lately, though.
And this this was the thing that we actually discussed real quick before we started recording
here is, look, cocaine is a theme.
OK.
And I'm finding it funny.
You know, we've had Cocaine Bear is a movie.
I don't know if you took note of that because you're not Mr. Movie Guy.
But no, apparently was a popular movie for a minute.
And it was about cocaine getting dropped in the woods and then a bear getting a hold of
it.
And of course, it is based partially on a true story at the height of the Iran-Contra thing.
There was a bear that ate a bunch of cocaine and went crazy in the woods.
Right.
Well, too much of anything, too much of anything will make you crazy.
Well, of course.
But I mean, you know, bears are really not designed to be taking cocaine.
As far as I understand them, I mean, we are humans.
I guess I use it loosely.
I don't know.
But I am saying that I'm sure the drug.
I'm sure that bears are not designed to take cocaine for anyone that hasn't done it.
If the first time you've ever done it, it's what it feels like is like you ever get some
really good news.
Anybody tell you like really good news.
Oh, that's what it feels like.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
Not the kind of news that lifts weight off of you, but like a surprise good thing that
just kind of sort of shows up and you're like, yeah, you didn't expect it.
Yeah.
In a very good way.
And I can see how people always want to continue doing it to reminisce that that initial feeling.
Most drugs are like that.
And that's what they always said.
Most relationships are like that.
Oh, yeah.
And that's what they always said was most dangerous about crack.
And it's funny you say relationships, because that's what I thought is that's like, you
know, when you first start up with a girl or a woman and you're really, really super
excited to see them and they're just everything about them is absolutely captivating.
And, you know, that high you're sort of on, it reminds me of that place to be because
it's going to go down.
There's no way you can maintain that.
Yeah.
It's why you want to start low and build up and learn to love the person or whatever.
You know, even when you end up in a situation where you're like, I would never be with this
person.
What am I doing?
You still you still have to make it work because of the world that you live in is that you're
right.
You know, lately I've been working with industry and various design things and on my own getting
my my, you know, act together and, you know, for being firm and what's known about these
particular subjects, let's say.
And it's kind of like everything seems they always all all scientific data that when you're
designing things in any industry always says it's compromises.
If you want to do this with the thing, this is the compromise, right?
If you want to go this way with the same thing, you're going to compromise that.
Right.
So everything is full of compromises.
And that's just how this reality is.
Well, like, for instance, if you want to make something mobile as opposed to it being, you
know, a place where it's just built in and set in one location, well, then you've got
to give up this or that part of it.
That's for sure.
Like an audio.
It's called Hoffman's Iron Law.
There are three things and you can only have two out of the three things.
Right.
You can't do them all.
Interesting.
Right.
So.
But yeah.
OK.
The cocaine is a no is a no.
No issue.
I mean, the distractions they put out.
I mean, the white powder thing is a meme, by the way.
It's not that it's cocaine.
The white powder.
I remember the this white powder a few weeks ago, again, being sent to what is it, GOP
people.
And then there was the white powder in nine around nine eleven.
Well, see, that's what was most interesting about this most recent news story.
And I brought up Cocaine Bear because, again, it was a comedy, but also based on some elements
of a real story.
What I found fascinating is, you know, people going, oh, it's a shocker.
There's cocaine in the White House.
And I'm like, it's a shocker if there isn't cocaine in the White House, first of all.
Secondly, the idea that I actually think, yeah, well, yeah, they know that the White
House is not part of this country.
Yeah.
Well, you know, look, do you really want to go there?
I mean, yeah, that's that's yeah, go there.
That's where it really is.
I got you.
But let's build off of this story for a second, because you brought up something interesting.
They found it in the White House.
Why is it that we're hearing about it was my question.
You know, couldn't this be just handled privately?
But apparently the Secret Service encountered it.
And I'm thinking to myself, well, the Secret Service had surveillance on this.
So they probably know exactly where it came from, when it happened.
I mean, 24 hour surveillance, you know, at a 7-11, you can figure out if somebody dropped
something on the floor.
It's the white powder.
See, I don't even it's the what is it?
It's white powder.
Right.
So they bring up the white powder.
Trying to get to that point.
The thing is that initially they had to call in, like the fire department and all this
other nonsense.
Why was that response there?
Because of the procedures put in place after what?
Remember the anthrax attacks that went after 9-11 and the fake anthrax stuff.
Now, I know that you were aware of the Northeast at that time, you know, around 2001.
I don't know if you were living there still, but no, I was not.
Well, in the Northeast, there were a bunch of events that, you know, have been sort of
scrubbed.
Nobody thinks about them.
I don't see references to them, but I do recall them happening where people were doing messed
up stuff.
I mean, I was at a retail location, which was part of my job.
Just one part of the many retail locations I was in charge of.
Across the street from me, some lunatic got pissed off at the, you know, the Wawa's.
You remember the Wawa convenience store?
Yeah.
I heard of it.
I've never seen one though.
Okay.
Well, it's, you know, it's a nice chain of convenience stores.
It's actually a fairly efficient model for convenience stores.
But anyways, they were across the street from me and somebody ran into that store, got pissed
off at the place apparently, and just dumped a bunch of white powder on the counter.
Right?
Right.
Because it was the thing.
It was the theme.
Right.
This was back in around 9-11.
Yeah.
This is, you know, early 2002.
So this is, you know, a few months after and people were still talking about the anthrax
attacks, which occurred immediately after.
By the way, if you do get a reliable report that it is weaponized anthrax, it's from the
military, what do you call it, where the cash, where they keep the weapons.
Oh, yeah.
Well, no.
It's always from-
You can't make that.
Yeah.
You can't make that at home.
No.
So, you know, not the good stuff.
And if it is a certain grade, if it's ground a certain way and it's very scientifically,
you know, consistent, then you're looking at Fort Detrick being a source.
Yeah.
Potent.
Exactly.
There's only a few places that could do that.
Right.
And it's the effort.
For what it does, it's not worth the effort, but they have it on hand, you know?
Well, yeah.
So, anyways, it's just interesting to me that because it was just commonplace, this freaked
everybody out.
Hazmat showed up.
You know, they cordoned off the area and all this other stuff.
I got caught up in it.
So, it was-
It's a show.
I mean, how much distraction is necessary is very little if the people were never aware
of what they should be distracted from.
So, when the distraction comes, it seems like it's the real thing, you see?
So, yeah.
That was kind of a confusing statement, but-
It's okay.
But this week, it just turns out that, you know, there was some powder discovered at
the White House.
So, they had this reaction to it, which did harken back to the whole, you know, anthrax
scare.
And I found it funny because people were like, why are they calling up other people?
They forgot that that was part of the justification.
It's a Freemasonic thing, by the way.
It's because in the Freemasons, you know, they go back to a lot of the ancient rites
and rituals from Egypt.
Whenever an ancient site was found, there was white, like they uncover what they call
a tomb or an underground place, there's white powder in vases and things like that.
And sometimes it's strewn about from earthquakes, you know, that'll shake, something will fall
over and break.
Right?
Are you familiar with, they call it monoatomic gold, and it's a very fine white powder.
It's a powder, yeah.
Whenever, you know, whenever tombs are opened and found in ancient Egypt and other places,
they find, if there's been an earthquake, it's on the ground.
If it's not on earth, if it's been intact, it's still in vases, you know, lots of vases
with it, you know.
So, it's the Freemasons, I think, make suggestions like that to signal, when I say Freemasons,
you know what I mean?
The secret societies.
Right.
The Freemasons are just a bunch of guys, drive around and whatever, and wear pressed slacks
and have a sticker on their car.
Not the guys that are trying to network and raise money for the local kids hospital.
No, no, no.
Not those guys that have the public barbecues.
Well, those guys, too, are pretty scumbaggy, by the way, believe it or not.
But they're not in control of anything too big.
No, no, no.
Yeah.
This is a secret society communication.
Just like everybody's looking at the 1333, they communicate with the 5-1 from Mayday.
So you'll see, like, this person, it's $51 million, or $15, or $1.5, or $5.1, however
you see the 1-5 or the 5-1, is that they're a form of communication, you know, like with
the COVID thing.
Remember, it was like 33 million people, 13, or 51, or Area 51.
Right.
So they have their own little stuff, and it's really a shitshow in terms of, I don't know
how you feel about, you're around youngsters, but you know, when you deal with the culture
they put on, you know, like toys, and games, and stuff for quote-unquote kids, that's not
as bad as what they're putting out for adults, you know?
No.
Like the Fisher-Price stuff is not as bad as the, yeah.
No, it's got hints and suggestions of things with the toys, but the other stuff is a lot
more direct and just blunt, you know?
Yeah, it's, well, one thing I spoke about in the interview, Chuck, is that the universe
abhors imbalance.
It always tries to make balance.
So if, I said about 90% of the society is NPC, it depends on its relative, right?
How many people are not NPCs, 1 out of 10, and how many out of those are actually worth
talking to in any capacity, maybe 1 out of 1,000, or 1 out of 10,000?
Believe it or not, from a societal, moral, ethical perspective, lawful perspective, that
seems like society's out of whack.
It's totally imbalanced, and I'm telling you it's balanced.
It only takes one individual out of, what, maybe 10,000, or 100,000 to balance the rest.
You know, that knows, let's say, to a point is aware, let's say, and somewhat intelligent
and knowledgeable.
You see what I mean?
Yeah, well, based on the level of maturity, for lack of a better word, of the majority,
they do require a leader, right?
So I mean, a lot of them do, because they don't know how to operate without one, effectively,
right?
They always need, well, who do I turn to for leadership on this or that?
You know, like you talk about all the time.
Well, yeah, on the other end, yeah, the 0.1% or 0.001 don't require, that's, they're the
anarchists.
They don't need anyone on top.
Yeah.
Right, and by anarchists-
As long as you have food, clothing, and shelter, you're fine.
Right.
By anarchist, you do mean those that are, you know, are leaderless, and therefore, you
know, there's no-
Yeah, it's castle doctrine.
Right.
Yeah, it's what, it's what this country supposedly, see, the, you have a representative and then
direct government.
This was really set up initially to be direct through representation, not just completely
representative, right?
Right now, it's all representative.
There's no, there's no, let's say, influence or whatever, like if you, people want to influence
the government, for example, there's a group you have to go and sign up for, right?
Right.
The lobbyists.
You can't do it directly.
There's nothing direct anymore, which tells you that this place has been run a certain
way and that's how this place is run, and, you know, get used to it or keep it to yourself.
So, anyway-
Yeah, because otherwise, there'd be, you know, a hundred people that would run for an office
as opposed to the two parties, and you would see, you know, people with different individual
ideas that actually were, you know, offering up their differences and they would go and
represent those differences, but you don't see that.
It gets funneled into a very, a very small group of individuals that are allowed to continue
long enough in the process.
I mean, and that's just the selective process of the representative.
Then you get into the process of what happens once that representative is installed and
And yeah, you're disconnected at every level, and your only chance of participation, allegedly,
is to become part of a party.
Well, we could go on what you, on that subject that you brought up, but I always have to
stop myself.
I want to stop you also.
The reason why is because in their laws many years ago, they stated that it's all commercial,
and commercial means you need money, and there's no money.
So the fact that there's no money, it's all credit, right?
And ledgers, until money comes back, undoes the commercial, and because the government's
undone and it's become commercial, you know, if you read the annotations to the codes,
the federal codes, it says that all crimes are commercial crimes, right?
So commerce means you need money, and there's no money, so that if there's no money, there's
no commerce.
If there's no commerce, the commerce part tells you there's no government, so there's
none of it.
None of it exists.
It's amazing how it's working.
So how it's really working is the way that it worked back before we knew anything about
how things worked.
That's why I always talked about the revived goddess religion, and what's coming is a system
that is revived from pre-flood times, right?
That we know nothing about, where nothing's been preserved, and by the way, when you look
at ancient documents, one thing I put in the chat, I don't know if you picked it up, any
ancient document that you, like the Bible or anything else, you know, you have all the
other books, Bhagavad Gita, the Mahabharata, the Koran, whatever, all that stuff is very,
very, very, very highly controlled.
So when you read an ancient text, whether you know it or not, or read it or study it, in
the back of your mind, I didn't say this years ago, but this is important to say now as time
progresses, in the back of your mind, you should always be asking yourself when you're studying
anything that's ancient, why are they letting this out?
Why are they, you know, why is it not illegal?
Why has it not been squashed?
Because here's the thing, this is a hard statement for most, well, if you understand Greek-speak
and have been around Greek-speak for a while, you'll see this right away, but nothing has
been lost.
There are ancient documents from 5,000, 6,000 years ago that still exist that are not open
to the public, and if you saw the documents, you'd say it can't be more than 100 years
old, it's in perfect condition, right?
That's the level of preservation of knowledge that there is, but not for the public, and
not even for the academics.
I had someone recently email me and say, Greek, I know a lot of academics, and I bring up,
you gave a whole example of things that I've said, they can't find it, not even on JSTOR,
which is their academic bank or whatever information.
I said, the academics are part of the system, they're like social rank, they're like the
sergeants in the enlisted, you know, they're not there to, you think they're going to give
the academics real information and give, you know, they're part of the, how do you become
an academic?
Just some schmuck in regular society decides to stay in school, because, you know, if you
get a student loan and you keep re-enrolling in school, as long as you're in school, you
don't have to start paying back the loans, that's how they incentivize these professors,
by the way, anyway, to stay in school.
But anyway, I don't think we've drifted too much off the subject, because we haven't really
started on a subject tonight, other than what we, the white powder, I think I'll lay it
to rest.
But the computer aspect, yes, you should be savvy about your machines, but you don't want
to go to great lengths, you know, the, what do they call it, the VIP, whatever it is, to
hide your virtual...
Or the VPN.
VPN, yeah, yeah, and all this other encrypted stuff.
When you do that, all that's put out by intelligence agencies, like, for example, there's a phone
service called Cricket, monthly bill, no contract, years ago.
It turned out that the local police started that, why?
Because they found that the people that were attracted to, like, the prepaid or not, it's
not really prepaid, were ones that they would like to use as, you know, for charges, right?
So they found out if the police own the cell phone company, they don't have to get a warrant
to listen to you, right?
You get it?
So...
Oh, yeah, same thing with the pager companies years ago, I mean, all of a sudden, they sprung
up with a whole bunch of independent pager companies, and you could go to a pawn shop,
and your pawn shop guy might have a pager service, and you could go and, you know, literally
get a pager from the pawn shop, buy it, and have it running right as you walk out, and
boom, yeah.
You don't need a...
If they're using your stuff, you don't need a warrant for it.
So here's the interesting part about computers, is just stay under the radar, just look like
everybody else.
Like, for example, what I do occasionally, I'll do searches, like, for a Barbie doll,
or canned beans, right, or, you know, something at Kmart, or, not Kmart, Target, or something,
right?
I can't imagine why you'd be searching for a Barbie doll, but go ahead.
Yeah, but you know what I mean, just to throw off the, you know, because if I'm using the
computer for referencing, they're trying to sell me, like, you know, EC meters, you know,
for laboratories, right?
Oh, yeah.
You know what I mean, electro-conductivity meters, because I'm using it for research
and other things like that, and for Skype and calls.
But, like, I'm getting ads right now for every kind of flashlight in the world, because I
wanted a magnifying glass with a light on it, you know, I wanted a magnifier with a
light, and I wanted to find a new one, and now I'm getting flashlights constantly injected
into my ads.
Yeah, yeah.
But they could...
If you think about buying a new couch, here's the scary part.
Well, it's not scary.
It's...
We...
You understand the reality is ephemeral.
It's...
Anyway, if you start thinking, I assure you, if five out of ten people or half the people
start thinking about buying a new couch, you'll see an ad for a couch, even though you don't
type anything in or say anything to anyone.
It'll show up.
It's funny how that happens.
Well, I haven't seen it through direct thought.
I mean, you're telling me that now it's up to the point of direct thought?
They could read your mind, yeah.
Because I've seen it...
Brain waves are like language, right?
So...
Because I've seen it directly with conversations.
Even if I have a conversation in the proximity of a computer about a product or something,
I'll see an ad for it just a short time later.
You know, like, say I'm talking to the wife about, I don't know, meatballs.
Next thing I know is I'll see that there is a sale on ground beef at whatever store.
Sure.
It'll come up, you know.
Or I'll have a conversation...
I'll Skype in Spanish with someone for a little while, and then I'll go into the living room
and turn YouTube on the Roku, and I'll get ads in Spanish.
Oh, and YouTube gives you the Spanish commercials, too?
Oh, okay.
I thought that was just me.
I guess.
Oh, no, no, no.
But it'll be specific in that vein.
Yeah, but...
Oh, I wanted to just mention, I use Mac, by the way, as a browser, I recommend Maxton,
M-A-X-T-H-O-N.
It's the most efficient that I've found, and it has an ad blocker.
I've never seen a YouTube ad, literally.
I've never...
Well, I have on the Roku out in the living room, but not on the computer because of Maxton.
M-A-X-T-H-O-N.
If you want to clean your computer, you clear...
This is, I've found, you don't have to do these fancy...
This is what these fancy programs that they want you to buy for keeping your computer running
efficiently do, anyway.
What you do...
Because I used to subscribe to iobit, it was like 20 bucks a year, whatever.
I don't do any of that anymore.
You do Ccleaner, which is real basic, it's free, Ccleaner.
And what I do is you go to the start menu, and you type in run.
I should do it.
It's probably easier to...
Let's see if I can do it from memory.
I don't want to mislead anyone.
But you go to...
You type in run.
You know what?
I'm going to do it right now because sometimes when you do this, you might miss a step.
Yeah, if you're in the middle of doing it, you'll be like, oh, yeah, that's right.
You got to click on this, too.
Yeah, go do it.
You go to the start menu, and you type in run, and then you select run.
It's known as Windows 10 app.
And then you...
It says open.
A little window opens up.
Type in the name of program, folder, document, or internet resource, and Windows will open
it for you.
Type in cleanmgr, clean manager, which is C-L-E-A-N-M-G-R, okay.
And then it opens another window, and it says files to delete, and check everything on the
left.
It's about seven or eight things.
The other computer I had is only like five or six.
And then you hit okay.
And it says, are you sure you want to permanently delete these files?
And you hit delete files, and it'll clean up the drive.
And basically, it's all temporary files, cookies, all the stuff that you normally...
These other programs don't get because it's directly what's been laid on the...
Through the Windows, where if you have a separate program, it has to go and prompt, you know,
what the program has.
It's not going through Windows, but this is through Windows.
So run, and then type cleanmgr, and just select all the empty boxes, and yes, delete that.
And the computer will run really well.
And back in the day, I know a guy who works for Microsoft, and when the computers were
slow, he'd come over for 75 bucks and do stuff.
And I'd say, hey, listen, I got this thing.
You do this, this, and that.
And he's like, well, you don't need me.
That's what I do.
I'm like, great.
For 75 bucks?
Yeah, sure.
I'll do it myself.
So...
Save you 75 bucks.
Yeah, to make your computer run fast.
So that's what make...
And then if your computer is running slow, you got to go in and start deleting anything
that's not being used.
But the run, cleanmgr, select everything, and yeah, that's been a saver.
I've helped quite a few people with slow computers or whatever.
So...
Yeah, because you end up retaining a ton of stuff, especially if you surf the net, you
know, you have temporary internet files and things that you don't even use anymore, yeah.
The other thing, some of the programs on the computer, well, the computers are set up,
when you shut the computer down and turn it on, it doesn't necessarily reset itself.
Sometimes it starts where you, internally, where you left off.
If you want the computer to reset and be more healthy, do restart.
Restart will prompt more of a clean slate on a start than a shutdown.
It's kind of counterintuitive because you think a shutdown is, you know, right?
But a restart actually resets the computer internally much better than just a shutdown.
So yeah, that's why very often when you install a new program, it says, do you want to restart
the computer now?
You see, it doesn't say shut down, right?
And restart, and then start.
Yeah, it's always restart, yeah.
Yeah, so do a restart also.
And if you do the clean run, cleanmgr, yeah, your computer should run faster.
So that's all I can suggest for computers tonight, because really, the thing makes me
sick.
Like, what I mean, well, it doesn't make me sick, but I mean, the stupid rectangle that
I've been using now for about a month, I use MaxTon, and I only use it as a phone.
I don't do whatever on it, but it's an iPhone 7, but supposedly it's a very old one.
I've talked about this before.
The operating system, regardless if it's Apple or Android or whatever, it has the mentality
and the ideology of a nine-year-old or 12-year-old girl with a credit card, right?
So I can't stand that.
I mean, well, I'm not saying that a nine-year-old or 12-year-old girl with a credit card is
a bad place to be, right?
But that's the mentality behind it, right?
So anyway, the computer thing.
The other thing I wanted to maybe entertain, just to segue back into it, is how everything
is in balance.
No matter how bad we see a situation, there's a balance that has to be made very quickly.
Give an example.
Very often it's unintuitive.
You don't see it.
Like, where's the balance in World War II or World War I or these plagues?
We don't know, always.
There's always something beyond our capability to perceive and even understand.
But what we do know is the mechanism—this sounds like Daoism or Daoist philosophy—
But wouldn't some people say that the baby boom would be the balance for World War II
because, you know, you have a population reduction based on the conflict, and then you have a
population refill, kind of in a quick-time sense, a culling, and then a restocking.
It's basically a culling.
Well, it's for different reasons.
World War I and World War II, from the research that I've done—by the way, I don't endorse
him, but Douglas Dietrich, if you want to know about World War II, go to his older stuff,
if you could handle his insanity.
And I'm not calling him insane.
He calls himself insane.
Just like with Ken Wheeler.
I love the guy, but he's a fat, ugly, bald guy, not because I'm calling him—he calls
himself that.
Fair enough.
Anyway.
Douglas Dietrich on that.
But from speaking to some old heads decades ago, World War I was about going after the
Germans because the Germans were synthesizing everything—synthetic ink, synthetic oil,
synthetic fuel.
As a matter of fact, you know Mobil 1, that really good engine oil, by the way?
Yep.
Heard of it.
It used to be advertised a lot in the 80s.
I got some recently.
I put it in the engine room.
It was really quiet.
I was like, oh my gosh, that's such a wonderful oil.
Well, years ago, from someone that worked in the gas industry, we were talking about
how the Germans were using plant-based motor oils that lasted forever.
You don't have to keep changing the oil.
And he said that Mobil developed their Mobil 1 oil from leftover World War II barrels of
oil they absconded with from Germany, from the market or whatever, and they tried to
technically figure out how it maintained its lubricosity and its viscosity, heat resistance
and all that, and they tried to emulate that.
So yeah, World War I was overstopping the Germans.
The Morgenthau's pastoral policy, it's called pastoral because he said Germany, everyone
should be killed, and Germany turned into a pasture, right?
Back in those days, they didn't mince words.
They would easily tell you you should eliminate these people in public documents.
People went with it, you know?
World War II was basically calling the population, I think it's 90% of the people that died in
World War II were not on the battlefield, it was civilian, it's all civilian, right?
So yeah, and then we have another main, the main calling that's coming is not going to
be through war, but it's going to be through cosmic, you know, calling.
That's still somehow a balance.
I don't understand that fully, but I do see it and I do comprehend it, right?
But excuse me, something that's unintuitive is from doing computer modeling, actually
advanced computer modeling from, not here, but someone in Switzerland that was modeling
pressure devices, and it made total sense.
Most people, so for example, when you have a piston moving forward, you think that there's,
you know, or a speaker moving forward or a hammer moving forward or something, the front
of the face of that device that's moving forward, compressing the air is going to have a positive
pressure against it, right?
That's of course, right?
You're moving, if I push you, if I punch you in the chest, there's a positive pressure,
right?
Okay, well, these devices that move very quickly like that, the moment they stop moving, a very
strong negative pressure builds up in front of it.
And it's not counted for in engineering.
And that's why they have a lot of problems with things that they don't foresee, because
they don't foresee this negative pressure.
And this engineer was going around telling people, there's actually a negative pressure
on the front of that piston.
And they're like, no way, it can't be, because it's all, you know, it's a tremendous amount
of positive pressure building.
It has to be positive on the front of it.
And he was showing them that it's actually for a very finite period of time, a small
negative pressure.
And I said, well, like a mushroom cloud, when a very powerful detonation goes off, it doesn't
just keep expanding outward and outward.
What happens is you have the initial energy and then what happens, it contracts completely
into a vertical column, right?
And then you form the cloud atop, makes total sense.
The only way a tremendous force like that would do that is if there's a negative pressure
in the middle.
Why would the column go straight up and not completely outward like the shockwave?
In other words, when a detonation of an atomic device goes off, all the material and everything
on the smoke and gas and all should follow the shockwave.
But it doesn't.
You would think, yeah.
It doesn't.
It forms a negative area where that's the only way you could form a column.
And it rises very, it shoots up very quickly and then where it slows down, it forms the
mushroom head.
Right.
Make total sense.
And he's like, oh, I never thought of that analogy before, but anyway, that's what I
mean by unintuitive.
There are so many things that are going on that can be modeled.
If someone wants to sit down with a computer and figure these things out or because they
are really good engineer doesn't need a computer, but he does it intuitively.
But what if something is unintuitive?
What kind of intuition do you need?
You see, if it's unintuitive, right?
Because I think even the best engineer would imagine if something creates a pressure front,
it's going to maintain the pressure front.
You won't see a negative pressure emerging on it ever.
You see?
So there are things that are, we're constantly learning.
And by the way, what I just mentioned is not going to be accepted by the main engineering
community.
I don't see in the near future at all.
No, you bring this to an engineer, they're going to tell you you're wrong, you're crazy
or, you know, that makes no sense.
It's a matter of either is a, you know, forced or there is no force and that's it, right?
That's right.
There's the mushroom cloud is an excellent example for that, right?
Because the material in the cloud and the smoke and the fire doesn't follow the shockwave.
It just goes up vertically.
So so this is in front of everyone again.
So what does this do when you start going and discovering the unintuitive, you put gives
you a little bit of an edge, doesn't it?
It puts you a little bit, uh, ahead of many things, you know, uh, in situations if it's
applicable or, you know, I can't see this very specific engineering part of the reality
and they haven't accounted for it, then it is a useful thing.
And it's an advantage because now you understand something that they're not accounting for
ever.
And, you know, uh, again, if it's something that consistently emerges, you have a definite
advantage because, uh, they're not accounting for it again.
You know, so yeah, but see, the thing is the part about intuition is supposed to supersede
now what you know about something that's supposed to work on a feeling and the people
that I've mentioned is the pressure, negative pressure building up in front of something
that's pushing.
They can't see it at all.
They just rather say, no, that can't happen, right?
So there's an interesting part of defending their ignorance, um, which is very interesting.
The other thing about intuitive is that's where, um, the, you know, we've been talking
about the emo a lot, right?
A lot of people, I've gotten some messages about the emo.
Some people think it's very powerful.
It is very powerful.
Some people still kind of like on the sideline with it.
Some people are kind of wrestling with it.
What, you know, what is it really?
Here's the thing.
And I came up with this analogy for someone I was speaking to recently.
The what the emo is, it's the energy.
When you have a thought, right?
And you want to perform that the thought, or let's say you have idea, idea comes before
thought, right?
Cause an idea is a flash, right?
I got this idea.
What is it?
And then the thought comes out, right?
Right.
Idea, thought.
And then the, the action, let's say there's even a few more steps there.
You have planning and action, right?
So yeah, I can give many analogies and that unnecessary.
It's pretty simple.
So what the emo does, it's the energy that provides, uh, that after the, the, uh, idea
and the thought come out, once you understand how to engage the emo, that provides the
energy for the rest of it.
And it sets up the energy.
That's why I was calling it a motivator, uh, in certain parts of that discussion, because
that's what it seems like, you know, motivator as in motive force.
Yeah.
It's a motive as in what is motive mean moves, but you need energy to move somehow, whether
it's, you know, free energy or any kind of, it's a fuel, but it's not, it doesn't in the
fuel to keep it, the emo going is the conviction.
Well, like look at it this way.
You can know how to do something.
You can have the idea to do it, but unless you have the desire to execute it, let's just
say, you know, you're, you're okay.
You're working in a room in the house and you discover that I should have something
here which would help me do it.
Uh, you know, and you have the idea, you have a practical application.
You have a concept, but unless you have a desire to create the thing and put it up in
that room, whether it's a shelf or it's a desire, I would say is beyond idea would be in the
thought category.
Okay.
You still need energy.
Yeah.
Right.
I'm thinking that that desire is in and of itself serves as part of the emo.
No.
Yeah.
The emo, I would say is more of the battery power that you need to fulfill the desire without,
without going physical.
Right.
So when, in other words, when you hit the juice on a light switch or a battery or whatever,
you don't really see it, you, but you, you don't see the juice, you just see what the
juice does.
Okay.
Right.
You don't see, nobody sees electricity even with a volt meter.
It's just seeing the volt meter.
So it's really the juice, uh, give me an example.
You have a desire to do something, you have a thought and you're working, you want to
do it, right?
And you get distracted.
Right.
And you, and then what was I doing?
Well, I need to go back to this.
But when you set up the emo, the distractions don't work.
You could actually keep doing what you're doing and handle the distraction better because
the emo controls the body.
Like we've given initially the example of mild mannered guy kills 15 people.
How is that possible?
Well, it's the emo that fueled it.
You see the power, right?
The power doesn't mean the actual, uh, physical manifestation.
It's just the power, you know, the battery doesn't provide or the hitting the light switch
on there.
There's nothing physical there.
But what do you mean?
There's nothing physical.
Greek.
It was dark.
Now it's light.
See, but there's nothing physical there.
In a way though, emo is always present though, in any of these actions, right?
Because again, if you have a desire to create something and then you do it, like I said,
and you have an idea.
I mean, I give a very general thing there, but at some point the emo is built into this.
Even if you're not thinking about it, it has, well, here's the thing, uh, like I've said
before many times with you and others, everyone is doing it anyway.
Right.
But here's the thing.
Uh, someone's not happy at their job and they've got an emo that they're not happy, but they're
still doing that job.
It's going to show them what they're doing and it's going to show on their health.
But if they somehow get it to the point where they can discipline themselves where the emo
is in line with what result they want, guess what's going to happen, right?
So in other words, you cannot avoid the emo.
It's just that we have it repressed and ignored and unacknowledged, right?
So there's a way to enhance your use of it, even though you're currently using it, whether
you have decided to or not bring up, bring it up, bring it up and specify what emo you
want.
We create a menu, right?
Make a menu for it and set yourself up.
It's like almost deliberately, uh, you know, when people are asked, why do you do this?
And they don't, you can't give you a straight answer or a clear answer or why they do something,
whether it's a custom or a belief or whatever.
Right, right.
Yeah.
It's, uh, it's kind of like, uh, it's that emo is the opposite of that.
It's like, cause if you ask someone why you believe this and they say, I'll tell you,
and they're very specific and cautious and everything is very detailed and if it's a
short amount of time or a long amount of time, they could, they could support what they're
telling you or their belief is, right?
The emo is like that support also.
So when you're going to do something, what emo it requires, you build in, you, you, you
discover or because it's a learning process because we live in a society where this is
not acknowledged at all other than, you know, happy, sad or angry or whatever, right?
Or affectionate, the rest, they, they don't discuss once you understand, uh, you're going
to perform a task.
What is the emo?
What is the best emotional state to be in to do this task?
Um, if you're distracted and the thoughts are distracted or your desire is distracted,
the emo still cannot be distracted.
It's, it's going to still, you could come back to it.
You see, if you don't, if you're not conscious of the emo, when you're distracted and the
distraction is over, you end up saying, well, what was I doing again?
What was I saying?
What was I supposed to be doing?
Right.
But once you have the emo in line at that, that power that carries, it's like leaving
the light, you leave, you leave the house and the lights are on, oh, I got to go back
and turn off the light.
It's very, it's very much in very, um, easy to perceive once you work with the emo, that
you're setting it up for yourself.
In other words, you're setting up your state that it's more than just what you're thinking.
See, and some people would use the word attitude to describe it, right?
Because your, your attitude while you're performing whatever task or while you're participating
in whatever activity or going to work or whatever, your attitude in and of itself changes the
way that that task goes, right?
Okay.
You've got a mindless, repetitive job.
If your attitude about it is not, this is mindless, repetitive, grinding me down.
If it's like that, it's going to be very exhausting.
It's going to be difficult to do.
You might even get it, but if you ask them what is attitude, they can't, people usually
don't answer.
It's an emotional state.
It's how you're set when you go into this, how you're set when you're going through it.
It does change the nature of that thing.
It does change the results.
It changes the experience altogether.
Right?
Well, it makes it, it, it, what it does, it's, um, it's really, this is a very interesting.
Here's the sad part.
And here's, here's the good part that we're discussing is the sad part.
There's nothing.
I've been looking around for this and the whole emo subject and it's, you can't find a discussion
anywhere on it.
Here, you know, it's in spatterings here or there.
In other words, where you separate and acknowledge that your emotional state that you choose
that you set yourself up for is a major part of, um, your, your manifestation in the world,
whatever you're doing.
Yeah.
Some of these like encouragement business people, you know, the life coach type people will
tell you this.
It may be, you know, your Tony Robbins type people, not necessarily him, but maybe he does.
I can't sit through it.
But it's attitude again.
But it's about the attitude.
But that's not emo though.
Is it?
Is it emo?
It's 50, 50.
I think it is.
It's kind of watered down.
Really?
Okay.
I think it is because look, if you go into, they tell you, set yourself this way, you
know, uh, perceived this way, feel this way.
But that you can be distracted from that though.
Well, it's different.
Like you're going to, the most, the basic example is when people say, send, you want
to send healing energy to this person and not doing well.
Okay.
So how do you send healing energy?
Well, you know, you set yourself up to feel like you're, you know, when you give someone
a hug, you only feel that giving feeling when you're giving us, if you know how to trigger
that feeling, that is the giving energy in the body.
You actually feel it.
Think about emo work your butt.
You can actually feel it in your body, right?
Then the energy, then it's now you're powering that thought and it has, and it actually will
carry over just like a wifi, for example, a very similar.
So these, I'm glad you brought up cause in the back, it was really in the far distance.
Like the, the, the life coaches, like Anthony Robbins stuff, they tell you have a positive
attitude, don't think negative, but that's not really emo, is it?
They don't tell you set yourself up for giving energy or guarding energy or, or an energetic
state, right?
No, they, their thing about energetic state is if you, if you believe you're going to
be successful, if you're just deciding you're going to be successful, you'll be successful,
which I think is an aspect of this.
It does.
Well, it does work on some levels, right?
They don't tell you how to do it.
That's why, but you know how you do that, by the way, and here's the thing, uh, you,
let me just preface this years ago, uh, and I have many witnesses, some more than a decade.
So I'm not doing anything anymore.
I have no desires here.
This is, I'm in the wrong freaking place.
I'm telling you, if I find out who sent me here, I'm going to kick them in the nuts.
Even if it's me and I have to kick myself in the nuts, right, somehow, right?
If they have nuts.
So that's how upset I am about being here, uh, in this reality, the way it is, um, and
the way it has been in the way it will be too, by the way.
Uh, but here's the, uh, part when you want something, and this works for everyone, by
the way.
Uh, and I've seen it happen many, many times.
I could give a hundred examples unnecessary.
When you want something, set yourself up as if you already have it and not never think
about how you're going to get it right.
Just set yourself emotionally as if you already there, right now, if you want to be the richest
man in the world, let's say, which is a stupid thing, whatever, uh, you, it may not work for
you at all because you see it's outside of the scope because the richest man in the world
is not the richest man in the world at all.
Really?
It doesn't exist.
So you have to be real things.
Um, I found this to be true where things came out of nowhere, um, and three months later
or six months later, I find myself in exactly a situation that I never imagined that would
be.
And you know, in terms of what I wanted to do, the main thing that people usually want
because they, this society is based on money.
If you just say, I want money, you're never going to get it because there is no money.
But if you got the money, what you're going to do with it, right?
Let's say you want a car, you want a house, you want this or that.
You just focus on the things that money will get you, not the money itself, and then you'll
get it.
You'll get those things.
Cause why?
Because you think the universe is dumb to think that there's money.
The universe knows that there's no money, but you, when you don't pay, let's say a bill
and they shut off the water, that's because he didn't have money, but there is no money.
So ignore that, that the, so you just want to, for example, someone who's having a hard
time, let's say just getting by, uh, the thing you would be set up as if you had infinite
amount of water, gas, power, whatever, whatever it was, what you call bills, right?
Infinite amount, not, not paying the bills cause you can't pay it.
No one's ever paid a bill in 70 years.
It's having an infinite supply and those things are ever present and you'll find it happening.
Somehow it'll be like, Oh my gosh, I can't believe it.
You know how it's all coming together.
I'm not worried about these things anymore.
So things that don't exist in reality, if you want them, guess what's going to happen
in reality.
They're not going to come because they don't exist in reality.
And if someone is, most of the people listening are not new, there is no such thing as the
richest man in the world cause there's no money in riches.
It's just who has more control or whatever.
And we don't even know who they are or what to model.
Right?
So something like that to the average person, this would sound insane.
What do you mean?
This guy on time magazine was the richest man in the world, right?
See, if you focus on that and you're never, you know, you're going to get it.
It's very simple.
Just more than imagination, the emo that you already have it or exist in that.
How would you feel?
Let's say you wanted something materialistic.
You only know most people when they say they want something, they only have the emo of
wanting that thing.
They don't never experienced the emo as if they already got it.
You know, that is a big difference there.
That's what the emo is about.
That's why, for example, again, the most rudimentary example I give on the emo, Oh, send healing
energy to that person.
Will you?
Everybody on this call or whatever.
You hear that all the time.
Right?
Right.
Okay.
When you set the emo up as if you are giving or receiving a hug, which you feel that rise,
even just now, if I stand up, I'm going to stand up and gesture giving someone a hug.
I feel a tingling sensation that goes up to the solar plexus and my legs are almost like
a warm feeling.
My legs feel really light, right?
That triggering, that's the, so when you have, you can trigger the body by just gesturing
a hug.
Even if you're alone, if you do that exercise enough, you can bring that up without doing
the physical gesture.
When you feel that in the body, that's like turning on the wifi, right?
Turning on making a cell phone call to that person.
And once you have an identifier for them, right?
And I said, you don't even know team.
So they are just asked the person that I'm sending this to, do they have anything that
makes them them?
Of course their spirit is unique.
And do they have any identifiers?
That's the one, the person that I was told to, you see, so, and then it works, right?
Then you have it.
Uh, I still get maybe once every 10 days or so, someone will give me a situation, uh,
with the emo.
They, and I want to, I'm just so happy.
The emo stuff worked for me.
This is what happened.
And this is what I did.
And this is, this is what I wanted to happen.
This is what I did.
And this is how it came out.
You know, it was like, great, great, great.
Yeah.
I'm glad it worked.
So, so anyway, the situation that people are in is because the general society is, well,
that call them the mushroom people, right?
You know what that is?
Keep them in the dark and feed them shit.
Right.
Yeah.
And, uh, then the other part of that is unacknowledged.
All the things that are unacknowledged, it's, it's, it's, um, something else to say that
they're ignorant of, because when I don't say they're ignorant of it, because let's say
you take someone who is ignorant and someone, this guy's not ignorant and he's got a doctorate
and whatever, you know, post whole digger PhD, right?
Whatever.
He's not ignorant, but he doesn't know about it either.
So it's not about ignorance for smarts.
It's about, is it acknowledged or not?
Right.
There's a big difference there.
Kind of like a lot of people mix up choices and decisions, right?
They interchange them.
They're not the same thing, right?
Very different.
You know, you go to a menu, they got 10 different sandwiches.
Those are your choices.
What do you decide?
Right?
People say, Oh, I'm even when you choose something, there's a big difference to deciding, right?
You see?
So all of these things tie in together.
By the way, before we go, there was someone I'm fond with also left a message.
He emails me frequently, left a message on the chat about flatbread.
I posted some pictures of food.
I messaged back on the flatbread.
Look up recipes.
And the thing is, look up recipes on making the Greek pitas and add yogurt and less yeast
if you're going to use yeast or no yeast.
But okay.
Now, here's the thing.
I like giving recipes and stuff.
But I also want people to be flexible and give feedback.
So in other words, when I say make something, I know there's some critical parts that if
you don't follow, it won't come out well.
I give those, right?
But I also like to see some feedback on another way of doing things, right?
So when you make the flatbread, by the way, you can just do water and flour and cook it
very quickly.
You may have a delicious flatbread, you know, non-yeasted.
And then you have all the other recipes in between that you could find online, which
most of them are pretty good.
I'm a no-knead.
I don't knead the bread at all.
I just mix it initially.
When everything's mixed, I let it sit.
Here's the critical part about anything that is going to have some rise to it, right?
This is not for Passover bread.
But you start it between 2 and 3 a.m. in the morning.
The atmosphere starts to expand, right?
It's at maximum expansion by noon or 1 o'clock, and by 2 or 3 o'clock in the afternoon, the
atmosphere does what?
It starts to contract, right?
It starts to go down, right?
So if you want whatever leavening you're using, a rising agent, to be most effective, start
your bread first thing you get up in the morning, right?
Presuming you get up early.
And then for lunch or for dinner to have it.
Because then, as the atmosphere is expanding, guess what your dough is going to do?
Naturally expand more, you see?
And that's the best way that I would suggest making anything that would have some rise
to it, is very early in the morning or very late at night.
This is why the real reason, you know, in the Northeast, again, where you and I spent
a bunch of time, this is why the bakeries always started to operate early in the morning.
They would begin baking, you know, because that's just the best time of day to do that.
Well, mainly it was commercial.
You want it to be as fresh as possible.
The people are going to start coming in the morning.
But it's happened to coincide with this phenomenon, which most people, you know, most people spend
their whole lives.
They don't think that, you know, in the middle, you know, let's say pre-dawn all the way to
noon, everything's expanding.
And then afternoon, in the afternoon, it starts contracting.
No one thinks that way.
Well, it seems to me that somebody might have thought that way to begin with, because I think
the commercial circumstance emerged after the natural circumstance just became, look, this
is commonly just the best time to do this.
And therefore, the commercial circumstance emerged around that, I think.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Just like breakfast is at the end of the day.
It's the last meal of the day.
Right.
When you fast for a day, you break your fast with breakfast because, right.
So yeah, very simple.
All right.