A sonic event rated Y, the number is 118, and here we go, Greek, the Middle East, and
God knows what else we could talk about, or the gods might know what else we could talk
about.
Maybe they do know.
By the way, is time even relevant to the gods?
I'm curious.
Of course.
They run everything backwards.
When they tell you the future, it's their history.
There you go.
There's an interesting scope with all that.
If you want to travel to another galaxy, you do it when you're here without moving.
There's a movie called, with Jodie Foster, Carl Sagan wrote a book, Contact.
She falls through the device, and to the perceivers on the ground, it looks like she didn't go
anywhere, but she went on a 13-hour journey, right?
That's how you go outside of here.
That's why when you read all the ancient texts about spirituality, they don't make any sense
from a linear perspective or a physical perspective.
That's why it's so important what you do.
Give you an example, I've been looking at Warren Buffet a lot lately, what I can get
old stuff 20, 30, 40 years ago.
Very interesting how he went the way of the fiat, he embraced the fiat currency system,
is proud to file taxes, proud to work with the Federal Reserve and all that, right?
Is there anything special about Warren Buffet, or is it just-
No, actually there isn't.
He's a good example.
No one ever talks about him in the, people, everyone knows he's famously rich, trillion
dollar company, Berkshire Hathaway, which was an old loom that was not a very good loom,
but he kept the name because it sounds authoritative, but he still lives in a house, a very modest
house, drives his own Buick, 1994 Buick, right?
So that's how I would be, by the way, and that's how I am.
I don't care about it at all, so he views it as a game, but what I think he does a big
disservice with is when he's asked about the overall picture, he stays away from it, right?
Which is fine.
That's what I do, I talk about the overall picture.
So he is worth like $700 billion or $400 billion personally, and his partner recently died
and all that, whatever.
He talks about the system as he works it, but everyone thinks that if they do what he
does and think like he does, they'll be like him.
It doesn't work that way.
The system is not made the way that everyone is talking about it, and I mean the majority
of the people.
It's kind of like, you got a busy bathroom where people take number two, you make sure
you have a lot of air freshener in there, right, to balance it out, but it doesn't really
balance it out because you know what's going on in there, right?
That's just the air freshener, let's get out of here because it really smells like shit.
And besides that, you get flowery smelling shitty things in the air.
Yeah, and that's exactly what the earth is and he doesn't talk about it.
I'll give you an example.
There was something he did in 1995, an interview, and he's pretty candid.
He knows what's going on, he just won't discuss it.
Someone said, you know, it's fiat currency, blah, blah, blah, went on that, let's say
point of view, and he says, yeah, it's basically the dollar is stock.
It's like holding a piece of stock coupon from a company, right, and if it's stock
is worth more, the dollar is worth more, and if you make too many dollars, it's like make
too many stocks for a company and dilute it, right?
So he does know.
Now, I'm against that because the system has prevailed now for over 100 years this way
and there's more poverty than there ever was.
People pay to the system the natural power.
Have you seen, I think it was Network, where they told basically he's too old, he's
washed up and he said a film and he goes on, he says, I'm mad, I'm not going to take it
anymore. Very famous.
Oh, yeah, that's yeah.
Yeah. And they basically told him, you know, what you did there on TV is going against
the powers, the natural powers that be, meaning people control the world.
Right. And he tells them there are no countries, there are no this and that.
There are just corporations and that's all there is to it.
It's all about things that are bought and sold.
So, yeah, ideas and all that.
Yeah. So Buffett can never get into that, but he doesn't he doesn't know how it works.
Now, personally, I am against the way the system is set up.
I think I briefly went over yesterday where the money they're actually literally the
money people are playing God because they create the money based on what collateral
they hold. Well, and they demand people to work for, you know, a banker and the banker
will make more money on a house than anyone else.
And they're dictating the behaviors of everybody on the planet, basically, by
controlling. Now they are now more than ever.
Give me an example. Like Kennedy could have been taken out in his sleep and said he
died of a heart attack. And it would have been very plausible because he took quite a
few. He was very famously known in many circles to be experimenting with drugs of all
kinds. He was also getting shot up with a lot of drugs by a doctor.
It could have been very easily.
Yeah. Too many famous doctor, Dr.
Feelgood. Yeah. The guy they call Dr.
Feelgood. Right. Right.
True. Him and Jackie, by the way.
But but good. Yeah.
Yeah. And all and all our friends.
Yeah. So so he would have been very plausible that he died.
But why did they do a public assassination?
Because they just want to tell you that the things you think of are not so right.
And they have to make it loud, just like 4th of July.
Ask people what's 4th of July.
Oh, it's fireworks, hot dogs, hamburgers, barbecue.
Because that's the loudest thing.
Right. They don't understand.
It's all set up. So basically, on the last Sonic, I mentioned that if we went to the
bankers and demanded that they from the collateral that, OK, when a poor person in
America or any Western country is born, their credit, their birth certificate is worth
just as much as the wealthiest person.
Right. It's all equal.
So Warren Buffett, it's around six million dollars.
Yeah. Warren Buffett is allegedly an American businessman.
So therefore, his birth certificate is worth the same amount as mine is.
If, say, at the time of his birth certificate, he would have been the son of like a
radio person who was an editor of a magazine and a homekeeper.
Yeah. So it doesn't matter if Bill Gates has a baby right now or someone like that or
the prince of whatever their child is worth six million to the state.
Actually, the Social Security Act between 1935 and 1942 amended, you'll find what I'm
saying. It talks about the birth certificate being goes from six hundred fifty
thousand to five million to six million.
Right. For the state collateral.
So if you go to the banks and say we have a birth certificate file, this guy needs
credit. So he's not poor anymore.
You know, they talked a little bit about universal income, right?
And all that stuff. But they're using their words.
Yeah. You have a universal basic income and it's supposed to be.
Look, you have a certain allowance basically each month.
And that's just to it.
Yeah. Yeah. That would be horrible when it's done by them.
Because if you say something that they don't like, they prevent you from getting food
the next month. It'll be worse.
Yeah. It's always worse.
Right. You're cut off. And now there's no way to even turn around and hustle around
that because either you got it or you don't.
Yeah, it's the social credit system.
So it'll get worse and worse and worse, no matter who says it's a benefit.
So there's this idiot.
What's his name? I was looking some stuff at marketing.
Godin, he's a bald headed Jewish guy with funny colored glasses.
What's his name? But he's Jewish.
I mean, he's super Jewish, whatever that is.
The multi hedge fund guy or the.
No, no, no. So Godin, he talks about marketing.
OK, this is this is a segue.
But just give us a stupid these people that everyone looks up anyway.
Godin, he's a marketing guy, talks about, you know, integrity and all this other stuff.
Anyway. OK, he gets he's doing this thing, the most important thing in his life is the
carbon thing because we're destroying the world.
And he says, well, whenever he hears a leaf blower, Seth Godin, whenever he hears a
leaf blower, his is his blood boils.
Right. Because of the carbon.
Right. This is what the idiot doesn't know.
Oh, God. He's vegetarian.
So when he goes to a Chinese restaurant locally, because one of the things he mentions, he
likes it's vegetarian fried rice when they prepare a medium to large size order of fried
rice from him. When that walk is blasting at 300000 BTUs, 200000 BTUs
to prepare that meal for him uses more carbon fuel than a medium
sized leaf blower going for eight hours constantly.
I mean, that's how efficient that little engine is.
Right. OK, so so here he is giving a public
anti virtue of using, you know, in his office, in his office, writing the carbon
newsletter. He hears in the neighborhood, you know, someone using a leaf blower, his
blood boils because it's destroying the environment.
He doesn't know that when he goes orders his vegetarian meal, that one meal is used
more energy than that leaf blower going for eight hours straight.
Oh, yeah. What am I what what's my point here?
Right. It's sort of like the people that say cryptocurrency will be a great thing for the
environment because now you don't have to print paper and all this other stuff.
And now it's not even on paper.
It's caught. Yeah, well, it's recycled.
Caught. It's made in North Korea, by the way.
But the worst thing is, is that this crypto stuff, they go, oh, no, it's on the
blockchain and therefore it'll save the environment.
OK, if you take a look at the farms that they have to use in order to mine that crap, it
actually puts way more wasted energy out there than anything.
Well, you could print a billion dollars.
You could print one. Hold on.
But let's let's I want to add to what you're saying.
Forget about just crypto.
Anything that has a thousand, two thousand, ten thousand percent profit is intelligence
agency operations.
Absolutely. Drugs were not that profitable until the intelligence agencies got involved.
When were they not involved?
Well, you know, let's say after the 50s and 60s.
Do you know, like you can make enough LSD to get the entire world tripping for less than
a hundred dollars. Oh, back then.
Yeah, easily. I don't know about now or even now.
I mean, yeah, you know, the you know, the entire world.
That's that's how cheap it is.
Right. In reality, the same with.
OK, there's a bunch of.
OK, so the same thing with Warren Buffett.
He talks about these things that sound great.
But if you look at what he's saying from a scientific point of view, they don't make
any sense. Right.
So but if you did equalize and got rid of poverty and misery that can be remedied by
money, which is mostly thing, everything tie into the medical, how that has to be
done and why then having money won't be that valuable.
Right. So Ferrari and all the luxury, all the items in neighborhoods go away.
So you have to restructure society, which is going to happen anyway.
Now, the medical system, a lot of people say, oh, we don't need to give millions and
billions because the NIH already spending a million billions on research.
This is how medical research is done.
Guys, don't be fooled by it.
If you go work in medical research, you're encouraged to play video games and watch
porn on the job because they don't want you doing medical research.
Right. The way that it works is you're given a list that go back to who's the guy that
decided how medical research is going to go.
He's got a funky name, 1902, 1912.
Anyway, you could.
Yeah, he's the guy who decided that there will be no new practices used in medicine.
He said this in 1912, only existing practices.
Right. So that means there's no research and there isn't.
Because what you're when you do medical research, this is the standard practice.
And can this be applied to this standard practice?
Right. So, for example, if you listen to Greek speak, we can go out with no money and
topple the entire medical industry for every disease that the first of all, 75 percent
of what they call diseases do not exist.
They're created by being diagnosed with such a thing and taking the treatment.
Right. So we only have to deal with 25 percent of what people think makes them sick and
with no cost at all, including sewing arms and limbs and doing transplants, effectively
no money at all. Research.
I mean, we could we could get a bunch of people that are well versed in Greek speak and
go around and do a tour in six months and the whole world won't be sick anymore except
for, you know, a minor amount. Right.
And trauma. Very simple.
So, again, the same with the money.
It's not about that.
And the money and the medical are tied in together because of the insurance business.
OK, now to go back to what you're saying about the crypto and then the carbon and all
the things in the Middle East, this all ties in.
Do you remember burning down of the rainforest?
That was a big deal, right?
Yes. In the 80s.
OK, that was all propaganda.
First of all, give you a little history.
Brasilia, when they wanted to they wanted to expand Brazil.
Brazil is totally developed on the coast.
The rest of its forest, river and whatever.
There's some desert, too.
But they wanted to expand the country.
So if they put the capital, Brasilia, the new capital in the middle of the rainforest
area, everyone will go there.
That didn't work. Right.
First of all, they hired Western architects.
They built these apartment complexes like you would see a modern apartment complex, small
little kitchen, living room, dining room, bedrooms.
Right. Got you. Didn't didn't work.
The people's culture doesn't work that way.
What they did is they went to the apartments and they said, well, we all gather around
where we eat. So they bought these portable burners and put them in the middle of the
living room, did all their cooking in the living room.
The narrow kitchen became a storage closet for clothing.
Right. They could they like to.
Right. You see what I mean? It didn't work at all.
OK, just an example.
Now, the reason you've heard of the 2030 environmental stuff, right.
They want to put smart cities, get people.
OK, well, that started with the burning of the rainforest.
No one needed to burn in you.
And rainforest does not burn like they said.
The same people who did covid 9-11, JFK, whatever, says, look, let's implement this.
Actually, I'm not going to mention any names, Jim Carton.
But anyway, his dad was one of the guys I know personally.
His dad was one of the guys that after World War Two, Marcos in the Philippines was very
instrumental in knowing where certain things were hidden, technologies, gold and all that.
But from the Japanese and all this other stuff.
Right. Underworld people he protected.
He wouldn't cooperate with the CIA.
So what they did was they, Jim Carton's dad, not to mention his name, went into the
Philippines with about 50 other CIA, 100 CIA and over a period of three months told
people, if you show up on this day, you get ten dollars.
Just all you have to do is show up at the Capitol.
So they got over 30,000 or actually 10 or 15,000 people.
Very much. And each got 10 bucks each, which is a lot of money back then.
And remember, money's printed.
Right. And they got them to protest in front of the Capitol like they wanted Marcos
ousted. So the CIA comes in with a helicopter and saves Marcos.
Right. You see what I mean?
So protests staged.
Yeah, I gotcha. Yeah.
Publicly, it looked like the U.S.
saved him. Right. You know.
Right. But actually, they're the ones that created the protests because he didn't want to
deal with them at all. And you know what happened after that.
So and the famous shoe incident and all that.
It's all distraction. Right.
What they did, these people, they went in and started burning the rainforest.
Like if you watch like a movie where, you know, it's supposed to be a theater full
of people and they only show like 10 or 15 seats because that's all the extras they want
to afford. And you supposed to in your imagination, imagine the theater is full because
they show you a stock photo of a full theater.
Right. And they play a little noise that makes it sound like there's a lot of people in
there. Yeah. So they started burning some areas of the forest down, saying trying to
create that national international outrage that, look, we need to pass laws to preserve
nature. It had nothing to do with the rainforest.
They were not burning down the rainforest.
They yes, they did make fires just like you can.
You know, they shot Kennedy in the World Trade Center was demolished.
Same people over and over.
No, same group, not same people because of the age differences in the locale.
Well, eventually people died.
But yeah. So what they want, which they got is international interest to protest.
That's so each country now can have laws that you can't cut.
You can't cut down a tree.
You can't burn wood.
You can't write. Sure.
It failed, though it failed because there was benefactors and people inside the group
that said, you know, if we use the sentiment that we've garnered by enraging the
international community, international audience about this and they notice that we doing
all these laws now in their own places and there was no rainforest fires really were the
ones that set them. It's not time yet.
It's not necessary.
So the 2030 agenda about the environment, the carbon tax is attached to the burning of
the rainforest. That's the history.
The same people, same agenda.
I just want to put this out. You can follow this.
Also, it was the birth of something called Greenpeace.
They would block whaling ships and all that.
Right. And they were actually, I think, recently, maybe 20 years ago or recently, they
would declare it a terrorist organization.
And that's right. So environmental terrorism, whatever.
So there's like none of these plans seem to work and they won't because we're in the
credits part of the society.
Right. But the reason I'm bringing this up is because all these things are tied
together. I grew up in the 70s.
I remember watching was that Leonard Nimoy in search of right.
Yeah. Planet of the Apes, Laverne and Shirley, Happy Days.
And there was something called Connections on PBS.
British guy. And he would start off talking about how does this thing lead to that?
And he would spend a whole hour showing you how one thing ties to the next.
Remember that? Yeah. OK, that's kind of like my own version of Connections, the
rainforest, cryptocurrency, what's happening in Gaza, all this stuff.
OK, there's a lot of credence, by the way, to bounce over to what Jason Breshears has
been putting out because I pointed, you know, given him ample time here on this
platform to say, hey, go look, people are listening.
Let me go listen to what he's saying, because it's a lot of it's very worthwhile.
You've stressed his chronology is good.
Right. Yeah, it's pretty good.
Yeah. It's not airtight, but no one's is really is.
But, you know, I see mine is more tight than his, but it's one or the other.
They're both good. So go look at what he talked about happening this year with all
this stuff going on in the Middle East to bring in this other seal, which would be
basically what you will be seeing.
And I brought this up, but not as direct.
The next thing you'll be seeing other than the covid is knife, small arms attacks, knife
attacks at churches, small venues.
And they'll be caught and it'll always be Middle Eastern men enraged about what
Israel's doing and the Western support.
Right. So American churches, radio stations, little, little venues, schools will be
attacked by these men.
Well, that's the next agenda.
Yeah, it happened a couple of days ago in what they call England.
You know, there was a couple of England is a big one.
Yeah. Like all of these people that are being sent what they call refugees or
whatever and migrants, they're all soldiers, they're all soldiers.
In other words, when you leave, you don't leave your wife and children behind, you
know, right. And they're also given big pockets of money by this by these.
OK, with Libya and other people like the people that supported the Obama and the
Western stuff, Afghanistan, when you the it's not really a lottery, but the American
State Department, when they find people that supported the Americans in Afghanistan,
Libya, Somalia, whatever, they said you can immigrate.
We'll give you a visa and a green card and your citizenship.
Come to the U.S.
What they that's very well known.
Right. The open businesses of what's not well known is that a good amount of them get
four hundred thousand dollar debit cards, just like they were giving ten thousand
dollar debit cards to the migrants in New York.
That's normal. That's like pittance.
That's why when you live in a medium sized city like I'm in Tucson, you'll see all
the used car dealerships now are Afghanis that have been here for less than 10 years.
You need at least a quarter of a million dollars to open a used car dealership.
The bond alone is one hundred thousand dollars.
Right. Right. They opened the 7-Elevens and all that.
And you can I know someone who opened a convenience store back in the 80s and it was
50 grand minimum.
Yeah. So now it's got to be one hundred and fifty two hundred.
Right. A few years ago, a Dunkin Donuts was precisely one million dollars.
That's what you needed. All in everything.
You had your Dunkin Donuts.
Million dollars. Yeah.
Well, McDonald's now is six hundred thousand and you have to have not borrowed and all
that. So OK, but either way, Dunkin Donuts is terrible now, by the way, they don't make
their donuts anymore. They're brought in from then.
They're made of they have silicone.
I got some recently and I like to warm up a donut.
It tastes better and it would not warm up and change.
It's it's it's nasty chemical stuff.
So anyway, speaking, let's just do a little segue.
I want to go to the chat.
Coffee still tastes good, though, I got to tell you.
But go ahead. George asked about the pan cake recipe.
Now, the difference between pancakes and pan cakes.
Now, pancake is a pancake.
The pancake. Yeah, whatever.
You need a lot of syrup and butter.
Hopefully using real syrup and real butter.
But we know what that is.
But then there's pancake, which is like a wonderful sponge cake.
It's literally like, you know, when you buy a cake like a strawberry shortcake or
something like that, or a vanilla cake, a three layer, a multilayer cake, it's the
cake is very different than a pancake.
Right. Yes.
And that's what you know, that's what the pancake pan cake recipe is asking for.
Now, what you do with that to start off, depending on your skills, I'll give the three
points that you need. You need a freezer.
You need and not for the reason why one would sound like you need a freezer.
You need some almond flour or almond flour.
Depends if you say aunt or aunt.
Right. And you're going to need some high altitude wheat or whole wheat flour.
OK, so what you do is if you already using a premix pancake mix like a Trader Joe's
one is pretty good. Multigrain or whatever.
You may not need the whole wheat, but I would still have it a little bit.
And you definitely need the almond flour.
So whatever pancake mix you use and even like the shittiest kind, it still works.
OK, when the mix is dry, add your almond flour and whole wheat to at a rate of 30
percent for both.
So you'd have two thirds of whatever pancake mix you use.
And the other third is a mixture of the whole wheat and almond flour.
And when you add your liquid, pre dilute your liquid with some yogurt, at least a
teaspoon or tablespoon of yogurt, more yogurt than you'd think you'd normally use.
And you mix it up.
Now, here's the point.
Don't over mix it.
You just stir it until some lumps are OK.
They go away. Now, what you do is you put it in the freezer for about two minutes.
The reason why has nothing to do with temperature.
If I said you need a vacuum chamber instead of a freezer, most people would say, well,
they don't have a vacuum chamber.
Right. For most people, if you have a fridge, you have a freezer.
Right. Right. Ninety nine percent of the time nowadays.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
So what you do, the reason why you put it in the freezer is to really air it out and
creates a tremendous amount of leavening effect or airiness.
Why have you ever been locked by hopefully by accident?
Have you ever walked into a walk in freezer box and the door closes and you can't get
out? Yes.
OK, what's the first thing you notice after about 30 seconds?
You can't breathe or it's hard to breathe.
OK. You remember that?
Maybe it wasn't more than 30 seconds for you.
Yeah, no, it was.
I remember feeling really weird about it because I felt the air kind of you couldn't
breathe. Yeah. Yeah. They're sucked out of there.
What happens is as the temperature drops, you creates a vacuum.
Yeah. Air contracts.
OK. Yeah.
So that vacuum on the on the pancake mix for about one or two or three minutes will
create a tremendous fluffy.
You don't want to stir it after that, by the way.
So that it will. In other words, the CO2 gas that you get from the baking soda that
makes things light and airy will expand.
No, you cannot, by the way.
No matter what kind of leaven you use, how fluffy and moist the pancakes are, if you
do not put it in a vacuum chamber or a freezer for two minutes, you cannot get that
type of bubble, that type of bubble in the cake can only come by mechanical vacuum.
I see. And that's the secret.
That's literally that's right there.
That's like, OK, that's a secret.
You could open a pancake house with what I just told you and sell pancakes for
where I've had some people come over and eat whatever.
Yeah. And you know what they when they taste it.
You know what they say to me? I mean, people that know business, you can you can
make a lot of money selling this after one bite.
Nice. Right.
OK. I mean, it doesn't matter what you know, like that's if you taste my chicken.
First thing someone from San Francisco said, you're going to make you could make a
lot of money selling this chicken or same with the pancakes.
You can make a lot of money selling because there's nothing like it.
Nothing like it. So that's the secret.
How do you get the let you see the quality of the sponge?
It's called sponge, by the way. Right.
The cake. Yeah. When you're baking, it's the cake itself is called the sponge.
Right. So the quality, you know, it's like the space between the bars defines the
cage. It's the bubbles and the cavity in the sponge that defines the sponge.
Right. Otherwise, it's just the start to compacted.
Right. Yeah. Then it's just so.
Yeah. Yeah. So the way it's created with the vacuum or putting it in the freezer for
two or three minutes is so unique and you will never experience anything like it.
Also, the almond flour with heat releases moisture.
So as you're cooking, you know, if you overcook something that's bread like where it
gets dry. Oh, absolutely.
And not just on the outside and crispy.
I'm talking about just tastes dry, just dry all the way through.
Yeah. Yeah. But when you do when you use the almond flour, which is a flour, it
actually the more you heat it, guess what happens?
The more moisture it releases.
So by the time it gets to your plate and whoever is going to eat it, it's still hot.
You know, if something is still hot on your plate, guess what?
It's still cooking. Right.
Right. So actually, your last bite will be moisture, more moist than your first bite.
And you're scratching your head.
Why? Because when things sit on a plate, they don't taste as good as when they were
freshly served. These are like magic cakes.
And I'm not exaggerating.
Anyone who does this will find it.
Now, you don't even have to be proficient and highly skilled to experience what I'm
saying. OK, the yogurt is also part of the leavening because something about the
culture in the yogurt reacts with the leavening.
But I say leavening is the existing baking soda or baking powder mix in the premixed
pancake mix. Notice I didn't get into making a pancake mix at all.
Use a premade one. Don't go get the aluminized entremime or by the way, Wal-Mart
used to have a good one that had everything in it.
You could actually live while they had powdered eggs, powdered milk, powdered egg
whites, powdered yolks.
Never heard of that. It was loaded with protein, like 11 grams of protein.
And they stopped making it's the kind of pancake mix you take with you when you go
camping. All you need is some water and you got like a whole, you know, it's loaded
with protein. It was in a bottle of cream, powdered milk, powdered yolk, powdered
white. I've never seen that so much protein loaded in a cake mix.
It looked like a small, it looked like a small detergent bottle, if I remember right.
Right. No, it was a box.
Oh, because I remember there's some more wholesome ones.
You could even do this with the cheap Bisquick one.
There's a whole, you know, Bisquick one has a very metallic flavor to it.
They use a really cheap aluminized baking soda.
I don't like Bisquick.
Yeah, I don't either. Yeah. But it'll still work.
I've experimented with the crappiest.
Yeah. And I'm not going to get into making a pancake mix from scratch because you need a
sifter. If you don't sift your leavening, you're going to, it's not going to taste very
good. You need a sifter. So I'm not going to get, I'm actually giving the easy route.
Any pancake mix that you already use that, you know, the kind that just says, and by
the way, if you have a pancake mix, it's like the trader just says, add an egg.
Do not add an egg. Do not add, never add eggs to pancake mixes.
Well, you could. It makes it rubbery because when you overcook an egg, it turns
rubbery. I don't care what style of cooking on the egg you do.
Sunnyside up, I'm aware, I guess, rubbery.
Right. Right.
So the amount of time that it takes to properly cook a pancake is way beyond the amount
of time to properly cook an egg.
So you're going to have rubbery pancakes.
Never add eggs to pancakes unless it's already in there in powdered form.
Just want to state that. Have you guessed that I'm a food aficionado?
Yeah. Anyway.
Yeah. You won't hear this. I mean, that's why what really got me on communicating how
to prepare delicious food was in the 90s when I started seeing there was a boom of
chefs on TV. And I said, sir, I feel great.
Finally, I could because when I go and eat at other people's homes, it was terrible.
When I first started dating my wife, she wanted to introduce me to people and I'd show
up late. Come pick me up at six.
We're going to dinner. I'd be here at six.
Fifty because you're late. I said, why are you late?
I said, because I ate dinner. She goes, why are you dinner?
We're going for dinner. You'll see.
Yeah, you'll see.
I don't eat. These are white people.
I ain't going to eat. You know, I say white people.
OK. Yeah. It's not the color of your skin.
It's the food. What they buy.
What's what they consider to be food is so processed, so denatured that I can't eat it.
I won't. Right.
I'd rather go without. So anyway.
So the reason I got into this is because after I was watching in the 90s and early 2000,
all these cooking shows, I said, oh, my gosh, no one is going to learn how to cook.
Watch. There's no one communicating fine points and what needs to be done.
So, again, the secret on the pan cake, it's not pancake, it's pan cake,
because it's just like a wonderful sponge cake.
Like it's like wedding cake.
It's like eating wedding cake pancakes.
Right. You know, the reason I stress the wedding cake part is how many times do people buy
wedding cakes? You're supposed to once.
Right. Usually, you know, some wedding cakes cost five grand.
Right. Maybe more.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. I mean, I didn't go that.
Yeah. And I'm not just talking because they're fancy when they make a wedding cake.
They really stress the sponge.
Got to be really high quality.
So everything will be of that quality.
Yeah. You make sure that that thing is presented.
Well, it's late.
You know, it's swarmed the quality and the flavor, the texture, everything on that has
to be right, you know, with a wedding cake.
So that's what you got.
So anyway, that's the secret.
The secret is the yogurt, the almond flour, some wheat flour.
The wheat flour gives it structure and nuttiness.
And it must after you do a mild stir.
And when you stir pancake mix, always stir from bottom to top, not just left to right.
Because if you have a strata in there where things are leveled, you know, things in
different stress, some things are at the top and things at the bottom.
If you start left to right, you're not going to get the stuff on the top to mix with the
stuff on the bottom. But if you start top to bottom, drop it, lift and then drop and
lift. You're going to not only get your left and right going, but you're going to get
everything on the top mixed evenly.
Right. Yeah, that makes sense.
Yeah. Always start top to bottom.
When you have a thick, starchy mixture, never stir it like you see on TV.
Don't stir it like you stir sugar and coffee.
Perfect. If the mixture is thick, you always stir top to bottom.
Right. So I learned that from an artist who worked with ink Pantone's and when they
would mix the paints, it wouldn't be.
You know how paints are mixed.
They drop a drill. You know, it's got the paint mixer spins, you know, left to right.
Right. Everything was always mixed top to bottom, you know, bottom to top, you know,
that way to get because it was a much thicker mixture, a gouache kind of stuff anyway.
And I said, well, that's how I'm going to do my pancake mixer.
Like what? I'm like, never mind.
I got it. You know, this is perfect.
In other words, mixing top to bottom is the least amount of energy you have to put into
the mixture to get the most amount of mix.
It's the most efficient way.
The other more efficient way, if you is, is you just pour it from one container to the
next and let gravity do it for you.
That's another way. And then you have a spatula, you know, like a squeegee spatula, you
know, what do they call those silicone spatulas, rubber spatulas that bakers use a lot.
Yeah. Use a spatula. I call it the squeegee.
And you get one container to the cleaning.
We don't want to be wasteful at all.
You could pour it from one to the experiment with your but if you have a tendency to whip
things into a frenzy, just pour the mixture left and right to two equal sized
containers and spatula and it goes into the freezer for a minimum of two or three
minutes. If you start going for more than two or three minutes, the freezing aspect of
the freezer takes over because you can't fight the cold in a freezer.
Right. It's just minus 20 and better.
What will happen is you'll start changing the chemistry and you you'll end up you'll get
a clear liquid on top.
That means you've failed.
Right. If you go, let's say you leave it in there for 10 minutes.
OK. Right. Because you got to answer the door.
You'll come back and you'll see is a clear liquid on top.
If you do get that because you left it in the freezer, just sprinkle some powder, some of
the pancake mix with the leavening on it and do another quick stir.
Take it out. You're ready to go.
So I just gave you the trouble to fix if you run into that.
There you go. So there's the secret of the pan cake and the troubleshooting fix in case
you happen to screw it up a little bit.
You can always you can always get it back.