And if your devices are charged and running, you are getting another sonic event.
This is the Greek, and here's Chuck.
Hey, Chuck.
Hey, we're breaking the pattern, right?
Everybody went, wait a second.
Yeah, yeah.
Rated Y.
You're listening to Rated Y because, well, and it's the unculting of humanity.
You know, we've never really brought up that slogan.
I guess you could call it a slogan, the unculting of humanity.
I was trying to explain this the other day to some people that someone described something
as a cult.
I said, wait a second.
All of humanity is in a cult.
So when someone tries to do something different, they're called a cult, right?
But of course, that has negative connotations and all that.
And they usually go along the negative connotation side.
But all of humanity, folks, the entire surface, and probably below the surface as well, has
been cultified big time.
Yeah.
Well, and that's the thing.
It's like a series of cults, honestly.
That's what I see.
And the funny thing is, by the way, there's this cartoon, I think, called Teenage Euthanasia
or something.
Or maybe it's not that one.
Maybe it's another one.
But this character actually utters in the trailer the unculting.
You know, the unculting.
Recently?
How old is that?
It's pretty new.
It's like just this year, yeah.
And it's kind of funny.
I saw it, and then I checked out the synopsis a little bit.
And the funny thing is, it's a comedy based on this girl, I think, that is inheriting
her father's cult.
It's all comedy.
You better keep it in comedy because you don't want the tragedy.
By the way, you know, tragedy means you know the outcome and you go through with it anyway,
right?
Oh, yeah.
You know it.
You know it's going to turn.
That's the point of the tragedy, actually.
That's why when people say, oh, it's a tragedy.
I go, really?
So you didn't expect it to turn out that way?
Yeah.
But the comedy is supposed to be funny.
It isn't always, right?
Well, comedy used to have a slightly different meaning, didn't it?
You know, speaking of meanings.
It's a Greek.
It's just a ancient Greek word for theater.
But yeah.
Right.
Exactly.
So speaking of meanings, somebody emailed me about this, you know, the story of the
10 plagues in the Bible.
And I asked him to clarify the question, but it's just an interesting thing they brought
up.
So that's supposed to be clarified.
But go ahead.
Well, no, but I wanted the question clarified so I could ask it properly because it was like,
you know, good.
Default.
Default is this.
Anything that's old.
OK, what's old?
Pre 1920, pre 1890.
All right.
Why is it out in public?
There's such a thing called an FBI book seizure list.
It was really hot and popping up until the 60s, by the way.
That's right.
And yeah.
So why are they why are they allowing it on the surface?
Right.
So here's the thing.
I used to be called a Bible guru and all that.
Yeah, I'll take that.
Yeah.
Well, you know, whatever.
And other compliments.
Thanks for the flowers.
Right.
But what I'll say is, yeah, you know, ethereal ones.
But this is what I'll say.
When we talk about something that sounds like it's talking
about that something.
Right.
So what I mean by that is there's no religion on the planet
that's doing anything or knows anything pretty much.
It's in the text that they allege to subscribe in.
Same with academia.
Go look at an academic textbook.
It's the current philosophy, political twist on it.
Right.
Yeah.
On a textbook.
Right.
And not what's held in research or libraries, let's say.
So when we talk about, let's say, anything in the Bible,
three things come up.
The first is, why?
Why did they leave it out?
Right.
And it's going to it's a double edged sword.
It's a brainwashing tool.
But at the same time, it's a foundation for what they're
how they decide to operate.
You know, the classic part of society or conservative part
of society.
The other thing is you're not really getting you're getting
a redacted, altered version.
And then the other thing is, why should you take interest?
Right.
So the majority will probably take interest because what
cults do is they they have to offer choices, but it's
the choices that they offer.
Right.
So when you look at the major religions, they're they all
come from the same place.
Power structure.
So if you don't like Christianity, you go to Judaism
or Islam or Hindu or Buddhist.
All those are heavily controlled and heavily, you know,
however, modified.
Right.
I like that.
Modified.
Yeah.
And then you have no choice.
It's you know, you see that all the time.
So you see these white Christian people and they are
disenchanted and they go to become Buddhism and they know
nothing about Buddhism in their whole life.
And because, you know, that's just for most people, these
I don't know, proclivities, your religion, your political
stance, whatever that's been given to you as a choice.
And you have no choice because it's coming from the same
place.
Now, here's what they all have in common, whether it's
academia, science, politics, history, the Bible, anything
like that.
What people.
You know, they're they're they're they're they're they're
when people bring up a subject that any of those things that
I mentioned, it's always the du jour current
political spin on that, right?
It's never what's actually been memorialized in the
text.
It's important to look.
I've had someone a couple of people during my lifetime
say, oh, I don't need to, you know, books to learn.
You know, I'm like, it's not the book.
What if it was a completely digital right
on the screen?
What if it was oral to tradition?
What if it was?
It's not just information that if I can access, you can
thing, which, by the way, is going away now that they're digitizing books, by the way.
Oh, of course. Yeah. And we're not talking about like the scanning of books where you still see
the original print. I'm talking about they're just you know, they're not they're rewriting
them essentially slowly. They're not going to do it in shock, you know, shock that many people,
even though it wouldn't matter. But yeah, I don't think here's the thing. I got into the Bible
because of the law form. And then as I tiptoed around everything else, I found out whatever
popular story, the 10 plagues, the burning bush, there's no burning bush, by the way.
It's an angel that was on fire, and he put the bush between him and Moses and
the fire did not consume the bush. There's no burning bush. It's a burning angel.
So anyway, crucifixion was an easy one. Actually, that's the most difficult one because
it's been so put through society. Right. That it's very hard to get over that, that there is
no crucifixion. Right. So based on understanding of what the text says. Right. So and it doesn't
matter if it's Mel Gibson or it's, you know, an open stage play during the Dark Ages that's going
on in order to, you know, memorialize this story. It's still a story. It's not actually based on the
text at all, at all. Nothing is. Now, look at lately what I've been hammering on is, quote,
unquote, the health field, biology, more biology than the health field. Right. Because
there's good biology, bad biology or whatever. But if you start off with anatomy,
like you do normally in that field, you know, right. If you study the anatomy, you'll see
there's no way all those those tissues are impervious. Right. Whether it's skin, long
intestine, organ tissues are all impervious. There are ducts that communicate in and out.
There's orifices and things like that. I like that word orifice anyway. So when they tell you
things are absorbed or when they tell you this process happens, but then they when something
appears this way, then this process occurs. But they skip everything in between because
everyone just says fine. In other words, where do the play? How do the where the
platelets come from? Never discussed. Right. Never discussed how the nutrition gets into the
body. Oh, it's absorbed. Oh, just two words. That's it. Don't ask questions on how it works.
Right. So let's just look at anatomy and see that it's impossible for anything to go. Well,
it's not impossible for anything to go through the tissue. If it does, you won't be living very
long. It's called sepsisemia. You'll die. Toxicity that which happens, by the way, also.
But essentially, there's nothing. It's all energy, all 100 percent energy. Basically,
if you want to know how it works, just leave the biology department or medical department and walk
down the campus to the electrical engineering, maybe or right or physics, maybe physics and
sit down and look about induction and learn about that and then go back. By the way, you know what
you learn in university about electricity. I think we've done this before. Let's do it again. It's
worthwhile. Sure. If you want to learn about electricity, you go to two places in university.
One is the physics department. The other one's electrical engineering. Two buildings opposite
each other. Right. So the physics, you know, they look at the circuit and they just study the
negative part, the ground. And the positive is just mark plus, let's say, plus one. So you put
a plus one. I mean, I'm sorry, just the ground, which is a negative. So they put a minus one on
the building. Go across the street to electrical engineering. They're studying the positive side
of the circuit. Everything goes to ground. Right. They ignore that pretty much. It's negative.
I just, you know, shunt the ground. Right. So you put a positive one on that building. So physics is
minus one and the electrical engineering is positive. What do you get when you put plus one
and minus one together? You get zero. And that's exactly what you're going to learn about that in
college. Right. And that's exactly the truth. That's what they're doing. The physics studies,
the negative and the one and the electrical engineering studies, the positive one. Right.
Put them together. What do you get? It's exactly what you're going to get with your university
education. Now, they'll say, oh, I'm calling bullshit on that Greek because my dad's an
electrical engineer. So am I. We work. Yeah, exactly. What you're going to learn is how to
work in industry. And that's it. And when I say industry, is anything from, you know, motorized
erector set. Young people even know what that is. Those are the worst things to get. Get those for
Christmas when I was young, because you just ended up with you need a box of Band-Aids, right?
Yeah. For that. It was all the sharp metal. But anyway. Yeah. They came with motors. You
make cranes. OK, so whether that's industry all the way up to whatever old devices, by the way,
that you're using now, the computers, all that stuff has been around except for since the 1800s,
except for the silicon chip, which was much a little bit later. And it's not there's no new
technology. All the technology has actually gone into miniaturizing it, making things smaller.
You're not getting it. You haven't gotten any new technology in 100 years, that's for sure.
That's why when you look at science stuff, all these new discoveries at MIT, they give you this
crappy video with a bunch of snotty 18 year olds from MIT. They're laughing at you, you know,
they put stuff together with hot melt glue and tell you this is what. Oh, my gosh. Mocking
humanity. So anyway, it's all about miniaturization and it doesn't impress me. And I heard
miniaturization does not impress the ladies either. So no matter how you look at it. Yeah. Why are
you getting what you're getting? It's all a distraction, which which is what I wanted to
get into a little bit. Not distraction, but what you're getting yourself into and what
what you could be doing. And this might sound a little cultish, actually, because I'm going to
bring up something that people should do if they can, because it's kind of like when you have an
engine that hasn't been maintained well. Sometimes it's recommended you do a flush. Right. Right.
To clean it out. But this is not about cleaning out. This is this will do that also. But what I'm
going to say pretty much is going to if people do it, it'll probably be the first time in their
lives for many of them. I know this, that they had they had something with such value in it.
What it is, it's basically cooking a very basic dish and eating it in small quantities and seeing
how you feel. And before I get into the dish, I just want to say that. I've had several people
through the years make comments like, you know, you talk about food, clothing, shelter,
that's so base, you know, we need more than that. Right. I'm like, are you joking?
If you if you can't take care of the qualitative aspect of the most basic things in life,
how are other things going to be helpful? Right. Well, that's that is, you know, and look,
all things begin there. Right. Look, if you're not properly rested, you're not properly fed,
you're not properly sheltered and you're not properly clothed. The rest of what you try to do
is why it becomes, you know, increasingly problematic. Right. Well, hold on to find
properly. That's what I've been trying to get into and why it's proper. And it's not really
something that's subjective. It's leaning towards the objective. Right. Well,
substantially, look, it may be proper to be dressed in a certain way, depending on what
the weather is like around you. OK, you might need a warm coat in some places.
Well, hold on. It's how you're built also, how you're made. Like you give me an example. Some
people will be depending on their diet will be colder in the same environment than other people
with a different diet. Right. Right. When I first came to Tucson, I had to go downtown to one of
the tall buildings here, 15 stories in the elevator. And there was it was winter,
40 ish Fahrenheit. So I was wearing a couple of layers. But there was a guy in a T-shirt
sweating his ass off. And he was in Inuit visiting Tucson. And it was 40 degrees outside. He was hot.
Right. Inuit Eskimo. Well, you and I used to live in the northeast. I mean, come on. Every time
somebody would come from Florida during the winter months, you would see it happen. They
would be losing their minds trying to get warm because they couldn't. You know, I'm standing
there in a T-shirt and I'm like, yeah, it's only 30 degrees out. And when I lived in Jersey,
that was fine. I was totally used to it. And they're sitting there dying. They're like,
oh, my God, I've got blankets on me. I got a coat. I got boots and.
Well, it's acclimation. That's that's what basically I'm glad you brought that up,
because I call it acclimating. Right. Adjusting. So people want to seek out all these things,
like what's going on with the world, what's going on with my family, what's going on at work,
but they have their own stuff. I've been trying to indirectly include a lot of practical stuff that
are helpful. You know, I do it mostly with they talk about hygiene, food and fixing things or
doing things, you know. But one thing I want to bring up is when you're going to start off,
I think I'll always be repeating that we don't absorb anything. The body is completely sealed.
It goes by induction. Right. So what is induction? It's energy. You know, I was having a
discussion with someone who's very materialistic and they weren't quite getting it. They were
they're pretty well versed in all this stuff, you know, quote unquote, college education.
And they were interested in science. So when I say induction, they definitely know.
I don't have to give them too many examples. Right. You know, like the wireless toothbrush
that has no metal contacts. You put it in the thing and it charges. Well, how is it charging?
There's no metal contacting. Right. So induction, stove top. I didn't give it.
They understood this, but I had to break it down in a material way where I said,
think of evaporation and condensation. Think of it that way. But with energy, though. Right.
OK. OK. So once you understand that and then you what it does is it overemphasizes the actual
qualitative, energetic nature of what we eat even more. Give me an example. I don't know
if you've ever heard of anyone working in a food processing plant like Archer Daniel Midlands
or whatever. When you look at all the ingredients on mac and cheese, there'll be a couple of chemical
ingredients in there. Right. And they make this in bulk. So when they get the ingredients delivered,
it comes in these big stainless steel tankers. You've probably seen them on the road, you know.
Sure. And they wear hazmat suits because they're poisonous. So why would you deliberately be adding
poisons or time? Yeah, they can be poisonous. Yeah. Toxic chemicals. Right. A refined, highly
refined. You know, it's tough. Well, so what if it acts as a preservative? Right. Actually
handling the product differently. Look, if it needs a preservative, damn, just put it just get
bigger fridges, just charge a little extra because it's in the cold department. Right. Don't put
chemicals in it. Right. Like that. So my point here is, again, again, a very basic one. If you
start off with food. Right. And understand that it's energetic, pure energetic. But here's the
thing. How can you get someone who eats mac and cheese and bologna and margarine sandwiches?
Right. To understand that the they're actually it's the energy in the food. Right. Well, what
are they going to get out of that? Right. So, you know, or a standard American diet. Right. Or they
think there's protein. You know, I show people carbohydrate that go to the chemical analysis.
They show you a diagram of the molecule of protein and a molecule of carbohydrate. I said, hold them
up together. They're exactly the same except for one nitrogen. There's no. Why the distinction?
Right. And we're not talking polymer chemistry here. Right. So what I wanted to bring up is
there's a how do you get started in this? And this is very, very basic. Learn to eat something
that is very simple, that is very, very highly charged with energy. And this is the part where
it starts to get cultish and like I'm almost being sponsored by them. But if you can get yourself some
Lundberg, it's a brand brown rice. Why? Because it's the only brown rice. Basically, unless you
get some from Japan, that's high quality and it's treated very well. What I mean by this is, OK,
they're what's that private radio station, W whatever in New York and YC. Yeah. Yeah. In New
York. And they were interviewed once the grandson of Goya Foods. You mean public radio? It's public
radio. That's right. Public radio. It's a Gary knows on there. And he wants to put the network.
Yeah. Right. Yeah. Let's have your back. But, you know, public radio. Yeah. Non-sponsored whatever.
But I remember this because I was doing a restoration project. I was in Manhattan in
the mansion and we were doing the plaster in the gilding and all that to make it look like
it did in the eighteen hundreds. And we were working 20 hours a day. And this came on.
And I just leave that on the background. No commercials, no pop music. So there was a recording
of the interview of the grandson of Goya Foods, G.O.Y.A. And he said, basically, the reason why
they started Goya Foods is because there was immigrants coming from Cuba, Puerto Rico, Dominican
Republic, living on the East Coast. And they like to eat rice and beans. So they would go to the
grocery store and buy rice and beans. And they found the quality to be inferior. Like, you know.
So they said, we need to do something about this. And it's true. I'm going to. So the Latin people,
when they eat rice and beans. OK, what I mean by this, if you go get a can of Trader Joe's,
let's say, organic black beans, you open the can, you look in there. All the beans are different
sizes. Some are broken. Right. Or Kroger or whatever, whatever, quote unquote, white people
shopping place. If you get a can of Goya beans and open the lid, all the beans are sized,
they're classified, they're all the same size and there's not one broken bean ever. OK, so you go
get rice, whatever white people, rice, American rice, whatever you look at it. You go buy a bag
of new, shaky rice from Japan. You pour. It doesn't matter. I buy it by the twenty five pound bag,
the short grain. You pour out the whole twenty five pound bags. You will not find one broken
kernel of rice, piece of rice. They're all whole and they're also the same size. Why?
What does that tell you about the quality? Right. It's kind of like going to a new car dealer and,
you know, you're looking at the cars. I don't want this one. It's the right color,
but I don't want it. Why? Because the headlights broken. Right. Well, you know, that's how they
come. Oh, my gosh. Right. So, I mean, that's just another way to think about it. So when you buy,
let's say, Nishiki or Lundberg or Goya can of beans or whatever, and you notice or you told
that they're doing this because there are all the grain and all the beans are classified,
meaning the same size, not one broken bean or broken piece of rice. Right. It's very clean
and all that. What does that tell you? They took extra time. Right. I don't know if you've ever
seen these food processing places, though, but it's basically guys with knee high rubber boots
and jumpsuits and shovels, snow shovels. They dump the food on the ground and they. Right. You said,
yep, you might have seen it. Right. Yes, I have. Yeah. Yeah. That's why you got to rinse all the
stuff that's dry, you know, before you cook it. Right. So, yeah. All right. So this is a
qualitative. I'm trying to just lean on that. So get yourself some Lundberg brown rice.
I didn't forget. Came back to it and learn how to cook it. It must be cooked under pressure.
They don't talk about that, really. They just give you a time. You need a good pot with a good
fitting lid. What I like to do is I use Lincoln cookware or all clad. Look it up. Whatever size
six quart is a pretty good pot. Not too big, not too small for court. You know, whenever you work
with a pot, you don't fill it all the way up to the top. You got to give yourself some room. Right.
Yeah. So six quart is a pretty good one. There's like 200 bucks for the pot or whatever you can.
Yeah, they don't. You know, rarely you find them on sale, but all clad. OK, what the lid fits,
the lid is a very tight slip fit. It goes down into the pot and it has a shoulder that stops
it from going all the way in. Right. Right. Very, very tight. Same with the Lincoln cookware.
Lincoln. I like the pans. I'll try to like the pots. Now, there are a lot of companies that
get yourself a good pot. You also need what's called a heat diffuser. It's like a perforated
metal sheet with a handle that you put between the burner and the pot. So when you cook something on
low for a long time, you don't get burn what's on the bottom and you need the pot has to have
a certain amount of thickness. And then you just follow the instructions on the rice. Now, it's
not that simple. I'll probably do a solo. I have neglected the solo sonic simply because of what's
going on outside of doing sonic events with the water project and other things. It's just a
shortage on time. If I tell you I sleep eight hours a week, maybe 12 hours a week. Right. You
know, that's not a lot, but I feel great. I feel great. But how long can you do that for? And no
drugs, by the way. Right. Yeah. No, it depends. Look, if it's working for you, it's working for
you. There are certain time periods I've been in certain time periods where I need a lot of sleep.
I've been in other time periods where I need very little. Yeah. So I'm just super excited. I'm more
excited now than I was when I was 12 years old or 30 or whatever. So. OK, so why am I saying this?
OK, so what I did recently was I was saying, you know, I just need to make some food. I just need
to eat some food, but I want it to be really good because the less of it I eat, the better it should
be. Right. So what I did is I made some brown rice. It has to be cooked under pressure. I remember in
the chat, someone put in even like a brick wrapped with aluminum foil on the lid to hold it down.
And the reason I say if it's a rock or brick, wrap it with some foil or something, because, you know,
they crumble, the pieces break off, you know. It's like, you know, you serve it and they're like, oh,
this is really crunchy. I mean, yeah. Oh, sorry. I can't tell them why it's so crunchy. Right.
But anyway. So, yeah, just be I use diver weights, four pound lead diver weights. Right. And also have
a mug that I filled with cement weighs four pounds. But I cut a groove, a half inch by half
inch groove across the mug after it was filled because the pots use a strap handle instead of
a single knob in the middle of the lid. It's a strap that goes across. So the mug. Right.
You can use a pressure cooker. Personally, I think it's the best way to go. But personally,
I think it's I don't like the pressure cookers because they have this rubber gasket that goes
around and I can taste it. It just it smells and tastes like rubber to me. I mean, most people
can't. But when I have something that's cooked in a pressure cooker with rubber gasket, I'm like
I can almost taste the rubber, you know. So in Japan, what they do when they pressure cook
certain types of rice, they have the pot machine totally flat. Then they get a thick copper plate
and they weigh it down with buckets of water and things like that. Right. So, yeah, I'm not
suggesting that's not necessary. The copper has an energetic property. Also, the copper plate that
would cover a pot would cost three, four hundred dollars on its own. The all cloud would be almost
as good. OK, so when you make this rice, what I did, I wanted something I kind of meditated on.
What would be like super modified, super nitro charged octane boosting body can induce it quickly.
It'll be very rejuvenating to the cells. Right. Also, energy, easy to digest. Right. All this
stuff. Right. So, by the way, when I make the rice, I have these I get these these plums. You
know, I've ever had a plum. You know, when plums are not ripe, they're really bitter. You bite into
them like, oh, this needs to ripen. Right. Oh, yeah. Yeah. OK. There's a type of plum that grows in Asia.
They could be grown here, but they're not. And it's called Umabashi plum.
Umabashi plum. You get them at any Chinese or Asian food market. They have some crazy ingredients
like they use a red coloring, but it's a natural red coloring, some alcohol or stuff or the paste.
But what you do is you put a plum with the with its pit in the rice, in the middle of the rice
before right before you add the water and you cook it with the plum. Why? Because the plum,
the Umabashi plum is world famous for settling digestive. I think on one spot on our fair,
we mentioned I recommended it to you, Chuck. It's world famous for
settling digestive issues of any kind, severe and mild. It would be the the most natural,
most effective Pepto-Bismol milk of magnesia or one of those products. Right. What those things
are supposed to do. Yeah. I tried to find that around here. Very difficult where I am. But
but yeah, mail order. It's got mail order, probably. Yep. They're just varieties that
have to be kept in the fridge. And there's varieties that are what do they call them
when they put them in free? They say it's like a Ziploc bag. It doesn't have to be fridged.
You know, I was a trader just once and they had pre-cooked rice on the shelf. It wasn't even in a
it's one of those pouches, vacuum sealed, vacuum sealed pouches. Yeah. They have vacuum seal or
hermetic seal. Yeah. Yeah. Vacuum seal. Right. So why am I saying this? Because I've been playing
around with food for so long and not until recently where I really thought I thought about
this for about a month. What do I need to do to get myself some like super nutrition?
They call them super foods. Right. You see that advertising all the time. Yeah. And I've been
playing with this for a while. And it really, really, really, really works not just with me,
but anyone who tries it because we make the rice this way. Basically, pressure cook Lundberg brown
rice. You can't get Lundberg brown rice. Try to get the best quality you can find.
And cook it with a new bashi plum in a pressure cooker type situation. Right. Now, what I mentioned
to people is you can rinse the rice and I'd like to parch it. And parching is as a term. We say
we're parched when we're thirsty, but it's a term. Well, it's a light roast. You know,
there's roasting. Right. Right. When you roast coffee, beans, peanuts or whatever.
But parching is a very light roast. It's like just beginning to roast, just beginning to get
that aroma and you stop. What you do is you rinse the rice. You rinse the rice. You rinse the rice.
Really? Well, you don't have to soak the brown rice. You could. It doesn't matter. It's not going
to get through the husk and let it strain out. And while it's damp, put it in the pot. You're
going to cook it in and go ahead and put the flame on medium and then start lowering it as you're
stirring it. The water will evaporate and then there's no water in the rice as you're stirring
it. You get that beautiful roasted smell. You know, you've smelled things being roasted. It's
just wonderful. Right. It brings the essence out. Right. Absolutely. Yeah. And then when you add
your water, when you add water at that point, add a hot water, have another pot going with twice
the amount of rice. So if you have one cup of rice, two cups of water, that's basically two
and a quarter, maybe water. So then you make your rice. OK, so this is the part where, well,
how is brown rice superfood? Well, it's part of it. I call it brown rice number seven. Right. You
know how the food industry, they name all these things with numbers. Right. Yeah. Right. So I
figured I'd do that, too. So what's the rest of it? Very simple. You got to get yourself some.
Let's start with the one to start with the hard to get vegetables first, Chuck, or the easy to
get vegetables first. Which one? Start with the easy ones. OK. Onion, white onion. Get yourself
some white onion. And when you make the cut on the white onion, by the way, the top of the onion
is the young part of the onion, the part that goes upwards towards the sky and the bottom parts,
the part that goes towards the ground. So when you cut an onion, you want to make it so when
someone gets a piece of onion, they're getting both the top and the bottom at the same time.
So you always cut it vertically. Right. So you cut it in half from top to bottom, lay it down,
take the skin off, whatever, and then go across the side. So when someone gets a piece of onion,
they have the top of where the bulb shoots up, the green. And also you also get near the root.
Right. So that's the best way to the flavor is better. Also, that's how you cut your onion.
The next vegetable will be carrot. The way you cut your carrot, cut it on a bias.
So you lay down the carrot. You might want to flatten it a little bit, slice a little bit.
So it's flat. You know, you can just scrub carrots. You don't have to peel them, by the way.
By the way, you know, when you buy potatoes, a lot of people like to peel them. I like that.
You know, they got certain ranch fries and things where it's got the skin on potatoes with skins
and they bake them. They taste good, too. Yeah. When I tell people, you know, I got you wash
a lot of stuff that's on potatoes is not dirt. It's not soil. It's human. It's humides. It's
like something that potato. It's like the soil that forms on the potato. Right. It won't hurt you.
It's not dirt. Right. But I would recommend scrubbing them anyway, because if you want to
see how potatoes are handled, you definitely want to wash it. Right. Plus, you don't know what they
came in contact with when they were exactly forwarded, et cetera. So, yeah, I definitely
recommend always washing. But don't be totally crazy if you see it's you know, it's got that
little bit of a clay kind of, you know, whatever. It's fine. It's a human. It's humus is what it is.
So one day we'll get into humides and by two minutes, look nights and all that.
So anyway, so the carrot, you cut it on a bias, which is an angle. We lay it down and you cut it
like on a. So let's say the carrots about three quarters of an inch in diameter. The piece that
you're going to end up with is going to be almost two inches long because it's on a bias. Right.
OK, you cut that in half again. All right. So now as we're going this way,
those things take less time than the other vegetables cook. So cut them a little thicker.
So actually, in this case, I would cut it about a quarter of an inch thick, no less on the carrot
and no less on the onion. All right. Now we get to the harder to get vegetables.
That would be something called burdock root. Burdock is in the thistle family,
and people have heard me extol its virtues before. You know why people eat meat and always
and prefer it? Because when you eat meat, whether it's fish, fowl or beef or whatever,
it gives you instant energy. Right. Instant. I mean, like, you know, within not too much life,
you don't get it while you're eating it. You're getting it right after the meal. Right.
That's why you feel that you either feel energetic or you feel strong. One or the other. Yeah,
it does. Yeah. But there's a price to pay later because it's very it could be taxing on the body.
That's why if you had to go somewhere and you had to be on the move for a long time,
you need a bag of dried fruit and some beef jerky and a water source, and you'd be good for days
just with a few ounces of that right beef jerky and some dried fruit in a pouch and a water source
from your water source. You could have, let's say, like eight ounces of that and go for a week.
That's how concentrated it is. But you'll have a hangover after a few days of eating that right
because of the way that it distributes the energy. OK, so in this case, the burdock root,
it does what meat does because it's the most young. It's the most bracing. It's the tightest
vegetable known. It's basically in the thistle root. And people that are into, let's say,
alternative healing and stuff will know that if someone has liver issues, they recommend milk
thistle. All right. You've heard of that. Yeah. And basically everyone, anybody that has most
like skin rashes, allergies, diabetes of any kind, you know what that is? That's a liver issue.
That's a liver dysfunction, by the way. Right. Right. Yes. Yes. Allergies or liver dysfunctions,
guys. Yeah. Wow. So. OK, so this is very bracing and strengthening in many, many ways because the
thistle family burdock root also cut it on the bias and that I would cut on like a 16th of an
inch, make it thin. Right. So let's say the burdock is a half inch to three quarter wide
a diameter. When you make your slice, it'll be, again, about two inches long, like it'll look
like an ellipse right on a bias. OK, what's the next vegetable? Next vegetable is taro root.
Now, you'll find that mostly in mountainous. It's a mountain. Now, there's two types of taro root
is large root and small root. Use the large root. Right. OK. It has more flavor. It looks like a very
white. You know how potatoes are white, but they're not really white. They're yellow. You
know, kind of right. Well, taro root is chalk white, like blackboard chalk white. That's how
white it is. Right. It's got a very dark skin. Yes. Super white. And it has little blue or purple
hairs throughout the starch. OK, now that one you want to cut the thickest, peel it and just
cut a slice of it about a half inch or more and then cut it into smaller pieces like you would,
let's say, potatoes. Right. I don't think I've ever had this. I mean, it's delicious. Yeah.
I mean, where would you find that available? You find that in a lot of South American culture and
Asian culture. They it goes both ways. It goes for savory dishes and for desserts.
It would be if you lived in a Latin neighborhood or Asian neighborhood, it would be more common
than the potato, the potatoes that we call, you know, it's a root. It's a mountain starch root.
OK, OK. You can get it's delicious. Actually, you know what I was addicted to about a few decades
ago is taro chips. Do you remember those? I never saw them. You never. Oh, OK. Yeah,
he was kind of all the rage. I know there's a bunch of people who had them and they are delicious.
Right. And it's not like it's a very broad flavor. Yeah. Lots of different chips became popular at
different points. There was all sorts of different chips, chips, sweet potato chips.
Chips were a big thing for a bit. Remember, those were a big thing. Which one? Banana chips,
believe it or not. Yeah. Yeah. I remember that. That started in the 80s. Yeah. Right. That's what
I'm thinking back to is the banana chips. And then all of a sudden there was all these different
types of first time I saw what they call deli chips or kettle chips all of a sudden. And yeah,
right. Right. And then I have I have enough plastic teeth in the mouth that I got to be careful if I
try to bite on something like that. But all right. OK, so the terror. OK, we got that. All right.
The next one, we're going to get really strange lotus root. It's the lotus plant. What does it
look like? It kind of looks like those Yukon gold potatoes. But when you and it comes in there in
pods, sometimes it's four or five minute pod looks like something, you know, in Star Trek,
they try to make like alien looking food and vegetables. Right. It looks like something
out of Star Trek, but neutral in color. If you cut a section of the lotus root,
it looks identical to the bronchi bronchi in the lung, in the lungs. Look up cross section
of lotus root. I don't know if you can do that, Chuck. I don't know if they'll mess up our recording.
No, no, I won't. I'll go ahead to cross section of the bronchi bronchi in the lungs and do a
cross section of the lotus root. And tell me if you see any difference at all. And the answer is no.
So guess what? The lotus root is good for. Right. Energetically, in other words, the energy that
takes to form the lotus root is the identical energy that it takes to form the bronchi in the
lungs. So they complement. Right. Right. I'm just sorry. I'm getting the bronchial tube up and
the bronchi. Yeah. Which are the little sacks, bronchi sacks. Yeah.
Cross section or cross section of lung would be an easy one. Oh, cross. You know what? Yeah.
Cross section lung. OK, that's easier. Yeah. Cross section lung and then do cross section
of lotus root. OK, got it. I type real slow, but I'm getting it. Yeah.
Yeah. So all these are these are based. They all they're all have their own very distinct flavor.
But this is pure energetic. This is like formulating a synthetic oil for a race engine is what I'm
talking about. Right. You notice I said race engine. Right. Right. So, yeah. Well, there's
a cross section of the root. And yeah, you see what it looks like. Go even without looking at
the lungs. I mean, familiar with sort of the structure. Look at the lungs and you'll see
it's identical in proportion and everything. Yeah. That's it's just a little more symmetrical.
Looks like in the in the root. Yeah, but it's identical in proportion. You know,
this is the amount of cells to the proportion of the body of the root to the bronchi.
Yeah. It's just laid out in a more organized pattern in the root from the pictures.
Yeah. As far as I've noticed, roots tend to be more organized than most people as well. Yeah.
Yeah. OK, there we go. You see that? Yeah, it's interesting, isn't it? OK.
The last thing is ginger root. Slice that real thin. It doesn't have to be on a bias. Just go
across. Peel it. And less than an eighth of an inch. And you could do Juliana like matchsticks.
Right. There's two options here. One is to put it in with the rice, all these veg in
with the rice as you're as you're parching the rice, because you always want to saute
vegetable dry a little bit to bring till it caramelizes. That's where you get the wonderful
flavor. Right. You don't have to do that. I suggest doing that now with the ginger. Is the
ginger more about flavor or is that more about? No, no. OK, no. I kind of skipped over that.
I didn't get over where the energy of the taro root that much either. OK. And the ginger root
is is a very it gives off the strong aroma of something you would imagine as being very
expansive. But its structure is extremely contractive and it's a root. OK. Any kind
of root vegetable, by the way, is bracing anything that is a root is bracing. What
do I mean by bracing? I was just going to hear about people like they haven't eaten
and they say, I got the shakes. Oh, yeah. OK, well, if you eat this kind of food and
you haven't eaten and you're really hungry, you'll never get the shakes. You still feel
stable. And if you don't, you know, you don't hear people say my blood sugar is low. Right.
Oh, you eat this. You eat this kind of food. You don't have that feeling. The hypoglycemia.
Which way it goes too much or too little. OK, so the taro root, though, just to jump
back on the energy and then they'll do the ginger root. The taro root is does everything
a simple starch does without being a simple starch. OK, if you're in a race or a marathon
or whatever, you're running out of energy. You need a simple starch right now to boost
you. Right. To get some energy. Right. Chocolate bar, energy bar, energy drink. Right. It does
that, but it does very much what that would do as a simple starch. Very easy to digest.
But it's not a simple starch. It's actually has a lot of minerals. It's also good for
chitin in the body, which is hair and nails. Now, the ginger root has got a very strong
peppery aroma, which was in the vernacular that I like to lean on. It would be make it
very lean, but it's very young. In other words, if you feel a ginger, it's really tight. You
throw a ginger root across the room and someone on the head, it's that knob is going to hurt
their head. It's hard. Yeah, it's very hard and very fibrous, extremely fibrous, believe
it or not. You'll see if you start slicing it. If you try grinding it, you have to do
a slice because the fibers get in the way. Right. OK. And also you could tell by the
segments on its skin. Right. How it grows is also giving a tremendous amount of energy
and then it stops growing and then it gives us tremendous amount of energy. So what the
ginger does is it aids recovery. Right. You know what I mean? Like you make an effort
and you got to recover to make another effort. The ginger will help in shortening the recovery
time, whatever that might be. OK, so this is all very much put together. By the way,
the burdock root, the carrot. Yeah, it's good for your eyes. You know why? If you cut a carrot
across the just straight across and you hold it up next to your eye. Yeah, it's just like
the eyeball. Same proportion. Right. Yeah. The concentric. Right. Right. And so all these
things have energy, energetic patterns, and they all work very well together. So back
to cooking it. If you think you have enough finesse to put it in with the rice and cook
it, you'll probably end up with the rice being too crunchy and raw. The vegetables will be
overdone. Why? Because the vegetables have moisture in them and it will not let the water
get hot enough. They act as a cooling. So what I recommend doing, even though it is a pressure
cooking situation, is cook the rice three quarters of the way, half hour or 25 minutes.
Let the pressure out. Add the vegetables, stir them in and add just a little bit extra water
and then bring it up to a high heat and a medium heat with your heat diffuser and finish the
cook. It'll probably be an hour when it's all said and done instead of 45 minutes.
So now you have this number seven rice that is a superfood. Literally, it works really,
really well. If you have a sensitive bowel and you're not good at chewing, you will know that
you have a sensitive bowel because you're not good at chewing. Right. I always recommend when people
do brown rice to make it a little soggy in the beginning, a little mushier until they get used
to it. Why the rice? Why? Well, some people say, oh, it's too much carbohydrate. No, it's not.
It's actually a whole food. Why am I leaning on this so much? And why are we putting a sonic
event on this? Because I'm so impressed with the performance of it in the body in terms of the
amount of energy that it gives. And this is not just like a recipe. I gave all of the ingredients
and the reasons why they work together and how they work together. And the more you understand
the induction principle in the body, the more you will see what's going on here, especially when you
try it. Right. If you have conditions known as whatever the C word or whatever, or you can't
recover or quote unquote health issues, chronic stuff, and you incorporate this into your diet
and then disincorporate your other diet and eat more of this, you will watch those manifestations
disappear. Usually, usually in most cases, but experiments with people and myself, something
chronic comes up like a dry spot or something, you know, like, oh, look, I'm getting older.
This dry spot here means it's too much eating and the body's blocking it. Right. So when I start
eating this way, it disappears completely. And we're talking about a chronic thing that
was been around for two, three, four, five years. You tried all kinds of ointments and stuff like
that. It doesn't really work, but you do this and it disappears. What does that mean? Right.
The energy. Yeah. Flowing commonly the dry elbows. Right. I mean, that's one of the first things that
always happens with the dry elbows. Yeah. That has nothing to do with dry elbows. It's a manifestation.
Right. Right. Well, it does. Well, it's a dry elbow. What do you mean? Does nothing to dry
to dry elbows, a dry elbow. Right. I know. But I'm just saying it's a manifestation.
Once you start. So what I've discovered is I'm able to sleep very little and eat very little.
And I feel totally satiated with this. Now, I wanted to go back to how I started taking care
of the most basic things in your life, starting off with food. I've got we've gone into the hygiene
quite a bit, too. Right. To a degree, which is actually simple, you know, washing. You know,
I talked about how the body demagnetizes right when you bathe or shower. Right. Whenever people
aren't feeling well, the first thing I say is take a shower, take a bath and let me know how
you feel after that. And you know what? Ninety percent of the time I feel a lot better. Right.
So because it demagnetizes the body literally, you know. You know what? Put it this way. Let's
go to the simple boy electrician stuff. If you're holding a live wire, standing in a puddle of water,
what do you think is going to happen? Well, versus not standing in a puddle of water,
your chances of getting hit pretty hard in the puddle of water increase. Right.
So water has something to do with electricity, maybe. Right. Yeah. Is the body electric,
you know? So yeah. So imagine condition, energetic condition building up in the body and you jump in
the shower, take a bath or whatever. You're fully grounded. The water running over your body.
What what's it going to do to that field that you had built up in the body? So wash it away.
Well, that condition is going to change radically. Right. All right. So, yeah, that's just that's the
beyond the hygiene part. So the reason I'm saying this is I've had discussions recently with people
that everyone's got their own specific thing for being here on this earth, what they like and what
they don't like. And when I listen to it, I'm like, yeah, but how do you eat? Are you eating
good food? Do you know about hygiene? Do you know about how the body really works? So when you're
when you see like everybody around, you say, oh, take this mangosteen. Your body absorbs it. It's
full. What are you going to say? You're going to go along with that or you're going to call
bullshit at somebody. Right. So I mean, do you know how your body really works? Do you know?
Right. So I found that most people that I've interacted with, we're talking about an industry
to these are, you know, OK, and all kinds of all levels. I'm like, they don't know how to eat.
They don't know how to keep themselves clean. They don't know how we're right. They get easily,
easily swayed in direct, you know, especially with health stuff. Right.
So, you know, I don't want to get cancer. Well, then keep the energy in your body moving. Well,
I don't believe that. Haven't they, at least for the past 20 years, for sure,
they've been trying to teach or put in people's minds that cancer is hereditary.
Right. Oh, yeah. That's another thing. Oh, my gosh. Your family history, your family history. That's
what they do. Yeah. Heavily leaning on that. It was an actress. She got her boobs cut off just
because she thought she might get cancer or something. Oh, yeah. That's right. Yeah. That
was what he called it. She was with Angela Jolie. Jolie. That's it. Yeah. Yeah. I don't know if
it's true or not, but I mean, putting that out in public is just freaking embarrassing. Well,
she said it. I don't know if she did it, but she said, yeah. Yeah. I mean, this is this stuff is
criminal. But here's the thing. Like I've had a discussion with an attorney general once and he
didn't. Obviously, he knew that I knew law and he didn't. Right. Yeah. Basically, the conversation
ended up with, you know, we get into that. We just put you in jail. He didn't know any law at all.
So their answer is, we'll put you in jail. We'll just put you in jail. And he could do it. He'd
make a phone call and put you in jail. Right. Oh, no reason. Of course. Right. So this is how
they're operating. This is how everything's operating right now. They're not operating
by by what they say they are. So why did I bring up this long thing on the sonic event about the
food and actually gave out the recipe? If anyone has any more specific questions on it, I will
answer. The most problem that I found with people living in, let's say, the Midwest or maybe even
where you are, Chuck, you may not be able to get the ingredients. That's OK. Just make it what you
can get. Right. And but here's the other thing. There's no substitute for lotus root because you
can use taro root for potato, but it's going to make a mess. So there's no substitute for the
taro. There's no substitute for the ginger. There might be like Galangal looks like ginger, smells
like ginger or turmeric root, but doesn't have the qualities. It's too strong on us. Right. You
see those these things I've been. This is this has been like masterly crafted. There's no substitute
for any of these things that I mentioned. Well, I experimented with to America. I don't think it's
a bad thing at all. No, but it won't do what the ginger does. It leans too much on one side.
That's why it's turmeric. OK, but you know what I'm saying? It looks just like ginger root,
right? It's pretty similar. So does Galangal. But Galangal just tastes like white pepper.
Doesn't have any as a very strong. It's very, very strong flavor.
So, yeah. So there's no substitute for these things. I mean, let's say you don't have carrots.
Actually, it's hard to say carrot. You can't find carrots and onions because that's probably the most
common thing you can get. Right. Carrots and onions, you should be able to find anywhere
in the United States for sure. Yeah. So you start off with that if that's all you can get.
Right. But what I'm suggesting, this is like on a master. What I'm giving you is a master level,
super modified, super food type combination. And prove me wrong that this doesn't help you
recover and rejuvenate your body. Just tell me you tried it and it didn't do anything for you.
It won't. It's incredible. I've been playing around with this and thinking about this for a
very, very long time, and I've been doing it recently. And I'm like, this works so well.
I got to tell other people, you know, and once you get that and hygiene, a few other things
together, you can have a completely different outlook on the way you think your outlook is now.
Absolutely. And again, if it begins with that. Right. You know, look, some of the old
adages make sense. Right. What you eat, you are what you eat. Well, kind of because
it does begin a lot of what you're going to be dealing with later. I mean,
but that's the point. Later, as we're getting into what we're getting into,
we're getting hit with more energetic stuff than ever. We're not just direct energy weapons and
the multiple, you know, the force multiplier of Wi-Fi everywhere. Right. You know what?
We talked about Wi-Fi 20 years ago and talk about it now. It's what? Maybe 100 times more
Wi-Fi everywhere. Right. Oh, yeah. Yeah. OK. And also cosmically, you know, some believe,
you know, people that are sensitive, they say the sun we have now is not the same sun we had 10
years ago. Right. That's true. You know, I've been observing the astronomical bodies. They look
very different because the atmosphere, everything's changing. So we need to humans are inherently
robust creatures, but we need to be even more robust now just to just to think clearly what
it took to, let's say, improve your body so you could have clear thinking. Let's say 20 years ago,
you need to do five times more now. Right. I can tell you this. Look, I've been alive. You know,
what they say is 50, 50 plus years. And I can guarantee you this much in the past 10 years,
I've been able to feel not necessarily identify everything that's happening,
but I'm certain that there is a lot more action going on in the unseen world energetically in the
past 10 years than in the previous 40 without question. Yeah. Yeah. But but energetically,
not in the woo woo happy, you know, airy, fairy side copy, but in the like the way your body
can recover and health issues and things like that. Yeah. Things are more intense, more oppressive.
The weight is heavier on you. You know what I mean? That's the way I interpret it. It's probably
not proper, but I mean, I definitely feel the difference in the past 10 years. And it's not
just me getting older. There is more happening. Yeah. Yeah. You can sense it. It's the easiest
time to sense it is right before going to sleep and waking up. You'll you'll notice. Right. Because
when you're unconscious and sleep, it's kind of shuts you down. Yeah. It's so I just I just wanted
to share that today. I hope people find it valuable. You'll find it extremely valuable if you
do it. And I hope you can find the ingredients. And if you have to go a little extra, it's worth
it. And I'd like to some feedback from it, because the difference between this dish
is just I'm talking basic sustenance now, which you just had to create basic sustenance and
something that, again, aids in recovery, rejuvenation, energy, digestion, all that stuff.
This this would be it. And I am a foodie and a food Nazi. But this is something that lies in
between everything. And it does taste good. And don't be afraid if you make this to put
condiments on it, any condiment you like. Yeah, I was going to ask about, you know what
with variations. But, you know, all these other things coming together, it seems pretty well
balanced. And I mean, I'm imagining it. I haven't actually experienced it, but it's a it's a pretty
sound idea. So I like it. One of these days I might ask you about mushrooms, but not that's
not green, doesn't have seeds. Mushrooms are. They still can't figure out if mushrooms are
animal or vegetable or mineral or what they are. You know, right. It sounds strange,
right? They're mushrooms. They're in their own class. I'm an Old Testament kind of guy. And I
loosely or no, I strictly interpret the loose explanation that your food shall be green and
have bare seeds. I take that loose description and I use it strictly. So do mushrooms are
mushrooms green and do they bear seeds, have a seed bearing structure? The answer is no.
It's like, you know, pumpkin is a fruit. Right. Right. Because it has a seed bearing structure.
Right. As like fruit does. Right. So, yeah. Yeah. So but do what you got to do. You know,
I've in some cases, some people have some conditions that I might have to put together
of something like cockroaches. So that's another story. Right.