This is Sonic Event 1, and why am I saying it?
Because we are now in Rated-Y territory.
What do I mean? Well, if you're hearing this, then you know what I mean.
This is the exclusive thing that you signed up for, so here we are.
And it's going to be a little different than the older episodic events,
because they were described as episodes, and then they were described as chapters.
I forget why it is that was done, but that kept things in order.
And yet again, this is something else.
So this is Sonic Event 1 of Ocelli in the Greek, Rated-Y.
Anyway, as I said, a little bit different.
Yeah, it's going to be, let's say, 1 to 999, let's say.
It'll be easier maybe to do the number.
Each Sonic Event has a number, so we can easily say, hey, that's on Sonic Event 3,
or on number 4, or number 5, and we'll say 1 through 999.
So there you go.
Look, it's just a matter of filing them away and putting them in order.
But are they to be filed away?
We've covered a lot of territory and haven't been doing it that much lately,
although you appeared on my show a few times, and that was done for the public,
and this was sort of proposed.
And I'll tell you, I'm actually really excited because, again,
you talk about different things privately than you do publicly, you know.
We can, yeah.
Rated-Y, as in a pun on after Rated-X, and also WH-Y.
I was thinking of just doing two asterisks, you know, and then the Y, but Rated-Y.
And the whole thing is about we're going to be asking why, actually,
who's we, if you ask why, you're at the right place,
because we're all trying to figure it out.
The only thing is when you sort it out and you can present it and communicate it,
it doesn't mean you've figured it out.
It just seems like it just shows that you can do that.
You can sort things out and communicate them.
So by all means, I want to stay open with whoever is listening to this
to give us feedback, questions, all this, that, and the other.
We're still putting this together.
So basically, to reach Chuck at Ocelli.com, right, you'll have a contact.
And to reach me at UncommonSenseRadio1 at gmail.com, which is the number one.
And eventually, we'll probably have an email that does both of us or something,
but we also rely on feedback from whoever is here to either stop talking
about something or talk about something else a little bit more, so.
Right.
You know, if you're on my website, pretty easy.
There's a little email icon somewhere that you'll be able to,
I think it's up in the upper right-hand corner most likely, if you need to reach me.
And we will share our contacts with each other.
So if you do just find your way to write to me or you find your way to write
to the Greek, we'll figure it out, obviously, and share these things as we talk,
well, without recording it for the most part.
But that way, we'll have some guidance as to what is being received, I guess.
And that's an important thing.
And I like how we start off with the question why.
Got to tell you, I've explored a lot of different topics over the years,
a lot of mysterious things, you know, in some people's minds.
They don't understand what happened during an event, this or that.
I mean, I always go to the JFK thing because that's something I spent a lot of years on.
So I'm very familiar with the ins and outs of it.
And, you know, one of the questions that's almost never asked is why did this happen?
You know, people want the details.
People want to get into the more exciting parts of this or that or the third thing.
But quite often, they don't ask why this extraordinary event occurred,
this interesting event, this rarefied event, whatever it might be.
I mean, it could be a solar eclipse or it could be an assassination
or it could be a political movement.
A lot of people don't ask why something happened.
And I always find that to be a little disheartening
because I think it's often the most important question, you know,
and everything else sort of follows after it in my mind.
I don't know.
Maybe I'm wrong about that, Patrick.
No, it's not.
Well, no, it's not about being right or wrong on that.
It's just what can we put together to see why that's happening.
And if we harken back to a lot of the older Ocelli in the Greek sonics,
you'll see me basically using the term moron and juvenile and whatever,
those kinds of terms.
I'm not using those as pejoratives.
I just, if I could find a better word to deliver, you know,
the cause of the message, I will.
But in essence, this is a very, very juvenile society,
a very juvenile, meaning childish.
You know, if you're in the biblical text, the ancient text,
men are referred to as children, right?
If you've watched anything like in the public media,
they speak to you like you're a child.
It goes that way all the way across.
So the juvenile nature of society and the way humans have been,
let's say, all the way back is the status quo.
So one way to look at the why is to not only why it happened, okay,
like we could talk about, let's say 9-11 was a textbook.
This is very serious about this.
It was a textbook nuclear demolition textbook.
I mean, if you were to look in a textbook how to do it,
that's exactly what happened.
But it doesn't seem so obvious.
But once you understand how a textbook nuclear demolition works,
it's all underground.
There's a lady that puts out a book, I forgot her name, doctor or whatever,
about using weapons from space and all that.
And when they asked her about it being nuclear, she says,
oh, blinded by the light.
Well, she fails to recognize that it's all of the,
90% of the nuclear testing after it began started to go only underground
and be studied what happens with nukes underground only.
And that's how they decided to use them.
So why did I bring that up as an example?
So I can very emphatically show you how it was a nuclear demolition.
But I can't tell you why, right?
Why they did it.
There could be many reasons.
You could speculate whether it was economic, social engineering,
whatever, religious, to get the, let's say, some kind of ritual or whatever.
That's very difficult to surmise.
And the same thing with the assassination with JFK,
which is your specialty, Chuck.
We know he was, anyone, you know, even just hearing about it
in the public media, it was a gunshot wound and it was fatal.
And then you could backtrack and then it's like, who did it?
We could pretty much figure out who did it.
In other words, there was more than one shooter, right?
And where they shot was not what we're being told.
But why, again, was it financial?
Was it personal?
Was it purely, you know, purely any one of those things, political or whatever?
No, we don't really know.
So exploring the why is difficult, but until you establish how,
what really happened, right?
And then the why is the preferential part.
Well, not only is it the preferential part, and, you know, again,
I urge you to add to this, but the why can also give you a roadmap,
a path forward, because once you understand the why of something occurring,
then it'll make sense when other things happen.
See, pattern, recognition of patterns.
I mean, this is part of the nature of the beast, so to speak, right?
This is all of us.
We recognize patterns.
So if we know the why of exactly why an event occurred,
if we know what the motivation was for it to happen,
and we know that that motivation persists,
then we can get an idea about, well, what might come next,
what also might be part of that pattern.
So isn't that a way of unlocking not only historical events
and understanding their motivation, but also understanding things moving forward,
or do you think I'm off about that?
No, not too off, but the thing is, I think that historic events repeat,
and I'm going to give a plug here, which is unusual.
There's a guy named Jason Breshears,
and I'm sure most people listening might have heard.
He has a channel called Archaics.
He's a Texas country meets the internet, so some people don't like to listen.
I particularly like to listen only because he has an intelligent,
let's say, dissertations.
He's a chronologist.
He has something called palindromes, which is a palindrome is like 6-1-6.
When you run it forward, it's 6-1-6.
If you run it backwards, it's 6-1-6 in time.
But the interesting thing that caught me with him is that he said
that 1998 is a very key year for doing palindromes.
Now, if anyone's listened to Ochoa in the Greek,
I think since the beginning, even before we got together,
I was always hammering what year?
1998 as the end of time, and everything after that is the credits, right?
So that perked me up.
He's got a couple of interesting things,
and the other thing that he turned me on to, or the audience,
that was, I think, his major work is every 138 years,
something appears in the sky.
And every fourth time, the 552 years, it does a lot of damage.
That's where you get the red rains, the mud flood, people disappearing,
you know, stuff written about worlds in collision,
and a lot of the Charles Fort that I've also mentioned speaks about that.
I'd never had the 138 Phoenix cycle.
Last time it happened was 1902, but all the elite went underground
because it goes after the elite, basically.
And this has been going on since time immemorial.
But I kept always saying there's several biblical chronologists
that I've looked at, and there's something called a cursed earth period.
It's every 440 years, and I've always discussed the 400 year,
not in depth because I'm not a chronologist, you see.
He's a chronologist, and he's got mapped out.
He spent 27 years in prison accessing old books.
That's a lot of time.
So when you get to the biblical stuff with him, I'm just going to,
because people, I know, once they start looking,
they're going to say that we're very contrary in a lot of things.
He has taken his biblical comments a little too far in terms of not like personal,
but in other words, he has not dealt in the documents long enough
or objectively enough with the original languages.
And he's basically taken the academic, let's say, side,
which is it was all written much later by other authors and all this.
And he doesn't know that there was no crucifixion.
He doesn't know about this and that.
So on the religious side, he falls pretty, he's confabulated a lot.
And what I mean by that, and this is by no way a negative criticism
this is just an objective criticism.
What happens when you introduce a subject in public or private to a group of people,
and you're the only one that knows about that, anything about that subject,
and it's just very surface to the others.
You can pretty much say anything about that.
And if you sound authoritarian and start making stuff up,
the other people will believe you because you, you know,
the first two details you brought up impressed them so much.
So the rest you could confabulate, you know,
make up stuff and make something that's hyperbole or whatever sounds factual
and the people will believe it.
Well, they do that all the time in the public media.
And in what they call the education system, which I call the cognitive,
you know, there's cognitive dissonance.
But I call the education system cognitive depravity.
So he doesn't like the education system either.
So a lot of people are saying I need to go listen to him in that way.
But I and then I come back with all the comments that I gave now
because he's blowing up.
In other words, he had 300 subscribers a year ago,
and now he's at 90,000 on YouTube.
Archaics, Jason Brashears.
I'm plugging him as a chronologist with the 138-year Phoenix cycle,
and the next time it's coming is 2040.
So I just wanted to give this, because this is, as we're starting out in our first episode,
so why is he referring us to go listen to other stuff?
Well, the reason why is because that is the only thing that has come across my table,
let's say, or keyboard in the past decade or more,
maybe 20 years or so, that I find worth absorbing.
The Phoenix phenomenon, because it lines up very much,
if you understand, if you read a lot of the biblical texts,
all these phenomenon that are going to be happening,
it lines up very much with his quote unquote chronology.
And it gets into a lot of the vapor canopy,
which I have not done publicly,
which was the time of Noah, where we lived in,
basically there was an ocean in the sky,
and it collapsed during the major flood.
That's why people all over the world have that flood myth, right?
So anyway, I just wanted to bring him up,
because I might be referring, as we go on,
to some of his work in terms of the palindromes.
And what caught my ear is someone was actually astute enough to say,
hey, look, he says 1998 is a critical year.
Haven't you been saying that, right?
I think, Chuck, you remember also.
He's saying the fall of 1998 was when time ended,
meaning time as time progressing into new eras and new epics, right?
So in other words, the movie ended at 1998,
but the film is still running.
Well, that always happens when the movie ends,
the film is still running, right?
Right.
It's called the credits.
Although sometimes they have a post-credits scene
or a, you know, during the credits scene that they add in.
You know, the bonus piece,
which gives you an indicator, usually, of something that's yet to come.
And it's funny, because when we did this a few years ago,
I hadn't thought of it.
But do we have sort of a post-credit or during the credit extra scene
that's going to come up here?
Because I'm thinking to myself often what happens,
and many people have made this observation,
it's not just me, but quite frankly,
Hollywood does indicate a lot of things prophetically.
You know, they normalize things and talk about things
quite ahead of when they happen,
and they present it as fiction.
And then a lot of people notice later,
you know, that was in a movie 10 years ago, 20 years ago, et cetera.
So I'm wondering if somebody caught onto that
and actually said, you know,
there's going to be something that's going to be easily observable
that'll be presented during the credit part of the film,
which, you know, runs a few minutes.
You know, at the end of any film, it runs a few minutes,
even when they shorten the credits, right?
Well, let's look at it from this point.
From a universal standpoint, you know,
the cosmic censorship or the cosmic realm,
which is beyond our world, let's say,
I'm not talking about space, I'm talking about, you know,
we could have a parallel world here.
It's just a different type of physicality, right?
The spiritual world and all that.
In that order, you know how you have, let's say, local,
the way you do things in your town,
and then you have the state, and then you have the federal,
then you have international law?
This would be more on the side of international law.
Like, it's the entire world encompassing,
not what each little geographic area has,
is what I'm trying to say here.
In a cosmic perspective,
knowledge and information is just that.
It's not separated as fact or fiction.
So, if you have a notion that, let's say, I don't know,
you could pick in your own mind,
we don't even have to give an example,
something that they've shown in Hollywood as fiction
that later has come true,
or is parallel to something that comes true.
Let's say the movie The Matrix, right?
Or something like that.
A lot of people have been saying
we're in a matrix kind of thing.
Okay, from a cosmic perspective,
when information is given,
it doesn't matter if it's fact or fiction,
is the recipient received a notion
or a concept of something that they didn't have before?
And what that concept they received,
is it done with enough accuracy and detail
that they actually, you know,
it forms a complete thought, right?
It's very much, let's say another way to say it,
it's in your face, right?
So, there is no fact or fiction in the cosmic perspective
because when you think that anything can be possible,
the, what you think, let's say,
if you went back in time
and talked about some of the technology we have today,
that was thought as being impossible, you see.
So, when Hollywood shows this, you know,
like the elite invented science fiction, right?
Not to show particular type of alien or particular type,
but just to show that we're not bound by gravity,
we're not bound by this material, you know,
like creatures walk through walls, things like that.
Okay, that is all, we have not done that openly in public,
but since we understand that a flying saucer
come down and land,
whether it's marked as fiction or not is irrelevant
from a cosmic perspective.
So, you can say that humans know about flying saucers
landing with little beings from Mars on the earth
from a cosmic perspective.
They already aware of that,
whether it's fact or fiction is irrelevant.
And that's understood by Hollywood
because Hollywood is like, you know,
or the media is what?
The third or fourth,
that would be the fourth branch of government, they say,
right?
Something like that.
Fourth estate, they often say, yeah.
Fourth estate, okay, there you go.
So, one thing I wanna stress,
and I have been in the past,
especially with previous sonic events,
is I bring up some things that sounded really askew
or tangential and not possible.
And when people looked into it,
and actually some of the things
that I said that you can do,
things that were never thought of or seemed impossible
are now brought down to the practical level.
So, in the beginning,
it's marked as fiction or opinion,
and then it becomes something usable.
And we're gonna get into that.
I might wanna read some of a email I got recently.
Someone is a writer,
and he's basically, when he found out we're redoing this,
he was like, why bother?
You know, it's like none of the alternative media people
have done anything that means a hill of beans or anything.
Everything's still the same, right?
So, obviously, he didn't listen to a lot of the other stuff
that I've done, and I don't blame him at all,
because here's an interesting thing.
When you tell people what to do,
they don't like that, so they don't do it.
If you give them a hint on doing something,
they may not get the hint and they don't do it.
So, there's something in between telling someone
they should do this or may do this or could do this,
and just talking about it as a hint.
So, there's something in between that we'll explore,
because, ultimately, it's all based on action.
So, I'm expecting doing this with you in a non-public way
is to actually impart more things that people can do,
should do, or may do, or find out about
that will improve, quote-unquote, their lives here.
Well, I always found it interesting when people said,
you know, look, you can go for instruction,
you can learn, and somebody can teach you
the how-to and so on, and quite often,
no matter what you attempted to educate somebody about,
whether it was very practical knowledge
or if it was something just purely academic,
it was irrelevant, it seemed to me as though
the people that, and I do despise this as a profession,
but there are people out there that are
what they call inspirational speakers, right?
But I think the term is sound.
I think the action is corrupt and absolutely ridiculous
since people just being fleeced, you know,
under the guise of, they make them feel good,
so they wind up turning over their money,
which is, you know, the profession of a lot of people,
whether it's a stripper or it's, you know, a musician,
right, you make people feel good, they end up with money.
Well, they just help the, well, the stripper
is stripping why?
To help themselves.
Well, of course.
The guys like Anthony Robbins, not to mention any names
or whatever, they're ultimately to help themselves
and most of their stuff doesn't work.
It makes you feel good at the moment.
Right, but the thing is the idea
of an inspirational speaker, though, is very sound
because if you inspire someone to take an action,
then you've actually accomplished something
because as you said, if you tell them what to do,
there's people that are more or less,
and I'm one of those people who's more resistant
when I'm being told what to do,
I automatically have a resistance.
Like even if something is popular,
I've always been like, you know what,
that's the thing I wanna be nowhere near.
You know, people tell me, you've gotta see this.
I go, yeah, I've gotta not see it.
You know what I mean?
Like, I automatically default to that.
And I think a lot of people have that tendency in them
to different degrees, but like you said,
if you give somebody a hint, they say,
well, that's a hint, that's not quite enough.
But if you sort of lay it out somewhere in between,
like you said, I think that becomes inspiration
or, you know, and this may sound esoteric to some people,
but the idea of the muse who inspires something, right?
And we talked about muses before even, you and I,
and that concept, but that is the thing
that actually creates what?
The art, the thing that somebody seizes upon
and does it their way with their talents,
with what they have available to them.
And really, the thing that gets things moving in a,
again, I hate to use these words,
but I don't have many others,
in a progressive direction, whether it's art
or it's construction or anything else,
is if you inspire someone who already wishes
to take action, right?
And also the why, why do we wanna inspire people?
Ah, okay, now we're back to that why.
I might wanna give that out because,
you know, charity begins at home.
You take care of, you know, like in the airplane,
if the oxygen mask dropped down,
you put your mask on first,
and then you help the people next to you.
But also, I believe that when this concept is understood,
like I say, if half the people of the world
help just one person,
well, then the whole world's taken care of, you see?
A third, each one would have to help two.
So, but here's the thing,
I'm doing it for actually selfish reasons,
and this is what I mean.
I can't, I have spent most of my life since nine years old,
knowing that I gotta put a protective layer around myself,
not an armor, because these people are nuts around me,
right?
But if I figure out something,
a better way of doing something,
and I show someone else and they do it,
well, then everybody around me is doing something better,
and that ends up being better for me
because, you see, right?
Because then everybody around me has improved.
Now, you know,
yeah, so like if you ride the public bus,
and you make sure.
Yeah, I was just gonna say,
I encourage it a different way,
and it's the same concept.
I talk about the random act of kindness,
whereas if you seek to improve things around you,
and you do consistently do that as an individual,
you improve the community,
you improve your neighborhood,
you improve the thing that is right around you
by improving things for others a bit,
and that automatically does what?
It returns to you because you've now,
look, if the people around you are less miserable,
if you've just relieved some of their misery
because you had the ability to do so,
I do this often by sharing food
when I have more than I need.
I'll often, you know, offer it to people
that I happen to know could use it.
Something very simple like that.
Now, that sounds like charity again, that word,
but it's about the improvement of the overall situation.
That is my motivator,
is that it improves everybody,
and by doing that, guess what?
My family's in a better place, right?
And myself, I am in a better place,
and things can be a lot easier on everyone if you do that.
So I like to say-
Sure, it's like moving,
it's like going to another neighborhood.
It's like changing where you live,
but the thing is to do it in a nondescript way.
So there you go.
I mean-
Anyway, I wanted to maybe,
because we're gonna eventually land on
why a lot of things are the way,
and it's still gonna be preferential,
like do you, you know, should you accept why?
You know, again, like Kennedy or 9-11 or many other things.
I can't really say why,
but we can narrow it down so well
that once you understand a little bit more
about what we even started the conversation with,
I haven't hammered on how juvenile, childlike the mind is
and of society, and I'm talking,
by the way, I think I mentioned
on the last time we spoke publicly,
when I use the term moron,
I'm not referring to the masses like most people do.
I'm referring to your professionals,
your leaders, you know, the upper echelon,
not the lower ones,
because the lower ones don't have,
they're like worker bees at this point, drones.
So again, when you look at the,
when I talk about juvenile,
it's, I'm talking about your judges, lawyers,
doctors, priests, CEOs of corporations, billionaires,
what people call Illuminati, elite, all that stuff.
They are very juvenile,
and you know how they have trickle-down economics.
If you cut the taxes of the rich,
they have more money to spend,
so that means they'll give it to their workers, right?
That idea.
So you have this trickle-down juvenile tendency of thought,
and it's, of course, spiritual,
because spirit is the mind as well,
that has trickled down in society,
and I want to maybe give a couple examples if you,
what do you think?
Should we get into that a little bit?
Absolutely.
Because remember, we run out of time quick on these things.
Sure, no, absolutely.
This is necessary, I think,
because how are you going to understand
any of what is being presented
if we don't know the landscape,
and this is a big part of the landscape,
the interaction, and leadership.
These are key things.
Look, everything that is discussed,
even in, you mentioned alternative media hasn't done anything
because they're doing the same thing.
They're talking about, yeah, leadership.
Well, that was based on an email that I got
when we were rebooting this,
is why nothing's going to change anyway.
Well, you know, I beg to differ
because we have given,
well, I have, and I don't like to say,
I always like to do third-person,
many things out there,
which we can give a short and a long list of,
and I wanted to trickle over to the why,
but let's just, like you said, the leadership,
but it goes beyond the leadership
because the whole lot is this way,
and I'm going to give an example.
I'll start off with this one.
I think, without mentioning names,
there's someone that's popular
that does stuff with sound, okay?
You record someone's voice
and you could tell if they're lying or their health
and all this other stuff.
I've been working on audio for a long time,
and I have a system which is a counterspatial system.
In other words, it's like a wafer.
You put it inside of a loudspeaker box or enclosure
and you get coherent sound.
So instead of getting
that really crappy speaker sound that you hear,
you know, whatever,
it opens up and becomes clear,
and it uses the concept of counterspace,
which exists in electricity, with magnets, nature,
all of nature has that, right?
It would be, counterspace is the idea of having,
let's say, a drain in your bathtub, right?
You have a large area that's affected by something,
but it all goes down into one spot.
So I'm able to develop that technology,
and when I found out about this woman
who worked with sound,
I immediately contacted her organization on the phone,
and I wanted to offer it to her.
But when I contacted the organization,
or someone who answers the phone
who works with the organization,
I had some time,
and you know how I can get very chatty,
and I said, it's kind of technical.
I mean, I mentioned what it is,
and she says, it sounds technical.
I said, it's actually not that technical.
A person on the other line said to me,
well, I don't like things that are technical.
I'm not technical, right?
And immediately, because I already prefaced,
this is a very simple thing.
It only has three parts to it
that you could make in your kitchen, right?
You could make this by going through your recycling bin
in your garbage, it's so simple.
But because I mentioned it's something
that no one else has figured,
anyway, she said she's not a technical person.
So immediately, what I said,
I said, okay, I'm not gonna mess with her,
but I wanna guide her along.
Let's see if I could do a quick psychotherapy
with this receptionist in two minutes.
So I said to her, ah, so you're not technical.
And she goes, that's right, I'm not.
I said, I just wanna mention a few things
that might be personal to you, is that okay?
And she said, okay, most people usually say okay
when I bring that up, right?
And I said, okay, let me just say,
while you were growing,
the reason why you're saying that,
even though it's something simple,
you haven't heard about what it is.
It just came up that it might be technical
and you're not technical.
So you've branded yourself as a non-technical person.
Just someone says, I'm not good at math
or I'm not good at this or whatever, okay.
And you go along, I said,
how long have you been saying you're not technical?
And she did, she was quiet.
I said, pretty much all your life, right?
Adult life at least, she goes, yeah.
And I said, let me tell you how you got to that place.
And she says, okay.
I said, all right, somewhere around your youth,
let's say between when you were born
to about eight or nine years old,
whether at your home or a familiar place
that you were comfortable in,
something similar to this conversation came up.
And someone that was well-respected
by everyone else and yourself,
let's say an aunt, your mom or dad
or a friend of the family,
when the technical matter came up,
they broadcasted to everyone in the room,
including you, that they are not technical
or good at math or whatever.
And everyone in the room agreed
that that was okay to say that
and it was okay to be that way.
And you being a child saw that happen
and now you're emulating it for the rest of your life
because your aunt who was well-respected
said she's not technical and everybody said it's okay.
You said, I want to be like my aunt.
All I have to do now is say I'm not technical
or I'm not good at math or I'm not,
you hear this often.
And you've shut that part of your life,
even though it was,
even though something might seem technical,
it's so simple, you've depraved yourself
and shut yourself off, right?
So I said, what does it take to undo that?
And she was like, I'll have her call you.
I have your number.
I got to go, bye.
Right, you see my point?
So very often when people say, well, that's math.
I'm not good at math.
Some point in their life,
they saw someone else say that
that was still respected after saying that.
And they said, I'm just going to emulate that.
So it's a form of laziness, right?
It's a form of emotional and spiritual laziness.
Chuck, I'm sure you've heard a lot.
You know, you've come up with a conversation.
Let's add these things in the presence
of I'm not good at math, right?
But look, we're just adding up
like single digit numbers here.
What's going on, right?
Well, right.
So there's, yeah.
I actually have a question, if you don't mind,
really fast because I'm thinking about this,
you know, from my own experiences,
I'm trying to draw on it.
And I'm thinking to myself, this is exactly right.
And I'm thinking that the reason
that she probably did that
is because it removed pressure
because now she would be dismissed from that conversation.
She would not be asked to participate in it
if she did that because that's what she saw happen.
Yeah, that's fine means, okay,
now we're not going to ask you
to do anything that has to do with that subject.
Let's just say it was math.
And somebody says, well, I'm not good at math.
Then that means that that person
is not gonna be asked to participate
in something that is mathematical.
And they see that and they say,
well, that's my way of getting out of being asked
or invited into participation, right?
Well, it's laziness.
It's an emotional laziness.
It's a spiritual laziness,
but it happens when we're young and impressionable.
But it also, because this young juvenile state of mind
is kept through one's life,
let's say a new field develops.
I've seen this very often with computers.
And I ask someone, I send you an email
and the person will be in their 70s or 80s.
So I'm too old to be into computers, right?
They'll say that just to get away from it.
Now I understand that.
Like when you asked me about something technical,
I said, I don't deal with the technical.
So that's because I decided not to.
And I could tell you why.
You don't want to spend hours and hours on this.
But the thing is, when let's say an older person says,
I'm too old to use computers or to have a computer,
I say, well, what about a telephone?
Can you use a telephone?
It's pushing digits and communicate, you see?
So it's this emotional laziness.
What I mean about that also is that the child would not,
let's go back to this particular example that I gave.
When I told her that someone influenced you
that also said something similar
and you decided to carry it on the rest of your life,
the point of not being that way is now you're missing out.
You're missing out on your personal growth
and also something that acoustic counter space
that I'm talking about,
it's just three pieces of material linked up a certain way.
It's so non-technical, actually, if I wanted to make these,
I could have third grader craft level skill
to make it, right?
You just need a scissor.
Basically, if you could cut cardboard, thin wood,
and use glue and felt, you can make it, right?
So it's not really that.
But she had decided,
I also asked her how old she was.
She was in her 30s.
So here's someone, we always encounter people,
but the most common, even more common than technical
is I'm not good at math.
You hear that often, right?
It doesn't matter what it is.
We're not talking about doing quadratic equations.
You hear I'm not good at math.
Even if you wanna say, look, there's two plus two
or plus four plus six plus seven,
right away, as soon as they hear it, they turn up
and they've decided to be emotionally lazy on that part.
And this is done by emulation.
And it's not only as a child.
So let's say when computers, PCs start to become popular
in the early 2000s and the person was 60 or 70 then, right?
They can say, well, do I wanna get into this or not?
Not really, because I'm intimidated.
I'll just say I'm too old for computers, right?
But they're missing out because it makes an excellent
a substitute for a telephone, right?
Right.
So there's this concept that goes on and on and on.
I've also heard when I brought up real history
to older people, like, well, I already was raised on this.
I don't wanna hear something different, okay?
Right, and so this is something that you can approach
someone who's later on in their life,
but they still have this very juvenile approach, okay?
So what is, for example, the storage capacity
of the human mind?
When you're exceeding, let's say you download 14 movies
on a new computer, it's gonna tell you
you're running out of hard disk space or memory, right?
What's the memory storage limit to human mind?
There is none.
I don't know that.
Yeah, as far as we know, there is none.
So you can, in other words, the way that we're set up
culturally, not possible.
But physically, the equipment that we have,
the mind, the brain, the body, the eyes and all that,
everyone can memorize every book that's ever been written.
There's no, if there's no limit,
if we haven't found the limit, right?
Because everything that's ever been written
or everything, let's say, in the Library of Congress
is limited, right?
It's confined.
So we can memorize everything, but we're taught not to.
Because imagine how open, what would happen?
How can you control people?
How could you put on the dribble that they put on,
quote unquote, the TV show they call the news?
If everyone that you're, if your audience has memorized
everything that's ever been written,
how can you put, you see what I mean?
They'll be able to access, cross-reference
every detail of the subject.
Right.
And say, you see?
So I took it to an extreme here that we're unlimited
because we really are.
But culturally, the culture that we're in,
the society that we're in, the way we were raised,
what I just said that we have unlimited memory
and we can memorize anything that's ever been written
through human history sounds ridiculous, doesn't it?
Well, no, it doesn't sound ridiculous to me
because simply the fact that I do not know
what the limitation is doesn't mean it doesn't exist either.
See, I have an open mind about this kind of thing
where there may indeed be a limit
to what the human mind can absorb,
but I do not know where that boundary is.
I don't know what that limit is.
It could be there, but I've just not explored it.
Look, I haven't explored outer space.
In the environment that we live in,
there is nothing that will limit us that way.
But go ahead.
Well, no, but that's the thing.
Like, I don't know what the limitation of outer space is.
Could there be one?
I believe there could be.
I'm certain that there could be.
I imagine that almost anything is finite
because I believe that almost everything
is finite in some way.
So...
Here's an interesting point.
You ready?
Okay.
And we brought this up.
This is kind of like a little bit of a salad,
a tossed salad thing, but I've studied a lot
on what they call outer space,
and I remember everything from what they told us
in the 70s and going to the library and reading about it
up until now with all the flat earth
and the dome and all this other stuff.
And I can recall stuff that I've read
in my third grade book.
Let's say, you know, primers, right?
I don't know, most people kind of shut it out,
but I could recall it pretty well.
Like, I have a scout handbook,
and I recall most of the stuff that's in there,
which is very helpful, by the way.
Very often when I'm out and about
and I tell people how to do a certain knot
or if you're gonna make a campfire,
put soap on the outside of the pot
before you put it in the fire
so that when it turns black and carbonized,
it's easy to rinse off, you know.
Where'd you get all that?
I said, I got it from the scout handbook.
You know, how old were you doing that?
I was 12 years old.
Do you still remember that?
Well, I don't know.
You wanna call it paying attention, you know, or whatever.
But everything that I've looked at
from what they call outer space
all the way through the Apollo stuff
and all the photographs and images
they show from telescopes,
I started saying more than 10 years ago
that everything you're hearing about that is untrue.
Not that it's fake,
but things that I tell you are far away are very close.
And things that are very close tend to be far away,
meaning out there, right?
And I'm not saying this.
And then the reason I said that
is because from all the information
that I remember seeing about it
and all the contradictions that they make, right?
And then when you couple that onto a lot of the commentary
that I have never seen a real image from outer space.
Do you trust it when they show you a picture?
I don't, because I can see right away
that it's artist's renditions, right?
When I went out and bought a telescope,
it's a big telescope.
And if I ever upload,
I think I have in the past uploaded photos
that I've taken of what they call the moon
and the planets and all that.
It just looks like an astronomy book, right?
It's a pretty big one, very good glass.
I don't see things the way through the telescope
as they're being shown.
I could, very, very different.
So when you have that experience directly
with what you've studied about it,
I could formulate this in a very educated way
in a very reasonable way.
Now, this is just an example.
You brought up outer space and the limit.
And I think that humans are gonna be in
for a really big surprise
when they find out what's going up there.
Let's just call it up there more than out there, right?
It's nothing like we've been told, but similar to.
By the way, let me just throw something in.
From speaking to someone who had flown in an SR-71
that basically you get to the point
where you can't go any faster
because there's no air, right?
You're skipping on the atmosphere.
And he was on the dark side of the earth
and say dark side of the moon.
And space is not black.
It's dark, dark, dark, dark blue, right?
So very interesting when you get up there.
And when he said that, it gave me a chill
because I remember the paint on that
in military grade paints,
when they want to make them really black,
it's actually a form of blue.
The darkest blacks are actually blues
that are toned down to look like black.
They absorb the most light.
Very interesting.
So I just wanna throw out there
because the guy I referenced earlier, Archaics,
he talks a lot about it being a complete construct.
And I agree with that.
I believe in the simulation and all that,
but it's constructed in a way
that we still physically interact with it as such.
Right?
It's not just a movie screen up there,
like some people would suggest.
But yeah, the juvenile tendency again,
comes in through that.
Like for example, juvenile,
it is, let me just bring this up.
And I brought this up before Chuck.
You know that in the Western culture,
more than other cultures,
we've created a subculture known as the kid's culture.
You know, a kid is a baby goat.
Yeah, yeah.
Right?
You got the meals at the fast food stores.
You got the toys.
You got the TV and the movies made for quote unquote kids.
It's a subculture.
Kids meals, kids channels, kids, kids, kids.
Yeah.
Everything.
Toys are okay.
In older, other cultures,
the children were viewed as just small people
that were bound to become like the adults
when they get bigger.
Right?
But they were not sequestered
and they didn't have a subculture for them.
Like there is now.
It is a subculture.
Now, if this society at large had a mature mindset,
meaning there were culture and mature,
ethically, morally, scientifically, mathematically,
every aspect of their culture was matured,
they would not agree to having a separate kid's culture.
Right?
Like that.
Why would you do that?
Because at what point,
there's no clear point when you're a quote unquote kid
and you do the kid's stuff to where you're not.
Where's the crosser?
Eight, nine years old?
Where you, right?
The children are told about Santa Claus
and when the child is about, I don't know,
gets their first bicycle, eight or nine or 10,
they ask about Santa Claus
and the parents immediately tell them,
what are you talking about?
There's no such thing.
Whoa.
It's like a slap in the face.
Right?
Right.
Suddenly.
So where does that end and where is it?
By the way, I also heard from someone,
you know, Santa Claus,
is a Santa Claus a hoax?
Well, come on.
If Santa Claus was a hoax,
do you know how many people would have to be in on it?
Right?
Well, you used to refer to it as pranks,
but yeah.
That's your conspiracy theory.
I gotcha.
Yeah, okay.
So this is the society.
So just the very fact that I see
that there is a subculture within the culture,
I mean, what else would you call it?
The kid's thing.
It's a subculture.
It's a culture within a culture.
Right?
Yeah, no, I have no argument there.
It is subculture.
It's a subculture by definition.
That means, that is actually not
because there is a separate subculture created.
It's actually the juvenile nature
of this society created that subculture
to run not beneath it or before it,
but side by side.
Right.
So only two things that are equal at parity
run side by side.
I see.
Okay.
So this is the juvenile.
So in other words,
if we did not have a juvenile,
we meaning the collective we,
did not have a juvenile mindset
throughout their whole society,
there's no way a subculture like that would exist.
You see?
Let's just bounce it.
If you bounce it the other way,
it's still juvenile.
You had like with 9-11,
the terrorism stuff, right?
So they develop all these terrorism,
anti-terrorism,
which actually goes after their own population, right?
What's interesting about that
is that if the authorities,
government administrators,
kings, monarchies, whatever,
were actually had the best interest
of the people in mind,
they wouldn't be threatening them
with surveillance and basically intimidation.
They would present a mature society
would present say we have a terrorist threat.
That means that we cannot lay back and be relaxed.
All everyone that quote unquote a citizen
has to be more vigilant.
And we have to learn safety protocols, right?
I'm not talking about just like snitching
on your neighbor or whatever,
but safety protocols.
No, but that's part of it.
That's part of it though.
Yeah, we got it.
Yeah, all of these preventive measures
more highlighted than the threat part of it, right?
Yeah, of course.
Yeah, so again,
it's like they're punishing children.
If you don't do your homework,
you're going to, right?
Yeah, but you're gonna,
you see there's a follow through.
All of the follow throughs,
the nature of the reactionary element
that you see with politicians and all this stuff,
you know, they don't,
no one speaks anymore like they used to.
Politicians used to get up and say,
oh, we're gonna look to the future generations.
We're gonna develop more bridges and this and that.
No one, the only time you hear anything political now
is when an event happens
or there's a complaint or something like that.
Again, reactionary.
It's reactionary as opposed to the,
you know, the,
like, okay, again, Kennedy's very easy to go back to
because he gave many, many speeches
in his short time in office as president.
And almost all of them were about
things that we were going to do,
things that were needed to be accomplished.
Some of the most dangerous speeches in my mind
were about, you know,
the possibility that we could literally abolish war,
not just, you know, make peace and react to somebody else,
but that we could go forward
and eliminate the need for the weapons altogether.
And that, to me, was a much more mature
way of conducting business.
You know, and that's the key complaint.
Whenever anybody says to me, for instance,
how would you improve planet Earth, basically, right?
Almost always my response is,
it's a little difficult to do
given that we have a society that needs to mature,
given that our species needs to mature.
And everybody's always baffled by that,
but I don't see how you can see it another way.
That is the only way.
Yeah, it's a maturity issue.
It's a maturity issue, right.
Because if you were to take it,
like you and I have talked about being all together
on this one particular place,
the boat concept and all being on the same rock,
I think we used to say, right?
Or something like this.
Or the cruise ship.
The cruise ship, there you go.
Everybody's going from point A to point B,
but while you're on the cruise ship,
you can do what you want, right?
That's free will.
Yeah, free will.
But see, there's the interesting thing, right?
Is that, well, I brought it down to a boat,
but the cruise ship, fine.
It gives you more options, all right?
But either way, the thing is, it's about maturity.
It's, you know, like what is it that would change
if that happened, right?
Well, I say, well, the first thing is
that there would be no requirement for prisons or churches.
They'd be gone.
Yeah, the church, but the religion is one of the reasons
we don't have visitors, you know?
Oh, well, there you go.
If we didn't have religion,
we would have plenty of other visitors from other worlds
saying, hey, you guys.
But anyway, so that will be gotten rid of, but go ahead.
Yeah, but that's the thing, though.
But that is part of a maturation.
If that happens, that would,
and people, they just don't, they don't get that.
You know, they don't want to hear that
because it steps outside of, oh, wait a minute.
It steps outside of exactly
what you just talked about before,
which is that someone who is respected
gave them a way to be lazy.
Oh, wait a minute.
Did I just come up with that?
I think so.
Yeah, that's a good way to say it, Chuck.
Someone that's respectable allows, you know,
emulating them allows you to be lazy.
Yeah, perfect.
You said it well, though, on that.
Oh, thank you.
All right, well, look,
I'm just putting these things together.
I'm trying to observe and report.
Yeah.
Something I, there's some phrasing
and a process that, frankly, I learned.
Yeah, we'll look at the.
Yeah, go ahead.
Sorry to step on you there,
but the pandemic thing that they did, right,
where they were putting that picture of a virus.
I mean, it looked like something out of,
what's that purple thing on Sesame Street?
They have, anyway, some dinosaur that's purple or whatever.
It's on that ilk, you know, the children.
The purple dinosaur was Barney.
He wasn't on Sesame Street, but I get it.
It's cool.
Yeah, but anyway, yeah.
It's all ridiculous, you know.
They're on a Barney level thing, and yeah.
So just to go back on the juvenile again,
instead of trying to figure out what is juvenile,
look at the other way.
Everything is juvenile.
See what is not juvenile, right?
Take it as a presumption and an assertion
that everything, like you said,
it's not a mature society, right?
If it's not mature, it's what?
It's juvenile.
Is there, adolescent would be in the middle, right?
Well, right.
I think if we made it to adolescence, it would be good.
So I think I've talked enough about eschatology,
which is how these things, you know,
the end of the world, meaning not the world planet material,
but the end of society, enough.
And we're gonna go over a little bit more in future sonics
with more precision.
But there is no, based on the,
cause I'm a catastrophist, right?
Not an evolutionist, you know, things get redone.
There have been points of maturity.
And what we're seeing now is the shades of it,
but we're not going to get it
because we're gonna be distracted by the revival
of ancient customs and ancient religions
and ancient ways of doing things
that we're gonna attribute
to the way this society has developed.
And it's not, it's actually a revival, right?
Of something that no one knows about.
Very little, very few people know about it.
And if you see it come on as new in the society,
you're gonna say, this is new.
And I'll say, no, it's not.
It's just something that's revived from 4,000 years ago.
Seems new to you, right?
Because you're not aware of this history.
But even when that's revived,
it's going to be done in a juvenile,
for the juvenile palette, right?
For the juvenile mindset.
So I can't stress enough on people look at society
like the email I got yesterday
about like why bother doing more sonic events?
It's not gonna change anything, right?
Well, no, it's not gonna change anything at large
because this society isn't gonna change for the better.
It has to be redone.
But in the meantime, I think you have an advantage
being more mature spiritually, cognitively,
and in many other ways, mature
when you're amongst juveniles, right?
You have an advantage.
I mean, imagine Chuck, you went back to the third grade,
but you looked like you did in the third grade,
but you have the mind that you have now.
Are you in an advantage, right?
Of course.
You wanna date the teacher, right?
Or something, let's say.
Okay, but.
Yeah, but that aside, you know.
No, it'll be difficult if you wanna date the teacher
and you're whatever, eight years old and she's 30.
That won't cross over, but most everything else will.
Right, right.
No, and there you have it.
I mean, again, so if you're able to mature a bit yourself,
and get ahead of the curve, so to speak,
this is a way of improving your own life.
But again, that concept that we also talked about
where if you improve the things around you,
the things that are within your reach,
the things that will have a direct effect on you,
you get both, right?
You get the ability to improve the thing around you.
And like you said,
if half the people in the world did this,
I mean, there you go.
Everyone would be taken care of.
So.
No, well, the thing is, you can't lean on it too much.
In other words, if, okay, so you wanna share things
that you know are objectively better,
whether it's whatever the subject matter is.
And the people around you might accept it,
if everyone does, and maybe somebody will get it and say,
hey, we can improve this, or maybe leave out this.
But generally, you can start everyone around you,
so it's going in that direction, great.
But what if you're doing that and no one listens,
and you're actually made fun of?
So you can't base, in other words,
don't be attached to it.
Because you know what?
Based on being on this planet now for six decades,
they're not gonna listen.
Even people, let me just go even more heartfelt on this.
If you're in a family unit,
whether it's wife, husband, children, whatever, whatever,
they're not gonna listen, you see.
In most cases, in most cases from a spiritual point of view,
you know, your real family is not the litter
that you were born in.
I say that litter meaning because it's purely physical.
Your family is outside spiritually
because you're spread out in a way that,
because if each family had done this,
then it would change, actually make some real changes.
And what I just said, each family does a certain way
based on the overarching culture that they're in,
you see, also.
So that's an inherent problem in that as well.
But I wouldn't be attached to it
if it doesn't happen around you.
Like you mentioned, let's make things better.
No, no, don't be attached to it,
but you have to do it anyway.
Well, before we get further into that,
I wonder if you wouldn't break that down a little more
about the difference between physical relationship
and spiritual relationship
because there is a huge difference.
I note that many of the people that I've interacted with
who have listened to you, but also listen to my show,
it's, they're a bit different from the people
that I just run into randomly when I go out in public.
All right, they have a slightly different thought process.
They are a little more akin already,
before they ever encounter what it is that I'm doing
or what it is that you and I have done.
They're already a little different
when they encounter us, right?
They're, how am I getting at this?
Why don't we take a break for ourselves
and for the listener?
Just, we could just take a little breather
and we'll come back and hash out
the spirit versus the physical.
I think that's an excellent idea.
Let's do it.
All right, let's talk about the status quo
and the partnership with the Greek community
on the ground level.
story tells from   igon,
it's going to go like this.
Okay, fair enough. I guess well, we could say one and a half one and a half. Okay, one and a half
Well, we're at the halfway point of one. So why not?
Exactly if you're moving it along the number line, it makes sense
Anyway back to making sense though. We were talking about the the the different relationships
Okay, again, one of those words. I'm skeptical of because when something is in relation to something else
Does it relate things like this people have sort of misused those terms a bit
But look there is something to the idea that there is a physical relationship
Because one thing is related to another as you said physically you might be from a certain litter again
It's about the physicality
Sure, you have your genetic connection, you know your family you look alike you came from
Similar stock all that kind of stuff, but there's another heartache
Physical the carnal the carnal the physical very good
But then there's other
Considerations here and I started to ask about you know, what about the spiritual relationship? What about those?
You know again not not having to do with the litter of the physicality. So how do we separate that? How do we?
Understand that these are well, I think related but also
Yeah, don't go back to what you remember when you started you were talking about relationships, right?
You said the word relationship. Let's define that think about it this way from a Greeks week. Let's well, okay
Think about it this way. Yeah, I think about it this way from a Greek speak perspective
You said relationship about four times earlier and I was thinking. Oh, wow. We got to bring this up. What is a relationship?
What the way I would define it which is actually based on a functional sense because you could use that term
Loosely when you're at work and someone says I'm having a relationship with so-and-so
I mean that could mean a lot right right or whatever or relations or whatever. Okay from the Greek speak point of view. It's boundaries
boundaries, okay, what kind of boundaries so let's say
You have a relationship with
someone next to you
Wow, that is so broad and so open. Well, what happens is there's brown boundaries that are set there
So for example
You can have a relationship with a co-worker and the way you relate to them is only at work on
On a verbal basis you keep your distance. You might have lunch, right?
so if you're gonna go ahead and grope them or
Ask them something quote-unquote, whatever. It's the quote is too personal
What do you see go up you think?
What they do is remind you of what the boundary you've overstepped or it's within the boundary, right?
You're out of bounds like in sports, right? So you're playing this game
It's a dynamic and remember it if no one's on the field and no one's nothing's moving. There's no there's no game
So it's about motion. So let's say you're very intimate with someone
You know, you know, I'm lascivious and could be carnal minded you can even let's say a wife a husband or something
Boyfriend-girlfriend like people still use or whatever. They even then have boundaries. Let's say take it to the to the limit
One person might like this sexual position or whatever. The other person says no, that's too much for me, right?
So what does that define the relationship? No, what I'm saying is
That the word relationship is an overarching way to say
What kind of boundaries we have so when someone says relationship and you hear that it's very loose in general and
When you start describing the relationship, you're not really describing the relationship, but you start with describing the boundaries that are set
If that makes any sense, no, it does because it is about the boundaries
I mean I could even say for instance
I have a relationship with someone I just regularly see or regularly interact with not even at work forget that
Because there's all kinds of terminology now attached to that which I think has gotten away from what you're talking about
But if you go to you just you are regular at a store say Greek, right?
You might have sort of a relationship with somebody there because they have a familiarity with you. They know your name
They might know the product you buy like you and I might talk about going to buy a pack of cigarettes
That guy knows something
So they have no comes in he'll let him grab a free bag of chips
But he may not let you because the boundaries are different, right?
He knows to get my cigarettes, but he's not hooking me up because I'm not his brother, you know
Where the brother comes in grabs a chips and a drink and waves and goes. Goodbye. That's cool
But you try to do that. He's gonna make you aware of what the boundary you just crossed the line. They say right? Mm-hmm
Exactly. Okay
So the relationship that we use the term in this Western culture usually means
More than friendly, you know, usually sexual intimate
Or whatever, you know, like for example three roommates
Sharing an apartment have a relationship. That's more of a loose boundary
Right, then then some people that are dating. Let's say okay
So right because you the chances of going on a date and the person shows up at the restaurant
Just came out of the shower wearing a towel around their waist. It's probably not going to happen
But if you're right, that's not acceptable, right? But if you have roommates all guys little girls, whatever, whatever
If you have a roommate gets out of the shower and they get out with a towel around them. That's it
I mean, it's acceptable right your roommates, right?
See so the setting and the pre agreed you could also have roommates say look
I don't want to see you like that. Make sure you're fully dressed. What'd you just do?
You just set a boundary
right, so this thing about relationships is all these boundaries and and
Let's go back to the familial. Like you said
The litter right? I said that earlier as well when I say litter it's it's it's like the most
Reductionist thing you could say, you know, it just means purely
Animalistic, let's say in a way out of the similar to animals
Basically, you come out of the the mother you're nurtured and then you're you're off to the wild, right?
Essentially people do that as well
So what boundaries now for example when you're in a family and you have an authoritative parent and
You bring up something at the dinner table. They'll tell you don't mention that again in this house
How many times have you heard that either in film or in real life, right? Oh, yeah
Okay, what did they just do they set a boundary
You can't talk about whatever at home, but you you can talk about that with your friends
Let's say out, you know at the park or somewhere another setting. So the boundaries there are much more loose
outside
So you have a spiritual boundaries in the in the home family which in most cases through a convention not all but in most cases
This is the religion that we practice here in this house, this is what we believe in in this house, right?
So you're you find out like let's say your particular religion you you find out or it doesn't feel right
Let's say intuitively is very important
Most people that are in any religion intuitively, they know it's not the be-all end-all of spirituality in most cases
Once they leave the boundaries of the home the mental boundaries of spiritual boundaries. They can discuss it outside of the home
You've heard that too. Yeah, right those terms being used
so these relationships basically when you form a relationship with someone what whatever it might be like you and I have a
Relationship doing these sonic events, right?
All the way to the most intimate relationship what it is
It's a series of boundaries that are either removed or set up to a certain point
So once we start viewing these these boundaries, I mean you see this legally all the time, right?
You can't like you can't go behind this line employees only right, right
It's everywhere
Boundaries are being set up constantly. Now. The thing is, you know, part of the legal thing is to get around these boundaries legally without
Seeing it being seen as a violation
Right in law. You don't have that because law is
Something that you don't get around you you understand and you perform right? You don't violate right on your own
And
By the way, one day we'll get into it biblically
There are a lot of it's very difficult to to put through a lot of the old hardcore laws that you find in the Bible
It's not as easy the certain conditions have to be met. It's not like people think right? So it is actually a very free system and
The only way I can give an analogy for that is when they look for legal legal
Loopholes the guy who has the better lawyer has more freedom, right? But actually in law, there's a lot of freedom
But it's more upfront. It's not let's try it a way to go around it the same way that I just mentioned
When you get into a relationship and boundaries are removed
Then certain boundaries are set to be more restrictive. So let's say you have
Intimate relationship with someone and you find out that they set this boundary here in a particular particular
Sexual
Position that you might want they don't
Well, what will happen if depends on how you affect that boundary affects you might say?
Oh, I used to like doing it this way now
Maybe I need to go find someone else that doesn't have that boundary even though I'm not in a relationship just to do that
You see so there's an aspect to it. Also that we have to realize
That when you hit a boundary like that that you find
Limiting or whatever to make sure that it doesn't get to you emotionally that might lead you off to do things that you
Normally, you know aren't right. Well, there you have it. I mean look an undesirable
Boundary, I guess would be the best way to put it right because if you're in a let's go back to the other example
Of you know in this house, you can only speak about this right when it comes to religion or whatever
I mean in some places somebody could say, you know, look you got to be a Yankees fan in this house
Or is something stupid? It doesn't matter. Sure. Sure. No, I've heard that. Yeah, you know, but but either way, okay
What that often does though is if somebody feels as though that is unjust or they don't
Intuitively agree with that they leave the home. They'll often seek to explore something other
You know again, you can't you can't say I mean I've heard this many times
I know this is a complex thing and could lead us in the wrong direction, but allow me to use it for an example
You know, the the only the only God we recognize in this house is it has to do with Jesus?
Okay, I've heard that many a time, right?
So you can't even discuss anything that isn't with that guy. That's it
now immediately when the
The children the people not in authority in that house the people not really in charge of setting those boundaries
Who are supposed to abide by them immediately when they leave the house? What is almost one of the first things they'll do
Seek to explore
Relationships without those boundaries one way or another or when then they'll find that there's still boundaries there
But they're different and they're favorable or more favorable based on what their desire is
That's why I say it's either a desirable or an undesirable boundary, right?
And also what their knowledge base is and when their knowledge grows they may not like it or whatever. Yeah, right. It's all yeah
It's sympathetic as well
In other words
What I'm trying to say is once you first thing that happens when you hit a boundary or a limitation is you have an emotional?
Response a reactive response unless even when you're approaching the boundary, you know, it's they're like, ah, we've reached the point now
There's always going to be an emotional and a reactive response and want to tie that into the spirit and the mind
Okay
But what did you I hope the people listening?
Relax into this because I might start using the boundary issue or the concept more than the relationship issue, right?
Because I think that I think that gives you more of the engineering of what we consider a relationship you the way an inch
Let's just put it this way the way you engineer a relationship is by knowing what boundaries are there
right, right, so
We brought up the spirit earlier and the family and where your spiritual quote-unquote family now usually when you say family
It's a unit or a group, right?
I'm I am against not against family, but the moment groups start to form
Again, the boundary is defined. You're in our group or you're not in our group, right?
So this is another form of boundary again sees the you know a member or not a member, right? So
When you look at something let's go
Delve into most people that have heard Ocelli in the Greek or Greek speak know that I'm a stickler about defining the spirit now
The all the reference material that's been put out that we have access to in any language through time
They wouldn't be deceiving us or trying to confuse us would they?
In reference material, right? Of course not never right. Okay. All right. So let's just do this
If you see something contrary to this I would consider it a typo based on logic reason and and good solid information
When you look up the word spirit
Etymology dictionary or whatever it tells you it is also the soul the mind the breath
When you look up the word soul
The definition is it's also
The spirit the mind and the breath whoa, whoa, whoa, wait a second
You know
That that's not much of a definition. Is it what's your first clue, right?
What they're trying to tell you is that the soul and the spirit are the same within the deaf, right
They just invert it whether you look up spirit or soul
They give you the same definition pretty much one after the other and that's it. Yeah, right
So what are they hiding there?
Well, the thing is is such a benign such a common like the word nice, right, right
You know everything wants to be everything to be nice, but when you look it up
It doesn't make any sense why we're using that word that way, but let's put that away. This is how everybody uses it, right?
Okay. Well you get a lot further
Because you understand what's called coding when the the elite or the people that run the planet
they're not the easiest way to survey people is just like
Social media if they want to find out about your personal life
They have to have agents and all these things to look at what you're doing
But if they put a social media you will volunteer to give it all away
Right, the social media is is a secondary
Part to the language coding
So for example when they see everyone using the word nice when anyone can figure out what it really means
They said well, these people are not looking they look at the society and say they're not looking at references
They don't care what words mean if we get enough people to use it this way the rest will follow
Right and the same goes with everything whether it's taking shoes off at the airport
Paying taxes what they call paying taxes this the money system or if we get enough people to emphasize
The rest will follow and that's pretty easy
System to employ, you know or a methodology so you can control the population
And the ones that want to show what it really is are the oddballs out and they're bad
Well, I'll give you a for instance
I actually have this question about that where I think it's just become acceptable and it seems to be a very benign
Sort of thing, but the concept of tying a piece of cloth around your neck right the tie
It seems to me to be functionally foolish to do so
Especially with the way a lot of people make them
I mean, they're basically putting a noose around their neck made out of cloth and yet
This is the kind of thing you do to what to dress up to look more proper
What sure what is the point of that piece of cloth?
I I wondered this this is one of those things I've carried with me since I was a child was a
Where I was a mark, you know, and I said to myself, it's a marker. It makes no sense though in a functional
Yeah, well, well, if you know anyone that worked for EMS or EMT
So anybody ever get hung by a ties that happens all the time. He wasn't wearing that tie. He would have been alive
Oh, yeah, it gets caught in a machine. Yeah, it gets caught a door. Yeah elevator, whatever. Okay, what what it
what it did in certain chivalry and
Heraldry when you wore that band
When you look at someone and the stripes are angled, you know striped tie and they're angled down towards the right
That means you're a right-handed. So your sword you're advertising that your weapon is at your side on your right side
if you were a lefty when you wore the band or the tie the stripes and the dip and the
Markings would go down towards the left and that would let whoever was coming that you're left-handed and the sword would be revealed from your
Left side. This is from the old days of heraldry and stuff, right?
Okay, and then it went on to people who wore markings to it being decorative to just being pure tradition
But let's go back to the spirit and the soul. So we'll do a fast, you know
I could speak really fast, but I won't well
But the reason why I brought up the tie is not not because of what you just mentioned, which is correct
I know that part of it now, but as a child I looked at it and I said that it serves no functional purpose
it is now just something that is a matter of
tradition and
Compliance so it's just an acceptable thing when you see someone with a tie on
They are elevating themselves in some way
But it's but but it's fairly recent because let's go back to the Revolutionary War period in the US or before that
You're not going to see people wearing ties. You don't see George Washington or whatever on the on the bills wearing ties, right?
It's a ruffle. So that that's a whole other thing. I have I did about 40 years ago
I did look into that and I don't read I do recall some of but I don't see or remember exactly how
It became fashionable like for example
The reason why haberdasher
This is just to go forward not get into fashion too much
But people stopped wearing hats if you watch all black and white movies
Everyone wore a hat when they went outside usually denoted what your profession was in your status in society
But it really fell off in their early 60s because Kennedy was the first
President to not always be publicly wearing a hat as a matter of fact
I've never seen a photo of Kennedy JFK wearing a hat in public and all the men want to be cool
So they stopped wearing their hats
that's something I heard from a woman that was around during those days people stopped men stopped wearing hats when they saw Kennedy JFK not
Wearing a hat right you see how this goes back to the coding
yeah, if you get someone important to do something right and
Okay, so the soul and the spirit and the body
They need to be defined because well, you know, I used to get into the wall
I used to say there's no need to define the body
But it is critically attached to the soul because when the soul dies
the body dies
Right the spirit could could leave the body and the body is still alive by the way if the soul so the soul is what?
Keeps you animated
The body is the physical all the physical stuff. However, you want to break it down to minutiae the soul is
Your metabolism it is the nervous system. It is the circulatory system your breathing
All of the way, you know all the organs function
When you speak on pulse in the Western world, they take your pulse
It's your heart, but in other cultures older medicines your liver has a pulse your kidneys have a pulse, right?
Your lungs have a pulse every every major organ in the body has its own independent pulse. They're 12 pulses that they take
Okay, and we've gotten into the medical we will again. We don't have a medical system. That's viable
It's basically barred from the military battlefield medicine
so
that pulse of all the organs and your heart and your lung is
being animated in the body by your soul by your metabolism, that's why a
Soul when when someone is not breathing and you administer CPR
You're putting your soul into their body until they can then be dependent on their own soul. It's not only breathing
It's also your metabolism because you know a healthy person can hold their breath for over two or three minutes, right one exercise
When you study Tai Chi Tai Chi or Qigong is how long can you hold your breath also in yoga, right?
And most people think it's ridiculous, but someone who's not fit can't do it very long, right?
Advanced you so advanced judo classes as well, you know, yes the pedestrian
Yeah, I just I know that by experience. Sorry. Okay. Good. So you confirm it?
From your experience, so
So this soul that everyone's being used. Yes. I know there's soul food. That's soulful and all that
It's been shoved over to the cart. Well, look if the soul is intrinsically connected to the body and vice versa
You'd have to be a very carnal materially minded
Society
Haha to lump everything together like that to make the soul you see what I mean?
So they take the spirit definition and tell you it's the soul because once you start going into the spiritual side
What happens to the body the physical materialistic side not that it becomes less important because you need it to animate
right
You know what I'm talking about Casper the ghost right floating around
We're talking about a physical material animation that requires the living soul to make a living body
So the when the soul leaves the body there's no more metabolism meaning no breathing no nervous system
No pulmonary system cardiac system stops. Then the body goes into
Decomposition you see spirit is something completely different from all of that and that is the mind
Now, let's go back
To the basic definitions. We said earlier
They wouldn't be deceiving us or giving us improper information in our reference materials
Would they when you just look up soul and it says spirit mind breath and you look up spirit
It's a soul mind breath. Well, wait a second. Wait a second. Why are they there's something being hidden here?
Just like the word nice
Right, is it really hidden though? Does it take up a lot of what does it take to find out what the word nice means?
etymologically not much
Okay, so the same thing goes here and when we get into the concept of the spirit I've given the analogy
if you gave a
CD or a movie or something to a material scientist
He'll come back with a report and he won't see what's recorded on that medium
Unless he has the proper thing device to play it and if it's a old magnetic tape
He needs a tape player if it's a CD. He needs a CD player or a computer
But as a material scientist doing his job
He's going to measure it weigh it tell you what materials are on there the grooves and what but he can't see it's the Beatles
White album
Until he puts it into a specific device
That's outside of his tools because the material scientist isn't going to give you a tour of his lab and say this is the CD player
Right very rarely
That won't happen. So when you get the material science report you give him Beatles white album
He can't see that and he went into and did an in-depth report on what's on that CD
You pull out your little whatever Walkman or remember those days and or a CD player and you say look it has all this music
on it
The physical body and the soul the physical body would be the CD player
The soul would be the electricity whether it's battery or plugged into the mains to power the CD player
Right the CD player won't work if you unplug it or take the batteries out. That's your soul. Okay?
So the spirit is what's recorded on the medium that cannot be seen unless it's played on a particular device
Your spirit your mind who you are which makes it's intangible
Even though they say there's 21 grams or 28 grams that leaves the body when someone dies, that's the levity
It's not the spirit
There's no material aspect to it. Just like there's no if I give you a
CD of Beatles white album and you weigh that CD Chuck and I
And you could play that CD and yes indeed
It does have the whole Beatles white album if you're able to wipe that CD and wait again, would it weigh any different?
No
Same with magnetic tape if you had an old cassette tape, you know, remember how sometimes you they had a little tab
So you don't accidentally record over it. You break the tab. It won't record
Let's say I record some music leave the tabs on weigh the tape listen to the music and then wipe the music
Where the magnet does it change any weight? No, it doesn't
Effectively, it's like saying well how much does my thought weigh right now?
Exactly it's a completely immaterial right just like I mentioned on the last call just I think this is a very good analogy when you
find someone
That has an ailment or a disease or whatever then you find a plant in the wild that cures it or alleviates that
Right, if you give that to a quote-unquote
Academically training whatever they're going to ignore everything about that situation
I want to find what chemicals material chemicals are in the plant, right?
To reproduce or patent or whatever right and that's not that's why the medicines don't work
Only medicines that work are the ones that go directly after the nervous system
you know like the
The things that bring you down on the things uppers and downers basically and painkillers. The rest of it is a total mystery to them
okay, so the spirit is the intangible part and it's the information and you are
Not only the carrier of the spirit
But you're also the device that plays the spirit an example of you being the carrier of the spirit is when you're asleep
Right, okay. You're you're not doing anything. Well, let's say there's no dreaming your your your soul is at a very restful state
when you get up in the morning, essentially you're hitting play and
The music comes on
well, look, I hate to do this to you, but I actually want you to go back over this because
Moving a little quickly. I just maybe it's just me and I hope nobody listening get upset because
It's a little odd to me that I am both
I mean, it almost seems like my body would have to be the CD player as
opposed to
Okay, so let me get this all straight and see if I understand or I I have followed what you were saying
the
The body is the CD player
The mind and spirit are
are actually interchangeable aren't they because
Yes, that's the same thing. Let's let's okay. The CD is inextricably connected to the CD player
In other words, it's a part of the material
physically related object and therefore so a CD the information on the CD is not
Perceptible unless you put it together with the unit that's supposed to play it the same with the spirit
Let me just maybe this is the part and remember you left out the soul
The soul is the power what powers this?
Solar battery. Yeah, I didn't get there yet
It's very important the energy the energy that makes it run because here's the problem
You could have all those parts and the information is there but if you don't have the energy it does nothing
It just sits there. So that's the soul. That's your metabolism the breath the breath, right?
So with and when you stop the breath the rest of the system goes down, doesn't it?
it is suffocation you end up with a a hole a
An empty shell and a well not really no
No, when you stop the breath and you get suffocated or asphyxiated, it's you could provide from that
You could revive you come back from that. Oh, yeah, usually no
No, I think it's revived before chemical decomposition, right? But once it really fully stops working. That's the end of it
It's just you know a thing there. There are ways to revive always but
But but anyway
Let me just make sure I got this. So
The difference between the spirit and the soul is that the spirit is the intangible?
Right. It's the thing that's not perceptible
It's the information. Let's stick with the CD. It's the information on the CD, right?
Thank you can cannot see that's the information the energy
though is
different because that's
See, this is where I'm getting energy. The energy is completely connected to the physical
It is the energy itself. It could be a hand crank like let's go further back from a CD. Let's say you have those old
Magnet, what are the gramophones the Edison you hand crank it and a physical needle is magnified through a horn
There's no electricity there
To play the record, right?
With those grinder boxes. Yeah, you can do a spring-loaded cameras even same thing. Yeah, you have to wind it up. Yeah, okay
Yeah, let's do it. Let's go to a little more technical years ago. It's called a prime mover, right?
So when you set up a generator
to power a city
Your prime mover would be a steam engine or burning coal or oil or something or nuclear to get the thing turning, right?
It's called a prime the soul in engineering terms is called the prime mover
Because it animates the body and without the body the whole thing doesn't play
Okay, so let's go back. Maybe this might be easier. Let's give a reference that is pretty solid
You know the English language most languages borrow from other languages, right?
They by the way in a I'm going to use the Greek prefix PNU is where you get
Pneumatic pneumonia that has to do with the movement of air
The soul in Greek is a pneuma pneuma
Pneuma
Pneuma they pronounce pneuma. Okay
That is the soul
So if we look at what the English is borrowing to communicate this the PSY prefix
Psyche or psyche means the mind or the or the spirit
We need that's where we use the prefix
Psychologists psychotic right that has to do with the mind
Which is the spirit so we do find?
if we go back and look at the root and how this
Concept of spirit and soul is
Communicated using Greek prefixes and we look at the roots of the Greek prefixes, which are typically pretty
Technical right, you know, we use a lot of Greek prefixes like pro or ante or whatever
So you can take any word and put the PRO prefix and it'll change its meaning or if you take any word and put the
Anti meaning the anti prefix it will change it
So the same goes true for spirit and soul when the PSY prefix shows up which means spirit
It means it has something to do with the mind
So if you run into someone that has a PSY in their job description psychologists psychiatrists, you know what?
They're if you really wanted to translate that word into more simple term
They wouldn't be called a psychologist or a psychiatrist. It would be called a spiritualist
Think about it, right? Okay. So when you say I have a pneumatic tire or pneumonia
Are you thinking about your big toe or your spit or your mind?
No, you're thinking about your lungs. It's air. It's a movement of air and pneumonia of the lungs. So yeah, exactly, right?
Okay, so if I say I have a pneumatic problem, do they tell you you go to a psychiatrist? No, that's right
Okay, so this is how in other words when I realized this decades ago. I was like wow
I just like split an iceberg
Because these things were all lumped together and they're really as different as anything could be but are they related, you know
It's like if you if you cut the cable off of the CD player the wire that plugs into the mains into the wall, right?
That is just a piece of wire, right?
But it's it's an it's very important that you that you attach it in order to play the thing, right?
So are there many aspects to this that are like that?
That's why I like to stress the soul and the body work together if those two stop working like you could have the CD player
But if you unplug it, you ain't hearing nothing, right and you won't because you're not going to turn it by hand
It's it requires a lot. The CD player is a better analogy than the gramophone that you turn by hand
You know the old grinder thing, right? Okay, so because you could physically just by hand turn it
Without even a CD player
You're not going to power the laser and the timing chips and all ain't gonna happen just like your body
You need the the cable. So you need the soul to keep the body going by the way when someone is on
What do they call it when you're in the hospital if they unplug you you die?
What do they call that? They got someone there's life support or yes life support
So what life support is a synthetic soul?
Mm-hmm. Think about if they if they unplug him he dies, right? So what so what's the difference?
Well one when you're plugged into life support, it's assisting the breathing with a ventilator, right? It's probably doing other things, right?
All right. Okay, that's your soul. It's basically a so the soul has been duplicated
Technologically in most cases right and so as the spirit, but that gets us so teric the speed of you know
That's the personality. You can have a portable spirit every time if you have a CD player or DVD collection
each one of those discs has a different spirit but if like I said on the last time we spoke publicly if you scratched all
The titles off and put them in a big pile
The only way to find out what's on it is to play it right the only way in this realm
There's no way you can detect it other than the in using the device that it was used to power
So the spirit opens up and it shows us that we are basically running an information protocol
Okay, I just took it forward and I
Don't know how much more to simplify it because certain there is no like out of the okay
I
Think I broke it down and I have been breaking it down this way for a very long time
What I gave the information that you have the physical body that requires the soul which is the breath and the metabolism
Once those two are working together and you're conscious awake
the spirit then
Can be can perform through that or it seems to be animated through the body right unless there's telepathy
Right. Okay, because if unless you're animating with your voice drawing or your actions the old as they say
I can't read your mind, right? You have to tell me right? Well, that's so you're gonna be vocal. Yeah, that's communication
Versus the internal. I mean you you can play the CD and if there's no speaker
To express it. It's not being heard. It is playing the information is running
And it is happening, but it's not being communicated. It's not being heard because you also require the speaker
That that would be a monk living in solitude, right?
You just he's still thinking he's still alive, but no one's getting anything out of his head
Yeah, nobody because he's not speaking to anybody. He's not can write so it's part of it. Yeah. Yeah the CD player
Let's say it's a boombox
But it's part of a system just like we are part of a system and those other
Attachments come on spiritually then they manifest physically like for example
You can get a mindful notion and then change your physical appearance. It's called fashion
Why do you why does this guy always wear black? Where did he get that?
Like every time he walked to the closet all the black clothing at the rack at the store jumped on him
No, he literally made a decision to do that tattoos what you eat
Where you
Everything communication is not just how you speak and write. It's actually you can communicate a lot. Well, it's not even such your appearance
Yeah, well, that's the thing too is that it's not even necessarily about a direct decision, right?
because when somebody is feeling differently internally and they tell you this all the time every kind of
life coach somebody who advises somebody professionally
Etc. What do they always tell you?
Your attitude will change the way that you present yourself to people because what's going on internally gets
Communicated why your posture changes you stand up straighter. Sure you present that's communication
So that's your committee, but your attitude is based on information in your mind
All right, if you have a negative outlook that if you analyze how you got the negative outlook you would see a transcript of
Information that lead led you that way and the opposite would be true
But the thing I wanted to bring up because it to bring it back to your spiritual family are the ones that you
Even though you're still communicating through the physical part
The mental part does not meet any of the spiritual part meaning the mental the information that you convey back and forth meets
No resistance until you hit a boundary and that defines what we call the relationship
Right. So let me give you an example how this has been corrupted
Okay, if you speak to a
Christian they say it's a personal relationship with God they say right
Okay, that is the same kind of juvenile cop-out as the person that says I ever I'm not good at math
He starts saying what's 2 plus 2 plus 7? I'm not good at math. Wait a second a chicken can do that
You don't even have to be right
I think birds count better than that can count that because again at some point in their life
Decided so they could spend the rest of their life saying that to get out of working on that particular topic
Right is emotional laziness the same thing when they say you have to have a personal relationship with God. Oh, wow
Personal means personal that means I cannot give you an opinion on that and you can't tell me what to do
I can't tell you what to do
So someone who says I have to have a personal it's about having a personal relationship with God
They just put themselves in a cage
Right because for anything from the outside to come in to either diminish that or improve it as nearly impossible
Well another way to kind of look at this is that and it took me a while to figure it out
You know, I admit it's slow learners sometimes
but
In personal relationships, right? What has worked? Everybody always says well you get comfortable with somebody
You don't get comfortable with somebody there is comfort in guess what there is a lack of resistance
right to your way of being like I point out all the time that the the people that I've had the longest relationships with
have been people where there isn't a
resistance you can just sit there and
Be around them and there isn't a need to perform. There isn't a pressure. There isn't a boundary there isn't
Constant rules because it's already boundaries are not rigid. They're not rigid because you're actually already
Sort of oriented that way. It's it's already there
You know, you don't have to build it and people say oh, no
You have to build these things and you have to establish them and if you're doing all that work, then obviously
You didn't you know, you didn't have that relationship on that level
And I don't know if I'm
No, well, it's not really a level because when we say level it's vertical, you know, yeah up or down I would say this
very simply if you if you
react to something
Whether it's positive or negative that reaction has to have some kind of a stimulus that brought it on right
Okay, so there if you have a very rigid boundary with someone and you hit that boundary and there's a reaction
Also, if you have a very loose boundary or no boundary there's a reaction
like if you let's say have a co-worker and
Let's say you're a guy and she's a gal and you find her very attractive and you're like
you don't know how to ask her out on a date and
One day right before lunch she gets up and gives you a big hug and tongue kisses you
Right, even though you wanted that a very passionate kiss or something like that you kind of freak out a little bit
It's almost as much as if you didn't want it the reaction right because it's so out of the norm
So sometimes it's not the impedance
The resistance is not only sometimes what defines a relationship. It's also that there's no boundary can define
If the spirit is the mind and knowledge when you have a situation where you have a quote-unquote a free flow of knowledge
There's no boundaries there for knowledge right like censorship for example, right?
Is a type of relationship, right? How many people do you hear?
I can't put this on YouTube. All right. I can't say this on YouTube, right or whatever. Okay?
What what they're doing is funny. I've been watching this for a long time
YouTube is controlling the relationship by putting up certain boundaries and penalties and
violations and all that the same thing happens constantly but
When we go over to the again the family and the the spiritual family not being in your family is not always true
But in most cases it is because of the culture that the family was in and then it also depends on the person's maturity
So think of it this way
Let's say you're a young child and you already established that from a young
Let's say the a formative years eight or nine years old
It is true. It is like a bit of wisdom that you have your your personal material family mom dad sister, whatever
dog and
But your real they may or may not be your real spiritual family
Your real spiritual family is out there and you just have to meet them
Think about what kind of an advantage you would have or also if you were very young and knew that and also
How that can be taken advantage of if it was part of your culture how you would be taken advantage of it, right?
So either way you can't be naive about this
but the thing to bring it home was because this whole thing that sparked off this one and a half parts is
the spiritual family and the physical family and the the concept of the
The the mind which is the spirit the soul the metabolism and the body and
Tying it all together. It will probably won't get done until we again mature and
What comes with that maturity is patience?
How many times have I been on?
Sonic events and I said it's not time yet to talk about this for years. Oh, yes
And then time goes by and then I do give more information and it's not because I'm hoarding or anything like that
I just don't see any relevancy or any value in it at the moment. That's my personal decision
but the importance of the
Which we're going to get into time a little bit more like when we were on break. I said look if you
cognitively
Train yourself first. You have to tell yourself and then becomes normal like when you first learn to tie your shoelaces
You might you really had to pay attention to what you were doing the first few times you did it, right, right
Okay, but then now you don't the same with many other things we take
As being everyday occurrences, we don't have to think about once you start acknowledging and making a reminder to self
However, you want to do it and I mean like in-your-face reminder that the day starts at solar noon wherever you are
You're going to have a reactive change in your body. That's you're going to feel suddenly like you just clicked in
It's kind of like
You know when you're setting up your musician and you're setting up the PA system or the amplifiers and all that
Even if you don't know what you're doing
You're going to get to a point where you say this is how it sounds the best, right?
If I do it this way I get feedback this way. It's not loud enough, right?
That's part of the timekeeping and isn't information flow
Also a matter of time, you know how many megabytes per second right, right
How many words can you type per minute or how many words? Can you read per minute?
right
And all this other stuff
So how about it when we start getting into a society that is has ratings constantly rated how many words per minute or?
Whatever, whatever
Once you understand that you could do it all at the same time
But you have to do it in a way based on a time function that it that it can be communicated and make sense
Right, like how many times have you heard someone I have I have so many things
I want to say and I can't say it all at once. I have to go down the line, right?
You have this serial kind of thing
You have to say one thing and then the next thing you can't be speaking it to
There are singers by the way that could sing multiple chords and tones very very difficult
Well, so or there is a natural thing sometimes built in
I mean, there's a semi or additional tone that is due to a physical structure
But it's it's rarefied to intentionally do that is is something that is difficult. But then again
if we look at
Communication as it's evolved. I know you know technology is a difficult subject, but here's the thing
The idea that I could transfer fully the information in a movie
To someone that would have required a whole lot of physicality not too long ago and a bunch more time
Nowadays you download it you have it you can watch it
You know quickening of the spirit kind of thing where you can get a tremendous amount
Basically communication or information being sent over and less time. Yes, right. So why is it that people I?
Have said throughout history was certain literary works when you read it, it's very dense
You have to read it more than once. Mm-hmm to understand it, right?
That's because it's very dense. There's a lot of information jammed into one right little package
So one way to get ahead of all of this stuff the cultural stuff. Who's your spiritual family?
The communication and all that is to get a lock on how you can interact with all this
Information because the spirit is all about information
It's it's not
How would you say it to get away from the religiosity that's been put on us
What's interesting the biggest sabotage on people that are quote-unquote in the convention talk about the collective now that?
They get this feeling of being spiritual or one with the source or God or whatever religion they're in
What happens to their information base it goes to zero they get really dumb clear your head don't think of it
Just feel it right and that is the complete opposite
with any higher cause dealing with let's say a divine being or
even dealing with someone that is in your spiritual family very rarely would it just be about feeling and
Even if you're looking at guys that get together for Sunday football with drinking beer or whatever
They're still interacting in the information how what's the score? How long does this player been there?
How much is he making what team was he before you see there's never this dumb lull
nothingness
It's always about managing high streams high levels of information within the context and within the subject so
There I could see why throughout the ages
The spirit in other words spiritual work quote-unquote
I know it sounds funny to say that but doing spiritual work has got nothing to do with what's been put out there
Whether it's in the alternative or in the convention it is all about information
And how you process it within your mind your spirit, and how mature are you and what could you handle right?
No right I know it's it's kind of like all these thoughts thrown together
I think we should organize it in the next few minutes here. Yeah, no I
That's what I was thinking here is that you know what if I if I imagine it this way
The speed at which you can turn your head allows you to see things at different angles, right?
There are things going on behind you that you're not looking at just if you're only using your eyes
Etc so
if
at the point where you're observing if
If you're able to take in more and process more and communicate more at a higher rate of speed
Indeed it creates a more dense experience it creates a more
Textured experience right it doesn't have to be though high-speed
But that but the if you're trained to do that if you can get yourself to take in more
Information and process and communicate more information more densely it would be better
Yes, that's how you get to a more mature point, but you have to adjust it of course right if you're going to do
Public speaking you're not going to you're not going to speak at 120 words per minute
You might get it down to 75 which is more listenable right well, but again. It's about the communication of it
But what I was trying to get at is that it's about the density of the subject
It's about the the the nuance and all the things that are contained within
Speed is is relevant though because you know at a very slow rate if you have very little to relate to
Or you have very little to communicate
Then it's not such a big deal that you take it very slowly
Sure, but but the thing to bring to bring it home Chuck is the spirit is where all this comes from
Right if you look at the ancient text you get knowledge from us at the spirit right from the divine you get a download even
With a computer it comes from an intangible sense there are no electrons right little
There's no mass moving along the wires or the Wi-Fi right you see so once
Okay, once we understand that we being conscious and the spirit the mind
Information that animates us is completely different from the way. We use the term soul and all this other stuff and we distinguish it
You've just gone to the next level. You've just been able to to segregate
I mean, it's it's the same thing like when the when an automobile is not working right the
Person opens the hood and they see all this stuff
They call a mechanic because they don't mechanic if the engine is running as he's approaching the cars not to look at
Oh, that's the that's the power steering pump. I can hear it right
They they have the information and they can communicate and they fix it right where the average person say oh the cars not running, right?
I don't know well the mechanic on a spiritual level is much higher much more mature and developed when it comes to cars, right?
Then your average person
right so
I was having a conversation recently with someone said you know in other worlds
Children, let's say they have a similar lifespan actually there are a few hundred years on other worlds
They by the time they're eight years old
They have already have what the equivalent of three or four master's degrees you would get here on earth at that age
that's the level of their education system and
You'd say oh, they're they're much more evolved than us. No. They're not there exactly. They're just us living in a different world
In other words were completely interchangeable in other words if you were raised there
You would also have the equivalent of four graduate degrees at eight years old, and if they were raised here
You would have a graduate degree and still be on a third grade level
You see
Completely interchangeable, so you know how we were saying earlier. It doesn't matter if it's fact or if it's fiction cosmically
Did you get did you get that information?
Right right in the cosmic sense
The information being fact or fiction is
Is not important is did you have do you have that concept?
Right you know how we have the sci-fi concept since the 1950s of flying saucers with aliens who become popular
There are far more people on the world right now than had that concept. Let's say 200 years ago
now
It doesn't matter if it's fiction. You know the concept
You see right
Well and and I look at art like that because a painting of something doesn't have to be exactly accurate to communicate the idea
it was
communicated and
Before the action takes place there is that inspiration or that desire to communicate said thing in the painting
Right so sure unless you're looking at the modern
Art world, then it's that's a difference to want to get conspiratorial you can on that, but you know
Yeah, yeah, but you know I'm not I'm not trying to go for the modern. You know oddities. I'm saying that in
Historically what has always been pretty much?
You know is is that you communicate an idea an image imagery a bunch of things not?
Just the you know when when when you paint a woman. It's not just about the woman
It's about where she's positioned what's around or everything else. It's meant to communicate a much more complex idea
But yeah, is it dark is it light is it religious is it punk is it what yeah, right exactly is there styles in this?
Thank you brought up the idea of style style the same thing goes with style
When you meet someone their personality is what you're dealing with is just their spirit
The the personality that's the other thing I didn't I didn't bring it up
But you're who you are personal personality is your spirit
Just like there's a Star Trek where they land on a planet and they're millions of years old
They don't need bodies anymore. It's just these globes and the globes talk right right and they want to get bodies
So they go into bodies just to feel what it was like again. That's the same spirit. That was in the body
It just needs to be animated somehow
So this the idea of spirit hit
This is a very good way to filter what's going on around and if you around you in in the world you are and when?
You hear people use the word spiritual or this is spiritual whatever examine it and see what it is in 99% of the time
it's going to be if not all the time fluff and stupidity and
vacuous and void of anything usable and
Mature and all that right so well back to the motivational speaker
You know where again they they are presenting something for you to feel something, but it's really about their benefit not yours
We'll get into that the emo what if you ask anyone, why do we have emotions? They don't know I?
I'm not saying that I know but I can tell you how we can use it and how like for example
Why do you have a pinky finger we write or any appendage in your body the emotional is a platform
I mean how many times have you heard?
He's a pretty cool calm collected guy, but he got emotional and you just blew every you got a gun and shot everyone
Right whoa wait a second you said he was common collective
So you think that his emotions drove him to do that wow those emotions are very powerful. How come we're not
Focusing on that well they used to say you lost they used to say you lost your mind if you did that right
Lost your spirit. Yes, because your particular mind or your spirit had a certain track or a certain type
And you lost it and another one or influence so influenced that it's no longer the same thing
So this I can't let me just say on the end the mind the way that I think and evaluate things is
First on a spiritual level what mind?
You know is is being communicated and what is being imparted like what mine is imparting like if you turn on the television show they call
the news
The you will see that they're imparting up before they even start speaking you see there's a certain
Thing that's set up, and when they start speaking
It's not how they look anymore
It's what they're saying right and you could see all the attachments well a sensitive person will notice something is not right here
But every other the way it's set up every other part of me says it is but something is not right you see
So and this is that's why the news and the media get over on people because they've been separated
They don't they have no control and no
Tangibility or definition to what is the spirit and the mind what is communication? What is thought knowledge?
it all based on the spirit and
That'll start to make sense if you start looking into ancient writs, and they're quote-unquote spiritual documents
A modern person looking at them is going to think it's woo. I should be feeling good. No. No has nothing to do with that
It's really knowledge. You know in ancient times
Written material was so rare I
Have mentioned this libraries and things like that that it was very expensive to interact with written material from the past
so
Okay, I think we're we don't want to maybe run down too much time
But what do you think we've we hit near an hour or so yeah well on this part
I I'm I am just simply following an internal clock on my part here, but let's take a little go
And yeah, I was feeling as though. It's about time to wrap this one up with with just one last little thing
I think we're going to have to get into time
again and
Go a little further with it. I mean you mentioned it here about starting your day
You know at at what they call noon
solar noon solar noon
But that is the reason I said solar noon is get away from the wind-up toy right
Because it's right okay, but that that is that is the appropriate time to start the day and and look there are reasons
why the day was said to start at different times and for different reasons and
we did discuss that in the past, but I think we could take it a bit further and
It will be interesting to to go over it
But really quickly before you go though you brought up something here toward the end which
Which I always find interesting almost always there's something at the end of these discussions that you and I have it seems to be a pattern
with us
Yes, that could sort of lead into another direction right away
and
In this case I would say
that the breakdown of the
of the
Spiritual relationship the parameters that were set you know when you're talking about the news that again is something that became part of
Convention right that this was an authority to present
Information this is how you became informed
You're right, but
Here we go. We know that there's some artificial about the communication. We know that there's something
Dishonest about it
Well the news Chuck is just like the lady that says I'm not technical or the guy that says I'm not
Mathematical at one point they got something important that was usable
Mm-hmm, and they said since I did get a piece of information that was usable here
Thus it must be all the time and even though I know intuitively it's not I still have to follow through on that, right?
Well, it's what I mean, yeah, no, it's much like the library
Or the libraries that used to exist in certain places if you were to go to one now
Which I don't know if anybody does anymore waste of time 20 years ago was a waste of time, but yeah
Well, it's become much more of a waste of time
Because of what do they have in there now a lot of computer stations?
So, you know, that's that look if it's if
Do you remember on the old sonic events?
Everything that could have been known was known by the 1890s and then everything went downhill from there and they showed it to you
after
1913 and by the 1920s in the 1940s
They proved it to you that all the knowledge was taken away all critical knowledge
continuation of
Sciences continuation of history, you know, all of that was taken away
So, I don't know unless you're what if you were born you'd be 83 if you were born in 40
So you'd have to be a hundred and forty hundred and fifty years old to have caught it on and you know
It to actually be out in the public venue and get something worthwhile
So if you're younger than a hundred and fifty, you've probably never been exposed to worthwhile information on the fly
Well, but that's it is that these things have changed over time and why that's happened
I think that that'll take us through a little bit
Yeah, and it just to give a quick thing the same thing. I've been talking
They know they don't have a lot of time left. The big one's coming, right, right and
They want to set it up. So when they reemerge they think
They'll have control. So that's basically it and look if I figured out
You know when this quote-unquote society will end and I'm just some Greek guy
Whatever Greek American running around here, right?
We want you on whatever trying to see what the hell is going on these guys who have the quote-unquote elite
They know
You know what's coming?
So it's all about control
So again, I think we had a we're kind of verbose on the on the soul and the spirit
But well, this is going to be revisited and I've always wanted to bring up that relationships are basically
Another word, you know are set by boundaries and the word really actually the concept of relationship is what boundaries are there and understanding that
You