So, Sonic Event 231, here we go, Greek,
I got a lot, a lot of questions
and comments for you, but first, how are
you?
I'm good, man.
You're right, man, that did come in pretty
loud on my side, maybe you need a
new mixing board or Jitsi or something, but
as long as people can make out what
we're saying, that's what counts, it's the message,
right?
Yeah, true, I may have an irregular kind
of like short in my stuff, which means
go back and replace the wires and, you
know, sometimes they start to get hot and
cold right before they die, wires, you know,
I don't know.
Well, get new stuff, all new stuff, you
know, get balanced cables or whatever, get a
board with balanced inputs, I don't like the
way it sounds for hi-fi, but it
sounds good for what we're doing, so.
Well, anyway, we'll get the message out regardless
of the sound, right?
All right, so first thing is knowing how
corrupt this world is and also knowing a
cleanup crew is what's being cleaned up, is
the question, the space heaters or the corrupt
ones or an even level of the hierarchy.
That's an easy one, I've answered that before.
Yeah, the world is not salvageable, is the
last comment there.
No, it's not, okay, allegiance, allegiance is the
most important thing, when you go to the
military, they make sure you have allegiance and
once you pledge allegiance or swear allegiance, if
you do something that's contrary to the command,
you can be executed on the spot.
Same thing works, these are all cosmic rules,
so let's say you're a dumbass, which is
a typical human and you believe, let's say,
this country is bad because they launched a
terror attack on your country, which your own
government really did or people within your government
did and you believe what they're telling you,
you're going to suffer the consequences as if
the story is true.
All right, that might be a little bit
of a twisted way to answer it, but
let's say you have allegiance to a corrupt
religion, institution, group, and you don't know anything,
you think you're doing the right thing, you're
still going to suffer the consequences, yes, be
mindful.
In other words, ignorance of the law is
no excuse, so you're going to have to
dig down and find out fundamental stuff.
Like, you know, for example, this is very
easily researched and known, no matter how it's
been marketed, but Catholicism, the Vatican is one
of the most evil institutions the world has
ever seen.
You can't show me another institution that has
lasted.
Formally, 1000 AD is when they built the
Vatican, started, right?
And they were around for about several, about
400 years, 500 years before that.
So you're looking at institutions about 1700, 1800
years old, and it's by hands down the
most corrupt and evil institution ever on this
planet.
Warning to you, billion Catholics or three quarter,
you think you're doing the right thing, you're
going down, bitch.
That's the, that's the cosmic way to say
it.
I would leave that place.
I mean, that's, that's not an opinion, by
the way, and I don't know if I
could speak for the cosmic forces, but what
I'm saying can be objectified, right?
So, yeah, so right away, most of the
people are going to go down just from
that one group, and then you got all
the other groups.
Believe it or not, the Satanists are probably
going to be, get it the easiest.
Why?
Because they're anti what the, they're, by the
way, Satanism is secular, by the way.
Yeah.
Right?
It's a secular religion.
It's not, it's, you know, they might throw
smittens, smittings of philosophy in there, but it's
secular.
But what they're doing is essentially anti-Christian,
anti-Catholic, anti-secular.
They're secular, that's anti-secular.
So, in a way, it's like the enemy
of my enemy is my friend.
So, they're going to have a much better,
easier time because they're more anti, but they're
also going to have a really hard time
because they bought into the secularness of it.
Like, I used to give an example.
You'll have, let's say, you're, you pass through
the pearly gates, no such thing.
Metaphorically, you go to heaven and you see
a little pastor that was handing out cans
to all the hungry people, but, you know,
pushed you into whatever religion they do in
the Midwest.
You'll see Hitler, and Hitler will be, oh,
I'm glad I wasn't one of them.
Right?
He's going to get it a lot worse
because Hitler wasn't promoting any kind of a
cosmic deity of any sort, was he?
Not at all.
Well, now- It was true, you're right.
Here's the thing about him directly, maybe not,
but some of his guys had these different
- Oh, they were super occult, yeah.
Super occult stuff going on.
So, and there's even like a Catholic breakaway
sect that was like really supportive and inspirational,
apparently.
So, I don't know.
It's hard to sort that out, to be
honest with you, to me.
Maybe I'm wrong.
It just seems like it's hard to separate
things.
So, that means eventually it's like, yeah, burn
it all, but we don't have to focus
as Yeah, there's going to be a selection.
If you go to, if you harken to
what Jason Brashear says, the phoenix is selective.
People that are afraid of it and are
misinformed are going to get it.
Those that know what it is and not
afraid of it are going to be just
fine.
I've talked about this all the time through
the years.
It's very selective, that type of destruction.
You hear about this often where plane crash,
200 people on board, 193 die, and seven
just walk away with not a scratch.
Right?
You've heard this before, right?
Oh, yeah.
So, yeah, and it's a bad metaphor.
It's actually, you'll see that kind of proportion
out there, but with, it's really hard.
All you could do is explain it in
metaphors, because we cannot objectify that outcome, right?
Because the knowledge of such an outcome is
given to us in allegory anyway.
Well, and I'll put it to you this
way.
There's also the selection that goes on, because
like you remember the Hindenburg.
We all know what that is, right?
The big airship that went down.
The perception is everybody died.
That is way far from the truth.
If you read the accounts, usually the people
that, the accounts that people wrote, they said
that the captain said stay inside, and everyone
who followed the captain's order survived.
Stay inside the cabin, because it was, come
on, man, it's German engineering.
They had taken that into account.
The cabin was designed to protect you from
flare up, shall we say?
Right.
And everyone who followed the captain's order survived
unscathed.
Whoever decided to take the matters in their
own hands, well, you know, those are the
ones you hear about.
You never hear about the ones that, the
good boys and girls.
You always hear about the bad boys and
girls, so.
That's true.
Hey, you know what, you know, a comment
connects to this.
I knew it.
The Greek has been quoting Snatch as long
as I've been listening to him.
Taking a windy walk through a Canaanite village,
how ze Germans are coming.
There have been a few more that I
can't recall now.
Glad to finally hear it from him.
Save your breath, save your breath to cool
your porridge.
See, I don't know this movie, but I'm
guessing.
That's the Jippo.
That's what, that's Brad Pitt's one of the
best lines when they meet him out in
the field to do another fight for a
caravan.
Pederinko Blue.
The size of our covers.
And he says, I'm not going to buy
a tarts mobile home.
What'd you say?
Save your breath to cool your porridge.
Yeah.
So anyway, I really liked that film because
of the metaphor.
Again, it's a metaphor.
The whole movie is a metaphor.
And it's interesting, too, because I'm just glad
to hear that you appreciate some films outside
of just, you know, your YouTube videos for
background.
Because I feel stupid sometimes making film references.
I'm glad you do it.
Also, Guy Ritchie.
This is another comment, by the way.
Also, Guy Ritchie films are well done.
Also recommended Revolver.
Sherlock Holmes.
King Arthur.
That being said, I feel like those.
That's the Hollywood influence.
The Sherlock Holmes one.
Another one is Lawrence of Arabia.
The classic one.
Good scene is when they take Aqaba.
And he took it on his own.
Because he was high ranking, he could make
a military decision.
And he has one of his boys.
And I think it was Pederasty.
I doubt it, though.
It didn't hint enough of that.
But there's a young man that he took
a liking to.
I think it was Pederasty, but they didn't
show it in the film.
And he brought him into an officer's club.
British officer's club in Arabia.
And you're not supposed to bring any denizens
in.
And he brought him in anyway.
And they refused to serve him, refused to
let him in.
And he says, you're going to give him
a lemonade.
And you're going to give it with ice.
And he's ordering.
It's kind of like the thing.
What's the lady who did not go to
the back of the bus kind of thing?
Rosa Parks?
What was her name?
It was Jonah Park.
It's a Rosa Parks thing.
And this is before Rosa Parks.
But that was being done.
The Rosa Parks thing's been going on since
the 30s, by the way.
I don't know why they just made her
popular.
If you tell anyone who's lived in the
South and was cosmopolitan about Rosa Parks, they're
going to laugh at you.
It was like 1,000 Rosa Parks.
God damn it.
Why'd they bring that bitch up again?
So she was the only one that made
it to the media, right, that took it
all the way, right?
Yeah, right.
Tons of musicians fighting with places.
Why can't I eat in a place that
I'm going to perform in, you know, for
decades?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
And they took it just as far, but
it just was not, yeah, it's not talked
about.
Right.
Exactly.
All right.
Guy Ritchie, hats off to him.
I feel he's definitely, this guy continues, though,
I feel he's definitely in the club, low
level, of course.
I don't know about that judgment, but, you
know, what do you think?
Well, he married Madonna, didn't he?
Or was her, whatever, whatever.
Madonna's as bad as you can get.
She's been, you know, I think it was
without her own volition.
She got led into it.
Like she's full on the host now.
She's not even Madonna.
She's a host.
Anyway, that's another, that's for the Donald Marshall
people, to know what I'm talking about.
You know, the covering the eye.
Yeah, well, she went full Kabbalah.
She went full Kabbalah, too.
That's the other, that was step, what, two?
No, I'm talking more, what I'm saying is
maybe really off on the fringe.
Like, she's a host.
In other words, the Madonna is dead.
The spirit that's in her is something else.
True enough.
Yeah.
That's what the left, you know, covering the
eye, the dark eye, the black and blue
eye.
You see that?
The, you know.
Okay.
So that's another, that's another, we should do,
we should do, we'd have to have Donald
Marshall on for that one, but there's plenty
of stuff about Donald Marshall.
You could talk about it, but right.
What else?
That would be interesting.
Yeah.
I'd love to do a guest.
Greek is right about the immune system.
If you had one, then you'd be free
of taxes and not bound to civic duties.
So if you know law and use it
to avoid taxes, then by definition in parentheses,
you have created an immune system.
In conclusion, all humans in the so-called
modern world with birth certificates are effectively born
with AIDS.
You could say that metaphorically, but you can't
pay taxes because like I said, FDR did
what no dictator parliamentarian or monarchy ever did
in history, which is tell people to surrender
their precious metals.
No one, the worst dictator ever in history
never even did anything near that.
And they pulled it off here.
So everything now is bills and bills of,
if you look up the definition of a
bill, a bill is a bill of exchange.
And if you want to know how to
handle bill of exchange, you read the bill
of exchange act.
So there's no such thing as paying a
tax.
That's they simplify it because you ever watch
like a regular TV show and then go
to watch like the ones made for young
children, like pre-nursery school, like just like
between Teletubbies between Teletubbies and Sesame street, something
between there.
Right.
That's the language that they use to the
public about taxes.
There's no such thing about taxes.
Forget it.
What happens is a tax liability arises and
they demand a payment from you, which is
nothing more than a promise to pay.
But because you don't know any better, you
think you have to go out there and
earn by working or investing somehow to give
it to them.
It's on your own fault on your own
head.
If you're going to do that, you can
ask the IRS is very good about receiving
bills of exchange.
If you follow the instructions that they give
you and I've memorized them and I've got
so much on my mind, I have a
notebook here where whenever I'm on a financial
conversation, I spew out what they should do.
And I could hear the pages flipping, but
I could give you, if you go to
the IRM I used to know it's 10
.48, but they go to the IRM manual.
That's their manual.
And it wasn't supposed to be made public,
but when it went public, it went public
so big now they can't retract it and
they don't want to redo it because you
can't redo it.
It's their manual.
If you redo it, you just what you've
gutted their operations, right?
So it's the IRM, which is the IRS
manual 3.8.45.5.10.1 remittance
instructions for the taxpayer wants to pay an
outstanding, whatever, with a bill of exchange or
registered bill of exchange, they can do so.
They have to order it or give you
permission to the campus to do so.
And when they send it with the instructions
to do so, whoever receives it in the
campus has to send it to the treasury
via air mail or the next day air,
very important.
And they give you the office in the
treasury.
So in the instructions, you tell them and
actually the office it's, it's in the IRM
manual there.
And when you look up that office to
make it even stick, even better.
Once you put in all the information of
the treasury office gives you the address and
the, and the suite number, put it in
the internet and you'll see the current director
of that office.
So don't only give the, in the instructions,
the office also find it.
His name is Steve, something slots, nickel, whatever,
or Schwarzenegger, wherever you find the name and
put the name on there to the director
of the office.
And they just, it just goes away.
It doesn't matter how much it is.
It could be a billion dollars, a million
dollars, a hundred thousand 90.
I saw one recently for 98,600, something
just goes away.
300,000.
I've seen goes away, you know?
So yeah, there's no, it's all promises to
me, but if you believe you have to
go work to pay a bill, that's on
your own, dude, that's your own head.
No, one's making you do that, but what's
happening.
Let me give a quick explanation on the
money system.
Someone put up a Twitter video, but blue
aliens laughing on how everything here is given
for us to use, but we create money
that devalues itself and they're laughing, right?
Like humans are rug.
That's fine.
That's true though.
We are on a planet that's self-sustaining,
right?
And someone had the idea while we were
extracting whatever we needed from the earth to
use.
Right?
But then the idea came up via authority.
It started with spiritual authority and people that
impressed other people with magic tricks or whatever,
or just bigger than others and compound you
to the ground.
If you didn't do what they said, they
came up with the idea of starting to
claim all these resources, whether it was agriculture,
mineral water, they started claiming it and forcing
others to do an exchange.
Like when, when the petroleum companies pull the
oil out of the ground, the earth doesn't
send them a bill.
When the farmer harvests is all the, the
crops, the earth doesn't send them a bill.
You know, there's a sky, right?
The fishermen doesn't get a bill from the
ocean, but these people came up with the
idea that if we can get the population
to accept our authority and they have to
give us more in exchange for what we
got for free, right?
Now, remember the labor that was used to
extract those things is already taken care of
by the way, right?
And that's another discussion.
So what happened was this carries on with
exchange of money.
Money is nothing but portable land.
Cause you're supposed to live off the land
with everything.
You know, everyone's supposed to share, right?
Not run with the scissors, whatever.
But when you travel from the land that
you're doing that, you need to bring portable
land with you, which would be the most
precious thing your land has to offer, which
is precious metals.
That's where we use precious metals.
So to make a long story short here,
all that has gone away.
And it's just a matter about, about, uh,
everything's paid for.
All you could do is order pay to
the order of, or promise to pay.
Right?
So you take the fishermen, takes the fish
out of the water and he promises to
give the water something back for it.
Right?
So everything is based on cooperation and demands
and acceptances.
Oh, I just mentioned the whole financial system,
but what's been going on is it's been
turned into a form of slavery.
Tech through technology, through, uh, the way cities
are formed through culture, that those that know
how this works do not share it with
those that they want to take advantage of.
Right?
so they use ledger domain and Presto digitization.
In other words, when a magician comes to
town, a real good one, and he's going
to saw a woman in half and they
advertise that 500 people come and buy tickets
to watch that.
Everybody knows that he's not going to saw
a woman in half and put her back
together, but they all go to see it
and they don't, and they don't really inquire
enough about how they could, no matter how
much it's a secret, right?
That's exactly how the money system works.
Oh, you know, like if you go to
court over the, let's say, you know, you
sign a bunch of notes, pay for the
car three times with your signature.
You go to court over and just, if
you want a free car, what was paid
for from where, where did the funds come
from?
So they kind of try to play with
this infantile logic on a system that no
longer exists.
Like what, what's done with the application and
stuff.
If you say you want to use the
application as collateral or go apply for something,
they say, do you have proof of funds?
Yeah.
Proof of funds, the full faith and credit
of the U S government asking me for
proof of funds is saying, first of all,
that I have nothing to do with the
U S government.
I have paperwork to show that I do.
Number one, number two, you're trying to say
the, the full faith and credit of the
U S government's not good, right?
The U S government is 31 trillion in
debt and that you're sending everybody checks for
a thousand dollars and cashing them just fine.
Yeah.
Where you want to see proof of funds
in the U S treasury.
I'll show you proof of funds in the
U S treasury, 31 trillion in debt.
I'm only a hundred thousand in debt, bitch,
right?
How come no one's using the most basic
what's going on?
I mean, because they've got everyone mind controlled
and every, no one knows what they're saying.
I've seen people that are close to me.
People are not close to me.
I listened to what they're saying and pretty
much 90%, if not a hundred percent with
some people is what comes out of their
mouths is oxymoronic.
They're actually contradicting like the last part of
their sentence contradicted the first part of their
sentence, you know?
So it's like plus one and minus one.
What happens when you put plus one and
minus one together?
And that's what you're getting out of everything.
But anyway, all right.
We did a lot on this last time
I got some comments.
I was a very good Sonic.
Okay.
That's fine.
I'm glad you enjoyed it, but it's very
frustrating to mull these things over, over and
over and see that, like how, how just
piss poor we are in our minds.
This is all psychoenergetic problem.
It's going to get worse, by the way,
it's going to get worse.
It's going to be okay.
This is what I would expect to people
to expect.
Do you remember right after nine 11 for
about a year, there was like this Muslim
phobia.
Anybody with a turban, even if they were
Sikhs, suddenly we're terrorists, right?
Yes.
Right.
People in gas stations getting beat up.
They're Sikh, right?
I was working in those gas stations.
I know full well.
Yes.
Yeah.
There's slots.
We have a lot of Sikhs here and
people think they're must use dumb fuck.
They're not, but you know, but anyway, they
do have certain rights and rituals.
They follow, you know, like cutting hairs, mutilation
and this and that.
They have certain things.
Their, their, their, their culture is based on
being very advanced.
Warrior ship.
They're very, very, very, very, you would never
want to go into battle with them if
they were prepared.
Right?
No.
So they're fierce warriors.
Anyway, all this stuff.
So you're going to have that nine 11
kind of fear, whatever coming up around finances
and international affairs that are going to affect
finances.
Yeah.
It's going to be interesting to watch.
So, okay.
What else you got?
So here's one of those weird questions.
If the Greek was stuck on a desert
Island and could only bring three food items,
what would he bring deserted Island?
Cause desert Island is just sand and rocks
and cactus deserted Island.
I mean, isolated depends on the latitude, right?
So let's say usually that, that terminology, there's
islands off of Greenland and Iceland, and then
there's islands off of the warm, warm.
So if it's a cold place, you would
definitely want to bring, uh, things that you
could harvest animal products with weapons, uh, ability
to keep warm food items would be, um,
root root vegetables that you can grow in
the snow, meaning you, you, you dig down,
right?
And the frost, uh, hot climate would be
salt, which would be easy to do anyway.
If you're near the water, um, no, I
wouldn't be concerned because food, here's the problem.
Uh, food items that are perishable are perishable.
So it wouldn't matter.
They wouldn't last very long.
And food items that are not perishable are
usually bulk items.
So what am I going to do?
Put like a cup full of Brown rice
in a pouch.
How long is that going to be good
for?
Actually, you can live off of it for
a month.
If you know, that's all you have.
Right.
I don't know.
If you got more specific and you said
like a hundred pounds of said food items
or something, you know, I guess they're looking
to see if you'd bring rice or whatever,
you know?
Yeah, probably a whole grain.
Millet would probably be better than rice.
Millet.
It's much smaller.
And, you know, it's, it's more packed.
yeah, millet.
I would do millet.
Oh, before I did Brown rice for sure.
Yeah.
But very, very consistent.
By the way, millet and barley was the
main.
Millet and barley was the main grain for
Asia before Westerners went there and convinced them.
Rice was a luxury item.
Always.
As a matter of fact, if you watch
some of the old Kurosawa films that are
not that, you know, that much back historically
with the samurai, the samurai were like, Oh,
you have white rice.
They offered like this one samurai payment by
a meal of white rice.
He's like, Oh wow.
You got white rice.
Wow.
You know, it's like, yeah.
Cause they eat millet and barley Asia.
It's like the 1960s, the Kurosawa films, right?
Yeah.
And it was right.
So Asia was based on millet and barley
oats, mostly barley and millet.
Did I say barley and millet or millet
and barley?
Yeah, you did.
Not rice.
Yeah.
Anyway, there was a continuation on the German
medicine thing.
Cause remember you said, you know, pay attention.
I think they did and continued to pay
attention.
From a, from a German new medicine article.
It is similar to what Greek says about
cancer.
Dr. Hammer's discoveries turned this paradigm completely on
its head by demonstrating that quote diseases such
as cancer are not as assumed malfunctions of
an organism, right?
Instead, significant biological special programs of nature designed
to support an individual during unexpected distress.
So they're linking you together with this, with
this concept.
So I don't know.
Good.
Yeah.
Let's, let's work that.
It's an, it's not a malfunction.
It's an overall function.
So there's a, a bad through way on
a road accidents happen or accidents do happen
and have happened.
So you have this overreactive force of vehicles
come by and they got sirens and lights
on that.
Other vehicles normally don't.
Right.
And the people look different and they're usually
more brutal.
They get out and they set up barricades
to redirect the traffic.
And you, you know, even approaching an area
like that, you're like, what's all this traffic.
There must've been what, Oh, it must've been
an accident up there.
I see the lights, right?
You can notice it from a distance.
So it's an over function.
It's an over function.
It's an emergency.
The, the, the, okay, let me just start
it from what I've been saying for 20
plus or 30 or 40 plus years is
cancer is what happens is you have energy.
Okay.
Look, you have energy moving through the body
up on one side, down on the other.
Right.
And then whatever.
So when you start sending too much, that
goes to one part of the body, the
body's like, listen, you're sending too much to
this side and it's, it's, I can't function.
And you, and it communicates that by like
various ways of not feeling well, it depends
on the individual.
So going back to the accident that you
talked about, here's what would happen with an
accident, right?
The first thing is they would block off
the area so that you wouldn't continuously have
traffic.
So, so stop.
This is important.
So first you start getting signals of cramps,
not feeling well, headaches, mucus on one side.
You ever hear people getting a mucus in
one side of the year or ringing on
one side of the air, but not the
other ear.
Yes.
Right.
On one side, you'll have pain one nostril.
Yeah.
You'll have cramps.
You might be accidental on one side.
You might always be bumping or cutting or
hurting on that one side.
And this happens for years and years.
And then finally a tumor or a very
bad skin manifestation or a very dark spot
forms.
That's the end.
That means like you were ignoring all the
other stuff.
It was very subtle.
Now we have to send, go ahead, Chuck,
you're saying with an accident, you show up,
go ahead.
Now you send all the, you know, the,
the people to block things off, to isolate
it, redirect traffic, et cetera.
And you isolate that area so that it's
now controlled momentarily.
Yeah.
I don't have the traffic.
Go ahead.
Yeah.
All the cops and wherever they show up,
don't they look like a tumor anyway?
Right.
I mean, you're right.
They're not there.
Normally, if you look at a helicopter view
of that, instead of seeing a nice linear
formation with movement, you see this big blockage.
Yeah.
And they stick out from the sky down,
you know, right.
They stick out.
Obviously there's rest different.
They got bright, bright lights spinning all over
the place.
Yeah.
It's exactly what the body did for you.
If you didn't, okay.
There are people that don't have the ability
to form cancer.
They die in their bed overnight.
Personally.
No one.
Jonathan butts.
You could look them up.
CEO of natural action technologies died in his
sleep at 49 of sudden death, not capable
of forming cancer.
He said he had liver failure to get
into personal stuff.
I'm not under HIPAA laws.
Am I anyway?
You know, the personal stuff, but at one
point he said he had a liver.
He had a liver failure when nearly killed
him.
And then like a week later, he was
totally fine.
It's like, wow.
Total shutdown of the most versatile organ in
the body.
And then he got okay again.
And he didn't look okay for a while,
but, and then he dies in his sleep.
He didn't have the ability to produce tumors.
Hmm.
Right.
Obviously, or whatever.
Cause I asked people, did he have cancer?
No, they didn't just sudden death.
And I was like, Oh shit.
And you hear about this often people dying
in their thirties, forties, sudden death.
they usually mark it as heart failure.
Sudden death is a more common one with
the, with the injections, the COVID vaccines have
been doing.
Oh yeah.
And there's actually a bunch of videos that
haven't been taken down about athletes dying on
the field.
Soccer player, boom, falls over, die, you know,
people, even a couple of newscasters fell over
and died while they're delivering the news.
Right.
So yeah, that's, that's like, uh, it's interesting
if those, uh, if they know something here,
what we already got a few, we've mentioned
on the Sonic, what they're doing in terms
of the injections, what they're injecting into your
body.
They're not nanobots.
We went into that.
It's memory metal that expands at a certain
frequency.
It's a tiny little coil of memory, metal
nano size, and it reacts to a certain
frequency.
And when that frequency hits the body, it's
no longer a very tightly wound coil.
It expands into a linear piece.
So it acts as a, as a spear
or a dagger going through the cell, right?
Because the cell can accommodate a very, a
very tightly rolled up ball of metal, but
it cannot accommodate something.
That's a tightly rolled up ball.
And then suddenly expands into a 10 times.
It's with like a spear puncturing the cell.
Right.
So we know that they have that.
And the other thing would be maybe the
MRA is actually a cancer inhibitor because they
are talking about, uh, these things, injections to
prevent cancer and people are welcoming.
They don't know that that kind of thing
will actually let you allow you to die
in your sleep overnight or suddenly anyway, just
entertaining the thought for you guys to think
about.
That's how to make sense of one of
the private questions I got, which was, you
know, does the Greek have any views on
this weird sort of a two fisted approach
from the Maha movement, which is a RFK
juniors thing.
Like he's doing some good things that like
a lot of people wanted to see done.
And at the same time, the, uh, the
government itself, literally doing the other stuff like
you just talked about with the MRA thing
is now going to expand and people think,
Oh, that's good.
They're going to do research on it, but
no, what that's going to do is stop,
which is a bad idea.
I believe.
Yeah.
I believe with a straight face, they could
tell you to prevent cancer and people want
to take it.
But preventing cancer is what allows you to
die suddenly.
Right.
I believe that's a very good summation.
It's like super hyper rational what I brought
up and, uh, it's most people have to
hear that phrase several times for it to
sink in because you've been bombarded for decades
about, uh, cancer is something that needs to
be cured.
That's like, we need to cure roadblocks.
You know, when there's an accident, we need
to prevent roadblocks from happening.
That's it.
I don't never that'll lead to even worse
situations.
So yeah.
Anyway.
Yeah.
Right.
Sorry.
If you're, if you're listening to me on
this planet, I'm sorry.
Sorry.
They sent you here.
Yeah.
Anyway.
Okay.
My apologies.
My apologies that you've joined us.
Although somebody said it's a pleasure to, uh,
be growing down with you quoting you from
the last Sonic.
Also, I wanted to let you know that
there is a bunch and I'm just going
to put these all together, but, uh, Mary
weather and a bunch of other listeners, uh,
wanted to say that they really appreciated a
lot of connected dots from the very last
Sonic, uh, that they felt as though that
was a very good, you know, uh, they,
they use words like truth bombs.
I'm putting things together here.
So much gratitude for the info and effort
that you put into this, uh, channel.
Appreciate it.
Thank you for answering these questions and putting
it together.
And one good Sonic solidly, uh, et cetera.
So I just want to let you know
that there was a very positive response for
that last one.
Anyway, moving forward.
That wasn't even that, by the way, that
was unplanned.
That was all, that was all brought on
because of someone who was analysis paralysis about
the law questions.
Right.
They had them.
Yeah.
They had one long and I, and I
thought it was worthy to focus on that
and it turned out to be it provoked
something.
That's that's what, that's what it's.
Yeah.
Otherwise I've got all that stuff in me
and more.
If you like that kind of stuff, go
ahead and poke me with a stick on
that subject.
And I'll come up with more, uh, that
I've learned over the years that seemed to
be senseless and mindless to talk about just
as we just finished saying cancer is actually
a life extended reaction.
And if you tell this to anyone, they're
going to think you're nuts.
Cause you, they've been taught that it's a
life terminating, uh, function.
So anyway, Right.
It's just like, you know, AIDS is a
thing too, which, you know, by the way,
that's why you had to say it was
a metaphor when somebody used it before.
Yeah.
Diabetes.
Diabetes and AIDS is the treatment.
They convince you it's, there's no such thing.
There's no such disease at all.
Not even the only way you can have
glucose measured in the body is in the
urine.
I there's, there's dozens of things you could
read.
They're still trying to figure out how to
diagnose it in the blood.
And there's a lot of medical idiots out
there that think that it's actually true.
Another, another fallacy other than AIDS and diabetes
is blood tests.
Blood tests are total fallacy because if you
know anyone that works in a blood testing
lab, they walk in and each technician calibrates
the equipment to their own blood.
Yeah.
They have no benchmark and they never will
because they don't understand it.
It's not about go read the Flexner report.
And if that doesn't make you want to
set your hair on fire and run down
the street.
And also I've been watching some of the
drug ads that, you know, pharmaceutical ads, they
very clearly tell you it's for treating symptoms.
Oh yeah.
Very clearly.
Now that's you, do you know that most
people are quote unquote alcoholic and severe alcoholic?
You know why?
Oh, because they're trying to treat their symptoms
and their life sucks.
And instead of fixing their life, they treat
the symptom, the sucky part with alcohol.
So if you think being an alcoholic, severe
alcoholic is fine, then go ahead and take
their farm.
They're telling you it's no different than pharmaceuticals.
That's a very strict analogy, very direct analogy.
Most alcoholics would tell you they drink because
their life sucks.
So why don't you change your life?
No, I'd rather drink alcohol.
That's why they call it self-medicating because
that's what you're doing.
You are self-medicating for the same purpose.
They're telling you they're going to give you
a magic pill to fix everything, except you're
doing it yourself.
No, they're not.
No, they're not going to fix everything.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, right?
So that's why it's all bullshit and these
medical people are actually an extension.
Okay.
You know how police are called paramilitary.
Yep.
Right.
So the, basically the the medical community is,
as the, is the paramilitary medical, the purpose
of the medical and medical.
Okay.
People that run the world would love to
shut down all.
give you no medical care at all, zero
whatsoever, and say screw you, right, but they
don't do that because then they know the
population would get together on its own and
emerge with a viable system that works.
So what they do is they distract you,
come to us, come to us, same with
university.
People would be far more intelligent and well
-read if all the schools and universities shut
down, and it was self-encouraged to be
autodidactic, right, so what they do is they
lure you in thinking, you know, with this
false thing, and the reason it comes from
the military is because the way you stop
an army or tactically slow down an army
is by injuring the troops, not killing them,
because it takes two good men, two uninjured
troops to take care of an injured troop.
Now if I were to form a military,
if you're injured, you take a suicide pill
or the guy next to you puts one
in your head, no injured people, just like
they say no prisoners, right, in the military
that I would create is if you're injured
and you can't move forward and proceed in
a tactical advance, you have to take your
own life or your life will be taken
in 30 seconds, and you have to sign
up for that, you know, it sounds kind
of cruel, but you know what?
You ever hear of the Spartans?
Anyway, so yeah, that's a real military.
The military we have is just a joke,
like I said, after 9-11, and the
society here is a joke, because if the
military couldn't do anything about it, we need
to immediately dissolve the U.S. military and
bring in whatever allies we have to protect
the country until we form a viable one.
9-11 was proof of that, so it's
idiot, idiocracy, you know, all the way around,
you know, so to me, the military, you
know, I say humans are morons and military
is just weaponized morons, right?
And yet there's a common template for hierarchy,
you know, where there are the uninformed troops
on the bottom and all the way up
to the people that command things, and they're
supposed to know, there is a hierarchy, there's
a business hierarchy.
Yeah, the command people are financer people, they're,
yeah, they're morons.
Who's that idiot that was head of the
army 15 years ago?
He had a lot of controversy, he had
an affair with one of his, what do
they call, attachs, the young girl again, and
he was like a weak-chinned guy.
Petraeus.
Petraeus, yeah, that moron.
He said, he wrote a paper and spoke
about it that he says that the U
.S. never lost a battle in Vietnam.
You can't show me a battle they won,
right?
Which one did they win?
I mean, this is the kind of horseshit.
Oh, am I beeping?
Yeah, I walked really far away.
Okay, all right, I can hear you.
I'll be back in range within a second
or two.
No problem.
I was making myself a coffee.
All right, what else you got?
Yeah, well, look, here's kind of, I combined
a few things, so here we go with
the last thing, and who knows what you'll
do with this.
Christianity is an interesting sect.
As a small child, I was the only
one who was not going to church on
Sunday with the other kids.
The local priest one day visited our primary
school and said in front of the whole
classroom that I'm the only bad boy there.
I was six years old, and he really
made me feel like crap, but I think
this listener is grateful for it now, but
he calls it an interesting sect.
Your thoughts on that one?
It is.
Well, what the hell is he doing interacting
with a six-year-old?
He should be interacting with the parents of
a six-year-old to then interact with
you as an intermediary, right?
So I would find that very, unless he
was the one, yeah, so anyway.
Well, he went to the school.
I think they're all scumbags.
Yeah, he went to the school, but, you
know, here we go.
I always think of fish, by the way,
whenever I hear the word school anymore, because
it's not really the proper human way to
educate people, but anyway, no, it's interesting.
We've spent a lot of time on the
school thing, but with the priest, I think
they're all scumbags because, well, no matter how
helpful they are, ignorance of the law is
no excuse, right?
And the first thing I always say, I'm
the only one speaking on this.
It was an article I found out written
about another Greek guy in the 1990s.
There is no crucifixion, no matter how much
they write it in your translation.
The Greek term stavros was actually a slang
term, stavromenos, which means to be crossed or
nailed down.
It's kind of like now, like a slang
term, like say, oh, what happened to, you
know, Tom?
Oh, he got screwed.
Does that literally mean someone went to the
hardware store and got a Phillips head or
a flathead screw and the wood screw or
metal screw and put it?
No.
So there's enough references in there from the
authority in the story.
I'm not saying it's true or not, but
let's stick, we don't have a license to
change what's being conveyed, right?
So if we're talking about Melville's Moby Dick,
we can't say that the whale was purple
with green polka dots because that's not the
case, right?
We can say that, but we have no
license to say that it's in the book.
What's in the book is that Christ is
brought to a chain of command, finally ending
up with the prefect governor Pontius Pilate.
In order to be a governor of a
territory, you have to know the customs and
laws of the people.
He washes his hands of the matter, which
is one of the ordinances in the Red
Heifer, which means to absolve himself of any
guilt because of a murder.
He does, it's like pre, what do you
call it when you do it before the
fact?
And he turns around, this is the book
of Mark, and it's what they call it,
a prima ficia case is what they call
that.
That's the first phase.
That's something to do ahead of time.
Go ahead.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, prima ficia means on his face, but
okay.
Preemptively, preemptive.
And he tells the Judean authorities, I didn't
say Jewish, Judean authorities to use their law
and they retort, well, he says, I know
you have a law.
It goes back and forth.
You could read it yourself, right?
So what's established is Judean law will be
used, which is death by stoning.
It's not Christ's crucifixion, but we're not that
stupid in the Deuteronomy 21, it states how
it's done.
It's on a tree.
And we know it's an almond tree because
there's all these references to an almond tree.
You probably missed that because you've over-signified
to look at the olive tree with the
olive branch and blah, blah, blah, and the
amount of olives, but you forgot to look
at the references regarding the almond tree.
And especially with Moses, why am I building
this seven branch lampstand?
Make sure it has almond blossoms on it
because that is blah, blah, blah, lights up
on fire.
So in book of Numbers, anything that is
on a tree is cursed and to be
burned.
So the thing was set on fire, but
his body, he wasn't burned.
The other two guys were burned.
Their femoral arteries were cut, blah, blah, blah.
The Roman soldiers there, which are actually Syrian,
the Romans didn't bring people from their land
to, they just hired people that were locals,
by the way, except for some Centurion, maybe
even not, because it said, they spoke Aramaic,
so he was probably Syrian descent also.
They didn't know what was going on, so
they had to explain to them, and he
says, holy shit, that's Herod's robe.
Well, that's going to get burned.
No, I want it.
Okay, cast lots for it.
The people passed from the third to the
ninth hour doing what?
How boring is it for six hours to
see someone nailed to a crew?
They were throwing stones.
They were participants.
That's why there's a lot of things about
the curse that was put on them.
It says, you know, what you're going to
do to the Jewish people, I mean, Judeans
there in Jerusalem is going to be also
put on their children.
They all participated.
It took six hours, thousands of people doing
this, throwing stones, right, and it's like a
decomposed granite and limestone.
It's a flat disk.
Imagine a playing card made of slate.
When you throw it and it hits you,
it'll cut a piece of flesh off.
It's not a river rock.
It's very sharp, so all the flesh was
torn off of his body, but no bones
were broken.
Didn't even look good, so all this is
in the text.
It's actually in the prophecies from hundreds of
years before it happened also, so anyone's talking
about a crucifixion doesn't know what they're talking
about because they haven't read the text.
They're going on what's called churchianity.
Now, I agree what the church is putting
forward is all BS, but if you go
in the biblical text, you'll find that, you
know, wow, but we have this thing, you
know, it's how different, we have this thing
that if you're reading, let's say, the book
of Exodus and you saw the movie, that
piece of shit movie with Charlton Heston, Ten
Commandments, right, if you saw that before you
read the book of Exodus, you're reading the
book of Exodus.
I don't care who you are unless you
know what I'm about to say, which is
having a clear mind and reading objectively, you're
going to fall for what I'm about to
say, Jason Breshears.
I'm saying that friendly, affectionately.
Oh, this is, I'm reading Exodus.
This is where they're leaving Egypt.
Oh, I saw this in the movie, and
they read over everything real fast without reading
any of the details at all, and they
think the movie was accurate, but if you
read the details, the wind blew all night
from the east in the springtime, which means
it could be as cold as 20 degrees
Fahrenheit.
Is that enough to freeze water?
And they walked on the sea of reeds,
which is fresh water, as if it were
land, and in the morning, it says when
the sun came out, Pharaoh pursued, but he
fell to the bottom.
He fell to the bottom like a stone.
He fell to the bottom like lead.
It says it three times.
Now, let me ask you something.
If you're walking through it, if you are
already walking on the bottom, how can you
fall to the bottom?
It's like saying, I'm on the fourth floor,
and I just walked up to the fourth
floor.
I thought you said you were on the
fourth floor, and you walked up to the
fourth floor, but you're already there.
What else do you have?
What you just said after that makes no
sense, so you see, so yeah, and oh,
my God, no one's paying any attention.
The big one, the big tell is when
you start using names like J-E-S
-U-S, you never hear me using that.
Occasionally, it'll come out, but I don't have
to make a point, but that's like, oh,
my God.
You know, yeah, there's no common sense at
all out there.
Yeah, what's the internet is like very much?
It's like when you, okay, there's billions of
people on the internet posting, right, every day
or whatever, billions.
There's more posts on the internet than there
are people by a factor of 100 maybe,
and people are impressed by that, but how
impressed are you by a sandy beach?
How many grains of sand are on a
sandy beach?
Uncountable, right?
It's finite, right, and it's all just a
sandy beach, so I'm telling you, internet is
just a sandy beach, dude.
Yeah.
You have to do it on your own.
Well, the beauty of the process is that
if you're dumb enough to not know what
details you're looking for, then you're also happy
with just not having an answer that is
complicated.
You know what I mean?
It's that simple.
The same skill set that would let you
know you're wrong is the same skill set
that gives you the confidence to think you're
right.
It's really, really fascinating when you think of
it that way.
You know, that's what we're looking at all
the time.
Well, you have to look at everything with
a sense of purpose.
What I mean is, okay, people ask me,
what's a good book I could read?
There's no such thing.
You have to know the bad books also,
right, because then you know that it's a
bad book and not just hearsay, right?
You have to read everything.
Well, I don't have enough time to read
everything.
Well, that's your real answer.
There's not enough time to read everything.
The other thing is, I've read stuff, like,
they used to have the, I call it
the trash pile in the library, like, the
books, misfit books that no one ever wanted
to take out.
Have you seen those in libraries?
They have them.
They put them out in a table.
And there was one, like, one book I
remember is back in the 80s, The 10
Worst Popes Ever, right?
I was like, oh, that's a great book.
No one wants to take that out.
Okay, I want that.
You know, and so you go through stuff.
In other words, the circumstances, like John C.
Lilly states, we're controlled by the ECCO, E
-C-C-O, which is the Earth Coincidence
Control Office.
They control long-term stuff.
We control the short-term stuff, right?
It's kind of like what's that, not Minority
Pro, what's the other one, the guys with
the fedora hats going around Adjustment Bureau?
The Adjustment Bureau is based on that.
Yeah, exactly, because there was no concept before
that.
So go along with it.
In other words, you have to always expect
the unexpected, be prepared for the unexpected.
Well, how can you prepare for something like
that, right?
So you have to have an open heart,
right?
Because your emotions and feelings in your heart
will close you off to certain things.
I'm not saying be open to things that
you know are unlawful or distasteful, but you
have to look at everything.
The other thing is I'm a Yahwehist, right?
And the reason why what really firmed me
up as a Yahwehist is in Exodus 15,
he says, Yahweh is a man, Yahweh is
a man of war.
Now, if he was Elohim or God, it
would state that, right?
So he's a man.
And I've had several people look at that
in various texts, and it does say man,
ish, ish, and woman is ishah, which means
flesh and blood man, right?
With certain powers, let's say, certain, certain powers,
whatever.
And the part that got me is war,
because if you think you're here to be
peaceful, and if you think that peace is
a matter of flower child bullshit, everybody holding
hands, you're an idiot.
The way you bring peace to a knife
fight is not by showing up with a
knife, you show up with a machine gun,
right?
So the way you bring peace to this
type of world is with ordinance that they
have never seen before, right?
And ultimately, it becomes nonphysical ordinance, you know,
and it's spirit, mind, right?
And anything goes.
And when you look at the laws of
the Old Testament, more than three quarters apply
to the temple function to priests and their
families.
So the other few that are left, apply
to basically the way you do business, the
way you eat what you wear, how you
raise a family, how you negotiate time, and
these other things.
And those rules, by the way, even especially
the ones that have to do with fitness
or health, I've all panned out to be
true.
Right?
I personally disagree with the circumcision.
I'm not circumcised.
Is that TMI?
But anyway, it's just a piece of information.
I don't see how it's too much.
It just is what it is.
Yeah.
Okay.
So, but if I had a son, whatever,
I probably wouldn't.
Now here, what that this, the order of
circumcision and man is made in his image
means that the gods are not circumcised.
So it can go both ways, right?
It can go both ways because it's supposed
to be a sign.
It was in Egypt also, by the way,
and make a long story short about this.
Do you want to, would you rather be
like a God or would you rather be
like someone who has allegiance to a God?
I'll lift that, you know, whoever can rationalize
that.
That's like a rabbinical, you know, how rabbis
talk about stuff and they over-rationalize, right?
Like, you know, why did this guy get
eaten by a bear?
Why did this guy die of sickness?
Because he, you know, there were two innocent
boys that he said a bear sick to
bear on to kill them because they made
fun of his head.
You know, that's why, or no, maybe it
was this or was that, but the simple
rationale is the gods are not circumcised.
I'd rather be like the gods and someone
having allegiance to the gods.
I think it trumps that, but that's not
for me to say that's very personal.
And I did give, that's a very personal
thought.
And I also gave a personal thing, right?
So the best, the funniest thing was whenever
I dated a Jewish girl and we're at,
I said, you ever been with a guy
that's uncut?
And they're like, what do you mean?
And we're like, oh, no, but anyway, that's
another thing, right?
Always have fun with that.
But so either way you do what you
want, but the rules work, by the way,
you're, you're, you know, like the U S
constitution, right?
States that anything that's contrary to the constitution
is null and void.
So when the cops and whatever, pull you
over and tell you all in the state
of Florida, blah, blah, blah.
Yeah.
But it's, that's contrary to the constitution.
So it's null and void.
You don't argue with those idiots, but you
know, you just stay on that one point
and it'll work out in the end.
They might put you through torture in the
meantime.
And if you know what you're doing, you'll
get a quarter of a million dollars for
every night you're in jail, right?
At least maybe 50,000 settlement, but that's
still not bad.
If you're in there for a week, that's
250 grand, right?
So you're not going to get it right
away, but on the, it could really be
two and a half million.
And believe it or not, what I just
said happens more often than you would ever
know, but you never hear about it.
Right.
The other thing is the, when you stick
to certain rules and you see that they
work out, it doesn't mean your life is
going to be easy, smoothie, whatever, whatever.
But in the end, it works out and
you're like, Oh, I'm glad I stuck to
my guns or whatever.
Right.
So that's, I found that works for me.
The most people think it's just about certain
food laws, which are open.
Like for example, most people think it's about
not eating pork.
No, it's not about that selectively.
No.
If an animal, a four legged animal is
to be eaten, it should chew the cud
and have a cloven hoof, right?
So you have a rabbit, you choose the
cud, but he has a paw.
So he's out.
The pig doesn't chew the cud, but he
has a cloven hoof.
Now let's say a pig were born that
chewed the cud with two stomachs.
Let's say, is he edible?
Hell yeah, baby back to pork bacon.
You see, because it's not about no pig.
So the, the most people take a very
juvenile approach.
Oh, it's all pork.
Now in the Quran, it says you shall
not eat the flesh of swine or flesh
that's been found dead, like roadkill.
And that's it.
So they eat camel, they donkey, they eat
shrimp.
They love, they have no discernment in that,
right?
It's just these two things.
And that there's no discernment, but the biblical
text teaches discernment.
I'm serious.
If a swine started being born with two
stomachs, I wish one did and chewed the
cud as a cloven hoof.
What would the rabbis do?
They would divide them completely, right?
Yeah, it would be edible.
It would be, it would be.
So for example, if you understand the old
Testament, let's say you mentioned the deserted Island,
but let's say we're in the Himalayas, unmapped
territory, and there's species of fauna we've never
seen before.
We're starving the death and here goes this
furry creature and we're tracking it.
And we observe that it has cloven hoof.
And we observe that it chews the cud.
Now we don't know what the, we don't
know what we're going to call.
The only thing we can call it is
dinner, right?
Because it fits.
Well, a juvenile will say, well, it's about
not eating pork.
Like when I go out to eat and
I say, well, everything here has got swine
on it.
I don't dig on swine, Pulp Fiction, right?
And, um, or something.
And, uh, and they're like, are you Jewish?
And I'm like, what does that have to
do with it?
You know?
Uh, not at all.
And there's, there was a very, um, very,
very, what do you call liberal liberal?
Oh, it's another word for liberal liberal.
You know, it's like bending the rules.
Rabbi in the Bronx years ago, he had
a liberal synagogue and he says, listen, the
Torah, where he says not eating pork, that
just means in certain restaurants, right?
So that, that goes out of the rule
that see, that's totally ignoring the discernment factor.
Now you got to listen to what this
guy says.
And that's what I see going on on
the internet period.
Is that the same guy who said it's
okay to eat Chinese food, any kind, because
whatever, is that that same guy?
Cause I remember a rabbi that was like,
Chinese food doesn't count.
I couldn't understand it.
No, but there's a whole bunch of liberal.
Are you kidding?
I mean, Jewish people are probably modern Jews
are probably the most liberal lot ever.
You ever hear of the Bolsheviks that they're
liberalism used to be something that was good.
Like liberal arts means you have a little
bit of everything or well-rounded and it
turned into something that's basically destroying culture that
works.
And the worst thing you can do is
start blurring the line between male and female,
man and woman, because in the spiritual world,
that's extremely venerated.
In other words, the, the effect of being
a man or a woman, there's not one
over the other, by the way, if you
believe that, then you believe everything else.
You've probably been told that's not true.
The women was the head economist, meaning the
head of the household.
And even in modern culture, if anyone, if
you go look at the Jewish community and
you look at the Latin community, it's the
grandma, that's the head of the household, like
it or not, or know it or not.
Right.
And I'm talking about in the household, not
in the community and the community, it'll be
the older men.
So in the private, the it's matriarchy everywhere,
pretty much, except for Asia.
That's patriarchy, very pay so much that the
women still walk behind them.
I've seen that here even right.
And sit in the backseat.
Have you seen that?
Yes.
The Chinese?
Yeah, they sit in the back, the women
has sit in the backseat.
So Rosa Parks, anyway, this is the veneration
of the male and the female, the man
and the woman is very high in the
spiritual world.
Of course, they're going to attack it.
Right?
A man who wants to be a woman,
is extremely neurotic, very extreme.
Neuro, what do you call psychosis?
Mentally not well.
Sorry.
So anyway.