Sonic Event 124 and here we go rated Y. Anyway, Greek, how about this? Let's just hit it hard
right off the bat. What is the meaning of life?
Exactly. That's right. You know, hey, you know, some people anyway, we'll get into it.
We will try to nan and then I know the meaning of life and you don't. Yeah, that's true. I do.
And this is with little exception. And I've been thinking about this for about 25 years.
Well, more than that. 27 years I've been thinking about this because I started taking notes on this
in Greek. I have a notepad that it's kind of a diary or just notes and I always write in Greek.
You know, if you would have asked me 27 years ago, though, I would have definitely went with
the be fruitful and multiply kind of idea. Sure, sure. But I have this black book. I have several
like a graph, you know, and, you know, you go to a coffee shop, you leave something, you know,
that people are going to page through it. Right. You know, if you leave it, you forgot how many
times years ago in coffee shops were more popular for me. I sometimes leave something on the table.
Right. Oh, yeah. I leave the notebook. I used to love it. Yeah. No, I'll Greek. I would love
doing that. Look, I left tapes on coffee shop tables. I left business cards on coffee.
I think everybody leaves stuff on coffee tables. Right. And I even went security,
even when I was at the border coming in from Mexico and they scared the shit out of them.
Someone told me they separated us. And every time when we rejoined each person that rejoined,
what the hell did you write in that book? Greek, you're terrified of it. And the next guy comes
quick. What the hell was in that book? That's what kept us so long. They had they scanned each page
and sent it to a linguist. Right. Nosy, nosy, nosy. So, yeah. Yeah. So I write these things
down. And the first notations I had was about 27 years ago. So then I know the meaning of life and
you don't. Yeah. OK. And I'll tell you what it is now. So you do. OK. Very simple. This is with
very little exception. You are here. You're a spiritual being. You're actually a mind.
What I mean by that, there's an old Star Trek where they go to a planet and they find these
glowing globes, very old beings. They transferred out of their bodies into these machines so they
don't need a body. And they wanted a body again. Anyway, you're a mind in a body. And because
you don't have memory or know where you're from. And believe me, no one's talking about where
you're from. Anyway, that's another discussion. Yeah, because everybody talks about arriving.
Everybody talks about arriving here. And they say all the time, you know,
we're a spiritual being. You are heavily. You're OK. Do you know how back in the days
Apple didn't work on Windows and vice versa? Right. Then they had this intermediary system
where you bought an Apple computer. That's right. And it ran Windows. Right. Yep. Because it has
protocols and things like that to do that. The protocols and all those things that are required
to be fully sensory in a human body does not allow you to have senses from where you understand and
remember the senses where you're from. And there's so many YouTube people like, well,
we've got memory. No, you're not. No, you don't have memory. You don't have just like you can't
jump from the sidewalk to the top of a four story building. So past lives are all bullshit is what
you're saying. Yeah, well, they're not. Well, here's the thing. There's a idea with past lives
where, for example, if you die now, you're reborn in ancient Rome because time isn't linear. So the
past lives is bullshit the way they just you could even be reborn before you die. Then if time
isn't linear, I mean, I can be right, but you're not. OK, because it's a cyclical. So my Mandelbrot
sets earlier. What's happening is in order for your mind to experience what the body can offer,
you cannot access the ideas and memories and things of where you're from.
So this happens because it happens in the physical. You don't remember being born.
No, you very few people do, because look, and that's a physiological thing. The brain is not
fully developed at that time. So you don't have all of it's a receiver. Yeah, right. Just like
when you have an old ham radio and the dipole is all wrapped up in the box, you plug it in,
doesn't work. You stretch out the dipole six feet or whatever, whatever it is, 40 feet,
you know, for whatever frequency. And suddenly it works. You fold up the antenna,
stops working. Right. OK. Now, that's not the meaning of life. That's the preface.
Now, let me just suggest that the operating system, in other words, the sensory system that
retains information. Right. Tesla cars, they can give you the car for free and pay you a hundred
bucks every time you get on it. You'll still make money because everything that you do
and everything that happens around the car via sensors. Right. Is recorded. So when I say sensory,
it's your sensory. Now, whether you remember it or not, I used to have a joke before digital
cameras. Everyone's got photographic memory. It's just most people are out of film. Right.
OK, so. So, for example, if someone keys if you have a Tesla and someone keys it, that's like
ghetto. I mean, that's city talk. Keys key. Keying a car means you use your key to scratch
the person's car. That's usually a malicious act. Right. Right. The Tesla car will pick up that
sensor and follow you as best as all the cameras that go around the car can get your image and all
that. Right. People don't know that. Now they do. OK, so all these things put together to make you
a body and a mind. Now, jokingly, most people have a mind. They just don't know how to use it.
That's not jokingly. But will that allow you to access source materials and things like that?
You can't. It would really wouldn't work in the situation that we're in right now.
So it's like so that's still not the meaning of life. So it's like having a computer that's got
an operating system, but it's not connected to the Internet. So you can't really get at
the information outside or you have a computer that you change the operating system and the
new operating system that you're using can't access anything or remembers anything from the
That would be a better analogy because we're talking about going from one realm to another
and the other realm, which is this one cannot access anything from that other realm.
Right. It's a total wipe, but it's not a memory wipe. OK, it's an accessible lack of access.
Access denied. Access denied is the easiest, most poignant way to put it. So that's why you
have people that supposedly have breakthroughs and all that. But yeah, it doesn't. You notice
that these spiritual people, whether it's true or not, that have all these breakthroughs from
the other side that come here. Does it change anything? Does it make any has really helped
anyone? No, because it's a completely different world. So then you don't know the meaning of
life. And I do and you will in about a minute. It's very simple. It sounds really sarcastic.
The meaning of life in that condition. I had to preface the condition because in order to have
good communication, you have to preface and form and discuss. That's the order. Most if you start
discussing without information or practice, like what the hell is he talking about? Right. So,
OK, so I just preface now and now I'm going to inform you and then we'll discuss it. The meaning
of life here, as you can see it through history, is for each individual human to waste the time of
the one next to them. So if you are a woman and you have a husband, his purpose is to waste your
time. If you're if you're a husband and you have a wife, her purpose in life, meaning in life is to
waste your time. If you are going to school, the purpose of the school is to waste your time.
And I literally waste your time. In other words, things that can take a minute, take days,
pun, no pun intended. Yeah. So. Husband and wife, get it, take a minute. He's really fast anyway.
OK, so the minute they said of the member, the minute men anyway. Man, yeah. Yeah. OK. So by
the way, we'll get into why that happens. But that's just it's like, anyway, anxiety. But anyway,
everybody's wasting each other's time. Everyone is wasting each other's time.
Constantly. If if how many times have you heard? I can't get that person to understand.
Right. Or that person won't change or that person doesn't learn or this person's too much like this
and this one's not enough like that. OK, from a stoic perspective, you take it all as it comes
and you deal with it within yourself. You don't openly lash out to people or complain or even
give advice unless asked. No, but almost anybody can identify that they're irritated with resistance
that they meet when they're dealing with somebody or conversing with somebody because they're not.
OK, let's say you have a hire. Let's say you have a hire. You got a coffee shop. You want
someone to just clean, empty, clean the tables, empty the garbage, make sure the supplies are
for everybody. Right. The chances of that person doing what they're supposed to do is like 10
percent when they first start, even if they've done it for a long time somewhere else, they have
their own way of doing it. So they're going to waste your time. And even when they're there,
they feel like being there is a waste of time because they'd rather be doing something else.
They have to pay the rent. So I can bring this around and every it's a very it's like Greek.
The meaning of life is just to waste everybody else's time. Yes, absolutely. Without a doubt.
With very little exception. Let me give the exception before we discuss this. The exception
of those. I'll give you an example, because I was going to say somebody hearing this might
listen to this and say, well, does that mean that you're intentionally wasting all our time
as you're speaking to us? I can't help but not to. Yeah, I'm not intentionally doing it. No,
because I wouldn't be doing what I'm doing if it was just like everybody else. OK. And if you want
to know what a waste of time is, it's something called alternative media. There's something
called mainstream media, voting, university, school, college. Look, when you're in an American
school system from K through 12, let's call it let's not call it 13 years. Let's make the math
easy. It's 12 years. Yeah. OK, let's make it easy. All right. So you're in school from, let's say,
depending on what part of the country you're in, from September to June. Right. And then you take
three months off and you take June off, July, August off back to school in September.
The north. OK, in the south, you go from August to May. But yeah. Yeah. And you finish in May. OK,
so very simply, you're in there from the morning, let's say eight thirty nine o'clock,
sometimes earlier, and you're out at three, five days a week. OK, everything I just mentioned
in terms of hours is a thousand hours a year. You could just pencil it out. I'm telling you
where I get the thousand hours a year. I just penciled it out for you. Yeah, it's easy because
one hundred and eighty days. OK. And then if you just imagine that it's a minimum of six hours.
Right. No, wait, seven hours. So if you go seven hours. Yeah, no problem. Good. It's about a
thousand hours per year. It gets there. Yeah, roughly some less, some more. But that's a good
average because we got rid of. So how many years? Twelve. So how many how many hours of education
getting twelve thousand hours? Right. I broke down basically the whole program back in 2008,
2009 because I was involved in the homeschooling stuff, different states across the union
advising. And I figured out that the core material that's taught within twelve thousand hours,
I can teach in less than four hundred. Right. So if you do the math, right, if that's if it's
ten times, it's four thousand, it's 30 times faster. So I developed a system where actually
you will remember everything. It'll be more, more, more than the core. You know what I mean
by the core programs, right? Yeah, I could get less than four hundred hours. I could teach
everything. As a matter of fact, I've done two and a half hours is what it takes. Yeah. I found
out that I could do it even less. And within the four hundred hours, I could take them up to
college level, like almost like a bachelor in any subject. And I show them how to do that.
Now, if you don't think your time is wasted by something that should be done a certain way,
it can be done 30 times faster and it's not. And how many people are involved in the public
school system? Millions. And how many people are noticing enough to make a little bit of
it, but no change? OK, everything is about wasting time, wasting time, wasting time.
Now, fortunately, your lives are short. Sixty, seventy, eighty nine, even if you go 100 years.
OK, let's say I say the average life span, 70. I'm talking about functional. You know,
yeah, I mean, I know I know an 80 year old or did he passed away a long time ago? He said he felt
better at 80 than he did at 35, which was true. He was kind of sickly all his life. He discovered
he was dying. He fine tuned everything. He was in great shape. OK. Right. So what I say,
let's say seventy five. Yeah. Yeah. Most people, they say, let my grandma live to 100. Yeah. What
kind of life after 90 she had? Right. Not much. So living, you're wasting each other's time.
So what does that mean? It means that the level of inefficiency that's built into the type of
mind and spirit we have into the physical body that we exist in every culture
is not fully compatible. That's why most related religions and spirituality is like,
oh, we're just passing through here. When you leave, you'll have a much better situation.
So in other words, the mind and body potential, the mind and spirit potential that we have is
much greater. Right. It's kind of like much greater than the body that we're in now.
It's what we can tune into. So, for example, you take a VW bug and you put a Corvette engine in it.
Yeah, it's going to be fast, but it's also very dangerous because, you know, what's impressive
about a fast car is, can it stop? You know, a lot of people used to soup up cars and they
couldn't stop. The brakes were terrible. So they crashed. Right. Yeah. And the steering
couldn't handle. Right. That's what I mean. So we have a very poor setup in terms of this.
Now, who put it there? I don't know directly, but I could tell you, basically, you can blame
the gods to a certain degree. And there's no blame. It's just things are the way they are,
because remember, life is really short at being 70 years old, 80 years old. That's a short lifetime
to be put into this. Now, the reason why I said that, OK, because there's no struggle in what
I'm saying. Now, you either take it or leave it. What I just said, you know, is it is what I said
about the meaning of life is for everyone to waste everybody else's time and people around you,
even yourself. OK, let's not even go waste the other person wasting time and you're wasting
how many times have you heard someone? I got to play solitaire. I got to play a video game.
I want to watch a movie. I'm bored. You're wasting your own time. You can't help it.
That's all a matter of right. OK, so no one knows anything was very little exception,
though, about anything. OK. I mean, doctors don't know anything about the human body.
Lawyers don't know anything about law on and on and on and on and on and on. Teachers don't know
anything about teaching. It goes on every field. Carpenters don't know anything about wood.
Right. The great majority, they do not. Now, when you start to get to more of the things that are
tactile, like trades and labor, you do have to know more about it because it's going to show
really bad. Right. But the professionals, the people that are doing stuff that is not tangible,
they know nothing about their field at all. This has been by design and it's been pressed on
society big time since 9-11, the whole world. The decree was that anyone that's doing intangibles
like politicians, doctors, lawyers, philosophers, professors, all these people that don't produce
the produce, they don't produce tangibles, but they produce a lot of billables. Right.
Those people are not supposed to know what's going on because of what's called a Freudian slip.
Now, if you remember on 9-11, there was a lot like the 9-11 Commission, a lot of Freudian slips.
One guy's being interviewed on the 9-11 Commission. I was like, I can't talk about it.
It's still going on. But the missile that hit the Pentagon, I'm like, what? What did you say? Oh,
no, I meant. Right. Right. OK. On and on. Remember the George W. Bush's thing,
the bombs that went off in the towers. Right. In the first speech. Right. OK. You're not supposed
to know anything. That's why Biden is perfect. Biden is perfect president. I've got no beef with
because he matches the mindset that is designed perfectly. OK, so and, you know, remember when
a society is going to go through a big change, they always put a president or a leader in that's got
Alzheimer's or dementia. I don't know if you remember Boris Yeltsin. He was an alcoholic
and had dementia for right before they went out. Right. Right. Before Gorbachev. Right. Right.
Well, right before the. Yeah. Well, Yeltsin came in after Gorbachev because Yeltsin.
Was it Yeltsin? OK, which one was a total demented? No, it wasn't Yeltsin. It was before
Gorbachev. The guy before him also had white hair. Anyway, Brezhnev or whatever. No,
no. That was an old dude. Right. Brezhnev was a Brezhnev. He must have been in power for at
least 30 years. Anyway, one of these things. Anyway, it doesn't matter. Forget about the
political scene. The U.S. is a corporation. Title 28, Section 3002, Subsection 15. The United States
is a federal corporation. Well, that's what I said when people were complaining about this debate.
And oh, my God, look, this guy is completely out of it. I said, yeah, well, good thing the
president isn't really important because. Well, it is for the corporation. If you go to Title 28,
Section 3002, Subsection 15A and there's B and all that. It's a federal corporation.
Some idiots might say, well, it's for doing banking. But only that he exists. It doesn't
have to be functional. You know, not really. Yeah. This is for doing banking. Why? Why is
government to banking? They're supposed to create, make them. They're supposed to regulate and make
the gold and silver. What do you mean? Anyway. Yeah. Again, I want to go back up and really
being big doses, binging on Brandon Williams, Brandon Joe Williams.
And I'm going to interesting to watch him. He's got a couple of flaws. He
got a fully automated email list. You email him, you get barraged back, you know, fully automated
stuff. I sent him a couple of messages based on the cases that he has what he should watch out for.
But it's best to watch and do it on its own. So it's time for that kind of stuff. So
like, you know, the I've never got into what's called the revocation of election,
but that's in the IRS code. You know, I remember Schultz. Schultz was the guy who drew Charlie
Brown. Yeah. Charles Schultz. Charles Schultz. Yeah. He has one from the 70s. Dear IRS,
please unsubscribe me. That's exactly what you do. But you do. It's a title 26 something,
something, something, or you could do what it's called. And the IRS says that we received your
letter of revocation of election as per the U.S. Congress. And when they approve,
the IRS will always write back and say as per the U.S. Congress. And when they don't approve,
they'll tell you as per the U.S. Congress. That's what runs them. So and I agree with
Brandon Joe that the IRS is the most receptive and they're the most, let's say, how would you
say agency in government? In other words, they follow the law. They don't interpret the law,
whatever the codes are. That's why Title 12, Section 411 is so powerful with them. They,
you know, they totally understand that you got rogue agents in there that like to chase people
down. And there's been plenty of IRS agents that chase people down and said, if you want your IRS
problems, go and meet me here. And they demand a bag of cash. They've been caught several times,
right? I don't know if you remember that. Yeah. Okay. So just like you got rogues everywhere,
you know, like the biggest, all the drug transports are still done by the law enforcement,
by the way, and the utility companies, you know, when they want to bring a big
load into the city. They don't have a police motorcade, but they use the utility.
If you see a bunch of electrical and gas utility trucks parked up against the warehouse or
whatever, you're like, well, that looks suspicious, right? No, never look suspicious because
utility company. Anyway. So let's get back to the meat, because there's, there's a lot of meat
before you get out anything that resembles a bone on this matter. And a lot of people might have a
bone in it. But yes, you're basically wasting everybody's time and everybody's wasting your
time. So what do you know about that? And what do you do about it? No, you just do what you do.
But you do it well. So if you're going to embark on something, learn about it, right?
It doesn't take much to learn, improve your memory, right? One of the things that got a lot
of people attracted to what I was saying, was I said, you know, you guys years ago, I'd make call
in on the internet, I said, everybody is talking about this, but you don't even know what words
mean. Look up the word nice. And I have to do that. And someone in the background told me,
you know, I said, look it up in etymology, not a dictionary, because dictionaries for
pronounced, that's why you get the phonetic spelling. Right? And people start saying,
I never knew it meant. If you look it up right now, it means foolish, stupid, senseless. That's
the first. Right? Yeah. So I started to bring a lot of these things up to people. And then another,
I brought up like water, and I brought up scientific stuff, and how magnets work,
you know, or how they don't work, as they say, politics, this and that. So how do I know so
about so many subjects, you just spend a few minutes looking it up. You know, here's the
thing, if you're an attorney, and you study the law for five minutes a day, and your colleagues
find out that you're doing that, and what you're going to be disbarred, guaranteed,
you will have disciplinary action, you have to keep it to yourself. The same with a doctor,
there's several medical people that I've known, and also heard from others, the same thing.
They wanted to make some improvements. And they get a reprimand letter saying, No,
we're not looking for improvements. We just look for you to do it the standard way.
Right? I don't know who that guy was in 1912, or 1902, or something that basically,
when the AMA first started in a small office, there will be no more medical research,
only current standard practices will be used, right? I forget starts with an S.
That's not schlotzky. It's nice. Last year was the transistor guy. Anyway, somebody will find it
and put it in chat in the future. He was a guy that wrote a lot of the codes that the medical
people follow. So all you have to do is spend a few minutes studying the history of the thing,
the functioning of the thing, who's supposed to know about it, of the thing, and don't count on
them at all. So if you try to study law, they'll say see an attorney, big, big, what do you call a
diversion tactic? attorneys don't know anything about law at all. And the doctors don't anything
about the human body. Now, from the discussions I've had about with doctors, when I pin them down
about certain things, and I don't do it as much as I used to, they basically just jump up and say,
you know, the body heals itself, the body heals itself. So they go, How are you going to help
that? You know, they don't understand what's going on at all, right? So procedure, which is
like a lawyer, it's the lowest form of what happens in the courtroom, which is procedure. It's kind of
like the altar boy in the church, you know, he is a procedure, he has to walk a certain way, right?
Right. And look a certain way. So you're locked in a world of procedure, because when you're wasting
time, you don't need anything that has any form or matter or meaning, you just go through the
motions, which is procedures. And that's what's going on. And I've been, I've been looking at
this. And I've been talking to say this publicly, and emphatically, emphatically, because I've
just kept coming up. And I tell people, you hear this often, not often, but someone will tell
someone else, you're wasting my time. You hear that often? Oh, they need to? Yeah, they need?
Well, it depends. You need to hang on that a little bit more and figure out how and why. Because if
you're criticizing someone, about they're wasting your time, see, I will never give criticism unless
I tell you why I'm going to criticizing the criticism and how to fix it. If one of those
three parts are missing, I will not criticize. And I'm very critical. In other words, it's so easy
and simple to criticize anything because, look, when I any anything that I purchased in the last
three decades, anything doesn't matter what is a can opener, a vacuum cleaner, TV,
anything, anything, anything, I had to make an improvement on it, like an obvious improvement,
like this needs an improvement, right? And I modify it, so it works better. Everything I have
not come in touch contact with anything yet that I've purchased, except for some night, you know,
what what's really high quality clothing, appliances, where all of them need modification,
all of them, you know, to example, I got this like high end toaster, toaster out it has all
these trays and stuff. And it has a little rubber feet under the appliance, you know,
the little rubber feet, right? About a half inch tall. Well, if you stack all the trays and extra
racks are about an inch tall. So where do you put them? But what I did was I removed the rubber
feet and I put in one inch, inch and a quarter rubber feet. So now I could slide all the rubber
trays underneath the toaster. Oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh. Brilliant, right? No, no one is paying
attention. And whenever I modify like a vacuum cleaner, anything, anything. I'm always like,
who designed this? Are these people out to lunch? All they needed to do was move this thing over an
eighth of an inch or add this or whatever. And most people will find that irritating, annoying,
but that's the core of Greek speak. In other words, if you're if you have a sense of opposites,
right, let's just break it down. You know, there's good and bad, cold and hot, right? The very
opposite. So if you can start narrowing down, you know, like if you're going to go to the store,
it's $75 until I'm rounded off to the nearest hundred, he keeps the change, right?
If it's $12, you can see rounded up to the nearest hundred, you keep the you keep the
whole thing you see. So you can do big I'm talking about big round offs like that.
Most some not most, but some people say you're pissing me off. That's great.
That's great. Because I know that person is here to waste other people's time, including mine.
So if I'm pissing them off, that means I'm doing the opposite of what they're doing in life,
which is wasting time.