Sonic Event 30, Ocelli in the Greek, rated Y, here we are, 30 episodes, Greek, what do
you think about that?
I don't know, what should I think about it?
I thought we would have maybe covered more up until now, but we didn't.
Speaking of 30, we finally got together with some of your car stuff and you're waiting
on a part.
We'll see how it works out for you.
I figured we might as well get back into what we were talking about a minute ago.
Yeah, a little update on that.
I mean, after all, you gave some driving instruction in the last one, I think it was, and boy,
that was interesting.
But no, I'm learning the hard way that car parts are up in price for sure no matter where
you go.
But yeah, so that's happening.
So if anyone, get in touch with Chuck if anyone has used or new car parts, he just needs a
starter for a 23-year-old Saturn, right, I could say that.
But you have one on the way, and you notice, let's just say the Greek encourages people
to work when it comes to turning nuts and bolts and things, because ultimately it's
just like if you know how to change a light bulb, it's not very different, it's just that
you need a tool.
Right, right.
And demystify it using YouTube.
Right, well, actually I demystified it by talking to you a little bit, and you saw me
struggle a touch with a few things, but look, I'm just not used to doing it, and I'm working
on it.
Yeah, but you see, I have a very different perspective.
I also made you run through some protocols that most mechanics don't even do.
So we'll see, you'll get it going.
Very useful, solid information, and hopefully I can just take care of this myself instead
of calling the...
Yeah, right, oh my gosh, it's a screwed up culture, like attorneys and doctors, their
culture, the people that are in those things, most of prefabricated, professional, whatever,
what's been done is the culture has been downturned, so in order to operate as one of those people
working in that field, you're going to have to operate in a downturned culture, you know?
Right, so I'm not calling the mechanic, okay, I'm actually going to tackle this thing myself
as best I can, and I'm working with the missus on it, you know, because she's got better
eyesight and we can team up, right?
Yeah, so basically it's just an elaborate, greasy light bulb, anything you approach,
there are things that you require special tools for, and there's especially diagnostics,
and especially when you get into transaxles and things like that, but otherwise the rest
of it is pretty, it's already, it's just R&R, remove and replace.
Yeah, I mean, again, outside of the computers and, well, transmissions are a little bit
more complicated.
That's what I mean, transaxles are generally tough to deal with, I wouldn't, because the
amount of tools, even something like dropping a gas tank to change a pump in a larger car,
I would take to someone who has a stand, even though a lot of the cars, you just take out
the back seat and they actually encourage you, you know, again, remove the gas, the secondary
gas cap for the pump, it's like changing a light bulb again, but.
So anyway, what else, what else have we got?
Well, we've got a couple other things, you're still working with magnets, and I brought
up something before we started recording.
Odd numbers.
Yeah, well, because you showed me a picture of something, and very, very cool, look, no,
I'm not going to learn that much from it, but it is interesting, because I looked at
the array there, and you had talked about using odd numbers of magnets in the past,
and I know some people in the chat are working on that a little bit.
By the way, for those of you that are subscribed, just a little warning, there might be a price
change soon, but if you're signed up and you're a current, you know, subscriber, your price
isn't going to change.
Oh yeah, because you said that current price is for up to a hundred, we might have gone
past that now.
Right.
Not that there's a hundred current, but a hundred people passed through.
So it could be that new signups after this, so this is to kind of encourage you to stick
around with us, because your price is going to stay where it is, and others might pay more,
just saying.
So magnets.
Anyway, magnets.
Magnetism in nature.
So I was noticing, though, and you brought it up, you said, look, you ever notice that
flower petals are always in odd numbers, and I said, well, logically, to me, there's always
magnetic elements in nature that are often ignored by those, you know, those people,
I forget how you describe them, but the people that just want to break things down to the
chemical and that's it, they don't consider the rest of all of what's happening.
And there is a magnetic element to, well, everything that's alive, seems like to me.
So of course, the presentation of flower petals, which have a practical, you know, outside
of their aesthetic value, they have practical use and practical function.
They would present themselves in odd numbers as well, because that's just the way these
things work.
What do you think of that?
Pushing daisies, right?
There's a little cute little song online about that.
Pushing up little daisies, have you heard it?
It's kind of bizarre.
It's a Weezer song, I think.
Yeah, maybe.
Yeah.
Anyway, yeah, go ahead.
Magnetism, when you have an overabundance of it, like light or heat or whatever, you
get an adverse effect.
And the adverse effect of magnetism is a noticeable pushing away, repulsive force.
Everything in nature pulls, by the way, even when you're, pushes, I'm sorry.
Even when you perceive a pulling force, it's actually a pushing force going from a high
pressure to a low pressure, let's say, less resistance.
But the bottom line with what's discussed about magnetism is very simple.
A magnet is to electricity, or the dielectric, as photographic paper is to light.
So if you have anything that you discern as being, quote unquote, a ferromagnet, that
is just no different than holding a photograph that has been exposed by a certain event of
light.
So a certain electric event, dielectric really, event, is memorialized in iron, what we call
a magnet.
Now, you mentioned those other people that talk about this.
I got a joke, by the way, this ties into what I'm saying.
It's real simple.
It's called peer review.
That's the joke, and that's the punchline also.
So don't fall for that, right?
That's the joke and the punchline.
That's the whole thing in a nutshell.
So anyway.
It's so funny because you don't know this at all because we didn't discuss it, but believe
it or not, the phrase peer review came up with me a couple of days ago, and I did start
laughing at it and didn't explain myself, and then others started laughing at it that
were involved in the discussion.
It was pretty funny because it was like peer review, sure.
Well, they trust the science.
All scientific evidence shows that there is no more science, right?
Anyway.
And who the hell are your actual peers, okay, really?
Well, yeah.
If you're peerless, you're in trouble.
The other thing, it's kind of like with the psychologists, you know, anyone who wants
to see a psychiatrist should have their head examined, right?
Definitely.
It's all along the same thing.
So what's going on in nature, as you see the budding action, let's say, of a flower, you
notice the repulsion of the membrane of the blossom turning into a flower growing, right?
That is just the right amount of magnetism, and also there are other factors.
But essentially, because we see things mostly in balance, if a flower is out of balance,
it won't grow, it'll fall apart, it'll die, whatever, it won't go into its cycle.
So we see the magnetism in balance, but we don't see it as magnetism until we start,
let's say, putting power lines together and they're pushing each other apart.
That's overabundance of magnetism, right?
So the electrostatic, the dielectric, pulls together and the magnetic pushes apart.
That's when you overdo it to display that feature of nature.
So in essence, you need both.
If you see things growing outward, it's magnetic, and if you see things pulling together, it's
electric.
So when you have a break in the skin, a cut, and it's healing, right, it's electrostatic.
When you see a break in the cut in the skin and it's not healing and it's swelling up,
magnetic.
Get it?
So speaking of which, we got into the last time we finished off was about signing void.
I don't know if I should bring it up again, and I said, holy shit, once they find out.
I just wanted to tie that in because there's a lot of people that have a lot of hang-ups
about how things should be done by following others.
Take a pause there for a second.
A lot of people have hang-ups about following what others do, and what happens usually
doesn't end up well.
And if you know that's a trait, a social trait that people have, all you have to do is, let's
say you have an alternative group, whether it's legal, medical, political, whatever.
Let them do what they're doing.
All you got to do is steer them out a little bit, steer them in a certain direction, right?
Imagine you're on a ship and you turn the wheel like a quarter of a radian, right?
And a hundred miles, you'll be 50 miles off where you want it to be.
You won't find you lost, right?
So all they do with these groups, all you have to do is steer them in a certain direction
and get them off the target.
And then you'll have people, again, use the nautical analogy, they'll jump ship.
Some will drown.
Some will stay on the boat and be lost, right?
Some will get hijacked and pirated, right?
So this is what's going on.
And the reason I say this is because the signature in the, quote unquote, the legal study people,
patriot, whatever, they base everything on it and they fight with it and they don't understand
what happens when you approach any situation with finesse, regardless if it's legal or
whatever.
And the finesse, by the way, has even been lost by the professionals that practice it.
So attorneys, by the way, if you look at how their organizations are set up, they very rarely
even tell you they do anything legal.
They're known as a professional office.
That's what the category is, right?
And by the way, the Congressional Record has the attorney bar association listed as a communist
organization.
You could look it up.
Put in Congressional Record, Bar Association, Communist Organization.
It's been well established.
Not that it's political or whatever, but basically you're saying about how all the prices went
up.
This is just bouncing around here.
That's attached to the woke stuff, all the clothing stores and all the ads, Victoria's
Secret having fat guys in bras kind of thing, not that I'm saying anything bad about fat
guys in bras.
I'm just saying.
Whatever, do what you want.
But why the hell is a starter motor, a starter?
It's all attached.
Yeah.
There's a lot of controversy about their woke agenda.
Their ventures are controlled by BlackRock, right?
Or the other one.
What's the other one?
BlackRock and the other one, right?
There's another one.
Even when they were giving out the stimulus checks, I told people, you're going to destroy
the economy.
For every dollar you get on a stimulus check, you're going to pay for it a hundred times
over the next decade, but that's okay.
Their Vanguard is the other one, yeah.
Vanguard.
They have a very strict agenda.
They said either you're going to fold, you're going to go with this, or you're going to
fold or you're going to suffer.
But anyway, they control all of that now on the back end, or on the front end, sorry.
Just like if you have one of those WIC cards, what is it, Eat Better, EBT, Eat Better Tonight
card or food stamps.
That is full.
That's not government at all.
That's fully controlled by JP Morgan.
It's on the card itself.
Well, it was the last time I saw it a little while back.
What I'm saying is the private interests are coming to the forefront.
They're trying to tell you in a hundred different ways what you consider government is a non,
how would you say, something that just doesn't exist.
It's basically all under private control, kind of like what the Dutch East India Company,
the VSO back 200 years ago.
If anyone looks up the Dutch East India Company in terms of adjusted for today's currency,
it's bigger than Apple, IBM, McDonald's and all those companies put together still.
It was the largest model of corporate, let's say, new world order under corporate control
ever.
That was 200 years ago.
There's nothing new.
There's nothing new that's coming in respect of that.
It's just more and more is being told while the older stuff is being pushed to the side,
but no one cares.
That's why business goes on the way it does.
Again, just to go back to the signature thing, you just be upfront and be honest about what
you're doing and what you see and you'll pretty much have more of the universal forces on
your side.
Instead of saying, I'm not going to sign that no matter what and you're thrown in jail for
that or you're listed as or charged with moral turpitude, that's my favorite.
If you're dealing with a cop, they'll write obstructing justice or interfering arrest,
but if you go up higher agencies, they use more elaborate terms.
If you get in trouble with DHS or FBI, they don't say resisting arrest or obstructing
justice.
They'll say moral turpitude.
They'll start using the thicker version of the dictionary or the thesaurus.
The whole thing is the same.
It's all just commercial.
In commerce, you have free will and you have free – in other words, one of the biggest
sins in commerce is to obstruct someone else's ability to do commerce, by the way.
Think about that.
That's for another discussion.
I could show you many places how that – what I just said, the biggest sin in commerce is
to obstruct another person's ability in so many ways.
It's written in many other ways where you're given rights and privileges also.
That's why it's called – when you do this, you waive your right or you waive this,
you waive that.
That has nothing to do with – it has to do with free will.
Obstructing someone's ability to do commerce is the same as obstructing their free will,
isn't it, until you get to waive it.
All these things are very interesting in how they interplay, but it is satanic, adversarial,
because it relies on your ignorance.
When you – let's say these law enforcement or whatever or legal groups, professional
groups or authorities interact with people, they don't interact with people based on
what is supposedly in the law or code, legal code or statute or whatever.
They act on the individual based on their level of ignorance.
You see, it's kind of backwards.
It's quite interesting, but ultimately, remember, you're dealing with a group of
people that have no problem sending 200 million people to their death.
Who sent 200 million people?
World War I and World War II.
You could study World War I and World War II, not in the bullshit textbooks that have
been peer-reviewed.
Remember the joke?
But study – you'll see no sound reason for any of those world wars, but yet you're
talking about throwing millions of people into meat grinders, right?
Same people behind that.
That's what occurs over and over again, though.
The next one is going to be actually pretty bad, but it's going to be over different
reasons.
It's going to be religious.
When I say religious, it'll be when they're in the middle of it, you tell them this is
a religious war.
They'll say, no, it's not.
You see?
So it's never noticed for what it is.
Kind of like when you deal – by the way, I've been out around the past few days and
mainstream interacting with people in various shops and locations.
They're screwed.
They have no concept at all about where they've been, where they are, and I don't have to
say this, but it's interesting when you – I'd say this to this audience, but they have no
clue.
In other words, the steering analogy I just gave, when people steer a certain way, there's
no way you could correct them.
It's really sad to see a waste of resources and human bodies that are so out of, let's
say, sync.
But they're in sync with something, and that's something I've talked about, known as the
end of the societies, what they're in sync with.
Kind of like – I used to give the analogy, you know that look, the look that you see
on the normie's face is the same look you see on a baby seal's face right before it
gets clubbed.
Now, most people listening are probably not old enough to remember, but Save the Seals
back in the 70s, remember that?
Oh, I do, yeah.
The fur movement, yeah, the fake fur, you know.
So anyway, they would show pictures of a little baby seal, you know.
For a little while, they would spit on people that wore fur, and then they'd fake spit
on you if you wore fake fur, yeah.
Or they'd dump red paint on a fox, on a $50,000 white fox coat.
Oh, yeah.
That was the other thing, right, dousing people with paint, yep.
Or spray paint.
Spray paint was another thing they did, too, for a little bit, the spray paint, yeah.
Yeah, so all that stuff.
So anyway, they have that look, a baby seal right before it gets clubbed.
I just wanted to bring that up because there's nothing out there, but, you know, hey, you
use them for what they're good for, which is whatever interaction you have, right?
You're going to be working somewhere or doing commerce somewhere, even socializing.
You just take all those things into account, you know.
It really sucks, though, because when you deal with the normies in the population at large,
you have to be very superficial, and if you're not used to being superficial, it's quite
the shock, by the way, you know.
So what else did we want to cover?
I think that's pretty much it.
Well, I want to continue a little more with the emo because I felt kind of like I gave
too much of my personal situation that day to illustrate what happens when you get involved
with the emo and what you perceive.
But right before that, I want to just go into the chat.
There was something about someone putting in something about their, I don't know if
you've read it, Chuck, one of their parents, I believe, health condition, and I went on
with some too long responses on what's going on, and I don't think there's the ability
to drive home enough what's going on with the human body in a more simple way, and I
try to simplify, and I just want to cover that again.
Did you read any of the chat this week?
No, I'm opening it up right now because I didn't catch this one, though.
I caught other stuff previous, but go ahead.
Basically, we're looking at an individual, I'm guessing is older than the one who's
writing the post, who's a sub, I'm presuming, and they had parts of their body removed
and they're in a state of what we call not doing so well and then recovering and on and
on and on.
Now, just generally, I gave a response, and what's more important about this is the point
of view on the response.
Very often, you hear people's parents and friends or co-workers or whatever, they fall
into the medical system, and it's either getting on a drug cocktail regimen or series of surgeries
or therapies along those lines, right?
Right.
Okay.
And usually, the person has to make the decision themselves.
Usually.
Sometimes, it's a court order, by the way, because they're all the same, you know,
it's an organization, but ultimately, the person makes a choice.
Now, they have to be in such misery and such pain or discomfort that they actually make
the choice to go ahead with the drug cocktails or the surgeries, right?
What's always never, never perceived, actually, it's not, is that the body's ability, right?
You'll never hear this anywhere else, by the way.
The body's ability to get sick, disease or ill, even growing tumors, is part of its system
that's built in, just like when you put up an important building, you build in safety
features, like a sprinkler system in case there's a fire, right?
Okay.
Or automatic shutoffs, you know, like for return vents and air vents, if there's a fire,
there's a switch, basically, it's very primitive, it's like a tube that holds a chain or a cable
and the hook is inside of a wax pot.
So if that duct gets so hot that the wax melts, guess what happens, it releases the chain
that closes the duct, stop the airflow, it's called a fusible link, could be a piece of
rope, right?
All these very simple things, but let me ask you, actually, without asking, let's just say,
okay, but once the event is over, okay, the body's just like that, the body has all of
these things built in.
So when things go wrong energetically, usually from food and mental state, these emergency
things click on to do what?
To block.
What does a sprinkler system do?
It douses, right?
To save the building, but what happens when the sprinkler system works great to save the
building?
Oh, everybody just come home and go back to work, or are you going to be like, the carpet's
wet, all the paperwork's ruined?
Yeah, clean everything up, replace carpets, you know, go ahead.
Yeah, you've got to call a restoration team and you've got to restore the building, but
it's not catastrophic, usually, right?
The same with the duct work, the automatic shutoffs, every time I talk about this, think
of the World Trade Center, because, by the way, the World Trade Center, before they
sabotaged the demolition scheme there, they had to shut down all the mains that are connected,
right?
Yeah, of course.
Yeah, because they have actually, on those big skyscrapers, they have shock sensors,
I forgot what they're called, there's a specific name for them, that if there's an explosion
or something, and the main senses a shock, it will shut off the water, it'll shut off
the power, right?
So they had a dilly-dally with all that stuff.
By the way, World Trade Center was not terrorism, it was sabotage, because everything that was
needed to take it down was already in place.
So anyway, just like pulling a fire alarm, right, it's a form of sabotage.
So the body has all these safety mechanisms built in, and when the diet, the intake of
the diet, starts to, let's say, inhibit the way the energies need to move, too much of
one energy or too little of another energy, the body will start to develop a blockage,
could be an aneurysm, it could be a tumor, it could be a cancerous cell, to stop the
flow.
No, you're not talking about a manifestation of something like...
Oh, you are, okay.
Various manifestations.
Okay, okay.
That's why very often when people are concerned with bad skin, I'm like, be thankful, because
that means your insides are not... you're doing it on your skin versus doing it on the
inside.
Okay.
Right?
Very rarely do you see someone with bad skin that has liver failure or kidney failure or
cancer, but they have to live with the bad skin appearance, right?
Right, right.
And you'll never hear...
It's funny how...
This is basic Taoist perspective.
By the way, the Western societies also had this, but it's been lost, obviously.
Could you imagine being in Vatican Europe in the 1500s talking this way when they wanted
to put their medical on you?
You know what they would do to you very quickly, right?
Yeah, you'd disappear.
So the body has all these built-in systems to shut down parts of the body.
It's kind of like on the extreme side, how many times have you heard of a wild animal
getting caught in a trap and having to gnaw its leg off to get out of the trap?
Yeah, I've heard about it a lot.
I've only seen it a few times.
Mice do that.
But yeah, yeah.
Mice, rats, yeah.
Right.
Yeah.
Occasionally a lizard or whatever, but there's no lizard traps that I know of.
So this is really how it's set up.
So in other words, when someone has disease or is ill, you ready?
That is manifesting the perfection of the human body.
Its ability to deal with such an adverse situation.
And by the way, before a tumor or cancer or organ failure appears in the body or manifests
in the body, it has given you sign after sign and signal after signal over a long, long
period of time.
But if you don't know that language, well, you're going to ignore it.
Yeah, that happens a lot where somebody goes, well, now I know why this was hurting.
I know why this was doing this.
I know, you know, and you figure it out afterwards because like, well, that makes sense now that
this was happening.
A lot of people catch it later.
So very often I hear, you know, my mom got cancer.
I was, you know, first thing I said, I have to be very careful.
My mom got a tumor.
So I say, good.
I say, whoa, good.
Like they think that you mean them negative, right?
Well, because what follows that is, because that means your body's, if she got, I mean,
she can get rich.
She could reverse it.
You see?
But if you go the right center medical route, you probably won't.
They'll kill you because they look, they want that kind of situation, you know?
So actually the doctors that are working, remember, whether it's legal, law enforcement,
medical, financial, if you have people interacting with the public, the less they know about anything
that they're doing, the better, right?
So if you are interacting with a medical, financial, legal, or whatever person, judicial,
whatever, they absolutely know nothing about what their field is about.
Right.
And if they did, they would be pulled back.
Not either.
The organization they work for would say, we have to make a decision.
Do we pull them out from dealing with the public and keep them here because maybe they're
valuable in this or do we get rid of them?
Make sure they never work in this again, right?
That is one or the other.
If they don't run away from it themselves, once they realize what's going on.
Yeah.
And this is a sad reality.
It's getting worse, actually.
By the minute, I want to say by the minute, you know, at any point they say, you know,
there's like 500 babies an hour being born, you know, there's 1,000 people dying every
hour across the world, let's say, that's why I say by the minute.
So anyway, the perfection of the body to not only persist in a robust manner as it does,
it has a very robust safety system that gets to the point where almost like you hear of
an animal chewing its leg off to get out of a trap.
And that's what all of these manifestations are.
I did post, it was kind of hard to find, a Michio Kushi playlist.
He's actually hard to listen to.
But in 1980s, I was made aware, I actually went to a dinner party and they asked me to
make the dessert for his party, which I did.
And I didn't appreciate all the information that he gave at the time, but I was mentored
by someone else, Shizuko Yamamoto.
Very simple.
Just like, you could be mentored, you could be around someone for a few weeks or a few
months and you could bring up a situation and they give you like a three-word answer
that you have to think about for a couple of days, right?
That, you know what I mean?
Most people considered learning or being a mentor sitting down for an hour and hearing
them speak for an hour, right?
It wasn't like that at all.
It was just pointing you in the right direction and this is how maybe you should think about
it, go for it, right?
Is he hard to listen to because of the accent?
Is that what the problem is or?
The recording.
And the accent.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Yeah.
Accent.
Very Japanese.
The thing that I don't like promoting about macrobiotics is really a modified Japanese
culture and modified diet, but it just means eating locally in the environment and it means
eating seasonally and it means understanding the energies of the body.
Recently I was discussing something with someone about diet and they brought it up how people
around them are not eating well and I said, look, it's not about changing, you never first
of all tell anyone they should change anything they're doing in an insecure world, right?
Because everything is so insecure around them that the thing that they have secure is their
diet and you tell them you're going to change that, it's like their whole reality just fell
apart.
The way to do it is by substitution.
So I think I've said this before, if you eat McDonald's for breakfast, Burger King for lunch
and Wendy's for dinner every day, you don't tell them to stop that.
You just keep eating that, but go home and prepare some of this and some of that and
bring it with you.
So when you go to the breakfast for McDonald's, eat some of that and don't order so much McDonald's.
So when you go to Burger King for lunch, bring some of that, eat some of that with your Burger
King so you don't eat so much Burger King and when you go home, don't bring so much
Wendy's home, eat that instead.
Gradual transition.
Transition, right, until it gets to the point where you'll notice that, hey, I'm eating
so little McDonald's and I'm feeling better eating this, I don't need that.
You see, transition, that transition could be a matter of days, weeks or years.
It doesn't matter.
Just get yourself into something that is going to work for the body.
The other thing that I had conversation with this person is they're kind of hung up about
proteins and carbs and measuring pH in the body.
I said, all of that is fiction and you know when I really got forthright and used a few
pejoratives when they brought up the word calories, oh man, I said, are you telling
me you're fucking pooping charcoal, right?
So all that doesn't matter, push it to the side because there is no protein by the way.
No one has ever seen a protein, right?
It's what they see as the presence of amino acids.
Guess what?
There's amino acids in carbohydrate food.
So, hey, guess what?
Oh, carbs.
You know what?
What they call protein foods, guess what?
There's carbs in that too.
It doesn't make any sense.
It's all energy.
Here's the short of it because I might lean a little bit into yes, you do fix most things
with diet.
I think I have gone on a sonic a while back saying if you have a very clean diet, anything
in your body, you'll start to see it healing in a few days to a week.
Well, that's why I've never objected to people that say, look, your food is your medicine,
your medicine is your food.
I've never objected to that because I think it's correct.
Right, but you don't need medicine if you're doing it right because medicine to me is like
a band-aid.
Well, no, but if your food is your medicine, excuse me, your medicine, then therefore that's
all there is to it.
You know what I mean?
No, but I'm saying you don't even need medicine because where do you put the medicine?
The medicine cabinet next to the band-aids and all the crap that you really don't need
to use unless you are trying to help something.
Yeah, the thing is to be robust, right?
Humans are robust.
Even the weakest mainstream normie that eats on a standard American diet, which is sad
food, yes, standard American diet, they're extremely robust.
Extremely robust.
In other words, the body can take tremendous amount of abuse before it gets ill.
What does that say?
For most people, for them to come down with an illness means it's many, many years of
abuse or giving the body stuff.
One simple way to reset this, which is very easy, I said, is get yourself brown rice.
Lundberg is a brand and short grain.
It doesn't have to be that, but that is a brand that has been consistent for decades,
and it's very high quality.
Then learn how to make a dish called kimpira.
Very simple.
Get yourself some burdock root if you can.
It's actually a weed.
It's in the thistle family.
Get some carrots and onions and some high quality sea salt and learn how to prepare
that.
I'll get into that on the food stuff.
The best way to prepare, you know the matchstick cut for carrots and things or the burdock,
you cut it on an extreme biased angle, so it looks like these very thin elliptical shavings
of the vegetable.
Then you lay them down flat and you go across them and you make a very thin, very fine matchstick
and saute that and have that with the rice.
Get some kuzu root, not kudzu, but kuzu.
It's a starch.
It's like corn starch, but it actually has medicinal properties.
It's an intestinal tonic.
What this will do, this food that I just mentioned is extremely bracing.
It will give you, for most people that are hungry and need some energy, if they sit down
and have a really good burger or a steak or something, if you eat animal, you get energy
right away.
That's why people like eating animal.
They call it stick to your ribs kind of meal, right?
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, when you eat animal food, even fish, it gives you energy right away, but at a cost,
right?
Your body has to produce something that is dead.
It's actually, we're not meat eaters, we're carrion eaters because we don't eat things
alive usually, so it's a form of carrion.
People that say, oh, I'm a carnivore.
No, you're not.
A carnivore eats a live animal.
That's different from-
You're a scavenger, you're a carrion, yeah.
That's why they encourage the bald eagle as a noble bird, but they never really talk about
its behavior.
It's mostly a scavenger bird, looks for dead things.
The only thing they show you is this beautiful, when it's in flight and it glides down and
dives and pulls a fish out of a lake, right, or something, but very rarely.
I've been around where the White Mountains of Arizona, where there's a very large bald
eagle population.
They are pretty big birds, by the way.
I mean, their wingspan is like a grown man stretching their arms out, right?
It's quite a thing to see.
Or you could just look at it as a good looking turkey, so anyway, because turkeys are pretty
big too.
Yeah, they're scavengers.
They'll go through garbage cans, they'll eat dead stuff, they'll even take a shoe away.
If you've got a leather shoe and you're sunbathing by the lake, they'll fly it on, swoop down,
mm, that's leather, I could eat that.
It's not like it took your shoe by mistake.
It will try to eat, it will eat your ... Anyway.
So, yeah, they're not ... It's not the noble picture that we get, right?
No, not at all.
But in essence, eating something that's very bracing like that, it doesn't have to be that
way.
In other words, brown rice and kimpura.
If you're ... In other words, take some time and assess what's in your environment.
If you have a farmer's market, whatever, if you are, let's say, in an urban environment,
go cross-latitude with your finger on a map and you can enjoy foods from anywhere along
that latitude in the world.
That'll be very similar, right?
So let's say where you and I are, I'm about 32 degrees latitude or something, I think
you are also.
Go across the world.
We could have Middle Eastern, Chinese, you go across, you're right, all along there.
Southern European, right, pretty much, North Africa.
So all those different varieties that I mentioned, those are very tasty foods and very rich menu
all across in variety.
That's another way to do it, cross-latitude.
But it should be whole.
If you were trying to heal the body and have food that is very bracing and empowering to
the body, when you go out and do shopping, if it has a list of ingredients on it, it's
probably not ...
In other words, it shouldn't be packaged food.
It should be as whole as possible, right, and not pre-packaged, right, and vacuum-sealed
or whatever, right, or made at a factory.
Yeah, I'm somewhere between 32 and 33 degrees, but yeah, I was just looking to make sure about
that, but yep.
Yeah.
A while back, I memorized all that when I used to talk more about all that stuff.
But if we just generate latitude, yeah, so cross-latitude is pretty safe for the seasonal
macrobiotic part, let's say, or I don't even like to use that word, but it's just a simple
thing to send people to, you know what I mean, to study.
But here's the other hard thing about it.
If you go online and study macrobiotics, there's very little there, and the other thing is
if you try to study the yin and yang online, forget it.
There's nothing really.
Oh, yin is soft and yang is hard, oh my goodness, right?
One of the questions were how does the body go, the energy move up, how do you know which
way it moves?
Well, these are old principles, and they will be discussed.
But essentially, for men and women, it's the same, the vertical, left goes down and right
goes up, except for the top, right?
One is counterclockwise, one is clockwise, you know, the crown of the head.
So, in essence, I don't know how to steer people to eat things that will empower them
and recover and heal the body, because it's very location sensitive, it's very seasonal,
right?
But one thing to avoid is, of course, anything processed, anything with a label on it, and
then the next thing would be things like nightshades, you could look up what nightshades are, right?
Or things that grow very tall and fast, right?
So, in other words, getting a sweetener made from a grain is not going to be as extreme
as sugarcane, because if you look at how tall grain grows, and how tall does sugarcane grow,
one is more expansive.
The same thing with fruit, what's interesting about fruit is it comes from a tree that bears
energy from the earth that is moving upwards, but all of the energy in the fruit is pointing
downwards, right?
You ever notice?
Well, that's where it ends up going, yeah.
And eventually, when it's, yup, right?
It falls to the ground.
It'll fall, right.
Yeah, but, so there's a point of, that's why in some ancient cultures they had many dishes
where they would use unripe fruit, right?
When it was still in that middle stage, I don't know if you've ever had pickled limes or pickled
lemons, you'd pickle them in a jar, right?
Things like that.
Or fried green tomatoes, right?
So, there's an art and a science to all of it, and the science is what you learn, basically
knowledge on these matters.
But essentially, there's another aspect I also talked about of resetting the body.
Easiest thing to do is, when you reset, you're new, you go back new.
When you were new, what did you eat before you had teeth?
Baby food.
Believe it or not, most of the baby food is still pretty unadulterated, so if you want
to help someone reset or reset yourself, just eat baby food for a week.
And like I said, most of the baby food, last time I investigated it was four years ago
when I needed to nurture back a cat, I gave him chicken baby food, and I said, oh man,
why am I paying like $2 for half an ounce of this?
I could make chicken baby food myself, right?
But most of it's still unadulterated, so what do you mean baby food?
Yeah, applesauce, pureed chicken, pureed beef, pureed whatever.
Whatever they got for babies, they'll get the menu.
It's actually not that bad, believe it or not, baby food.
And warm drink, no cold drink.
Stay away from milk.
By the way, milk is for babies to grow, so if you're an adult, you don't need it.
Then there's, of course, there's the animal, right?
But there's an old saying that if you drink cow's milk, you'll become like a cow, right?
And that's why there's a lot of problems with it.
There's more problems with cow milk when it's processed, by the way, than whole milk.
That was one of the first things they did in the U.S. was make sure that they were going
to, well, they knew they were going to give people in the U.S. a hard time, and they knew
they were big on cattle, so let's make it even worse for them by putting in regulations
where they can't drink whole milk, right?
So they can't get any nutrition anyway if they're starving.
But the larger the animal, you know, the cow is not really compatible with the human.
I like what Dr. Lorraine Day says, you know, you go to a cow to get milk for your babies
or your children.
Do you ever have a cow knock on your door asking for human milk for its calf, right?
And a larger animal, something like a whale milk, by the way, yes, whales are mammals,
A lot of mammals make milk, you know, right?
You would die if you drank, because it's so extreme from that point, right?
Actually you would be probably, I'm just saying from an energetic point of view, I don't know
if this is, I'm just speculating, it would cause death, pretty much, if you try to live
on whale milk, right?
Because look at the conditions, extremely yeeing conditions and extremely yeeing body, and
then you have a yeeing liquid that carries all that energy, it would just tear your system
apart.
So if you're going to have any dairy, a small animal, coven hoof would be very compatible,
sheep's milk, goat's milk, by the way.
By the way, speaking of small animals, you know there's something called mouse milk,
but it's not really a milk, it's like a WD-40 in a syringe.
It's for really fine instrument, like it was developed around World War II to put into
like very fine gear mechanisms, right?
So anyway, I thought I'd just bring that up, let's take it as a joke, if you will.
No problem, didn't know it, but good.
Yeah, it's called mouse milk, but anyway, very fine oil.
It's a very, very high quality oil also.
Yeah, so I would suggest that, you know, this is one of the hardest things to suggest, I
would suggest, is what to eat or whatever, but I would always by default, if you can
cook the Lundberg brown rice and make kempira, do that.
Just make it, eat whatever you're eating and add it, just start adding it and see how
you feel, especially with the kuzu.
You can always make simple ingredients, but here's the thing, you should never suggest
someone prepare something as food if you know they cannot prepare it well, right?
So, I mean, I've gone through the years, through many people's homes that were not good at
cooking and they just ruined the meal, right?
Does it mean that the meal, let's say, Chuck, I say it was a sirloin steak with mashed potatoes,
right?
What's wrong with that?
It's delicious.
Sounds fine to me, yeah.
Yeah, but can it be ruined?
Yeah.
It could be ruined.
You know, they put the steak first and then the potatoes, right?
They started cooking the steak before the potatoes started cooking, right?
Guess what happens?
So, anyway, it goes on and on and on, I mean, so with the rice, you have to put it under
pressure and rinse it well.
Now, here's the thing someone once asked me, I'll get into some of the food, food sonics,
but can you roast the rice?
Yes, go ahead and rinse it, put it in a strainer, let it sit and go ahead and roast it.
It'll be wet, but the rice doesn't, the brown rice does not absorb the moisture, so it'll
just be on the husk.
So, as you're, well, in the husk, it'll be on the shell, I think it's called.
I think you have the husk on the outside, then the shell.
Anyway, the brown rice will not get soggy.
Go ahead and stir it in the pan to roast it, because when you roast the grain, it has a
nice flavor, right?
Mm-hmm.
Right?
Like roasted peanuts versus non-roasted peanuts, let's say, right?
This is a big difference, almost like a completely different thing.
Roasted chestnuts on an open fire, right?
So, kind of thing.
So, yeah, you can roast it once you've rinsed it.
So, I don't know what else to say about food, because here, the most difficult thing is,
if you're suggesting someone eat something and try something, you also must include how
to prepare it well.
It's just like, for the reason, writing a book.
It's like writing a book and putting it out there, you're presuming that people know how
to read, right?
So, telling people or suggesting that people eat a certain thing or try a certain thing,
you're presuming they know how to cook it well, and I don't mean well done, but cook
it so it's delicious, and that's not a good presumption, right?
But I think giving the step-by-step on how to, and things to look for to produce it well
to make a delicious meal should always preempt the actual introduction of the food.
So, yeah, it's a more complete way.
Yeah, and again, it goes back to the, you know, upgrade your food and your shelter and your
clothing, right?
Good food, good shelter, good clothing.
So, you know, these are all excellent pursuits, right?
Not to most.
The water, energy, silver is after food, clothing, shelter, and those are very broad, but you
notice I didn't, when it ends up with silver, I didn't say gold, you know, but, you know,
that's a perspective that I've introduced recently and that we'll work on that again.
Another thing I want to work on, which we started, I gave a lot of personal stuff on it, was
the emo work.
Right.
One of the things I want to put out with the emo is, I think it's self-evident from the
previous Sonics and even previous to that introducing the, let's say, how, the purpose of emotions,
why we have them, right?
Like, what's your pinky for, you know, kind of thing, you know?
Well, you can kind of make up things like that, but the emotions, I think, override
what a pinky is, especially if you, someone in the Yakuza, right, it wouldn't matter,
but, well, you know, they chop off their pinky, they cut their pinkies off to atone
for their mistakes, right?
But something like the emotions is never, ever, ever addressed.
It never is.
So kind of gone on that theme on how to guide yourself and guide actions and things around
you, it's actually one of the keys and carrier waves of, let's just use the word manipulate
or influence the world around you, physical, mental, and yes, physical, did I say physical?
Yes.
Yeah, world around you, and I mean literally.
So the thing is about the emotional state, we have these emotional states always, even
to the point of boredom, that's why, I don't know if you've ever heard me, when people
say they're bored, I always ask, could boredom be a form of anger or is boredom an emotion
on its own?
I would suggest it's more of a form of anger, right?
And if you actually get someone who's bored, they're pretty easy to tick off, by the way,
aren't they usually?
Oh, yeah.
You set them off one way or you could set them off in another way, because anger is
a release, it's a, that actually some might make people feel well, good for a short time,
but then it, of course, has its own constraints and can be negative to the individuals feeling
it.
So the emo aspect is be mindful of your emotions, and then also be mindful of what you want
to accomplish and find a corresponding emotion.
You know, we've always said the easiest one, the analogy was the hug, it's when someone,
there's a lot of that giving, people want you to give, right?
Give that person, right?
Send good energy, give, that's the hug, when you give a hug, the, right?
You have the emotion, that is the giving emotion, right?
Denial is the protection, you know, when someone accuses you for something and you deny it,
that is your protection emotion, right?
And all these other things.
There's the love emotion, which is doing the right thing, which covers everything, right?
You know, sometimes punching someone in the head is doing the right thing, right?
To stop them from doing something worse, you know?
So there is love in that too.
So the, on the emo part though, the technical aspects, one thing I'll throw in here is aside
from understanding that is something that should be understood, that is completely negated,
is that once you start getting into the emo, you'll notice that the way it works is not
the way other things work.
It works independent of time, it works independent of distance, right?
So and it also works independent of things that we consider to be the what they are.
An example would be someone says, hey, I have a friend and I want you to send them some
healing energy.
That's all you need to know, right?
Usually in many other quote unquote disciplines, you need to know who they are, a picture of
them, they go even further.
I need a, when you get into some of the other magical stuff, they want a hair sample or
some nail clippings, right?
Or something.
Yeah, this is very, very, this goes above that.
So let's say, let's go back to this.
You know, hey Greek, I have a friend that needs some healing energy, could you please
send it to them?
Okay.
How do you send, how do you identify that person?
All you have to do is ask to yourself, and this is by the way, again, because ask yourself,
you're going to have that inner dialogue, you know, you have to be very careful who's,
you know, where that voice is.
Yeah.
And this is done with no voice.
In thought, when you are asked, requested to send energy to someone, how do you create
the identifier?
All you have to do is ask this person that is to receive what I'm going to send, do they
have any unique properties?
And you can think of where his social security number, telephone number, if they had an eye
scan or a fingerprint, do they have anything, a gene, a code in their genes that's unique
to them?
Yes.
The answer is yes.
Everyone has something that's unique to them.
That's all you have to do, is focus in on the thought of what makes that person unique.
And that's all, the only identifier you need.
It's not like when you're ordering something from, and who will, shall I be sending this
to?
Will I please have their address or their name?
You don't need any of that.
Okay.
Right?
You see how it works?
And it actually works better that way.
Better if you don't have the specific, if you just have the...
If you don't have a photograph or a hair sample or their name or anything like that, yeah,
it works even better.
The reason why is because once you start to get specifics, it starts to tie you down into
this physical realm, and now it's no longer 100% emo work, it's 50% physical, 50% emo.
Okay.
You see?
So now it gets to the point where eventually, once you start working with emo, you'll notice
that the physical world ain't shit.
And there's a lot of shit in the physical world, by the way.
But in other words, you're detaching from that and you're going for identifiers that
are beyond what...
How many times have you heard one of the pitfalls of society is what they identify things as
being?
Right?
Yeah, that's always a problem, yeah.
All within the misgivings and the misinterpretations and the misinformation in the world.
Now I'm not saying that if you do have a photograph or a name or you've even met the person in
the past, it's a negative, but don't dwell on that at all.
Just asking the question, is there something unique about this, right?
So now this allows you to pretty much send energy or whatever you so desire in your transmission
or in your transmittal into a very, very specific place without even knowing anything
about it in the physical realm.
And one thing I would suggest, the less time, the less that time is considered.
In other words, if you send energy there, well, when will they get better?
Oh, maybe five minutes from now, maybe three months, or maybe they have even before you
asked, right?
Don't leave time out of it.
In other words, yes, there is time as a function, right?
In other words, a person might say, they got better in three days after you did that, right?
Or they got better in five minutes or three months or never.
That's a time constraint.
So leave the time constraints and all the physical constraints out of it, right?
And learn how to create these identification markers based on the information that you're
getting and the email that you're going to send out.
See, this gets very, it seems, woo-woo, airy-fairy.
Well, doesn't it help to just, like, say that something is as opposed to something is going
to happen, though?
Yeah.
What you do, and when you say something is going to happen, it's all reference points.
In other words, it's a waste of time, in most cases, to say, I want that person to get
better, even if you had the specifics.
Because the coordinates in the reality that we live in don't work that way.
They require specifics, but not physical specifics, conditional specifics.
What I mean by that is this.
If someone is not doing well, you would wish that they go back to the state that they were
before they were not doing well, is the simplest, most general one.
All you hear in culture and society is, I hope you do well, I hope you feel better.
That never works.
Very rarely does it work.
But once, if the stimulus or the impetus in the ethereal world is put out that they go
back to before they were, because that's a condition that already exists, it already has
been achieved, right?
So someone who's in their 70s who's suffering various illnesses, you would put out, make
that person like they were when they were 18.
The problem with that sometimes is, what if they had that condition when they were 18?
Then you should go back to when they were born.
What if they were born with it?
There's another problem.
The time of conception.
What if it was carried over from one of the mother's side or father's?
Then you have to go back to the genetic line before that thing emerged, you see?
So all those have to be taken into consideration.
So you do need specifics on that to know what to avoid for when you want them to go back to.
Well, yeah, that's just part of the menu.
One thing that, I'll tell you what I do with that, is I go back to the whole genetic line.
All of the ability, all of the reworking, the ethereal reworking that they came from,
you know, because as more babies are being born over hundreds and thousands of years,
because we are degrading, we are not getting, right, our, in other words, genetic code,
hereditary code, and our bodies are not as fit and as strong as they were, let's say,
a thousand years ago or 5,000 years ago.
We're constantly degenerating.
And this is even shown, let's say, in the quackademic because of the cosmic rays damaging
the chromosomes and the DNA consist constantly, right, because we're not shielded.
We're barely shielded, let's say, right?
Where in former days, we had more shielding and the codes were much more robust, right?
It's kind of like carrying someone's business card in your wallet for five years.
What do you think it's going to look like, right?
Generally, it's going to get mangled.
It's going to look like crap, yeah.
So from that perspective, what I typically do is go back to the line,
the entire, I do it on a genetic ethereal level, like in other words,
I'm going back to what a perfect human, whatever perfect human they came from, right?
Yeah, it is typically and then move forward.
Typically, it's very rare that I don't get any information.
So then I include some of that any information when I get it and very carefully.
What I mean by that is within that information that I'm getting is how long have they been
this way and were they a happy person?
I always ask first and were they a healthy person?
So you got to get an idea of what was in the past in order.
No, you don't have to.
But usually it comes up in conversation than I do anyway.
It's supplied before I even consider doing an email.
It's supplied like, hey, Chuck, I know this guy.
I've known him since I was 12 and he was pretty happy all the time.
And recently, you know, he's in his late 50s and he's got this and that, right?
Right.
I got a lot, you know, already, you know, I don't come back.
Were they healthy when they were young?
They actually supply enough information, I presume that.
Right.
But you go back to where the human, the perfect human.
This is almost like you read about the resurrection.
When you're brought back, you're in a perfect body.
Perfect human body, physical body, that type of body.
It's actually transmitted by light.
You know, when they look at matter, you know, they don't find matter.
If they look at it fine enough, they just find energy, right?
Right.
And usually they know it's energy because it's somehow photoluminescing, right?
Yeah, well, that's how you end up with those.
Every couple of years, there's a new eureka, right?
That says that everything is energy.
And then a couple of years later, they come back out and say the same thing again,
as if they just rediscovered it.
But it just keeps happening.
Well, it's a distraction.
It's to make sure that you never really, it's to keep you going around.
It's an amusement park.
Well, what's the purpose of going to amusement park?
It's the only place that has a purpose to have no purpose.
Right.
That's what's going on.
Because it changes, right?
You're on the teacups, you're on the merry-go-round, the power slide, you know, what?
There's no purpose.
What's the purpose here?
What do you mean there's no purpose here?
Look at all these various things you could do.
Look at all the various professions and things you could study here.
I'm telling you, all these things are purposes with no purpose.
How do I know?
It's kind of like the same thing I hear about, oh, the Greek philosophy.
Oh, look, OK.
If all that stuff was so good, how well has it served you?
How well has it served society?
Where are you?
Where is society?
Right?
So I kind of like, I recently heard an Eric Dollard.
And he says, Eric, he says, the society is going down the toilet bowl.
And it's at that point, you know, that sound that a healthy toilet, that burping sound
that a healthy toilet bowl makes.
He's always, if you asked him that 40 years ago, he'd say the same thing.
But I like that analogy.
I just say it's just someone needs to go into the room and pull the chrome handle on the porcelain
bowl, you know?
Now, fair enough.
I guess the purpose of being at the amusement park is just being there, is it?
Yeah.
Yeah, exactly.
What's the purpose?
Well, there was a lot of purpose to build it.
And there's a lot of purpose in it.
But when you're all said and done and you're tired, time to go home.
What do you say?
Did you have fun?
That's it.
So when you come to Earth, did you have fun?
Right?
I don't know how everybody's going to answer that one.
Well, that's what's going on here.
Did you have fun?
Did you?
Because, you know, you're going to be made fun of for being here in the first place,
cosmically, right?
I mean, well, you're going to have the sympathetic side.
You're going to have the side that's going to mock you.
You're going to have the side that's going to be judgmental, right?
Yeah, of course.
Yeah, it's pretty obvious.
Like, how do you know that Greek?
It's like, oh my gosh, boy, have you never done any homework?
Sometimes people, when I talk about law, these things,
it was, where'd you get that from?
I'm like, oh my gosh, you know what you just said?
Like, yeah, I just asked you where you got that from.
I said, no, let me translate that in English.
What you just said by asking that question means you've never done any homework.
Right?
What happens if you stand up in front of class and never done any homework?
It's going to show, right?
Generally, that's what happens.
Right, yeah.
Yeah.