Sonic Event 21, Ocelli and the Greek Rated Y.
Anyway, I keep announcing that as if, you know, there's some explosive thing happening
and we're not broadcasting, but if you're hearing us, then you've subscribed and welcome.
Anyhow, Greek, how are you doing tonight?
Pretty good.
We had a pretty interesting moon yesterday, the day before yesterday, so I'm reckoning
roughly two and a half days into the third month.
Yeah, it was a big temperature change.
I always make a note that whatever's happening, I'm in the desert southwest, full moon comes,
we got a cooling period, right, and how much it's going to cool by the moon and all that,
and I've been watching that and it's pretty good.
It's interesting, as the lunar influence gets stronger, building up, you know, during
the summer months, the cooling is greater, which is unusual, because like I just said,
it's during the summer months, right?
So what I mean, it doesn't mean we can have snow, it just means that the temperature
drop is greater than it is in the winter.
Fair enough, and it's about ten hours after my day started, really, about ten hours after
the solar noon time where I'm sitting, but anyway, that's the way that is.
I noticed in the chat, though, somebody said something about exactly what time a year something
starts, and what would that be?
It was the year, that's what they mentioned in the chat, because yeah, since the year
starts.
Yeah, that's someone maybe who can get help from other people without going over it.
The year starts when something starts in the beginning, but you don't count it until all
the eggs are in the basket, which would be the seventh month, right?
So you go to the store to buy a dozen eggs, and you got to bring your own container, so
you go to where all the eggs are stacked, and you go one egg, two eggs, three eggs, and
by the time you get, let's say, to the seventh egg, let's say you get seven eggs, right?
That's when you finish your count, you see what I mean?
But you started with the first one, so the year still starts with the first day of the
first month, but the count of the year is not done until all your eggs are hatched,
right?
Okay.
So it makes sense.
It's very different from the pagan papacy, which is they drop the ball or whatever, and
the year changes, and it's a new year, all at the same time, and everybody make a New
Year's resolution, it's in the darkest time of the year, they don't realize what they're
doing, right?
Of course.
Speaking of which, before we get into the usual thing and looking at things and having
our conversation, have I, from memory, maybe you tell me, or it's just you and I right
now, but did I get into blotting out corporate logos on packages at home on the Rated Y?
I know we did it on the Freeman interview, I don't think we've done that here, have we?
You know, I don't think we have, you might have mentioned it, but I don't think we went
into it.
It was really interesting on Freeman, though, because you had even suggested people could
go get a marker, and we wound up talking about album covers and all kinds of stuff.
Yeah.
So it doesn't matter how you do it, but okay, just a quick one, because I think interjecting
practical stuff, that's what it's all about, and here's the other thing, people that really
like Greek speakers, here, they like it when I'm rough and edgy, because you go on the
internet, everybody wants to be your friend, and from the old Greek philosopher, as a friend
to all is a friend to none, right?
So, you know, I'm talking about all these fakers, you know, I love all you guys and
this and that.
Well, how do you, you don't even know them.
I mean, you don't even love the people you know, how are you going to say you love the
people you don't?
Anyway, anyway, okay, don't go down that line.
I got you.
I often say that I appreciate people that tune in and stuff like that, because I do,
I appreciate that they're there.
Yeah, and that's right, hold on, that's another thing, tuning in, there's no tuning here.
Well, yeah.
You're clicking, yeah, I know, but it's an old language thing, like glove compartment
in the car, we don't put gloves in there anymore, right?
Well, and frankly, even though you're casting, right, you're broadcasting, you're not exactly
broadcasting.
Yeah, it's just digital.
Yeah, because tuning, I don't know if you, well, if you ever did, built your own radio,
but the crystal tension and all that, it literally is a tuning, well, an instrument,
you know, when you leave the guitar in the trunk of the car and it's on a rainy day,
you take it out, try to play it, what does it sound like?
Yeah, right, things go out of tune depending on the conditions, yeah, but no, I played
bass a little bit.
It's a fine, there's nothing fine, see, tuning requires a fine adjustment, there's no fine
adjustment on the internet, it's either there or you got it, it's just like back in the
day, getting those digital cables, HDMI cables and this and that, you go to a big box store
and they got one for $5 and they got the monster cable, one for $75, this is better, and I
say, well, come over here, come over here, I tell the salesman, come here, come here,
what is it?
I said, listen, this is digital, it's zeros and ones, the $5 cable and the $80 cable will
do the same thing for resolving that, you know, and he's like, yeah, yeah, I guess you're
right, you know, so the only difference is durability and capacitance, you know, but
so, yeah, there's no tuning, all these things are interesting, it's kind of like being edgy
and rough about it is the only way that it gets across to people, now here's the thing,
most people, if you're part of the collective Greek speak, you'll freak out, you'll think
the guy's angry, he's an asshole, what's wrong, you know, no, he thinks he's better and all
that stuff, the collective is, anyway, we know the collective is finished, in other
words, when the catastrophes come, that's who it goes after predominantly, the tears,
you know, whatever, the chaff, okay, so then you have, let's go to the other end, there's
only about half a dozen, maybe a dozen or two dozen people max, I think, out there that
have really gotten what I'm trying to say and then the percentage of everyone else,
that is, not to disparage subscribers, you know, it was the subs and all these other
people that like Greek speak, it's somewhere between entertainment, information and whatever,
but I don't think a lot of people really get it, you know, there's, what I mean by get
it, okay, it's a smattering of finesse, it's a smattering of skill, if you're not improving
your skill, you know, people who do yoga or martial arts know this, right, you know, people
go to the gym, know this, right, they're getting better as they do it, play the piano, whatever,
if you're not doing things to, where you either gain new skills, increase your finesse, your
ability to perform physically and mentally, you don't really get what I'm saying, because
that's what it's all about, there's something that the, I forgot the name of the award,
there's a managerial award in Japan, the Deming Award, Deming was a statistician and in the
army and he basically told, back in mid 20th century, he was one of the good guys, let's
say, he was saying there's no quality control, you can't control quality, you're either improving
it or you're letting it degrade, there's no, you can't keep it stable, there's no way you
can keep something consistent, you're either constantly improving it or you're letting
it degrade, so if you think you're doing quality control by keeping it at a certain rate, you
know what's happening really, it's degrading, so Americans kicked him out, they didn't like
him, so he went to Japan with this concept, they loved him and the highest award, I think,
was up until the 80s, was the Deming Award and that was about constant quality improvement,
constantly, how to make things better is really the point.
Okay, the other thing is about Greek speaking, what's rough is you came into this world alone,
you're going to leave alone, well, you know, whatever, unless you all do, you all decide to
jump off the bridge at the same time without a bungee cord, you know what I mean, you're going
to leave alone, even then, you're going to sense the leaving and coming in the same alone and you're
going to be alone for your whole life, period, you think you have a good relationship, whatever
more power to you, but I'm telling you, you're still alone, that's why I got into speaking
about the inner voice and learn how to read the quiet and one thing I mentioned in the
chat there was the inner voice that we're used to, that we think is us, is like reading
signage, reading a book, you know, reading letters, but the silent voice, reading that
is like reading braille, you're removing that sense, so listen to the silence, it's based
on feeling, I know I've talked a lot about the emo, but emotion and feeling are different,
right, the emotion is labeled and discounted where the feeling is what we really should
be driving us and that comes through, by the way, you know how they say it's not what you
say, it's how you say it, right, so that's the emo coming through, so yeah, I noticed
that there's a, it's not like Dr. Phil tough love, but there's a certain rough element
that I like to portray, it's not quite being angry, it's not quite being irritated, it's
not quite asshole-ish, but a mixture of those things, you know, a little bit of that, a
little bit of this, just to get people kind of like, you know, snap out of it, was it
Cher and the moon, was it moon, whatever struck, she says, snap out of it, she smacks
some kind of, if I could just do that for an hour straight with people, you know, I
want to get one of those big cartoon gloves, you know, like the Mickey Mouse that has
four fingers on a stick and just drive down the highway, have everybody stand on the side
of the road and just smack them all, just wake up, you know, but there's nothing, I
mean, you're already awake, right, so the whole thing here is you're really doing solo,
you know, you're all doing a solo, everyone is doing a solo with a particular arrangement,
whether it's familial or spousal or acquaintance, you're all here solo, so it's really what
do you do, why do you empower the solo and all that, so with that said, I want to get
back to the rough aspect of it, I don't think we've ever really got into it, maybe some
people have gotten the notion about blotting out corporate logos, okay, I was having a
conversation recently, go ahead, let me hit you with this, because here's the thing,
you know, we talked about it and I always like to go straight for the why, because everybody
talks about, or not everybody, I'm exaggerating, there are a certain segment of individuals
out there that like to talk about the symbolism in different things, it means this, it's the
eye of Horus, it's actually this, it's actually that, yeah, those people, those are the ones
that think everyone, that want everyone to be their friend too, yeah, it doesn't work
that way, get Horus out of it, I tell them, what did he do to mess, even the Satanists,
it's like, why are you bitching about the guy being a Satanist, what did Satan ever do
to mess you up, right, and what is this guy messing you up for, right, because, you know,
when I say, wait a second, Greek, isn't Satan the adversary, yeah, he is, but you've got
to realize what he uses, so, and it's not he, it's a collective, right, so.
But the thing about it is this, they talk about the symbols, they go in all these different
directions and by the time you're done, your head is spinning, whatever, but here's the
thing, I think you should be able to universally agree that you don't want any part of these
things, you don't want any part of the empowerment, the messages being sent, whatever it might
be, that is being transferred via the symbolism, okay, so we can boil it down to that, you
don't want this, okay, so if you don't want it, how do you get rid of it, alright, to
extract yourself completely, look, there are certain people that could probably live off
grid and never see a corporate logo attached to anything because everything they get is
from the forest, from the earth, from the animals they raise, et cetera, okay, but outside
of that, the majority of us, okay, are going to go ahead and purchase stuff from what we
call a store, we're going to go get things, it's going to be in packaging, it's going
to have these symbols, so let's get into the why, why do this even, to block this out,
yeah.
Alright, if you ever build a house and you've got a liberal budget, hopefully you do, one
of the things I used to do was be a liaison for the client to the contractor and architect
that because people, when they want to build a house, they go hire an architect that designs
it, then it's either one of the architect's buddies or their own quote-unquote general
contractor that builds it and most clients are not aware that the architects and contractors
are full of ego, they're so full of ego that part of like prosecutors, you know, like they've
won 99% of the cases, right, it doesn't matter if the people, right, so what the architects
and the builders say, oh, I built the most expensive house, right, so a $400,000 house
that cost you ends up costing you 1.2 million because he wants to say he builds 1.2 million
houses, he's kind of stupid if you ask me, right, so what I used to do is represent the
client and the architects hated me and the contractors hated me for that because I'd
say, wait a second, what the hell is a shelving unit, $75,000 shelving unit, oh, yeah, yeah,
I've never done that, you know, it was like, no, no, no, no, no, first of all, you don't
want a built-in because what if you want to rearrange the room, what if you want to put
the couch there, that's built-in, make it, you know, oh, oh, so the shelving unit price
goes down to less than 12,000, architect's like, I hate this guy, I hate him, right,
but the client loves me, so another quick story is they build these bathrooms, you
know, like you walk in, shower, beautiful, all this stuff and I said, okay, you got a
beautiful bathroom and when you move in, your wife's going to go to Bed Bath & Beyond
and buy one of those cheesy racks that you hang on the shower so she could put all her
shampoo bottles because you only have one shower niche, right, so right now, before
you put the marble up, why don't we use the space in between the studs and build these
little niches, you know, pockets, you know, shelves, they have marble and put pool lights
in them too on a dimmer, right, and the client's like, oh, this is great, so anyway, I shaved
the price of the, the building would come out better and the price would go down, way
down the cost of building and all that, but the contractor and the architects hated me,
so I couldn't work in those fields, I could only work by representing clients, you see
what I mean, so what does that mean? When you understand instead of building it and
just having it done with anything, how is it going to go, how are you going to interact
with it over time is what it's about and what I mean by this is this, again, going
back to the building aspect, you know, they have fiberglass insulation, they put it in
attics and walls to keep the house, you know, insulated, right, so when I see a house going
up, especially in the bedroom area, I want insulation in the walls and they're like,
great, we don't need insulation in the walls, yes, you do for sound, right, so if you want
to sleep and someone's playing a radio in the next room, you don't want it to coming,
through, as a matter of fact, you don't even want the drywall applied directly to the stud,
you want to put a shim that absorbs vibration more in the bedrooms than in the living room,
dining room, like in other words, in the chances that someone is making noise in the living room
and bothering someone in a dining room is very slim, but if you got two bedrooms next to each
other, at least try to make it a common closet wall, so you got that two feet of airspace,
but if you don't, you want to heavily insulate and isolate those walls and you'll thank me
later, but like in 30 years, you'll thank me for having such a quiet home, but you'll
never thank me because you thought it was supposed to be like this anyway, you see what
I mean, it's kind of thankless, because you didn't suffer the noise, you know, and it's
too late, you could still do it after the house is built, you see, it's kind of like
one of these subtle things that doesn't make, that's in your face while things are happening,
so okay, so what do I mean by this, I was having a conversation today about food supply, Cisco
and American Foods and one other supply all the foods for all the restaurants in the country,
pretty much, unless, you know, there's some restaurants that source out their own stuff,
of course, but the majority, now here's the thing, the people that own those companies
or CEOs are Satanists, all of them, not some of them, all of them, and this is something
that was established 100 years ago, all of these large companies that supply your food,
and the things that you rely on, your car dealers, by the way, new car dealer,
also they're a part of the brotherhood, whatever, yeah, they have, you know, the 85,000 missing
infants, and not children, but the ones that go missing from hospitals, I'm talking about now,
the newborns, they tell the mom, the baby died, it never did, and look, I see the baby,
why do you want to see the baby, she just chalks it off, right, these are all your business people,
right, and what they do is they're very much attached into the other realm where
they offer human sacrifice, you can get more and more and more and more into this,
you're politicians also, you don't need to look at Pizzagate or whatever, all that crap they're
putting on the past 10 years, this is, you just go back to the beginning of mankind,
you know, a civilization that we're in today, it's been so also, what they understand is
energy transfer and control of their subjects, so you're eating their food, which you mitigate,
by the way, what I mean by mitigate is this, let's say you go get some spring water,
and it's the, I don't know if you've ever, people have ever had really good spring water,
when you drink it, it's almost like a drug, when you drink it, well, then immediately you get this
incredible refreshment, and then like a lightheadedness, and then you feel really
invigorated and almost effervescent from it for about 20 minutes, okay, and you could put this in
a bottle, keep it in the dark, keep it cool, and it'll give you that for a few days, maybe even a
week or two, but if you take that same spring water and put it in a pot and bring it to a boil
and cool it down, it doesn't do that anymore, it doesn't have that feeling anymore, because you've
changed it with the energy transfer, so, all right, you can, you research sigils and all this stuff,
it's all over the internet, what they do, there's plenty of hoop to do on this corporate,
occult corporate logos, right, there's plenty, even Jordan Maxwell did a book on it, and David Icke
and all these guys, right, sure, yeah, it's been around for a while, so everyone's familiar with
it, these things are very carefully engineered and designed to transmit, literally transmit
from a radionic perspective to the living beings and the space a certain energy,
right, now let me give you an example, there's something I used to do, there's two things that
you could do with sound, and this is much finer than sound, one is Sonic Bloom, there was a company
that grows roses in greenhouses, if you bought a rose, it probably came from Holland, they grow
almost 90% of the world's flowers, they had problems with some of the plants blooming or not,
so some guys said that, you know, birds play birdsong, record birdsong from dawn till about
10 a.m. and play it in the greenhouses, what do you know, they put speakers everywhere,
birdsong was played for three, four hours, all the plants started blooming in unison,
wonderful, right, another thing is you do like what's called like silent space recording,
you go to a place that is a wonderful place like a spring or a mountain, a power spot on the earth,
and you set up a microphone, it could be completely damped and quiet where you don't
hear any wind or it doesn't sound like anything and you made a CD recording of this for an hour,
you give the CD to someone and you say play this CD, whatever volume, it doesn't matter,
for an hour and you see, tell me how the place feels, this is great, I put it on, there's no
sound coming out of it, right, but everyone else, you know, but other people say, yeah,
there's no sound coming out, but I could really feel it, you know, and I didn't tell them how
they should feel or anything, right, so these are two more like things regarding to sound,
right, now if you get finer than sound is light, right, the color of things, right,
and then finer than that is geometry, shape, proportion, and then finer than that is the
intent behind those geometries and proportions and back to what we're talking about, corporate
logo, it's the intent behind it, an incantation, like you can empower something, an object,
through an incantation or a ritual and that will transmit that, right, it'll hold that energy,
all of your logos are like that, little corporate logos, even if it's just a word, the font,
like craft or whatever, right, it's still enchanted, okay, it's a form of enchantment,
all right, so what you do is you blot that out, basically two ways, several ways to do it,
piece of masking tape, real cheap, right, electrical tape, real cheap, one of those
fat magic markers, the tapes will work better than the marker because if the marker dries,
it's not going to completely cover the logo, you can still see it, right, and if it's a piece
of glass or something, it might wipe off, right, so people used to, when I first settled in here
in Tucson, then I had met my wife, she comes over where I was staying and she goes, this is really
weird, why do you have marker over this and that, and I said, oh, don't worry, I just cover up all
logos, I know it sounds crazy, but you know, so this is how it's done, when you go, let's say
you just moved into a place and you do your first shop, you usually show up with shopping bags or
a bag or something you have all your goods in, right, what do you do, you bring in and you put
it on a table or somewhere and you start putting, unloading it into your cabinets, drawers,
wherever, you unload it, put it in its appropriate places, this goes in the refrigerator, this goes
in the cabinet, that's when you do it at that point, so as each thing comes out,
book, tape, craft this, shame on you if you're buying craft products, by the way,
but you know what I mean, right, it doesn't matter, baking soda, it doesn't matter, detergent,
whatever, some of these things are pretty big, you know, don't tell me you're buying Cap'n Crunch,
right, then it would be post, right, or whatever, you cover just the logo, you don't have to cover
okay, right, now the other thing is I had done this, it was a total NPC woman who was constantly
ill, she worked for like the government accounting office here, it was a federal office,
and our sister used to visit and do stuff for her and all that, and she, her sister was into,
the woman was not into holistic or this kind of, any, anything natural, she was loaded up with
pills, and her sister was into it, but they both listened, so one day I asked her, can I go
through your apartment, would you give me access to everything, if it was anything personal,
just put it away, but she was, no, no, I have nothing personal, you know, actually she did,
but you know, she was very open about it, she was very cool for, you know, very just
oblivious person that was always ill, anyway, so we went through with her sister and we covered
everything, and we didn't tell her why we want to do this or what we were going to do,
but the next day, the next day, the next day, how are you feeling, I feel great, I never felt better,
next day I feel even better, I feel even better, she goes, yeah, I noticed there's some,
what'd you guys do, I noticed, she wasn't even curious, she says, oh, I noticed you put a piece
of tape through the whatever, you know, thing here, okay, but what'd you guys do, I noticed
there's a mark, she says she noticed it, but she didn't make a point, is that what you guys came
here to do, right, so it was perfect example, and she got better and better, and then she kind of
leveled out where what she had was treatable and, you know, normal, you know, ailments until her
body recovered, so in other words, it affected this person's health, I've done it with other
people as well, okay, what this does is it's a fractal antenna, if you open up the cell phone,
you know how it's not like so sensitive, you could walk around, you know, as long as the energy's
getting to it, it's not like a ham radio, it's what's called a fractal antenna, these logos are
designed like fractal antennas, look up fractal, look up antenna, put the two terms together,
what they do is they emanate the intent behind that corporation, which is not only that corporation,
but they're part of an elite group, call them the brotherhood, brothers of this, this of that,
blah, blah, blah, blah, it doesn't matter, and they're not your friends, as a matter of fact,
they hate you, they hate your guts, and your children's guts, and they want you all dead,
yes, they do, but in the meantime, they're gonna make sure that you get your products
and are as miserable as possible within what they can offer through their products, I know,
it sounds crazy, right, but welcome to planet earth, if you don't know this right now,
this is going on on this earth, then you got a lot, you got a long way to go, it's very simple,
so it doesn't mean that these products are lethal, it just means that's the intent behind it,
so and if you don't believe that, look at what happened in 2020, right, so anyway,
by the way, when it comes out that what happened with that pandemic was a total scam,
what are the people going to do, yeah, right, not much, it's not going to be like the end of the
frankenstein movie, where they all show up with pitchforks and torches at frankenstein's castle,
right now, it's not going to be like that, it should be, okay, so these little, all these logos
and things are these fractal antennas and they're constantly emanating at a very slow drip, drip,
drip rate, now, I don't know if you've ever had a leaky faucet or a leak where it was a drip
and then a drip and then a drip, all right, put a five-gallon bucket on there and come back the
next day, how much water did you collect, a lot of water, sometimes, right, sometimes you're like,
well, that was a drip, but you got to dump the bucket, right, not a five-gallon bucket,
but a nice-sized pail, it's like, oh, shit, I got to dump that, look at that, it's almost full,
right, that's how it works, drip, drip, right, so get these things covered, the hard part is books,
these publishers, when you have books, like I'm in the office, you have a library wall
and they're all over the place, I have not defaced those or covered them, but the blue tape is very
good, there is a blue painter's tape that has an adhesive that does not leave a residue and it's
good for 10 years, 15 years, even more, I've tried it, the blue tape, don't be a cheap ass and get
the white masking tape, the cheap one, you can on a throwaway product, yeah, get that one, but
something like a book or a CD or an album where you want to remove the tape and you don't leave a
bad residue, get the blue tape, there's also, they have it in yellow and green, it's painter's tape,
it's like five bucks a roll. Yeah, I have a roll of that, yeah, right over there. Yeah, it's great
stuff. Yeah, I use tapes for all kinds of, before tape, it was string, you know, if you watch an old
movie, everything was tied with string, right, and ribbon, now it's tape. All right, so this is the
thing I wanted to get across because it's a constant feed, here's the thing, yes, the 5G,
the cell tower is harmful, yes, it is harmful, but it's not as harmful, the reason why you don't
have people dropping from that is because it's not that strong, but when you combine that with
the company logos emanating, the intent, the frequencies of everyone with all the crap
they're thinking, you know, someone, not even your neighbor, let's say down the street turns
on Fox News or CNN, the garbage that's emanating from that TV, even though it's not near you,
is still enough, but it's faint, right, it's like if someone makes a barbecue three houses over,
you can still smell it, right? Well, I don't think people notice it anymore because you're bathing
in electromagnetic fields everywhere you go, pretty much, I mean, whether it's emanating from
an electronic device or it's coming from a Wi-Fi that you don't see or, you know, it doesn't matter,
it's constant everywhere, so, you know, but, yeah, go ahead. It's not the electromagnetic so bad as
how the electric magnetic is done at the pulse rate, and that's a very subtle thing. Okay,
we, you go to a room, you open the door, walk in the room, there's a light switch on the wall,
and you go on, off, on, off, on, off, right? Now, I go into the same room, and I go off, on, off, on,
off, on. What's the difference? It sounds like the same thing. It sounds like I'm just playing
around with words. No, it's very different, right? If I go off, on, off, on, off, on, and you go on,
off, on, off, on, off, it's a different frequency. You see, like, you see, when I'm turning off and
then turning on, you're turning on and turning off. Okay. The way they, it's where the two pass each
other, at what point do they pass is whether it's harmful or not. It's pulse width modulation
is the key. Okay. It doesn't even have to be electromagnetic. Here's the thing, it's when
all of these things start building up, and you're not aware of it, then they could be fine-tuned
to be harmful, but they never, but they, you see, in war, wounded cost the army more
than the dead, right? You understand that principle? Of course. So, also, the wounded in this case,
they, see, when, here's the thing, if you die, the government has plenty of insurance policies,
and they cancel, and they cash you out, but they think they can get more out of you if you're alive
and sick. It's kind of sick, but, right? The same thing with all loans, by the way, they're all
insured. So, when they repossess a house, a boat, or a car because you didn't pay it, they already
got paid with the insurance that they have on it. So, it's all about keeping you miserable,
keeping, you know, the penalty, motivated by penalty, having people do stuff because if they
don't do it, they get punished, not because if they, right? Not because they should do things
because it's the right thing. This is the type of society, the way it's set up. Okay, so, back to
the labels, what it does, it just compounds, but here's the thing, if you acknowledge that there's
5G and it's harmful and say, that is not for me, I understand, I comprehend why they're doing it,
right? It's not for me, it's for them, whoever the them is, you know, you just wipe the whole
intent out. Like, people get upset about chemtrails, I'm like, it's all right, it's not for me,
right? Did they say we're going to set up the 5G and give a list of people who it's for to hurt?
No, it's for those that don't know that it's happening and then are susceptible to it and
then chase treatments the other way, right? Like, somebody might be sensitive to 5G and they get
sore throat or red or skin rashes from it. So, what do they do? They get skin rash medicine and
throat medicine, right? Does it get any better? No, because it's, you see, so those are the people
that it's for. So, all these things, it's like transmuting it because it's not going to hurt
you unless your body induces it. Now, if it's turned up enough or whatever, then you can't
physically avoid it, just like, you know, crossing the street and getting hit by a car kind of thing.
It could be that strong for some and not for others. So, here's the thing. What you're doing
here is, I used to say, you come into this world, it's a shithole and ethically and morally for sure,
but you want to like, you know, and the people that are doing this are, we don't know who they
are and they're way out of reach, but if you had a chance once in your lifetime to kick them in
the shins at least once, wouldn't you do it, right? Hell yeah. All right, so this is how you do it.
Cover up their logos. You see, what's one way, right? Because it's always about choice, you see.
If you look at what they call the founding fathers of the U.S., they gave some pretty stark
messages. It's a republic if you can keep it. Or another quote was, yeah, we were doing this,
their constitution and the Bill of Rights, but they're going to forget about it and they're
going to get tyranny because that's what the people want, right? I don't know if you've read
quotes like that, you know, in fact, all those papers and all that. Okay, they're very, they had
the people in very negative light, as do I. You know, I got an email recently from someone I
consider very friendly and he says, I don't like it when you call people morons, so I'm putting
it out to everyone. If you got a better term for it, moron or idiot, I'll use it, but you know,
hey, because, you know, obviously there are people we love that are morons and if I tell,
like I said, look, if I tell people, everybody you know is a moron and you just sat there and agree,
who might argue, right? So I know that. So anyway, all this stuff that's going on,
there's nothing going on unless you don't know about it or you know about it and see it a certain
way. And you'll notice that all of it is based on intent, right? So just like when people get upset
about the media and all this stuff, they're past, or what they call science or doctors,
they're past the point of reason. How do we know? How many times have people confronted or try to
confront media scientists, academics with logic and reason and they're from their own stuff and
they don't want to listen, right? Well, at this point, they're past that. Now they just make fun
of them. Like they're a bunch of retards that they are, right? Just make fun of them. Well,
what do you do with someone who is completely insane? And how do you define insane? Well,
somebody who's denying reality, no matter how much you try and show it to them,
what are you going to do with that? You're done arguing. You don't handle them that way anymore.
So just contain them if you can. And if you can't contain them, make them an object of entertainment,
at least. Because that's all you can do. All right. So I hope this message about the message
that the corporations try to put out is effective for those who try it. Because it is, it does work
on a very subtle level. And none of this stuff is based on time and distance. So ultimately,
what I mean is, if your neighbor has it, and you've blotted out all your logos,
it could still affect you, right? But not as much as being in your space, right?
Well, let's just be a little more specific about the logos, though, just to make sure,
because look, there are corporate mascots. And there are things that are meant to represent,
you know, they're, again, I guess, mascots. They're meant to represent because there's intent behind
them. Yes. Right. But some things are there, like you mentioned, Captain Crunch. Okay,
well, there's a cartoon guy on the box. You don't have to cover the whole cartoon guy on the box.
No, just Post. Yeah, I think it's Post or General Mills, whatever it is.
Whichever cereal company it is. You'll find the main corporate, the parent company.
Right. Like Crest, hopefully you're not using that. But if you look at the back on the
bottom right, it's Palmolive or whatever, Gamble, cover that.
Right. So it's like your Procter & Gamble, your Kraft, as you mentioned before, the,
oh, Purina, the, oh, man, what is that other thing that's out there?
Well, here's the thing. You know, when you go to Starbucks, and they have a marker, and they mark
which one it is, latte, they'll put latte or whatever flavor, you know, on the side of the
cup, they'll put a marker. They have a marker at the barista. Yeah, and they also put the name
on there. Yeah, they always try to get it. Yeah. And so what I do is give me the marker,
I said, and I go across the whole Starbucks logo of the woman and all that, and through the name
and it there, thanks. And they look at me like, what did you just do? You get it? Anyway.
No, I'm sure nobody has the logo on the cup, right? Yeah, yeah.
Just give me the marker. And I go through the whole, I fill in the whole logo.
Ah, much better now. There you go. See? So, yeah. But don't, you don't have to obsess with it,
but just try it. It works really well. All these things work on a level that is beyond
what we're taught, you know? Well, I think-
So there, we got it out. I don't think, because I was doubting, you know, I thought because we,
I thought we got this on Rated Y. I think we might have, but at least it's a, it's a vital recap.
No, look, it's an excellent recap. And one thing to go, to go after it in another way, just really
fast, is the reverse engineering really, really quickly, is they often encourage things like,
you know, showing the logo, representing the logo, this kind of thing. That's why-
Yeah, because the intent, it's a weapon. It's weaponized. It's not a weapon. It's weaponized.
Weaponized, right.
If you say it's a weapon, I would know, come on, Greek, now it's pushing it too far. No,
it's weaponized. Yeah.
Yeah, yeah. No, but that's the thing. It's weaponized. But the thing is, this is the reason
why, you know, they put your, you know, your brand of soda or whatever, they put the corporate
logo on a t-shirt, too. You know what I mean? To continue it, to have it, you know, to encourage
you to constantly put it out there. And again, you know, but what is the why? Is it all the same?
I mean, does it all come down to the same thing, where it's just, you know what-
And it's just about-
It's all about intent.
Just about the intent to be miserable. Be miserable, be unwell.
No, to influence. To influence them as subjects, because it's branding. What do you do when you,
with your animals, you brand them with a hot iron or a tag, right? So, but by the way,
I've been saying this stuff since the 80s. In the 70s, by the way, the polo shirts with the
Izod Lacoste, the crocodile, and then the polo emblem sewn in.
Oh, yeah, yeah. And then later on, they put other little animals and stuff in.
Yeah, that was really popular. Well, that was, the Izod Lacoste was for golfers, and it took
off for the main shoot. And then the polo, and I would see people, this is back in the 80s,
they would approach me, you know, whatever, they're wearing a fine shirt, and I'm zeroing
in on the logo, and I'm squinting my eyes from a distance as they're walking towards me,
and they're getting self-conscious. And they say, I think you got some bird shit on your shirt.
What is that? And I point to it, and they're like, really, what? And I point, right, point
finger right on the logo, and they look at me like, oh, you know, what's, is that bird shit
on your shirt? What is that? You know, just to make people conscious, because sitting there and
going over all this 40 years ago is still just as, you know, nutty as it is now, let's say. So.
Anyway.
Continuing with the look at the chat, I found some interesting things in there,
and I know you did too. So there was a reference to one of the previous Sonics now,
where you mentioned the Heavenly Father. So that, that, that's super, super common people
use that phrase. But yeah, go ahead. Yeah, I put it actually, I didn't mention it was actually
something I typed in. There's a lot of stuff going on BS about this, this, that and Heavenly Father,
right? They don't know what that means. Just like, you know, God is within you. I think we went over
that. By the way, just do a quick recap. Oh, yeah, there was within you, besides you, inside you,
remember, Kingdom of Heaven is in you and all that. Someone also mentioned that they remember
looking this up, which I do. Also, decades ago, two decades ago, looking it up, and it said beside
you. Now it says inside you. So it's changing, right? Right. But here's the thing inside you,
meaning beside you, meaning amongst you, meaning in the village, there's no God in you,
because then that would be the only two ways someone else can be in you. One is through
physical penetration, surgery and sexual or assault, or possession. So when you say God in
Kingdom of Heaven is in you, you are possessed. Well, you still sound like yourself. Right? And
you're not being penetrated as you're walking down the street saying this. So you are in you.
And when you couple that with who you think your inner monologue is, that is an external
influence, but it's not in you. It's external influence. Now, here's the thing. If God was
already inside of you, why would you go through all the stuff that you're going through?
Well, I always found that strange when I saw, you know, I used to love to observe
these preachers, you know, and it was interesting, because sometimes they would use the phrase like
I'm possessed with the Holy Spirit. And sure, I don't say that. Well, okay, but it's not true.
It doesn't. You could say, Yeah, you want to know people saying things is not true. Turn on
politics. Look, I can tell you. I can tell you I'm from the planet. Where was Superman from again?
Xenon or Krypton? Krypton. That's right. I can tell you I'm from Krypton. It doesn't mean it's
true. I don't believe I am. I'm just saying, I could tell you that, though. And I could act
like that's something because I'm able to do something that Superman does somehow or way.
Yeah, either way, the thing is, either way, even if it's not true. If you remember, you just asked
me what planet is he from? You didn't want to make up a planet because it was already written
out. Right? Yeah, I didn't notice how you said which planet was he didn't want to make it because
you know, it's already been written out from the Superman genre. We need to go. If he neither one
of us knew what the planet name was, hold on a second. Let me what? Look it up. We'd probably
look it up and find where it's written. Yeah. So do we have license to change it and say he's from
Jupiter? No, we can say that, but we don't have any license, meaning permission to do that. So
when you start using things out of scripture, you don't have any license to change it. And that's
right. Ultimately, here's the thing. I've confronted a lot of higher ups in the religions,
rabbis and in the Christian, the Catholic bishops, Eastern Orthodox. And as you go high up,
the low guys, the ones that always look government, if you go to the DMV office
and the clerk or where any registrar office or attorney court, you're talking to the clerks,
they don't know shit. They don't know anything at all. No, eventually you get the I just work here
explanation. Yeah, because they don't know anything. So that your local pastors, priests,
you know, they don't know anything. Okay, when you are have a control mechanism, as it is on the
planet, those that are interred, the less the ones that interact with the populace, the masses,
the collective know the better. Because, you know, I don't know if you remember 9-11,
some of the politicians and other people in the in quote unquote, government, the acting government
were clued in on what happened. And they would be on an interview and by accident say, Oh,
the missile that hit the Pentagon. Right? Yeah, oops, or whatever. So it's best not to tell
put people that don't know anything. And also, there's no such thing as what they call a Freudian
slip. Alright, so this is what the people have. morons, you know, basically acting as there or
whatever. So yeah, so you there's no license to change it. But the interesting there's two
interesting points here. One is no one's really thinking about it when they say it's just one of
those feel good things. But if lies make you feel good, you still feel good, right? So it doesn't
matter. The other thing is, if any God is in you, that God has a voice. And if they're in you,
they're not meek enough and meager enough to sit there and be totally silent. If they're here to
experience something with you. So yeah, it's not going to happen, guys. It's not happening. And
again, the interesting point is how the scripture is actually changing, even in the interlinear,
it was noted by someone else. I don't want to make a big deal about it, because things are
changing. Look, have you ever noticed your own body changing? I have, of course, I've noticed
my sometimes like, like, I'll get up and tell the wife, I think I got a I got, you know,
time slammed, because I know I trimmed the nails, toenails, fingernails really close three,
two or three days ago, and now they're long, right? That's not possible. I mean, I'm not eating my
diet is excellent, but not that excellent. And I'm not on steroids. So in other words, how do
you get two weeks of fingernail and toenail growth in two days? Right? You see what I mean?
So anyway, I don't lean on this too heavily. I might in the future, if I can put it all together
in a more cohesive way. But again, there's no God inside of you, you are you. But the problem is
because you are you and you're you are who you are a human surface dwelling earth inhabitant
that has been throttled back, you know, governors have been put on you there, you know, they say you
use 10% of your brain. No, you're always using 100% of your brain in essence, but you you're
actually 10% of your abilities. In other words, the the the most masterful, masterful master
you've ever heard of even people walking through walls are only 20 or 30% of what they can still be
done. You see how we've been, let's say, dumbed up, dumbed down, throttled back governor, you know,
like Volkswagens in Europe go 150 miles an hour, but when they ship them here to the US,
they put a governor, they can't go over 110. It's on the computer. As soon as the speedometer goes
to 110, boom, it throttles, right? The same thing with semi trucks, right? 75 miles per hour,
usually or 80. They put a governor on there, so that we have that now that's being done by a
species that's outside of this realm, that physical realm that is within the physical
realm non physically. If you could follow what I just said, and they duplicate your voice
and inject it in you as a child, here's the thing. There's a point that some people remember,
I remember it and other people that I've discussed this with, within the right setting,
because you can't just bring this up, you have to prepare people. Sometimes it means just chilling
out, turning the lights down, everybody laid down on the couch and on the floor, and start slowly,
get them to recapitulate their memories, let's say, right? Okay, from a child, there's some point,
usually between the ages of five and eight years old, remember where you were, where you develop
the inner voice that you rely on is your inner voice right now. That's when it usually comes in
and gets into if you remember your youngest, youngest years, your voice was different.
Actually, here's the interesting point. You ready? If you remember your earliest, earliest thoughts,
they were actually more sober and reliable than they are now.
Right? I remember being about a year and a half standing up in the crib and I'm like,
why am I surrounded by stupid people? Right? I'm still asking that today. But anyway,
if you can go back to about what you call, let's say, within this,
let's say the social parameters that we are in kindergarten to third grade between there,
let's say, right? Because you're out in the world, you're forced to be out in public, right?
Right. You're in an unfamiliar, very rarely is anyone in kindergarten with their brothers and
sisters and mom and dad in the same room for four hours, right? So now you're thrust into a public
setting, semi-public setting between, let's say, kindergarten and third grade. See if you could
remember what inner voice you had back then. And I'm telling you, that is more you than the
influence that was put upon you later. You see? So if you could quiet that, here's another thing,
because we did talk about, and I'm going to go back to the heavenly father. This is not a tangent.
It is a tangent, but it's relevant because it's how we dictate and talk to ourselves.
You know how they say, be a good listener. Okay. When you're listening very acutely and intently,
that inner voice that you think is you, mutes out. So that's why people, car stereos are so
important, right? Because they like to put the music on it and that inner voice goes away, right?
Where you should actually be listening to everything that's going on. But anyway,
if you're going for a walk, if you're doing something or whatever, try to also listen.
If you're sitting down eating, try to listen. The more you try to listen, even to the finest sounds,
that inner voice, but while you're listening, don't try to describe or explain what you're
listening to. Just take it in. Like when you hear, well, let's say you're going for a walk
and it's really quiet. Initially, it'll seem really quiet, but if you start relaxing and say,
there's got to be some sounds out there other than my feet on the ground, you start honing in
and honing and tuning in your ear and you'll start hearing things off in the distance that you didn't
hear before you, let's say, made yourself go into the finer hearing. And when you're also seeing,
when you try to look at something very carefully, that inner voice mutes out also. That's another
way to mute it. So that cliche about be a good listener, there's more to it than you think.
It doesn't mean listen to whoever's talking because what the hell are you going to say
that makes sense anyway? You're on earth, right? Remember, well, they tell you before you come to
earth, listen, it's beautiful here, enjoy it, but don't talk to the humans because anything
you say is going to confuse them. They're idiots, right? That's why. Yeah. So I remember. Well,
anyway, that's another story. Well, I constantly have audio. I constantly have audio going when
I'm doing things because it does allow me to focus on what I'm doing better.
Okay. Yeah. As long as you don't start asking yourself things or in other words,
if it mutes that inner dialogue, I think the best way to do it is with silence.
If you're in a silent room, you can still hear things. You just ask yourself to reach your hearing
senses and your sight senses out and don't try to discern, like, but describe or explain what you
see or hear or think about it. You'll notice that voice mutes out and then you'll have a chance to
pick up on the silent part of yourself. Eventually, most people that exercise on this will
develop their own voice, who they really are. In other words, through the silence. What I mean by
that is like learning to read Braille instead of reading with your eyes, right? By feeling and
touch. Okay. So there is no God in you other than you. What's in you is you, your spirit.
But unfortunately, the voice that you think is you within your dialogue is not you. It's influenced
externally, kind of like the old cartoons where someone's faced with a decision in the cartoon
and there's an angel on one shoulder and a devil on the other. That's a perfect analogy of what's
going on. But instead of being an angel and a devil on one shoulder and a devil on the other,
two different, it's one thing that's influencing you. There might be people out there that are
not under such influence, by the way. But I'm just saying that I found that as the general
whole, most people are, including myself. So there's no God in you. Everything that's being
done and said about the gods would be completely futile if there was. The other thing is the
Heavenly Father. That's a thing that people are using and it's very inspirational. It sounds good.
Okay. When we look at the structure, let's say through scripture, it's a series of counsels
down from God beings down to human counsel, which are in temples and the authority.
It's all about counsel and it's all about knowledge on how to manipulate both realms, let's say.
When they say Heavenly Father, it's very similar to the way that the Catholics do it when they
call the priest Father because that's an authority figure. Also, there's a verse in scripture more
than one place, I'm going to paraphrase, and it says that a son does the will of his father.
So where you get your law, where you get your education, where you get your right and wrong,
where you go for counsel is your father. How many times have you heard that... I've seen this
many times where someone has a biological father, but another person raised him and mentored him,
and he considers him more of a father than the biological father who was never around.
You see? Also, the Catholics, you go to the father, he's the priest. You go to confession,
which is a form of blackmail, by the way, and all this other stuff, right? Because you go to him as
your leader for whatever it is, right? So where you get your law from, it also shows inheritance,
by the way, and authority. So where you go to get your guidance from is your father.
It's not a physical father. It's not a genealogical father. It's not a father as one
would consider in a family, because like I said, why do the Catholics... the priest is not... they
call him father. He's not your family. He's the priest. He's family. I mean, he's not family. He's
a priest. He's called the father because he's an authority. So the heavenly father is basically
referring to the heavenly authority as personified by one, let's say, not the council, right?
Because, you know, a lot of people, you know, they blame the president, for example,
but it's really Congress that calls the shots, right? If you have a beef with an aid government
agency, you know what they say? Well, you don't talk to us. Congress is the one who ratified us.
They don't say the president, never, right? But he's just an executive body. I told you what
presidents are for. The mobs wanted to do a shell company to pass off cordless tools back in the 90s.
They needed a CEO. Who's going to take the hit? Because, you know, they were going to take a hit.
I said, there's a bunch of homeless people out there that look good.
Buy him a suit. Give him a thousand bucks. He'll go downtown and sign up as the CEO.
Sure. You know what I mean? Yeah. Who knows? He might run the company.
Remember, there was one guy, he used to hang out there, a homeless guy, had a very nice angular
chin. He almost looked like Gregory Peck, if you remember the actor. He says, yeah, man,
I got involved with some stuff. I was an American Airlines pilot, and I had a house in Nevada near
Las Vegas with a kidney-shaped pool. He opens up his wallet, and he has all the photos.
This is my Jaguar. This is my garage. I was like, oh, man. This guy had some life experience.
Anyway, so you're looking at a series of authorities. It's not a familial term.
When people say father, they don't understand. Here's the funny part, right? You have these
Christians going on. Oh, I'm washed in the blood of the lamb. Jesus took all my sins.
I'm born again. My favorite is born again. Oh, my gosh. That's like saying moron right
on your forehead tattooed. I said, why go to that church and say you're born again? Just tattoo
moron and white on your forehead or whatever color skin you have. It's the same. You're being
made fun of. Anyway, they have no law. You know where they get their law from television and all
that? Then they say they have a heavenly father. What a mockery. What a mockery.
The reason you call the heavenly father is because you're doing his laws. By the way,
verses in scripture where the Christ says, when I return, will there be anyone that has the faith
or keeps the law? He's asking, will there be anyone left? I don't know. Here's the thing.
If he says on the 13th and the 14th days of the first month or on the 10th day of the seventh
month, it's not January. It's not September. With no sunset, sundown, with no sliver moon,
I'll tell you that for sure. Is there anyone left? I doubt it. Very few. Here's the thing.
When I make fun of all these things, it's on a double level. It's like when people say,
Greek, are we in a simulation? No. Right away. Of course, we're in a simulation.
But I say no. Why? Because if I said yes, all the junk that they've gotten in their head,
defining what a simulation, how it works, is going to be validated. You see what I mean?
Greek, is there any reincarnation? No. Right away. 0.3 seconds. No. No. Because if I say yes,
they're going to take all that junk that they've been heard about, reincarnation,
and they're going to say Greek validates all that garbage. You see what I mean?
All these things, I say no. No, it's not like that at all. Do you believe in the Christian? No,
I don't. No, I'm not Christian. Of course not. You see? Because you start agreeing to these
things. What you're doing is you're anchoring yourself, and it's all these attachments.
You're signing up for all the rest of the crap that comes along with it.
Yeah. And even though it's not, who has enough time to sit there and correct all that?
Right. Yeah, it is, but it's not like this and that. You're going to be there for eight hours
later. They're drooling, and I don't know. What do you say, man? You talked for a long time.
I don't know, man. I don't know. Something about, you know? Yeah, so I just don't bother.
That's why even recently I was out and said, you need to write a book. I get a crowd around
me publicly, and I'm like, yeah, I don't write books. Just go to this hotel or whatever.
Anyway, I want to do a plug for Greekspeak.com. That's Sam or the Archon. He spent a lot of time
writing articles about stuff that I've talked about, very professionally done. So if you guys
want to check out some stuff there, that's another place to get Greekspeak stuff. Speak with a double
E. People write a book. I say, well, look, if you write a book, you're presuming people have
reading comprehension, right? You're writing a book for moral and ethical reasons, not to get 50
cents or a dollar per copy. You're not going to make a living writing books. I know someone who
moved down South America as an American guy. Anyway, he's written books and sold over a million
and a half copies and he's barely over 15 years. That doesn't end up being like, I don't know,
you can't make a living on that. No. No. Over 10 years, a million and a half books,
he's not going to make a living from that, right? So what are they doing? What are they using the
books for? I mean, I don't know. I said, how many responses? Yeah, I get very few. I was like,
what the hell? What are they doing with the books? It doesn't make any sense. There's no
comprehension here. How about one book that gets a million and a half people excited
versus a million and a half books that get no one excited? I would rather do the other one, right?
One, get people excited with one thing, but no, I'll never write a book. Never write anything.
Why? There's no reason for it. The reason you wrote things is to memorialize. Now you memorialize
it on the internet. After the internet and all this stuff goes away, you won't care about the
stuff I'm saying. You're going to be more interested in how to stay alive. I've got a lot
of stuff on that as well, but there is no heavenly father as the way people are using it. It's a
heavenly authority. If you are doing what TV tells you, like the latest keto diet and blood pressure
and wearing a mask and all that, wherever you got that information from is your father.
That's why the Christ said that Satan had sex with Eve because Jesus told the Pharisees that
Satan's your father. Remember at the rocks, he says, we're sons of Abraham. He says, we could
turn these rocks, which were the stones that they put when they crossed the Jordan, Elohim could
turn these into sons of Abraham. Your father is Satan. Well, that means if their father is Satan,
a spiritual means that they're doing what you say, that's where they're getting their
law from. So it's where you get your law from. And most people that say, use the term
heavenly father have no law. They're lying because it's not a heavenly father. It's a CNN,
doctor, father, whatever, whatever, whoever came up, whatever bullshit, they have many fathers.
You see the collective and the Christians or whatever, whatever the Catholics bless their
heart. The Pope is their father, whatever the Pope says, you see, that's pretty clear by the way,
or their local father for the Eastern Orthodox and the Catholic people. Right. So then I've
said this many times, the way you become Christian is very simple. You get yourself a saw. It doesn't
have to be so sharp. Cut the top of your skull off, lean over real good. All your brains fall
out. Leave them off. Leave the brains on the floor. Put the top of your skull back on. Voila,
you're converted. You're Christian now. Now you're Christian. Congratulations. Yikes. Yikes.
A lot of times I get really harsh and I say, listen, has anybody ever told you any of this
before? No. I said, you know what? You're never going to hear it from anyone else anyway. So,
you know, they're like, yeah, thanks, man. All right. So where you get your law, think about
that by the way. Think about that. Think about that. Where you get what you do from is your
father. That's pretty freaking scary when you think about it for most people. For a lot of people
it is. For a spiritual level, from a spiritual point of view. And is there anything else other
than spirit? Right. Because we already know that the physical is, you know, manipulated to the
point where, and the spiritual is manipulated to the point where, you see, you can change things.
But the spirit, the physical can be destroyed. The spirit, not so easy. Because when you destroy the
physical part, it just jumps out and it's not animated anymore to be either animated or not
animated again, right, in another state. But it's easy to destroy the physical. The spirit will go,
when you die, it leaves and it goes into a disanimate space, but it's still there. It's
destroyed directly later, but it automatically leaves the body, you see, and the body gets trashed.
So either one is influenced very heavily. So where you get your law, your morality, you know,
when I say law, I'm not talking about traffic law also. Everything is part of law, because when you
go live amongst a certain people, just because you're a highly ordered individual doesn't mean
you need to create chaos, right? You shouldn't. The best place to create chaos is when you go out
into nature. I'm not talking about making fires and things, but you know what I mean?
I mean, if you've ever found a secret little body of water in a forest, you just want to take all
your clothes off and run in the water, right? Or a waterfall that you didn't know was there,
no one knows is there, but you want to just get naked and, you know, just get in there, you know?
So yeah, it's a form of chaos, but you know, the thing is not to create chaos.
So that's what I have to say about that's my story, and I'm sticking to it. It's very, very simple.
By the way, you know, this is probably another thing, but I can go through the most popular
biblical cliches and stories and give the interpretation for those things based on the
Bible, right? Because, you know, there's only one interpretation, but there are many versions,
right? You know, when you go to the UN and it's cohorts of different languages, who do you have
next to you? What's he called? An interpreter. Now, they have to be very specific, right?
Yes.
About what you're saying. Actually, there was years ago, one of the guys made a mistake,
and they brought him, went back, and they shot the guy. Do you remember that?
I remember reading it. It was an interpreter that either deliberately or indeliberately
misinterpreted things, and they killed the guy.
Yeah, I do remember something about that. I don't remember exactly which country it was,
but it was a long time ago, right?
Yes, I don't remember the details, but it's serious stuff.
But versions, you know, the versions are, you know, the funny papers, you know?
And the thing is, if you have something as comprehensive as what's known as the scripture,
it gives you enough definitions of what it's talking about that you can use it to define
itself, like the Mark of the Beast, right? And all that stuff. There was a lady who was
blaming the Illuminati. I forgot her name. She was into Orgo and all this. They killed her.
She's one of those people they found hanging. I was on a Skype. It was Revolution Radio a
long time ago, and she was talking about this is the Mark of the Beast, and it's gotten popular
about that. I don't know. I forgot who it was. It wasn't Tracy Twyman. It was someone before that.
And I said, oh, Mark of the Beast, that's in Numbers. It's in Deuteronomy. It's defined.
It's not a chip. It's not whatever. She's like, oh. It's like, ah. She's like, ah. She was like
going through some kind of like Wilhelm Reich orgasmic thing. And I'm like, here, here it is.
Using it from the Bible, this is what it is. It's defined right here, by the way. It's not a chip,
microchip, right? Again, it has to do with law. It's the way you function, is the Mark of the
Beast. It says, my law will be a mark on your hands and a mark on your forehead. So whoever's
law you follow has a mark on you, right? Anyway, make your mark, right? Yeah. So the Heavenly Father
is the heavenly authority. If you say you're Christian, you go ahead and do whatever you
want to do, and you do whatever, whatever, that's not from the Heavenly Father, I assure you for sure.
So, yeah. So is there a Heavenly Father? Yes, but it's not a father. It has to do with
the father being called and the authority where you get your guidance from. Not the familial term.
It's the, yeah. Not lip service, yeah. Right. Yeah. So, yeah. I just wanted to cover that because
we can cover any aspect of scripture and just show you what's in there about it in a practical
way, and it's not what you think, but it's so easy that, you know, what was that commercial,
oh, I could have had a V8, you know, right? And it's so simple, right? If you don't get ticked
off or triggered from it, right? And by the way, you're not going to make friends, right? Because
part of the friendship and the social stuff is to be like everyone else, right? Oh, yeah, right.
Everybody wants to fit in, you know. Do you feel we covered that satisfactory?
I think you can't cover it any better than that. Yeah, and if you go to the...