82 rated Y. I'm running out of cigarettes, but it is what it is. Hopefully you're doing
good, Greg. How are you? I'm okay. I've got a cigarette lit right now and I'm making some
coffee. Nice. It's around 8.15 Tucson PM on the wind-up toy. And yeah, we'll get into a
few things, a few things I've been mentioning lately. I just want to thank anyone who showed
up at the water seminar. It was fun. And to talk about it, like I said, year, years ago,
months ago, I was asked to not talk about it for a little while by a bunch of typical corporate
cutout morons. And we're probably listening to, and I just gave up on them. And it's good
to drop what I call dead weight in your life. Even if you keep dropping people through your
life relationships all your life, it's fine. If they're determined to be dead weight, right?
You know what I mean by dead weight? Oh yeah, absolutely. Dead, dead, dead weight is a very
relatable concept. I don't have many friends. Let's say, Oh my gosh. F R E N D Z with a
capital D is how I spell friends. F R E N D Z. Okay. Capital D Y. Yeah. Why? Oh my gosh.
First of all, it's planet earth. You have any human friends, you not too smart. First of all,
you know, you know, outside of this world, I tell people you've been here more than a,
excuse me, a week or so. You know, the humans, okay. You don't have to go. Okay. I'm not going
to go down that route. If you read the ancient Ritz, any of the holy books, humans are ahead in
a very, very negative light. The entire collective, except with some exception. You have a few good
ones here and there, but generally they are not a good group. You could say it all this way. Are
they bad? No, but are they good? Definitely not good at all. So yeah. So now what were you saying
about friends? You want to make friends with this type of unit? Oh my gosh. I feel a little
lonely sometimes. You sound like a Hallmark card. I've been telling that to people. It's like,
you want to talk to me like the rest of the collective, like a Hallmark. You know what I do
cards? You know, I'm going to do that to you. No, I look, I don't bother with them. I'm just
saying it's just, I don't know. It just feels like there should be some level of, you know,
even if it's a small, this is earth and get over it. But when I say it meets earth, it's more than
just what people want to call it, not what NASA calls it, whatever. It's a, it's a place where
everyone has congealed and conjoined and whatever. Right? That's what I want to get into.
Lately. I brought up the notion that society, just like anything, any universal movement,
you have the contractive formative, and then you have the expansive destructive,
right? But it works both ways. Now we are in the expansive destructive part of society. It's not
doomsday ship by the way. A lot of people say all this doomsday stuff. That's like the real simple
mind. The NPC it's, you know, and if you say, if it's not doomsday, what do you want to talk
about? Right? Your future, like you have a future, you freaking moron. Don't you know that go, go
back to the 1950s, 1930s or whatever. And when they show you how your future is going to be in
the year 2000 with flying cars and hotels on the moon, do you have any of that jerk off? No,
you don't. You never will. You know, the NPC that, you know, that's the, and then, oh, well,
you know, so it's not doomsday. It's the cycle. It's a universal cycle. It's, it's welcomed. And
actually, it doesn't matter if you welcome it or it happens anyway. It's a cycle. But you know,
how I brought up? Well, I was just like, stop. Not how I brought up how I keep bringing up the
concept of yin and yang still haven't figured out another terminology for yin being expansive and
yang being contractive, for example. But what I what I brought up recently is the front of the
body is the yang part in the back is the yin. And I was watching something short about meditation
and cheat. And they're like, well, the yin energy runs across the front of the body and the yang
energy runs up the back of the body. Of course. Why? Why would the yang energy go to the back
because that's the yin side, right? And why does the yang the yin energy go to the front of the
body? Because that's the yang side. Okay, so when it's all like the batteries, the way you set up
batteries in the flashlight, you just keep looking where the plus and minuses are, right? That
depends on the configuration. Sometimes they have them all in the same direction. And they do the
twisting and turning and cross polarity on the bracket or whatever. But what I'm trying to say
here is society unraveling. Imagine a spiral expanding and dissipating on the edges. We're on
the edges, like the arm, the outer arm, right? Okay, so because of the general tendency,
the universal general tendency of this expansion, it's classified as yin. But to counterbalance
that by necessity, by the Greek word for necessity is anangi. And it doesn't really
translate very well to necessity directly. It means actually does translate pretty well.
But when you use the term necessity, it means like you have no way out. It's exactly how it
is. There's a lot of terms in Greek that are not open or poor persuasive or presumptive,
like in English, when you say a necessity means there's nothing anyone can do about it.
So as the society of the spiral is expanding out, it's considered yin. So that means that
in order to balance that type of yin condition, you will have what? Yang manifestations in that
society. So what is a young manifestation in society while it's coming apart? Yang is
contractive, right? So let's look at it the opposite way. When you have a society forming,
and that spiral is contracting and forming, it's yang. And in order to balance that by necessity,
you will have yin manifestations in that society, expansive. So let's look at it that way. First,
you have, let's say, a time in history where the universe is contracting and forming society,
very young. To balance that, you have yin manifestations, things that are expanding,
right, to balance out. So as the society is forming, what do you see? Agriculture expanding
instead of little gardens. Now you see these massive agricultural fields, expansion, right?
And more abundance of food, yin abundance, right? Okay, so in a contractive society,
I mean, an expansive society, where it's dissipating now, like smoke dissipating out
of a room, there are going to be yang manifestations, contractions. So
where you once had wide, vast farming, fertile, lots of production, it's going to become yang.
Fertile lands are going to go away, and the food production will be absolute, almost down to zero.
Wow, you could figure all that out by understanding yin and yang. Damn sure,
you can, right? And it goes on and on and on and on. Population expanding, is that yin or yang?
That's yin. So as the society disbands, what happens to the population? It becomes yang,
contracts, fewer people. Wow, you could figure all that out with just yin and yang?
Absolutely. You go on and on with every aspect of everything, down to the atom,
down to social affairs, psychology, biology, on and on and on. Once you understand these principles,
someone can approach you with a list, let's say a book of a quarter of a million pages,
with two million chapters, right? And 5,000 subjects, and you will have the correct answer
for everyone, everyone without fail, if you apply this principle that I just mentioned.
But you must be able to diagnose each aspect of each question,
is it yin or is it yang? Is it yin posing, or yang posing? Is it yin ready to manifest,
or yin has already manifested? So you have to understand the condition, both the cross-section,
what is actually happening right now, and what is about to happen. And you will answer everything
correctly, and you will be able to actually create, look at something like the periodic table,
and see where there are missing elements that have not been discovered yet, and describe what
these elements, what the properties will be, without even knowing about them, that they
haven't come into existence yet. And you'll be quite accurate, you see? Well, that part I don't
quite understand, but I am understanding that when you have something that is in its expansive
state, it's going to move toward the other direction, that is the pull, right? So when
the movement itself is going toward the other thing, that's just the way it is. It's going
one way or the other, that's the way it's moving. In cycles, yeah, and that's time cycles depending
on the distance covered, because remember time, people say there's no time, that's correct,
but you ask them to describe why, and they shrug their shoulders, because they heard it from
someone else. There is no time without distance, and meaning if there is no movement, there is no
time, and there is no time if no one records it. A very perfect example is you go to bed at night,
you wake up in the morning, how much time went by? Oh, I feel like I got eight hours. No,
are you sure? Because you can have a good nap, you can have a good nap after a good blowjob,
what did I just say? And to have a 20-minute nap and feel like you slept for eight hours,
right? Or you can sleep for eight hours and feel like you just shut your eyes, either way, yeah.
Yeah, there's no sense of time there. Someone must measure it. What do you do? You look over
to the wind-up toy or the digital clock? Let me see, I went to bed at 10, and at 6, yeah, I went to sleep for
eight hours. Right, you measure it. Ah, you measure it, but if you don't, you don't know. But if there
is no distance, no movement, there is no time. So this is not evolved, by the way, this is a very,
if you can distill everything down to its simplest form, not only is it going to be
its simplest form, it's also going to be its what? Its truest form.
Well, it's easiest to communicate it as well, because you're not going into all these complexities
where you have language, which starts to confuse things, like you were saying.
Right, which is a technology, yeah. Language is a technology.
When you were saying, what was the Greek word you were trying to, you were saying is...
Anangi, necessity. Necessity is anangi.
I was thinking to myself, it's more like certainty than necessity, but...
Yeah, but it's a necessity, because anangi, that term is used as a proposition, like when you're
talking about something, and then you're ready to, because of this, then that, right?
Okay. And then when you, before you go into,
because of cause and effect, you're leading the person in that, because of this cause,
you cannot escape this effect, right? Which is very true in many cases.
Yeah, still, to me, leads more to what I would say is a certainty, but...
Right, these are certainties, yeah, and requirements based on the universe we live in
and perceive, more like the universe we perceive. Like, you know, the standard kind of like,
here's your expected reaction, and you've narrowed it down very much so,
because this is the action we should use. Okay.
Well, there's different, if the people are programmed to not observe and get,
there's a difference between reacting and responding.
Well, if you don't know what happens when you light something on fire, okay,
yeah, it could be a surprise, all right? Other times...
Well, no, no, in other words, people have predetermined responses to things.
I was in a long conversation earlier with someone regarding technology,
and when I show people things, you know, I was telling them, basically, I sound pretty,
like, full of myself when I explain these things, and I'm not, because what I'm really full of
myself is my passion to go ahead and move forward and do something with it, not the thing itself.
Like, I would never take credit for anything that people think I've come up with,
but I take a lot of credit for my passion and drive to achieve it, make it happen.
That's a big difference there. And when I show it to people, and I say,
make this or build this, and they're like, no way, I'm like, what do you mean?
I just told you to make it and build it. You looked at it for half a second,
you're saying, no way. How did you formulate the no way?
Where did that come from? You mean you process the entire thing
in one third of a second, and you said, no way? Or is that some pre-formulated response that was
stuck in your head by the collective? That you just say it by habit without thinking of it,
you just slap hack. Imagine like you're going around town and people are waiting at the bus stop,
right? You know how the bus stop has rails and guards and posts and, you know, stuff like that.
So can you imagine when the bus pulls over and the door opens, suddenly everyone stands up and
slaps a handcuff on their own self and locks themselves to the gate? Why would you do that?
It's like you're waiting there to get on the bus and here comes the bus, you handcuff your own
damn self to the bench. Oh my gosh. Can you imagine? That's a crazy visual. But this is
when I hear people respond to things that I say, it's exactly what it looks like in my mind.
I show things to people and tell them there's no way I could, like, wait a second, you don't
have enough time to think about it. And you're saying no way. You know, you're doing this.
I like this, what Brashear calls dungeon programming. They've all been corralled
into this dungeon automatically. So they've already, yeah, imagine, imagine just slapping
a handcuff or a neck cuff or a ball and chain on yourself every time you're ready to take a run.
Wait a second, I'm ready to run. OK, I got to put this ball and chain on first. Oh my gosh.
Well, isn't that the same as the whole thing with the math you talk about where, you know,
somebody says, oh, I'm just not good at math. I mean, yeah, but then it gets worse than that
because not being good at math means you're not good at what you're ready. Logic and reason.
Oh, my gosh. And you know what? The people that say that they're not good at math,
if you spend enough time with them, you'll find, guess what? They're not good at
logic and reason either, probably at all. Yeah. So. True enough, true enough. But,
you know, when you try and fit into it, stuff like the email work, right?
This also has to do with the yin and yang concept, but it's a little different, right?
Yeah. Well, you get both. Yeah. If you think on something a long time and email something,
a very general feeling is very yin. If you hold it long enough, it needs to be by necessity
balanced out by something yang. And suddenly you'll notice something like a lightning bolt
hit you, an idea or an effect or something. That's the yang part coming and vice versa.
Vice versa, if you have a very short burst of emotion.
Uh, internal or external, vocal or whatever, very short, but very powerful. Once it's over,
you become very yin, very like, oh, I'm out of energy. Here is someone go through a real angry
fit for two minutes and then after that, they're just ready to go to sleep. They're the calmest
people in the world. Oh, yeah. They become totally yin. Yeah. Again, by necessity, yin and yang
always works. So the emo does that too. So if you know how to control that, because it is a function
that we know through Greek speak, what the purpose of emotion is clearly definable instead
of this thing again for, what did I say earlier? Hallmark cards, right? Right, right. Uh, you can
actually use it now. The thing is, you know, how well are you, how good are you? Depends on how much
you practice and how well you practice and training is. So if you have like lousy training
for five years, that's no match for good training for, let's say five days, right? Right. So if
people say I have 20 years experience, I'm always when they're using the long time experience
because they're good. I always shy away from that because it's possible to actually have one year
of experience. 20 times means you stop learning after the first year and you've just been doing
the same shit for 20 years. That's all I see, by the way. That's generally the case. Yeah. They
learn everything pretty much. Yeah. Because, you know, put it this way. If you've got more than
three to five years experience in any field, you are easily, easily with no effort now,
world class at the top of the field in the world and any subject. So you got all these jerk offs
running around. I've got 20, 30 years experience. Yeah, I know what you got. You got anywhere
between three months to one year, 20 times or 30 times, you know, because I know for sure,
without a doubt that if you are compounding that experience for at least three to five years,
you are world class, the top of your field, any field. Right, for sure. That's not a doubt.
But what is the collective? No, it's 30 years experience. Oh, my gosh. No, it doesn't work
that way. Remember, this is planet Earth, guys. It's not it doesn't. Yeah, it's pathetic.
But the thing is, OK, what is the plus side of being on planet Earth? You have a short life,
a short life. This is the way the spans work here on Earth. You need at least 50 to 100 years to
master something on a master level where you can go beyond all of the physical things. It's
the difference between 30, three to five years and being a world class, world class among the
moronic society that you live in. Right. But to be a master, like a cosmic level master on, let's
say, furniture building, you're going to have to do it for 50 to 100 years. You don't have that
kind of time. You don't have time to become an adolescent, do 50 or 100 years of work to become
a master and then continue as a purveyor of that trade. It doesn't work. So you can't really
master things up to a universal cosmic level here. That's your first sign. The second sign
is look how people have allowed themselves to be drawn into these all these false
paradigms. Like, for example, I talked about academics talking about getting dead weight,
getting rid of dead weight like doctor. And by the way, if you're an academic and I spend time
with you, that's solely for entertainment purposes. I get I'm just having fun with you.
Like I'll play with a neighbor's dog. You know, nothing, whether you're a doctor, physicist,
engineer, whatever, whatever. I'm just having fun with you, dude. I'm sorry. I'm not messing
with you because I tell you this from the beginning. You don't really know any. You've
got find yourself. You got caught in the trap. And there's no song. We're caught in a trap. Right.
Can't get out, whatever. And now you are part of the welfare state. In other words,
you are reliant on the state to keep everyone in mind that you are important and you have some
social rank and you can go work in a company and make a good salary and buy a nice house,
have a good pension and all that. But that's part of the welfare state system.
And when you say welfare, say you think usually poor people living in public housing, right?
Leaking along. Right. Now, the welfare state, most of the welfare state is academia.
Actually, it is academia and corporate corporate cutouts and all that stuff.
People make these corporations, they think, oh, my gosh, you know, nothing. That's part of the
World Economic Forum and the monetary fund. They know nothing, nothing. And if I'm talking to you
and you're one of these corporate cutout types, I'm also having fun with our entertainment purposes.
I never hear. I have never gotten anything useful out of you, the corporate types or the academic
types in my entire life at all. They just drag you along. And oh, my gosh. Yeah. Yeah. So I just
have to put that out because, look, I put this out right away when I talked to you. You're an
academic, dude. You know, you're an academic. You know that. Right. You know, and I guess to
reiterate, I walked into the pizza parlor the other day. I said, hey, everybody, you know,
what's this guy crazy or what? Hey, listen, I got money. I got money for somebody who can
answer this real fast and real soon. Can you think of anything that you use
commonly or uncommonly or that has helped advance society that was created or invented by an
academic or university? Everybody's like half people like this guy's crazy to look down at
their plate, you know, that people are like, you know, he's right. So let me give you an example.
How about the electric motor? No. How about the airplane? No. Right. How about the light bulb?
No. And they're like, yeah, I can't think of anything. What are they good for? I said,
they're good there to insult you. They're part of the welfare state. What they do is in order
for you to go into the into their world, they ask you how much of a college degree do you have?
Are you kidding? Are you kidding? You're asking me if I took part in that useless
form of education. It's not education. It is absolutely useless. But give another example.
This is a conversation. This covid thing, not only was it for to execute millions of people
by asphyxiating them on ventilators, by the way, if you and all these there are millions of
doctors involved in this and they're just being thanked by the people's families who they killed,
by the way. Oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh. You would have the biggest Nuremberg thing where you would
take like you have to close half of I-95 for a few hundred miles and put enough rope to hang all
these bastards. Right. All these hospital administrators and doctors. OK. Anyway,
the only other stuff that they wanted to do with this covid thing was to flush out any good doctors
that were left in the system, because if there were any good doctors left in the system, they
spoke out. And guess what happened to them? They got booted. Right. So what covid-19 did is it?
Yes, guys, it flushed out anything, anyone that was left. So guess what you're left with now?
Uh-huh. Yeah. Avoid the hospitals, avoid the medical clinics if you can, if you can. Yes.
We start stocking up on what you think you might need and start applying it. Right. This is where
you're at. Yeah, I'm sorry. And it's going to get worse. The next one is going to be even worse.
And the one after, by the way, when the real pandemic comes by the end of this decade,
it will be completely denied. People will be getting up to go to work and not and not making
it through lunch. And it will be denied. We don't know why they're dying and it will be contagious
and it will never be in the media at all. The real one, when it you write, you see, I haven't
gotten into this. Real terrorism is never on TV. Right. It's a drill. You know, I was like, why
are these Blackhawk helicopters all over L.A.? We're not getting any response. Eight hours later,
our Pentagon says it was a drill. Yeah, sure. Well, we know rush hour. You got Apache helicopters
flying at, you know, traffic light level buzzing around. That's a drill. Sure. It is. Sure.
Well, like right now, I was reading a news story that there is the largest NATO drill since 1988
going on now. And I said to myself, I wouldn't trust it. It's the opposite. But then again,
look at what they're doing with 9-11 was a drill. Right. Well, that's what that's what I'm saying.
That's what it was. Yeah. So, you know, but NATO is the North Atlantic Terrorist Organization.
That's that is how I would. Yeah, exactly. That's how you call it. I don't know. They're
calling it something else. Treaty Organization. I've seen nothing of the sort. It's the national.
Yeah, it's a terrorist organization. It's all backwards. I mean, this is no you have to make
fun of it. This is not this is not what I'm telling you is 100 percent accurate. It's it's
not a parody. It's like, wake the fuck up, you know, or actually don't. It's better to sleep
through this mess. Right. Yeah. That's yeah. That is actually the unfortunate thing is that I
sometimes say to myself, you know, I've got just enough awareness of this crap to know that this
is going to suck, you know, like kind of sucking, sucking for vacuum cleaners and girlfriends is
fine. So it's not always bad. But here's the aspect of it is this. You can still have a lot
of fun with it because you belong to the earth. Your mind doesn't. Right. The the principles that
you can understand don't actually for the regular people. Yes. Everything. Right. And people say
no way right away without thinking about it. And those people don't count. They're like the props,
the fill ins, whatever. They don't count. And that's most people, by the way. So what's going
on is you can still have, quote unquote, fun with it. Right. Just don't put your hand in the fire
and get into a lot of pain or whatever. But, you know, everyone's number does come up, you know,
to be pulled from here. So there's nothing really bad to look to look at it as being bad.
Is it good? Here we go again. Is it good? No. Yeah. No, it's not good. But is it bad? Not
bad either. Right. So it just walk in the middle. Yeah, it just is what it is. And it's and again,
like you said, the you know, the good news is it's a short time. So and by the way, just to recap,
you know, I know plenty of quote unquote academics, academics, I mean, medical doctors,
sir, surgeons, right. Physicists, engineers. There's a lot of quote unquote academics that
are here is a military, military people, a colonel, stuff like that. Right. And I just want
to recap. I do mention that they don't know. When I start half the time when we converse,
what I inject in there is what how they don't know what they're supposed to know and what they do
know is not true. And they always agree every time. Right. And when they try to defend it,
they go through this kind of like, fading when they try to defend something, they fade away.
It's like they imagine someone speaking in this voice gets really low. Like they can't project
at all. Right. You could tell like, Oh, you ran out of batteries there, dude. You know,
your robot with the program, you know, you ran out of tape or something. Yeah. And it's not to make
fun of them. It's strictly for me to have and have fun on my own as entertainment. Because again,
they are part of the welfare state. They're done. They're finished. They had plenty of
they can see they made the decision on eighth grade to continue for whatever reason. I know
you made your bed. Got to lie in it. Right. Okay. It doesn't mean they're going to have a bad life.
They could probably never fat pension tenure. Right. All that other stuff. Whatever. Yeah.
All those little societal perks or whatever. Yeah. And it makes it come. But internally,
they're miserable and ignorant internally, every one of them.