And we're ready to roll.
Rated Y Sonic Event 219, I guess.
Anyway, how are you doing, Greek?
Doing okay.
Real busy.
A lot of brain juice going.
A lot of stuff I'd like to one
day talk about.
More water devices.
Interesting stuff.
And other stuff, yeah.
You sound a little calmer today, I just
wanted to say.
I don't know what it is, but you
sound a little less juiced up.
I mean, you were like, extra level the
last couple of times you got together.
L-tryptophan from roasted chicken.
If you guys ever make chicken.
Actually, any fresh chicken or whatever.
Soak it in, do a brine with salt,
ginger, and garlic.
And it helps if you put the ginger
and garlic in a blender so everything's liquefied.
For about three hours.
And then when you cook and undercook.
You think you're undercooking, it cuts the cooking
time by a third or cuts it in
half.
So like a three and a half pound
chicken, I was able to roast it outside
in under 25 minutes.
And it was done.
And never follow instructions about killing salmonella and
all that foodborne bacteria.
Because the heat doesn't kill it.
So you always want to use organic meat
that never has or typically doesn't have salmonella.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, so when they tell you that you
have to cook it for food safety, you're
an idiot if you believe that.
It means it's diseased meat.
You should never eat anything diseased.
So, yeah, there's no guarantee because they say
it about everything.
But usually the only reason the salmonella and
all that stuff exists is because of farming
practices.
It's not even a real natural occurring thing.
It's kind of like how whores have STDs.
Right.
It's because usually that in a society where
that kind of lifestyle is put down, the
people don't take care of themselves.
It's not that all prostitutes or whores have
STDs.
Right.
It's because when they get pushed into a
certain category and certain people that are bad
at hygiene.
Right.
So it's the same thing.
It's true.
Yeah.
Chickens are whores now.
Right.
Anyway, chicken head.
But anyway, I just want to put that
out there.
That too.
Hey, listen, speaking of safety, a quick question
because they asked me about like BPA and
BPPF and all this stuff.
And we're wondering if your water devices do
anything about that kind of chemical influence in
the water.
Or do you have some suggestion regarding that?
Unknown.
The best thing for that, because they are
considered organics and VOCs and all that.
Charcoal.
Charcoal is an absorber.
And also learn to use adsorbers.
Absorber, adsorber.
It's absorber with a D like zeolite and
magnetite.
But carbon.
Carbon is the number one deal.
When they pulled all the coal out of,
you know, the coal mining in the Appalachians
and all that.
The spring people were getting sick from the
spring water because it pulled the carbon layer
out.
That was actually helping the water stay clean.
They were getting radiation in the water and
all kinds of stuff.
Yeah.
So you need carbon for absorption.
Fair enough.
And look, I mean, it does have standard
uses even among medical idiots.
Because, you know, if you get enough of
something toxic in your system, they stick a
bunch of charcoal in your gut.
It does help to soak up some stuff
and get it out of there.
Well, yeah.
The stuff in your gut doesn't stay there
very long unless it's like stuck there.
Yeah.
They're never, they're never.
The whole, the whole system, the medical needs
to be completely scrapped.
And the theories are all wrong.
What needs to be kept are the basic
procedures that have been adapted that work.
And the rest of it is just an
idiot's heaven or idiots.
It's actually the medical system is a heaven
for idiots and hell for anyone who has
got at least four brain cells.
Yeah, I understand that.
I'm just saying that it has a practical
use even in that system.
It's sort of like using sand or an
abrasive when you're cleaning stuff up.
And, you know, you got the soap and
you add a little extra grind to it.
It helps.
You know what I mean?
A lot of people don't think that.
But anyway.
Mechanic soap.
Yeah.
What was that?
They used to go, but it was lava.
Lava soap was the big thing.
Lava.
There was gojo.
There was a couple of them.
Yeah.
It's like abrasive.
Pumice is usually what they use.
It's not so sharp.
Yeah.
Well, that's, but, you know, you can do
that with a good sponge or a good,
or stone.
You know what I mean?
It just got a little bit of an
abrasive to it and it takes away a
little bit of skin, but all the rest
of the stuff that's on top of it.
Anyways, I read one time in a book.
This is from a listener.
I read one time in a book that
immortality is the continuation of memory, no matter
where you go after leaving the physical.
What do you think about that?
This is a question for you and they
have a follow up.
But what do you think about that?
Well, it seems it's interrupted now.
Yeah.
Right.
If you were, if there was a before
for you, it's been shut off and interrupted.
That's why I keep saying there's no school
here.
You know, like imagine someone go gets a
doctorate degree and then they wipe your brain
at the end of college.
Right.
What do they do anyway?
But you know what I mean?
Yeah.
So no, I don't know enough about that.
I think that's one of the things that
it's one of those first principle questions like,
you know, if you're on a TV screen,
you can't talk about the pixels.
Right.
I understand.
You know, but I look at it this
way too.
Just because you're in a library, you pick
up a book.
It doesn't mean that there isn't another book
that tells you about what happened before that
book was written.
So, you know, you may just be in
a certain book, but everything is in the
library.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
But if you could consider immortal also being
there's two types of immortality, right?
One where you can't be killed and it's
a continuum, right?
Or the other one where you're killed and
you're brought back.
Right.
Well, and in that way, I think in
this one, it's definitely the latter.
Well, and in that way, the reaches of
people who are into like the transhumanism and
transferring your memory and your personality into stuff.
Yeah.
That new entity, that new machine language thing,
if they were able to actually pick up
the human brain and stick it onto a
computer, we'd think it was you.
Right.
Even though it's not.
Well, yeah, yeah.
Sure.
But the way it's being done now is
not because of anything with people.
They're at war with nature.
The entities that control mankind are not human,
but they use human agents to intervene or
as agents to interface.
They're at war with the natural world, the
way it's set up.
That's why you have the transgender and all
this other and the chemicals and all this
other stuff.
You know, in other words, they want to
change things.
It sounds like a commercial.
What nature intended.
Right.
What's a natural path like when a man
wants to be a woman or one wants
to be a man has nothing to do
with whatever it has to do with.
You've fallen for a narrative that is against
nature.
It's the same.
So someone who wants to be transgender is
no different than the people who want to
make synthetic whatever food or want to do
the transhuman agenda.
The transhumanism thing.
Yeah.
Their follow up fits in perfectly with the
chronology of what you're talking about right here,
because because if our memory can be completely
erased, this this listener asks, how can we
talk about the immortality of the spirit?
Question mark.
If we are if we are in mind,
then memory is the fuel that feeds the
mind.
Could acting on intuition be the proof that
we indeed have these memories stored, but we
access them through what you call the emotional
or the emo of the mind?
Yeah.
Very good.
The intent is formless.
Like, for example, when you have clay and
a pot is made out of the clay,
you can't say what is the essence of
the pot?
It's clay.
It's just clay in the form of a
pot.
Can you separate the pot from the clay?
No, because once the clay is gone, the
pot is gone.
So you have like a the spirit, the
realm of the mind, which is purely intangible.
I've always said that when I define spirit
and soul, soul is tangible.
It's a life force.
You know, you can put your soul into
somebody else's soul and revive them if you
could.
And, you know, CPR, for example, someone's not
breathing.
Your breath is your soul, but it's more
than the breath.
It's the vital signs.
So but it relies on the breath.
If you read a lot of the ancient
stuff, everything turns into breath.
So the spirit is completely intangible.
So speaking of it, because it's intangible, even
trying to apply an adjective or pronoun or
whatever of immortal to it is not appropriate
because it's intangible.
In other words, for something to be immortal
or mortal, it has to be tangible.
Right.
So like the pot is really what we
call something when clay is made into a
pot.
When we call it a pot, because it's
really still clay.
Right.
It's because you cannot separate.
Once you take the clay away, there's no
more pot.
So in essence, most of the things that
we describe through language and our notion can
be considered intangible once we consider the things
that they're made of.
So this is a very logical or philosophical
thing.
But I just right away break it down
to if we're discussing something that has tangibility
on its own or not.
But I'll tell you the mind and the
spirit has no tangibility on its own.
It has to be animated somehow.
At least in the way we can see
it now.
Yeah, but is the animation an evidence or
is it a resulting effect of the thing's
existence?
There's a difference there.
In other words, can you be a spirit
inanimate?
Yeah, sure.
For example, if you have a CD collection
or something on a computer chip, as long
as it doesn't get corrupted, you can animate
it at any time and then put it
back into spaces or storage, right?
Right, right.
That's what I was getting at.
Like pure information.
Right.
That's the thing.
Pure information is intangible.
That's why very often you have people say,
well, how am I supposed to use that
information, making it tangible?
It's a very big thing.
It's easier.
Okay, the way we're set up, the way
we're wired and all that, that's an easy
way to explain, is the only way we
can perceive it.
Again, it's a first principle thing.
Like the ether, very difficult to discuss.
And just like if your entire existence is
pixels on a television screen, you cannot discuss
the pixels no matter how you can try.
Fish have that same problem.
Like most fish, before they die, they realize
they're in water.
Then you've got these fish that go to
the other fish and say, do you know,
I think we're underwater, and they all laugh
at them, right?
Oh, yeah, of course.
Anyway.
No, that's interesting.
And the other thing is this started more
of a conversation, and basically I'm going to
condense this.
They're asking about, you know, look, they hear
ideas, right, and they have no technical knowledge,
not even a hint of what it is,
especially on the discussions that you and I
have here.
They say they hear stuff, and it resonates
with them somehow.
They know it's right, and they know it's
right.
It's not a matter of they're guessing it's
It sounds good, but they know it's correct.
And it feels like they do have some
knowledge somewhere, but they can't access it.
They have no idea where it is.
And they're asking, you know, is this just
something where they're waiting for a button to
be hit, and that's going to lose that
knowledge, or they're going to do something, and
that's going to bring them that knowledge by
inspiration.
Yeah, it is, just like the pot and
the clay.
The clay is very easy to understand, and
so is the pot, because you've used a
pot.
If you've never seen a pot before, or
any purpose that you would suffice to need
a pot for, you would need some explanation,
and then you get it.
So it's the same thing.
But then again, you know, you could discover
that clay a long time from now.
It doesn't resemble a pot, and then you
take it and once again form it into
a cup.
Now, it's still the same clay, but it's
been reformed once again, and now it represents
something else that is finally tangible.
See, that again talks about the transition between
the inanimate and the animate, like you were
talking about before with the information on the
CD, right?
So the information on the CD is still
within the clay, but you have to do
something in order to bring it out, right?
Yeah, but there's another level to that.
Water shows that, like water has memory.
See, water's an exception.
See, water's a different thing.
That's what's weird to me.
Like, I don't know how to articulate this,
so I ask you.
You know, water seems to me to be,
yes, it obeys the majority of the laws,
right, of the physical, you know, circumstance here,
but it's got extra to it.
And it's not a profound, like, you know,
it glows or it makes noises.
It doesn't obviously present itself as extras, but
like you were talking about where it's got
that weird sink in the temperature.
Last time we talked about this.
And, you know, it's difficult to get it
out of the one temperature from, like, well,
you can get there easy.
In other words, it's quite the coincidence that
our blood temperature is at 98.6, and
that's where water likes to stay.
Right.
When it reaches that, yeah.
It's resistant to moving, you know, lower.
Yeah, it sits at 98.6. In other
words, you could take heat and cold.
It'll stay stable at 98.6 with variations
in external temperatures, yeah?
Right.
And that's an interesting thing, but that's where
water is different from other things in the,
you know, in the.
.
Yeah, it's got a lot of other interesting
things other than typical.
.
They call it a universal solvent, but it's
actually a universal oxidizer.
And because it's an oxidizer, water is actually
burning all the time.
That's more on the alchemic.
.
It's equivalent to fire.
Because fire as an oxidizer.
.
Like someone who's, you know, into the chemical,
control of the chemical world will always see
fire as an oxidizer, but most people see
it, oh, that's just fire.
It's hot.
Well, it's oxidizing.
Right.
And water is an oxidizer, so they're paired.
But most people take fire more seriously than
water for obvious reasons.
Right.
And, of course, I'm a little more simple
-minded, so I always say, you know, look,
don't laugh at the people that told you
that fire, water, and earth are elements, you
know.
They do the same thing.
As a matter of fact, you know, when
you put wood in fire, it gets darker
and darker.
And if you put wood in water, what
happens?
It gets darker and darker.
Right.
Look at the color of driftwood.
It gets darker and it changes.
It actually stains black.
Right.
So there's a whole level.
.
One day I'll .
One day.
One day we'll talk about the stuff I've
been looking at for a long time.
I've worked with some people.
We've done a bunch of transmutation.
Enough that will fetch a bunch of trouble
if you talked about it.
I have a .
.
I'm actually in the office.
I was moving things around.
I have a box full of samples.
There's about 250 samples in there of things
we've actually changed.
And we .
.
Yeah, based on the principle I just mentioned,
that water is actually always burning.
But you can't say it like that because,
well, burning is not hot.
Well, you know, I mean, it's an oxidizer.
Once you learn to judge fire always as
being an oxidizer.
So anyway, yeah, and the water does the
same but in a different way.
Fair enough.
Look, this is more focused on the questions
this time, and this one's a little different
but somehow falls into the same category.
It's weird the way this stuff comes together.
Anyway, could you ask the Greek because they're
addressing me in this one.
Could you ask the Greek about ways to
improve gas mileage, question mark?
Yeah, definitely.
Remember him saying it was possible to drive
across the country on a single tank of
gas.
I'm curious what it would take to make
that happen and whether it's still possible with
modern combustion engines, maybe modern governors and all
kinds of weird things on them.
Yeah, but here's the thing.
I doubt it because if you do the
math, I don't know about cross-country.
I don't know because there's the long way
and the short way, New York to Florida,
and then you've got New York to California.
But it depends on what some country.
Maybe it's a small country.
But typically automotive design, like sedans and things
that people, like a family would buy or
whatever, usually have a 300-mile range.
But increasing gas mileage, the newer the car,
the harder it is to do because they
have fuel injectors which are controlled by an
electronic control module, ECU, PCU, and there's a
whole bunch of them, and that will sabotage
the engine.
In other words, you could put a whole
bunch of fuel-efficient modifications on the engine.
Most of them, you don't have to buy
anything.
You just remodify what's there, and you'll get
good gas mileage for maybe 15, 20 minutes,
maybe a day, and then it will go
back to maybe making it worse.
This is all malevolent shit.
The only way you could do it is
if you have something with a carburetor.
That's why I tell people if you have
a lawnmower, usually they run about 20 minutes
or so.
I can very simply extend it so it
runs 40 to 50 minutes.
I'm sorry, about, yeah, 35 to 40 minutes,
usually almost double.
Somebody sent me a Honda generator.
I wanted the spark plug and the carburetor,
and he usually got, I don't know, 7
hours run time, something just under 6 or
7, between 6 and 7, and we got
it to over 12.
Simple modification, 15-minute modification.
It's got to have a carburetor, though, a
natural, not just naturally aspirated, but a carburetor,
not fuel injection, no electronics controls.
Some very rudimentary electronic controls, like pre-1990
cars, we can do it.
But after 1995, when the OBD-1, which
is the onboard diagnostic systems, came out, they
really started building in these, I call it,
sabotage protocols.
One thing, there was a bunch of group
of people that got around the sabotage protocols
and were building 100-mile-per-gallon Ford
Tauruses and stuff like that.
And that got out, and they were threatening
to make that knowledge worldwide, and that's when
Obama did the cash for clunkers.
Let's get all the old cars that potentially
benefit from this off the road and fill
the engines with cement, right?
So, yeah, there's always a reason, a very
nefarious reason behind all this stuff.
Very nefarious.
We're in a very...
All of the authorities, religious, financial, medical, they're
all at war with the population.
They're elements of war.
It's just like what they did with coins,
Greg.
The reason why they removed the precious metals
from the coins is because the precious metals
were worth more than what the coins represented.
So what did they do?
They either priced you out of it, or
they destroyed them, which is exactly what they
do with even the cars, right?
They either price you out.
It's now a classic car, so now it's
worth so much more that it's not even
close to affordable to get something that's 80
years old, or it's destroyed.
It's no longer available.
So you can make it unavailable or unattainable.
The two things you could do to improve
gas mileage real fast, but don't hope it'll
work if you have anything past 2000.
Actually, anything past 1998, really, it'll help.
It'll get more power and all that, but
the electrode on the spark plug should have
a tiny hole on it.
The J-strap, the part where the spark
hits, has a very small hole.
Recently, the past two years, I've discovered that
geometry of the hole is critical.
It has to be exponential, which looks like
a cone.
It's not a straight hole, so it's narrow
on the spark end and wider as it
goes out through the strap.
Is this the relative equivalent to boring out
the pieces on a dirt bike like they
used to do in order to make them...?
No, no, no.
This is just the spark plug.
So the spark, the forward motion of the
ignition...
Yeah, they used to do something to the
spark plug, plus drill a hole in the
carburetor, I thought, which was...
I didn't understand it, but these guys told
me something very interesting.
We have to be very strategic about it.
The other thing is there's something called a
gadget man groove by Ron Hatton.
You could look that up.
I offer that.
I offer my own version of it, which
is superior.
Yeah, grooving the throttle body.
You could look him up.
Now, Ron, I was in discussion with him
for many years, and he was always saying,
we're going to make the world a better
place, we're going to make the world...
He killed himself.
Well, basically, he took a bunch of drugs,
drove on a mountain pass, got into a
really bad accident.
They tore his arm and leg off or
something.
Yeah, not necessarily in that order, but yeah,
go ahead.
Yeah, and they sewed it back on.
He woke up and he pulled life support
off himself because he got really depressed that
no one really cared.
And I said, no one cares here, dude.
I kept telling him, dude, nobody cares.
Stop saying make the world a better place.
That's supposed to be.
You don't go to a fun house.
You don't go to a carnival and say
the house of horrors, let's paint it and
clean it up.
No, it's supposed to be a house of
horrors.
This place is supposed to be this way.
So anyway.
That's why the second that you actually have
a true solution to a problem, you're done.
You're over.
Because if you try to share it with
anybody, you're gone.
Anyways, last question here, and it's a weird
one because this person knows you well enough
to know that they really shouldn't ask you
about politics.
So I'm going to condense this, but they're
telling me, make sure he understands.
I'm not asking about the politics or the
news.
And the question is the core question.
What is Donald Trump?
Not who?
What?
Yeah, I would look into Donald Marshall cloning.
I think what's been going on is because
the reason why he brings this up.
Now, I want to tell you the reason
why he brings this up, because you might
have not caught this, but he started to
tell a weird story at an energy conference,
right?
And he started saying that his uncle, you
know about his uncle, he had some degrees.
Yeah, yeah, who emulated Tesla.
Well, okay, but he didn't bring up that
part at the Energy Summit.
What he brought up is that he said
my uncle taught Ted Kaczynski, you know, the
Unabomber guy?
Yeah, yeah.
And my uncle was the longest standing professor
at MIT, which, first of all, is incorrect.
Secondly, his uncle was a professor at MIT.
He said he had three degrees and Trump
didn't hit any of them correctly.
Dr. Trump's degrees, okay, on the record, were
in electrical engineering and in two other places.
And he had three degrees, but none of
the ones Trump mentioned.
Then he said that Kaczynski was one of
his students.
Now, problem is nobody knew who Kaczynski was
until 96, and John Trump died in 95.
So, you know, he told a weird story
that was totally screwed up.
And this is what inspired the question.
Again, very carefully I'm saying this for the
listeners more.
The Greeks got it already.
What is Donald Trump?
I don't know.
The only way I don't think Donald Trump
knows what he is.
Okay.
I've heard that he died already.
I've heard that, you know, here's the thing.
They're very bold.
They're putting out their, I think they're putting
out what I would call their best technology
for cloning and other things, facsimiles of humans.
They're doing a lot better with that than
they are with the AI, because there's something
I call AI aftertaste.
You know, when you see an AI thing,
you're like, it leaves an aftertaste.
Well, there's that, plus there's what they're calling
delusions now, or what's the other term they're
using for it?
Where you're imagining stuff.
What do you call that?
Yeah, yeah, that's right.
Hallucination.
That's what it is.
The AI is having a hallucination, according to
their terminology, and I'm cracking up.
It's like, no, it's not working right.
It's having a hallucination.
Yeah, but the thing is, it's all based
on their creator.
You know, when you go to a different
culture, like China or India, something is radically
different, or even Mexico or whatever.
Everything they have there has a certain version,
like a pot.
If you get a pot from China, you
can tell it's made in, not just American,
but it's a Chinese pot, or something from
India.
So the AI, it's because of that culture.
Okay, so the people, the culture that makes
the AI is a certain culture.
It's not just people taken from whatever willy
-nilly, and they do, initially, but they breed
them or groom them into this culture.
So if you understand that culture, of course
it puts that way.
It's the geekdom.
They're geeks, but not in a good way.
Their geekdom is put into their product, and
I see it.
I see right through it.
Well, that's the crap they do, even with
stuff that I try to access to accomplish
things like broadcasting or whatever.
Their geekdom is always built into the background
of it, and I have to sort of
learn the new language and logic of it
in order to operate their crap properly, to
do more than just the surface-level things
that simple people want to do.
You've got to know the geekdom.
Otherwise, you can't do it.
You can't touch it.
What does that mean?
That's right, and I don't like that.
That's why I said, what was it, the
phones, the phones, the stupid rectangles, the smartphones.
They're designed around what was hammered into the
geeks to make these a 9-year-old
girl or a 12-year-old girl or
a 14-year-old girl where the credit
card is the entire premise behind these things.
Now I hear from other people I've discussed
things with, people that worked in tech firms.
There's a whole other level to these things
where you have to completely scrap it.
It takes four hours to redo the phone,
so it acts more like a PC.
Yes.
Right?
Yes, yes.
Yeah, yeah, all that stuff.
So I'm not going that far because, you
know, like today there was a call that
I missed because when I was out, the
phone, like I said, like in the 1960s
and 70s, was hanging on the wall with
a long wire attached to it, in this
case the long wire being the charger.
Yeah, you just leave it on the charger
all day, and therefore it is now wired
to the wall because you've chosen it.
Yeah, that's how I roll.
When I go out, I know people, if
I have to make a phone call and
I'm out, I just ask someone, can I
use your phone?
I'm just making a local call.
Fine.
You know, sometimes they'll dial it or whatever,
and it works.
I mean, people are still, they're not bitching
about it, and, you know, you're not going
to find a pay phone.
And it doesn't cost, you know, in the
days when it used to cost, you know,
$50 to make a call, I understood, hey,
look, I ain't lending you my phone.
But now everybody's got, you know, it doesn't
cost me anything.
Yeah, sure.
Well, it does, actually.
If you call Canada, you get a long
-distance charge.
It was real funny.
Oh, you got an even dumber plan than
most people then because, to be honest with
you, most people in America, they got a
North American calling plan.
Oh, okay.
It must be the plan that's very old.
But I was told, you got a long
-distance call.
I was like, really?
You know, and they gave me the number.
I was like, who did I call in
Canada?
I don't have a girlfriend in Canada.
What are you talking about?
That's the thing, though, is, you know, and
there's the other funny part is if you
take a phone, right, you buy it in
Canada.
Now, that phone is based in Canada, allegedly,
the number is.
Now, you move to here, Georgia, you're making
your calls, your phone is still from Canada.
I mean, you know.
It's roaming and all that stuff they have.
Yeah, but they've, there's, yeah, it's just a
business.
Those bills, by the way, are checks written
out to you anyway.
One of these days I'm going to shorten.
Well, we'll do a talk about the financials.
And I've really been simplifying it in my
mind and how easy or much easier it
is and what's being put out online about
it and how to get moving on that
again.
But I won't do a, what do they
call it, a seminar or a private group,
but we'll just talk about it here because
the private groups don't really go anywhere.
I think just doing it on here is
better, if that makes any sense.
Well, you know what?
I know that we'll get a result.
If you give a very simplified version of
something.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Get more people onto what's going on and
stuff they could use.
Someone sent me an email recently.
It's akin to, you know, anything that could,
like, go against the fuckers that put together
this control system, you know.
And I'm like, great, you know.
I'm all for that.
It's not because I'm anti-control systems.
You have to have control systems.
But when they're malevolent and you know it,
going along with it makes you one of
them.
So, anyway.
And the other thing is that in any
system, look, no matter how big the beast
is, you always got to give it a
black eye once in a while anyway, even
if they call it.
They kick in the shins.
They kick in the shins?
Same thing.
Bush Jr., you're either with the terrorists or
you're with us, you know.
So with us or with the terrorists, right?
I'd rather be on the side that is
not malevolent.
How about I don't want to be with
either one of you, you bastard.
Anyway.
Any other final thoughts on this today or
what do you say?
Because I think Tuesday is going to be
different, interesting, et cetera.
There was a personal question for me.
I'll answer that on my show because nobody
cares about that here.
I know my lane.
All right.
Anyway.
I don't know about that, but that's fine.
Let's make it a short one then.
Yeah, let's do that.