Rated Y 67.
Here we go.
And there's a lot to there's a lot happening in the world.
I always I think, but you know, it's, it's, it's, it's, I know you're not keeping track
of the news or anything.
What are they, what are they on to hostage exchanges now, stuff like this?
Yeah.
You know, and it's becoming more and more divisive.
I note that as we go into the next phase, because I know we're about, I don't see that
at all.
Let me interrupt for a moment, because as long as people, okay, you've got firemen that
drive around in big red fire trucks, right?
I'm not trying to make any ensuing anything here other than, you know, there's fire departments
that have heavy equipment to extinguish fires on structures, buildings and cities and towns
and whatever.
Okay.
And then you have toys that children want to acquire, whether, you know, whatever desire
they have, they don't put out fires and do anything like that.
Right.
But they want the same stuff.
Okay.
So if you see people in a society that takes sports seriously, they buy the paraphernalia,
they take time off, they watch, you know, they make a big deal, right?
They pay two, three, four hundred dollars, three thousand dollars for special seats in
stadiums.
Right.
All that.
Okay.
That's the toy.
Right.
So the toy doesn't really put out fires.
Okay.
So now it's false.
Tribalism is all it is.
I mean, because, yeah, we think it's real sports in action, but you ever listen to these
guys.
We we won today.
You didn't win.
You watched a game on TV.
You know.
Yeah.
That's people.
There's something wrong with me because people ask me to watch sports and all I can see is
people in uniforms chasing a ball.
I don't see any.
Right.
Okay.
So in essence, you have the people that desire the sports, which is the child with the toy
fire truck.
And then you actually have a fire department with a big fire truck that puts out fires.
Right.
That's all war is.
So the problem is this.
When people get away from the competitive sports, they will view the wars for what they are.
And they, too, will go away.
It's a it's it's just a parallel.
These wars are not really wars.
They're not.
It's a sport.
That's why the terminology, the technical terminology is put this way.
The legitimately accepted technical terminology is war is what a theater.
Right.
Yeah.
So the same thing.
So as long as people are the way they are and the culture is the way that it is, you
have it.
I have no problem with it.
I just don't want to be a part of it.
It does affect everyone, of course, but so do sports and so do holidays.
Right.
Like, for example, why I want to go downtown on December 25th and file a document down
in the county.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
And I go down there to file a document, important document on December 25th.
Then what?
They're what?
Closed.
Why?
Your religious attributes, your religious observances are disturbing my ability to do
commercial my commercial affairs.
Yes.
Right.
But they say that they don't have any religious observances.
So what's going on?
It's well, it's a commercial.
See, to me, it's a commercial arrangement.
It's not about, you know, it was allegedly created out of the religion, but it's about
commercial arrangements anyway.
So, of course, it's going to disrupt other commercial arrangements, is it not?
Yeah.
But they tell you on one side that it's not.
See, so the whole thing is just set up the way that it's set up to confuse and whatever.
But it's all very simple when you when you see through the confusion.
Right.
Yeah.
So it's all the same.
It's all the same stuff.
Well, you know, they give you Santa Claus, right, which I used to love our discussions
on Santa Claus, which are absolutely horrendous.
It's a symbol.
Yeah.
It could go either way.
Right.
Well, it's a symbol, but it has a basis.
There's a reason why a glowing red thing has screaming children put on its lap.
I mean, that's right.
Wish of prosperity.
Same with the birthday cake.
Right.
You make a wish of prosperity that that's what they call Bronze Age stuff.
You know, the human sacrifice.
So it's a holdover, right, from that society and from other worlds also.
Right.
You can see there's a time when it goes away because, for example, in the U.S., let's say
we're talking about what they call Christmas.
It was illegal and it was made legal, illegal, meaning in the sense that it was not accepted
and viewed to be unlawful.
And New York, New Jersey, Massachusetts, right.
They brought it back.
Right.
In the 1800s.
So Dickens.
By the way, all these popular writers that they tell you to read, Twain, Dickens or whatever.
They suck.
Have you read Dickens or Twain?
They can't write for shit.
Well, Dickens bores me to death.
I kind of like Twain a little bit, you know, because you can get into the story, kind of
draws pictures.
But it's poorly written.
I can't stay with it.
Even Melville.
Right.
And Emerson.
There's not very good.
Emerson's better.
But but here's the thing.
Just like now they put out trash.
Right.
This was the trash that was put out then before the, quote, unquote, reset.
Well, Steinbeck put me to sleep, too.
I could not get Steinbeck in, you know, in those.
It's not very good.
The class, what they call it now.
I was having a conversation with someone engineering type recently, and I said, look, if I were
to be in a deserted, if you were to be on a deserted island, what would you bring?
One book?
What would it be?
Or one author?
And he didn't have an answer.
My answer was Shakespeare.
Easy, easy.
Try to read Shakespeare.
It is so dense.
Yeah, it is.
And and is refined at the same time.
Yeah.
Right.
I'll make you think.
Most people say, wait a second.
I know what they I know what the Greeks are going to say.
The Bible.
Right.
No, no.
Sorry, guys.
Wouldn't bring that.
I would bring Shakespeare for sure.
You being that English is my primary language.
Right.
OK, well, it makes some sense.
Yeah.
You know, the Bible is something that you should be.
You should acquire the knowledge therein.
You should acquire the history therein.
And then you also have to understand where you are in time and what they've done to it
or what they want you to see.
Why are they allowing you to see that?
And how has it been changed?
Right.
So.
Well, there was a point in time where the majority of the population really didn't seem
to know how to read anyway.
And it used to get read to them.
Right.
I mean, that practice is still kind of in play because you go to these churches, right?
These circuses, these theaters, all of them, all those words apply.
And a guy gets up there and usually picks a passage.
Right.
You know something.
And that's always driven me crazy, too, about people that that like will insist upon reading
from the Bible on a daily.
And they get nothing out of it.
They get nothing out of it.
It's the weirdest thing.
It's like I've never seen dedication to a book where you get zero out of it.
Yeah.
That literary method.
Try it with any book.
It won't work.
You won't get anything out of it.
It's not it's not it wasn't set up to be written that way.
And it wasn't set up to be written by chapter and verse, you know, no matter what is said
about it.
Because here's one interesting thing in the latter days that there will be people scoffing
at it.
Right.
There's a lot more scoffing at the Bible.
If you go on YouTube, maybe it's because of conversations and things that I have, you know,
they select what they should show you.
If I open a YouTube homepage, half of it is Bible commentary on how, you know, the Bible
is fake or this, you know, this, that and the other, you know, negative, you know, or
contrary.
Right.
And then there's a whole portion that is pro these Christian stuff because they don't know
what to show.
We'll just throw this stuff at the Greek because they I've had conversations on the on the
phone and I've cleaned everything off the computer.
Right.
By the way, clean MGR.
If you have Windows, go down to your taskbar and type in run.
And when it comes up, you in the run box, I'll run as an RUN.
Type in clean MGR, just C-L-E-A-N-M-G-R, enter.
Select all the boxes on the left, hit OK, and it's going to ask you, do you want to
delete everything you selected?
Yes.
That does the same thing as all those other virus things that they want you antivirus
clean up hardware stuff, programs to install.
Right.
That's that's how you do it without downloading, you know, a program that's going to want to
take as much information from you as possible and stick a whole bunch of secret programs
on you to write.
The weird thing about that, though, is for me, I got to tell you, no matter what I do,
Google gets my conversations.
Yes.
So anyway, I did this and then freshed up the computer and I go back to like a YouTube
or whatever news homepage and it actually starts referring things that I had in conversations
an hour or two, three, four or a day before.
Right.
Interesting.
And I've done experiments with this.
And I said, look, I'd call someone and say, listen, this has nothing to do what we're
talking about.
Do you have you ever restored an old teddy bear?
Do you collect teddy bears?
You know, teddy bears.
Have you ever fixed a teddy bear?
And where do you get high quality teddy bears?
Right.
Yeah.
OK, that's it.
And then I clean up the computer where I open up, let's say, YouTube homepage and guess
what videos are there?
Teddy bears.
Antique teddy bear.
Yeah.
No.
Look, the weirdest thing is I've sat in my room, you know, because I have a little office.
But even when I rented a room from somebody, the same thing happened.
And I'm staying in different places.
We would have conversations, just two guys or three guys having a conversation.
And whatever we were talking about would be the thing that they would show up to me on
Google, on YouTube.
You go to a Web site where it picks up the ads.
The ads are for this stuff.
It was hilarious.
It was like, you know, I like two or three guys get to talk and they start talking about
women.
Right.
This kind of thing would happen.
So we have one of these kind of, you know, salacious conversations, whatever is guy
talk.
OK.
Normal stuff, I think.
Anyway, I go to my computer and what am I getting?
I got, you know, would you like to meet Russian women?
Would you like to meet these kind of women?
Do you want a porno site?
Do you want to? I mean, all kinds of crazy stuff.
I go on YouTube and it's like the pickup artist book.
Audiobook is, you know, by the way, I would interject if I was there instead of talking
about women. I said, you guys know how to talk to women or with women.
Big difference. Right.
Of course. But we were objectifying them, you know, typical lowbrow stuff.
All right. So, yeah, well, it's not typical for me.
I cut that stuff short real quick.
But go ahead. OK.
Again, I'm a different I'm just accommodating who was around me.
But I mean, the weirdest thing was that Google wants to sell me, you know, Russian
brides and important to the Russian brides want to be sold.
Is it voluntary? Is it by consent?
It looks like it. I mean, it looks like it may not be, though.
That's true. By the way, there's a bunch of people.
The alternative is 2013.
I forgot her name. Came out with a bunch of stuff about bafflement and all that.
And she uncovered and showed how YouTube videos are have codes for finding children
for sale, human trafficking.
And then she said she's not suicidal.
And a week later, they found her hung in her garage.
And then her boyfriend died a couple of weeks after that.
Oh, you're talking about the D.C.
Madam. No, I think it's Tracy Twyman.
Oh, yeah. Tracy, did she die?
Yeah, they found her hanging.
By the way, there's that sound again, people.
It sounds like a dog with a, you know, dog is a collar with the plates on it.
The name tags. That's what it sounds like.
Moving around or a dog tag.
That's what it sounds like. You have interference.
So, by the way, guys, we before we started recording.
Yeah, we're trying to find this noise.
And Chuck always called it scratching.
I was wondering how am I so much, you know, wondering.
So then we started.
Neither of us knew that this dog tag sound started coming on.
So if you hear that, it's a technical thing we'll work out.
But I think it's not so anomalous to mention it.
But Tracy Twyman, she brought out some stuff.
And when the moment she got involved with a group that was showing how
YouTube codes videos for human trafficking.
She's hanging in her in the garage.
Right. Right.
So, well, that's serious.
That is what happens when you touch on the serious thing.
And you actually get it, something that's workable.
I mean, whether you're Gary Webb or whoever.
The DC madam is an example of that, though, by the way.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, they have.
Yeah, she was very adamant about says, I'm afraid for my life.
I'm not suicidal.
So in case I write, you find me, you know, right.
And what happens is they say she commits suicide.
What is what does the public do? Where's the outrage?
No. Did it like, you know, a thousand people, 10,000, a half hundred thousand,
half a million people must have heard her say she's not suicidal.
Right. Right.
And she feels her life might be threatened.
And then they say they find her hanging in a shed or something. Right.
Yeah. I'm taking a look at this.
She died in 2019. I didn't even know. Yeah.
Yeah. I was aware. Where's the same with this one?
Where's the outrage?
Yeah. Nobody cares.
Well, you know. Yeah.
No, there was no outrage about a matter of fact,
she was real popular in the alternative media.
I remember she was on like everybody's show.
I mean, the big ones, the small ones, everything
about the Merovingian stuff about.
Now you sound like women talk, the big ones and the small.
Anyway, here we go again.
Anyway, I'm just saying I remember there was just a bunch of stuff there
and I see some Reddit threads about her and things like that.
But I mean, I just did.
I didn't even realize she died.
I just thought she was one of these people that disappeared because she disappeared.
All right. Well, but see, but that happens
to where they disappear for a while and then they come back.
But what's very strange to me is that she was pretty young.
Looks like I believe I might have.
I believe that might relate to what to the Greeks, too.
Slightly. But yeah.
So anyway, where we're on people, you know, I say,
are these guys entertaining a tangent or is this conversation going somewhere else?
The idea here, Chuck, is very simple, is that again, where's the outrage?
Right. Where's the outrage? Where's the outrage?
And every time I say, where's the outrage is for a completely different topic.
Right. Where is he?
Look, you go into a store and they sell this is organic food and this isn't.
Where's the outrage? Why?
So what's the difference?
Well, one has poisons and toxins and pesticides.
The other one does. Where's the outrage?
Well, why don't we stop?
Why don't we go get the people who are putting poison, right, and stop it?
So it's all organic.
We don't have to have a separate organic category.
You see how screwed up that is.
I ask this question all the time and people get pissed off at me.
I go, look, you see, you go into a food store and you see there's this little tiny
section they call health food, right?
So if that's the healthy food, what is the rest of this crap?
And they're telling you that there's only this little section of health food.
Right. And I'm not even saying that that's really health food.
But isn't that weird? Nobody says anything.
People who are not committing outrage
for showing outrage for sports and war, organic and non-organic food.
People saying they're not suicidal and then being suicided
don't deserve any more than what they have.
I think they have more than they deserve right now.
What I'm trying to say is very simple, is there's no there.
What am I trying to say? That's very simple.
I don't know. We deserve to be pranked by Santa Claus.
Those of us that are, you know, it's not it's not very good.
It's in other words, it's an example for a very few that are passing through here
to see. Don't try to change it.
You can't change it. But if there's outrage or whatever, again, those right.
It'll be shown very quickly that the ones that are outraged are crazy.
Right. So you're never going to get a majority,
at least in the ever that we have to change things more in the right way.
This is not the type of place that it is.
Right. Well, people do get outraged, but it's always about dumb things.
It's fake outrage. Yeah, it's like misdirected.
They're they're not really angry at the stuff that's really stepping on them,
but they pick a new savior.
See, I was going to ask you about that.
And hold on. They don't.
Nobody picks. Nobody does anything.
Like, for example, whenever there is a movement, even the 60s, that's artificial.
All of those protests and stuff is artificial.
One hundred percent. All of them.
Well, let's say ninety nine percent artificial.
In other words, they're funded by the same people that have created the problem.
That's why I could George Carlin say, if you think you have a solution,
you're part of the problem because this place doesn't need a solution.
This is the way it was made to be.
What I mean to say is, though, is I've been inundated lately again
with, you know, people saying that, you know, Trump is going to be the guy
is going to come back and set everything right, you know, again.
And I say to myself, well, what what is this investment?
This is where they're focusing.
Their outrage is.
Yeah, but hold on. Very simple.
Anything political?
Are they coming out and telling you, sorry, guys, we did some bad dealings
in the 1930s and we had to put up your country as collateral
to a private, non-surface banking cartel?
Gangsters, everybody.
OK, no receivership.
You kidding?
Well, then you're part of then they're part of the problem.
Right. But it's not a problem.
You see. Right.
So because this is the way the place is made.
This is the way it's supposed to be. OK.
Yeah. Until. OK.
You've got an amusement park.
It's got all the different rides, the fun house, the scary house, the roller
coast. You can't go.
You can go in there and modify them slightly and put new ones.
Take out. Right.
But the theme has to stay the same.
But if you come in and tear the whole place down.
Right. So the whole thing has to be torn down.
OK. With health, you're saying this.
It's not possible.
Here's the thing. The liver in the body loves coffee.
You could soak the liver in coffee.
It's it's in heaven.
It actually gets high off of it.
But it hurts the kidneys.
It can't hurt the kidneys. Right.
On and on and on. Things that help the skin hurt the liver.
Sure. Right. Things that help the lungs.
Right. Hurt the muscle tissue.
Right. So there's nothing that's healthy or is there a more healthy, quote
unquote, regimens? And we've gone over those, by the way, eating seasonally,
eating minimally and understanding based on energies, stuff that builds
muscles and weakens bones.
You know, it's just one way or another. Right.
I mean, there is no health food.
There is nothing healthy. You must understand.
Like, for example, when I put out, by the way, I want to thank the people for
is still frequently get for the one one recipe that I went to
and O.N.G. with you in depth.
So we've never gone into cooking in depth.
But that one episode we did on how to do brown rice, number seven or brown rice,
number eight, depending if you use an umeboshi plum or not.
I'm still getting feedback on it.
And it's always like beyond what.
And it's never it tastes good.
It's not about taste.
And one of the comments that I got, someone wanted to add garlic or something
to it. No, it's not about flavor.
It's about matching these things purely based on energy.
And when you put together a meal based on energy,
not what you flavor, you desire,
you will have this outcome and learn how to do that. Right.
By the way, most traditional cultural food was based on energy combination.
Right. Unless you get really crazy like like like pomfret,
pomfret, which is French fries.
Yes. And steaks, you know, steak for it.
You know, the best steak sauce when you have the French fries
and steak is like it's like a liquid pate.
It's butter, wine, garlic and pureed chicken liver
as in the sauce for your steak.
I mean, oh, my gosh.
You know, it's huge, right?
Amount of stuff.
Yeah, that has an energetic counterpart to it as well.
That's what I wanted to ask you about that, actually, because, look,
flavor in and of itself, can't that create an energetic result?
If you secondary, it's secondary.
But I mean, there's like a heavenly flavor in your mouth.
Even they tell you when you eat chocolate and stuff like that,
it does this or that to your brain when you eat certain foods.
If they're pleasurable to you.
Yeah. Well, OK, so sweet would be for the spleen and the pancreas.
Stimulation. Right. Taste.
The bitter would be stimulation for the liver.
Right. On and on and on.
Right. Then you have tastes in between.
Well, what's really good for the brain, you know, because this is the thing
no food at all, actually, is best for the brain.
Because I was, you know, I was told, you know, like fatty stuff
because the brain is kind of like of a fatty material.
Well, that's another thing. The lipids and all that. Yes.
But but to a certain degree, water.
Look, OK, you know, this is, again, several conversations.
You know how there's side effects for drugs, right?
And there's also they all have psychological effects also.
But they don't state that, right?
Especially with young people.
I used to do this.
So when a child gets whatever, you know, unruly or whatever, OK, fine.
So call me over.
I want to come over and speak to the child before mealtime,
like a half hour before. OK.
So I come and speak to the child a half hour before
and I have them write their name and five or six years old.
You know, they they start to, you know, how they write, right?
Basically, you can do this with an adult.
Sign your name, write your name.
Then go ahead and have your favorite food.
What's your favorite food? What would you desire?
Child was chocolate milk, chocolate milk and something else.
I don't recall. It wasn't savory.
But anyway, after they had that, waited 10 minutes, write your name.
And oh, my gosh, the T didn't look like a T.
It looked like an A without the center part. OK, right.
And it was like, oh, my gosh, so distorted.
The same with adults. Write your name, sign your name.
However, have your favorite food or what you're even just a normal meal
that you normally eat without being, you know, conscientious about it.
Remember your name after the meal.
I had one adult once say, I can't even write.
I can't write.
It's like, what do you mean you can't write?
Of course you can write. Just drag the pen.
Just if you can't write, just drag the pen.
I mean, it's the best you can do.
And that's all they could do is just drew basically a crooked line.
They couldn't even sign their name and adult. Right.
So, OK, so everything has an effect on the brain.
What will happen is if let's say you have, quote unquote, healthy food
after you write your name, after you write your name,
when you're comparing before and after.
Yeah. Even with the healthy food, you will notice a drastic change.
There will be a change if it's a sweet food or a savory food in one direction.
Right. And it also the way you write your name, the distortion
in it conforms to what you've eaten as well.
So, OK, there is no no.
Look, if we were meant to be healthy, we wouldn't have to eat.
And yes, does he mean does the Greeks say we should be breatharians?
Yeah. But not the way breatharianism is discussed.
We would not eat need to eat.
We gather most of our energy from the environment anyway.
That's why when you go out in the summer, you don't have you notice in the hot
summer days, you don't you don't eat much.
And yet you have the same amount of energy.
We're in the winter. You need to eat more.
By the way, speaking of energies, I've also been getting messages
about health things and a few concerns like, are you sick?
No, no, I'm not. I'm just dealing with a couple of things.
You know, I mean, my I'm going to be 60 pretty soon.
So which amazes most people because they say I don't sound that old.
But either way, so we don't.
Yeah, I'm just going through some stuff, nothing too serious.
But here's some concerned emails.
And when I get more than two or so, I'll bring it up.
And what I've noticed is the environment is being stressed.
Before we started recording, I said I want to talk about how we're being stressed.
What I mean about that is I live in the southwest, Tucson, Arizona.
And after monsoon season, which is late summer rains, usually you've got to go out
and get the weed whacker if you live on a property and got to cut the grass
because it grows really seriously fast and tall.
And yeah, it looks pretty wild.
The place looks wild.
Well, this year after the monsoons, I keep saying, you know, there's no
we don't have to cut any grass, nothing's growing, nothing's growing. Right.
What happened?
This is the first year that I've noticed this.
I've been here since 1990, what they call 1998.
And I've never seen this before.
Right.
Well, see, now you don't have to cut the grass.
Now, I see that in the southeast all the time since I've moved here.
I see it all the time.
There's a certain time.
No, no. I'm talking about this year.
There's a stress level.
OK, that's happening in nature.
If you don't cut the grass after monsoon season, it grows up to about knee
or waist height and it turns brown and falls over and it makes a mess. Right.
Right. So in some some neighborhoods, they write you a fine and all that.
And I'm prepared here to cut the grass after monsoon season.
Actually, even before monsoon season is over, you cut it for every week.
Otherwise it gets out of control. Right.
Right. Nothing, nothing at all this year has grown.
The garden has done well because I have the scale rate or the water treatment.
Right. It's garden has grown stupendously.
And anything that you run through this device grows really well.
You know, we've had like a
sweet potato plant produce over eight pounds of delicious sweet potatoes,
which is unusual. It's way above average, almost double the average.
And so one plant, one plant produced eight pounds of sweet potatoes.
Yes. A basketball. I want one plant. Yeah.
So so imagine you had a farm like with a thousand plants.
You'd have quite a, you know. Yeah, that's quite a bit. Yeah. Yeah.
So it would probably do even better.
But here's the point.
Why isn't the grass growing?
Let's just say let's set a timer.
This is the end of November 2023.
And I'm still waiting.
It's like the weed whacker is ready to go.
It's the trim line is wound up.
I've got a cordless one.
I've got a corded one.
No weed whacking. Oh, I'm so happy.
I hate because it's a pain in the butt, right?
To cut all this grass everywhere on the property.
But there's nothing growing.
Well, what kind of a stress?
I've had a mesquite tree die, started dying last year, which is unusual
because this is a desert, a very hardy tree.
It's a hardwood tree.
Mesquite, right?
You people have heard of mesquite.
Yeah, very hardy.
And it's it was about a 15 year old tree, almost 20,
actually about more than 20 year old tree.
But still, it died, just died.
Right. And I have a pizza oven.
I don't mind going up to the tree and pulling off dry branches for the pizza oven.
But outside. But here's the thing.
There's the environment is being extremely stressed, at least here in the southwest.
And here's one thing.
Will him right came to the Tucson in 1952, 53 time to break a drought
that was ongoing for a few years.
And he did. Right.
And they asked him, why?
Why did you pick here?
And he says, because all of the ether, you know, the weather,
the weather causing ethereal elements enter
the southwest at this area for for that effect,
the entire North America and Europe.
Right. This is the entry point of the cosmic ether where I am.
OK. And this is this is according to Wilhelm.
Right. And I've been playing with it.
And I could see it is pretty valid.
So if I'm not getting any kind of simulation or growth here,
in terms of vegetation, naturally, what's going on everywhere else?
Right. This is the entry point. Right.
Very interesting, as this is.
It's kind of disturbing to to ponder this over the past few weeks.
And I just figured I wanted to inject it into the conversation.
What do you think is is the cause for that effect?
Stress, stress, obviously.
Like, for example, it's a fertility issue.
But what is causing that stress?
What is what is the cosmic?
It's cosmic, totally cosmic, because the air quality hasn't changed noticeably.
Materially, I don't OK.
I don't see a material cause for it.
OK, that's what I was right.
A material, it's a non-material cause.
So that's open. Well, that's what I remember.
No matter how much we.
Some people in Arizona reported to me that there were,
you know, increased chemtrails and this and that.
And I said, OK, you know, I never know what to make of that.
You know, the worst chemtrails was more than 10 years ago.
It was really bad. Right.
All year round. Not anymore.
Well, yeah, this year it was reported to me, though, that it increased again.
And I wasn't and I said, well, I don't know what is that actually.
It's it's always a little bit.
Not much. I remember 10 years ago, it was really bad.
I mean, they were doing literally like half of a tic-tac-toe in the sky.
OK, literally the grid with the zero and the X's, you know,
but not completing the game. Right. Yeah. OK. OK.
No, I look, I'm asking because I I'm not able to observe it.
I'm, you know, on the other the other.
Yeah, no, it's not it's not material.
And so it's not chemtrails. It's not harp. It's not.
Right. So it's nonmaterial.
It's a natural. It's a cosmic nonmaterial.
Now, no matter how much people,
whether it's the Greek or other people talking about ether and actually
putting out information, how to make practical devices and all this,
we've all been raised in a culture where we have to break away from
to see and acknowledge the nonmaterial. Right.
Because we're told everything is material.
Atoms and electrons and things like that. Ridiculous stuff.
Anything else is a figment of your imagination. Right. Right.
So, you know, you have to break away.
So this is like the breakaway group, you know, that thinks about these things.
So when you say nonmaterial, we don't know.
But acknowledging it is is is enough to start, you know, pondering it.
Yes, it can be effective.
I know that if I dedicated
anywhere between 10 to 30 days, I can change the environment drastically.
You know, using the ethereal devices, basically basic water guns
and other things from Trevor James Constable and things that I've developed
along those lines, it could drastically change
the environment.
But without doing that, just seeing what's going on is very unusual.
Is this a reduction of water in the environment?
I mean, is that part of the stress?
Like it's been dried out?
Water is material.
Because I would think without the grass growing.
But water is.
You know, we had a lot of season.
We had a lot of monsoon material.
Yeah. OK. OK.
That's something that is stressing.
OK, here's another way to put it.
During times of war or women in prison or women,
they stop menstruating during times of stress when women is very stressed.
Let's say a woman that is in the age or time of her life
where she menstruates, meaning that she's ovulating.
Yeah, that ovulation cycle stops.
It's during times of high stress, turns around and skips.
And it does all kinds of weird.
So it stops. It just stops.
It'll be this.
You could read about during the wars in Europe and all that,
that women did not menstruate for years.
And then when the wars were over, they started again.
So not all, but most most, believe it or not, more than half.
So so this is just, you know, some simple example that you see
animals in zoos, right?
They write, why are they having a baby?
You know, why isn't the lion right?
Why isn't the pandas right?
The pandas was the big one, right?
Yeah, they're stressed out from captivity.
I mean, that's not material.
It's not because they have all the food.
They have all the water.
They have all the comfort, right? Right.
But they it's an immature, immaterial, immaterial.
Sounds like a more it's not a material factor
that is not considered by the mindset of the people that are on the surface.
Now, I always have to qualify on the surface.
Sincerely, Greek speak surface dwelling earth inhabitants.
If you if you remember Greek speak from way back in the days,
I've always said surface dwelling earth inhabitants to imply
what that there are earth inhabitants that are not surface dwelling.
Right. Could be above the surface.
Could be below the surface.
Mostly. Yeah, mostly.
And both above and below.
If you have to mention that they're on the surface, then that means there is other.
Yes. But yeah, try to be specific when you want to guide them.
You know, the thinking process. That's exactly right.
Right. I understand all this.
Well, OK, but the stress on the environment, it's it's an odd thing.
Because the material.
So then, yeah, go ahead and point at it.
You can't. It's immaterial. Right.
So but you have to understand the reactions.
You can still ask why, though, right?
Yeah, that's that's pretty important.
That's what this is rated. Why isn't it?
Of course. Of course.
But that's that's my that's my question, though.
It's like, why now?
I mean, are we because you're saying that?
OK, I've got an answer for that.
You want to hear the smarty pants answer?
Because when you things are thrown at you that are, quote unquote, problems
and you have a solution, go ahead.
Then if you think you can do it, implement the solution.
So if it's strictly just the grass not growing.
Yeah, we can make the grass grow a simple water gun.
Wilhelm Rake water gun not fully charged and grounded with no water
will make create green greenery.
By the way, the there was a big drought,
touted drought in California in 2013.
Twenty fourteen was big in the news.
Headlines is to stress people out, quote unquote.
And I was like, oh, I'll try to make rain in California.
And while I was trying to make rain in California, it greened up.
It greened up all of California without any rain.
And NASA, actually, you could still look it up.
Twenty thirteen NASA photographs of high altitude
photographs of California vegetation.
It's still up online.
It'll show you the year before the drought.
Most of the state is pretty brown with some green spots.
But the year of the drought, the entire state's greened up.
How is that possible?
Yeah, that makes no sense in the material, in the material sense.
It makes sense.
But if you if I just if you understand that a Wilhelm Rake type device
that is well grounded with no water running and it will do that.
Right. Well, it makes complete sense then because you could scientifically,
you know, you can go to a place
that doesn't have green and make it green.
You don't want to redeem the deserts because the dust storms
the deserts produce are vital to the fish crops, by the way,
because the dust storms go into high, not low level dust storms,
but high altitude dust storms that form in deserts are carried
throughout the high altitude and are deposited in the ocean.
And guess who likes to eat that silica dust?
Plankton. Plankton.
And the plankton are really, really small,
but they're eaten by things that are a little bigger.
And those things are eaten by things that are slightly larger.
And those things are eaten by things that are right.
So they're at the beginning of the food chain.
Yeah, I mean, they showed us that in cartoons years ago, right?
Where you would see the little fish gets eaten by the bigger fish
is eaten by the bigger fish.
This is starting to sound like a cartoon. I get it.
But here's the thing.
If you cut off the head of the top of the food chain,
which is the smallest thing by cutting off the silica by
because you redeem the desert, right, you will lose the fish crop.
And the big that we're talking about, the big fish crops,
you know, the ones that the commercial fisheries,
you know, like the sardines, the tuna, the right, everything that depends on.
Right. The mass, the massive crops. I get it.
Yeah. So the deserts are a function.
If you would like the type of fish that you're harvesting,
if the deserts were all redeemed and we went into, again,
a pre Noah vapor type canopy
ice field around the earth,
you would have a different type of fish crop.
But in that situation, you wouldn't need to do agriculture things.
There'd be so much vegetation and animal life.
You would just have to go outside your door and your food would be there.
Well, being that this is a cosmic implementation, right?
Can we determine the reasoning for that?
Or is this an indicator of cyclical reasoning?
Always. OK, you always apply cyclical reasoning to any process.
Right. So, you know, baby crawls on his newborn baby,
crawls on, you know, on his all fours when you're really, really old.
You crawl on all fours. Right.
So it's a cycle. Yeah. Right.
OK, well, so it's just a cycle.
So you got crazies.
You got crazies going in both ways, crazies that want to fix it.
And you got crazies that want to fix it and can fix it.
By the way, most crazies that want to fix it can't fix anything, by the way.
And then you've got the crazies that want to blame something else
and will never fix it.
But they're the ones that are most suited for this environment.
The ones that don't you know, the ones just make a lot of noise.