Rated Y episode, or not episode, haha, haven't said that in a while, there's a pattern break,
Sonic Event 64, thank you, and here we are, my mistake there, but I caught it, I was saying
episode a little while ago for something else, and that is episodic, this is not, so there
you have it, 64, kind of interesting, this is more than, I think, in total, not necessarily
in hours.
Yeah, but Chuck, episode is not as bad as saying show, so it's alright.
Okay, well, but it's not episodic in my mind.
Well, yeah, 64, Hebrew gematria is emet, which means truth, is 64, yeah, well we were, yeah,
speaking of the truth, we were getting into finance, I think we might have overloaded
some people, underloaded others, frontloaded others, backloaded others, you know, and so,
yeah, I'm not sure about the reaction, because I've actually gotten less feedback regarding
the finance discussion, which was, in my mind, really loaded with a lot, than I usually get
from these Sonics, you know, a couple of days later, I usually have more feedback, and I,
we didn't get as much, yeah, well, I think just for the economy of time, that some of
the terms that I mentioned, I would just say, if you're more interested, just look up on
the browser of choice, fractional banking, but only take it to a certain degree, I would
avoid little cartoonish things that show how money is done, right, because that's all put
out by the same people, right?
Well, the Federal Reserve puts out some cartoons that do look informative, even on the fractional
reserve banking, I know you've seen them, right, the cartoons?
Yeah, it has nothing, yeah, it's false, none of that is like that at all, because everything
right now is done in secret, and there's two ways, one is to simply hide the secret,
the other way is to just never make people aware of it, so they don't know that there's
a secret, and they don't know what to ask for, and that's more in line with what I'm
doing here.
I've also had several contacts, emails, in the past, let's say year, about why don't you
talk about money a little bit, in terms of like, if you're earning, you know, working
in a company, or you know, doing books, or how would you handle that, right, so I might
want to get into that a little bit more.
Before we get into that, go to YouTube and look up David Merrill, Federal Reserve, it's
called the Federal Reserve, is the name of the video, I think, I could maybe take a moment
and look for it, but he did something about eight years ago, or five years ago, or something
like that, very dry, very, whatever, on the Federal Reserve Act, and what your signature
really does, what it really means, and I could cover that, because that will help a little
bit.
David Merrill, he has a YouTube channel, Lawful Money Trust, I don't endorse these guys, but
because they're a little narrow, a little too narrow, but nothing, I haven't found anything
what they're putting out as incorrect, so it's viable, it's valid.
If you just, if you, let's say joined his group or whatever, and you did exactly what
he said, yeah, you'd be fine, it's just totally cool, but it doesn't have an open perspective,
that's all right.
The other thing I would suggest is he, they have a forum, it's called a Suitors to Savings
Club, suitors, like a suitor, like the suitor in the Constitution, a suitor is someone who
can competently go into court, right, where, you know, a non-suitor has to be represented
by an attorney, so it's presumed that everyone is incompetent, right?
The first David Merrill I find, by the way, is David Merrill 101, is that him?
Depends on, his name is spelled a little bit differently, the title would be David Merrill
Federal Reserve Banking, would be the video, by David Merrill, yeah, yeah, so on YouTube,
I could actually, let's do that, because that's actually very important, and because the most
important part of that video actually is what you do when you sign unconditionally, you're
actually bonding it, so you're basically bonding means you're putting everything behind, right?
What they do, it's kind of like voting, voting has nothing to do with electing, it just says
that you are voting for the system, basically you have faith in the system, and this is
if you were an elector, who you would elect, right?
People don't understand that, let's see, let's just do a quick search, David Merrill, and
it's a double R, I, double L, I believe, unless they've, yeah, contact David Merrill on top,
oh my gosh, it's, I got that one, I'm sure that, yeah, I'm gonna push it to the bottom,
what reserve is to put in fractional, let's do, I'm glad I'm doing this, because it didn't
show up, yeah, see, that's why I was asking a follow-up question, because, yeah, fractional,
how does a fractional reserve banking work?
No, let's go to the channel, and I got one of those cartoons with the, oh yeah, they
like doing that, they sure like doing that, no, I don't think that's David Merrill, 101,
no, I don't think that's him.
That's not him, okay.
No, that's not him.
Well, we'll have to, we'll have to come up with a way to find him then.
Maybe they, maybe they killed it.
They might have taken it down.
Yeah, yeah, because he, yeah, because a lot of this stuff is, ah, this is for fractional
federal reserve, David Merrill, let's put lawful money next to it, yeah, oh boy, okay, well
we have some pretty savvy people, I brought up stuff, here we go, federal reserve, the
name of the YouTube, the title is Federal Reserve Act of 1913, hyphen, your remedy under
the common law, and this is what it should sound like, I'll just play it through the
microphone here.
Federal Reserve Act, written in 19, I'm David Merrill, and I'd like to speak for a moment
about the Federal Reserve Act, written in 1913, and the remedy found therein, and how
to apply it today.
That's it, 10 years ago, it's really noisy in the background, which, yeah, that's it,
if you can get that, it's very dry, ah, you know what, I'm going to copy that, and I'm
going to drop it in the chatango right now, just as a reference.
Yeah, let's put it there, I can go get it from there.
I'll put it in there right now, ah, you know, I'll drop it in the chatango.
If you like, I can get it from there, and we can play part of it as audio right on here
directly, if you like.
No, we could, I just wanted to bring that up, whether you got it or not, that's what
it should sound like, and that's fine.
No, no, it's, I don't know where to, I don't have any time markers, but let's get into
what's going on with it, with the system.
It's all based on your signature, remember, just on a quick recap, bankers found out that
only 10% of their people came back to pull their money out, right, everyone else left
it in, so they figured if they lent out 90% of what they had at the time,
they'd be okay, right, because, you know, if 10% of the people came in and took it,
they have nothing, but at least they're not busted, right, there's no bank run, they don't
look like they're, right, like they screwed up, right?
True enough, and if it floats up a little bit, maybe 20% comes in and takes it, you're still
doing good.
Yeah, but either way, that was the general, and also coincides with mostly people of Jewish
persuasion religion, and also the Torah, which is 10%, right, the tithing, so it kind of
worked out all right.
When the gold was all taken away, and the U.S. went bankrupt, every country has a bankruptcy
clause, if you can find it, and like for the Netherlands, it's different than for Brazil.
Most of the countries by the 50s were in the condition that the U.S. was in by 1933.
You know, like all the banana republics and all that, they probably came in as late as
the 60s.
So the whole world is under the World Economic Forum.
One way to know when the whole world went under this system is find out when the World Economic
Forum came into existence in the U.N., right?
Because that means they got all the 186 or 196 countries now.
All right, but that's not a real, that's the history, this is not a history lesson, I'm
not a historian, but I just want to bring this up because it's important.
Why?
Because anything and everything can be accessed through some form of enumeration or currency
or money, right?
That's what makes people, that's what's really enslaved people.
You know how you're on a slave society, pick anyone and ask them if they could have anything,
what would they want?
And they always, it's always luxury.
Yeah, I want this car, I want that, blah, blah, blah.
A non-slave society would say, I want my needs met, you know, food, clothing, shelter, and
I want to be in harmony with everything around me, right, you see?
So, because of the slave nature, this money thing is very important, right?
So, and there's many aspects, so you know, I'll give you an example, I'll share something
personal.
Going through a health challenge, right, physical challenge right now, and it's very interesting
because I'm kind of doubting myself a little because I'm not getting, I'm not getting too
much improvement.
I'm okay, but you know, kind of watching this condition, right?
So part of it's like, oh, the Greek talks all this smack about how you can take control
of your health, and he went to a doctor, right?
Or, I'm just telling you what's going on in my mind, or I don't make progress and it gets
worse and worse and gets sick and dies.
Oh, the Greek was talking about health, he got sick and died, oh my gosh, so either way
it's no good, right?
So either way I have to succeed, right?
Yeah, I mean, on a long enough timeline, everybody knows.
Yeah, in other words, from a public perspective, right, if I keep sharing, right?
Let me just recap, like, oh, the Greek had a health problem and he went to a doctor, ha
ha ha, or the Greek had a health problem and he killed him, ha ha ha, so the only thing
I can do to quote unquote save face once I start making this public, let's say, is to
fix it myself.
Successfully repair.
Because that's what I talk about, okay?
So the money stuff is just like that.
Everything is like that, right?
So once you start becoming independent, right?
Less dependent, let's just say.
Okay, so, very easy.
The fractional system, now, what happened, the signature was replaced by the gold.
Now, let me just do a recap.
All the countries, everyone there, meaning on planet Earth, has a social security number
of some kind, most likely, right?
If you have a central government with a central bank.
Those used to be called exemptions.
You know, by the way, you can't use it for ID.
It's a really screwed up system.
Corporations need that from you, right?
Why?
Because did the people give consent and get full notification and disclosure about how
they were going to go bankrupt to this world finance cartel?
The answer is no.
And because they can't be held culpable, they were given an exemption.
They're exempt from all the machinations and maladies that might come from it by giving
them a number that goes to the treasury.
It's considered public funds, and you're supposed to use that when you need something,
if the money system is not around, right?
Okay, and that's being done all the time.
So, by the way, I knew someone who could finagle it.
No, I won't get into how to finagle it.
He went and bought anything he ever wanted with a social security number, and the attorneys
finally, through the bookkeeping, his name kept showing up.
Why is this guy getting all this stuff using his treasury routing number?
Because he needed the number, he needed a treasury routing number.
So they kept going after him, kept going after him.
He spent five years in jail because they basically said he was using public funds.
All right.
I also brought up the bar associations works with these guys, and the bar associations,
you can't tell people they could use that exemption or social security number and get
wherever they want, right?
Nothing will get done, and they're right from that perspective because it's a group
of society of savages.
Now, the other side is they run everything.
Give me an example.
Let's say you have the legal system, which has nothing to do with law, by the way.
You have the medical system, various social systems, political systems, right?
So you go to a doctor, which is part of the medical system, and you say, I want to use
this alternative therapy.
What did you say?
I legally can't say, right?
Oh, wait.
So now you're an attorney.
Now you're an attorney.
I thought I was in the medical system.
Now you're telling me about legal stuff?
Oh, okay.
So let's go to any social whatever.
Go talk to a politician or whatever.
Oh, you legally can't do that, right?
Oh, so now this is about attorneys.
Oh my, legal, right?
Legal, right?
So you go with finance to a bank.
Hey, I'm going to give you this signature.
Oh, legally, I can't do that.
Oh, wait.
So now you're not finance.
Now you're an attorney.
You see how the Bar Association runs everything by default, right?
By the way, did I get into this?
Do you know about the book?
There's various, it's called a book, a catalog, whatever.
There's a human trafficking going on, and there's photographers involved, the actual
kidnappers, the people that run the market, and the attorney generals of every state and
country.
How does that work?
Well, I've heard of this, but I've never heard you speak about it.
Yeah, I have in brief.
It's called a catalog.
What it is is these very wealthy people who like to predate on children look through a
book with children, and when they pick one, they bring them the child.
Usually, they tell them how available the child would be.
Now, what happens is the people who set up this market go to public places like parks
and beaches, whatever, and take photographs of children.
And the better looking ones, they just write down their license number.
They were with the parents, right?
We're talking like three years old to five years old, eight years old, right?
So when you're taking a picture of a child at the beach or a park or whatever when there's
gatherings, most likely there's an adult nearby, and most likely the adult got there via a
car, right?
So what you do is you find out, you hang around, and you find out what car they're going to
take a picture of the license plate.
So when that child gets picked, right, they have the license plate number.
So guess who they call?
The attorney general.
Here's the license number.
Give me all the info you got.
So what does he give them?
The address, where they go to school, all that stuff, right?
So now they know where to go make the pickup.
Get it?
So that's a big part of their business, by the way.
Yeah, all of them.
By the way, if you don't do this as an attorney general or whatever, you will not be an attorney
general for long.
That's part of the, you know, right?
Now imagine you become an attorney general and you try to blow the whistle on this.
Ooh, in Spanish they say, pobre si, pobre si, poor you, poor you, right?
You're going to be deep fried monkey.
Okay, this is the world you live in, so stop being so naive.
Why are you calling me naive?
I'm not naive, right?
All right.
So what's going on is they have these systems, they're called programs, that most of the
people that work in the banking industry do not know what's going on at all.
Your signature is the most important thing to them.
Talk about litter, right?
If a banker's in whatever, he finds a piece of litter with a signature on it, he could
and, you know, some other information, which is an address.
Okay, so what's going on is very simple.
I think I brought up CTOs, which everything is a CTO now, the confidential treatment order,
which is illegal as hell, by the way, to do all these secret deals.
But anyway, it goes on and on and on.
So what's going on right now is how many signatures can we collect?
And also, after 9-11, they did what's called the Paperwork Reduction Act.
If you read that, it includes in there that, well, if you have a signature with a particular
phone number, we can also monetize the phone number now, right?
You get it?
Because this big phone number equals your signature, blah, blah, blah.
Part of the Paperwork Reduction Act was making it easier for them to monetize more than your
signature, right?
For example, one of the CTOs is – just a quick review.
Chuck, this is what's going on.
You write me a check.
Let's say we use regular slave talk, regular common whatever.
You have a bank account.
I have a bank account.
Sure.
And you have a checking account.
I have a checking account.
So you write me a check for $100 because you've got $1,000 in the bank, $5,000, whatever.
You can cover it, right?
All right.
Write me a check for $100.
Okay.
Now, I go to the mail and I get it and I'm like, oh, Chuck, I need a check.
So I go to the bank teller.
I want to cash it, right?
I want to cash it.
I don't want to deposit it.
But the same thing happens on a deposit.
Okay.
I take the check out of the envelope.
I hand it to the bank teller and she gives it back and she says, I can't use that.
You can't cash that.
Why?
Remember, I just took it out of the envelope and handed it to her.
She can't cash it.
Why?
Because she says, you have to what?
She needs you to sign it.
Endorse the back.
I have to endorse it.
You need two signatures.
That's why when you pull out a Federal Reserve note, you see a signature on the left signature
on the right or one on the top, one on the bottom.
You need two signatures to do this.
Right.
That's what I'm telling you.
All right.
So the moment I endorse the back, she looks at her terminal and what the bank has in its
inventory is transaction numbers, just blank transaction number.
Just like, you know, when you buy, when you go to the movies and you, let's say right
now you want to do a thing where you sell tickets and the person who comes in, you tear
the ticket in half, give them a stub that has a number on it.
Right.
You know how you're going by.
You can actually buy a big roll of tickets.
Right.
Sure.
And they're all numbered.
Right.
That's what banks have in their inventory is a transaction reel or transaction roll or
transaction bulk.
I forgot what they call it.
So they got a bunch of these things digitally that are basically just like a ticket roll
at a movie theater.
Like a raffle ticket.
Right.
Like you might see a raffle ticket nowadays where they buy them already printed.
They have the numbers and they both say you tear them in the center and each of them has
a number on it.
So this way, if they take it out of the box, that's what banks have in their inventory.
So she turns to the terminal and here comes the next ticket number.
It's a transaction.
And by the way, what I'm telling you, any, any bank transaction you do when you get a
receipt, it does have a transaction number.
It's like 24 or 32 digits.
Look at it.
Yeah.
That's that number is their inventory.
OK.
So she pulls up a transaction number and it's blank next to it.
Everything's blank.
She types, she sees the two signatures and she types in a hundred dollars and she cashes
a hundred dollars away.
The hundred dollars come from the two signatures.
Now, what happens is the check that you sent me not only has your name, it has your account
number on there.
It also has the bank name and the bank information on it.
Right.
Well, when the check gets scanned, it has magnetic ink now, too, so it could read the
numbers like whatever.
It tells your bank right away that I did the deed.
You know, in other words, I did something with that check and created a hundred dollars.
Right.
My bank tells your bank that that happened.
Years ago, it used to take two or three days.
Remember, it takes two or three days to clear.
Yeah.
But nowadays, no, it's instantaneous.
And yeah, they would.
Yeah.
They would have people.
They would use like Morse code, basically, to do it.
You know, a telex.
Well, you used to be able to say go to a grocery store, right?
You can run a check through.
And even if you didn't have money until Friday, you could go on Wednesday and run the check
through because, you know, they weren't going to get it to the bank until Friday anyway.
Yeah.
Stuff like that.
In other words, you wouldn't be in there.
Sometimes the check would be cashed and you still have a hundred dollars for a few days.
Yeah, exactly.
Right.
Unless they got on the phone.
Right now, it's pretty instant.
So when that hundred dollars gets when that when that instant that transaction that I
did is your bank is notified, your bank, what it does is like, oh, the Greek cash check
or deposit or whatever.
We because Chuck O'Chelley went to kindergarten and his grandparents and his parents were
dumb.
I'm sorry.
I mean, but, you know, everybody's dumb.
You know what I mean?
In that way.
Right.
About how the banking works.
What we're going to do is take the hundred dollars out of his account.
So when he looks at his account, he makes everything make sense.
Right.
But when the hundred dollars take it out of your account, it has nothing to do with sending
it to my bank to pay me anything because it's already done.
I got the hundred dollars from the two signatures.
Right.
So what are they doing?
The front of the check, which is for me and the signature on the back of the check, which
is you endorse.
Yeah.
They created the hundred dollars based on our two signatures.
They didn't need the hundred dollars from your bank account at all to do that.
But they take the hundred dollars out of your account because they make it seem like something,
you know, the money's worth something.
Right.
They can't leave it in there.
All you need is a hundred dollars for the rest of your life.
Keep using it.
Actually, that's what you do need.
But anyway.
Yeah.
So what they do is they take it out and they put it in the CTO part of the legal parts called
the comptrollers, the legal part of the bank, legal department.
Right.
And your name is in there, too, by the way.
You are.
If you call the bank's legal department, they'll find you say, is there a choco Charlie?
Yeah.
He's in here, too.
Right.
Got another like personality in there now.
They know because it's in the legal department.
It's in this part where it's special transaction orders that you're probably never going to
access that.
You don't even know it exists.
So they feel pretty safe that they give you like 10 days, 30 days, maybe a little less
between 10 and 30 days.
And they know you're never going to go and call that hundred bucks.
You don't even know it's there because the regular retail side of the account shows the
hundred dollars is gone.
Right.
But it doesn't show where it went at all.
You presume that it went to me.
You're presuming.
Right.
So it sits in your own bank for and then what bank knows that you'll never going to find
out what they did.
So they want the money.
So what do they do?
The credits.
They file a 1099 on it, which is an IRS form, which is a stands for abandonment of funds.
Those are abandoned funds.
Right.
And it sits there.
Then they file a 1099 C, which is a claim form, and they take it.
But they don't just don't file a 1099 A on your thing.
They bulk all the transactions that happen during the day and the week.
And they file 1099 A on that could be millions, could be billions in some cases.
Then they claim it.
Well, how about this?
How about you put like a thousand dollars in the bank, run it all down during the month,
get the statement back.
And it shows you you start a thousand dollars when you did all the shopping, whatever you
did transactions.
And it goes to zero.
OK, you take that statement that they send you and you staple it to a 1099 C right away
that you want to claim this, just send it to your own bank.
Oh, oh, no.
Goes back to what the attorneys say.
Right.
Remember.
They're going to say, well, who do you think you are?
I never address the point.
By the way, if you run into a bank attorney about doing this, they will never address
what you're trying to do.
Who do you think you are?
Are you an attorney?
Where did you learn this?
But I never get always side skirting.
And they close the bank account, by the way, and they tell you there's no reason they don't
have to give you a reason closing the account because under consumer laws, they could deny
service.
Right.
Now, don't they do this when people die to the same thing where it's like, oh, yeah, they
do it all the time.
OK, because allegedly you have money in a bank account.
Right.
And so now on the sheet, it's different.
It's different.
It's the people.
Don't talk.
Forget about.
No, no.
This happens with all the old day transactions.
Now, this is important that it gets out to the public in mass.
Why?
Because there's so many people that get thrown out on the street or can't eat because they
did have a thousand dollars in their bank a month ago.
Right.
Now they go.
The cards is zero.
They swipe it.
Nothing happens.
You can't write checks.
Right.
They think they can write all the checks they want.
Actually, it's best to let the checkbook go to zero and close the account and then write
checks off of it.
That's another story.
Close the count is even more.
Then it goes directly to the Treasury.
It never goes to.
OK, so.
So all these people that are living hand to mouth, they spent the electric banking, whatever
checks, cards, whatever.
Right.
What do you think they would do if they find out that their own bank was using.
Think about it.
We would end the system right away, which it should be.
It should be.
But anyway.
Yeah.
But it's up to the people to do it.
By the way, the people like this and they don't care.
I brought this up to very, quote, unquote, commoners just above NPC.
They're like, I don't care.
I get what I want.
Well, I don't like it.
I'll tell you that.
I don't like it at all.
That's why.
That's why I'm talking.
You know, when I talk about all the death and destruction that's coming, there's no
way out.
That's the only way to change.
So, OK.
And it's not going to be done by humans, by the way.
You can't because the humans want this to continue.
So, by the way, another thing is when you sign these electronic, you go to a hardware
store, you return something, they want a signature or you write whatever, you sign these electronic
pads.
Right.
In their paperwork reduction act and all that, that signature has to be relayed.
Once it's collected by device, they call it, they call them devices.
It has to go through.
It's OK to go through several third parties and the third parties could also be part of
the bank.
It says.
Right.
Because, you know, it's electronic.
It has to go through a program.
The warranty of the device itself might usually the people who supply the device also supply
the program.
Right.
And they could have various partnerships and relationships, not just vendor.
So let's say you make these signature electronic signature boxes.
Right.
You also be smart to make your own program, too.
And you could be a vendor and sell those devices to the bank or you can go into what with the
bank partnership with the bank.
Right.
Or you could lease it to the bank.
Many arrangements you can have when you supply this equipment.
Right.
You supply the equipment or the data.
Turns out they all go into partnership and they bounce the signature around before.
Oops.
What happens is your signature might end up on a blank contract, like a credit card application
that you didn't even know existed.
Oops.
Would you remember a few years ago, Wells Fargo got busted because they opened up like
four million credit card app credit cards accounts without anyone.
Oops.
You see how this is being done.
I was talking about this and trying to avoid signing a check because electronically they're
using this.
And then a year after I was pushing this, Wells Fargo opened up like was the four hundred
thousand or four million credit card accounts without their people.
It's so stupid.
The system is so open.
They started even sending bills for transactions that never happened because it's all you know,
it's crazy.
Yeah.
Right.
You've heard of it.
The Wells Fargo.
That's that's exactly what happened is people got these notices that they had these open
credit cards with all the stuff on it and they went, I never applied for this credit
card.
What are you talking about?
Yeah, exactly.
Well, but this is being done over and over and over.
Unlimited.
OK.
So.
So what do we do?
Well, first thing you want to do if you don't like the system is don't approve it.
And the way you find out not to approve it is by doing a conditional endorsement.
So when you endorse to sign the name, make a clause before it lawful money only or lawful
money only per 12 USC, USC for 11.
Right.
12.
And what that does, it tells them that now you're operating on a lawful money side.
Now, what happened was you're able to get silver at the banks up until Bretton Woods,
up until the 70s.
Right.
But no one or you can get U.S. notes, but no one asked for it.
No one cares.
By the way, the lawful money, most states in their labor law statutes and codes, when
it talks about wages, it says and wages will be paid in lawful money and issued by check
in person, in cash, electronically, in lawful money.
Actually, the state codes actually say that state codes are telling you it does say in
lawful money.
Yeah.
If you look at.
All of them do in some place.
And all states and countries do have a restricted.
You can you can do a restrictive endorsement.
So when you pay so you can't pay taxes with funny money doesn't pay for anything.
So the reason why people say pay taxes while no one's really paying taxes, what you're
doing is you're filing a return to return a certain amount back.
It's private.
It's not public money.
Right.
Yeah.
And everything that you do is under the penalty of perjury signature.
So if you do something they don't like, there's prison for you because it's perjury has nothing
to do taxes.
Right.
No one is illegally in jail for not paying taxes or evasion.
It's usually if you look at the case, it doesn't say tax evasion.
There is no clause.
There is no crime like that.
It's usually false information to official government official.
Right.
Like Martha Stewart.
People.
You know what?
She was in there.
False information.
Look up the case.
It's the charge.
It's false information.
Not because she whatever they said.
Remember, everyone thinks, oh, she was betting on Wall Street.
No, she she did time because of false.
Right.
Yeah.
They said it was insider trading or so.
No, no.
It's false information.
If you look at the case to a government official while she was being interviewed.
Yeah.
It's always.
OK.
Very interesting.
So very, very interesting.
A couple of more things that the way you're getting you get got is there's a presumption
by the legal.
Now, legal and banking cannot separate the two.
It's the same thing.
Right.
OK.
They're trying.
Right.
So people are trying to separate them, whereas it's all medical and legal is the same thing.
All of it.
It's the same.
It's all controlled by the bar.
It's like a giant trust.
And they're the trustees.
But the thing is, attorneys are dumb as dumb as you know what?
Because you can't let them know what's going on because they're subject to it.
Also, the thing I wanted to bring up is that it's a presumption that everything you're
doing is that there's a lien on it.
Right.
Or when you say you've paid something and you're using these credit just without demand
for lawful money, there's still an attachment because you use their private money.
Right.
OK.
So that's where the clause comes in.
That's why even if you buy a house or whatever, you can't really own it because you use funny
money.
There's certain verbiage, you know, lawful money, some kind of you have to make to do
a separate transaction or notation that you completed and not just discharged, but settled
everything and satisfied everything with lawful money.
Right.
So the other thing is presuming that everything is in commerce.
So for example, property taxes that people pay or even stuff on the car or whatever,
but the property taxes are there of OK, let's just do it in the negative form.
OK, who doesn't have to pay property taxes?
Yeah.
Not if you know only nonprofits, nonprofits, 501 C three.
Nope.
Doesn't say 501 C three.
Well, a lot of just nonprofit.
OK.
Any nonprofit.
You don't pay property tax.
So let me ask you where you live in your house, where you eat, sleep, fuck shit, sleep and
all that stuff.
Are you doing any of that for profit?
Some people might be.
But well, no.
The answer is not.
So why the hell are you paying property taxes?
Because, you know, if you, quote unquote, have right now, they have a problem with that.
And there's another way to handle that, because they're afraid that, well, if they let too
many people go.
And by the way, the money that you pay in property is not one penny goes to do anything.
Right.
Not one penny.
It all goes away.
And you're just showing an account.
You can't.
How do you know?
If you're driving down the street, does it say, thanks for your taxes, paying for the
road?
And this is bonds, the bonds, everything you've bonded.
Right.
They're interested in what you're bonding and get into that video.
David Merrill, the 1913 Federal Reserve, you'll see what he talks about bonding.
I like it because he kind of flips it on people a little bit.
If you feel like you get smacked on the side of the head from him, good, because that's
what he's trying to do.
So everything is supposedly commercial, presumed commercial.
When you do these conditional endorsements, it's kind of like, you know, I'm tired of being
messed with and I know what's going on and you can't provide lawful money.
But I'm asking for it.
So, you know, don't mess with that.
Don't mess with me, please.
On the rest of it.
Right.
They really don't like that.
By the way, again, with the property taxes, they don't want people knowing this for several
reasons.
It's not just that they doesn't matter if no one paid taxes tomorrow, not everything
would be exactly the same.
These services and everything, maybe not because the bankers control the nukes.
If they find out that they have been found out, they'll drop the nukes.
The generals, by the way, you can look up all the generals in the military.
They all have degrees in finance.
There's a reason for that.
Yeah.
Look, come on.
Look up any general right now.
Pick up a general that, you know, look up his Wikipedia page where do you go to college
for and for what finance, because that's where they get you in finance school.
That's how they'd start taking control.
Right.
So anyway, pick any general.
I am.
You'll see.
Yeah.
It's fine.
It's looking right now.
Yeah.
OK.
So anyway, the reason why they don't want you to find out about the property taxes, because
if they admit that they're wrong for doing it now, they have to come up with what the
back taxes that you paid.
That's a lot.
That could be a lot.
Right.
So when you go after them for that, they just I don't want to do it from now on, you know,
and they always ignore you.
But what you do is you drop you drop and make it a federal case because the taxes are county,
local, state, whatever.
So you drop a federal case and you say, listen, guys, you're ignoring me.
But I see this.
I'm sending you a copy of the federal case.
I'm going to be filing in three days.
Let me know what you think.
Oh, finally.
Oh, come and talk to us.
Hmm.
Right.
I was looking up General Petraeus.
He doesn't have a finance degree.
What does he have a degree in?
He has a let's see, a B.S. degree in military science, of course, military science.
He also has a degree in let's see where Petraeus is also one of the last of the old school
ones.
Yeah.
He's got military degrees.
He was one.
He came in on the tail end of the old school, you know, after him.
If you guys are well, just portrays in the 70s.
Got to be right.
Well, let's see.
Petraeus was born in 1952.
So he's 70.
He's barely 71.
Yeah.
OK.
I was just looking him up.
Yeah.
Look at the younger guys in there in their 50s.
Usually you're not going to make general unless you're in your 50s.
What about that General Milley that we see on the news all the time?
What do you think about him?
I don't know.
Never heard of him.
OK.
He was the Joint Chiefs of Staff.
Anyway, let's let's see what we get.
I was just curious about it, you know.
Yeah.
Check it out.
Well, let's just be more accurate then with the finance in indirect proportion of them
are in finance degrees.
OK.
So, yeah, once the bankers find out that, you know, and you want to change, they will
they control the military, by the way.
How do I know?
Well, how does the military get paid?
With what?
With the budget.
Right.
OK.
Where do they get that from?
Right.
Congress approved.
From what?
Federal Reserve.
Treasury puts in the order.
OK.
Police.
I think you guys I think you guys remember where police came about.
Right.
The banks.
The banks took control of the city hall and the state governments.
And they're like, wait a second, we own everything in the state or half of half of everything
in this state.
But if there's a riot or something goes, you know, people get crazy.
That's our property.
You know, what I'm seeing is they get degrees no matter what their main degree is.
They always end up with these other degrees in international affairs, they call it.
Look, that's that new school that that, you know, everybody's going through the past 25
years.
Yeah.
Because I was looking up General Milley here, who, again, let's see, Mark Milley, born 1958.
Wow.
OK.
He's a little younger.
So he's yeah, he's in the 60s.
Yeah.
Well, I'm going for these younger guys that I just know are generals, you know, but OK.
Good.
I'm sorry.
Anyway.
Yeah.
Look around.
You'll see.
And yeah.
So, yeah, that's pretty much it.
So the wonder of international affairs.
You can get in depth in any of these things.
Well, maybe let these two sonics fly.
Yeah.
And I'm wondering, is there a reason to get specific on anything other than things that
directly affect people?
It's important to know that every time you sign something, that's the gold.
Oh, yeah.
No, absolutely.
I'm wondering what a degree in international affairs actually is, you know, because I'm
wondering if that's not exactly what you're saying.
You know, international affairs really just boils down to finance, you know.
Well, yeah, that's what it is.
Yeah.
Basically, I wouldn't say that.
No.
I've seen research.
These guys in the military, upper colonels, generals, admirals, whatever, they all had
degrees in finance.
Right.
Well, here's the thing.
You know, I haven't done this kind of research in over a decade because I don't care anymore.
I got you.
But here's the interesting part of it is that all these guys with these degrees in international
affairs, they have tons of them.
Anytime they're a general that moved up in the government.
Right.
It's vague.
But here's what it's like.
Liberal.
It's like liberal arts.
Yeah.
But here's what it's supposed to encompass.
All right.
It encompasses politics, economics, communications, art, religion and possibly literature.
So it looks to me like a liberal arts thing.
But look at what the second thing that's mentioned is economics.
So it's politics, economics, communication.
So I think that's the.
That's the World Economic Forum stuff.
Yeah.
You know how they're grooming.
What was the other school like the one that the Clintons went to and Rhodes Rhodes Scholar?
Yeah.
Right.
Yes.
They get you through all these.
That's the Cecil Rhodes.
Started that.
Yeah.
Rhodesia.
Right.
Yeah.
Rhodesia.
That's another thing after him.
But right.
Rhodes Scholar.
Rhodesian Redback.
Redback or Ridgeback.
Beautiful dogs, by the way.
One of the most beautiful dogs ever.
Oh, yeah.
And Mel and Melanoise also, which are Belgian.
But yeah.
So Rhodes Scholarship, Rhodes Trust, University of Oxford, because remember, that's where they
sent them.
You know, that's right.
By the way, all the Ivy League.
Look up the history of all the Ivy.
This is a little tangent.
All the Ivy Leagues were either religious schools or families that did it did really
well in the opium trade and wanted to give back, quote unquote, right, and cover their
sins, you know, kind of like Nobel, you know, the Nobel Prize.
He wanted to cover his sins supposedly for coming up with high speed chemistry and by
giving awards, you know, explosions.
Yeah.
It's called high speed chemistry.
That's what it is.
It's measured in feet per second.
It's a chemical reaction.
Yeah.
But common parlance, explosives.
Right.
Yeah.
You don't have to use that word, though.
But yeah.
In other words, if you say high speed chemistry, those that know, know what you're talking
about.
Those that don't know, don't need to know.
OK.
Fair enough.
Yeah.
But I'm looking at the Rhodes Scholarship thing.
It's pretty interesting.
It was established in 1902.
And, you know, again, it's Cecil Rhodes doing this whole thing.
Yeah.
It's all one big club.
Because they know that if they control the money, they control.
Right.
Especially.
OK.
The more urban you are, the more, quote, unquote, society.
Let's put it this way.
OK.
Let's maybe finish off with this.
Was it Karl Marx?
He said that.
I'm paraphrasing that money is one of mankind's most alienated inventions.
Think about that.
Well, yeah.
Because it's disconnected from the thing that it's supposed to represent.
You know, you invented it, but you.
But at the same time, you're trying to get it.
Well, how could.
What do you have to do?
Why are you trying to get it if you invented it?
Why not just print some more?
Here's an interesting thing.
It's not just based on printing out of thin air.
They do keep books and ledgers.
OK.
Well, OK.
Another thing.
The state does this because they're they're a banking institution.
Basically, they're bankrupt.
And you notice how they misprint everything.
Like if you get a title to something, they it's all capsized.
And they never finish the word or rarely do.
Or is it right?
Because later on, if they if there's a, quote, unquote, gathering of these people for being
unlawful and some kind of judicial, they'll say, well, you could see it.
So we didn't.
You can't be the same thing because it's spelled differently, meaning all caps or right, right.
But no real thing in the world in English language is spelled with all caps.
You know, no real thing.
Yeah, it's a fiction.
Yeah.
But it's also Ohio is the only state that has it in there.
There's it's what it's called.
It's a title.
And it talks about fiction has to be in all caps.
It's the only state, I think, that has it.
Yeah.
But that's but that's the reality.
Office.
Yeah.
Has it also.
And that's the reality, though, is if you see something in all caps, it automatically
indicates it's not a real thing.
It is a thing.
But look, they're not doing anything to anyone.
It's this is what everyone prefers.
And the statistic, everyone, the majority.
Right.
So this is the type of society that you live in.
It's it's unethical, immoral, however.
And you wonder why.
Well, because it's on that basis, basis of of the money system.
And of course, anyone might take it.
Let's just go to a Gaddafi in Libya.
You know, he basically knew this and he used it for the people.
Basically, they all got bills and they said, just sign them, send them back.
Yeah.
That was the big problem.
And then he said, well, we'll just make our own money.
And here it was.
What I'll do is I'll lend you my money so you can build stuff and you don't need these
other banks.
Sure.
He cut them out.
That's that's why he had to go.
You know, the little green book he wrote, you know, the green flag of Libya.
Right.
And they tried to, you know, say all kinds of oh, he's a cannibal and he's a killer.
He's a terrorist.
Yeah, of course.
What really he did is he pissed off the bank.
Yeah.
And when they whenever they say something about someone else, it's what they're doing.
Well, of course.
But this is how the people want it.
How do you know?
Just go out, go outside and take a poll.
First of all, 90 percent of people have no idea of money.
They think it's still based on something and at all.
And 90 percent of that 90 percent doesn't care.
Well, that's why that's why I object to you and everybody else talking about the fractional
reserve where it's like, oh, by 10 percent, this and that, because they gave up on that.
They don't even know.
They don't even bother with the 10 percent.
It's the system.
Yeah.
But the system doesn't bother with that anymore.
It's not on 10 percent.
That's the way it started.
Now, it's whatever.
No.
Well, Paperwork Reduction Act, it could be nine hundred to one.
It doesn't matter anymore.
Right.
That's what I'm saying is that.
Yeah.
I think it's silver.
The silver is like nine.
Eighty six to one.
Yeah.
So when you when someone does a commodity silver exchange for a one dollars of silver
becomes one hundred eighty six for the silver market to leverage on the market of silver
production.
Right.
Great.
And they don't need the silver, by the way, for this electronic circuitry and all that.
But it doesn't exist.
I mean, that's the thing.
It just doesn't exist.
It's a measurement.
It's a metric.
But it's on something that isn't in hand.
See, here we go again.
Just like the money, whatever.
They don't need the 10 percent like that.
That used to be a rule.
But no longer.
Chuck, before we go, type in 12 U.S.C. 411 and read it.
The first site that comes up should be Cornell Law and just read it.
It's really short.
OK.
Twelve U.S.C. 411.
Exactly.
That verbiage used to be in the Federal Reserve Act.
They took it off.
Federal Reserve Act.
If you have a book that has the Federal Reserve Act and Constitution, that's SCAN, it has
the same verbiage.
Yeah.
Cornell dot edu.
OK.
Go ahead and read the verbiage.
Has 12 U.S. code and then a symbol there, which I'm not entirely familiar with.
Well, it's section, a section for the title 12, section 411.
It's a little squiggly tilde line.
It's like a weird like it looks like two S's on top of that section.
Section 411.
OK.
Issuance to reserve banks.
Nature of obligation.
Redemption.
Right.
OK.
Is the title of the section.
That's the title of the section.
It says Federal Reserve notes to be issued at the discretion of the board of governors
of the Federal Reserve System for the purpose of making advances to Federal Reserve banks
through the Federal Reserve agents as here in after set forth and for no other purpose
are authorized.
Stop.
All right.
So.
If you just reread that, which you probably don't have to, it gave you the purpose is
supposed to go to the Federal Reserve agents right through the banks and no other purpose
is authorized.
Right.
No other use is authorized.
Do you need an attorney to explain that to you?
No, it's it says for no other no other purpose.
So that means this is the only purpose period.
So but everyone's got Federal Reserve notes in their pocket.
So that can't they're not authorized to use it.
If you're not authorized to use something, you have possession of it.
What is that object considered contraband, contraband, contraband, stolen, ill gotten
this many different things, misdemeanor, misappropriated.
It's a misdemeanor.
Misdemeanor.
Your demeanor is your attitude.
So I continue reading.
Oh, you want me to continue?
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Let's see.
OK.
Here.
The said notes shall be obligations of the United States.
Stop.
Yes.
If you look at if you get a check, it has the bank on top and then it has your name
printed right below it.
Right.
And then you issue the check.
When you pull out a Federal Reserve note, it says Federal Reserve on top and then right
below it says United States of America.
It's a check.
Yeah.
The client.
The client is the United States of America because they're bankrupt.
So they gave him this checkbook.
Go ahead.
Right.
OK.
Let's see.
Shelby.
Whoa.
Hold on.
Let me back up a second.
Start from the beginning.
OK.
The said notes shall be obligations of the United States and shall be receivable by all
national and member banks and Federal Reserve banks and for all taxes, customs and other
public dues.
All right.
Stop.
Who's who can use them for customs, taxes and public dues?
The Federal Reserve agents.
Right.
Yeah.
The only ones that can use it.
That's right.
And I had an attorney get my face.
Well, you can use it.
I said, go see.
See.
First paragraph.
Right.
OK.
Go ahead.
Yeah.
They shall be redeemed in lawful money.
Now, wait a second.
Let's back that up real quick.
They shall be redeemed in lawful money.
Now, let me stop on my own here.
Keep going.
No, keep going.
I'd prefer you keep going.
All right.
No problem.
They shall be redeemed in lawful money on demand at the Treasury Department of the United
States in the city of Washington, District of Columbia or at any Federal Reserve bank.
Right.
Now, stop right there.
On demand, you have to make a demand.
But it takes when you make a demand, it has to be fulfilled by another person.
So if you're alone, right, and you're making demands and the only person in the room, well,
this guy's crazy.
But if you have two people in the room and you're making a demand, that demand goes towards
the somehow influencing the actions of the other, isn't it?
The other person has to be the one making the demands.
So when you show a demand, when you're making endorsements or whatever lawful money on anything,
you're demanding them.
In other words, you are relieved of anything that might be attached.
So if there is a tax liability or some liability after you've shown to make the demand, it's
not your onus.
It's on whoever you made the demand to, first of all.
And second of all, I don't know how this is.
This is kind of hard to say.
How do I want to say this?
Because this opens up a whole other sonic.
It doesn't really make it lawful money because so few people were really demanding silver
or for it that they don't do that anymore.
But it relieves you.
It should relieve you from all the liabilities that if you did a full endorsement now.
Well, not now.
Let me ask my question here, because this is the question I was going to stop at before.
OK, they shall be redeemed in lawful money.
I wanted to stop there because here's the problem.
What you're telling me directly there is that I use these to redeem lawful money.
So this in and of itself is not lawful money right there.
No, no.
That's right.
That's why when I let's say I'm doing a transaction and you do cash, right, that's all I do.
And I the woman looks, I said, you know, where they get the serial numbers on here and this
and that.
This is a check.
Because, huh?
I said, take this to the bank.
You're supposed to take this to the bank and the bank's supposed to give you money for
it.
Yeah.
Well, that's the thing.
And they look at me like, wait, I thought you said it is money.
What are you talking about?
Well, that's the thing.
You're redeeming this thing for lawful money.
It says it right there.
Yeah.
So, OK, let's just this is a very hard thing to wrap up, but a very simple way to do is
go back and listen to David Merrill, how he explains what the bonding process is about.
Because remember, when you're in a public place and it says thanks for the bonds that
paid for these roads and never says taxes.
Right.
It's the bonding.
The other thing I wanted to bring up with reading this section of the title, every country
has something like that.
We found one for Canada and it doesn't talk about lawful money.
It just says that you can make a restricted endorsement.
We found one for Australia.
We found one for the EU.
It just basically says that you should not be impeded on making.
It says account holder, bearer or something of bonds cannot be restricted from making
cannot be impeded on making a restriction.
You know, they use they try to because if you if you have a new something like the EU, which
is fairly recent, not really, but let's say and you make very clear language, people pick
up on it.
Right.
So they kind of make it obscure.
But the whole purpose of this is there is no way out, but there is a better way while
you're in it.
Right.
I got you.
So there's a better way to handle it since it's here and you're here.
Yeah.
Ever since you've known me or whatever, I said, do you make a restrictive endorsement?
Are you just signing these things?
Right.
You've heard me say, right.
Yes, because it does work.
Now, when you make the demand, it's actually you're actually you're influencing someone
else to act on your behalf and you are relieving yourself of any liabilities or restrictions
because you've made the demand, which also means you have to have record keeping good
records.
So whenever you handle cash, like, for example, when I get cash, a person saying, I say, I
need all the notes, the serial numbers on the notes written down and did not denominations.
And if you don't want to write them, you just photograph the bills or whatever, if it's
a money order.
Also, you do the same thing and you keep a record book of that, you know, and you send
it at the end of the year, the Treasury say, look, I've got all these Federal Reserve notes.
Here's the serial numbers, all these checks.
I'm sending you the serial numbers and I need money for this.
What are they going to tell you?
Ha, ha, ha.
We don't have any more money, but it relieves you from any other liabilities.
And now this is very important because a very simple thing like someone saying, well, Greek,
I'm going to 1099.
That's fine.
Just put the full amount on there.
And at the total is zero.
So when you do returns and they told you to itemize, you just itemize, go ahead.
You did one hundred and twenty seven thousand four hundred sixty three dollars and thirty
six cents on this.
And don't even, you know, you want to show expenses, whatever.
And then on the very bottom, the total you put zero and then you have an attachment because
you redeemed everything for lawful money.
But you have to be able to show that you did.
Right.
OK.
And it's really hard to do with electronic transfers.
You need something in between.
Now, I think David Merrill on Lawful Money Trust, it's like eight hundred a year, a thousand
dollars a year because he has a PayPal.
I'm like, how the hell do you do a restriction with PayPal?
Yeah.
Without paperwork.
Because he's doing a paper.
So he must have figured something out.
It might be worth for someone to join that and figure out how he did it and just tell
everybody else.
Yeah.
Because I'd love to know how that works.
With PayPal.
Because I tried to do the PayPal thing and the whatever.
And if you put in lawfully, it has an A.I. that looks at the address, try to put it in
the address box as an invalid address.
I put the address in lawful money, only invalid address, invalid address, invalid entry, invalid
entry.
I'm like, oh, my gosh.
How do you get around it?
I don't get around it.
You want to show that you're making you're not getting around anything.
You're making a demand.
Right.
A lawful demand.
Listen to that video.
It was a 1913 Federal Reserve Act.
Right.
Yeah.
David Merrill.
It's got that annoying buzz.
I think they put that on there deliberately because most people, you know, don't don't
care about the content.
They just, you know, care about the fluff.
Right.
Like if someone sounds like they have to clear their throat, they can't listen to it.
But no matter what the information is.
Right.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
It depends on the individual.
So they made it hard to listen to this YouTube video.
But the information in there is gold.
And he does smack you around a little bit.
You'll you'll listen to him and he'll be like, yeah, but you endorsed it.
You bonded it.
Right.
Like, yeah.
Yeah.
Tell him, man.
Tell him.