Rated Y, Sonic Event, 1-0-3, Ocelli in the Greek.
Anyway, how are you doing, Greek?
I'm doing good.
Listen, I'm excited about cooking because, you know, you do something and other people
get excited, it bounces back, right?
What I made tonight is, by the way, some pretty good responses I've got.
Not that many, but, you know, the ones that came in were pretty good about the cabbage
pot roast, right?
I think two or three Sonics ago, I gave the directions on how to do it.
It's not cabbage, it's how you cook it, right?
So that makes it different.
And what's wonderful is you do that and cut a wedge off of that and make yourself a very
simple spaghetti, make your pasta, and on the side, you make a compound butter, which
is basically compound butter is when you chop things up, various things, very fine,
and mix it with butter.
And the butter is not even pre-melted.
You basically cut the butter up as you're cutting the other, after you cut up the other pieces.
And in the compound butter is black pepper, parsley, and onion, white onion.
I'm surprised you don't make your own pasta, Greek.
I've never heard you mention that you make your own.
Yeah, I do all the time.
You do?
People come over.
Yeah, especially when I make an Asian brothy noodle thing, and the people are always debating.
I once served some people like a ramen, a vegetable ramen broth, and I was listening
to them talk.
I said, I wonder where you got these noodles.
Did you get it over at that Asian market on Pima Street?
And where I'm laughing, I'm like, I just made them.
But anyway, what you do is you chop up the white onion very fine and the parsley, and
then you use a couple of pads of butter chopped in there with some black pepper and salt.
And in the same pot, when your spaghetti comes out into the colander, turn it up high, and
you have that compound butter mixture, and just get it hot as possible.
It doesn't even have to brown.
Add some olive oil, mix your spaghetti in there, and then a little bit of tomato paste
that's slightly watered down.
And you have a very simple pasta.
It's not saucy at all.
You put some really good fresh grated cheese on it, and you serve that with a side wedge
of that cabbage pot roast.
Oh, my gosh.
The food combining there is amazing.
And you're talking about using enough tomato paste and watered down to just make it pink,
basically.
Just make the pasta pinkish, right?
Yeah.
Just to pink it off a little.
Yeah, yeah.
So add a little bit of fat.
Whenever you're cooking pasta, don't use the water that they do in restaurants, huge quantities.
Just have a hot pot of water, so as the pasta begins to cook, you add it.
You just want to cover it, but you have to keep adding, because it absorbs quite a bit.
And as you see, the pasta doubles or triples in size, depending on the cut.
So you add some fat to the water.
You want to add raw sesame oil.
Don't add toasted or olive oil or some butter to the water with the salt.
Nothing wrong with a little olive oil.
That'll go into the pasta.
Yeah, nothing wrong with a little olive oil and butter, both, right?
No, that's a great flavor.
And the other thing is, yeah, I notice a lot of people, when I watch them cook pasta, I
mean, they totally drown it.
You got to look at the pot, and you're wondering what's at the bottom of it, because it's got
so much water in it.
But no, you're right about that.
You only just want to cover it.
Just get it over the pasta.
Also when you start it, you need enough water to hold its temperature, because if there's
not enough water when you start the pasta, the temperature will drop too rapidly, take
too long to boil, and you won't get a good al dente day.
It'll be soggy on the outside.
You know, the yin condition.
So yeah, I just wanted to bring that up, because it's just that combination of just a pink
spaghetti with some onion and butter and parsley chopped up.
Here's the thing.
If you chop up the onion really fine, talking like a mince, and the parsley fine, and you
don't combine it with the butter on the cutting board, it's not going to taste the same.
If you just put the butter in the pan like many people do, let's say they're making pancakes
or eggs or something, and then you add your ingredients, it won't work.
It has to be mixed in cold.
And you can do an experiment.
I've spoken frequently about the cut changes the flavor, right?
Well, an extreme would be puree.
You know, most people have bitten into a carrot, and if you slice the carrot really thin on
a bias, it tastes different.
If you make it matchsticks, it tastes different.
If you grate the carrot, it tastes different.
And guess what?
If you made the carrot into juice or puree, it would taste different again, the same carrot.
So the cut does make a difference.
And the preparation time, again, just to reiterate, with all the star chefs on TV and all the
cooking shows, not one person has learned how to cook from watching that.
You will be entertained by it.
It's just like that TV show they call The News.
It's really entertainment.
So, excuse me, put these little, I don't know, hints and techniques in, because life can
be more enjoyable with good food, and I think it should be.
Oh, absolutely.
I noticed you didn't mention garlic there, though, when you talked about the onion.
No garlic in this.
No, no, that's true.
Garlic's played out.
I had some tuna steaks yesterday.
I made a sushi rice, and the next day I sliced the tuna very thin.
It was broiled, just blackened slightly on the outside for a minute on each side.
I sliced it really thin, had that nice mesquite smoke flavor.
But what I did with the leftover rice, I made some very hot sesame oil with a lot of crushed
garlic until the garlic turned brown.
Then I added the rice and basically did a toasted garlic stir fry with sushi rice and
had the tuna steak on top with some lime and a Thai pepper sauce.
Yeah, I call it pepper jelly, because it looks like a clear almost jelly, kind of like a reddish
jelly with floating pieces of chili in it.
Yeah, very simple.
By the way, the Thai chili sauce, sweet chili sauce and lime go very well together.
So yeah, you've got to enjoy it while you can.
By the way, speaking of enjoying it, I wanted to ... There's not much to address in the
chat other than the food thing and some general questions, but the yin and yang thing will
keep coming up with me until we figure out another way to call it, the process, it's
universal process.
Nothing is completely one or the other, but generally the condition of all organic stuff
is yin.
Plants, animals, people are yin generally, right?
Not as hard as a rock, right?
But within the body of the animal or the creature, the living creature, there is yin and yang.
All nutrition that's taken in, whatever is taken in as nutrition is yin.
Once it's considered to be a form of nutrition, then it's subdivided into yin and yang and
that will tell you which direction it will go.
So it's basically a method for looking at process more than what something is empirically,
right?
Okay.
So nothing is yin and nothing is yang.
It's a way to explain the processes of change.
Wow, I don't believe I got ... I think that's a really good explanation.
Yeah, that is a good explanation.
That's pretty much what it is.
Once you start to understand that ... Here's the thing.
You'll never understand yin and yang unless you work with it.
You have to have ... Yin and yang is something that you either have a working knowledge of
it where you're applying it or you don't.
There's no way you'll take a class somewhere and there'll be a chapter on yin and yang and
then you go to something else and you'll have any idea of how to use it.
It is a completely ... It's a working process.
If you can't work in it, you don't know it.
If you don't know it, you can't work in it.
So it's one of those things.
You said garlic is kind of played out, but one thing that I miss is I used to have these
little things where you could put it in the oven and then it just ...
Yeah, yeah.
A little terracotta thing that bakes it?
Like a garlic butter?
Yeah, and then that turns into just a garlic butter all by itself.
You don't add butter.
You just squeeze it out and boom, there it is.
What I mean it's played out is because it's very ... Well, it's stereotypical when you hear
spaghetti and pasta to have garlic, right?
I enjoy it, so that's why I have it.
Oh, no, so do I, but I have it because I did it yesterday.
But I think of these things also ... When you go to Michelin star restaurants, they minimize
the ingredients, right?
Yeah.
It's the absolute minimum, but it's the best prepared.
You use fewer ingredients and what you're using, have it used in a way where it shines
through and still retains some of its character and you have some contrast, unless you want
to put two things together that make a completely different flavor.
One of those things is I call it cheat and cheddar.
You know how there's cheese dip, right?
Typical of parties.
Well, if you want to make one that's purely vegetable, you take equal parts of miso, any
miso you like, paste, and equal parts of sesame tahini and you just mix it together and it
tastes like ... When I present it to quote-unquote white people, they say,
this is like cheddar dip.
I'm like, yeah, there's no dairy in here.
This is completely vegan, and they call it cheat and cheddar.
Someone ought to just put that together, put it out there.
It'll be pretty big.
It's actually quite delicious because if you go to Japan, for example, where miso is the
most popular, there's miso shops with 500 varieties of miso, broken down from white
miso all the way to very dark, broken down from various types of soybeans.
My favorite miso generally for flavoring, something like that, is a chickpea miso.
If you can find a chickpea miso, yeah, it's out there.
It's quite popular.
Do that with the sesame tahini.
The reason I brought that up, if you taste the flavor of tahini by itself and taste the
flavor of miso by itself, very distinctive, but when you put them together, they form
a completely new flavor.
If you didn't tell someone that was miso and tahini, they wouldn't figure it out.
I love that kind of stuff too, right?
It's a total transformation.
Speaking of transformation, I've gotten some requests to speak about Trevor James Constable
and that kind of work.
There's been some interest, especially the newer people about weather work because I've
gotten into it to a degree, but not in a rudimentary way.
Again, like Eden Young, where you have a working knowledge, and that's what I want to pretty
much discuss.
Ultimately, the more you learn about it, you'll find that it has less to do about working
with the weather and more to do about the soup that we're in, meaning the ether, denying
of the ether.
I've spoken to these Ivy League people.
By the way, Ivy League colleges or universities are brand names, and whenever you bring up
the ether, they really poo-poo it.
By the way, do you know how to game?
You can game the Ivy League, by the way.
It's a quarter of a million to 400,000 to get a degree there.
Once you have one of those, you're a desirable prospect for a lot of corporations.
You can game that system if you're young or if you're in that position before you go there.
I'll tell you how you game it.
Pretty simple.
Let's just pick an industry, the tech industry.
Very good.
All right.
Let's say IT, like Silicon Valley, right?
What you do is you do whatever it takes to apply to Harvard, and if you do really well,
they will send you for free an acceptance letter, and it doesn't cost anything.
You can apply to Harvard, and if you have good grades and recommendations and all that,
you get accepted, let's say, to Harvard, and they will give you that acceptance letter
for free, don't they, right?
So what you do is you take that acceptance letter and you go to Silicon Valley Corporation
and you say, hey, look at this.
I got accepted to Harvard, but I'd rather work for you, and they're looking at the thing
and they're like, okay, great, and they'll start you off just like they would start someone
who graduated from Harvard.
So now you have a Harvard reputation pedigree without paying the ... You see how you can
game the system?
Right.
You don't wind up having to pay the $30,000 a year or whatever it is to go there.
I don't even know what it is.
Because actually, when you get out of Harvard, if you ask most people that have graduated
from Ivy League, that's just part of your education, then you move on to something else.
Like, no, the reason I get this is I could wave it around and get a better entry position,
right?
They said if that wasn't used, in other words, about 90% of them that were able to be surveyed
said that, no, I did it purely so I can get a better position in the workplace.
I didn't do it for just basic education to edify myself at all, because they teach the
same stuff, right?
Right.
So this is how you can game the system.
You could also ... It doesn't have to ... You could be with a technical school, you get
into Northeastern for engineering, go to an engineering firm and say, hey, look, I could
have gone to Northeastern, but I'd rather work for you.
And they'll be like, wow.
They might even, in the lunchroom, the ... What do you call them?
The superiors or the seniors say, we have a Northeastern graduate or a Harvard graduate,
even though you're not.
Because you have enough credentials to also show that you have accepted into that world,
but you also show that you have more ... It's more than motivation.
What do you call it when someone starts out as a good starter on their own?
Potential.
You take initiative.
Yeah, exactly.
Someone who takes initiative.
Because they know that when you go work in a corporation, no matter what university,
after a few years, four or five years of being in that corporation, your education doesn't
matter anymore.
What matters is where you are and what you're doing in the company, right?
Yeah.
What you've done since you've been there now.
Yeah, exactly.
So, yeah.
That's how you can gain that.
Now, I had to bring that up because I run into these Ivy League idiots once in a while.
It's all social positioning, social signaling to ... You signal on from Harvard, or whatever.
They poo-poo the ether big time, and they make up all this flash physics that doesn't
matter and doesn't make sense at all.
So, I wanted to get into the weather work, especially my experience with Trevor James
Constable.
I've worked with him for about ... Up until 2013 or so, until 2016 when he passed away,
we would speak once a week for hours, and he sent me a few boxes, FedEx of his paperwork,
stuff like that.
It's quite interesting.
In the beginning, when I started speaking with him ... By the way, Trevor James Constable,
if you don't know who he is, he's furthered the work of Wilhelm Reich.
Anyway, he was very cautious, and by the three years or so after that, I was building devices
and sending them to him, and he was testing them out and saying, yeah, they worked.
Because a lot of people want to contact the hero worship or whatever, because he was quite
popular with his books and his internet presence that others did for him.
He gets a lot of people contacting him, so I had to, again, not game it, but I said,
listen, I've got some things I want to send you, and he said, no, no, don't bother sending
it.
Don't send me anything.
I'm like, no, I'm going to send it to you, you tell me.
So we had a very effective relationship in this.
But Trevor will always cite the weather work as being from Wilhelm Reich, and let me just
start off.
Wilhelm Reich did the Orgone work.
Now let me just get into this in a minimal way.
This stuff called Orgonite, where you mix this resin with metal shavings, this has nothing
to do with what I'm talking about, because the principle is layering.
It's like an inverted capacitor.
You have a distinct layer, if it's rectangular, box, circular, spherical, whatever it is,
of organic material completely closed upon itself, and then another layer, concentric
or applied to it, of metal, and then again, organic, and then metal.
The Orgonite is a resin where everything is mixed in, there's no distinctive layering,
right?
Yeah, they make that stuff in pyramid shapes, and then there's-
Yeah, it doesn't matter what, yeah, yeah, penis shape, whatever, it doesn't matter.
I don't do that stuff.
Now, it has a place, for example, it's called doping, but that's another thing, it's dielectric
is what it is, and it could be, if you know how to use it, it works well, but that's not
what we're going to talk about, I'd like to talk about, because the internet is flooded
with that stuff, and most of the purpose of it is junk, but it's not junk, it has a purpose,
but it's not with the weather.
So, Wilhelm Reich built these Orgon boxes, he was infiltrated, and by the agencies, because
they don't want to rock it, because, okay, he was a psychiatrist, psychologist type person,
and he stepped out into biology, you can't do that.
Once you have, you can, but you will not progress, so let's say you have a professional degree
in something, you cannot go and do something else, you must stay in that narrow focus,
right?
So, he was bouncing around into physics, biology, psychology, all these things, oh, no, no, you
can't do that, he was infiltrated, because he was viewed as a threat, as others were,
and one of the reasons they didn't stomp him out immediately is because all the devices
he made, his Orgon boxes, which were layered boxes, basically, if you walked into an Orgon
box, it was exposed metal layer, the entire inside was metallic, then adjacent to that
was non-metallic, and then metallic, right, and you finished off with non-metallic on
the outside, metallic on the inside, at least three layers.
Okay, the reason why they kind of left him alone is because these devices work really
slowly.
Okay?
In other words, when you want to, let's say, garner an effect from them, you, whatever
you do with it, usually takes days, if not weeks, to see an effect.
It's not like the hundred-mile-per-gallon carburetor, right, where it works right away,
and you know, or a new weapon, or free-energy stuff, where you hit the switch, and boom,
it's off and running, right?
Nothing like that, it's very slow, typically a couple of days would be to see effect, so,
but it was profound, you know, in view of thinking, but anyone who understands the original electrical
engineering will see it as an unbalanced capacitor, right?
So, what, he was experimenting with this for many years, and the way it got to the weather
work was when he was up at Wrangley, I think it's Wrangley or Wrangley, Maine, he was building
a center, you know, a Rikian center for himself, in the country, because he knew that it was
the best place to be, away from the city, especially the experiments he was doing.
Part of the construction project involved like pipes, stove pipes, you know, those thin
galvanized steel pipes, right, four-inch diameter, like flue pipes, right?
Well, he was there on the site, and he noticed when some of these sheet metal pipes and other
types of pipe were delivered, there was a ditch that was going around some of the property,
you know, to prepare it for foundation work or wall work.
When one of the pipes fell into the ditch, where it slanted upward, it was still pointing
fairly upward, but the tail end of the pipe was in water in the ditch, and he saw that,
and he looked up at the sky, and it was a cloudy day, and he distinctly saw a hole in
the cloud forming, and he made the two connections, and he said, well, you know, if I move the
pipe the other way in the ditch, will the hole form on the other side?
And it did.
So he's like, oh, so you put a metal pipe in water, and you get a hole in the clouds.
So this was basically an accidental...
Yeah, just like Viagra and penicillin and Post-Its and escalator, in a way.
Start trying to use something for one reason, it turns out, hey, wait a minute, it does
something else.
He wasn't even trying to use it, it was a very superficial, you know, pipe delivery to a
construction site.
No one's paying attention to this stuff, right?
Right.
Go ahead.
Sure.
Yeah, so this is...
So it was by accident.
By the way, this is important.
Now, fast forward is just another thing kind of jumping around.
One of my mentors, when I first started getting into this stuff 25 years ago, or 24, 22 years
ago, was a guy named Joe Blankenship in Tucson, and he was really cool.
He met, well, actually more, he met Victor Schauberger, President Nixon would call him
every day after he got out of office, as a buddy-buddy thing, he was well-connected.
Howard Hughes, Joe Blankenship's mom had a diner here in Tucson, and Howard Hughes would
patronize it, and before he would go in to have lunch, he'd send his guys in there and
pay her for an hour's worth of business, because they'd close the diner when he was there.
Yeah, that's the kind of thing Hughes would do, right?
Yeah, yeah, he paid for the...
Yeah, so basically, a burger cost him $50, back then it would be like $500 or whatever.
So anyway, cool story as well.
Joe Blankenship was running around in these circles, so when Reich came to Tucson in 52-53,
Joe was young, and he wanted to meet him, because he already heard about him, and Reich spoke
very little English, so Reich needed to be shown around, he says, I'll show you around,
and he ended up being Wilhelm Reich's driver, while for the couple of years that Reich was
in Tucson and built a house up on the northwest side and all that.
So he drove around Tucson and turned into a job for him, because he was going to move
to Tucson.
Well, yeah, well, he came here to show off, to break the drought, he had already discovered
the cloud buster prior.
I'll mention one thing that you won't find on the internet, Wilhelm Reich was a nudist,
and Joe would tell me he hated that, because they'd arrived to the house that they built
that they were staying in, it was a lab in a place that he lived here in Tucson, Wilhelm
Reich did.
So Joe would go and unload the car, groceries or whatnot, and Wilhelm Reich's already in
the house, and Joe comes in with the groceries and all the supplies and whatever food that
they went out for, and there's Wilhelm Reich totally naked laying down on the couch with
a cigarette.
It wasn't even in the house two minutes, right?
So Joe didn't like it, he was, ah, I'm not into that, right?
So you know, whatever.
So it was quite aloof, and it was pleasant to be around from what I got.
All right, so that's pretty much the story of Wilhelm Reich, now, Trevor James Constable
had picked up on this, and Trevor James Constable knew, by the way, I'm not going to get into
how the cloud buster works, there's plenty of stuff online, it's basically pipes connected
to grounded in water, okay, there's many elaborate ways to build it.
Someone posted a picture of an aluminum one with rods and extended, in the chat, I did
not make that, no.
But Trevor was working on a merchant ship, he was a radar man, and he was playing around
with this in the ocean, it worked very successfully.
And he had running water and hoses and stuff on deck, and the captain said, you know, I'm
tired of this water running all over the place, you know, you got to keep a ship very tidy.
So he says, stop the operation, and that kind of bummed him out, but he's like, no, I have
to figure out a way to do it waterless.
So what he did, basically, you can find information about this also online, is Trevor James Constable
basically did the layering effect that you find in a orgone box, metal on one side, non-metal
on the outside, metal on the inside, non-metal on the outside, and started building these
things called translators, and evolved to the point where when you make a tube like
that, metallic on the inside, non-metallic on the outside, with a double mirror on the
end, you know, the business end is open, the back end is a double mirror, what I mean by
double mirror is, you know, a mirror facing inside the tube, and then a mirror on the backside
facing out, right?
And we'll simulate when you're moving on a moving vessel, and it worked well, he tried
many geometries and stuff, and now we've evolved it to the point where I say, we even
back then, and I still make them for people, even recently, someone, I sent one that was
about less than a foot long, two and a half inches in diameter, person sent me photographs
of a rainstorm, right, recently, with that device, and also you can do with towing, you
have to be on a moving, let's say, airplane or a car, it's more difficult in the car because
you're on the ground, less atmospheric effect.
What happens with these devices, call them P-guns, potential guns, I call them translators,
there's stuff online about that, there's a PDF you might be able to find, Loom of the
Future, it'll be posted in the chat as a PDF, it's called Loom of the Future, it's Thomas
Joseph Brown, it's basically a transcript of Thomas Joseph Brown of Borderlands, interviewing
Trevor James Constable.
But anyway, when you operate one of these in a car, you can make, actually the larger
they are, the better they work, but the small ones work well, well enough.
What you can do is tow a storm, so let's say you're in a, you're driving and it's raining,
and you know where you're going to, it's not going to be raining, or you turn around and
go back home, these devices will have the storm follow you home or wherever you go.
I call it towing, and so did Trevor, it's quite an interesting phenomenon, right?
So you could literally go to a place where it's raining and bring the rain to a place
where it's not raining, within a certain reason, because all these weather events, whether
it's a hurricane, a drizzle, a sunny day, are pulsations in the natural environment, right?
They have a buildup charging point, and then they discharge, right?
That's rain, basically, right?
So you have to understand that aspect of it.
Now, what is so interesting, this is working with what we call the ether, the soup that
we're in, we're in this stuff called the ether, which is not a stuff, it's an organization
of conditions that we call material, energy, our existence, and all that, and somehow,
the unbalanced capacitor, you know, the layering of metal and non-metal material, seems to excite
an area of influence, right?
Whether if it's a closed organ box, it'll be inside the box.
If it's open on one end and you can direct it, it'll excite the area where it's directed
towards, right?
And it excites it in a way that is not completely understood, but it's repeatable, and because
it's repeatable, if you're a really good observer, and you take notes of what's happening,
you make a list of effects, right?
And now you know what you can do with this device, and we call it the ether, right?
Because there's always a debate about it.
Now, with Trevor, he leaned very, very heavily on the dry devices, which is just basically
an orgone device, dry, but with conversations with him, he would call me sometimes, he would
watch a parade, and well, he knew like a holiday was coming, and there was going to
be a parade, and he'd call me, and he'd say, hey, you know, there's going to be a parade
in two days in New York, or whatever, why don't you make it rain on the parade?
And I was like, okay, there's no rain in the forecast, he says, yeah, I know, that's
why I'm calling you, because he was 90 years old at the time.
And I said, okay, so I make it rain, right, from Tucson to New York City, right?
So what, but on a call like that, we had already evolved to the point where I had conversations
prior with him, what device to use, and there's no substitute for a large water gun.
What I mean by a large water gun, a large water-based cloud buster, the kind of pictures that you
see where either multiple tubes, I think a large galvanized tube is more efficient.
You know how the geometry, pi D and pi R squared, right, the relationship of circles, right?
If you double the diameter of a circle, it's four times the area, right?
So like a four-inch or a six-inch stovepipe, a quality galvanized pipe, or like they use
it for air conditioning ducts, but the heavy ones, the wound ones, are far more efficient
than, let's say, a grouping of three-quarter or one-inch pipes.
And don't use copper, don't use, it should be, a magnet should stick to it, it should
be ferrous-based.
There are other things also, but copper doesn't work as well, that's another discussion.
So you're better off with the one with the larger diameter?
Yeah, more efficient, yes, in most cases, yes.
I do like the smaller diameter, they work well also, but not as efficient for portability,
because you can take them apart and have a small bundle of pipes, right?
Right.
And they're easier to break up into sections and couple them, and use couplings that fit
with friction than a large pipe.
So the smaller diameter are more efficient for packing on the go, and the larger diameter
is more efficient for just large field work.
The one that I predominantly use is an eight-inch pipe that's 12.5 feet long, on a tripod, it's
water-fed, it's water-fed with a mister, and it's grounded, there's a ground rod on one
of the hoses from the center body that goes down 10 feet, and there's another 10-foot
iron rod, it's actually a one-inch conduit, steel conduit, driven into the ground, and
it's filled with magnetite, and then I have wires that go from the bottom of that pipe
that's filled with magnetite, so you want a really good ground.
Just like if you read Tesla's Colorado papers, they couldn't get the experiments going until
you got a really good ground, the soil was too dry, so they had to dig these bores and
fill them with water for days to get lower the resistance, so you can get a good ground
into the earth.
So that's what I use and would use, and I've also done that to abate hurricanes, and whatever,
you can go through the earth.
So my experience with Trevor was, even like the stories I've heard from Joe Blankenship
about Wilhelm Reich, the internet is a good introduction point to get you a roundabout
working knowledge, maybe, but not enough to sort things out.
This is where you would need someone who knew Wilhelm Reich or Trevor to be in a community
situation where people can raise questions and whatever, because let's say you have
a group of people that want to do weather work, right?
They go online and research it, you'll find dozens of websites.
Some of them are pretty good, some are better than others, right?
I wouldn't say there are any bad ones, because they, you know, that are not, you know, maybe
whatever.
And you have a community of people interested in doing weather work based on Trevor James
Constable and Wilhelm Reich, just from internet, you're not going to, you can do, you'll be
able to make holes in clouds and you might make a bad weather, right, when it's unintended,
but you won't have the finesse and the understanding of what is really priority and what's not.
For example, if you research Trevor James Constable online, you will get the feeling
that you need to make these potential guns, you know, basically a metal tube wrapped with,
you know, a couple of feet long or a foot long, with a mirror on the back, and that's
the be all end all.
It's not.
You have to understand what you want to do, and what I want to bring up, and speaking about
this, with all the development that Trevor did over 50 years, let's say 35, 40 years
on the P guns, potential guns, the dry method, which is based on Wilhelm Reich's organ box.
He agreed every time that for a long distance or a big operation, you need to go back to
a water gun.
And the best and most efficient would be a large stovepipe type thing.
And this has been proven over and there's nothing like that.
You won't find that little bit of information online.
So what's important is to run into people that know Trevor and work with Trevor, Wilhelm
Reich, to give you not necessarily advice on what to do, but to at least say what they,
you know, those other people had said about it, right, and also from your own experience.
So but ultimately, my experience with Trevor was, when I first met him on the phone, he
was very standoffish, like, don't try to do weather work, you're just going to make bad
weather or won't work. Or, you know, by the time he passed away a few years later, he
was calling me to make bad weather.
But it was very not not in a way like just make bad weather, but like to target a parade
or something, right. Or stop the snow.
Another one was he called me and he said, you know, they're shutting down New York City.
This is in 2015 or 1615, I think, or 16, OK, the winter, they're shutting down New York
City because a big snowstorm is coming.
I said, is it so started yet?
Says, no, we'll be there tomorrow.
Why don't you do something about that?
Why don't you stop the snow?
And I did. I don't know if you remember, they even preemptively shut down New York.
And after that, the weather people got in trouble.
And it was very popular. So because we were using the European computer model, right?
Yes, I don't remember that in 2015.
Yeah, that's what that was.
Yeah, that's what Trevor calls me.
And he says, go ahead and do something.
Make stop the snow.
It might have been 16, 16, 16.
Yeah. So he would you know, there was like an Easter parade.
Once you rain on their parade, you know, and we rained on their parade.
Right. So but this is a full time job, you know, for it's going to take a day.
I mean, you really have to pay attention.
These devices, especially the water gun, you cannot lean into it.
And right. Called it drilling.
You cannot leave it in one place for too long because then the ether, the environment will
ignore it. Case in fact, if you look at houses that are being built, they have plenty of
these chimney stacks that are metal that go up vertically.
Right. Right. Those are ignored.
Those are not making weather.
Now, they will change the weather initially when you build suburban houses or a city
somewhere. The weather will change.
That's a fact. Very well known.
But because you have the same stovepipe as he has on his chimney or his hot water, his
water heater or his fireplace using the same thing and waving it around, he's doing the
same thing you are, because when you leave these devices stationary for too long, especially
I'm speaking mostly on the water grounded ones, the environment will ignore them.
Right. So you have to understand the subtleties of movement and the ebb and flow and
when to push. By the way, you can I think which it's clear is you can use these devices to
stop bad weather or to make bad weather, right?
Like, for example, tornadoes are some of the easiest things to make downwind.
Right. So.
But yeah, so it's a there's a wide gamut, but there's a lot of subtleties.
Now, if you have the Trevor's devices, the dry guns, the small translator tubes with the
mirror on the back, there is a benefit of aiming those horizontally or slightly up from
horizontal in a general direction to generally change the season slightly.
So if you know what's going to be, those can be left in position for as long as a week or
two. But the water guns cannot be left in the same position for more than 20 minutes to
an hour. You must move them.
Now, what I what I suggest about that is let's say you have you make a P gun, a translator,
which is basically a metal tube with non metal wrapped on the outside.
Trevor James Constable style with a double mirror on the back on a tripod.
Let's say, you know, it's going to be a cold winter, right?
Oh, it's going to be a cold winter.
Oh, no. You set one of these up.
It could even be indoors.
And you have it aim west.
And every day you nudge it a little bit towards the north.
You nudge it all towards the south for about two weeks.
Aiming west will whether this works, whether you're on northern or southern hemisphere.
Will create a slight warming trend.
And you're going to really baffle and change that.
Oh, it's going to be a really cold winter thing, although a really cold winter didn't
come. Right. So you can do it like that.
Another thing is, let's say, oh, it's going to be a really hot summer.
Heat waves coming. OK, well, you have a similar device on a tripod indoors.
It could be and you aim it east because when you aim it east, it creates a cooling trend
because it blocks things from passing slightly.
Right. And when you accumulate the ether, it has a cooling effect.
Right. When you rarify the ether, it has a heating effect.
Usually that's why deserts are places that are typically rarified ether.
And they're typically hot with a little bit of sun place like the rainforest, which is
concentrations of ether is typically cool.
Now, most people won't think so.
But if you're in a rainforest, it's hot and humid, but it's never as hot as it will be
in the Sahara or the Mojave Desert.
Right. So that's basically the small and long of it in a short way of what I got from
working with Trevor is a summary, basically, of that.
And I continue. I don't continuously do weather operations, but anyone can go online and
see what all that's about.
As a matter of fact, what spurred me on to do this is something someone posted greening up
things. It's a German website on.