Sonic Event 37, Ocelli in the Greek, Rated Y.
So, a lot of things could be going on, a lot of things are going on.
How are you being trained?
Are we going to get into that tonight?
I don't know.
Let's find out.
There's a bunch of things we could get into.
Greek, how are you doing, first off?
I'm doing all right.
I was wondering how you were doing.
You sound a little congested, but I asked you about are you eating too much ice cream
and you laughed.
I guess I take that as a no, but this is something I haven't brought up.
This has been very well known for a long time, but dairy, by the way, the more dairy consumption
you see in a society, other than people growing really large, is occurrences of people with
depression, in terms of depression, not like your belly button, if it's in any, but depression
as in the psychological condition that they dub.
Right?
Right.
The way that it's been described to me about the use of dairy, because what is the sense
of taking the milk, which practical purpose, right?
Let's look at its practical purpose.
You take the milk from the cow, which is meant for the baby cow, okay, nature has a use for
this.
Why would you do it?
I imagine that it initially was developed as a way of just being able to survive at
a time of year when you weren't able to harvest as much, and that would be the practical point
of it, and then it becomes something else, right?
You could say ovolactic, eggs and milk, you don't have to kill the animal.
You can harvest from the animal, you don't have to kill them, so you have a resource
which is, I hate to say this, but sustainable, right?
Because you can continuously harvest from it something, and also, it's not necessary
to grow an entire other calf or whatever to harvest the animal directly, so you get it.
Well, as long as you, like people, if you keep milking them, they're going to keep
producing milk, right?
But there's the thing.
There were women that went around, right?
Back in the days.
They continue to be wet nurses even after the time of them feeding their babies because
they keep the process going.
Yeah, exactly.
It's an impulse.
Induction.
So you need, you know, Wilhelm Reich talked about when you have mechanical movement creates
an electrical charge, and then you have a biological discharge.
Yeah, and you know, that's another level of induction and that process that could be
talked about at some point, you know, because look, the body takes in and then creates through
induction certain things and then is able to put something back out.
You know, I'm talking about the practical process.
So there's something about the functionality of the body.
Of course, only women do this, although there is a weird thing that happens sometimes to
men where they kind of produce a little milk or whatever because their hormones are off,
right?
But there was a South Park one when they were looking for semen, and Eric Cartman says,
if I go into the alley, I can drink it out of a, to get it out of a straw.
Yeah, this fool gave it to me for free.
I just had to go in the alley and suck it out of a straw.
Oh my gosh.
Oh my God.
That's pretty bad.
I never, just cut that part out, you know, later, maybe, yeah.
So the, the induction, you have the prime mover, which is the mechanical one, but then
most of the stuff that's going on in the body does not require a prime mover other than
the presence of the soul, the metabolism.
Now initially it's very easy to, let's say, hmm, implement examples of the induction
implementing useful, uh, by the mechanical stuff, even to the point where you graph trees,
you can have a tree that has various fruit on it where they graph branches from other
trees and it heals up and it, uh, it takes to the original tree.
So, but then there's the induction that is very subtle and it's like the ether base
that's in the soul, meaning a living being does like, you know, you know, you're not,
you know, people talk about it.
If you're eating a meal, they say, yeah, I'm digesting, but you're not really taking part
in digesting.
You, you know, you just say you are, right?
You're not really functioning in that way.
It's just functioning and you trust it, right?
Well, it's an automated, it's a process that has nothing to do with you about the decisions
beyond what you've decided to put into the equation.
Then the body just takes over and does what it does, right?
Autonomous.
Yeah, exactly.
That's when you start learning that and how to create impulses on that.
Now you go to the next, like I was speaking with someone in engineering and he's like
another octave or two octaves up, right?
And that is, requires very subtle thinking and it requires a group effort, meaning not
group with people, but grouping into the environment.
Speaking of which, this was really what I was thinking about venting and ranting about
tonight.
Regarding the dairy stuff, right?
No, not dairy.
Actually, it might, might tie in eventually, but people buying new stuff instead of fixing
old stuff.
Yeah.
I brought this before.
Don't buy.
If you can avoid buying new stuff, avoid fix it.
If you've got it.
Here's the thing.
Most people are, okay, this, well, I'll just finish the sentence.
Most people are disencouraged because they say it's not worth the money to invest to
fix it.
Buy a new one, right?
That's the common.
Yeah.
A lot of times.
Right.
Yeah.
I suggest not even if it caught, if you think it costs more, it stay with that and go ahead
and fix it.
Number one.
Number two.
Again, from speaking with an engineer today, kind of hit me and it was like the 10th person
that said this in a few months, I wanted to talk about it.
Planned obsolescence.
When you have a problem in industry that makes parts wear out or break down, manufacturer
won't address that because he wants you to buy another one.
Right.
So the assumption is they won't make something good enough to last.
You know, they could make a screw, anything from a screw to a complex machine that could
last forever.
But why do that if you can sell somebody 10 of them in the course of their lifetime
instead of just the one, right?
Or let's say, for example, with pumps and valves, you have, instead of offering one
pump and one valve to everyone, let's say you offer two types, one for, let's say, sweet
water and one for hard water, right?
One that builds up minerals and has got a lot of salts and then one that doesn't.
So this way, it's more custom tailored to their situation and it'll last longer where,
let's say you make one pump and you sell it to the public, you'll notice that the ones
that have hard water keep coming back broken.
Well, you know, why don't you address that?
And they're like, oh no, that's how we make our money.
That's how we up our production, you see?
So this is already built in.
Now, most of the people below mid-level management don't know this.
They do.
It's spoken throughout the whole field, it's known, but no one presses about doing anything.
So when I was growing up in the 60s and 70s, I think I was already grown up in the 80s,
I would say that there was something going on called boycotts and strikes, right?
Okay.
And you don't see that anymore.
And two reasons.
One is the society has changed in terms of the programming, the brainwashing.
And the other thing is, I believe that those were not organic movements.
I think those were also co-opted.
They were engineered, you know?
Well, a lot of times it is by some people that are looking to compete in a corporate sense.
And we've seen that revealed before, right?
Where somebody causes a boycott, a sort of an outrage of the moment, not like the idiotic
things we see today where it's just something that's triggered based on a public statement,
but literally there's something going on, right?
A company has a backlash because they knew, and somebody else makes sure that people know
that that company knew that they were releasing a product that would do harm, right?
So their competitor turns around and releases information to show that that company knew
it.
Well, workers strike because they're not happy with wages, let's say, was the main one.
Right.
I think people are too apathetic.
But there were whisper campaigns that went on there with the workers too, you know?
And that's another way, like not just engaging with the public and trying to manipulate their
responses, but maybe specifically targeting workers, right?
And saying to yourself, well, look, I want to disrupt this manufacturer over here because
that way they'll have a harder time competing with me.
And if I knock out part of their human resource department, so to speak, they'll have delays
and issues, in which case my company comes in, fills the gap there where people still
need said product or think they need it.
I think it's beyond the companies.
I learned this a long time ago.
So maybe now it's more, but if you have a company, by the way, if you have a company
and you want to shut it down, it's more work to shut it down than to start one.
Oh, yeah.
Always.
Anything.
It's more work to shut it down.
Because you're taking their monetizing it.
They have that as collateral.
Right.
The collateral.
Anyway, you actually signed it over to them.
That's why here I'll give something out.
If you want to really set something up, you could do a C-Corp.
Don't do the LLCs like they say.
Whenever they tell you something's in vogue, don't do that, because then that holds you
personally culpable.
You do like a C-Corp, even an S-Corp, and you have more than one person in there.
Never have just one person.
Set it up just like a trust, right?
And then you have a trust involved in it, and the beneficiary of the trust is the United
States of America.
So if they want to come and attack you, guess who else you see?
Oh, they have to attack themselves, which.
Yeah.
So you're actually.
Well, no.
They're not.
They're foreign.
All attorneys with a bar card.
This is the truth.
You could look this up.
Well, it might be hard to find.
All attorneys, bar none, no pun intended, with a bar card, are unregistered foreign agents,
which is a no-no, by the way.
Yeah.
I was just going to say, technically speaking, that would be one of those things that's illegal.
That's why I keep saying there is no one legally in prison, especially no one is lawfully in
prison at all.
That's for sure.
Using any kind of system.
So yeah, I'm not saying that a typical idiot would say, Greek, you're saying no one should
be in prison?
No, I'm not saying.
Yeah, actually, I am saying that no one should be in prison because there's no reason for
prison.
Right?
Right.
So yeah.
You know, the laws already has provisions for that.
But it's a legal function, not a lawful function.
Right.
Which is money.
Yeah.
So if you make the United States of America very important, the America part, a beneficiary
of anything you're doing, it's going to take like balls the size of Mount Everest to come
and try to penetrate what you're doing.
Right.
And also, if you try to do everything with private contract, you're not operating under
privilege.
So these are other discussions.
These are long discussions.
I do have not as much as I used to.
I talk to people in the corporate world and I have conversations and I bring these things
up and they're like, oh, my gosh, I never heard that before.
It makes total sense.
I said, yeah, because it's so simple.
So anyway, what they're doing with the corporations, if you're more than one hundred and fifty
million, you get infiltrated.
In other words, there's divisions.
Yes, there's divisions.
And when you most people use the word CIA, they don't know that that broke off from the
army.
That was a division of army intelligence that broke off after the Roswell event.
And people don't know that the Air Force is a break off from the Army Air Corps.
There's plenty of people that do if you live in a military town.
But after Roswell, they wanted to hide that there were Japanese prisoners of war flying
their advanced craft, see their craft.
Americans and white people had a hard problem flying their their craft because you laid
in a supinated position.
In other words, you laid flat on your stomach and you had two joysticks and the whole cavity
of that for you to squeeze in was less than 18 inches.
And these people were small.
You know, the average Japanese person was five foot zero back then.
And, you know, an adult Caucasian couldn't even get in there, you know.
So anyway, they flew those things around Roswell and they crashed them deliberately.
Suicide run to get away from the American prisoners.
By the way, the Americans are playing really dirty during World War Two.
You know, you've seen movies about American prisoners of war in Japan.
What was the thing about the bridge River Kwai or something like that?
But the Americans hardly had any Japanese prisoners.
So they went to the largest populated city of Japanese outside of Japan, which is Sao
Paulo, Brazil.
And they started kidnapping Japanese people, really dirty, really dirty, very, very dirty.
But anyway, all these imperial powers play very dirty.
The Turks played very dirty.
The Romans, the Greeks.
So, you know, whenever you hear of an empire, imperial, you know, yeah, well, hopefully nobody's
getting offended.
But here's the bottom line.
I mean, in Brazil, you can pay off anybody to do anything just about.
So it's you know, that makes it easier here, too.
I think I heard the prices for the 80s.
It was 10 grand to get a hit, man.
And then it went up by the 2000s to 50.
I hear it now.
It's below 10 grand again.
So, yeah.
It's apparently gone cheaper.
That's what I hear.
It's like 1970s prices.
My gosh.
Right.
Don't ask me how I hear these things.
But, you know, I look at what is in the head, right?
The voices in your head.
Oh, yeah.
You know, I'm imagining this, but I'm not imagining it.
Yeah.
I got you.
That's right.
So.
So, yeah, they take control the way I've seen it firsthand.
The public cable access TVs, they they put an army intelligence person in there, usually
a woman because the least suspected because, you know, when you see certain people, you
presume they have a military when they say they have a military career, you kind of presumed
it anyway.
Right.
Very rarely do people presume women have military careers.
Very rarely.
There are different presumptions for women anyway, if you notice.
I mean, in any in any circumstance, I've noted often that, you know, like, say, homeless
women are treated differently than homeless men.
You know, for instance, people spend a little more time talking to them.
They don't dismiss them as easily.
They're a little more sympathetic.
You know, there are automatic ideas about women.
And I also have noticed that homeless women typically are in much worse shape than homeless
men.
Yeah.
Typically, most of them are true, true.
But they also are given more by the general public.
You know what I mean?
There's just a more sympathetic default position.
Women are just treated differently, is all I'm saying.
Yeah.
So what I've witnessed is despite what politically correct idiots want to tell you about how
we're all, you know, exactly.
No, we're not.
And the thing is that there are certain defaults to that.
And one of the things you're talking about here regarding the military background.
Yes.
The first assumption is that women don't automatically have a military background.
People don't presume that they do.
They don't make that presumption.
And the other thing is they're also seen as less threatening because, you know, matter
of fact, point of fact, the general population.
A man is a little more capable of violence with the better upper body strength.
And here's the interesting thing.
And this has been written about for many, many years ago as well.
Centuries ago, women make a better army because they would go in and get the job done.
They won't rape and pillage like men do.
Right.
There's that.
So they're actually more efficient, more of a threat because of these things.
We've also noted that they more efficiently use like things like water.
You know, a certain circumstances, you can find that their their bodies are just better
set up for certain things.
Yeah.
Their attitude.
There are two races.
The two races are there's man and woman.
Right.
OK.
So.
So anyway, we're not getting into the story.
There's no necessary for it.
They do plug these people in corporations, usually mid-level management, where the jobs
don't get rotated and things like that.
And they could make or break a company.
In other words, you go along with the plan like a perfect example is the the coviditis
or the crony, the crony virus.
Right.
Yeah.
It just happened.
Right.
One hundred and twenty CEOs quit in January.
They announced it in March.
Right.
Exactly.
And one hundred and twenty or something, maybe more, maybe less around there.
Quit.
Big companies quit in January.
They knew it was coming and how all the companies were in on it.
Right.
Yeah.
Like as if they were on lockstep.
Right.
It's a heads up phenomenon where it seems like, gee, you see a trend where a whole bunch
of people got out of a certain business right before it crashes.
You know, this kind of thing.
There's a heads up circumstance.
Yeah.
They didn't want to.
They didn't want to play.
They gave it.
Well, those guys got the option.
You play along or you leave.
And they said, I'm leaving.
Yeah.
You know, they get certain.
Some people don't get options.
It depends on how they start with you.
Right.
Well, I think sometimes they also just get told, listen, this is the way things are
going to be.
You do what you want.
And some people make a calculation.
Hey, listen, I don't want to be involved in this.
I got to go.
So I think all these people like the richest people in the world, people think that, you
know, who's the richest man where there is none.
These people are told what to do consistently.
I did some work for a woman a long time ago and her sister recommended her sister.
I did some mural work, artwork, restoration of plaster work.
And I get there like eight, eight thirty nine in the morning, start working.
And she's already having some wine and reading a book.
Right.
And it's very quiet.
And I asked her what she did.
And basically, she goes, she want to tell me.
But her sister was there one day and she says, tell him, you know, it's cool.
And basically, the sister told me the whole story, which I'll make it really short.
She punched a few numbers on a keyboard.
This is in the 90s, the wrong numbers for some reason.
And because of that, she doesn't you know, she got fired, but she also is going to be
taken care of.
She doesn't have to get another job once you're fired.
Right.
But it's not going to be like what she was basically what she was doing was I've mentioned
this many times before.
You got a guy like Bill Gates or Jeff Bezos or the really other rich people you hear about.
Right.
They have influence, public influence.
And they're told they should go and talk about this policy change in whatever light they
want it spoken on.
If they don't agree, their bank account goes to zero.
And the way they do that is there's someone on a keyboard that does that.
Right.
And the intelligence agencies, by the way, you know, have control over the banks.
They're a function of the bank.
And then so what they know when, you know, they're even back then when you check a bank
balance on the phone or whatever, they know you just checked it and then the moment you
check it and Jeff Bozo, let's say, goes down to zero, he gets a phone call right away.
And all they have to say is, are you going to reconsider now?
What do you think he's going to say in this?
Here's more proof of that.
I think less than a year ago, Bozo came out and said he's going to give all his money away.
Something like that.
Right.
It was really after the divorce, because he's worth like one hundred and fifty billion.
I'm going to give it all away because he wants to get another one was Prince.
You know, he was packing up a bag and all this stuff to buy an island or go somewhere
far away.
Right.
And he gets a call.
What do you think you're doing?
You can't do any.
Yeah.
None of these people that are rich and famous have any control over their finances at all.
They're given some cash, some cash, you know what I mean?
And this and that.
Here's another example.
There's something that came out a few years ago, 50 cent everything he has, jewelry, car
house, everything's rented.
Yeah.
Do you remember that?
I don't know.
Maybe.
I just want to ask you if you remember these things.
I wonder if I'm imagining it or Mandela effect or whatever.
Right.
You're not imagining it at all.
You know, there was even if you want to go to something a little more current, you know,
Kanye West.
Right.
People forget about this part of the story because they focus on, you know, the whole
thing.
He showed up.
Oh, you know, I like Hitler.
Blah, blah, blah.
Right.
They did all that.
But that was, you know, Kanye saying that with a mask over his face.
But when they when they did all that, there was part of the story where they said, you
know, something like, I don't know, five hundred million dollars or whatever or what he had
just suddenly disappeared, was gone like bank accounts were just taken.
Yeah.
There is.
There's nothing there.
Yeah.
Well, just digital.
We're in the worst kind of situation we've ever been in.
But at the same time, it seems like we're not.
Right.
So he did something that was not according to what he was told.
And therefore, they said, hey, you know, why don't you check your circumstance again and
see if you still want to keep doing that?
And, you know, I'm pretty sure, actually, he stopped whatever it was.
Everybody's focusing on, you know, as per usual, look, a distraction.
But yeah.
But what I'm saying about they have nothing and at any moment they could go down to zero
is not a presumption.
It's been shown many ways.
I mean, we don't need more concrete, let's say, evidence or beyond, you know, because
when I when I first heard this 30 years ago, almost now, it made total sense to me, made
total sense, because, you know, I knew back then we're living in a fake world or, you
know, controlled world.
I just didn't think it was that fake because how much energy it takes to control so many
people and you really don't have to.
You just have you control a few people that control others, right?
A whole mass of others.
And you keep them peaceful until it's not right to be peaceful.
But back to the theme that I wanted to discuss, stop buying things, fix it.
Don't even a car.
I hope you're doing well with your car there.
Got all the parts.
And I'm trying to encourage people to work on most.
If you don't live in a major city, you're probably going to need some kind of engine
driven wagon.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
I guarantee you.
Yeah.
Or yeah.
Or someone in the family or someone nearby or a community car.
We once had a community car when I lived in New York.
It was a car that we between three or four different people we shared.
Right.
That worked out really well because it was a beater, you know, and it just worked.
So yeah, everybody goes in with the right if everybody goes in with the right attitude,
you can easily do that.
By the way, I would certainly recommend that if you can arrange it.
You know, if you've got a couple of neighbors that can cooperate on something, that's a
great thing to arrange for, because this way there's always a vehicle available.
Right.
So actually, that's what I was about to say.
It's not when they wanted to go to a bike race.
It was not available.
Just almost like clockwork.
Well, see, but you got to you got to arrange for it in Jersey and stuff like that.
So you got to arrange things.
It's sort of like, you know, waiting to shoot pool at a bar.
Right.
As long as everybody follows the rules and you use the you know, they did follow the
rules.
It just when they did.
You're right.
They didn't follow the rules.
You're supposed to call each other when someone uses the car or call two people out of the
four or five.
And there was no call.
The car wasn't there.
I called the pound.
You have alternate side of the street parking.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
You know, tow it.
Right.
And you call the pound.
No, it's not the pound.
I called the pound three times.
Is he sure it's not there?
Yeah.
So anyway.
Stop buying things.
And by the way, if I can encourage anyone to work on things, most things, OK, let's
say cars, cars, bicycles, dishwashers, washing machines, dishwasher.
I would forego.
I have one.
I never use it.
I store all the, you know, what do you call left over the plastic containers and lids
in the dishwasher.
Right.
I never use it because it's so slow and inefficient.
Now, restaurant dishwashers work really well.
They're three minutes.
Yeah.
But that's an entirely that's an entirely different machine from what you get at home,
though.
It doesn't have to be, though.
Yeah.
You could read.
You could design it to be very much like that.
But but any washing machine, all these car, bicycle.
If you can change a light bulb, here's the encouragement part.
It's true.
If you can change a light bulb, you could pretty much work on any of these machines.
But instead of holding the bulb in your hand, you're going to be holding a tool.
Right.
So, right.
A wrench or something.
Yeah.
Hopefully it's not.
You could use a hammer, but not too much.
Don't use hammers if you can avoid them on machines.
Wrench, screwdriver.
Sure.
Good.
Yeah.
If you could work a light bulb.
Right.
If you can operate replacing a light bulb or, you know, that's why years ago when I used
to get people and people chose, do you know how to operate a screwdriver?
And, you know, and the ones that are comfortable, of course, you know, yes.
The ones that weren't confident would laugh and laugh and laugh, said, you haven't answered
the question yet.
Right.
So, yeah, you prove this with me recently where, you know, you basically instructed me about
a couple of things.
And that's all I really needed to know is how to thread and unthread things a bit until
I got up to a point where I had to replace a belt because, you know, to actually get
that done, that's a little different.
You know, it requires.
Did you get the tool and the serpentine belt tool?
You know what?
I tried to do that, but I had problems visually, so I had to, I sought somebody's assistance.
I mean, that's another limitation.
It's complicated.
You got to follow.
Sometimes they have a little sticker on the hood that shows you the path the belt has
to follow.
Yeah.
I was having trouble with that.
So I had somebody, you know, but that's a visual limitation.
I think if somebody is, you know, generally about common as to their visual acuity, they
would be fine.
I say the other thing, by the way, folks, if you're working on a car and one of the
wheels are removed, do me a favor and stick the wheel underneath the chassis of the car
somewhere.
So in case the jack fails or it's the car slides, the wheel will stop.
It'll knock you out, but it won't crush you.
And that way the car doesn't go all the way to the ground.
Yeah.
So that's a good idea.
And even if you think I'm going to scratch the nice five star alloy rim, it's, but you're
better off doing that.
But anyway, it's sometimes I do feel, let me just go outside, remove the wheel and get
under the car and drop the jack anyway.
But anyway.
No, I try and slide like a cinder block under there just to make sure that there's a guaranteed
amount of, you know, pretty much a guaranteed amount of space that you're changing a flat
or something, you know, and you take the wheel comes off, throw it under the car somewhere,
you know?
Yeah.
That's, that's the most practical way.
And then just in case or whatever.
See, sometimes you don't have cinder blocks and things like that.
Of course.
That's, that's something you'll have.
Use the wheel.
Yeah.
Because the, I've seen jacks fail, not because the jack failed, but they, they just weren't
on good footing or the car slid or whatever.
Yeah.
So, um, start fixing, start learning how to fix things, sewing machines, washing machines,
uh, cars, um, you know, goes on and on and on anything, uh, anything you could fix the
next level.
Okay.
Here's the thing I discussed a while back.
Very important in the near future.
Not so near, but near enough, uh, get to know your neighbors, not because you need to whatever
I believe in good fences, make good neighbors, right?
But, uh, figure out what people are good at and start using that and use the barter
system if you can.
Right.
In other words, um, find out, uh, not a re not what they call a certified, you know,
the, the, the doctors with permission or whatever, cause they're, they don't do much, but someone
who's good at whatever they're, you know, you'll find people like, Oh, this guy on the
block, he's good with cars or this guy's a plumber, this guy's an electrician, but very
rarely do you find someone that's a good at medical stuff.
Right.
People have been shied away and scared away from that, right?
So when I say fixing stuff, I'm just fast forwarding to the end here.
One thing that you're always going to find lacking in any community is other than going
to what they call a licensed doctor is someone who's good at medical stuff.
So if there's a lack of that, that needs to be developed, someone in every community needs
to start learning.
It also, there's a, there's a knack for it, right?
If you're too squeamish, you know, it's not going to work.
There is a knack there, there, there, there are natural attributes that certain people
have towards the healing arts and medicine and even surgery, right?
There are natural attributes to that.
So that's one thing that I just fast forwarded because that's lacking.
For me, I'll tell you, I'll do most of it.
Most of the medical stuff, minor surgery and dental, or, you know, pretty much all that
stuff.
So, uh, like the old barbers, you know, uh, back in the days, the barber was the hospital,
the, uh, well back then, if you said you're going to the hospital, it was hospice, you
were going to die, right?
And it was for quarantining people with contagions and, uh, things like that.
Right.
And, uh, yeah.
Uh, or, yeah.
And they got a bad name because they were, uh, kidnapping.
The church was kidnapping people to do a medical experimentation on just like today, uh, simulated
heart attacks.
Uh, yeah.
Anyway.
Uh, I can get into the horror stories, but yeah, it's the, most of the people in the
medical professional that have clout are similar to the, most of the people that work in the
animal testing.
In other words, you don't have to pour hydrochloric acid in a rabbit's eye a hundred times of
the hundred rabbits to know that it's bad for the rabbit.
Yeah.
So there's a certain personality.
Just take it this way.
The kind of one that, uh, uh, goes out as a child and burns ants and bugs with a magnifying
glass.
You know that, right?
Those people.
Yeah.
And unfortunately, most of the community, the medical community that those, I'm talking,
I'm not talking about the people that do all the grunt work.
I'm talking about the people more up top are like that.
I hate to say they're pretty sick, uh, individuals.
Uh, so no pun intended there actually, there should be a pun, get it sick medical anyway.
Uh, yeah.
So one thing I would suggest is people learning how to do the healing arts, which, uh, when
it comes to fixing stuff.
And here's the thing right now is the most practical time to do it because if it's not
working out well, you can always go to the conventional, you know, a clinic or a hospital
to back, you know, whatever.
Right.
But whenever I've done anything and they ended up going, it was an emergency situation to
a hospital and they said, who did this?
Whoever, there's a doctor, right?
Whoever did this, you know, set it up or blah, blah, blah.
So many situations I've done, uh, say, well, this must've, you went to another hospital
like no.
I don't know.
So in other words, and it's, it's, it's learn how to demystify these things.
There's nothing mystical about it and that would, that would be like the end of the fix.
Right.
But back to the, the, the more practical fixing stuff, people are, you're going to always
encounter fixing stuff and most of the time it's either leave it alone or hire someone
or buy something new.
Right.
Uh, everyone that's listening or anyone that could possibly listen has enough time to learn
to fix things.
You're right.
I mean, unless you're really put it this way, if you're working 20 hours a day or 12 hours
a day and you have no days off, well, you might be one of the exceptions that you might,
maybe you should hire someone you see, but most people don't have that kind of rigor.
Most people have enough free time to do other things.
And I would suggest learning how to fix stuff.
And uh, I think the, the shenanigans that they pulled three years ago, it's been three
years already, should be a little bit of a wake up call on what's coming.
So learn how to fix stuff.
And again, most things that you're going to fix machines are like changing the light bulb.
Just keep reminding yourself of that.
And when you, uh, the more you do, the more confidence you'll develop.
Now, most people think that if you're doing something and it ends up in failure, let's
say even catastrophic failure, you should lose your confidence.
No.
What it does there is you'll be confident if you have a good memory on how not to do.
Uh, if something fails or doesn't work, you must retain the memory of everything that
you did.
Uh, and that is just as valuable, right?
Because now you have caveats.
So when you're instructing or doing it again, make sure you don't do this, right?
Right.
Yep.
Okay.
So, so anything that you do should develop confidence, no matter if it works out the
way you thought or not is what I'm trying to say.
And I'm not trying to give a pep talk here, but this is just really how it works.
Right.
Um, the really good, the old learn from your mistakes, uh, adage, you know, well, actually,
well, no, no, no.
My point, this is my point I was going to say next, you just, uh, you got it for try
to learn from other people's mistakes because it's cheaper.
Right.
They paid, they paid, they flipped the bill.
Cause usually if you, if you learning from your mistakes, guess who gets the bill?
You do.
Oh, right.
So it's good to know.
You're in a store, you break it, you buy it.
Yeah.
So try to learn from other people's mistakes.
And unfortunately, when you go to YouTube university, I actually keep saying YouTube
university.
Some people say, I looked up YouTube university.
There's nothing like that.
No.
I said, I mean, you go to YouTube for how to DIY stuff.
That's what I mean by that.
But there is no such thing as YouTube, but there is Google scholar there, but Google
right now is like, Oh my gosh.
Yeah.
That's another thing though.
But yeah, no, you can learn from people just showing you how things work, how they, yeah,
exactly.
But they very rarely video themselves screwing up and what the screw ups are very rarely.
Right.
They don't do that.
Then I think that would make a better video because they, they're, you know what?
It's very popular.
They have these fail videos, right?
Right.
Fails and things.
And those things get millions of views.
You just pop up, you know, sometimes I was like, what the hell, like 7.8 million views
on fails.
And it's just somebody that gathered videos from everybody else.
Didn't know production costs, you know, and they're 7.3 million videos.
If it's monetized, that's $7,300, right?
It's a penny per view, right?
So yeah, there's very little, um, don't so much on the dues, I suggest, uh, you know,
here's the interesting part.
And just to go back about fixing, to learn how to fix stuff yourself.
One of the things I was known for back in the day for speaking, I was speaking on scripture
and the Bible and it basically saying, you're all doing it wrong or everything that you
think is in there is not in there.
And what's in there.
You don't know anything about, right.
That was like one of my main things, right?
Right.
Now here's the thing.
And, and, and I always shied away from religion and I always shied away.
What are religious people do with the Bible?
Biblically?
Oh, you got to read your Bible every day.
Right.
And what do I say?
Read the Bible.
Are you joking?
Put it away.
You shouldn't read the Bible.
Why?
Why shouldn't I read it?
Cause you're not going to understand a thing in it.
That's why.
Why waste your time?
Right.
So for some that worked out really well because you know, when you tell, uh, let's say you
have a child and you say, you're going to spend the day in this house, you got to have everything
in this house, but you can't go in the drawer in this room, right?
20 rooms in the house, arcade pool, everything, right?
TV.
The moment you leave, you know where he's going, right?
Yeah.
Of course.
Right to that drawer because it's a, yeah, of course.
So what this did was it actually, by telling people not to read the Bible, and this is
in genuine, I've said this, it actually got the people that were more inclined in being
curious to actually go and read it.
And when you read something, don't read it because it's popular.
You read it because you're really curious about it.
You're going to get so much more out of it.
Most of the people that have ever gone back and read the Bible after hearing Greek speak
have gotten so much more out of it because of that.
And it's not this, I'm not doing this reverse psychology stuff that they call whatever at
all.
I just know how the human mind works and how it's wired to, uh, you prepare the mind.
In other words, you put something out that seems very unprepared, that only those that
are more inclined to be prepared, even though they're not prepared to do it.
Right?
So that's why I said earlier, very important just to fix things.
The ultimate thing to fix is the human body, right?
I say, fix machines about, you know, don't buy anything, just fix it.
You know, if they tell you the car in blue book is worth a thousand bucks and you need
2000 bucks for new transmission, do the $2,000 transmission.
You know why?
Because you're going to spend, let's say three, 4,000, 5,000, 10,000 on another car and you're
still going to need the transmission anyway, eventually the liability, right?
But here's the thing about the body and remember, uh, there are some people that are more inclined
to be quote unquote, a doctor or a surgeon or a healer, you know, when in the healing
arts, let's say, right then, then all, you know, if you got everyone in the neighborhood
together and said, everyone's got to learn this basic first aid stuff, some people would
be like, why am I here?
I hate this stuff.
Right.
And other people that give me more.
So how do you sort them out?
I think they need to be sorted out just by putting the word out and it happens naturally
again.
So many of the things that I started with was biblical stuff because the Western society
leans very heavily on it and there's a lot of misunderstanding and misdirection and misconstruing
of what it's about.
The second thing I always talked about is just learning about, uh, what's in front of
you, uh, paying attention and being objective about it.
Right.
And paying attention.
I mean like really, really, really listening to what things mean and what they're saying.
Yeah.
And, and all this stuff comes together by the way.
Right.
And if you hear me now saying, don't buy anything new, fix the stuff if you have it all right.
Well, when I say don't buy anything new, I don't mean like if you need something, don't
go buy.
Like if you don't have a hammer and you need a hammer, as Greek says, don't buy anything.
Don't go ahead and buy the hammer.
But if the head falls, let's say a wooden handle and it falls off and it doesn't work,
you know, it's dangerous.
Fix it.
Don't buy another hammer.
Make sure that's a function.
You see what I mean?
Right.
So if you need to replace something, think about it.
If you need to acquire something, acquire it.
But here's the point.
If you need to acquire something, get it used, get it pre-owned, find, um, this is what I
do.
Find a, I'm looking around in the house here, uh, and let's say 75% of the stuff I've had
I bought, uh, either at a thrift store or used on Craigslist or one of these offer up sites
or whatever.
Right.
Yeah.
Okay.
So, right.
Anything.
Uh, and things that have been handed, uh, given to me, hand-me-downs and things like
that.
I very rarely buy anything, uh, new first, seek to buy it new, uh, first, um, buy it,
uh, pre-owned if you can, is the point, uh, it has, it has, look, it's beyond economics.
There are a lot of quote unquote, cover your ears, white people that think that if they
have something, uh, they, that costs a $40 brand new, they could sell it for 35 and
they even sat on Craigslist.
Well, it's $5 less and less the tax.
I'm like, no jerk off.
The moment something leaves the store, it's worth about half, right?
You know, they even say this with cars, you know, you drive a car 30% 40% right.
So you got a lot of these white people, uh, cause I was looking for a washing machine recently
and the guy has a washing machine, you know, it's $700, it's $900 at home Depot, 700 for
me or 800 or something like that.
It's a hundred dollars less and less the tax.
I'm like, jerk off.
The moment you took that washing machine home, the same, the next day it's, it's $400.
It's 450 if it's 900.
So yeah, yeah.
450.
And he's, but here's the thing, there's all these other white people that are going and
buying it cause they're buying that line.
They're buying the line that, Oh, it's a hundred dollars less than, uh, you see, and
then they go ahead and it's telling the wife, they just goes, yeah, but they'll actually
go and buy it.
They fall for that.
So you can't make everyone savvy is what I'm trying to say, but there's a good percentage
of the population, depending on where you are, they're not very savvy at all, but that could
also be used to your advantage.
So why am I saying this?
Why, why fix everything?
Why do industry is gotten to the point now where it's pretty, it should be pretty obvious
that they don't know how to make anything anymore.
In other words, many of these hard goods like cars, refrigerators, washing machines, these,
these things, if you see a new model every year, the simple reason is that they're appealing
to your ego and some sense of fashion and trend.
And they really haven't figured out the only logical reason is the reason that it's different
every year for a car is because they really haven't figured out how to make it yet.
Right?
Right.
Because if you look at shoes or other things or clothing that change, it's based on fashion
and trends, but shoes are, we've already established, by the way, don't take shoes for granted because
only up until about a little more than a hundred years ago, you didn't have a left and right
shoe, right?
It was a straight shoe and you had to break it in.
That's why there was so many, uh, if you growing up maybe long time ago or whenever you met
someone very old and you've got new shoes, Oh, be careful.
They could hurt your feet, you know, because shoes were straight.
They were no, there was no left or right.
Yeah.
And there you had to break it in.
And, oh boy, oh boy, was that painful.
But anyway, many of the things that we see, like I've mentioned hardware stuff, uh, if
you have a shovel, uh, or whatever, it's this growing up, it's the same right now because
they figured out, right?
A hammer or anything, a saw, it's the same thing because this is how it should be.
So when you see things like cars that they change every, that is not, it has nothing to
do with what you think you need a car for.
That is appealing to some strange distraction, some strange fashionable things, some bizarre
that should not exist in my, in my opinion, of course.
It works the same.
It's built the same.
They just changed the color because nowadays it's more fashionable to wear bright color
as opposed to a muted color or whatever.
You know, that's it.
But I got it.
But here's the, yeah.
But here's the thing.
Are people that shallow and that stupid that they think that because they have a newer
car that makes things better or them better somehow.
And don't answer that because we know the answer to that.
We know that if it wasn't, if it wasn't true, it wouldn't be happening.
Yeah.
Some people think that directly, by the way.
I mean, we're like no, no in between, no practical practicality to it at all.
It's just a matter of, Oh, it's better.
Things are better.
I can prove that because I have a new car.
I mean, literally that's, they're directly, yeah, better than the Joe.
He got a Cadillac, you know, I've got the iPhone 15, but you only have the 10, you know?
Yeah.
So, yeah.
So, so the way you get, uh, you know, one of my things is don't you want to kick them
in the shins at least once before you leave here?
Right.
Meaning those that are running this thing, which we don't know who they are directly.
The way you kick them in the shins is by example, if you start fixing things and becoming savvy,
uh, uh, dwell in the used market, uh, by the way, uh, all of the washing machines that I've
ever gotten are used.
And if I put a photograph of it, you know, let's say that's a brand new machine that
you have to be savvy.
Right.
So, I mean, uh, just got one cause that's changed the bearing on another one and I figured
get a backup.
Right.
And, uh, it looks brand new and there's a hundred bucks, you know, uh, uh, anyway, and
there were other ones similar for 350 and 400, but I just happened to get the right
email.
Right.
Anyway.
So, um, let's, let's just do it this way, uh, fix it.
But when I say let's do it this way, you fix it, be savvy.
It has nothing to do with, with saving money or making money or whatever.
What it has to do is it's called contracting the economy.
You've heard of that, right?
When they contract the economy, there's less demand.
Um, uh, look, if they say people are going to be losing jobs, no one will ever be out
of a job.
What you do is you ban them, uh, weed killers and you have people picking weeds for food
and shelter.
That's not a big deal.
Hey, do I have to show that as there's no place I can go to do that as an example, let's
say, say, well, Greek, you'd be the first one to do it.
I'll do it.
I'll pick weeds for the rest of my life and just for food and shelter room and board.
Sure.
Do I have to, do I have to like prove that there's no place I can go and apply for that.
So these things need to be created.
Um, by the way, most of the doctors and attorneys will be first runners up for, you know, for,
for that job, by the way.
Right.
Uh, uh, and judges and, uh, a lot of the movie actors too, cause they haven't, they'd
be suck.
But anyway, if you have no skills at all and you can be told to take care of a job and
you can be instructed about it in less than a day, I mean, that's the kind of thing that
anybody can do as long as you're physically capable.
So sure.
And the story, it doesn't require any background.
You don't have to know anything.
You don't have to be able to read.
Just look, you see this thing?
It's this color, right?
You understand that?
I'm saying that indirectly too, because what you would be as a herder, I wouldn't, I wouldn't,
uh, it wouldn't be practical for a human to do it.
What you do is you raise some goats or, and sheep and you just become a herder and they,
they clean up.
They took, they eat everything.
Now, uh, if you have too many sheep grazing, they could make the land a little barren because
they pull everything out of the ground where the goats only eat the top usually, you know,
each animal is characteristic.
So the soil might stay a little more moist with the goats.
But anyway, I'm using that as this is all metaphor.
Everything is metaphor by the way.
So yeah.
How do people become savvy?
Uh, you retract another first thing that's going to happen.
Let's say you hear this and you're, it sparks something in you that I'm going to start fixing
stuff or whatever.
Uh, don't worry about the mechanics or the repairmen and all that.
They've got, the reason why is because I assure you even not good repairmen or for machines
or mechanic car mechanics, they're always busy.
You're never going to find one that isn't right, right?
So they could taper down a little bit.
But what I mean by this is if you start doing this and you're known to do it, not just,
you'll have maybe one out of a hundred people that would try to follow your example, but
you're going to have to also learn how to vocalize it and speak on it to inspire others
to do it.
Because I have learned after all these years that most people do not learn by example.
That is an old adage that people will learn by example.
I am telling you, they do not, they do not learn by example.
So you, you, you're going to have to somehow have come some kind of spiel to go with it,
which is Yiddish for speak, I guess, uh, that will inspire them some kind of, uh, whatever,
uh, to go along.
What this will do again, contract the economy and it'll put things into perspective.
It actually will raise the value of the notes that you're using, right?
Right.
And, uh, yeah.
And, and best thing is you'll become more self-sufficient in a direct, in a direct sense.
You get to raise the value of the notes that you possess immediately because after all,
you're able to get more life out of something than you were before.
Again, repurpose, reuse and re rehabilitate anything you can.
That way you're not having to go buy another one.
It doesn't matter if it's a plate or if it's a complex machine, right?
Um, because you're, you're just getting more for your money, more bang for your buck, so
to speak.
Well, also you're not, yeah, yeah.
There's many, many, I mean, there's lots of discussion you can get into as an end up in
a landfill or whatever.
Go, go look at these recycling places like for, they got recycling for all kinds of things.
They are jam packed.
There's mountains of stuff there.
And, uh, every recycling place has a place set off to the side where the good stuff,
it's like they're actually selling it.
All I had to do was like fix something really minor and they're, you know, they're selling
it as a used thing, right?
That was given to be recycled.
You see what I mean?
Right.
So yeah.
Uh, so none of the, in other words, don't be concerned about servicemen, repairmen, mechanics,
recycling places, or refurbishing places being compromised because you're, everyone's fixing
stuff on their own.
And they're not, they have their hands full more than, more than they could.
You can imagine.
Also, there's no guild around them.
They, uh, all of these people that work in labor, uh, have no dedication, uh, to society
at all.
I think I've gotten over that.
If you hired a carpenter years ago and he hung a door for you and it fell off and you
called him and he didn't come back to fix it, make it right.
You go to the guild and you say, Hey, uh, this guy, so-and-so one of your carpenters, uh,
did a lousy job.
Well, Oh, I'm sorry.
They would, the guild would sit, would come and fix it for you.
And then they would go and admonish the guy for giving out all the carpenters a bad name.
You see?
Right.
So where are the mechanics when there's a bad mechanic going and making the car right
and admonishing and telling the guy who did a bad job, you're giving us mechanics a bad
name.
Is that going on at all?
No, never, never.
Yeah.
No, not never.
It did at one point.
Well, never.
That was the norm.
Well, you said, is it going on now?
I'm saying never.
Not at all.
It's not at all.
It's, it's even unheard of actually.
If you, I've brought this up to several people in the trades and they laugh and then a couple
of the old heads said, yeah, I remember my grandfather, this guy's already a grandfather.
My grandfather told me about something like that, like ancient, like it's ancient history
or something.
And it's not.
So in other words, they have no, um, dedication to you, right at all.
So why don't you reciprocate by fixing your own stuff?
True.
Okay.
I got you.
Yeah.