Rated Y number 53, okay.
So let's get right on into it and well, first, hey Greek, what is happening at the moment?
I got to tell you, I love the chat room and everything, but the most wonderful piece there
was actually this little sound effect.
Oh, okay.
You got sound effect, but no, no, that's not a, that's from the chat room.
Somebody put a cricket noise sound effect on YouTube.
Oh, that's fine.
Yeah.
Well, the chat is just another outlet.
It's a communicate.
It's all communication.
Absolutely.
No, I just, I love the cricket sound effect though, because that's one of the best, you
know, like, you know, nobody is going to react.
Nobody's going to do anything and you can actually hear the crickets cause nothing moves.
Nobody speaks when something happens, but yeah, yeah, but here's the thing.
When you played that, I was like, okay, should I say anything at a, yeah, most of those sounds
that people call crickets are not crickets at all.
They're roaches.
Ooh, that's nasty.
Crickets.
They sound very similar.
Yeah.
So most of those night sounds that you hear the night insects that people listen to, they're
not crickets.
They're roaches and they are the, um, the American roach, the larger ones, not the small
ones.
So that noise I just played, that might be a roach, not a cricket or yeah, it sounds
more like a roach cause it has that high metallic squeal kind of sound.
Oh God.
Well, you know, I've lived in neighborhoods where you can actually hear them rustle in
like army formation when they go rushing away from a place I've lived in some bad places.
Uh, and you can hear them in the grass and they make noise as they move through the grass.
I've always wondered about that if anybody else could hear it because I ask other people
about it and they don't know what I'm talking about.
But I swear if they move in mass, they make noise.
Have you ever heard that?
Yeah, yeah.
I have a compost bin and they, and they like to take control territory of that.
Okay.
Uh, and that's why I know that it's roaches and not crickets.
Yeah.
Well, like most of them, they don't discern very much of that online, but if you dig into
it, you'll see it's true.
See when a house burns down in a bad neighborhood though, a mass exodus occurs of roaches.
Some of them possess self-preservation, so they go running in mass and you can hear them
shuffle through the grass.
It's like really weird.
Um, so, but, but that's, that's, yeah, that's something that I said I was going to bring
up a tangentially on a, on a previous sonic regarding remedies.
And I said, I'll bring this up and I didn't.
So remind me, is it the better I hold off on it, the better it is for the audience, I should
say regarding roaches.
See, a long time ago, you briefly touched on that there was an entity actually in control
of that particular species.
And you started talking about entities being in control of certain animals or creatures.
Oh, entity.
It's always plural.
It's never entity.
Yeah.
Okay.
Always plural.
Uh, so entities that are in control entities, bugs, animals.
Right.
And, uh, so, I mean, we never really broke that wide open, so I'd love to get into that
too.
Well, there's only so much you can do because we're limited, you know, we filter all that
out.
Otherwise, you know, the people who don't filter it out, end up in mental institutions
because they can't cope with the others that are heavily filtering.
You see what I mean by filtering is we only see a small part of the spectrum.
They, they, they put this in your face.
You only see a certain part of the light spectrum.
You only hear a certain part of the sound spectrum, but you notice they never say you
actually perceive mentally, cognitively the, let's say cognitive spectrum.
They never talk about that because they don't want to just tell people that they've been
dumbed down, but the same thing with that.
That's why on the last Sonic, I talked about how a higher conscious can always, what was
the term that I use?
It wasn't absorb or anything that can contain a lower one, right?
So when you have a higher conscious person, let's say interact with the lower consciousness
one.
I'm not saying one is better.
It's the same like two cars.
One is mistreated and the other one's not, you know, one you put, you know, the best
fuel and you maintain it meticulously and the other one never gets maintenance and gets
the worst fuel.
They both came from the same place.
They're both the same, right?
But eventually they degrade to higher and lower quality.
So like I mentioned last time, you can be of higher consciousness.
You could fully contain, you could almost predict, anticipate everything the lower consciousness
will do.
But once you approach the lower consciousness about the higher conscious person, what do
they always say?
Man, I don't understand what he's saying.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Oh, he's real interesting.
Oh, I don't know.
You know, right.
Yeah.
That's a very simple example.
Well, I'll tell you another thing about that.
And I wonder how you interpret this.
But I have noticed a trend among, you know, the people that I end up having to interact
with for one reason or another, that they have defaulted to a new thing in the past couple
of years.
It seems like, and it took me a little while to figure it out, but it's sort of like, unless
you're here to tell me something I already wanted to hear, yeah, I don't acknowledge
you and I get hostile.
That seems new.
Yeah.
Good.
Well, that's part of the culture.
That's part of the culture.
Yeah.
But it seems like a newer part.
That's the scene on TV, people.
Yeah.
But now it's social media.
Sorry.
Now it's, yeah, it's got to be social media because TV isn't the big influence.
It was, you know, say when you and I were growing up, now it's all about whatever you're
carrying around in your pocket, which I guess answers my own question, you know, because
you're determining what it is that you're being fed through your, you know, your dumb
phone, right?
Because it's supposed to be a smartphone, but it's not very smart.
But you are always setting the parameters by which the algorithms will feed you.
So you're deciding what you want to hear anyway.
And I think people are actively doing that and they get real.
But I'm noticing this great hostility toward anything that contradicts what they like.
In other words, OK, you and I decide to go do a public presentation.
The people that show up there, whatever their expectation was, if we don't meet it, we'll
be met with hostility.
If we meet it, exactly.
Even if it's really stupid and low grade and adds no value to their life, even though they
paid for a ticket and whatever, whatever.
It doesn't matter.
So long as we played the hits they wanted us to play, you know, well, that's used to
have LeBron in the crowd that he wrote about that 120 years ago.
It's the same people.
Well, look, I'm not a romantic, but I am regarding certain things that happened that created
a cut off.
In other words, everything that could have been known was known by the late 1800s.
And they and they decided to dumb everything down.
Right.
So I'm romantic about that.
But in terms of people are way better now than they were in the past.
Right.
They're not as dumb, actually.
But the the there's a squeeze, there's a spiritual squeeze, because they don't have a lot of
time left.
You know, in this, you know, this is what you say, culture, society, the time, right, the
age.
They don't they know that, but they can't discuss it.
To give you an example, OK, this is a little bit of a tangent, but there's a new film that
came out called Jewels.
It's about old people and UFO crashes.
One of the in Ben Kingsley, he's the actor in the backyard, destroyed his azaleas and
broke his birdbath.
And he helps the alien back, nurses the alien back, and they develop a friendship with two
other women, Jane Curtin and another woman.
And it shows how challenging it is to be aged, a senior citizen, how you start losing
your mind.
And I was watching this and I said, the reason why it's like that is because of the culture.
Older people were regarded, right, of high regard.
And so the culture now and also without getting into people know what I'm talking about.
But what they may not realize is the older people themselves do not have wisdom because
they never worked out how the system works.
Both systems, all systems, even presumptively, meaning the manmade political system, which
is the medical, economic, all that, and then the spiritual systems, which is above the
religions about themselves.
So they really did turn into a bunch of dummies and they're not really worth that much.
The older people. So this movie kind of shows the plight of the older people.
And it's because there are no better.
It's cultural. They're no better off than the young ones.
It's like I've said, they've stopped developing at around nine or 10 years old people.
Right. And then you get really old.
Now, if you have someone who spiritually and mentally and cognitively stops developing a
whole society and talking about your professionals, judges, Supreme Court judges, doctors
also, they stop developing around nine, 10, 11, 12.
There's only that mentality of nine, 10, 11, 12.
That's also the way the operating system works on smartphones, by the way, is good for a
certain active lifestyle.
Right. And when you get old and you lose that activity or become rigid and you're viewed
as no longer being part of that society, you're disposed of.
Right. So if you watch the movie called Jules, J-U-L-E-S with Ben Kingsley, you'll see
most people feel sorry and they, whatever, you know, for the old people, how they're
always mentioned in the film, how they're lonely and this and that, that has nothing to
do with, in other words, it's not an age old thing.
This is a very recent thing because the society never reaches any mature cognitive
level. And when I say, you know how I say it's the society of morons, right?
I'm not talking about the masses.
I'm talking about those that you call professionals, the masses of no effect.
Right. They're only as good as what they put forward.
Like what I mean by the society being morons, you know how the spaceship lands on the
front lawn, the little green Martian comes out.
What's the first thing they say in the film, especially the comedies?
Yeah, take me to your leader.
Right. And that's what I'm talking about, those guys who they bring them to, like
they're scientists, you know, regular Joe, let's say nothing as regular Joe, like
regular Joe. But you know what I mean?
An average, quote unquote, person, who average means damaged, by the way, brings
them to their best scientists, their best whatever, whatever, whatever, that alien's
going to look and say, these are morons.
What the hell am I doing here?
Right. That's why I've given my credo on if you're going to visit this planet, don't
talk to the humans. Anything you say is going to confuse them.
Right. Anything at all.
But anyway, back to that, the violence part.
No, I see it as being fine.
Look, you know, when they were talking about all the gun stuff, I was like, oh, come
on, gun violence.
That's great. Just just tell me when you want to do it.
I'll get under I'll go underground or behind some concrete.
Just everybody, just please shoot each other.
Please just go ahead and do it.
And whoever comes out from the other side, well, those are the worthy ones.
Right. So, you know, all this threat and the violence, it's like the same with the
nukes. Drop the nukes.
Go ahead. Drop them. Just let me know when you're going to drop them.
You know, who cares?
You know, so it's the sort of Damocles, you know, holding a sword over people's
mentality, you know, like this is what we know, especially with the nukes.
You know, it never happened.
Right. And by the way, I've explained loosely why it cannot happen.
Right. Because one when one goes, the EMP takes out the other one.
Right. So you can only do one one or two a day unless they're underground and then
underground. You can go every 30 minutes.
Right. And that's how they're going to be used, by the way, underground, not above
ground. Well, I shouldn't say that they are using them above ground and they're up
to eighth or ninth generation.
And most people are all vaguely familiar with first generation.
So, yeah.
So, again, back to that with the consciousness and all that.
Speaking of which, this is like a puppy rate.
I'm doing something.
What am I doing? For the past 10 days, I've been eating sad food, which is standard
American diet. I made homemade White Castles.
I think I've informed you about that White Castle hamburgers.
Right. I've been doing turkey and roast beef sandwiches, lasagna type stuff, you
know, stuff that regular people eat right for about 10 days now.
And how do I feel? I feel like I wouldn't say I feel like crap, but I definitely don't
have any energy and I got an itchy spot on my ankle that's coming back.
Right. It sometimes if you scratch it too much, it bleeds, you know.
OK, so. But so now you are eating a lot of cheese, you know, some cheese, some
cheese, you know, because I know you said dairy was definitely kind of a, you know,
well, people that live on it.
Yeah. People that you know, what I mean, dairy is like, you know, make sure you drink
a glass of milk every day for the children.
That's what the depression goes up.
OK, so what I'm going to do now is I'm, in other words, aware of how I feel and what
manifestations I have in and out of the body.
OK, now I'm going to go back to a whole food diet based on energy.
Right. And have a change and I'll report back on specifics.
Now, George Asawa used to do this a lot.
He says you could cure anything with food.
And he did.
But he got a little extreme.
He went down to the East Congo and contracted some kind of several things.
He contracted a form of TB and an amoeba in his intestines.
And he tried to he couldn't get enough of the things that he needed.
You know how I put out a recipe and people can't get the ingredients.
Right. And he died from it.
So you can get pretty extreme.
You've heard of people testing things on themselves, right?
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
So I'm kind of this has been a test and it's been about 10 days.
So I'm going to go back to what I preach and teach, let's say.
And I have gotten some feedback regarding the rice recipe, which it's not it's not
to be all and all, but it is a very well balanced.
What it would be would be like a tune up in a pot.
You know, in mechanics, like WD-40 is like a tune up in a can.
Right. If you have an old car, isn't running a long time.
You definitely need a can of WD-40 to get started on it.
Right. To make everything move around nice and easy.
Yeah. And give you energy in this case.
So the brown rice number seven or number eight, because I think it's number eight.
If you count the plum is a wonderful reset meal.
And the way I think we went on over the sonic and being redundant here, because it's
very important. Each ingredient has a purpose.
Right. And it covers a certain energy path.
And it may if you're trying to treat something, you may not want ginger right in
there. You may not want the burdock root.
But I found that the burdock root works pretty much generally across the board because we
are deficient. What I mean by that is, have you heard of how the farm in agriculture,
all of the soils have been depleted of essential minerals and things right in the past
hundred years. Right.
So we're not getting that nutrition in the food like selenium and forms of magnesium
you won't find in soils that you did a long time ago.
So that's where the burdock root would work well.
And what I'm suggesting is, yes, you must start with food because when you're trying
to heal something and I've had several discussions about the C word, what they call
cancer and just to broadcast what's going on, you know, and it's kind of harsh to tell
someone there's no such thing as cancer.
Well, yeah, it's a label.
Right. But it's a blockage.
It's a blockage that the body creates because the energies and the way the body's
functioning is not working.
It's a failsafe, actually.
And they've turned it into a disease or something has to be cured.
You'll never cure.
It's like saying, you know, let's eliminate roadblocks when there's a car accident.
Right. It's never going to happen because if you try to do that politically, the people
would start doing it on their own anyway.
The organism right of society will do it.
Someone will get out of their car and redirect traffic.
Right. Let's try and direct people around it.
Yeah, of course. Yeah. Yeah.
So that's exactly what it's doing.
And yeah.
So the easiest way to do that, of course, is with food.
Why? Well, you know how they say you can go, what, 30 days without food, three days
without water, three and then three minutes without air or something like that.
Something like that. Actually, it's more like 30 minutes without air.
But yeah.
OK, so that's how you view your when you want to tune up or get back on track, you
could do it in reverse.
First, work on your breathing.
There are people that have cured and healed diseases and conditions just by learning
how to breathe. You know, the yoga type of there's so many types of breathing you
could look up. Right, right.
And then it would be water improving their water quality and then food.
You can actually do it in that order if, let's say, you ran into someone who was
very ill or low energy or whatever.
First thing is the breathing.
Second thing is the water, you know, upping the quality or doing it right.
And then it would be food.
I just wanted to throw that in there in that order.
And then. Sounds like up the quality of the primary things that you need to survive in
the order of priority based on time.
Yeah. Because you're breathing water and food.
Yes. Yes.
And thought, of course, you know, when people are stressed, they have a physical
reaction. Let's say you're hungry.
You go to a place, you look forward to eat with someone you like and you get some
really bad news.
What happens? Lose your appetite completely.
Yeah. So there is a physical effect of the mind.
That's and vice versa.
If you get extremely happy, you also lose your appetite.
Right. So it's these extremes that I'm talking about.
Well, I don't know. Sometimes I get into a celebratory mood and I want to eat.
I have a desire to eat certain things when I'm in a celebratory mood.
Well, that's celebratory, but an immediate impulse from really good news, let's say.
Oh, OK. Well, that's like snorting something up your nose.
Actually, that's what that does.
But yeah, so that's a long way from where we started.
But that's that was very important to bring out that order.
I have not done that. Fair enough.
You know, there's another factor here, which I want to bring up.
Have you ever heard of the Rashomon effect?
They say that again. Rashomon effect.
They call it. OK, I'll describe it for you.
This is the Wikipedia description, which is fairly concise, although Wikipedia is
definitely everything for idiots.
But you got to use it if it's concise.
OK, it's it's intelligence agencies.
They rush. OK, I just typed it in.
I just got into the case.
There's a storytelling and writing method in cinema, which the event is given
contradictory interpretations or descriptions.
Right now, this can be expanded into a wider
understanding of the way people interpret things.
OK. And the effect is named after Akira Kurosawa's 1950 film Rashomon, in which a
murderer is described in four contradictory ways by four eyewitnesses.
The term addresses the motives, mechanism and accuracies of the reporting on the
circumstance. And OK, so you get the point here is like civil wars and revolutions
are based on also kind of thing.
Well, the thing is, though, OK, from a certain perspective.
Right. Somebody is either a tyrant or they are the victor in a righteous battle.
Right. Depending on which side you stand on.
But people interpret everything according to their perspective.
And this sometimes changes exactly how they describe it.
And I find this interesting.
And that's why I brought up the whole thing about, you know, people want to hear what
they want to hear and that's it anymore.
It's an oversimplified version of this where you can interpret anything and describe it
in a different way. And I mean, I'm just encountering this constantly.
And no, no, no.
It's not about you, though.
Is it is it something that, in other words, is so deeply implanted in the society and the
culture that needs to either you need to change what you do to go around it or ignore
it? You see, that's the main thing that I like to talk.
That's the ultimate question I have.
Exactly. That is, what do you do with this?
If you are being objective and, you know, viewing things as objectively as possible.
Well, does it affect your food, clothing and shelter and happiness in any way?
Well, if you have to interact with people, it does.
Well, it's all about how you interact with them.
Yeah. Right.
So, in other words, what interest do you have?
Right. It's your interest.
You know, like that's a major thing.
You know, have you ever heard like politically, you know, we went and attacked Libya because it
has the United States has interest in it.
And that's good enough. Right.
So you have the broad the broad aspect to things like that.
You know, you can have a broad put it this way.
When I go out into society, people know I have a broad aspect like that.
I want nothing to do with anything that's going on.
I'm just here for this. Right.
You see. Yeah.
OK, I just I brought it up because I just thought it was interesting because this thing
about the inner voice again has come up.
Right. And as I said, I I'm hearing about it because it is most interesting to people
that, you know, to consider where that's actually coming from.
What is the issue with it?
What is the problem with it?
What is the danger of it?
If you're getting well, you're getting your cues, you're getting your inner voice from not
you. Well, you do the JFK research.
You're never going to find out the front end of it.
You're only going to write what was front loaded to it, to only to a certain degree.
Right. The same thing.
It's kind of 9-11 is really good.
It's positively, definitely without any doubt that was an atomic, you know, actually was
thermonuclear demolition.
There's no doubt about that.
Right. And most people have a psychological hard time.
I actually found the trace of how the Department of Energy gave the OK.
Right. And said they hold the triggers of the devices.
Right. It's kind of like you have a gun.
Someone has guns, but they have no bullets.
Right. OK. Well, no triggers on the guns.
The DOE holds all the triggers for all the civilian nuclear devices and most of the
military ones. So when one's ready to go hot, they deliver the trigger and they use
the OST, which is the Office of Special Transportation.
It's a branch of the Secret Service.
Right. And FEMA arranged all that.
Right. And you've always heard how FEMA was there two days before.
But there's more to it and also found one of the the lower OST operatives.
Right. All this other stuff.
Right. So wait a second.
Why is the DOE delivering trigger mechanisms to New York via the OST?
Oh, to somehow thwart planes crashing into the building and a diesel fire that caused its
collapse. That's right.
That's right. GP8 or G8, whatever the fuel is.
You see. And also the NNSA, if you look at every photograph of high resolution post
demolition of the World Trade Center, you go to the bottom of the photograph.
Credits go to U.S.
government and then parentheses.
It's NNSA.
Well, what's the NNSA?
The National Nuclear Safety Administration.
Oh, the reason why the National Nuclear Safety Administration took all those photos is, of
course, they were set up to manage, you know, jet fuel disasters, of course.
Right. OK, so why did I say this?
How contrary of what I said is to what the people believe happened on 9-11.
Of course, they say 50 percent of the people don't believe in what they've been told.
But where are they going to go?
Space weapons, dynamite on each floor.
Right. It was rigged for explosives.
They saw the plumes coming out of each.
Right. They're never going to go to the nuclear thing.
Right. Never, ever.
But here's the thing.
Is it so important?
How far? We're never going to find out more than that, I think, because no one's come
forward. There was over a thousand operatives, American operatives, involved in
pulling it off. And how many have come forward?
Very fewer than those that were involved in JFK.
I don't think anyone ever involved in the JFK come forward either.
Is there? Well, they may have because they may have anonymously.
Well, not even necessarily anonymously, but mixed in with a whole bunch of false
you know, a whole bunch of distracted people searching their own 15 minutes of fame,
this kind of stuff. And if you mix it all together, well, you know, you could have
legitimate people that come out and they're just, you know, all caught up and they all
come out seemingly at the same time and they all get grouped into.
Well, these are just, you know, nuts that are seeking to write a good story.
But with either JFK or 9-11, first thing is what the authorities are telling you is
absolutely impossible.
Can't happen that way.
That's the first problem.
Yeah. What's the first?
And then the second thing is we know how it was done.
Like with JFK, it's not one magic bullet.
It was at least three, right?
Maybe five or four were fired to definitely make contact, maybe three.
Right. Right. Oh, yeah.
OK, not one.
OK, so 9-11, it's the same thing.
It wasn't jet fuel.
It was definitely something that shook the ground and the towers collapsed and the steel
vaporized is only one thing that could do that.
Right. But the people can't believe that.
Now, there are people in the military, by the way, that know of atomic gates.
And I've spoken to people in the nuclear industry, in military, that I said, you know
what atomic gate is? And they're like, no, never heard of it.
I said, oh, my gosh.
You know, I think I've gone over this real quick.
If every country plans for the worst, I'd hope it never happens.
Right. So do you think there's a plan of a contingency plan?
If the US contingent states and Alaska was ever, ever suffered a successful ground
invasion, do you think they have a plan for that?
A contingency plan?
Yes, there is. Yes, they do.
Yes. So. OK, so what do I mean by that?
Ships showing up, planes dropping people from, you know, parachutes, air droplets, sea
land and sea. Right.
Invasion. Right.
Like a D-Day type thing.
Oh, yeah. There are plans to retake New Jersey in case a hostile enemy force decided to
occupy it. There are plans for boots on the ground.
OK, so so here's the contingency to make it short.
I just wanted to give a little more detail on people.
What do you mean? OK, that's what I mean.
Like boots on the ground, you know, whatever.
Coming here and taking over at gunpoint and heavy artillery and ordnance of every kind.
Red Dawn on to anything you can imagine.
They have contingency plans.
Yes, exactly. OK, so here's one of the called an atomic.
Do you think they're going to leave the Golden Gate Bridge, the Verrazano Bridge, the
Brooklyn Bridge, those big buildings up the they're going to leave the power stations
running for the enemy to take and use?
No, I see what you're talking about is what I think of as destroying the infrastructure
so that it can't be inherited by an invader.
OK, got exactly.
Main bridges. Yeah.
You think they're going to leave the Golden Gate Bridge up so they could cross, have a
nice crossing for their for their tanks and stuff?
No, no. Just like they're not going to leave the power grid intact either.
That's not going to happen if there is an invasion.
Why give it to the enemy who can just, oh, I'm going to take this over.
It's perfectly. You think while the invasion is happening or before, they're going to get
about 30 or 40 thousand people to wire up about four million tons of TNT to do all those
things? Or do they already have small nuclear devices that, you know, disintegrate
anything right underground?
The more intelligent thing would be to have it already sitting there waiting just to be
utilized in case.
Exactly. Yeah. So all these things, all these major buildings and major parts of
infrastructure have what's called an atomic gate.
There's a section of it.
Now, you know, they say you don't want to if you if you have a dead body in your house,
you got to get rid of it because you don't want your mom to find it in the freezer.
Right. So when you have maintenance people that maintain these skyscrapers and big
buildings, you don't want them to find the device.
So it's never actually in those locations.
It's nearby. And there's a small access tunnel right to it.
That would make sense. That's how the World Trade Center was done.
You know, that's why they took down Building 7.
Building 7 was the control center.
There's international symbols for that.
Also, if you know which where these devices are, we can get into that another time.
So they use atomic. So there in other words, there are thousands of atomic and nuclear
thermonuclear. There is a difference between atomic and thermonuclear, by the way, already
in place within hours and several hours or a day or so are activated to take down the
infrastructure. So the invading land force doesn't use it.
By the way, this whole contingency has been in place since the time of ancient times, by
the way. Right. So, yeah.
So, yeah. And there's people in military never heard of this or don't know.
It's like, oh, my gosh. So what is that compartmentalization?
OK, so we've gone off quite a bit on a tangent.
But the whole thing is any situation that you see that may not be favorable for the
collective. Two things.
One, you avoid it or see how you could use it as an opportunist.
Right. If you can be and without going into the black market necessarily.
Right. And doing things that are unlawful.
OK, give you an example.
Real simple example is the alternative media.
Right. The mainstream media is doing such a great job that there has to be an
alternative media to counter and tell people, quote unquote, the truth.
No, it's not because they're doing it's because they're so shitty.
There's a alternative media.
Right. And there's always been an alternative media.
I remember years ago looking around for old periodicals because you'll find more, you
know, old books already been targeted and periodicals get spread out more than books
sometimes and find catalog.
There was a lot of anti-Catholic magazines in the 1700s warning people, do not let the
Catholic Church here.
You will be you will suffer the same thing that you suffered in Europe.
That's right. Remember why you came here.
Right. Right. So what did they do?
They let the Catholic Church in.
But they did have quite a push against it.
You see, but you won't find too many books on that.
You'll find periodicals.
Right. So now you have like Nexus magazine.
Right. And all these other now it's an Internet alternative media.
Unfortunately, before the digital, there was plenty of underground newspapers and zines
and magazines and independent publications.
Allegedly, that was sort of the alternative media of that day.
If you knew where to get those limited printed printings on this and that and the third
thing. And it was remarkable how much information might be in their alternative
information. And then later, shortwave radio and things like that.
Sure. So that will.
So anything you bring up that says something in society, you're always going to see a
counter movement against it.
But the only problem that I see with that, whether it's the thing that you mentioned, that
effect or whatever, is that when certain people decide to take that path to provide an
alternate source of information in this case, where do they come from?
Where is their education from?
The same group that is subject to it.
So they're not going to it's very rare.
You're going to have a clear answer.
You can example is in the medical.
I've been on many conference calls and seen many videos that people have sent about an
alternative doctor and they said they have this herbal concoction they made that will
lower your blood pressure.
Oh, my God. Or help you with diabetes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, what? What?
What? Fictional diseases.
Right. So why?
Because they have the standard education.
Right. So you almost I once commented on a video that someone spoke on a few months ago
and never got posted. They didn't allow it to be posted.
People are looking for the truth.
It's not just somebody that's going to come and give them the truth and it's all said and
done. The best they're going to get is one person starts peeling back.
There are many layers. So like an onion.
Right. Or it's not really like an onion because onion are thin layers.
You know how the most of the layers on the onion are very even.
This is very different.
Like the first layer could be 10 feet thick and the second layer could be only a half an
inch thick. Right.
It's not it's not consistent.
What the best information people are going to get is by peeling back multiple layers.
But the problem is when they peel all the layers of misinformation and deception away,
when they get to what's the truth because of their previous teachings and background, they
will not recognize it.
They'll just walk right over it.
And they'll notice or they'll notice it's been in front of them the whole time.
That's one of the slogans of Greek speak, discovering the obvious.
You see. So, again, with all these things in society, if I'm always saying we're better, way
better off today than we were a hundred or two hundred thousand years ago, way better off.
Right. Because to me, it just shows you there's another inherent problem which goes back to
the inner voice.
The inner voice doesn't necessarily have to be OK.
The inner voice entities were here before us.
Right. So they're playing with us because that's their realm.
And you can take them as a teacher.
You can take them as a hindrance.
You can take them as a help.
Right. You could see them as a friend.
You can see them as an entity.
I mean, an enemy.
You can take them as a form of God.
Right. You can take them.
Right. It's all a matter of how you structure what you're doing.
But no matter what they do to you, you're going to be OK if you start to understand the
situation. Right.
Meaning that, you know, what much like you were talking about information streams, much
like the argument I make all the time of like, no, do pay attention to the guys who are
giving you the misinformation, because if you're aware that they are misinformed, then
now you know exactly what is BS, because you can call it.
It's like, I know that this guy only provides the best BS.
Yeah. Watch. Listen to that.
Pay careful attention.
Yeah. It has a structure to it.
So once you recognize the structure, you're.
Yeah. Then you can utilize it for your own purposes.
So that makes perfect sense to me.
Is that OK? So the inner voice could teach you a great deal about what's not you.
It depends on the structure.
Like we've mentioned, we've gone into great length on how you develop.
They change the they change the inner voice.
Right. And if you get to a certain level where your consciousness is high and your
knowledge base is high, the those on the other side that provide the inner voice are
fewer and fewer to provide it.
So they start bringing in bigger bad asses.
Right. And if you get really advanced, they start giving you anticipated moves and you
think you can tell the future.
But they're actually giving it to you.
Right. OK, because they're just you know, it's a very efficient way to throw you off
because once you find out about the inner voice, now it's like we can't be so obvious
anymore. Right.
We have to distract them a little bit by let's say he'll be able to see a minute into
the future pretty much half the time and he'll get so impressed by that he'll forget
that it's us doing it.
Well, very much like there used to be a lag in news.
Right. You could do something on the other side of the world and nobody would hear about
it for a few days. You knew you had a few days to control the spin, to put out a story
before people found out about it up until a few years ago.
Now, instantaneous information travels.
So well, and even more, they anticipate they give you what's called the predictive
program. They'll tell you what's good.
Right. Yeah. That's where I was going next, is that now now they get ahead of it.
Now let's put out the predictive programming because they're going to find out about the
event immediately.
So but like I said, again, going back to, you know, around the time you and I are growing
up again, it took a few days for things to travel even from state to state.
It would take you're in New York.
OK, something happens in Ohio.
You didn't hear about it that day unless you had a friend in Ohio that called you up on a
phone and said, hey, did you hear about this?
Well, there were some actually news channels that ran 24 seven that you would get it
through the API or the UPI Associated Press.
Yeah. Or the or the United Press.
The two they would do a hot sheet.
Right. They get it. The radio station would get a telex or a fax or something.
Right. But it wasn't it.
But it wasn't as commonly accessible.
So you didn't have as much of it like, you know, cell phones with cameras and posting
it two minutes ago on YouTube.
Right. Right. Exactly.
That's my point. Right.
By the way, that's still under control.
If you added a legitimate UFO land in front of your house and shot a video and put it
up on YouTube and you actually made the post and you go back and view the video, it'll
look very different from what you put up.
There's there's fail safes on that already.
That's you know how they're telling with the A.I.
They can do it. They could screen every pixel and know what it should be put up and
not, you know. Oh, yeah.
No, it only takes a couple of minutes for all that stuff to be filtered real fast.
At most, you know, so your your video of that legitimate UFO might exist there for
about two, three minutes and then boom, you might be able to see it, but no one else
will. Yeah, because through your IP, right, it'll be blurry.
It'll look fake, you know.
Right. Or it'll be cut up or whatever.
Yeah. It's it's fine.
But so still much better off or you'll end up with sound and no picture.
There's many ways to do it.
Actually, they're sophisticated enough to actually put something else there.
Yeah, that's similar.
Sometimes that's all ready to go.
Look at 9-11 when they put the airplanes in.
You know, there was a few black frames.
If you look at the recording with CNN, we're showing the plane going in as soon as
they switched over this black frame, black frame, black frame, three or four black
frames or 16 frames per second.
So for a quarter of a second, it was black.
Then there's no background of Jersey anymore.
The sky is different. And then you see the plane go in.
Right. There's no because right before the plane, you could see the Jersey shore.
Right. The Hudson.
And it was a blue sky, no clouds.
But when they put they switched over to the plane, you don't see the Jersey shore
anymore. Same shot, same angle.
Right. And the sky is like a whitish blue kind of featureless.
Yeah. So and that was I think what's her name?
Victoria Roth. Was it Rebecca Roth?
Rebecca Roth. She did some pretty good research on that.
The young guys that did the CGI effects for that.
They were pretty much they exploded into doing no pun intended there, into doing
the the promotions you see on lines of scrimmage at baseball games.
You know, when you're watching it on TV, you'll see an ad behind the play.
But if you're sitting in the stands, you don't see it.
You know, the CGI effects that you see in sports games.
They were given that contract to reward them.
I think that was a really good piece of it.
They didn't say that they did, but she followed the group around and notice how
they were interesting on that.
It's very, very pertinent, by the way.
I like to give 9-11 references because the biblical stories are also pertinent, like
9-11. Right. How radical this what people think happened compared to what is
memorialized. Right.
So, yeah, there's many levels.
One more thing before we go.
What I bring. I think I've mentioned this with you before about vacations.
There's a certain mentality, you know, behind vacations.
You know, I understand.
OK, people have careers.
They work on a schedule.
They get what? Two weeks off or whatever.
They get sick days. You know, the typical corporate structure.
Sure. Right. They offer certain.
Yeah. Depends on who you work with or for.
I've had a job or two like that.
I think I told you before I worked for Exxon for a bit.
So, yeah, I had that sort of thing.
Yeah. Yeah. So it's structured, very structured.
OK, I get the structured part.
But the part where your people are looking forward to go on vacation, I've
experienced this to get away from everything.
Right. So they're there.
They have like, oh, you know, close up the house or wherever you live.
We're going to be away for a week, let's say.
Real simple. And they're always unplug a bunch of unnecessary things, you know,
shut off the service.
And during the vacation, they're wondering, you know, did I unplug this or
whatever. Right. And how much money they're spending or whatever, you know,
whatever, whatever. And then it's like they're so happy to go back home.
Ninety nine percent of the time.
Oh, we're going home. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, if you're so happy to go home and you're thinking about home while you're
on vacation, why are you going on vacation anyway?
Again, it's the cultural thing.
That's the programming, right?
I think I never participated in that, though.
I got to be honest.
But there are a lot of people that do.
When I got time off from work, for me, it was like that means I don't have to go
anywhere. I can just, you know, stay in the house.
Well, here's the thing, because recently someone I know, some a couple, let's say,
and they're like standard, you know, conventional collective people and they're
going scuba diving somewhere in the Caribbean or Costa Rica or something.
And I kind of chuckled when I heard that they're away doing that, because I'm
like, first of all, what are these people offering to society?
What do they do? What do they think about?
I know how they are. And it sounds critical and judgmental, but it's like, you
know, they believe, you know, what they see on mainstream.
They believe what the doctor knows about the human body.
They believe they have to pay tax, their taxes.
They believe. And they're going on a vacation, scuba diving, elaborate vacation,
all that. And I'm thinking about all the energy to do that while they're there.
Yeah, I wish them a good time and all that.
But I have to chuckle.
I have to chuckle. So in order to do that right in good consciousness, you have to
imagine like, OK, all the water you're drinking is good.
You've done everything you could to make your life better or whatever.
They never think of stuff like that.
They just do. I've had people tell me we're conventional.
We're mainstream. We do what everybody else does.
Right. Yeah. And and part of that useless existence, to me, it's completely
useless, is the vacation thing that they enjoy.
Right. I would I would never do that.
It's like you should you know, there's an old saying, make your vocation your
vacation. Right. In other words, you should always do what you like.
I never understood that.
And it's funny when I because I don't socialize much and get into the mainstream
stuff when I hear about someone doing that.
I'm like, that is so funny.
That is so funny because, you know, the thing is, first of all, they're going on
vacation, enjoy themselves and like so many better things to do to improve your
life. But on the same time, aren't they always on vacation here anyway?
I mean, it's kind of an interesting thing to look at, you know, in other words,
the conventional collective people going on vacation.
That is so funny because I've been around them when they do it.
Right. The whole thing is, is just it's it's here.
Here's another way to look at if you want to know someone, let's say you just meet
someone or you're socializing with some you want to know a little bit more about
them. This is easy to do now, especially and I came up with this after the digital
media, because with cameras where you had to develop film and you had to develop
film. Right. You take the rollout, send it away.
You know, it's not an immediate event.
Right. Well, recently with the phones recently past 10 years, at least you want
to learn more about someone that you're acquainted with or whatever, just to do a
test. And this is the test.
Tell them to take a picture of something like a meal or an object, take a picture
of it and show it and then look at the picture that they took.
That tells you a lot about the person when someone takes a photograph.
Should you should you pick the thing or let them pick the thing?
You can pick the thing. OK, it probably be better.
Right. Or you pick, let's say, take a couple of pictures, but one of them is one
that you picked would be good. OK, and then let them show you the photo.
And that will tell you a lot about the character of the person.
Why? Because when you're taking a photo, you're memorializing an image that should
just be a form of communication to someone viewing it.
Right. It's not just the image itself.
We're not doing modern art here.
Right. And when this is not self-expression type modern art.
What I mean by this is you'll learn a lot about the person if they're selfish, if
they can see, if they can perceive or if they can communicate.
Like, for example, when someone takes a photograph and they show you the
photograph, you'll notice like the angle, the lighting, the position or whatever
just shows the object out of context mostly.
And you don't really know what it is.
OK, that is the type of person that is more on the selfish side or whatever,
because they're there.
They're taking a photo of the object.
Right. And they know what the object is.
They're walking. You know, they're in 3D motion.
Right. And they see the setting that it's in and they get to see it from various
angles. Even if you don't move, you could just move your head a little bit and you
get more of an angle.
When they take the photo and it doesn't seem it seems out of context or it's out
of scale or whatever.
See, they know that they're there and they can see it.
And but the photo doesn't really show it very well.
It's like, well, I don't care.
I see it. If you don't, that's your problem.
It's just, you know, a bad photo.
Right. So someone who is a who is considerate will make will take the photo in a
way that will give more than just what the object is.
It will show a sense of scale, a sense of perspective.
Right. And so it's like you're when when you're in the situation and you're asked
to communicate something in a photograph, you need to make it so someone who is not
there sees the photograph and gets the maximum effect or the maximum amount of
information from it.
Right. So a simple example would be too close.
Yeah. Only from above.
Let's say it depends. It depends on the situation.
But actually watching how people and what people do in photographs tells you a lot
about them, how considerate they are to others, if they can actually see.
If they can actually see and if they can communicate and they're interested in
communicating. And I've been doing this for a long time, and it works really, really
well. Yeah, I got a question about that.
Just another little qualifier here, because I look I've exchanged a lot of images
with you over the years.
And clearly, anybody who knows me knows I got a bit of a visual problem.
So I'm thinking that probably skews what it is that I put into photographs when I'm
trying to communicate with a photograph.
But I think also I've communicated this is this is a high level, though.
It's very it's subtle.
OK, it's subtle.
Well, I was just curious, but it's less subtle as time goes on, because most people
have taken if you have the stupid rectangle, it's actually not even a phone.
You know, it's a camera that happens to be a phone.
If you look at the level of technology and the focus and the emphasis on the device,
it's for media, not for speaking on the phone.
There's way more. There's way more put into the you know, there's two different
cameras. You got a front and a back camera now on all of this.
So as it develops and keeps going, when you look at photographs, it's the how the
person perceives themselves when they're communicating and engaging with others.
It's an interesting one.
And I've also got, you know, a job application.
Right. It's actually whenever whenever I was in a situation where I needed to have
people work with me, let's say hire people.
Typically, if you were to do that, let's say most people on the receiving end of
that. But if you're on the opposite end, let's say, you know, like George Bush W.
Bush Jr. said, the French are not good at business because they don't have a word for
entrepreneur. Right.
Yeah. Well, if you're an entrepreneurial industrialist type, eventually, as you
start needing help, you're going to put an ad out or ask for people to come.
Right. Right. And so you could screen them, interview them, quote unquote, job
application. Give you an example.
What I did with several businesses.
How would you do that? How is it typically done?
You show up, you give you a piece of paper, you write your history, your school and
all that, your past experience, and they ask you a bunch of questions and then they
kind of wonder and scratch their head, you know, you know, he smelled didn't smell
good. I don't think I want to hire him or whatever.
And there's just what they wrote down on a stupid piece of paper.
And then you're going to see if they work out there on what do you call it when you're
on probation for 30 days or something?
What do they call it? Or they're going to try you out.
Right. You're there for a trial.
Total bullshit. That's total mainstream garbage.
I'll tell you how the Greek did it or would do it and does it.
OK. Have I ever gone over this?
No, I don't think so. Things are a little different nowadays, though, from the old paper
application, you know.
Oh, yeah. This has nothing to do with it.
Yeah. Because now it is. That's total garbage.
This is in line.
Asking someone to take a photograph is more subtle.
I'm going to give you something that is less subtle, but works on the same subtle
energy. OK. And you'll learn you'll know more about the person that they know about
themselves. And OK.
What I do is I have a small table or an area set aside
with a big pile of coins.
So it would be copper pennies, dimes, nickels, quarters.
Big pile would be, you know, a few pounds.
Right. Then I have twenty, thirty dollars worth of coins.
Yeah, at least.
And then in front of them, I have a jar for the pennies, a jar for the nickel, a jar
for the dime and a jar for the quarter.
There are four jars there.
And I ask them to separate the coins.
And one says pennies, dimes, nickel.
All right. All right. They're all labeled.
Watching them separate those coins will tell you more about them than if they worked
free with with you for a year.
I'll tell you more about how they are when they're not at work.
How's that? Well, first of all, the coins are the job
is for what money.
Right. What's the first thing your grandma, your uncle, your mom and dad gave you when
you're four years old? You wanted some money.
They hand you a hundred dollar bill where they give you some what coins give you some
coins. So it's the first thing that you engage in.
You actually probably got a coin.
The first thing getting a job is a commercial venture, commercial interaction
before you went on your first commercial interaction as a child, no matter how old
or how young you were. I assure you, you got coins first.
Right. Right. If you are five years old and you have the freedom or six or seven, you
anticipate going buying a piece of candy.
You're not going to just go in there and say, well, you're going to anticipate you have
to get some coinage first.
So, OK, first interaction in commerce.
It's coin, so you're very familiar with them, they're very common.
Also, the coins are distinctively separate.
Now, the first thing here is the thing I've had people come in and sit down, this is
what you want me to do. I don't want to do this.
This is beneath me by great.
So now you have a serious narcissistic ego problem with somebody.
Right. I have an engineering degree.
You can have me sort coins on a job interview.
That's bullshit. All right.
Bye. You just learned more from that person that they may look great on paper.
Right. But there'll be a real shithead if you work with them.
You see right away. Right.
OK, here's another one. Sorting out the coins, not only.
Well, three of them are silver, one is copper, but they have different sizes.
You watch how they sort out things, how fast they do it.
Are they using both of their hands?
Are there how many fingers are they using?
Right. What's their body posture when they're doing this?
Right. And how they're putting them into the jar.
Are they making a lot of noise, tossing it in?
Or are they place, you know, placing them in their hand and carefully putting them in
the jar? And and by the way, I had someone sort out coins.
And they put a penny in with the nickel.
So after I let them go and go and they put another penny in with the dimes, I let it
go. And I said, hold on a second.
I said, you know, these are Mark penny nickel dime quarters.
Yeah, I know. I know.
I said, well, there's a penny in with the nickels and a penny in with the dimes.
They go, yeah, I know. It doesn't matter.
I'm like, whoa, what did I just learn?
Wow. What did I just learn?
Right. You see how deep this is.
And no one does this. And I know someone in corporate that I told him how to use that.
And he's like, oh, my gosh, that is like the deepest psychological wash through I've ever
heard of. Right.
OK. Especially especially when someone says this is beneath me.
I don't want to do this. Bye.
You see. So this is the way I do it.
Because why? Because it does four, five, six.
It's working on so many different levels.
It's working on the first thing they've ever done in their lives, all the way to how they
see life now and how they would react given a situation very, very deep.
The other thing I mentioned just when you're doing if you're a corporate doing a hire and
you're speaking to someone who has experience in a similar field, let's say.
Right. Let's say you're a mechanic and you want to hire a mechanic shop.
You want to hire a mechanic and you talk, whatever.
One of the questions that's important is have them describe.
Ask them what is the worst situation in a mechanic?
Previous experience they've ever had.
Why? Because when they recall that they're going to you're going to see an emotional
reaction in their body when they recall that worst situation.
So when they're working for you, if you recognize that the emotional condition in them
or state, that means something bad is going to happen because you've already.
Right. OK.
You're not asking them what's the worst thing they've ever seen happen on the job.
Because you want to hear a story, you want to see how they how their body reacts to it.
So if you ever pick up on that later, you know something bad's happening here.
Right. So there's many levels to this, by the way.
You know, I should write a little handbook and give it to corporate because you don't you
don't doesn't have to be just sorting coins, by the way.
There are other methods.
But I just wanted to share this because it's just another way to perceive what's going on.
And I hope you found the sharing the coins profound because it's one thing to hear it and
see its effect. And there's another thing to be there when it's happening.
Well, I'm thinking to myself, this is the kind of thing that a lot of corporations actually pay
somebody like, you know, 10, 20 grand to show up and give a PowerPoint on.
Yeah, well, over the 10, 20 grand, you got to be joking.
It's got to be a lot more than that because.
But here's the thing.
Well, there's many other ways to do it.
I haven't quite figured them out, but there are ways.
And this is someone I was talking to.
This is like a psychological wash through.
Yeah. But in the early 2000s, I guarantee you it would have been like a twenty thousand
dollar fee.
Yeah. But believe me, 20 grand is not is not enough to really make an effort in anything
anymore. Sorry, but that's why we're giving it out to the subs.
They'll let them do it. But I do business consulting, by the way, but not the way that
business consulting is done.
Fair enough. Fair enough.