Sonic Event 3, actually, just for the record, Ocelli and the Greek, welcome. Anyway, we
will continue with the discussion from last time, sort of. And I always love doing this and creating a segue, so that's actually what we were discussing before I started recording. Just again, for the record, Greek, how are you this fine day?
Oh, it's fine enough. You know, we haven't been doing the timekeeping. I'd say today is the 14th day of the 12th month, right? And the year, you just add, you know, from 1998 to 6000, so you add two years, so it's 6025 since that atomic thing went down, supposedly.
Well, there you have it. But of course, to the listener, it's kind of irrelevant, because they could be listening to this a year later, they could be listening to this a few hours later, right? So their timekeeping will vary as they are hearing you.
Yeah, let's just timestamp this one, that rough. What would it be the other way? Was it the 17th of February 2023 on the Pope's calendar?
Yes, indeed. And the day started, you know, according to the time we're at the day started on their schedule. Well, let's see about what 16 hours ago. But
Oh, you mean? Yeah, right. Midnight. Yeah, day starts at noon. So I know high noon. Yeah. But that's the point is that 16 hours ago versus about four hours ago. Right. So when did the day start? There you have it. All right. But again, this your experience will vary. And that might come up, especially when we have to talk about something like, oh, boy, health.
And we were talking about that in the previous sonic event. And health, health in general. I'm hearing this more and more, by the way, and it's striking my ears rudely, in my mind. Because what do we have to say here, Greek? I want to increase my health. I want to make my health better. I want to be healthy, Greek. What do you say?
This is not for children. Right. But so but anyway, I'll hold back. I usually start off with a bunch of pejoratives. Right. Cuss words, you know, who Greek said the bad word. I'm gonna tell my mommy. Right. Kind of stuff. Whenever I'm brought into a health discussion earlier on the Sonics, I brought up telling people right off the bat, they should do this or consider this.
They get they see it kind of a fronted affrontive. And that's too forward for me. But if you give them a hint, they can't take a hint. They don't get it either. So there's somewhere in between. And this is this. I'll try to stay in the between spot. I always start off yelling at people. Why are you asking about being healthy when there's no such thing?
Okay. In ancient tradition, you bid someone at a greeting or farewell. You you bid them good health. This is you'll find this more and more, you know, Saludos in Spanish greetings. Right. This means basically health. Right. So most of the toasts and all that is to health. But it is so general.
But when it was done in ancient times, it was understood that it attached to your behavior, your profession, what you did in life, your age. When someone was very old, they wished them, you know, that may they live to 100, even on their ninety ninth birthday. Right. So you got to be careful with that one. But either way, there is no quote unquote health in general that can be discussed.
And what is he saying? I think I broached this before. I'll recap it real quick. Health for what? In other words, it implies some level of fitness and recovery that you will be able to sustain in the body. Right. So recovery would be you get tired when you get your energy back to continue. And fitness is how you know your endurance, how long you can go, let's say.
Right. And this goes if you're just sitting in an office all day. You got eight hours of sleep, four hours of sleep. Let's say you got two hours of sleep every night working in an office. You're not doing well. You need more than two hours, even if you're just sedentary. So it gets I mean, I can give a million combinations on how there is no health per se. But there are certain things like lack of sleep, lack of nutrition, what that'll wear you down, no matter what you're doing.
But essentially, most of the people that are coming in to interest to have a health discussion already know that if you get an hour or two hours of sleep or sleep deprivation, you're not going to do well. Or if your food is devoid or intake is devoid of nutrition, by the way, air is also nutritive.
OK, so, for example, a poor, poorly nutritive or poor air quality. Right. You will not feel as good as fresh air quality or good air quality. So water, food, all of these things are well known.
So these general health discussions appeal to me off to the max, because when you're generally in fairly good healthful state, discussing health in general is completely moot, must be specific.
Are you going to be climbing the mountain, the mountain, the tallest mountain in the world or a short hill? Are you sitting at an office? Are you a UPS driver? Are you doing construction work? Are you a mom raising children? What are you doing that you need certain health for?
And I'll give a few examples and maybe we'll bring up a direct. What would you say a question? We have a chat right on the members site. Sure, we do. Actually, that would be a good thing to let people know in case they haven't taken notice of it.
If you are on the Sonics page at Ocelli.com, there is a wide open chat tango, which anybody could either sign into or post anonymously if they like to enter any sort of feedback, a comment, a question, a suggestion.
All of these things are there and it's actually not run by us, but we do have some access to it and are able to observe it. Us meaning myself in the Greek, but someone else has taken on the duties of sort of running that and they will be responsible also for handling it.
And you're free to post there. And again, you don't have to identify yourself, but it's only being seen publicly easily on that page. Now you could access it without going to that page as well, but it is a useful little tool and we will be utilizing it in future presentations for sure.
And somewhat in this one. Yes, in a bit here. And the comments were good, by the way, so far, all of them and pertinent. Let's get into an experience I had when I was peddling water. Spring 2.0, we synthesized tap water into the finest quality spring water, similar to the finest quality spring waters in the world.
And we were peddling it at a high end health food store, two of the high end health food stores in L.A. One of them is Arowana. The other one was Rossum, who got busted for selling raw milk a decade ago. So when I was at Rossum, their whole thing was you're going to get healthy if you eat raw food.
In other words, up until 108 or 110 degrees, if it's more than 110 or whatever degrees, it's no longer raw. So everybody's got to eat raw to be healthy. Well, people would come over while I was peddling water and ask me about this and that. I said, well, what about the raw deal? Do I eat raw? And I said, well, right now I don't because I'm not fully, fully active.
What do you mean by that? I said, well, it depends on what kind of work you do. And they're like, what do you mean what kind of work to do? I said, okay, let's look at the goats, the sheep, the cows, whatever, the monkeys or whatever. They eat raw food, right? I don't see them showing up with a kitchen, you know, the skillet and the pot and the crock pot or anything like that.
And very few of them have time to enroll in a chef school. I mean, let's be honest. Yeah, right. And by the way, the thing about people when they say I went to cooking class, chefs that get formal training that can't get a job because they're not very good at cooking end up doing what? Teaching cooking classes. Think about that. So you have people who can't cook teaching other people who can't cook. How is that going to end up anyway?
Isn't that the way most professions work anyway? Okay. Yeah. But we're on the food topic. So I figured I'd hammer those guys. And I've proven this to people. But anyway, so I basically said, look, you know, these animals that eat raw all the time, what are they doing? You know, they're moving around constantly, constantly. So if you're not, let's say you have an office, what kind of work you do? And the person said, well, you know, I work in an office and this and that a file manager or something.
And I said, well, how much is sedentary? This is about half of it. And I said, well, then I would say right off the bat, you know, half raw, half cooked. And because if you ate just raw and you were sedentary, it would just it would be kind of difficult to. Are we still on? Yeah. Yeah. I was wondering why you were pausing.
Yeah, we somehow dropped the connection. Oh, and it's not letting me know. It might be on your end, maybe my end. I didn't hear drop at all. So yeah, it's as if it's recalling. Okay, so let's see where we were left off, basically with the what kind of profession they did. And they were half sedentary, half not sedentary.
Right. And then you said that. Well, it depends because if you're active, if you take in the raw, if you were entirely raw, what would happen? That's where you'd be miserable. Yeah, you've got this very energetic, high fiber, pretty dense stuff sitting in your gut. And you'll wish you'll wish that you were moving around more.
While I was saying this, some of the principles of Rossum pulled me aside. And not only aside, they took me out of the whole place outside and reprimanded me for saying, how dare you? Right. So that I kind of ran through my mind. I said, OK, all right. So this is about sales, not about reality.
So, well, of course, let's just look against your your your guest in their in their what do you call their proprietary space? Right. So, well, they gave me a spill. I was selling out of there to his commercial. But by the way, yeah. But either way, it's for a liter of water. So it wasn't cheap. Right. But either way, you can't work against the place you're working in. That's part of the deal usually. Right. You can't sit.
You know, in other words, you don't set up a coffee stand in the middle of the bookstore and then tell everybody the books all suck. You know, I mean, it just it's not what I was. It was at least in this case, it was half half suck. But, you know, I basically I did bring up the point that if you're really active, raw works fine in most cases.
Let's let's take an analogy when you're not feeling well, when you've lost levity. And I'm saying that literally you no longer can levitate as much as, you know, stay vertical. You have to lay down because you're not feeling well. What are they prescribed? Soup, right? Chicken soup.
Right. A light, a lighter diet, a liquid diet, eating soup. It's cooked. You've lost levity. You can't stay vertical anymore. You're laying down. You're sick. In some circles, it's called Jewish penicillin chicken soup with the schmaltz on top schmaltz, which is the fat. All those things have in common is they've been broken down and they're warm.
So when it gets into the body, it's already in a in a state where it's just can't be broken down anymore. And the body just takes over when the food is raw. It's on a very high state and it takes a lot of energy from the body to break it down.
Well, quick question is the fact that it's warm at the moment you're you're taking it in. Is that relevant or is it just relevant that it's been warmed and therefore broken down?
Cool. Both. OK, both. Yeah, both. That's that could be complicated. But the simplest thing is in sports. Very often the football coach, you know, the team goes in and they start guzzling cold water. What do they say? Don't drink the cold water. Right. It's too cold. Right. So it'll shock the body.
If it's warm, it'll be more accepting. It has that warming energy. Yeah, I would avoid. Well, if you go to certain Asian cultures, they drink hot tea, whether it's hot or cold out. You know, it's they don't they don't seek icy drinks. Also, when you have an icy drink, for example, with a very fatty meal, you know what happens with fat in the refrigerator, right?
So I always recommend a warm drink with any meal. But the basis of this is an example on how people get dogmatic about one thing. I mean, this is the way to go. You have all these ridiculous diets. I think the most recent one is the keto thing. Right.
And it's all pranking, by the way. The people that know how the body works and all this are silent. They're just watching everyone fall for all these dietary pranks throughout time, which is funny, too, because like a merry-go-round, like these things come back around all the time to write a different version of it.
They call it something slightly different. But here's what you do. Just eat all fat and you'll be OK, you know, or just eat all one particular type of thing. Grapefruit every every day, every season doesn't matter. That's what your body needs. I mean, I'm not saying this is what to do. Let me just be clear. I'm saying that I'm giving examples of the repetitive and revolving cycle of this that I see.
Right. I mean, it's it's absurd. Yeah. But again, no one's there is no public outcry. And most of the public goes for it. But it's coding. When you see people go for that, it tells you a lot about them. Obviously, those that are also wondering whether they should go for that don't see what's going on. I'm talking about those that have risen above all that muck.
Yes. And I mean, above in a vertical sense, you were looking down at this stuff. Right. But anyway, besides the food part, I gave that as an analogy. There is no particular way, because I can imagine that if you're new to hearing this type of speak, maybe someone might say, well, I should ask the Greek about this type of diet or that or eating right. Right. So get that all out of your head.
It all has to do with what you are looking to do physically and setting yourself up.
Yeah. Well, the one size fits all, regardless, whatever it is, is it's purposeful and it's part of the coding. I think we might have discussed that in the past where if you see a certain amount of people repeat something and use it in a way that it's not supposed to be used, you immediately broadcast what level of, you know, let's say not just intelligence, but what level of knowledge they have based on the thing. Right. So and they're easy to control that way.
You know, using things improperly, believe it or not, is one of the main, especially language is one of the main ways that if you want to control a society used to observe them.
So that back to the the general health, I just want to jump into because one thing that we haven't talked about is physical exercise. Again, irrelevant, completely irrelevant. What are you physically trying to get your body in shape for?
Right. You just well, you know, if you have a some kind of exercise regimen or you physically work in a UPS driver or you go to the gym, you do construction, whatever, whatever. Yes, you do feel better than when you're sedentary. Right. But again, it's irrelevant. What kind of fitness do you want to achieve and for what you see?
Like for when I see people in the gym on those life cycles or treadmills and all that, they should be hooking up generators to all that so they could put it back on the grid. I mean, that's a purpose. But OK, so the physical thing, I'll just put that aside for a moment.
What I want to just quickly jump into is one of the comments. I'm just I'm not going to read the comment I don't have in front of me, but from memory about a person had listened to Greek speak and cut out dairy from their diet.
OK, and eat seasonally. But they still have, quote unquote, allergies for grass and grass season. But it's it skips a month. It's like May and July, I believe.
And skip June or something. Right. So that's a summer grass. Right. And I did answer the comment, but I'm not even answering reading the answer. I'll just go over it again. Sure. One thing when you hear allergies, it's a sensitivity.
This is more of the allopathic, you know, the way they accept it. But unless it's extreme, like, for example, I'm allergic to bullets, you know. OK. OK. So it can go that far.
What I would suggest here is just like the one size fits all reversal. You everyone is sensitive, more sensitive to certain things, including tastes and others and smells. Right. Someone might smell something before someone else does in a room or in the environment.
And that other person who didn't smell it first might smell something else first because they're more sensitive to that. So it's perception, you know, olfactory, let's say the aspect of being allergic, quote unquote, to a grass.
We have something called buffalo grass in Tucson that some people are very and desert broom. They're very sensitive to. And I've done this with several people and it's worked. What I suggest that is going to the energetic side and component of it, by the way.
Again, what kind of health do you want? The allopathic medicine, the pharmaceutical, the stuff that's made from petrochemicals that you get at the drugstore from companies that don't give a rat's you know what about you, if it works for you, use it.
OK, and I just want to give an example. I've worked with many people over. I've been doing this alternative, quote unquote, health stuff since the 1980s.
There are one case that jumps in mind. There was a woman. She was in her 30s and she had you ready for this. A double horseshoe fistula abscess.
Say say that twice backwards. OK. And we did all kinds of remedies for about five years. And finally, I said, you know what, you're a Westerner, you live in a Western society, you're in the middle of the city.
Go Western. Go get it cut out. Go to a surgeon. Have the whole mess cut out. Right. And guess what happened. They did that. Took about a month to recover. Gone.
Five years of remedies, energetic, doing this, that and the other. Didn't do anything. You see where I'm at with this?
That's why I prefaced by what do they give for allergies, antihistamines, supposedly to suppress the body's reaction. OK, if that works, use it.
But what I found to be successful from an energetic perspective, and again, just to recap, if you have a malady and you find a plant that heals it, treats it, it's the energetics of the plant, how the plant looks, when it grows, where it grows, how you consumed it.
That's the energetic. The chemical materialist wants to take it and assay it, means like crush it up, centrifuge it, burn it and find out what the active ingredient is.
OK, so that would be the over-the-counter medicine. The energetic would be, again, the color of the plant. How tall does it grow? When does it grow? What kind of soil does it grow in?
How did you consume it? Did you eat it raw? Did you boil it? Did you dry it? OK, all those things matter because each one of those things adds a component to the energetic component.
So again, going back to this comment, it was, I believe, May and July or so grass. OK, so I'm presuming this is North America because May and July in Australia is wintertime, right?
So I'm presuming it's summertime. The energies are rising. So from a Taoist perspective, when you're in alignment with the rising energies during that season, you should be fine.
So if you're getting allergies or whatever, sensitivity to it is because your energy in your body is not used to that rising energy, that elevating energy, right?
In the summer, the energies go up. In the winters, they go down. So what you do is you start coaxing the body by intake of things, a light, leafy, what's a rising energy?
An extreme would be sugarcane or bamboo. More moderate would be plants that are not as tall. And so when you want to, let's see, before you even have to treat, you want to set your body up so you don't have to feel sensitive to this stuff.
You know May is coming. So before May, you start drinking green tea, which is a bush, could be about shoulder height, easy to get, very elevating. You can do parsley tea, you know, things that are moderately green and light that you can make a tea or eat.
So before that time comes around, and as you start to consume these things, your body is intaking more of these rising energies. So as the rising energies come around from these plants, you're not affected.
It's the same idea that if you're standing on a sidewalk and somebody drives by at 30 miles an hour, right? The concept here is what if you're in a car going 30 miles an hour next to another car going 30 miles an hour?
You both roll down the window. Even though you're both moving at 30 miles an hour in separate cars, it doesn't look like you're moving. You could shake hands, right?
Right.
That's the idea.
Okay.
The next idea is the remedy.
Well, the inverse, just really quickly, the inverse of that, if you wanted to promote a slowdown a bit, would you do something like consume potatoes, which don't necessarily reach up?
They're characteristic as they grow. They're in the dirt. They stay down there. They're a root, right? Like a carrot, too. Same kind of thing. The energy is heavier, is it not?
Downward. It's more about direction. Everything is about direction.
Direction.
Which way is up, right?
Well, which way the plant grows tells you a lot about the direction of the energy, right?
Right. Usually when you harvest it to consume it, it's what's manifested. It's how it manifests. Because something can grow down and then kick up again like a sprout.
Okay.
They grow downward first and then they kick up. So that's why sprouts have a very balanced energy.
Okay. So from a Daoist perspective, again, the remedy, instead of trying to get yourself in line with the energy, is you hit it with the opposite.
Okay.
Like putting out a fire, right? You throw water on it, right? Or you take the air away. It needs air, so you take air.
Okay. So the opposite would be, let's say you find yourself and it is those months that you're having a hard time and you wake up and you're like, oh, crap. I'm feeling it. It's getting me hard.
Then it is too late in actually getting the rising energies to align yourself. It is not going to treat that.
So you go with the opposite. You go with downward energy. You would take root vegetables and make a tea. Ginger tea. Burdock would be the strongest. Burdock is the most tenacious root vegetable.
Usually when you try to pull burdock out of the ground, you really can't. It just breaks off at the top and you got a foot still stuck in the ground, right? It's very tenacious.
So burdock tea, ginger tea. Potatoes are kind of difficult because they're considered a nightshade, right? They bloom at night. You know, the nightshade is aubergine, eggplant, tomato.
Right. I didn't think of that. I was just simply thinking about the directionality. Not the direction, but the way it grows, the way it presents itself. I'm thinking that's got to be down.
We can get into nightshades someday, but they're antagonistic. At night, the energies are going down, and here you have these plants that are blooming up into it, right?
So what it just means is that they're very extreme. In other words, extreme.
When I studied nightshades, growing them and studying them, I was like, with the right amount of tweaking, this is just a side note here, you can turn any nightshade plant, which is tomato, pepper, eggplant, potato, into a hallucinogenic.
They're not hallucinogenic right now, but if you understand what I'm talking about from an alchemic perspective, you can take those plants and make derivatives with some form of transmutation and turn them into hallucinogens.
Very powerful ones, actually. This is something I've discussed with some people. Years ago, when I was doing this with Dr. Joe Champion, we were making silver into gold and making gold out of copper and all this stuff.
But anyway, I just wanted to throw that out there because it's kind of trippy, and if you're really in line with what I'm talking about, you'll see it.
Again, when you know something is coming and you can discern the energy quality, get yourself set up for it.
It's kind of like, you know it's raining outside, grab an umbrella. If you run outside in the rain and then come back for an umbrella, you're already wet.
So in this case, if you know what's coming, set yourself up at least one month before with the lighter, greener teas and things to uplift and supplement that uplifting energy.
If you find yourself hit with it, then you go with the opposite, and that's the simplest way to explain the Taoist perspective.
It's just as simple as saying you put out fire with the opposite, you start a fire with the same.
This Taoist perspective, it was in the Western culture, but we have this group called the Church that made sure that all that stuff went away, because how the hell are you going to control people when they don't get sick and understand their environment?
In that way, I was wondering about the carrots too, because that was the other thing I brought up that had the downward or that direction, and that's different than a potato.
What about that as energetic, in this case?
You also look at what's in the ground and what's coming out of the ground.
What's interesting about the carrot is if you're prepping yourself before the event or before the time when you do feel sensitivity, just do the carrot tops.
If you look at carrot tops and parsley, they're very similar, almost undiscernible.
I grow both in the garden here.
What's good about the carrot, you can go down and just have the root as the remedy.
There's a difference between setting yourself up for the condition and a remedy, which is to actually put out the fire.
They're very different.
That's why very often you'll see something put out like ginger tea or this tea or this or whatever, good for this.
Well, good for this, usually it means it's too late.
Why?
It's just too rudimentary.
There has to be just a little bit more understanding.
Plus, you're telling me about the whole plant as opposed to the different components of the plant.
I'm not talking about the chemical elements.
I'm talking about the root of the thing and the bark of the thing and the flower of the thing.
These all have different characteristics.
Because of the manifestation, it's not the chemical.
It's the way that it manifests.
That's what I'm saying, not because of the chemical.
When I said component, I wanted to make sure we weren't talking chemicals.
There's different characteristics.
The thing is, just because they've done so many harmful things and misled society with chemicals doesn't mean that they're bad.
A baseball bat is not bad unless you get hit over the head with it consistently.
Once, you can forgive it.
But if you're always being beat up with a baseball bat that's made for playing baseball, you've got to say, grab a tree, grab a branch instead.
It's still the same thing.
But if you look at the intention, you're still getting hit over the head with it.
Because it is very possible, by the way, to get hit over the head with this natural, quote-unquote, stuff.
Also, if you've been around some of these naturopaths and airy-fairy, I call them the granola, earthy-crunchy people.
They're always putting down.
Whatever.
You could see anything.
It's not that chemicals are bad.
They're just chemicals and when they're misused.
Everything that we see in the material world is a manifestation of an energetic.
An easy way to look at that is if you look at the baby being born, it's a manifestation of the mother and the father.
They were also born in a similar way.
But if you take a slice off, the mother and the father exist because they eat plants and animals.
And if you go back and if you see they eat the plants, that's the water, the soil, the air, the sunlight.
If they eat the animal, well, the animal relies on the plant, which is the water.
So that means that what feeds the plant, where does that come from?
Where does the water come from?
Where does the soil, where does the light come from?
Then it goes back to energy.
Right.
Well, also the animal will feed the plant because the animal, when it dies, it ends up in the earth and those components get returned also.
So there's a relationship there, actually.
Yeah.
But there's a chain.
Imagine a chain of events that goes around in a circle.
Right.
Okay.
So this is basically what you want to tap into if you wanted to complete or be more overall in your understanding.
Now, in no way would I say omit standard medicine, you know, the allopathic, the mainstream stuff.
The problem that I see with most of the mainstream stuff is people are too trusting and they have too many other things they want to do in their lives.
You hear this all the time.
I do this for a living and I'm not interested in studying medicine or the human body.
I just need to find a doctor that I trust.
That's fine.
But I'm telling you that that doctor that you trust has been narrowly trained with the best education government has to offer.
Right.
And he can't do any more than what he knows is what the point is.
And it's getting worse and worse and worse as time goes on.
Now, when I say it's getting worse and worse and worse, I'm talking about from the 1800s on.
It's gotten worse.
So at this point, I think I addressed the chat and I address that point because it was a very good point.
Most people will tend to suffer, quote unquote, allergies and sensitivities more than anything else.
Right.
Because some people might get a fever, catch a cold once, not every year.
If you do, you have to address it the same way.
But, you know, every so often, every few years, people come down with a fever or whatever.
This is different.
This is if it's a recurring thing and it's on a schedule.
This is how I would address it.
But, again, just to recap, if you have to go get antihistamines or whatever, do it.
But I wouldn't go all the way as far as saying, oh, you have to come in and take a steroid shot.
Right.
I wouldn't do that.
That's a little too extreme.
If you're at that point, it's more than just allergies, you see.
So that's what I'd say about the health aspect.
There is no general health.
I love the term general health practitioner.
Oh, my goodness.
How is that going to work out?
When I used to be involved in bicycle racing or people that I knew that were fit and they wanted to go see a medical doctor,
it's funny how I'd say I'm going to go see the doctor like there's the doctor, right, but a medical person.
I'd say whatever you do, don't go to a general practitioner.
You must go to a sports doctor.
You must.
You have no choice at this point.
The reason why I said why, Greek, because these regular general practitioners, they're used to seeing people that are out of shape,
people that are old and people that have been hooked on drugs and don't know how to take care of themselves.
You walk in, even if you're feeling like crap, you're like a very well-developed specimen of a human,
they're going to look at you and you're the best looking and the most fit person they've seen in like five years.
They're going to tell you there's nothing wrong with you.
You see what I mean?
Because they're just used to looking at really crappy specimens, let's say.
So if you're in good shape, you must go to a sports doctor,
someone who's used to seeing people that are already very fit so they can discern the fine point.
You see what I mean?
This analogy goes with pretty much everything.
Whether you have a car, you get an oil change at one of these quick stops
or you go to a place that's a performance, you get a completely different oil change, right?
So yeah, that's what I would say about the health.
It seems like I always end up in any health discussion, even one like this one,
where I just don't know what to say about health because I don't know.
You see, I don't know what your situation is.
And talk about the antithesis of a one-size-fits-all.
If what I'm saying holds true, I've pretty much destroyed about 100 million videos on YouTube about health.
Easily.
So I guess this would be for the listener to discern and apply.
What I'm saying also involves you in the process.
You can't be lazy about it.
You ever heard about these life coach, I don't know, self-help people?
Make a list of all the things you want to do.
Just don't leave it up to chance or whatever.
Just make a list of where you want to be and what you want to do.
Well, I'm sorry to say that's pretty good advice.
Yeah, yeah.
Make a list of what you think your health should be.
And by the way, when you plan, it's called planning, you will achieve it with minimum effort
because it only takes a small amount per day.
This is the same thing about studying.
I used to always tell people if you want to learn about a subject,
you don't try to eat it all in one bite.
You do five minutes, a half hour, 20 minutes, whatever per day.
Or three times a week.
And before you know it, you've gone through thousands of pages of whatever,
memorialized or videos or whatever, after a year.
You see?
It's the same thing with the health situation.
Unfortunately, with most cases, when a personal discussion arises,
something very specific, and it's usually too late.
So you have to usually submit the remedy, you know, the opposite energetic
to cancel out what they're experiencing in most cases.
Right.
Well, you know, I think this subject has been addressed quite well.
And again, you know, it's rather interesting to me
because immediately when you started talking about these, you know,
life coach type people, I thought of Tony Robbins, you know, as an example.
Where, you know, on one level, you know, he's a clown like most others.
But on another level, some of it's rather practical, you know.
And what do I mean by this?
Well, a lot of times people talk about, you know, your level of confidence,
how you carry yourself, right?
Things like this, what you're transmitting.
And we touched upon that briefly in a previous Sonic,
regarding, you know, the gestures and things like this,
what it is you're communicating,
not necessarily always with your voice or your words particularly.
But what about the idea, though, of, you know, like, again,
thinking about these people who say, okay, draw up a plan,
draw up a dream board, so to speak, whatever.
You know, a lot of that is based on confidence and what you project.
That's not invalid, although I got to say it's very childish
the way it's presented a lot of times.
And yeah, you're making useless a whole bunch of YouTube videos
and sets of videos and probably people's channels
that they're making a living on with the health thing.
But when it comes to this, what about the idea of confidence
and, you know, how it is projected, I guess, and attitude?
I mean, what about that?
Because that's a big part of this as well, isn't it?
Perception versus confidence, I guess, would be the way to think about it,
or confidence of your perception.
Or by addition, confidence and perception, right?
Sure.
Okay, let's talk about that a little bit.
Well, you know, think about it.
We perceive however we perceive, usually with our eyes and ears,
and we think about things, and we take the menace to be true
or as a basis of knowledge, or whether it's cultural
or we like the way it is very often.
You hear people in a discussion, someone will say,
well, I don't agree with that.
So what they're telling you is it can't be true
because I don't like what you're saying, right?
So this is the confidence and the perception mixed.
So when you perceive something to be true, you hold it in confidence as such.
What if you find out that what you perceive to be true is not true?
Well, in certain cases, you might still want to hold it out
because it's a form of control and acceptance.
But let's say you perceive something now very differently
as it was before perceived.
Should you still remain confident in it?
And the answer to that in most cases is no.
You lose confidence, right?
Now what about the other way?
What if you have perceived something and are confident in it,
but it is contrary to what other people perceive and are confident in?
A quick analogy would be people perceive CNN or Fox News or MSNBC
and they're confident in the information they're getting, right?
So then you approach that individual or person or group
and you're pretty confident that it's all BS
or 90% of it is 100% BS, okay?
Well, what happens there?
They're going to perceive you as a nutcase or contrary, right?
And here's an interesting thing, which you went over really quickly,
but I want to just hit it again.
This idea of agreement, it's a misnomer
because when somebody says, I agree or I disagree,
that's a loaded statement.
They're not just talking about their agreement or their alignment.
It's a bit more of a loaded statement, like you were saying,
which is interesting to me in that some people have different motivations
for their alleged agreement or alleged disagreement,
which again goes far beyond what they are saying,
because it's not just, okay, I agree with you, Greek.
It's I'm saying that not only do I agree with you,
but I perceive what you're saying as true.
It's not just that I align with you.
I'm not qualifying it by saying I have the same experience
or I have the same understanding or education,
and I don't mean education from a standard point.
I mean literal, true education.
You've actually learned something where you might recognize,
oh, I have learned a similar thing or the same thing.
There's a difference there, but people in shorthand kind of go,
I agree, I disagree.
Well, yeah, I'm just translating the gesture.
You ever listen to a host?
He's interviewing someone and they basically, oh, yeah, absolutely.
The host says, well, absolutely, absolutely,
and then they change the subject?
Yes.
That word absolute is a very, very heavy term to use it loosely like that.
But if you translate that, when you hear that,
the host placating the guest, yeah, absolutely, absolutely,
and they change the subject, it's basically saying,
yeah, I want to make this an interesting quote-unquote show,
so let's keep moving on to other topics,
and I want to sound like I still have, you know,
there's many ways to translate that, but they're not listening.
They're not listening.
So, in other words, being able to translate words as gestures,
gestures of dismissal, gestures of cognitive dissonance,
these are all gestures, and they're cloaked in these words,
which are heavily coded.
But the thing is, going back to the perception, we're perceiving,
in other words, you could be in a, let's say,
the greatest, most secret library in the universe,
and it's pitch black,
and you rely on eyes to read what's there.
It's a reading material, and it's always dark.
You're not going to be able to perceive anything.
You're not going to be able to,
and nothing will be imparted to you because your perception is off, right?
So there are many ways to block that,
also having a language you don't comprehend.
But we take in through perception, and then we, whether judge it,
in other words, ruminate, meditate on it,
you know, is this something I should be confident in, right?
And then you build up this confidence,
which is your measuring stick on that subject,
and there's conflict based on that.
Because if other people, let's say someone has perceived
that the opposite of what you are confident in is the truth,
and you believe that this is the truth, which is antagonistic,
you both come together, your perceptions clash,
and what your, the thickness of your armor,
and how you defend it is based on how much confidence you have in the subject.
So the ultimate point here is, just to fast forward,
we live in a reality, let's say we, the collective we,
that responds to your input into that reality.
And it's, you know, everyone's saying,
what can I get out of it?
It's actually what you put into it.
You know, your desires, your wants,
what you want to manifest is put out.
You say, you know, what is it?
You harvest what you, you reap what you sow.
And all that, right?
So you're sowing as we put in to the ground, and then it comes out.
So you're, we live in a reality where,
whether you want to attribute it to the gods, to the ether,
to a simulation, to a construct, to the matrix, whatever.
It is very, very receptive to what we put out into it,
and what we get back is what we've put out in most cases.
It depends if you join a group.
If you join a group, and you're one of those in a group,
the leader of that group puts something out that affects you.
So that's another concept of the follower and being individual.
But I would say the idea that you perceive something
and now have made it confident,
you're confident in that, and you hold that around,
will benefit you, right?
How many times have you heard, I'm meeting people of like mind?
When you hear that, that means that they are also confident,
similarly, in things that you are confident with.
Let's say knowledge base, right?
Okay?
The quote-unquote conspiracy researchers and all that,
they'll have a convention, and they all,
they might still be a little antagonistic,
but generally they're all there because they're confident
in this particular subject as being true,
where everyone else would say these are where the nutcases go.
Well, an easy example.
I go to the JFK conferences on occasion.
I'm planning on going this year.
And the reason why I'm there is because we all,
at the very least, have an agreement
that it is valid to question the official conclusion
regarding that assassination.
And we believe that we have an idea that there is a difference.
I'm going as open as possible on this
to make it as common as possible among us
that we all believe that, at the very least,
the official explanation is incorrect.
And we wish to present the real or the truth or et cetera, right?
So everybody there can agree on that.
Now, they may have disagreements about how to get there,
what the methodology is, what the most important aspect is,
but we are of a like mind in that way,
so therefore we convene, right?
Sure.
Or you're looking for a more plausible experience
because you might think it's this shooter
or the other guy might think it's another shooter,
and you might argue about it,
but at the end of the conference you both know
that your shooter or the other guy's shooter
is not part of the main narrative anyway, you see.
Well, that's the development of it in the purpose for the gathering,
but that's what happens in many cases,
whether it's a lunch meeting or a convention or a conference.
You know, you confer, right?
Yeah.
Well, you and I have gone through that.
I have a strong feeling intuitively that James Files
is one of the guys that pulled the trigger.
He'll even say there were two others,
where you don't think the guy has got any, what would you say,
when you validate or verify.
He's not verifiable or validatable or he's not genuine enough, right?
You and I can go through whatever.
You just give so many details that he seems to feel, right?
But neither one of us will ever say Oswald had anything to do with it
when he was most likely at the Coke machine, right?
There you go.
Fair example.
So the perception and the confidence here is this.
There is going to be a clash.
The different perceptions will give the variety,
but the arguing, how much energy someone puts into
either offending or fighting someone
or defending their own belief is how confident they are in it, right?
So at the same time, when you consider that this reality that we live on
rewards those that are confident, right?
So then you have always a two-fold decision.
Like, okay, so I'm into this quote-unquote alternative stuff, one might say,
but if my family finds out, they think I'm a wacko, okay?
But you still have to maintain the confidence in that
because if it is true,
because that confidence that you maintain in it will reward you.
In other words, the construct will reward you.
The universe supports those that are confident, not those that are not.
But at the same time, you have to realize that if there is a possibility of antagonism,
it's not going to be with what the other people are confident in.
It's just their perception.
So there's a fine balance between exuding your confidence in what you know
and also offending and others perceiving it,
that they might be antagonistic to it.
But you want the simulacrum or the construct or the matrix,
whatever you call it in your mind, to receive that confidence.
You must broadcast that confidence in what you quote-unquote believe in and know
in order to reap the benefits of it.
But at the same time, tiptoe around everyone else's perceptions of you.
Right.
But you will run into the criticism, though.
The main thing is when someone is set off when you say something, right?
Or they call it triggering, right?
People around you, it could be critical sometimes.
You might lose a job, right?
That's the latest common term.
You trigger somebody because you've offended some preconceived notion
of one type or another.
I'm trying to do this as objectively as possible, right?
Well, it's perception.
And their ability to fight you on it is how confident they are on their position.
Well, not necessarily their ability, but their enthusiasm,
their level of effort that they're willing to exert.
It may not necessarily be their ability
because they could be a very poor debater or defender of said belief, let's say,
or said thing that they are confident in,
but they have no adequate way to defend it.
That's a possibility as well.
They could just have the confidence,
and the confidence is unfounded by anything that's useful.
Well, how could they be confident in it?
Well, I observe this happens.
I'm not saying it's logical.
I'm just saying I observe it happens.
It's an observation as opposed to something that makes sense,
as many things are on the planet.
Well, you see, it's a difficult thing to explain,
but what I'm trying to convey here, especially after the help,
that this is part of your situation here in this reality,
your meaning the general you, the corporate you,
however you want to perceive you,
the way we interact with our environment,
meaning not just people but just our thoughts.
If you're alone and you're planning your day,
you're putting out a field and energy, literally, that will come back to you.
Let's say, for example, listen to a bunch of Greeks speak.
A lot of the comments that I've gotten is,
no one around me believes what I'm saying.
They think I'm crazy, but I know what you're saying is true.
I've looked it up and validated it, right, for example.
So then what do you do?
Well, what's happening is you're trying to blend your confidence with their perception.
In other words, somehow it doesn't mean throttle back how confident you are.
It's just don't affect their perception.
You have to sort of tiptoe around more on the overt
because most of the people, for example, that believe in the BS that's out there,
and let's say for a moment all the BS that's out there is fine.
The reality that we live in, quote, unquote, the mainstream, let's say,
which has been mainstream since ancient times,
is fine and is hunky-dory and it's just the way things should be.
Let's just say that, and you don't need to hear another side.
Actually, you never need to really look up what things are supposed to be based on.
Just go along with what everyone thinks they are.
Will you be okay?
Yeah.
So, for example, if you're in the mainstream
and you believe that it's okay to get sick for a week with a fever or the common cold or whatever
and be sick as a dog, as they say, that's totally normal.
You will never know that there is a, quote, unquote, better way
or a way you can, how would you say, take control of that so it doesn't happen.
In most cases, it may not work,
but at least you have more of the possibility in your mind that you can take control over it.