69, just because I want to say that up front, okay, there you go.
I got to be childish for a moment.
Why not?
I feel childish because I'm on a planet, I think, full of children, in a way, anyway,
Greek, how are you tonight?
How's your time going?
From a lascivious point of view, we used to say Muff Divers Union Local 69.
That's it.
But anyway.
But then again, what is it, the mid-90s or so, I guess I noticed that Muff Diving became
an endangered sport because, you know, things change.
Whatever.
Actually, they don't.
There's many things that, what is it, acquired immune deficiency syndrome, right?
There isn't.
No, it doesn't exist.
It's a way to take advantage of the continuing genocide program.
What happened with it, by the way, we're not going to talk about this tonight, but I'll
just bring this up again as a refresher, that there have been genocide programs, you know,
the Native Americans in the U.S., and at the same time, you know, every 50 years all over
the world, there's a genocide program, you know, the Armenian-Greek genocide, the genocides
during World War II, and then after that in Cambodia, right, with Bopat.
And, yeah, so what's happened with genocide, this is a sonic on its own, really, and I
could bring up more on it because I've been watching it since the 80s when it was really
hitting on the retrospective perspective.
Oh, yeah, and it knows no boundaries because, I mean, you had the Tutsis and the Hutsis
or whatever over there in, you know, Rwanda, you had that, you had...
Sort of, yeah, they just go to villages, cut people's arms off.
But what happened in the 80s, they retrospected all these genocidal things that were going
on, but what they took it, they took the nationality, ethnicity, and culture nationality out of
it, and they just made it now it's across the board, all humans are subject to genocide
through medical assassination, I call it.
So in short, what they did was they came up with a variation of something called a test,
which is totally random, an AIDS test.
It's also been used on the COVID stuff, the same test, right, but with a variation.
And supposedly it counts certain, basically, pus in the blood, right, which you can increase
by eating raw meat or certain food preservatives.
Yeah, there's a whole bunch of their alleged tests that, quite honestly, you can throw
them off by eating too rare a piece of meat and you'll come up positive for a whole bunch
of them.
Yeah, I told anyone that if you want to test positive on an AIDS test, just eat a rare
hamburger, especially, and you'll test positive on it.
But they don't, this is what I found out even later, they don't even run these tests.
I mean, they batch them and it's just random, you know, it's random, like the lottery.
But a bloody rare steak, I mean, you could literally turn up with anything from colon
cancer to AIDS on the various trips if they run them.
If they run them, but they didn't, actually, because there were so many people doing it
and so many few that were equipped to do the test, which they knew didn't work anyway.
Just like most DNA testing doesn't show much.
But what happened was the propaganda machine was already set up.
So anyone who tested positive or not, but usually positive, they got bombarded.
See, they in order in order to get the test, they want your contact information.
So now that they have your contact information, they barrage people with propaganda that,
you know, you have been potentially all presumptive language that people take as a fact
that the language went like you potentially have something that might be a very serious
disease. You have potentially tested positive.
Never, you know, they never say you tested for anything, but the presumptive language.
But when people take it as fact, so they keep barraging you should consider treatment.
But I don't have any symptoms.
Well, that's it'll be too late if you have symptoms.
You should try the treatment before you have symptoms.
Right. Well, guess what happened?
The drugs that are being used, I can I remember I did have all the technical breakdown on
this, by the way, they do. It's easy to find.
Well, I don't know about now. You're talking about the AZT and all that, which is a
hormone. There was a guy that you might have interviewed also that supposedly died of
tooth abscess. He was he wrote a book called Official Stories for Officials Only or
something. In fact, yes, he was a good friend of mine, Liam Sheff, Liam Sheff.
Yeah, I think they he died of a toothache.
Basically, I think he was getting a little too close to being popular on what he was
saying, which was very unpopular, which was that AIDS didn't exist at all.
No, it doesn't. It's the drugs that cause it.
People went out and the mechanism.
Yeah, people went after him very badly.
He didn't die of a toothache, actually.
But but what happened is he went to the dentist and then suddenly you I did not know you
knew that story. Yeah, he had an infection and it got worse and his ears exploded
internally or something.
Did you know? Yeah, yeah.
I had spoken to him a couple of times.
Yeah, I was introduced to him on the by Vinny Eastwood and I broke it down and he was
just amazed that I knew about the inner workings of it.
He says, you're from New York, right?
This is. Yeah, I could basically says I could tell a slight accent.
I'm like, oh, that sucks, man.
Don't tell me you could tell a slight accent from New York.
That's not good. It's very anyway.
It's very, very subtle with you.
Very, very subtle. But the thing I mean, you know, with me, it's like you can tell him
from Jersey, Jersey.
Yeah, of course. If you watch any Pesci or you watch any Jack Nicholson or you watch
any of this, you watch The Sopranos.
You know what it is. It's exactly like one of those guys.
No, I'm totally not aware that you were because I was actually the last person to
speak to him publicly.
And I knew he technically speaking, he took his own life.
Great. Oh, OK.
Well, I could see that from pain, right?
Or discomfort. Or, yes, all of the above.
And what happened is after he went to the wow, I've never talked to a dentist.
He went to a dentist and he yeah, there was such a horrible ringing in his ears
afterwards that it started driving him crazy.
He could not stop it.
And then there were too many problems in his head.
And he said, you know what, I don't want to be here anymore.
Yeah, that's the typical microwave weapon, by the way.
It just cooks a little bit of the brain, cooks a little bit of the body.
And the ringing that is very typical of radioactive radioactivity, by the way.
Well, that's what if you used to be I did look at a study back in the library back
in the 80s and 90s of what if you die of radioactive poisoning, there's several
we're talking about just the melanomas and the skin manifestations getting irradiated
from the inside. There's like major things.
But the typical ones was, you know, like severe pneumonia, severe diarrhea
and ringing in the ears, tinnitus.
But it was beyond tinnitus, you know.
Right. Well, Liam, really bizarre.
I did not know that that story was publicly or it was known by very many people
outside of myself and his partner at the time.
No, I kept looking him up because he was the only other person drawing attention to
this that I knew of in public.
Well, that's when they actually started to go after him.
You know, he touched on every other, you know, conspiracy, whatever, conspiracy in
the culture of medicine.
It was fine. Yeah. Food, medicine, all that was fine, fine, fine.
And when he really wrote extensively about the the charade of AIDS, that's.
Yeah. Well, he got impressed that I knew this because he he never got into it.
He thought that people would just lose it.
I said it was very simple.
It's called epithelial apoptosis.
It's a thing in the body that, you know, your cells, you know, they say you're in
all the cells replacing your body every seven years.
Well, there are cells, especially like in the cheek and the nose and in the colon
that replace every day.
And that's epithelial cells.
And when they replace they and they grow back, they they release a small hormone to
let the body know that, hey, we've grown back.
So what all he was was a synthetic form of that hormone.
And all you got to do is give it to someone.
And when they have the natural epithelial apoptosis cells falling off, that hormone
says that the cells have grown back, but they haven't.
So that natural process of cells falling off don't get most of them don't grow back
because you're bathing and your blood is full of this hormone that says that they've
grown back. Right.
So then you get these fat tumors and or some people get these big lumps and fat
tumors and die of toxicity.
Others look like they're the concentration camp, you know, on the food when you fast
for, you know, whatever, you know, yeah, not eating starvation diet like one of the
starvation. Yep.
And sores all over and pneumonia because the lungs are very sensitive to this.
So and that's what it was.
There's a person died of AIDS because test of AIDS.
Everybody applauds and goes and thanks the doctors for all their help.
And no one, I assure you this, no one positively, absolutely no one has died of
AIDS that put it this way.
No one positively, without a doubt, anyone who has tested positive for AIDS, doesn't
matter how many times that did not receive treatment, died from AIDS.
No one. Only the people that receive treatment that, of course, didn't have symptoms
because there is no symptoms.
Right. See, so there is a level of where is.
So it's a big distraction.
So, you know, how many doctors and scientists and politicians and regulatory people know
what I just said? Thousands.
Where is the outrage?
Why aren't these people being pulled out of their homes in the middle of the night?
Right. And arrested and taken.
Right. Why isn't this made public?
Well, because that's just the way it's supposed to be.
You're almost you're almost saying verbatim what Liam said.
OK, you the both of you are you're you're actually like seriously, like this is exactly
the speech that he would give to me off air on air didn't matter.
And he absolutely he talked to me and said, you know what, it's liver dysfunction.
And it all that stuff you just described with the epithelial cells and the the problem
with the toxin. It's all liver.
It's all liver. Yeah.
Yeah. By the way, by the way, the liver loves coffee.
I've been trying to kill myself with drinking a gallon of coffee for the past 15 years.
It's not working. And I have a hard liver whenever I go to typically when I was bike
racing and get massage.
Your liver's real hard. I said, oh, yeah, I'll just finish myself off by drinking coffee
because I'm a speed. I'm an upper kind of guy.
Right. Right. So I'm drinking.
I still drink coffee.
My liver is doing great. Thank you.
I'm doing great. You know, you don't have such a great you got a bum liver, but, you
know, I'm doing great for the coffee, but it taxes other parts.
So anyway, what I'm trying to say is that anything you take, especially if you look
at the big diabetes epidemic, is no such thing.
Go look up anyone.
Do a search on why my blood sugar tests are not accurate.
They'll tell you it's because you're either dehydrated or you just drank a bunch of
water because there is no such thing as blood sugar.
There is a blood glucose derivative that appears can be measured directly.
If you had sugar in your blood, you'd be dead, by the way.
Right. Just like these other things.
Right. So it's a derivative, you know, like, for example, when you work in the oil and
gas, there's something sulfur hydroxide.
It's a rotten, rotten egg smell.
Right. Yeah.
And it's it's in comes up.
But when it gets to a toxic level, it becomes odorless.
Imagine because really, logically, you'd say, well, the stronger the the rotten egg
smell from the natural crude means it's getting worse.
We should get out of here. No.
What happens is smells like rotten eggs.
And when it gets to a lethal dose level, it goes completely odorless.
So you don't even know. Right.
You see, it's very lethal that way.
Right. So and there's no they have no way of measuring this gas directly, but they
know it reacts with other gases.
So when they see this reaction happening with other gases, they say there's a lethal
presence. That's what the meters, how the meters work.
There's no way to measure it directly, just like there's no way to measure blood
glucose levels directly.
You see, it's an indirect measurement and it's based on liver function.
That's why when you're thirsty, OK, you've heard this many years when the football
coach at high school, everybody's thirsty.
They run off the field. He says, drink just a little bit of water.
Don't drink a lot. Right.
Don't guzzle. When you're an athlete, you don't want to you just want to sip a
little bit of water no matter how thirsty you are.
So you don't put your liver in shock.
But in Asian, by the way, medicine, the pancreas are not considered an organ.
They're an adjunct to the liver.
They're not considered a separate organ.
Right. You know, it's a grouping.
You know, the kidneys are the liver is, you know, the stomach.
But the pancreas are not they're not considered just like the ancient Egypt.
They didn't mummify the brain.
They had didn't consider it to have any value.
Right. So it's part of it.
So anyway, all this stuff that they're putting on people is exactly what the
it's the same mindset.
So where is the outrage?
And there is no outrage because that's look, this is what I wanted to really talk
about tonight. You asked maybe about time.
Yeah, I'll tie this.
I did. But hold on a second, because this ties directly to something else.
Just really quickly.
The only thing that I have noticed people agreeing on as of late.
Right. And it's very strange.
It's very subtle, is that if you if you get people that have some level of
outrage that are upset about what's happening, they
all only seem to agree on one thing.
And that is that we are dealing with a massive culling here.
That there is no.
But I disagree because you when you say culling.
But I'm not asking you to agree.
I'm telling you what I'm noting from the general population, OK, is that they
are saying that they feel as though the entire
group that is humanity is basically eligible.
Now, this is not.
Yeah, yeah. Well, I agree with that.
That's what the AIDS was about before.
It was nationality, race or whatever.
More beefs. Yeah.
Now it's a beef with everyone.
Right. That's that's the odd thing that is just starting to emerge
in the consciousness.
I see. I don't know how to explain that.
But it's it's so wild that you bring up, Liam.
I'm sorry. I knew Liam before I knew you.
And I wasn't aware that you knew him, you know, because he was very compartmentalized
with who he spoke to and stuff.
I messaged him a little bit. He was just impressed that I knew about the, you know,
the epithelial, how the drug I was targeted because most people.
Oh, right. Here, let me just lead off to another thing real quick, another tangent
here. It's not really a tangent, but it is when when AIDS
came up in the 80s, I remember in New York City they were putting up these
bills, you know, like posters at night saying, oh, AIDS is created in a
government lab. Right.
That's right. So people think it's still real.
It's another diversion. So when they do something like 9-11, COVID or AIDS
or diabetes or whatever, actually, they haven't done much.
But what they do is they have the event, they have the official story, then they
actually put out a few alternative stories to mislead you.
Right. Well, that's where they came up with the whole the guy had sex with a
monkey thing. Yeah, exactly.
Same people that they put that out.
So the people that don't say, well, if the government says it's this or the
officials, it can't be that it must be the monkeys.
So they divert just like 9-11.
It's a one on one textbook nuclear demolition.
You could watch a hundred videos on Project Plowshare.
It's identical, the mechanism and everything.
The react surface reactions and all that.
But they say, oh, you got Judy Woods and these other people, not to mention
names, say that it's space weapons or
or the idiots who put dynamite on each floor.
Oh, my gosh. You know, so they put out the same thing.
But it's it goes on and on and on.
But here's the thing about the to go back to what I was saying.
Whatever you say about people, most of the people on the planet are backdrop.
You know, when you're going to create a realistic simulation or a situation
in art, whether it's theater, film, what have you, you need a backdrop.
Right. So the backdrop is the place and it's also the people.
So I assure you, it could even be your husband, your wife, your children, your
parents. They're not real.
There are very few real people, meaning people that have a level of development
that can actually function as what a human can be defined as.
That's a mouthful. Most people are backdrops.
And I would suggest that the amount of people that are real is getting to the one
in ten thousand, one in a thousand.
So you can you can actually go out and meet a hundred people and ten could be real
people. You can go out and meet five thousand people.
Only one would be real. It's not an even spread, you know, but you're not going to
meet real, very rare.
It's getting more rare, more people.
So no matter what, again, people thinking this and people believing that there's
still the backdrop people.
Right. You get it.
So now this is where I wanted to go with this on time.
You said, well, let's talk about time.
Well, how many times have you heard me say on the airy, fairy new age?
There is no time. They're correct.
But if you ask them why there's no time, they can't tell you.
Just like a Christian, you're being saved.
Saved from what? They don't know.
Right. Right.
Time is mainly the recordation of events.
That's all it is. So if you have no record of time, like you're not going back and
memorializing, which means either digitally or writing it down or drawing a wall, a
picture on a wall of an event that happened with a time marker, astronomical or made up
calendar, there is no time.
Correct. The time that you experience during the day, whether you had a long day or
short day, that is also variable.
Right. How many times you heard if you're busy, the day goes by fast.
If you're in a waiting room all day, it feels like you were there for a week.
I experience it all the time.
Yeah, experience. It's purely the event.
So but what I'm trying to say is for those that are real humans, you will notice
that especially in the past five years, regular chores and things that you did, whether
it was laundry, cleaning the house, washing the car, going to work, something, the
normal stuff that didn't that is taking longer and longer and longer to do and
becoming more of an arduous task.
You'll notice that what I've hypothecated till now and I actually voiced it
yesterday was that we're basically here.
They're the real humans to waste your time.
Basically, is it a waste of time?
No. But what it is, it's stretching, stretching out your life, things that you can
accomplish in a couple of years, stretching it out to take 70 years.
Right. OK.
Stuff that perfect example would be the education system in America.
They have kindergarten through 12th grade, right?
K through 12. Let's just call it one through 12.
It's when you look, you're in school from fall to spring.
You take summer off basically in the morning, the three or seven to two.
When you add up all that, it's a thousand hours a year.
So it's 12000 hours to go from K to 12 or first to 12th grade.
Right. By the way, college is also in grade.
So you're your next four years in college means you are 16th grade, right?
Graduate level, 18th grade, 20th grade is PhD.
Yeah. OK. That still works that way.
If you go look at government records, what great if you look at someone's government
file. Greek, how do you know this?
OK, that's another story.
If you have a bachelor's degree, it says you went to the 16th grade.
Right. So anyway, it's commercial grading, right?
Like grade A, grade B, whatever.
OK, so what's happening is if you look at the 12000 hours of education, I can
personally teach someone to exceed that in less than 300 hours.
I can teach what they teach in 12000 hours or anyone can do it.
All you need is 300 hours of that 12000 hours to get the equivalent of what they
write. So they're stretching out their time.
Most people, they call them NPCs.
I do agree with that. They're non-player characters.
You'll see them. They gravitate towards they don't question anything.
They complain when the rest of them complain.
Right. They're like on a hive kind of thing.
And they do the sports.
They do the job, you know, this, that and the other.
And they procreate. And out of the procreation of the NPCs, they could they can
have a real person.
Like, for example, my parents are NPCs.
Right. To most of the degree.
Most of the people that I've met and had relationships are NPCs.
Most. So where does that put me?
Well, how can you parents be an NPC Greek and you're not?
Well, maybe I am an NPC.
It's up to you to decide. You think where it fits.
So what I'm saying, it's a mixed bag of stuff.
It's very much how you can have everyone in the family.
He's got brown eyes and brown hair.
But suddenly, little Joey, he's got blonde hair and blue eyes.
How'd that happen? Well, way back.
There's you should go back in the log pile.
You'll see that your great uncle was like that.
Right. So the gene just happened to emerge at that point.
Very similar.
The recessive gene, they call it.
Sure. Whatever.
Yeah. Whatever name they put to it.
I have very low credence in the science.
So what I'm trying to say is like, think of life as a bubble.
They have these bubble things.
You know, you buy soap with a little ring and you blow these little bubbles
and they have the more deluxe kit and it's a bigger bubble blower.
And then they have the ones where, you know, the showman, you know,
you hire clowns or whatever at a birthday party.
They have these big loops and they have a big cookie sheet when they put the soap
and they blow this big bubble. It's like three feet long.
You've seen them, right?
But they're all bubbles and they pop just the same.
So your life here on this incarnation is like this soap bubble.
And it's a long soap bubble.
Unless you try to be like a little bubble
and you just sit in there with the collective shows to do.
What I've noticed is
almost from a retrospective
recapitulation of looking back at all this stuff.
It's like, you know, you get a lot of woulda, coulda, shouldas.
I have no regret ever because I've processed what that is, you know,
and you always learn you learn more from mistakes and misgivings
than you do from everything being smooth. Right.
So that's why actually people with a college education are not revered
as much as those that have experience in the same field. Why?
Because you're going to learn more.
No, you learn more because you learn because you've actually seen
more screw ups in the field. Right.
It's not because you actually see the experience shows you more script.
So they know how not to do it.
If you learn, the thing is, if you can learn from the scripts,
that's where it's really, really is.
What I've noticed is that everything that I've done in my life,
I'm almost approaching 60 in my sixth decade already.
I'm going to be 60 soon.
Is that everything that I've accomplished and all of it
could have been done in less than 15 years.
But not that I've accomplished anything noteworthy.
I'm just saying that anything that I have achieved and learned from,
I could have done if I compressed my life down to being a 15 year old,
I could have achieved this, which means that
I could have done it all in just a few years,
because you really don't have a lot of liberty until you get to 12, 13, 14, 15.
Anyway, right. Right. Actually, 18 years old.
You're not allowed to participate in many things. Right.
But back in the days when I was growing up,
I mean, I pretty much did everything by 15 years old.
Yes, everything. Now, you know what I anyway.
So gotcha. Yeah, everything.
So I've done everything that I need. Yeah. OK, so.
So if you break it down to that, my entire life,
I could have experienced in one year if we lived in a real world
where things were encouraged.
Like, give me an example.
Well, I'm going fast tonight and I haven't even had any coffee.
Well, I have coffee, but I'm not drinking as much as I usually do.
But here, maybe it's the fresh air.
This is the thing.
The. How do you say this?
It's really hard to explain, but I'll just give more of a description.
So the element of time.
Is is not is not the what's recorded, but how the quality of the event.
So in essence, let me just sum up everything I said.
I actually feel like I'm a 15 year old
because I have the experiences of a 15 year old up to this point.
I have not. I have not done a lot.
And actually, I have done more than most people several lifetimes have.
Right. I get I discuss people that have worked in heavy industry
and ask me, well, where do you work?
I never worked in heavy.
How do you know so much about heavy industry?
I talk to a cardiologist.
He says, where's your residency?
I know he's like you sound like a cardiologist.
I speak to an attorney.
Where where are you practicing?
I never you see.
So it's like catch me if you can.
I can sit with many, many, many disciplines and discuss the
that discipline as if I've been working in it for many decades.
And I haven't.
And I feel like I have the experience of a 15 year old.
Why? Because we live in this artificial kind of
stretch elastic kind of reality
where where here's an example.
Have you ever heard of someone discovering a process, a device or something
and other people don't want to know about it or use it?
And you almost have to convince them, you know, convince others
to get involved or use what's actually good for them.
Could you imagine that?
What kind of a retarded situation is that?
Right. Yeah, I've heard of that. Sure.
Yeah. Imagine having to convince someone just do this.
It'll be better for you.
And they don't want to.
And you have to actually convince what when a real reality,
all you would have to do is make them aware and acknowledge it.
And then they would naturally see that as the better alternative.
We should, of course, we should do this.
Right. So the level of resistance that is put here.
In other words,
for to to blow a big soap bubble, you have to have a lot of resistance
for that to happen, right?
Because if there's not any resistance, the bubble won't form. Right.
You have to have equal amount of resistance on both sides of the bubble. Right.
Right. So the temperature changes and all that, you know,
make it easy to pop in the surface tension and all that.
So we live in this thing where if you recapitulate on your life,
think back of everything that you've done, you'll notice it's not continuous.
It's just certain events that you try to latch onto and copy
in these big segments of time in between. Right.
If you were to, you know, put someone in a room and write down
everything you've done in your life in the next three hours,
you'll see there are big gaps between certain events.
You might concentrate most of the in a few years.
And there's a huge gap. Why?
Because it's it's this we live in this distorted, perceptive thing,
almost like the Mayans said we live or the Aborigines.
We live in the dream world where this is not real.
That's why some people have dreams that are more realistic than being here.
Right. Right. So I still don't have a handle on fully what's going on.
But when something is brought forth
or to me or to anyone, I would suggest try to learn a little bit about its history
and how and how others perceive it, if it's different from how you perceive it.
So if you go somewhere, for example, everyone says this is the way we do things.
But to you, it doesn't feel right.
You should look into it.
Just don't jump in and do it because everyone else is doing it.
You know, trust that feeling, which is more than the gut.
Right. It's the heart. Right.
So once you start looking at that and now, believe it or not,
it's getting even harder to find stuff.
You can't go to a good you can't find a good library to find reference materials
anymore on, you know, good things, things that were memorialized
and kept in good record form.
So what I've discovered and I was thinking and talking about this yesterday
is that it's just like a soap bubble.
You've got different sizes and you've got these big, you know, tricks up soap bubbles.
You might have seen a member of Washington Square Park in Manhattan.
You'd have these carnival guys going on, blow these eight foot long soap bubbles,
you know? Yes. Yeah.
So that's what it's like.
It's very fragile and and whatever.
And it's stretched out.
And just to go back to how I started this
is anyone who is a real human.
Just try to recall your basic chores that you do.
Right. And how how it felt a few years ago and how it feels now
and how it's like just drudgery now. Right.
And I've talked to several people that are real.
And it's like, you know, notice things are just stretched out,
you know, and harder and harder to do. Right.
So some people would describe this to me as you just in a holding pattern
for a while, like you're waiting, waiting room, the waiting room.
There you go. Yeah.
We talked about the waiting room from back in the days.
Hello, Robin, if you're listening.
I don't know if you're around anymore, but she started a small blog,
a little window thing called The Waiting Room a long time ago.
One of the early, early Greek speak stuff in 2015, I think.
Yes. Back in the time you were talking about the closing credits
were just in the waiting room waiting for the. Yeah.
It's stretching. So the whole thing is, you know, to say, have fun.
Daniel Ramirez said, like, have fun, guys.
Remember, it's always said, have fun, have fun, have fun.
And don't be nervous.
Or he'd give you a slight dinner from American Freedom Radio.
He's a good guy.
And regardless.
And he would just say, yeah, he'd give you some criticism.
Use this mic or that. Don't worry about that.
Have fun. Have fun. Have fun.
He kind of that's the message. Right. Really?
You know. Right. Just.
And yes, having fun at the expense of others sometimes.
Yeah. You might have to do that sometimes.
It depends on how serious you are about having fun.
Kind of like the the the simplified message of, you know, what is
what is the meaning of life? It is to live.
Yeah, it's just life. It is the meaning.
It's it's it's an all inclusive package.
It works. It works out well in the end.