54, according to my count, and here we go, the higher consciousness and how it can contain
lower consciousness.
You know, I'm not sure that we quite understand exactly what that means, Greek.
So why don't you start there?
There you go.
It goes.
It's a one way street.
You know, they say shit flows downstream.
OK, well, in other words, OK, think about it this way.
You could put a five pound bag in a 10 pound bag, but you can't put a 10 pound bag, you
know, loaded in a five pound bag.
Right.
That's an old thing.
You know, you're like a 10 pound bag, a 10 pound potato and a five pound bag.
Right.
Yeah.
Well, the old the old insult was what you look like, 10 pounds, 10 pounds of shit in
a five pound bag.
Right.
So that means I haven't heard that one, but that's maybe a Jersey thing.
Maybe so.
It means you're spilling out all over the place.
You look like a sloppy fucking mess.
Well, no, a higher consciousness, for example, I brought this up, for example.
Let's say this just is an academic example.
Someone who is a graduate student mathematics can walk into the third grade math class and
completely comprehend everyone's ability to do math, where if the third grader walks into
the graduate student math session, they will not be able to comprehend what they're doing.
Well, look, you talked about this thing with the change.
All right.
Where somebody thinks they're sorting change and oh, that's beneath me.
Different.
Well, that's different.
That's not the level of consciousness.
Well, sure.
That is a type of character.
Well, wait a minute.
But that is isn't character related to consciousness, though, because they're not conscious of what
it is they're demonstrating at all.
They're taking nothing quantitatively, maybe there is a correlation, but qualitatively consciousness
flips.
OK, usually a higher quality consciousness has also a larger quantity and vice versa.
A lower quality consciousness has also this is where the quantitative qualitative flip
happens.
You know.
All right.
You know what I mean by that?
OK, so a higher quality consciousness will also have a much higher capacity, volumetric
and quantity quantified, a higher qualitative consciousness can quantify more, a lower qualitative
consciousness quantifies less, always, always.
It seems to be a correlation.
Here, let's let's spin it off to this.
Like the I gave the analogies of having someone take a photograph to kind of read their character.
Right.
Most people will see.
I don't we'll say Greek.
I don't see how that does anything because they're that's that is an example of perception
and examination that requires a higher consciousness to see a higher qualitative and quantitative.
By the way, when you when you it's one of the few things where if you increase the quality,
the quantity automatically increases.
I would think you'd have to be an idiot to not understand that, you know, here's you
make a whole bunch of you make a whole bunch of subtle choices.
Look, just like with the change, you're making a whole bunch of subtle choices that to you.
No, no, no.
It's not choices.
What you're doing is you're exhibiting on many, many, many levels, which I gave a little
bit of the background.
Why is it coins and not jelly beans?
Yeah, but you because you're in a commercial setting.
I understand that.
Yeah.
But it's a primary thing.
OK, I'm comparing the picture to the change.
Bear with me a second.
The thing is, you're making a bunch of choices.
Let me let me just finish that, because there's a whole bunch of built in things that you're
going to reveal through those choices.
OK, more actions.
OK, very active.
If they're sitting there trying to make choices and decide on what they're going to do, that's
another aspect of, well, the action with the examination, really, you know, I'd say taking
an exam.
Yeah.
It's an examination.
Well, of course, that's what you're doing.
But when the person taking the photograph, OK, is really making a ball, you know, OK,
we're going to go back to the photograph.
That's different.
Yeah, that's a bunch of time.
OK, it's completely different.
That's a bunch of choices they made, though, because they choose an angle.
They choose a setting.
They choose how to focus.
It's if they can't see.
They don't see the choices to decide on.
You notice I keep bringing that up.
You know, there's a decision, but they're not doing the quantitative.
You are doing the quantitative and qualitative examination.
They're not.
They don't.
OK, but the camera example I gave is different.
OK, let's let's go over it real fast.
I know I'm going to get a lot of emails on this sarcastic ones.
I'm sorry.
But in a good way, it's revealing.
OK, I'm trying to sort it with you.
Go ahead.
Good.
Yeah.
No pun intended.
So here's the thing.
The camera is totally different.
OK, the camera is you have you're in a room with someone and asking them to take a picture
so you could sort of examine their character and how they perceive things that other people
will perceive that are not there.
It's a form of communication.
So, for example, if you are standing somewhere and you have an object on the table and you
ask someone to take a picture of it, you're both in the room.
You both know what that object looks like from many perspectives, meaning even if you're
not moving around, you have the central focus and then you have the peripheral, right?
You have slight movements.
Even your breathing is enough movement.
That's why they hold your breath when you do something very critical, like paint a line
or draw a pull trigger.
Right.
So even just the slightest bod, normal bodily movements are giving you more and more perspectives
on that object, even if you're not walking around it.
So you're in the room with the person and you already perceive all these things about the
object when the photograph is taken.
The photograph is taken to show others what you are both seeing is the intent and what
you are seeing about the character of the person when they take the photograph is thus.
You know what it looks like and you're trying to communicate through a photograph what this
looks like to others.
How well did you do that?
Right.
Very often I see this in people.
I'll say this.
So someone send me a photo and they send me a photo and I'm like, I'm not quite getting
like there's things missing, like very important things like scale.
The angle in which the photo was taken does not reveal the topic of why I wanted the photo.
Right.
So the first thing I tell people is like, look, you're there.
You see it.
I'm not there.
I don't see it.
So you have to express to me with a photograph the most revealing it would perception that
you have of the object that would represent as if I was there, by the way.
How many times do you hear a critique, a positive critique on film or music, photography, whatever?
And what is the critique of the audience?
I felt like I was there, there, right?
That's because who is the poise selection, final shot and finished delivery of that visual
or audio visual thing was considering how do we maximize that as if the person as if
to give the similar impact.
OK, so OK, as if you were there.
OK, so here's a simple.
Well, Eric Greek sounds like you're just making a point and I may not get it or whatever.
But here's the thing.
When you take a photograph of something, look at it and then ask yourself a question.
If I didn't, if I wasn't here and I just saw the photograph, how much of that does it give
me the feeling as if I am here?
And I'll tell you, most people when they take pictures versus what you don't have any clue
of a very slight clue, actually, I hate people when they say I don't have any idea.
Of course you do.
Don't you?
You know, on Earth.
Right.
So you do have that idea.
But anyway, you see what I mean?
So when someone takes photographs, I critique that often.
I said, look, I'm not there.
If you by the way, if you send me a photograph and I say I'm not there, you are.
You need a better photograph.
I'm basically calling you a fucking idiot.
Sorry.
Did I just say that?
No.
Sorry.
Actually, we don't edit that out.
Right.
Never.
Yeah.
OK.
So anyway.
But that's normal.
Right.
OK.
So do you see my point?
And look, this is this is part of the normal vernacular.
You'll hear common people see a photograph or a demo of something and say, wow, I feel
like I'm there.
Right.
And of course, that object they're talking about or seen or event or whatever has been
photographed many, many times shown to them many other ways.
But they don't say the same thing.
It's the same thing.
Right.
Well, you know, it's the way it's.
So when you do something, when you write something, when you say something, when you photograph
something, it's all forms of what communication.
Right.
And the level of how considerate you are, the better the communication.
Someone who's inconsiderate, whether they know it or not, is irrelevant.
Right.
The poor, the communication.
Give me an example.
You've been around white people at takeout.
I would say white people, usually I mean Americans and Westerners that have been Americanized.
I get it.
This has happened many times.
And I give people that I know a really hard time about.
I've seen this my entire life.
So it's a four or five.
You're doing something and you're hungry.
You take out.
Somebody comes in with the food, three, four bags or two bags or one bag.
And everybody's got a slightly different order.
Let's say you order burgers.
You know, yours is not mustard.
Yours is a double.
Yours is the cheese and French fries and a couple other things in there.
You know what they do?
They all sit down ready to eat and they pass the bag around and you've got to go searching
for your thing.
And then they they pass the bag.
I'm like, what?
What are you doing?
We're sitting down having a meal.
Why?
Give me the bag.
So I take the bag.
I put it down on a flat surface.
I go, wow.
And I rip it open.
Now, Greek.
It's like, oh, my gosh.
So angry.
No, no.
First of all, that big ass brown paper bag.
It's usually brown paper now became like a tablecloth.
And I spread everything out and I'm like, OK, now we see what we got.
Everybody sees everything at the same time.
Yeah.
Right.
What's this shit about passing the bag around?
Find yours and pass the bag.
And I've done this.
I've been doing this my whole life, by the way.
And I've even told people about this.
And then when it comes time to take out, guess what?
They're still passing.
Remember, I talked about it.
Talk about what?
Oh, my gosh.
Now, this is right now.
If you're around white people, you'll know what I just said is true because you've experienced
it.
Hey, you might even be doing it yourself.
When I'm around those people, what I got to do is I go, OK, let's go back over what everybody
said they got.
And then it comes all everything comes out of the bag and I kind of deal it out like
cards because I can't stand that.
Yes.
Yeah, exactly.
You know what?
You've seen what I'm talking about.
Yes.
But that's why I deal it out, because I'm just like, no, we know all of what's here
all together.
So nobody's going, oh, I didn't get.
But I don't I don't even bother.
I just ripped the whole bag over.
You're talking about.
Yeah, of course.
So now we have a tablecloth because the brown, you know, if it's a tall enough bag, you're
right.
Plastic bags.
The same thing.
I've seen that every someone person's, you know, sometimes you do the takeout.
I don't want to get into this, but it's interesting because here's the other smaller optional things
that happen.
It's a plastic bag.
Right.
And the person who you're all busy doing something, you're all haven't arrived.
Somebody's washing their hands.
The other person.
One person gets there and they take out their thing and they start eating.
And there's this plastic bag.
And from there is like, OK, where's the food?
Oh, the food's in the bag.
Man, if I'm the first person at that setting, I start taking everything out.
Now, most people say, well, we don't yeah, we don't do it like, you know, here's the
prompt.
If there's a whole bunch of cutlery and plates in there.
Yeah.
They typically take everything out of the bag because it kind of supposedly it's like
synthesizing dinnertime.
Right.
You know, you know what I mean?
The hint like take.
So there's so many things that I've seen like that.
And it's cultural with white people, typically white people, meaning Americans.
Right.
And I was listening to a gorgeous audio book.
I'm working on a scale reader today.
And that's the water device.
And I have audio books in the background.
And I'm like, oh, my gosh, this guy wrote this in like 1904.
He sounds just like the Greek.
It's terrible.
You know, I mean, terrible or good or whatever you want to say, you know, like one of his
comments was, you know, when I was in America, I spent most of my time in the movies because
the culture.
So whatever.
And they don't think that they tell me that, you know, American life is not like American
movies and he begs to differ and he explains why I'm like, oh, my gosh, he's so crazy.
Sounds just like you listen to Greek speak.
But he died before I was way even before my parents were born.
So anyway, there's a lot of commonality to what I'm saying and most people get it.
That's OK.
So that's the idea.
The same thing.
The camera is very simple.
We're here or you're here and who you're sending the photograph to or showing it to a later
months because we're more alive.
Let's say whether it's film print, we've got to go to photomat and print it.
Yeah.
Right.
And you have to wait a few days or whether it's digital.
It's memorialized unless you delete it or tear it up, throw it away.
So it's memorialized.
You're going to be showing it to people most likely who were not there.
What are they going to see?
Right.
How much of that situation of fear and feeling of being there is being transmitted and communicated
through what you're memorialized?
See, I do my best, though, to communicate the information required.
I'm just saying that when I am asked to take a picture of something, I do my best to take
into account the information that they want.
If they want a detail on a particular thing, I try and know.
Chuck, I'm going to I'm going to step on you.
That's not about you.
It's not about me.
What I'm trying to do is an objective, objectify the situation.
Yeah.
Right.
And if you can give me an example of another objective example of it, go ahead.
But don't I don't like to say what I would do.
And the only reason I bring up the personal stuff that what I would do is is because I
need to back up the reason.
So I could always you know what?
OK, how about we do all the sonics based on third person?
Because very often I talk about the Greek in third person.
Well, no problem.
So we'll go objective on this because you know what?
The information required that needs to be communicated.
Forget about who is who.
Oh, there's no requirement to be a difference.
With most personal situations, there's no requirement unless you're doing what a technical
manual.
If someone asked for a photograph to be taken, they generally had a purpose for that.
I'm thinking, you know, generally.
But you'll see requirements like a few example, like the Haynes motor, you know, the car fix
it manuals where they have photos included.
Those must be as communicative as possible.
But what I'm saying is the population at large has no idea what I'm talking about.
But once it's mentioned to them, like, yeah, of course, of course, that makes sense.
Of course, that's how it should be done.
Here's an example.
Like years ago, paper, ink, books, magazines were precious in the medieval ages.
It would be equivalent of 10 to 20 thousand dollars for a book in today's money.
Right.
Back in the days when they printed newspapers.
Oh, you know, we get the impression that they're mass producing.
Well, they're mass produced, but they were very they were.
When you finished reading it, you gave it to someone else to continue reading it.
Right.
It wasn't thrown in the recycling bin.
It was still very precious.
Right.
So.
So let's just say the even when at the height of photography, film photography, which was
by the late 70s, right, everyone had a camera.
That's when the Polaroid camera instrument, right.
Tremendous amount of.
I think there was almost anyway, there were more cameras and cars being sold until the
late 70s.
Right.
So.
So that was the peak.
And then it went down and then it picked up again.
And now what now you have no choice because what you have, the stupid rectangle is really
a camera that happens to have the feature of acting as a phone.
So what I'm trying and this is even more important now because there are more photographs
being taken now and it's not viewed as anything precious because you could just hit delete
and do it again.
But, you know, it is precious wasting the time of who is looking at that tripe.
Can't make any sense out of it.
Right.
You see the difference.
So now where's the preciousness coming?
Where is the scarcity?
The scarcity is in time.
Now, you know, here's the thing.
It has what it shows you about the character of the person is how much they care about
communicating and also how much they see.
Some people can't perceive what you think.
You hand them something or they're in a room with you.
You think they perceive what you do.
No, they may not.
You know, they may not see that you see it.
So what that does again, I take me a picture and I look at the picture.
It's like I can't make out what it is.
I mean, I kind of know what it is generally, but it doesn't help me in any way.
Right.
What that tells me is that person either can't see or doesn't know the importance of communication.
By the way, when you say communication, most people think it's speaking.
Right.
It's not.
What do you think?
Graffiti is right.
Tags.
Right.
People.
That's a communication.
Right.
All these things.
You know, when you ever see, you know, when dogs go on a walk, they stop and smell reading
the emails.
Right.
So anyway, communication to me is just a transfer of information.
I mean, yeah.
Yeah.
That's why the dogs.
Yes.
Smell the pee to us.
It's just to them.
It's a female.
It doesn't matter.
You could do that with a scent for people.
You know, when you pick up a smell going into somewhere, just by the fact that you permitted
a smell in an area, you're communicating something, aren't you?
Sort of.
Well, we just it just jogs our memory.
It doesn't give specific information like when a dog smells a female, it's got just like
we would do an email.
You can have any amount of detail for us.
Smells pretty much just trigger something from the past, because if you smell something
that you didn't smell in the past, you what's the first thing people say?
What's that smell?
Right.
They don't get information from it directly.
Well, they're still catalog it so that they can, you know, because they want the recognizable
that smells like this.
It smells similar to that.
Yeah.
Let's jump to the coins.
Very simply.
The coins are completely different.
The coins are.
Remember, it was a job application, right?
Or a job.
You know, the difference in a job and a job.
Right.
Anyway.
Yeah.
No, man, I got I got a job today.
OK.
So that's different than a job.
Right.
But still, whether it's a job or a job explanation application, what is that?
That's commercial, isn't it?
OK.
So that's why I gave all the details on why we do coins.
It's the first thing that you engaged in commerce.
You say, no, Greek, first time I engaged in commerce, I was four years old, I bought a
piece of candy.
Yeah.
What did you use to buy a piece of candy?
A piece of coin.
This is the first money.
Right.
Because jobs do money.
And then all of this has to do with time, ego approach.
Right.
I think I gave some examples on one person walking in.
So I have a master's degree.
This is bullshit.
OK.
You know what that person would do?
You hire them based on their credentials.
Right.
Mm hmm.
And you and you have you go into their work area and there's a wastebasket is full and
overflowing and you're like, dude, you know, your wastebasket.
Yeah, that's that's that's.
But I don't do that kind of empty wastebasket.
Right.
You know what I mean?
You see what I mean?
So you want, you know, so it shows you.
So in other words, can you can see the person who got offended by doing that coin sorting
exam?
Mm hmm.
If you hired him, you could see how that would be an example.
Right.
I don't have to get the garbage.
You know, it's like, whoa.
So you learn so much, by the way, if this has helped out some people that have businesses
and.
All right.
So that is completely different.
Also, what's the other example I gave is there was a penny in with the dimes and the nickels
that say, well, you know, there's a penny in with the dime and the nickel.
They're clearly different, not only are they different sizes, but the first thing you notice
is the color is very different.
Right.
Because I noticed it from across the way, let's say.
OK.
And when I asked him, why, why did you decide to put that in there?
Says it doesn't matter.
Oh, my gosh.
Now, let's say you hired that person.
I can't even give you an example because of what they could do on the job, because it's
freaking ridiculous what they could do on the job.
Right.
Can you imagine someone who has a doesn't matter attitude?
Would you.
Right.
I mean, can you give an example on how something can go?
No, because pretty much everything will go wrong with that.
No.
Right.
Even even though they look polite or whatever.
It could because they won't seek to correct something if it's going in the wrong direction.
Yeah.
Although just let it go.
And it's like you will find if it's not something that's brought to your attention, it could
go.
These things can get right.
It doesn't matter for a long time.
It doesn't matter that broken glass fell into the candy bat.
Whatever.
Yeah.
Or the or the milk delivery has been sitting out in the sun in the back of the building
for four hours.
Right.
Or the cow or whatever.
The cow peed in it.
You know, I mean, it's fine.
Yeah.
Gosh.
And you know, it's interesting.
This thing is very objective.
The coin sorting, because the person walks in, oh, this guy looks really clean cut and
he looks like he has a good demeanor and they're, you know, pretty handsome and they make a good
presentation and they're well spoken.
Oh, this one's a pretty good, pretty good potential.
And then they tell you it doesn't matter.
It's like, oh, my gosh, if I hired him on looks alone, I would have been screwed.
Yeah.
Right.
Because seeking to preen himself does not mean that he seeks to keep anything else well
kept.
It's just himself.
Right.
Or it doesn't.
Or maybe he's well kept because it just happens to be that way.
He still doesn't care.
But here's the point.
Could just be out of habit or reflex.
You know.
Go ahead.
Yeah.
That is an exam that covers on many.
Actually, if you go through that audio again.
Yeah.
And I'm actually covering about 99 percent of what they teach in psychology about human,
you know, in that type of environment, because there are a lot of stuff written about.
Actually, I first started learning the importance of the mental state and financial state of
the quote unquote workplace from the reading stuff in the eighteen hundreds.
You know what?
That was a very big topic.
There was a lot of stuff written about it.
In modern hundreds.
Right.
In modern studies, they would file this under behavioral science.
But whatever.
It goes to psychology degrees.
Go ahead.
Yeah.
But yeah.
But the mindset.
They didn't use psychology.
They used mindset.
Right.
Mindset, desires, anticipations and behaviors.
I was like, wow, this is stressful.
Maybe I just came across literature that addressed these points because it was.
Look, at that time, there was the industrial revolution was in full swing.
And what's the industrial revolution?
Is it people outpushed, you know, behind some cattle on a farm?
No, it's about a whole bunch of people crammed into a building making stuff.
Right.
Yeah.
So you have very high density.
Like on a farm, you might have 20 people on 100 acres.
But in a factory, you might have 20 people in less than 50 and a thousand square feet
or less easily.
Right.
Yeah.
On an acre, you might have a thousand people working.
So it was very important.
So anyway, I gave those examples.
But here's the thing.
The higher consciousness contains the lower one.
By the way, both of these examples, the coin sorting and the and the camera shot is from
the point of view of a higher consciousness or a higher consciousness, both qualitatively
first, higher quality will automatically get a bigger quantity.
Now, there's an exception with savants like so this guy's a mathematics savant.
He can tell you anything with numbers, but he's an idiot everywhere else.
Right.
So so he's actually super narrow.
So without being a savant.
But as the consciousness increases in quality, its quantity of able.
Right.
So it's basically this way.
The higher consciousness being able to contain the lower consciousness.
This is the cartoon image of a big fish swallowing a smaller fish.
Right.
So give you an example.
Like when you look at what the official stories are, it doesn't matter.
By the way, what people think is official is not official.
Like with the pandemic, they're saying we're doing this because the CDC.
CDC is a corporation.
It's not even it's not part of the government.
It's it has a cage code, which is corporate and government entity.
Right.
It's funny how it's called cage.
Yeah, of course.
It's not part of the government.
It's it was basically set up.
And that's why the head of the C it's military.
It's part.
It's a quasi military organization.
That's why the head of the CDC is always in uniform.
Right.
Always.
Well, not always, but it has been typically as a military person.
Right.
But anyway, and the same with the surgeon general.
It's always a military, right.
Uniform of some kind.
Regardless of that, they're not official.
So most of the stuff that you're hearing, let's say that you might think or is
touted as being official, is really dumb.
And it's usually not.
Forget about that.
It's all bullshit.
Even from the beginning, you know, 200 years ago or more from this country.
Let's say it's all BS.
But let's say you don't consider the BS part, but just consider on what mental
state, cognitive or intelligent level it's written on.
It's very, very low.
But most of the people go for it because they are contained by it.
In other words, even though you might look at what the government tells you
about aspartame or chemtrails or the vaccine, and you're like, that's real
total BS and it's stupid.
Most people look at that as that's coming from a higher consciousness.
And to them it is.
Right.
So here's a quick way to gauge.
If you find what's put out officially, whether it's the Vatican or your
government or some major corporation to be really stupid, which it is.
And others don't.
Others take it very seriously.
Guess what?
It's like they're four ounce bag and you're a one pound bag.
Right.
Or, you know, they're a hundred grams and you're a kilo.
You see the difference?
So the person who believes the official stories or thinks whatever,
they cannot get any more information on the subject.
They're already saturated just being told junk.
Where someone who sees it as bullshit can take a lot more, would research
the evidence behind it or, you know, the real history behind it and
contain more information, you see.
So automatically they.
Right.
So imagine taking quote unquote average Sam or average Joe who believes
that the government is absolutely correct about taking an injection.
You know, there's no evidence.
There's no.
Well, I don't.
That's too much for me.
You hear that a lot.
That's too much.
Right.
You hear it, right?
So we've got a low consciousness.
It doesn't mean they're bad.
Here's the part.
Maybe if you're listening to what I'm saying, it leaves a taste that you're
getting the taste that I'm saying these people are bad.
No, they're not bad at all.
But are they good?
Hell no.
They're not good either, but they're not bad.
You see what I mean?
And by the way, again, another term.
How is that?
That's not bad.
Oh, but is it good?
They say it's not bad and they say it's good.
I got a hard time with not thinking they're bad, though, because of the
results of your actions are destructive.
Doesn't that make you bad?
If you're pretty much not doing anything but taking up space and you get a
shot and you drop dead in my book, I don't see that as being destructive.
In other words, what I'm seeing and saying is this.
If these people are operating on that level, the only form of destruction
that they could cause is their own demise.
Unless, of course, they join the army or the police or work in a bank or
work in the medical community.
Oh, man.
Now we're covering most of this.
So it goes both ways.
You see what I mean?
I got you.
I'm just thinking.
How are they destructive?
How is the common whatever?
Oh, who's awful?
Destructive?
How?
Littering?
I don't know.
To me, the destruction is basically taking up space.
We're running generators down at the end of town where the big electrical
generator is burning all this coal to power their CNN and their football
games and the refrigerator that's full of toxins.
Yeah, that could be.
Indirectly, they're destructive.
Yeah, I could see.
But directly, I don't see them as being destructive.
They could join the army or become a doctor.
Right.
Or work in a bank or whatever.
But you see how it goes the other way, too.
I just figure that the actions of somebody actively attempting to
destroy, you know, it was just not even not even a positive thing.
It's got to be negative to do.
What are they destroying?
Even if they're destroying useless, useless people, you know, is it
their right?
Oh, no, no.
I'm talking about those that are on the lower consciousness of being
destructive.
I think we came off on the thing.
No, I don't think they're destructive.
Is what was what my point was.
No, they're just use.
I mean, they're useful for something.
Look, ask the military.
Ask the prison system.
Prison system is the prison in the hospital is the bank, by the way.
Of course.
Right.
If you ever see road signs, your bonds are paying for the roads.
Bonds are paying for the state.
Right.
Never says your taxes.
Never.
It's the bonds.
Where those bonds come from.
Right.
You know, bond of the birth certificates on.
And prison people charged and sucked in prison.
Oh, here's the other thing.
People are talking about how you fix the system and all that.
So what do you mean if everyone just follows the rules?
Like, for example, if you're at a poker game and it goes awry.
All you got to do is go back to following the rules.
But game will straighten out itself.
Right.
Usually.
So like all these people want to send less than all you got to do is get enough people
to sign a petition, put any government, local, federal, state officials on notice that all
the current laws, statutes, codes and regulations and ordinances are still in effect.
That's all you have to say in the letter.
That'll scare the bejesus out of them.
Because that means now, you know, it's kind of like with voting.
If everything the government says is a lie, that means that every election result is also
what?
Right.
A lie.
So right.
So people are complaining about the recent election being.
Wait a second.
It's kind of an oxymoron.
And if you really want to make a change, don't vote.
If no one showed up to vote.
I've been saying this at all.
They would all pack up and leave and it would be empty.
Anybody could walk in and take over.
I'm serious.
Well, I mean, wouldn't be.
But that's the metaphor.
So it's the same thing with all of this stuff.
But anyway, to make a change politically or even in court, if you're going to go court,
just say put the judge on notice that all the whatever, wherever local, whatever it's
state, federal, whatever, that let's say it's a state.
You see all just put them.
This is a notice that all the state laws, codes, rules and regulations all the way down to
the little smallest statute are still in effect.
That scares the hell out of them.
That scares the hell out of them because they're not using or don't they don't.
First of all, they don't know any of them in context.
Right.
So, yeah, that's all.
So all you have to do.
Right.
Any of this stuff is whoever's running the show in whatever department or group you're
a part of.
Just tell them that you think of the Catholic Church.
The Bible is still in effect.
Right.
We go by the Bible.
If you go to any Catholic institution or Catholic authority and say that the Bible
is the authority, that's they'll poop in their pants right there.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
Because to them, the church is the authority, not the Bible.
Right.
But they do mix it.
So the same with the courts, the same with the politicians.
It's policy.
Well, you could do your ever policy you want, but we're putting you on notice that the
laws, codes, rules and statutes are all in effect.
People say, well, it's not law.
It's code.
No, no, no.
Codes and statutes are codified under law.
That's all of it is law.
Well, that's why I say the power vested in me.
Right.
That's the always the state.
The power vested in me by whether it's a, you know, a.
That's OK.
There's many ways.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Just put him on notice.
OK, so if a card game goes awry.
All you got to say is the rules of poker still hold up.
Watch how everybody straightens up.
Right.
Oh, whatever.
Playing Monopoly.
OK, the rules of Monopoly have to be observed.
Everybody straightens up.
Right.
It's very simple.
You know, in other words, people are taking these three.
Why did I bring this up?
Because the taking the camera to review someone's character and the coin sorting thing are very
specific to the character.
But going back to the rules that are that are in place is for everyone.