Sonic Event 9 here on Ocelli and the Greek Rated Y and we continue with very
much the discussion that took about an hour last time, who knows how long it'll take this
time because after all, we don't actually have a pattern here that's established, unlike
previous Sonic Events where there was a two-hour template that we had to fill, however it was
or not had to fill but did fill and that's the way it went, this is a little different.
So you never quite know what you're going to get, I think even before we started recording
today, the Greek even referenced Forrest Gump, the box of chocolates, you don't know
what you're going to get, there you go, I know it's a bad impression but best I can
do.
How are you doing, Greek?
I'm doing good, this is about everybody's leisure, ours and theirs and ours and theirs
and whoever's listening, it's about leisure.
So you find out what we've said and you hear it and hopefully it works out for everyone.
Yeah, what I wanted to bring up was what we usually do lately is going back to the feedback
and there's a ton of it and at the same time, there's not that much.
A ton of it meaning there's so much depth you could go into with all the various questions
and things that are brought up, whether it's emails or the chat but at the same time,
I think they could be answered in short but poignantly given the important stuff.
Right, fair enough.
And look, I do appreciate the multiple messages I get just saying, you know, look, this is
really great, glad this is happening again and thank you and this and that.
I appreciate all that but frankly, there's nothing I can do with it constructively and
neither can you.
Now when there's more proactive, I guess would be the right term, communications, we can
do something with it, right?
Yeah, just picking up on any communication is fine, which is good.
But by the way, this is number nine and the last one we did, we finished up on a bunch
of stuff, mostly on timekeeping, right?
I just want to bring up real quick, the chat lately has been mostly on the timekeeping
and one of the comments there was why three sticks and you can make any visual representation
of the solar measurement that you like, you get creative, right?
If you're into making things, right, a constructive type, you'll notice that let's say you're
building a frame, let's say a picture frame and you got four sides, it's supposed to be
a square.
There's several ways to figure out whether it's a true square, you know, by 90 degrees
in each corner or you can measure the diagonals, right?
If you measure the diagonals and they're equal, right, you can make spacers and all this other
stuff.
So long as you're, yeah, but you got to make sure your diagonal line is exactly straight
because if you make the diagonal line a little crooked, then it's not quite right.
But yeah, there's various ways to make it rigid.
Rigid and straight.
Yeah.
Just tell the ladies like it.
So anyway.
I don't know.
I've heard they don't necessarily always like straight, but look, I'm not going to speak
for that.
I'm sorry.
Go ahead.
I have not been lascivious since we've done this.
So anyway.
No, but there's plenty of opportunities.
Anyway.
Of course.
Yes.
And that's what they say too.
Okay.
So based on how constructive you are and how you would like to view it is the way it's done.
You know, there really is, there's slight mention in, let's say the book of Isaiah,
there was a sundial.
It's actually, it was called a sun stand, if you translate it in Hebrew, what it looked
like.
We're not sure.
So anything works.
Even a building works.
I use, I have a metal shelf.
That's one of these like restaurant type metro shelves with, it's kind of like an open.
And as the light comes through one of the empty shelves, it forms this very interesting
shadow, and you can tell when it's noon because the shadow is the shortest, right?
And instead of building things that you're going to trip over if you don't have enough
space, which I do have enough space, but I just happen to rely on whatever is around.
So the three lines in the dirt, as they would say, they would be parallel in a sense.
But they would also exaggerate what angle is happening instead of one, right?
Instead of having one line, it's easier to see three lines.
Let me just say it this way.
An angle is more visible with three lines than just one, for example, right?
So that's one thing.
I thought it was an interesting proposition to have three things showing a shadow, and
it was an interesting question why.
The other thing I wanted to mention regarding time was the datum line or the reference
when the day starts, or let's just, the day would be your local solar noon.
But when the day for the new moon starts, meaning the full moon, I never really brought
that up.
I think I brought it up once or twice.
I'm not sure if I did it on the old Oteli in the Greek, but it starts around central
Iraq.
There's a website called Time and Date Night Sky or Time and Date.
If you put in night sky, it'll show you bodies.
And also, there's several other websites.
There's one that is geographic that shows you the earth, what they call the earth, the
planet, let's say, and where the moon is.
You could look that up, the moon in the sky or the moon on the earth.
I think it's that die.net also if you navigate that site.
And you will see that when it comes down to the first day of the month, it begins around
central Iraq.
So prior to that, you'll see the moon, it'll be 99% full or 95% full.
And when it goes, when it's coming around the time to be the first of the month, when
it reaches the moon over what is visibly known to be full over central Iraq, you will see
that it switches from 95% or 98% to 100% or 99%, which is usually 99% or 100% is pretty
much 100%.
And that change happens over central Iraq.
Think about that for a moment.
That's been highlighted and underscored in history as Mesopotamia, right?
Like you said, the cradle, mankind and all that.
Yeah, the cradle of civilization, a lot of people call it, yeah.
From a cultural perspective.
So this phenomenon of using the full moon or the moon to gauge the month, which actually
it's not a phenomenon, but it is the actual month.
Well, is there a why on this or is there just a, that just happens to be the circumstance?
I mean, that's just how it is.
It happens to be the circumstance.
In ancient calendars before the moon and before people got used to the cycles of the
moon, it was just a day count, like the Julian calendar is just a day count.
Right.
Okay.
So we live in a very changed world.
One day there's a presumptive history that things that we see that we're told are hundreds
of millions of years old or not, some things that are hundreds of millions of years old
that really are, we're told we're not.
So everything's kind of inverted.
But yeah, the earth is a wanderer, a strange planet.
We don't see it wandering that much because there's high precision in astronomy, but not
too long ago it was wandering around.
That's why when you read some ancient stuff, Mercury was Venus and Venus changed places.
Yeah, pretty interesting stuff.
I don't have enough of reference material or background to, let's say, speak on it,
but it might be something in my future to look into again if the opportunity comes up.
Well, the astronomical bodies above, right, they're always of interest because they are
relevant and people say, I mean, look, people say a lot of things about the influence of
them over us and over events on the planet.
Of course, astrology is a whole industry devoted to it at this point, on top of the reality
of it.
How many astrologers reckon the month starts with the moon?
Yeah, well, there you go.
They've missed it.
It's like doctors talking about blood pressure.
Yeah, it's, sorry, but you're not going to find that.
Well, that's stuff for the collective, which is generally baloney.
I think we were speaking on this once, I'm not sure if we did it on air, but if someone
comes to you and they call themselves a shaman, well, real shamans don't call themselves shaman.
Right.
If someone comes to you and says they're a witch or a wizard, guess what?
Real witches and real wizards don't label themselves as such.
Right.
If someone comes to you and says they're a healer, guess what?
Real healers.
If someone comes and says to you they're a prophet, guess what?
They're not.
Okay, you see where I'm going with this?
Oh, yeah.
So when someone says I'm an astrologer, guess what?
They're not.
There you go.
We've just proved it just by what they can focus on, even not what they do focus, what
their limitations.
You just look at their limitations.
Right.
Speaking of limitations.
I was going to say exactly that, actually.
Speaking of limitations and doctors.
Let's go back to one of the previous things we've talked about.
Because the body, I mean, look, you just brought up doctors right there, right?
As soon as they start talking about blood pressure.
Now, they should be talking about pressure or the pressure of a vacuum, as we discussed
with the container originally and have expanded upon and rated wide now.
But some interesting things here, because one of the most common ailments, so to speak,
is diabetes, right?
I mean, this is definitely, of course, there are people listening in other countries, but
in America, I'm not sure if the whole world is like this, but in America, diabetes is
a dominant issue, let's say.
It's not an ailment, by the way.
It's a diagnosis.
There's a big difference between having a diagnosis and having an ailment.
It's kind of like if you talk about the judicial system, if you're a criminal and you're dubbed
a criminal, labeled as a criminal, well, you say, why?
Because I was accused for stealing rocks from the moon.
And I didn't put them back.
Right?
You see what I mean?
Okay.
How ridiculous is that, right?
What I'm saying is that this is very important, actually.
They even say it's diagnosed.
No one has ever had 99% of the diseases that they proclaim to treat or that they have in
their book.
Those are all diagnoses, you see?
So anyway, what I wanted to bring up about that is with recent short conversation, what
inextricably anyone who's been long enough diagnosed with diabetes and receives the quote
unquote standard treatment, they end up being on what?
Kidney dialysis, aren't they?
Don't they?
Usually toward the end of their lives, yeah.
There's always a period of dialysis for sure.
Due to kidney failure.
Due to kidney failure, but yeah, go ahead.
Yeah, yeah.
So what it is really is a liver function.
I also brought up before we started recording, it's really difficult to broach on a subject
that requires eight hours of study, and I'm talking about just quickly going through stuff
for eight hours.
In the ancient Eastern medicine, which is not woo-woo, it's not superstition, it's based
on 3,000 years of observation or more, and that's what real science is, by the way.
You have a theory or a hypothesis, and you make an experiment, conduct an experiment,
and through observation, you come up with a conclusion.
Through observation, right?
You keep going through observation.
So this is what the Eastern medicine is based on.
And based on the ideas that they have, from formative energies to all the way to human
manifestations, it seems very contrasting to the way we speak on medicine in the Western
world because of the cultural difference and the point of view that they have.
But their point of view is that if you study Eastern medicine, the pancreas do not exist
as a solo organ, right?
There's no blood sugar and all that.
By the way, what they're measuring with blood sugar strips is not sugar in the blood.
That's absurd.
It's not possible to do that objectively.
They're measuring your level of hydration.
And you can even go online and research, if I'm dehydrated or I drink water, what does
it do to the blood sugar measurement?
It goes crazy.
It doesn't work because it all has to do with how much water the liver can process at a
dehydrated.
So if you're taking those tests, they have electronic ones or the paper prick, that's
just measuring how your liver is handling your hydration level.
That's all.
There's no blood sugar test at all.
So forget about all that.
Forget about the pancreas as a solo organ.
It's really a liver function.
And the liver, in plural, if you're talking about more than one person, let's say, is
tied completely to the kidneys.
And in the Asian viewpoint, that manages the fire energy in the body.
And if you want to be, let's say, a juvenile perspective, I don't know if you remember
the little choo-choo trains, the steam engines that they used to show us as children in the
60s and 70s as an example of a machine.
If you think of the human fire, by the way, the human energy, there's an aspect of it
known as the fire aspect.
That is managed by the kidneys and the liver back and forth.
So when you have a liver function problem, anything that goes into the body, even air
by the way, will be reckoned by the liver.
The liver is the fastest reacting organ in the body.
It's an internal organ that has no exposure to the outside.
And it's tied to the kidneys.
So here we have something that people are overly toxified or stressed or whatever, and
they diagnose it as a blood sugar problem, completely off kilter.
And what's really going on is the liver function is being broken down or it's out of whack
as they say, but it's tied to the kidneys.
And proof of that is by watching the historical progress and degradation of people diagnosed
with diabetes.
I just wanted to bring up the kidney aspect because when we did lay into this subject
a few episodes ago, sonic events let's say, I didn't emphasize the kidney tie-in on this.
So it's very important.
And maybe when we get into food, which will probably be solos in the future, not too far
from the future but not next week let's say, I'll bring up how these various things affect
various parts of the body.
I just wanted to throw that in there.
Very, very, very important.
Because as you mentioned also, Chuck, that they always end up on kidney dialysis.
So what does that have to do with blood sugar?
Not much.
No, not much at all.
And it's always, to me, I always think of it as a problem with filtration.
Because that's what I think of those organs as doing a lot, is filtering.
They're not actually.
They're not.
They appear to be.
They appear to be, right?
What they're doing is, it's no different than what a radio and a CB, it's kind of like the
brain transmitting and receiving in the non-local environment.
The body is, all the organs are transmitting and receiving within the contained environment
known as the body or the container let's say.
And they're actually taking materials in the body that are lost energy and it's time
for them to exit.
So they dematerialize and they rematerialize within organs that have ducts that lead to
the outside, like the bladder and the kidneys and things like that.
Right.
And when they rematerialize, they get their last bit of energy.
Now, what's important, and we'll go on to other topics, the eliminative organs, the
intestines are different because it's just a tunnel.
But the eliminative organs in the body, kidneys, bladder, and all this other stuff, have a
very crucial job because they take things from the blood and the lymphatic fluid and
other aspects of the body, there are gaseous aspects to the body as well, and dematerialize
them from the internal body into the organ to then exit the body.
And I've never brought this up before, because I've been contemplating on this and observing
it for a long time, but I've never brought this up in any sonic event in public.
What's very important that has been missed on this also is when this dematerialization
takes place to the kidneys and the bladder, sometimes the colon, but the intestines are
different, because it's just a tunnel again.
When this dematerialization takes place, it's very important from an energetic point of
view and materialist point of view that those nutritive factors, let's say that you've
gotten from food, do not revert back to being food once they're past the intestinal system.
So what I mean by that is if you eat a banana, it goes through the intestines, whatever the
body recognizes will dematerialize in the intestine and rematerialize inside the body as what
we call nutrition to build cells and whatever, vitalize whatever it could vitalize.
And when it becomes devitalized, after it's been reproduced in the body, it's time for
it to go, so it gets reproduced again in, let's say, the kidneys and bladder to exit.
It's like opening an old flashlight, toss the batteries out, but it dematerializes.
At that point, for example, the kidney and bladder point, when it dematerializes to go
out, it's very important that the body keeps it together so it doesn't want to revert back
to a banana, its constituents that was originally in the body.
If it does so, you become toxified, and that's one of the causes, quote-unquote, of cancer,
tumors and all those other things.
It's very interesting.
I'm trying to find a study.
When they did biopsies on tumors and things like that, they didn't recognize the DNA or
the molecules because they ended up looking just like food.
So you see, it didn't look like human tissue.
Sometimes it does resemble.
Some tumors actually develop certain body parts, like teeth.
There are tumors that have been removed from people on different parts of the body, and
when the tumor is examined, there's a tooth in it.
How is that possible?
Or hair, you see.
It's kind of bizarre, right?
It is a strange thought, that's for sure, but I'm thinking to myself, if you dematerialize
and then rematerialize, when that happens, it's building something like that, and it's
just building it in the wrong place.
It's just building the thing in the wrong place.
It's not putting hair on the head or something, you know, where it should go.
Yeah, it's inside the tumor, a tooth inside, or a banana.
You'll see what looks like just a cooked banana or pieces of food, but not in, you know, it'll
be on a molecular level, you know.
It's very interesting.
Well, it's kind of like in one of the Star Trek movies, or the movies that they did,
not the series, where they fired up the, what do they call that thing, where they beam people,
the transporter.
The transporter, yeah.
And there was a malfunction, and they ended up, the person ended up becoming like a lump
of bones that was screaming, you know.
Oh, yeah.
That was at the beginning of the very first, the Star Trek movie they put out in the 70s,
the first one.
Right.
And they started to rematerialize him, it wasn't going well, so they sent it back.
And when they did, they got a message that said, what we got back didn't last long.
There you go.
They didn't actually show it, but the implication was.
It was the transfer of information that got screwed up.
Right, right.
You see?
So the same thing happens in the body.
I like to lean heavily on that transporter in Star Trek, because that's exactly what's
happening, but every time the energy and nutrition goes in and out of the body, it gets transmuted
or transported into the form the body can use, right?
But what I'm trying to maybe summarize here is that when it doesn't and it reverts back
to how it was before it was put into the body, before you ate it, it's very dangerous, right?
And that's why I also brought up the body in that screw-up mode will produce teeth and
hair and other body parts in the tumors that are removed.
I'm talking about tumors that are removed from the abdomen, tumors that are removed from
the neck, tumors that are removed from the brain, all different parts of the body.
So this is bizarre.
By the way, this is very well recorded in medical manuals, but that's all it is.
It's just listed what they found.
There's no why, there's no how, there's no ... And you know what?
No one's asking.
Because if people did ask in the medical community why this is happening, there would have been
a revolution within the system and it would have been revamped a long time ago.
Well, they would have had to automatically start including the idea that there is this,
for lack of a better term, dematerialization and rematerialization of things going on in
the body, which would absolutely contradict the majority of what it is that these people
tell you through absorption and all that, right?
Yeah.
Well, they're telling us we're, in essence, I've summed it up as that we are pressurized
filter bags.
We're sponges almost because we suck up things and then whatever we suck up, we can squeeze
it back out.
And I mean, that's pretty much what it's like, but we're-
Pressurized filter bag.
In industry, like a vacuum cleaner bag or something, you use filter bags in water also.
But yeah, so it's bizarre.
It shows you a severe lacking in cultural, let's say, integrity.
I wouldn't say advancement.
There's no integrity in the system.
So what else do we want to ... Let's just bounce around over here.
I just wanted to throw those things in.
These are like afterthoughts.
I could shoot.
I should have mentioned these things.
And they're very deep, by the way.
The aspect of the human body, the way it works, I've been discussing this for over two decades
now and minimal feedback, and it's hard to see how it could help someone directly.
But once you start working it in your own mind, each individual that hears this content,
let's say, about how the body works will figure out their own way how to apply it.
Right.
Because we haven't gotten a group of people together to fund a massive research project
and to develop this as, quote unquote, functional science that's available to everyone.
You know, ha, ha, ha, it's not going to happen.
Right.
And I think I've prefaced that.
This is not going to happen in this society.
But I just wanted to bring it up because if it's in the mind, where do things start?
As a thought, right?
Oh, that's true.
If you get somebody just ... Like I observed about the timekeeping, when I started just
to internalize the idea and place in my mind that the solar noon beginning of the day,
there's already ... I can't even really describe the changes, but I feel quite differently
about a bunch of things that I'm trying to ... Well, not that I'm trying, that I am accomplishing,
that I am working on.
It's different.
It's a double negative because you know what?
The day always started at noon whether you knew it or not.
You just realizing something that you were, let's say, quote unquote, deprived of or distracted from.
Right.
But it's given me a different comfort zone in the day, which is one weird thing, where
I used to have a certain time of day where I just did better whatever task I set myself to.
It was better for me to do things at certain times of day, right?
But this has changed things a bit because just ...
So if you have a sedentary lifestyle and people make fun of you because you wake up at noon,
you got a good answer.
Mm-hmm.
That's what I tell people about it.
Right.
Sleep till noon, till the new day starts.
I'm just joking.
That's not how our sleep cycles work anyway.
No.
Our sleep cycles work with light most likely.
By the way, people that do work at night and sleep in the day, it's been, even in their
science, it's shown to have a much shorter 15% to 20% lifespan as a whole, generally.
So it doesn't mean that you need sunlight directly.
And the other thing that sun causes cancer is baloney because 90% of the people spent
90% of the time in the sun for the past 5,000 years.
If it was true that sun caused cancer, everyone would have been dead 4,000 years ago, right?
Mm-hmm.
1,000 years of this cancer-causing element.
Right.
So 90% of the people 90% of the time are in the sun.
It has to do with the photosensitivity, right?
Certain foods will break down your ability to process the light, let's say.
Okay.
Yeah.
So I wanted to cover, these are just little afterthoughts that after we've done the sonics
that I should have thrown in somehow and just didn't, just to help, bouncing around.
Right.
Fair enough.
But you also got some emails too, and I don't know if you want to address any of them directly.
Yeah.
Sure.
I don't know if you do also, but like I said, the majority of them were just complimentary,
like, glad to hear this.
This is good.
I know I got one from, I think we both got a message from, let's call him Joe, and you
know who I'm referring to probably.
It was very nice, very kind that he enjoyed.
Look, I'm more than happy to see someone just enjoying the discussion and the information
for sure.
You know, if it's pleasurable to somebody, then that might let it settle into their minds
a bit easier too.
Right?
I mean.
Yeah.
But no news is good news.
So the positive ones or the negative ones, either way, you know, just don't send poop
in the mail.
You know?
Yeah.
It's kind of counterproductive.
That's the good thing about emails.
But that's fine in terms of that.
I think I've always gotten more from criticism and it is possible to have positive criticism
also.
I mean, I think that's what this is about.
What we're doing and have been doing is just bringing things forward that are just right
at everyone's doorstep, so to speak, but no one's discussing.
And once these things are discussed, you have a more thorough examination of your reality.
Right?
I mean, talking about going to other planets or going to the bottom of the ocean is not
as relevant of what's going on five feet in front of you and that's what the whole thing
is about.
No.
And all the other Greeks speak.
Right.
But look, there was absolutely nothing wrong with touching on the vehicles that we talked
about, the space vehicles, toward the end of last Sonic.
That's always interesting.
I think you and I were, yeah, we didn't get that on recordation, but yeah, they've been
trying to go to space.
I noticed the key word trying with what they show us.
It doesn't work that way and I'm not sure how it works, but it's not what they're showing
us.
That's the other thing to remember.
Whatever you're being told as this is how it is, it's not that way.
Well, we did record a little bit of that because we were talking about AI toward the
end, actually.
Ah, yes.
That's right.
Yeah.
I don't, don't worry about that.
I brought this up.
I've been bringing this up for about two years now and I've stopped, but I don't know if
you guys remember about a decade ago or more, they were blasting and blasting everyone
with quantum this, quantum that, quantum batteries, quantum fishing poles, quantum juice, quantum,
quantum, quantum, right?
Remember?
Mm-hmm.
They stopped.
Now it's the AI, AI, AI.
You know what?
There is no quantum, right?
There's no spooky action at a distance.
There's none of this stuff.
They don't understand what perturbations and pressures are and there's no gravity waves
or anything like that.
Gravity's not a force, by the way.
People talk about the force of gravity.
Mm-hmm.
It's an acceleration.
Accelerations are not forces.
If you guys want a good primer on this kind of talk, by the way, look up, I'm going to
do a plug for Ken Wheeler, Ken Wheeler, spell it just like it is, like a wheel, Wheeler,
Etherea Apophasis, the big, fat, ugly, bald, tattooed guy, and I'm not giving him a pejorative
that he doesn't use himself.
He calls himself that.
He's wonderful to listen to.
In terms of that, he sounds like he's technical, but if you get a feeling of the words that
he uses, it won't sound technical after a few videos.
He's been running parallel to, his research is parallel to what I've been doing for many
years before I even knew about him.
I like his take on it.
Why go over most of the stuff that he goes over?
Again, I don't.
I just throw in my own originality in it.
Ken Wheeler, I'm throwing a plug in for him, definitely.
I wasn't aware you were aware of Ken Wheeler, actually.
I've encountered him before, too.
If you watch his stuff, it won't hurt.
Actually, it'll help, especially if you don't get intimidated by the words that he uses.
I like to keep stuff simple.
Cosmic censorship, dummy load, whatever, whatever.
He gets into more technical stuff, but you'll get used to it if you have the interest.
At some point, I do want to go back over cosmic censorship because, again, I feel as though
there is a shift that is happening.
We talked about that.
When we get into more discussion of the gods, I'm going to bring up how these things happen
as a mechanism.
Right.
That's what I'm interested in.
Matter of fact, we were going to discuss a little bit about the gods today.
We are.
I think some of that might come from those emails, right?
Mostly the chat.
The early chat from a couple of weeks ago.
Talk about the gods was on blast.
One of the things I wanted to bring up in the emails was a question that I've always...
I'm not sure if I did it so much publicly as privately.
One of the questions was...
I get the same question once every six months from various people.
How do we find a partner?
Or if it's a man, how do I find a wife?
It's mostly from how do I find a wife or a partner?
It seems that the ladies are more relaxed about it, but I've gotten it from them as well.
This is number Sonic 9.
Let's call it the interjection Sonic.
We're just all over the place like a banana in a monkey grove.
I know.
Get it?
All right.
How do you find a mate?
What it's about is...
Jordan Maxwell brought this up about partnerships.
It's all business.
Even on a personal...
Someone's asking you something personal.
People respond, it's none of your business.
Right.
Even if it's a personal thing, right?
So everything seems to be commercial.
Isn't a marriage a covenant, an agreement, a contract, right?
It is a contract.
Look, I often bring up the idea that, look, when you go get a marriage license, you're
asking permission to form a merger, which is what you're asking the government to do
when you're doing that with their paperwork.
Now, there is a difference between that and really forming a covenant or actually getting
together with a mate.
There are business contracts here.
That's true, isn't it?
It is.
It is, but there's a big difference when it's lawful and legal.
Like a marriage contract...
Is legal?
No, it's lawful.
It's lawful, but the marriage license is legal.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Yeah.
Because legal pertains to law.
See, in law it says you have a right to do business, and in the constitutions you have
a right to secure in your papers, right?
You've heard that?
Yes, of course.
Okay.
In all government paperwork, the word security does not mean like locking your doors.
It means money.
So, do you know the hidden translation?
One of these days...
Actually, this is something I need to write because I brought this up to some old attorneys
and they told me I should write a book on it to basically translate the constitution
and old law, let's say, into English.
What are you talking about, Greg?
It already is written in English.
No, it needs translation.
When you read to be secure in your papers, and it has nothing to do with locking them
up.
It has to do with commerce and the monetary value.
They're basically telling you that if you don't want to monetize your records, your
lawful records of birth, you shouldn't have to.
Let's think about that for a minute, right?
So, legal, all that legal stuff.
Driver's license, by the way, came out from the Uniform Slave Codes or Marriage License.
Uniform Slave Codes of 1750 here in the colonies because when a slave escaped one state, there
was different punishments in all the different states, right?
So, they wanted to make it uniform.
So, when the slaves married, they had to be licensed.
Passports, driver's license, liquor license, gun license, all the licensing came from the
Slave Codes.
So, yeah, in a lawful situation, legal just means it's been securitized, monetized.
March the 9th, 1933 is all I got to say about that, right?
So, for the Americans, every country has its own March the 9th, 1933.
So, how do you find a wife?
How do you find a partner and all that?
And it's an agreement.
It's based on  and everything I'm going to be speaking on is in law, not legal.
It doesn't mean that legal is bad.
It just means that legal is like a very low form of law that's applied to those that
are not really aware of law but are more aware of their fiefdom without admitting it, right?
So, when a lawyer walks into a room, into a situation, most people get afraid.
And I've actually spoken to people, older people, oh, I was raised to be afraid of them,
right?
Because they were used throughout history.
They were used throughout history to control the people that were in fiefdoms, you know,
serfs.
Intuitively, I just wish to avoid lawyers when I can.
No, I don't mind.
I like interacting with them every time it's  this way I don't know what's going
on in their field.
But when I speak to a few attorneys or what they call police, every so often I get a feeling.
You go look beyond the character also.
But I just wanted to lean very heavily on  I don't think I ever have, maybe a
little bit on lawful versus legal.
It's not versus.
It's just that legal is a very low form of it, right, of law.
It means you've already  you're under privileges and things.
It's not very good.
It means you lost everything and now  but you're still functioning.
So in law, OK, it was kind of a long roundabout way.
When you meet a partner or you would like to have a partner, how do you meet them?
How do you hold them?
OK.
First of all, the whole thing is knowing thyself.
Are you the type of person that does better solo or a person that does better with others?
Personally, I like being hitched up, being in a partnership with mostly anything I do,
especially in the long term, having a wife.
I enjoy that.
I've tried both, being  living solo or living with someone and not just a roommate
because actually some people that do have roommate situations like, oh, I'm going
to get my own place.
I can't stand having roommates.
So this is very different.
This is where you're intimate in every way.
OK?
With finances, with your personal life, with everything.
So how do you find that?
Well, it's very simple.
One of the ways  I think Thoreau actually said love should be like light and not like
fire because  right?
OK?
So that's just a quote.
By the way, I do like those Thoreau quotes.
Everyone wants to  Henry Thoreau, look up his quotes.
It's the closest stuff I've ever seen to Greek-speak.
So basically finding and hitching up and finding a partner, a husband or a wife, is very, very
simple.
It doesn't mean it's easy.
First of all, you have to make the determination long term, which how do you know if you haven't
passed long term, right?
Either way, whether you should be with someone or not.
But for most people, it is better to be with a partner.
It's what set of covenants or rules do you live by and is the person that you're with
as a husband or a wife also going to live by those rules?
It's very important to have those rules.
And I'm not talking about rules like rules of a game or something like that.
But there are general rules.
When you get into a situation where it's because this  the man has authority or
in some places the woman has authority.
And in Native American culture, it's still customary that all the judicial judges are
women, right?
Because it's a matriarchal system, which we'll get more about when we talk about the
gods.
But in essence, when you have one over the other, you have conflict and resentment.
But when you both agree these are the rules that we live by, then sometimes when something
happens that's in question, you go to the rules and it favors one.
And other times, it favors the other.
It's never always the husband says what goes on or the wife.
Also, if you're familiar with Latin cultures, especially South America, it's grandma,
abuelita or abuela that makes the final say, right?
You know what I mean?
You might have seen that back east.
And to tell you the truth, Italians kind of function the same way too, certain ones
from certain regions.
The grandma.
Not all Italians because Italy, remember, is a fabricated country.
But I will say that amongst Sicilians, that's true also.
Now, when you go out  that's within the home.
Now, outside of the home, there's a difference.
But these things are generally accepted.
Cultural.
They're cultural.
And I would consider them or have always spoken of them as roles, to be honest with you,
is that depending on a situation, there's a role.
Well, a situation is cultural.
And what I'm trying to emphasize here is that when you do have an objectified set of
rules, it doesn't work that you go to one person.
You look at the agreements that you've made.
And like, for example, personally with my wife, sometimes something will happen before
an argument or conflict ensues.
We say, well, what does it say here?
We're Old Testament people.
Well, sometimes it favors her and I'm like, oh, yeah, you know, I fucked up, right?
I'll admit it.
There's no arguing.
It's pretty simple.
It's written on a fourth  an eight-year-old can understand it.
And sometimes she messes up.
You see how it works?
It's not like the certain cultures, right?
So this is another problem that people have, what culture they come from and so on.
Okay, so again, I have not  you know, I'm giving a lot of background.
Where is he going with this, right?
Where is he  he still hasn't said how we pick a mate or a spouse, right?
No, I haven't because this is very important.
These things are very important to consider personally before you go on the endeavor of
how do you pick one because how you find a spouse is very easy and very simple.
But it's not easy and I'm getting into why it's not easy before I say how to meet one.
No.
Okay, let's just jump to the point and maybe we'll give a little more background on what
I've discovered.
Okay, so finding a spouse or a mate, first thing is physical appearance.
What I'm trying to say here, ultimately it doesn't matter who it is.
Are they trainable?
But with physical appearance or when I say by trainable, I mean are they willing to accept
what I just mentioned?
You know, a neutral objective set of rules that you both live by.
Not you will do what you say or you will do what she says or he says.
You see?
Okay, so once you discover that that is an objective and the best way to go when you
have a neutral set of rules or laws that you will live by, it's a physical appearance thing.
So if you, for example, like someone with small feet, don't go pick  to cultivate
a relationship with someone who has big feet because that's kind of hard to change, right?
You see what I mean?
It could be height, foot size, color of skin, sound of their voice, their nose shape, the
cut of their jib, right?
That's the way their grill looks, right?
Their face.
Their natural scent.
Their natural scent is a thing too, I'll tell you that.
But that changes.
I'm glad you brought that up.
Would you remember to bring that up again further on the conversation because that's
very important.
Yes, yes, of course.
And how it's not empirical.
It changes.
In the beginning, okay, well, yeah, okay.
No problem.
We'll get to that later.
But I mean eye color, hair color, all these things.
All those things can't change that easily.
In other words, you could run into someone who has no clue of what they're doing.
They run their life based on what they show on sitcom television.
If they're physically not, it's not to find someone who is physically attractive, but to
find someone who is not physically repulsive to you.
That you are not repulsed by.
Don't worry about finding someone that's attractive.
Oh, that person's attractive.
No, find someone that doesn't have things that are repulsive to you.
Look, a really good objective sort of thing is freckles, right?
Let's just say somebody absolutely despises the look of freckles for some reason, then
yeah, don't bother.
But those are easy.
I think they charge a dollar a freckle, literally.
They hit them off with a laser and they charge you a dollar per shot.
Yeah, well, for some people that could be.
So you gotta count the freckles.
For some people it would be easier to buy a house, you know, depending on how many freckles
they got, right?
But you've seen people that almost-
My wife has red hair and freckles.
There you go.
So safety second, you know what I mean?
Okay, look, if you're happy.
That's safety first, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Well, happiness is not something that, if you've attained happiness, you're done.
It's something that constantly is happening.
It's an aorist.
An aorist is a grammatical mechanism where it's something that's constantly going, you
know?
It's not like the water came out of, you know, you got water that ran through your
pipes.
You got water running through your pipes.
You see the difference?
It's constant.
So, but anyway, yeah, we got off on that.
Yeah, but what's more important than finding someone who is attractive, because remember
if they spike you as being attractive or you're falling in love, that's very high on the
curve, and that curve is going to come down and normalize.
You want to start low on the curve and build up.
So the main thing is when I see people, even throughout my whole life, like, oh, I don't
find them attractive.
Well, you just met them.
You just saw them like a minute ago.
What do you mean you don't find-
Well, I say, do you see anything on them that is repulsive to you?
I say repulsive is a strong word, but it just means to repel, you know?
Just like when you see something that you don't like, so I don't want to look at that,
right?
That's a repulsive reaction.
Well, maybe there's a better word for that then, because to be repulsed, to be repelled,
I mean, because I hear the word repel, repulse.
It's a strong word.
It's fairly strong.
I mean, it could just be something that's undesirable.
Yeah, undesirable, but I would take it as a strong thing because if it's something undesirable
and it's minor, it's minor, it might escalate to something like with regret later, so I'm
saying if anything, even if it's undesirable, stay away if you're not the type of person
that would compensate for it, right?
And it is, it can be compensated for, but again, there's a general, certain proclivity
that people have.
I'm not talking about fetishes, but some people don't, I personally don't like women with
big feet.
I find them to be cruel.
I'm sorry.
It's a phrenological thing, generally.
No matter how nice they seem on the surface, you get to know them and they're pretty cruel.
Sorry.
This is actually, I felt happy when I read about this in some 17th century literature.
I didn't know that that existed in 17th century literature, but I got to tell you, I concur
with you.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, that there's an odd thing to, no, listen, I just want to pause for a second.
There is an odd thing with women with big feet.
They are not like over a size, like an American size.
If you've got a woman with over a size nine, forget it.
She's Sasquatch.
Yeah.
She's not.
She's not kind.
She's not pleasant.
She might be very much on the surface.
She might be a great stewardess or a great waitress or a great philanthropist.
No, but to me, to me, to actually interact with them, I don't find them pleasant.
Yeah.
Okay.
And it's consistent.
I'm sorry.
I just never heard that from anybody else before.
No, no, it's fine because we can, you know, there's so many parts of the body on both
sides we could discuss, but that's not the point.
The point is this is a, how do you feel?
Everyone's got their own personal filter is what I'm trying to say.
Oh yeah.
Maybe.
You have to figure out what your personal filters are.
Okay.
So in short, up until this point, when you're looking for a mate, a husband or a wife, pick
someone and literally someone, anyone, as long as they're not, they don't have features
that you don't like.
How about that?
That's better than being repulsive.
There you go.
Okay.
All right.
Features that you don't like.
And also age might be a consideration to a certain degree, to a certain degree.
Okay.
So once you've gotten that step, that's very simple.
Right.
And it's materialistic.
Yes, it is.
But these things matter.
Eventually you're going to get to the more important thing, which is in order to have
harmony, you have to both live by similar covenant or set of laws.
So hopefully if you're listening to me, you've established that already within your own life
through a form of discipline.
You know how some people say, well, I needed to go to the military to learn discipline,
right?
It's like, oh man, you went through all that bullshit just to learn discipline so you get
up, that you couldn't get yourself to get up exactly the same time every day or comb
your hair or do this or do that.
Wow.
Some people need that, right?
If you're one of those, fine.
But if you're not, you should be able to figure out what kind of a discipline and set of rules
you live by.
The question now is once you've targeted someone, are they trainable or do they happen to have
the same rules?
Well, see, I was just going to ask a question there because, look, because somebody doesn't
have the same rules when you meet them.
Here's the thing.
Sometimes you enlighten them about something and they change, right?
So, okay, let's go with a simple thing.
Dietary habits.
It's very important, actually, that you're able to eat similar things, okay?
Let's go with a harsh one, right?
If you did not have a mate currently and you were searching for one, you find one who doesn't
have a problem with eating pork.
Okay, maybe you explain some things to them and they change their mind about that and
say, you know what?
I don't want to do that anymore.
There are certain things that could change.
Behaviors, right?
Yeah.
Well, this is more in line of how you make, what you're really finding is the physical
features.
The rest of it you have to make.
You see the difference?
In other words, there's a certain amount of, okay, this is what dating and courting is
about.
People go on a date.
They go all the way from, oh, did you score on the first date all the way to we've been
dating for six months and it's not going anywhere, right?
Okay, this is not what I'm talking about.
The purpose of courting and dating is to get to know each other, but not like what you
saw on TV and what you think about this, but what do you think about this, meaning proposal
time, right?
When you go into a business meeting and whether it's negotiations, right?
One side makes the proposal of the offering.
The other one either accepts or counters it, right, with conditions.
Or they just say, throw up their hands, say, hell no, and walk out.
You see what I mean?
There's many ways any business meeting can go.
The purpose of dating and courting is not to sit down and watch movies and eat popcorn
and then kiss each other or whatever and leave.
The purpose more dating, what was it?
You went out to dinner, right?
So what are you going to talk about when you go to dinner?
What you saw on TV?
What your grandmother did?
No one cares about that.
The purpose of courting and dating is to make proposals and offers and negotiate the rest
of your lives together.
Hello?
Do you see how down bare bones and how hard what I just said is and should be done by
everyone from a young age?
All right.
Well, this is to explore also where they're at regarding their way of conducting business
or they're conducting their lives, right?
Yeah, but keep it simple.
You could find that there are certain behaviors that are entirely repulsive and completely
unacceptable, right?
Right, but the behavior is changeable unless they were raised by gorillas.
Well, most likely, but there are certain people that you'll find will not change from their
patterns.
I'll give you a common break point, right?
Somebody's consumption of alcohol, which you can learn by going out to dinner with them.
Okay, you might find it acceptable to have a couple of drinks with dinner.
This is perfectly fine.
Maybe somebody else drinks a little more than that.
Yeah, I've been on quote-unquote dates many moons ago where we've had four bottles of
wine.
I had one glass out of the four bottles of wine.
I was like, this is a little too much, right?
Right, right.
That's an excessive.
So, okay, those things, the behaviors are changeable.
It depends, again, on the maturity of the individual that you're dealing with.
Do you remember the analogy I gave when someone says, well, I'm not technical?
That's because at a young age, someone respected around them said, I'm not technical, and they
just latched onto that thought.
I could be lazy now.
Okay.
So, when something technical comes up, I don't have to ever learn anything.
I could just say, I'm not technical, and people accept it.
The person who has a behavioral quote-unquote or resists behavioral adjustment, you know
I was going to say behavioral flaw, right?
But there is none, right?
Depending on the culture, right?
Right.
So, if someone resists a behavioral adjustment, I would suggest that a strong reason they
resist it is because at a very young age, usually formative years, which is less than
nine years old, they had seen someone that attended either a family gathering or within
their house or out, that someone was generally respected, made a comment about something,
and everyone found it to be acceptable, and that child or yourself also found it to be
acceptable as something that you're going to attach to as part of the conduct for the
rest of your life.
You forget that moment.
This thought that I brought up that you're going to attach to what someone said when
you were a child observing them because they were still respected when they said it, that
contemplation as a child only could be like a third of a second.
It may not even be quote-unquote conscious to you that you just did that, right?
Right.
You see?
Like, again, I'll repeat myself.
There was a receptionist regarding some technical stuff that I was proposing to an Internet
person.
It has to do with sound, and I wanted to bring up this has to do with such and such, and
it sounded technical, and the receptionist says, I'm not technical.
And I said, well, can we get personal here for a moment?
And I just broke it down.
I said, at some point in your young youth, you saw your aunt or someone else, your mom
or a friend of the family say, I'm not technical, and it was applauded or accepted, and you
just said to yourself as a child, if I say I'm not technical, it'll be accepted.
So, I don't have to expand in that area ever, even though I have the capability, let's say.
I mean, they don't know that, whether you know it or not.
So, I could spend the rest of my life now saying, I'm not technical, and people will
say, that's fine.
You see?
So, when people say, I don't do that, or I don't, you know, that's not how I do it, right?
Or I'm not, whatever.
I'm telling you, 99.999% of the time, because of what we know about unlimited capability
of most humans, 99% of the time, that's something that someone saw as a very young
child that was impressed upon them as being acceptable, and now they held this for the
rest of their lives.
It's a form of laziness, by the way, right?
Let me just go to another sense.
Have you ever heard of people that when they get stressed out, they have to eat a big
chocolate cake?
Not a piece of chocolate cake, but the whole chocolate cake, right?
They run to the fridge to eat sweets.
Yeah, there are people that react to stressful situations, and then, yeah, that's one of
the things they do.
Right.
Or whatever.
Yeah, they think, okay, this is very similar to that, but it's purely mental versus having
to get a substance when you got stressed out or confronted with a situation.
Because if you've been saying, you're not a technical, or you're not good at math, is
another one.
You hear that very popularly.
Oh, yeah.
Because, again, someone was very young, and someone said, I'm not good at math, and your
mom and dad, or whoever was around you, in Aramaic, it's called a gawra, which is your
guardian, said, that's okay.
And you said, oh, I know that in my mind, someday I'm going to have to learn math, but
this person got away with saying that they don't do math.
If I do that, I'll get away with all that extra time I have to think about math.
Wow, what a great, as a child, you don't think that way, but it happens.
It's interesting, right?
So, these things exist also, and those are extremely difficult, because it took .3 seconds
to be embedded in the mind of a child, and what makes it even more difficult is the people
that are saying these things, I'm not good at math, I'm not technical, or whatever, or
I'm not good at cleaning.
Pick any subject, right?
It's usually in the negative.
They don't know that they've embedded that, right?
They don't know that they've embedded that.
What I think about, is the analogy I give with this, is the CIA has this umbrella gun.
If they want to off someone, they have a gun built into an umbrella.
It's a very tiny pellet with the poison of one of these snakes, I forgot, this was back
in the day, and when the person is in a crowded place, they trip over them, like really push
them down, and they shoot the umbrella into their, usually the leg, the pellet into their
leg, and you just feel a little sting.
Yeah, at one point they had a toxin from a fish in the cartridge, but yeah.
Right, so you'll feel the bump of someone almost knocking you over more than the sting
in the leg, right?
So, in other words, it's a distraction maneuver, kind of like when your pickpockets use this
a lot, they'll nearly knock someone over to take their wallet, and the person turns around
and you're like, what kind of a person did that, you know, pushed me over so hard, and
you see it's a pregnant woman, right?
Well, it's a woman wearing a thing like she's pregnant, and no one's going to get mad at
a woman who looks like she's eight or nine months gestation, right?
Instead of calling her out or whatever, you'll say, just be careful next time, you won't
get too mad, right?
So these things are hidden that way in a very, very deep, let's say, cultural, quote-unquote
spiritual sense.
So we can get into a very lengthy sonic on all the various attributes that people carry
with them their whole lives that you will confront on a quote-unquote courting or dating
scene to figure out if they're trainable or whatever, you see?
So this is, I just wanted to give, those things that I mentioned were kind of in-depth and
redundant, I've mentioned them before, but they are very important because you can branch
off from there how it goes.
But essentially, finding a mate or a wife or a husband is simple.
Very much, someone who doesn't have features that you don't like, they don't necessarily
have to be attractive, right?
Because you're going to start high and then you're going to go low, so you want to start
low and build up and go high, right?
So, right?
So...
They just can't be automatically negative to you.
That's the problem.
That's right, automatically negative.
It's very rare that turns around also, by the way.
This is not in partnership relationships, but general acquaintances, people that are
called friends.
I had several times run into people that we just didn't hit it off the first 0.3 seconds
and then later on we met again and became close.
You see what I mean?
We're not talking about partners here, we're just general associates, let's say.
That's happened.
It is possible that this could happen also in this situation.
You might approach someone or not, or they might approach you, or you might happen to
be in a situation where you quote-unquote hate each other, but within a little more
exposure that flips and becomes the opposite.
You see, that's possible.
I've seen it.
Well, thinking about it very carefully, I had a second wife who, frankly, initially,
there was nothing negative about her.
In fact, there was some things there that, you know, look, I'm not going to list the
physical attributes, but there were physical attributes there that weren't necessarily,
okay, that's the greatest thing off the bat, but frankly, because it wasn't negative,
I kind of grew to appreciate certain things about her as I got to know her.
So, this makes perfect sense with what you're saying.
Mm-hmm.
Well, there is no perfect sense in the sense that this is going to be easy.
What I'd like to do is give the general landscape, and to summarize, let's say, to some summary,
it could be anyone.
How do you pick a spouse or a mate?
It could be anyone.
Well, I'm just saying I grew to appreciate things that weren't necessarily right off
the bat.
Wow, that's great, you know, about her.
And I sort of, like I said, started to appreciate.
She had some of those things that I thought were great to begin with, but there were some
things there that were kind of like, eh, okay, that is what it is, but it wasn't negative.
Right.
And it doesn't mean also that you can't have that attraction in the beginning.
Like, good soul history, like for many years in my life, I was attracting the supermodel
types.
They were coming after me.
Right.
And I was like, oh, great, I'm set for life.
Right?
And I was like, no, it never lasted more than a year.
This is in the past, let's say.
So I could say strictly that the attraction, either way, whether I was going after them
or they didn't matter, I was hitching up with supermodel types.
You know what I mean?
But I'm not exaggerating.
And it just didn't work out, but it wasn't because they were supermodel types.
It was because the rest didn't fill in.
Right?
And the rest is, how are you going to live?
What rules are you going to live by?
Right?
This is what the training is.
So, again, if you pick someone, and through conversation and courting, what is the typical,
even that they show in Hollywood on TV?
Boy meets girl, girl meets boy.
Hi, what's your name?
What are you doing later?
Great.
Okay, you're available?
I'm not available tonight, I'm available tomorrow night.
Okay, you meet and you order a bowl of soup at the cafe.
What are you going to talk about?
How do you bring up the subject?
Well, I'm the type of person now that brings it up right away.
So what covenant, what rules do you live by?
Are you religious?
Right?
What's your view on the way things are in society?
Is a more roundabout, indirect way, right?
If you run into someone, you ordered your soup, you know, you've had only two minutes
of contact, they agree to go on a date with you, instead of getting very direct.
If you say, what do you think of what's, I'm not political, but what do you think about
the society we live in?
If they say, well, I'm quite happy with it, everything's going great, we just have to
work a few things out, that's a 50-50 point.
But if they say everything's going well, chances are, unless you're part of the collective,
right?
Right.
You see, if they bring up political stuff or religious, meaning conventional religion
or stuff, chances went down really fast.
But if the people, see, if you're not part of the collective, it doesn't matter if you're
living now or 2,000 years ago, you're never going to be happy with the collective.
So you create your own life, your own world within your own household.
So there's many ways.
So here's the point.
Boy meets girl, girl, you know, you're in the apartment building or on the street, you
know, you're not going to ask someone out on a date if they have physical features that
you find not accommodating to your desires, okay?
So once you get past that point, you see, but the part that's not easy is what if you
run into someone that has physical features that you don't like, but is very ready and
willing and immediately comes pre-downloaded, preloaded with the rules that you want to
live with, right?
What do you do then?
See, now that sounds on the face of it like, oh, well, just get accustomed to the, you
know, but I got to be honest with you.
I don't think it works that way.
No, it's going to be, it's going to be the reason why, yeah, you said it's not going
to work that way.
Why?
Because those are things don't change.
Where if you run into someone, let's say who is either attractive or doesn't have
things that you don't like, the attitude and the behavior is changeable.
A lot of it is, yeah.
Yeah, most of it.
But the hardest part, again, if you find you meet someone and they have things,
attributes that are not changeable and they're not addressing them and telling you there's
a 99% chance that it goes back to their formative years, right?
Like we mentioned earlier, they attach to some kind of, they got, they fell for some
kind of bug or a virus.
It's okay to be that way.
You see?
You know what I mean?
That's a very important one and those are the most difficult ones to address.
Well, right.
And the interesting thing here though is that, and I always, I have tried to advise others
about this, you know, this concept of, well, this is the kind of person they are and, you
know, you can't change people.
And I go, well, look, okay, fine.
Forget about your ability to change somebody.
Here's a reality that a lot of people don't consider when they're in their twenties and
their thirties, especially no one that I know who was in their twenties is the same person
when they reach the age of 40.
Uh, you're, you're different just based on different things you've been exposed to in
your experiences.
If you are exactly the same at the age of 22 as you are at 42, uh, I, I, I don't know
what planet you're from because I don't think that's even possible.
But, uh, well, I don't know.
I don't want to go back and forth on this, but I've met 70 year old plus that are still
that I could show you many ways how they did not mature past nine.
So they, their visage in their appearance changes, but I'm telling you their brains
are, uh, they stopped, uh, their voice gets deeper, but there's a little, it stopped growing
at nine or 10 years old.
Most people in society are like that.
But it's not even necessarily about growth or maturity.
I mean, there is no way that you maintain exactly.
I mean, if you do, then, you know, I mean, that's very strange.
Yeah.
Well, and when you, as you get older, you have different needs physically.
So, but I'm saying most people don't mature past a certain age, but no, no, the, the here's
okay.
But the age thing is, is another thing I like to counter.
Very important.
Sure.
You have certain cultures where you have arranged marriages.
And for example, my great grandparents married at 12 and 13 or 13 and 14 years old respectively.
I think, uh, the grandma was a year older, which was bizarre because usually it goes the
other way around, right?
Um, uh, for late 1800s.
Um, and the grandparents also married around 15 and 16 arranged what's, what's cool about
an arranged marriage.
It's usually when there's a confined culture, right?
You're not going to have an arranged marriage with someone that's from Pakistan or someone
who's in France.
You're usually going to have it within a Pakistani village, right?
A place where most people don't travel more than 20 miles from where they were born.
You know what I mean?
Right.
So the likelihood is that the covenant that they live by, the agreement.
It's already established.
So that's kind of the good thing about it if they have maintained connection to their culture,
right?
If they haven't traveled more than 20 miles from the village that they were born.
Right.
Okay.
Today.
But now with the smartphones, it's different to a certain extent.
The stupid rectangle.
But, but here's the, here's the interesting thing about that is that the, the divorce
rate is almost zero.
What the range matter marriages.
And I'm not talking about dishonor.
You set your wife on fire or kill your husband because he dishonored you and wants to leave.
Right?
No, no, no.
Yeah.
We're talking about a range.
There was the concept of divorce was not a concept.
It was heard of, but not unheard of in terms of practice.
Right.
So this, what I'm doing is going back to what works.
Okay.
So if you're going to hook up with someone for the rest of your life, divorce is not
an option because if divorce was an option, why would you consider hooking up with them
for the rest of your life?
You see?
So when you hook up someone the rest of your life, it's permanent, literally permanent,
you know, as long as you're alive.
So we don't need to reinvent the wheel because we can examine the idea that arranged marriages
have rarely have divorces.
What is, what do arranged marriages have in common?
Well, the people usually don't travel more than 20 or 50 miles from when they were born.
They have a set culture.
That's all they know.
It doesn't mean they're ignorant by the way.
Right.
And that's, they don't know any other thing to apply to themselves.
So for example, we sound like we're talking about the, by definition, you know, what's
called a pagan culture.
You know, they live off the land and all this, right?
The ancients, they called them pagans or whatever.
The peasant culture.
That might hearken back to more what's considered ignorant, but not necessarily.
But just because you have that rigid structure, which could allow freedom within its rules
by the way, it doesn't mean you're ignorant.
You see?
This is another thing that's important.
Because if you, let's say, have a successful relationship by picking someone, and then
both of you through the courting and dating decide on a set of rules to live by.
And by the way, you can even make up these rules, but I don't suggest you do that.
If you have a difference with the culture, the core culture, and the two of you agree
upon it, let's just go with the Pakistani ideal where, you know, maybe alcohol is something
you're not supposed to drink culturally, right?
Among your village there.
But the two of you who are living in a slightly different place agree, listen, you know what?
We can have some alcohol here as long as it's, you know, okay, the bottle of wine.
Modified.
You can modify it based on a mutual desire to modify it as long as it's mutual, right?
Yep.
So again, you notice what we're leaning on heavily is all agreement and what rules you
live by and not what he says or she says.
Now, sometimes there is a dominant factor, right?
But it's not dominant the way that we consider dominant, you know, just because I said so.
No, it still goes back to the rules, right?
So like a final say.
You know, like for example, in government, who has the final say to a quote unquote bill?
It goes to the chief executive officer, right?
Right.
The president, right?
No matter how, no matter what the dynamics are within the various houses of government
or whatever, when it, by the time it gets for the chief executive officer to sign it,
it's might as well, it's finished, right?
So there are things like that, too, in personal relationships, but.
Well, fair enough.
But you also told me to put a pin in this concept of the scent, the smell.
Yeah, the pheromone.
The pheromone.
True scents and smells are not sensory like, you know, one smells like roses or chocolate
or whatever.
There's a pheromone that one will pick up with a partner that after they've been together
for a long time, long time could be anywhere between six months to five years, you end
up finding that person even more attractive because their pheromone, now your body chemistry
and all these other things have adjusted where you find pleasure with being them, not
just because you're comfortable with being with them because of your experiences and
time, but the actual, their smell.
But it's not a direct olfactory.
What I'm trying to say about this is you might meet someone in the beginning as you're going
through this courting process and you may not find their smell pleasant, like a bouquet
of roses.
You may not find it offensive either.
You just notice there's a smell there, right?
Right.
What will happen is after you spend enough time together, that scent will go away that
you sense overtly and you won't sense it anymore and you will find more comfort with
that person because now they've switched their body chemistry to yours.
The two have come together and you each are giving off a complimentary pheromone that
actually makes each other comfortable within the proximity.
It's very interesting how that works.
Anyone who's had the experience of being with someone long enough might remember how
they perceived their smell in the beginning and as time went on that you didn't perceive
it anymore, but you found you enjoy spending time with them.
I'm telling you that scent changed.
Now it goes into the pheromone status, which is you cannot smell it, right?
It's almost, you know, it's like there's a non-visible light that's still measurable,
right?
Or non-audible sounds that are still measurable, right?
Like a dog can hear a certain pitch that we can't, right?
It's in that level.
We can't describe what it smells like.
It's just there.
It's a very interesting thing that happens.
There's some studies on it also, by the way, if you want to spend time on it.
So what I'm saying is the two, after spending enough time together, it's not just physical
time like you're inmates in a cell, but you actually desire time together in that partnership
mentality or idea of forming a partnership.
Your essence, your smell that you give off will change and become pleasant to each other
over time.
So what this is, is if in the beginning you don't find it pleasant, if it's offensive,
it's something that might be what someone has in their diet, by the way.
But it will change and become positive almost every time.
By the way, the diet has a big, since we're on the smell thing, I've met people that
were in the military here and they go to Korea, they're stationed in Korea, and the
first week they have a really hard time because everybody smells like fish and onions everywhere
you go, right?
Well, and after a week or so you don't sense it anymore, but when they come back to the
U.S., all their family members and friends are saying, now you smell like fish and onions,
right?
Right, right.
So until you change again.
So part of it could be geography.
I just want to, thanks for bringing that up, having that pinned, because that's an important,
I went over it kind of quickly, but I assure you, you will actually experience physical,
physiological changes when it comes to quote-unquote olfactory stuff.
You're with someone.
Yeah, definitely.
So I don't know how else to sum it up other than repeating myself.
In essence, you pick someone, or they may pick you, and then it's about deciding how you're
going to live.
Now how, okay, let's just give a personal example.
My wife and I, we're Old Testament type people, okay?
Not religious, and we don't go to church or synagogue or anything, because people want
to pin you into these pigeonholes, right?
It's just a set of rules that I live by, because it covers, it's such old and tried and true.
Old and tried and true for me is more than 100 years old, right?
Okay.
So what to eat, what to wear, how to keep time, all these things.
How do you engage in business?
How do you engage with each other?
All this stuff.
If you don't understand what something is about, and your understanding is only from
what is popularly perceived about it, right, you're going to have a problem figuring out
what covenant or rules you want to live by.
Because if you say you're an Old Testament, I've said this to several people, by the
way, and these are academics, by the way, people that are book editors and scientists
and doctors.
I said, I'm an Old Testament kind of guy, and they said, oh, you're just like going
around killing people, huh?
You know?
I'm like, huh?
Where do you get that from?
Because there was probably some commentary about, well, you know, the God of the Old
Testament said, go and kill everyone, and that's all that stuck with them.
Remember the little thing that's the impression that got stuck in the little child's mind,
right?
Right, right.
Yeah, similar to that.
Somebody once said it, and it was perceived as acceptable, and therefore they figured
they could just say that, and therefore it's acceptable, yeah, okay.
Yeah, so for example, you can look in any ancient text or any ancient culture, but if
you start looking at what people say about it, you're going to be really far off the
mark, right?
Just like, again, with the body.
You look at all the medical references.
Disease is induced induction.
It's not physical, right?
But it has physical manifestations, okay, but the virus theory and the bacteria theory
don't work, and what I want to say about that is that if you're making wine, cheese,
fermented foods, yeah, bacteria and virus theory, well, bacteria is important, right?
Right.
You know, a cheap bottle, you know, okay, you understand fermentation.
If you're dealing with that, yeah, bacteriology and all that stuff matters, but when you're
dealing with human disease, no.
See, and this is within their own reference manual, so what I'm trying to say is, on
the face of it, what is popular is not true.
So, yeah, and also being that most of the audience, I'm presuming, is of Western culture,
which will have it, mostly, is, when I say Old Testament, yeah, it's the rules and
laws that you see in there, and they're actually, maybe I've said this many times, I'll say
it again, if something is not expressly prohibited, it's indirectly encouraged.
Okay.
Indirectly.
So, in other words, if you find a set of 100 rules to live by, and let's say, well, let's
say 500 or 600 rules, only 200 apply to you, and about 50 to 70 of them are prohibitions,
like the acts, you know, that you shouldn't do, well, what are the possible amount of
acts that one can perform or be engaged in in their life?
Thousands?
Millions?
Right?
Yeah, right.
Billions?
I don't know.
Let's say in the millions, right?
Your whole life.
Sure.
Well, if you only have 70 prohibitions or so, doesn't that give you a lot of freedom?
Seems pretty good, yeah.
I mean, if there's only 70 things you can't do, and there's millions of possibilities,
or shouldn't do, yeah.
Actually, if you break it down to less than 20, you see, where when you live in the legal
system, what was okay to do now is not okay to do, and what was not okay to do now is
okay, so where are you going with that?
You see?
Back and forth, right.
Yeah, and yeah, it doesn't work, obviously.
It's inconsistent, at best.
Yeah.
So I think we covered, basically, just pick any, in short, I used to tell people, just
pick anyone, anyone, literally, and look, here's the thing.
You need to practice, also.
Right?
It doesn't practice, and if it doesn't work out, don't you have, quote unquote, an acquaintance,
an associate, possibly a friend, right?
Or they might go around saying, avoid this guy, or this gal, because they're nuts, right?
That's okay.
You'll get something out of it.
Either way.
But you see, this is very simple.
Again, what does the collective, in short, tell you?
We fell in love, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, ends up, we divorced, it's totally normal.
How many times have you heard, we fell in love, and we've been engaged six years now.
We've been engaged 10 years now, right?
Yeah, right.
Then they get married, and two years later, we're having a divorce.
Well, what?
What did you do in between?
Well, when you were engaged, when you were engaging, what was going on?
Talking about what's on CNN, and eating chocolate cake?
I always wonder that myself, when somebody's engaged for five years, but they only stay married for two.
Yeah, it's common.
It's very weird.
Yeah, it's very common.
Weird to me, but yeah, very common.
Yeah, to me, that's trash.
I mean, that's total trash.
I mean, just write everything that happened in your relationship from day one to the day you divorced,
and on a piece of paper, so I could crumble it up and throw it away.
I mean, this is the level that most people are operating on in the Western culture right now.
Now, what I'm saying is a stark contrast to it, but you know what?
It works, and what I've just said works every time.
It doesn't mean that when you pick someone, the first one and the only one is the only one, right?
But once you start exercising this principle, it'll end up  well, this is not a guarantee.
By the way, I never say guarantee.
I say assurance that this will work for you personally because there's two ways to find out
whether you should spend the rest of your life living solo.
One is by conscious decision, and the other one is by unconscious exclusion,
which is you want to get into a relationship, and you've been at it now for 50 years.
You're in your 70s, 80s.
It hasn't worked out for you yet.
Well, guess what?
By unconscious exclusion, you're the type of person that lives alone, right?
You see, there's two ways.
So it's rough, but fortunately our lives are short.
You know, 70 or 80 years in cosmic time is not even measurable.
That's how short it is, right?
Very short, yeah.
Yeah, so I don't know.
What do you think so far?
I think this is really interesting and different from many of the other sonics that we've done,
and I'm enjoying it, I've got to say.
So very interesting to contemplate.
Well, not too much because you notice one thing that Iyou notice how simple the rules are.
There's not much to contemplate.
It's more of ahow would you say it?
It's a do.
It's something you have to do.
It's not somethingyou could think about doing this for 10 years.
It ain't going to make it.
You're not going to get anything out of it.
You have to do it.
Right.
You've got to go out there and mix it up with people, and you see, it's a doer's kind of thing.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I get that.
I'm thinking back to my own relationships and how they worked out and made many mistakes.
It would have been very different, I'm sure, if you had this under your belt.
If I had this, yeah, exactly.
I was thinking that, that if I had been thinking this way to begin with,
I could have saved myself a lot of time and agony, actually.
Yeah, but where would you save the time?
If you put time in a jar, time is going to pass anyway, so it's okay.
I might have had more time with people that I wanted to be with as opposed to those I found out I didn't want to be with, is all I'm saying.
Yeah, and the main point here is you actually make the situation.
It just doesn't happen, right?
The people that are engaged for six years, marry for two, and then divorce, they have no control.
They think they have control of what's going on,
but they're just following what has been thrown out by some Illuminati, whatever.
Let's try this.
And when I say that, you know, the 60s movement was a farce.
The 70s movement was a farce, right?
All that stuff, right?
It was all fabricated, right?
All the way down to the way people view how they should be in a relationship is fabricated.
If you speak to people in the Western world, if they have a television or watch movies or whatever,
99% of their behavior is what they are mimicking or copying what they've seen on television or within their family,
which is also because, look, well, I don't do what is shown on television or the movies.
All right, how old is your mom and your dad?
Well, they're so-and-so.
They were born in the 60s and 70s.
Well, guess what?
You're doing what they did, and they got it from television, you see.
So it's one of these things that I'm saying now that's very influential.
Okay, the other thing that I haven't brought up, and it's not minor, but here it's at the end,
is what if you're already in a relationship and it's working well or it's not working well?
Well, it goes both ways.
Which one should we do first?
You're in a relationship that's not well or a relationship that's well?
Which one do you want to do first, Chuck?
Well, I'm sure everybody would want to hear the not well one first.
Okay.
If it's not going well, when you start getting a proposal together to speak and negotiate with who you're with,
what it will do, it will be like the sort of the Gordian knot.
If you could untie this knot, you get our kingdom.
If our relationship is like this knot, we have a problem with it, we've got to just untie this knot or whatever.
Actually, tying the knot is being married.
If you have a stark proposal and let's come up with some rules or whatever to live by, it will go 50-50.
It won't stay the same for sure.
It will 50-50.
In other words, if you bring this up, let's pick a covenant to live by,
at that point, once that meeting happens, the relationship will never continue the same way.
It will go 50-50.
One, it will get better, or you'll break up.
It will get worse.
That's the good thing about it.
Because sometimes it not going well and continuing for years and years and years is like the water torture drop on the forehead.
Right?
Right.
So would you rather have it right there, draw the line as a fork in the road, it ends in disaster or we get better?
I think it's better than the water torture, right?
Oh, I think it's decidedly better to at least have a direction and we know where we're going.
Yeah, definitely.
Exactly.
That's what happens when it's not going well.
And most of the time, believe it or not, it ends up when the relationship is not so great and you do that, it ends up  I'd say 70% of the time, 80% of the time, it ends up getting better.
Only a small percentage of the time does it completely break up, which would have been inevitable anyway, either way, and also for your health and all these things.
Okay.
Let's go to the other one now.
What if your relationship is doing well and it just happens to be doing well?
What do you think?
And you bring up a firm covenant.
90% of the time you're going to break up.
You heard me.
If not 95% of the time.
What?
Greek?
It doesn't make any sense.
Because earlier you said if your relationship is not going well and you have the meeting and you bring this up, 80% of the time it will go well, about one-third or 20% of the time, let's say, it will break up.
But now we move over to the relationship is going really well.
Without a rudder, you're just floating on the lake and you bring this up, 90% to 95% of the time you're going to break up.
It doesn't make any sense because it sounded like it was a good thing when it was applied to the relationship that wasn't going well.
And now we apply the same thing to the relationship that's going well.
They're going to end up breaking up.
It doesn't make any sense, does it, Chuck?
Well, actually, it kind of does to me because if you already have a situation, you know, the old, if it ain't broke, don't fix it, right?
Mm-hmm.
There you go.
You know, that's what it kind of, I mean, I know that sounds real ignorant to a lot of people, but sorry, I agree with it.
If it's working, then it's working, right?
Yeah, but it's working and you don't know why, you don't know how.
Once you bring in a set of rules to live by or whatever, it breaks up.
And I've told this to people that are in private and whatever for years now, almost a decade and a half.
I would like to say two decades, but I didn't really, I wasn't really a proponent of what I'm discussing until a decade and a half ago.
Oh, me and my wife were okay or whatever, and I guess we're okay.
You know, the key word is I guess we're okay.
We're, you know, nothing, no big deal, nothing, we don't have any problems, but I want to start living lawfully.
Oh, really?
You're going to, she's going to leave you.
You're going to break up.
Not only her, her whole family's going to hate you.
Guess what?
Six months later, Greek, you were right.
I'm living on my own now.
Right.
What?
Every time.
Not every time, but yeah, most of the time.
Well, because there's already unspoken agreements in place.
Now, you're coming in to change it, and that person was probably pleased with it.
The other, you know, the other party, the gal, the guy, whatever, it doesn't matter.
Chances are you were part of the collective, and you were leaning on television and what everybody else says,
and now you brought something in that's hard and tangible, and it shattered the smoke, you know?
Well, whatever it was, it contradicts what was already in place.
So, yeah, there you go.
In most cases, yeah.
And believe it or not, even in religious quote-unquote situations,
so let's say you were in a religious Jewish family, and you want to be lawful,
and you start figuring out you're supposed to live with the Torah,
and you hear some Greeks speak because you're not going to get anywhere else,
and how to keep time?
They're all going to banish you.
You see?
I don't think people are expecting us to say that, actually.
If you're just floating along thinking you're doing well,
once you bring in some structure, it's going to break up.
I don't think people were expecting that.
So with that said, I think we're going to wrap this one up.
There you go.
I think that's a perfect time to do so.