The Sonic Event 84, Rated Y, and here we go.
Why?
Because...
Mickey Mouse.
I'm not going there.
Anyway, how are you doing today?
Oh boy.
Doing okay.
By the way, you know, we haven't brought up the lawful timekeeping in general terms.
We're in the last month of the year for about almost a week, not quite.
We're speaking on the 30th of January, 2024.
And I reckon, I think it was Tuesday, Wednesday, previous, actually, I'll give you a date because
this is the end of the year.
You know, it's funny how most people just pass it off as whatever, but it's an intelligence
office.
When I say intelligence office, they've been run by the Jesuits since the 1500s, right?
And before.
Yeah, right.
I mean, most people think of intelligence as just those things that were established
by more modern governments, and then it's an offshoot, allegedly not part of it, and you
know, blah, blah, blah.
And they all play the same game after a while.
Yeah.
So let's say around the 23rd or so, it was the change of months, or like I said, a week,
because it seems like today's the day off, right?
Okay.
You know, a good way to look at that, but I don't want to pass that by, the intelligence
off.
Hold on.
How about this?
What is a good way to look at it?
You have, no matter what the governmental structure is, it's irrelevant as to what language
it's in or anything else, you have a supposedly governing body, right?
One way or another recognizes the will of people, either to be accepted as subjects
or to be part of a democracy or a representative republic or, you know, the democratic republics
of nonsense that they tell you.
That's an intelligence off, too.
Whenever you hear revolution or civil war, that's, that's Freemasons, right?
Oh, yeah, sure.
But supposedly a governing body then comes up with the need to do what?
Okay.
A good thing that a government could do is collect together resources to create defense
and an army is built and made and so on and so forth.
And then you need to inform that army.
So often that's the justification for creating a intelligence group.
And this sort of thing, even though that's not what it's called, has been there ever
since.
I don't know.
People have decided to organize their little sub societies out there, right?
These little nation states, these areas that are governed by we're all part of one particular
geographical area.
So might as well combine forces and resources.
And then intelligence ops grow from it.
Now, that's the typical understanding of it.
But there's a spiritual end to this, isn't there?
Well, yeah.
Well, the spiritual, it's all the same.
Okay.
Well, we've been talking about this for a long time.
Last thing I want to get to just real fast, and then I want to hand it to you because
this is big to me.
You have all sorts of organizations, even when we talked about the hierarchy of the
gods, right?
Small g.
Okay.
You have a whole lot of these entities that all come together and they send intermediaries
of sorts to collect information, to gather certain things, to create certain things,
right?
And those things are not necessarily the gods themselves.
They're not representative of you.
They're certainly foreign.
But they go out and there's like intelligence ops among the gods even.
Right?
I mean, an intelligence op is something that's, yeah, go ahead.
Here's an interesting, most people are well doused in Greek speak.
Go listen to some of the archaic stuff based on the historical.
You put out some stuff, I'm not endorsing him, but when something's good, we're all
here to learn, right?
So I'm still learning.
Everybody's learning and we share and that's how we learn.
And I like some of the stuff that he gets into with the history and how it ties into
a lot of the holy rites and how I remember being on Revolution Radio back in 2011 or
12 with Seth Michael and other people on these round tables and they would bring up the gods
and I was like, they're just humans, man.
They're just humans all the way up.
We don't have anything else.
This is a human creation by humans for humans.
You know, all that other stuff.
Right.
But it doesn't mean the part.
OK, when I talk about the gods, OK, some people think I'm religious or whatever, and
I'm not. I get my law from there because hell, if I'm going to get it from Nancy
Pelosi or whatever, right, or Ronald Reagan or George Washington or Congress.
Oh, my gosh. You still must you still help to follow those.
Right. And you're supposed to.
So I got my law from there. But the thing that's always irked me now for more than
two decades is that when people speak on the gods or even let's just say the Bible
or whatever, and you look into what's been memorialized, right, if they say, I say,
where'd you get that? We got it from the Bible.
I'm like, that's not in the Bible.
So so what's going on is we have like Dmitry Kaluzov calls it the third truth.
There's three truths. There's the first truth that the people think is true.
Then there's the second truth, which is the administrative, the more the elites think
is true, which is also not, by the way.
Then there's the third truth, which is the best you can do closest to the truth.
You can call the truth. Right.
So it's undeniable.
So, for example, when I used to hear people talk about the biblical stuff, I'm like,
that's not in the Bible. That's not how it goes.
What's this? And because all you got to do is read it.
So it's not it's not special information, even in the piss poor versions that you
have. You talk about anything, whatever you want to bring up.
I'll show you. Read it.
It's not what it says.
It's pretty easy to the easiest thing about situation type literature.
It has a setting.
So most people are visual kinesthetic, right?
They can't process the words.
And, you know, it's a whole other discussion that we've had.
But visual kinesthetic.
So what you do is let's say a scene is described biblically.
You do. You can actually take the time out and do what's called a storyboard.
Filmmakers do that when they read a script, you know, where they do like a storyboard.
It's actually a sketch where people are standing and they make description.
It looks almost like a cartoon comic book, you know.
Right. Like a comic strip, actually.
Strip to strip where you see a progression of events.
Let's draw a picture. And when you read something out of the Bible, it's OK.
If you don't get it, let's draw a quick picture.
And you just you could even have to be good at drawing.
Just start sketching things out.
And it's like, isn't this what is being said here?
Isn't what I'm sketch. So why?
Why? Where'd you get? Oh, they told me that at church.
This is what I believe.
Oh, my gosh. I've even had Christians say to me, I don't need the Bible to believe.
I'm like, oh, boy. Well, where are you getting your story from?
Right. So this is why I got into that.
And that's why I talk about the biological vacuum when it comes to medical stuff.
I mean, how can you trust anyone that tells you the heart is a pump?
And by the way, a mild tangent.
Any new drugs by this is just like a public advisory.
Yeah. Any new drugs that have come out since 2016?
Because by the way, the twenty nineteen covid thing started around Obama.
I don't know if you remember.
They were ready to vaccinate everyone with the swine flu and everything.
Almost make it mandatory.
But they didn't. Do you remember that?
It was like twenty fifteen, twenty sixteen.
There was a progression for about a decade, actually, of a whole bunch of these
different big threat diseases.
Right. Everything from Zika.
Let's go Zika. We'll go Z first.
Yeah. Which which by the way, the Zika was because they had a mosquito problem and
they were spraying insecticides that caused nerve damage, just like polio.
But anyway, public service announcement from the Greek, any drugs that have been
developed or put on the market since then, 2016 are dangerous.
Doesn't matter what it's for, whether it's an antibiotic, a painkiller
treatment for restless leg syndrome, urinary this.
Do not take any.
If you're going to go with any pharmaceutical, make sure it's something that's
like first or second gen, more than 20 year old formula.
Do not repeat.
Do not with a capital T have any drugs that were developed more less
than 20 years ago administered to you at all.
It doesn't matter what it is. They are dangerous poisons.
They do absolutely nothing but harm the body.
Now, it's very rare that I give such a discreet public information
announcement. And I mean it, you know, a moment of silence.
I really mean that. Do not take any medicines that have been developed after,
let's say, 2000.
So if you feel like you have to do, let's say, an antibiotic, do a penicillin
or amoxicillin. And as a matter of fact, there are a lot of articles written 10
years ago about how dangerous antibiotics are.
They don't do anything other than destroy the body.
So I just wanted to bring this up.
It's pretty bad.
And even without saying this, you should have an intuitive feeling about it.
Since what happened in 2019, 2020, you should know this right now.
Right. So but anyway, to go back to what I was saying,
when I heard stuff in the religious circles and when I say religious circles,
I'm talking about Islam also.
I was like, that's not in anything that where are you getting that right?
Even Buddhism, where are you getting that?
I mean, so what I became a stickler for is if we're going to talk on a subject
and that subject relies very heavily on reference material, i.e.
literary material, stuff that's been memorialized and praised to be containing
the information, you do not have license to deviate.
Right. You can't start making stuff up.
And that's what's going on. It doesn't matter if it's medical.
It doesn't matter if it's scientific.
I always gave the analogy.
It doesn't matter how powerful of a microscope you have.
If you cut a wire with electrons flowing through it and you have a dustpan ready to
sweep up the electrons, you will never find any electrons there.
It's all bullshit.
There's nothing flowing in those wires.
Right. So I've tried to explain this regarding what they call paganism,
whatever, the multifaceted universe of that stuff.
There is this paganism, by the way, from from a proper point of view.
I always knock it because I try to drive a wedge between the thinking of a man
of a man or a woman or a human or person, let's say, of the people
between what they're handling, because most people are able to handle
two thoughts that contradict each other at once and then and they mix them.
And that shouldn't be done. Right. Right.
Well, so but real paganism is just polytheism, which is also biblical, by the
way. Yes, because it says do not worship other gods.
Well, if there are no other gods, why would you say that?
That's totally redundant and stupid.
But I don't really go down that road because it does.
It sounds like I'm more being apologetic and a mediator.
People do not need that.
They need to be hit across the head with a wet newspaper to wake them up.
No, but even the people that say that they are steeped in paganism, to be honest
with you, they have deviated from all of the standards by which they're swearing
by exactly in the same way anybody does who is a Christian or a
Jew or a, you know, or or what is that?
A member of the nation of Islam, whatever it is, Islamic.
Sure. But but here's the thing about that entire subject.
We don't know what I've been harping on is that if you are
leaning either towards the Islam or, you know, the Judeo-Christian
side as your model for law, because that's really the only reason to go there,
by the way, is to figure out what what's right, what's wrong.
Right. Based on your culture.
And you must go back to the founding document
at least. Right. You know, you hear that a lot in the Patriot community.
It's the same thing.
So what I started off with, if you want to get more of a handle on the
chronology, archaics has got it pretty tight.
It actually opened my eyes to a lot of the stuff that I went back and knew
about, but did not research.
And I'm slowly looking into it again.
And it is true that the biblical text did exist.
It's a it's a compilation of other writings put together.
But it doesn't matter if you don't know it.
So like someone like archaics, he really doesn't know the Bible.
He says he's read it 40 times.
He has the notes to prove it. But he really didn't.
He read it once. Forty times is the difference.
Right. Right.
So it's like saying you have 30 years experience.
No, you have one year experience.
You just keep doing the same thing over and over.
No, you don't. He doesn't even know it.
And he has the whole thing on dark scriptures and whatever.
It's not wholly accurate. He drifts away and confabulates.
That's fine, because if you put him against the wall, he'll say, well,
I'm just a chronologist. Right.
But he's delves in all these other things. Right.
And that's OK. But you have to understand how untidy he can get.
I'm not knocking him, but I'm not endorsing him either.
The chronology is tight.
And what's important about that is if you study the chronology
and how the Greek gods came about, they were people.
Right. If you study these gods, they were people.
If you study the Bible, they were people, all of them.
We have when it comes to the divine,
the closest thing that I could sum up if it was going to be my last words is this.
I'm a big fan of Tesla, but he's not like a demigod,
like a lot of people put him, because a lot of the stuff that he designed
really didn't work.
Not until Steinmetz came around 20 years later.
It wasn't for Steinmetz.
The AC motors that Tesla did would would not be working.
They exploded because he used solid cores.
He didn't use laminates and all that.
So anyway, this is a whole other thing.
He didn't know about the the fusion math that was necessary,
where you pull and derive
from another dimension in all this.
Tesla didn't do that.
But to go back to Tesla, I'd venerate him from this.
He says that the mind does not think it is connected
to a central core in the universe somewhere.
And he's always trying to pull from that, you know, ideas, thoughts, inspirations.
He doesn't know what the core is, but he knows it exists.
That's what that's where I put as my belief.
Now, some people some people describe that as the Akashic Library
and this kind of thing on and on, but no one can prove it.
But we know it exists. Here's the thing.
Right. We could talk about the Akashic Library.
But if someone argued that it doesn't exist, you'd have to agree.
But if someone but you couldn't argue that something like that does not exist,
you can't because it's so obvious that something like that exists.
But to make it so specific, it's this and this and this.
I don't know about that.
But does something like that exist? Absolutely. Yeah.
Again, like like Tesla said, we do not think we extract
from a core in the universe somewhere.
But with this, he doesn't know what it is, but he knows we're extracting from it.
Right. With this certainty, you can prove that information travels
without the benefit of conventional roadways for it to travel on. Right.
I mean, even the twelve. Yeah.
Sure. But here there's OK.
You know what I'm saying?
The twelve monkeys thing where you end up with the monkeys who learn something,
even though they've never been connected to the monkeys on the other.
That's actually I heard a lot of just contrary things.
I heard that was just urban myth that didn't happen.
But yes, that's good enough, even if it didn't happen.
Just like the lemmings never happened.
You know, they were thrown off the cliff.
They didn't go off on their own, supposedly.
But yes, those are analogies and metaphors that we use
to sustain some form of rationale.
Right. One way or another, information does travel.
And it's not because it was spoken directly or written down.
It does travel from one place to another.
And sometimes people would say it's carried by a muse.
It's carried by this information superhighway of a spiritual sense.
It is part of the Christ consciousness.
It is part of, you know, we could go on for thousands of years on that
because that's what's been going on.
But if you start dissecting it chronologically,
you'll see that all of the entities, biblical or non-biblical, are all human.
As a matter of fact, even if you don't believe in Exodus 15, it says Yahweh is a man.
And I was doing a study on Exodus with a Hebrew speaker, someone raised in Israel.
And he says, no, no, not really.
And he goes to reads it in Hebrew and says it's ish.
And he's like, oh, my gosh, it is ish.
Right. Meaning it's it's a man, man.
Meaning that's not, you know, it's an ish is it means carnal.
So, you know, and I've been saying since the longest time the gods.
Are just super high tech, whatever.
Imagine meeting someone that has a technology a million years ahead of you.
A million years ago.
Oh, my gosh. Of course, you're a god.
We use that term very loosely and it's fine.
But we draw from a place
that we do not know enough exactitude, but we know we're drawing from it.
It's good enough.
Just like when you go buy bottled water because you don't want to drink tap water.
You know, it's better than tap water.
Do you know exactly how it was processed and exactly?
No, but you know, it's better. Right.
So you lean towards that. Right. Right.
So it's the same thing.
One thing that people get really confused on is their ability.
They cap off their they create their own limits
and they get confused about how to deal with that.
Again, something brochures from our Kickstarter because of dungeon programming.
I really like that.
It's like you're programmed to be in a dungeon.
And there's an old analogy.
If you were born in a jail cell and I've done this with dogs, by the way,
with kennels, if you all you knew was a jail cell,
if you went out into the world and you felt there was trouble,
guess where you're going to run for safety.
So you're going to run right in the jail and close the door.
That's why whenever I had a dog, I always first day I got him,
put him in the kennel, fed him in the kennel, loved him in the kennel.
Came time to night, go in the kennel.
If I gave a command to go to the kennel, he went into the kennel.
That was good for the dog.
Wouldn't get in trouble that way. Right.
And he went into the kennel by himself.
I had one dog was just a lovely dog.
I said, oh, he's too cute.
Come in the bed with me.
Guess what? After a month of sleeping without no way I'm getting in the kennel.
Right. Right. So.
So, I mean, love can spoil something also.
From that perspective, you know, what is love?
Right. Doing the right thing.
In that case, it would have that was not really love
because the best thing would have been kept the dog trained for the kennel.
But for humans, for some humans, if not most humans,
that dungeon program is it works.
It's best for them to feel safe in the jail that they're in.
And I've tested this, by the way. Right.
They get really angry if you poke at that concept.
And that's just the way things are.
And that's fine. Accept it.
But the thing I want to say most people have a hard time with
is how to remove the cap that they put on themselves, the limit.
Most people have limitations.
And it's beyond the jail cell safety or the dungeon programming.
It's the way they perceive things.
Like, for example, mostly I remember we did a thing
where I talked about, you know, well, someone said, you find out about that.
No, I'm not interested in that subject.
You know, people say, oh, I'm not interested in that. Right.
I'm interested. Oh, my gosh.
As a human being, as one of the people
and what the faculties that you have in connection to the core,
you can or may be interested in everything, everything.
OK, to say it this way, everyone should be interested in everything
and what depth of matter and breadth of the matter
and how much time you dedicate to it is another issue.
But for someone to completely dismiss something that they actually interact with.
As because they're not interested is a cap and a limit
that was somehow placed on them. Right.
And what you will find is one thing transfers to another.
I was on a long call about building scalerators.
And I said, if you've never built anything like this,
go put on a YouTube on how cars are made and just watch it.
You'll see the metal being pressed, painted, fitted.
One certain things are put in and whatever.
It's the same exact mindset.
It doesn't matter if you're building something with two parts
or something with 2000 parts productions, production, manufacturing,
building stuff is building stuff. It doesn't matter.
If you watch a house be a modern house being built or a straw hut,
the principle is exactly the same.
So transfer. But I'm not interested.
OK, the moment you hear I'm not interested the right way.
What the person is expressing is they put a cap and a limit
self-contained on themselves.
And that's that's a self-inflicted wound, I call it. Right.
That that leads to trauma, personal trauma.
So you want to deal with that?
No, I think you should skip that one and go to the next one.
No, but in defense, in defense of that person, though,
in defense of that mindset, isn't there a point at which some things
you could say are just good enough, like the bottled water?
And I really want to focus my energy, my effort, my time on other things.
Maybe they don't want to know.
But hold on. That's not what I'm saying.
I'm saying that the person dismisses it completely
by just simply saying not interested, just like when the person says,
I'm not good at math. Oh, that's fine. That's OK.
There's plenty of good people not good at math.
How they arrived to that is because of laziness.
And by the way, when someone says, I'm not good at this.
Well, gosh, you know, you're not good at that's what you should be working on.
Right. Because if it came up now, it'll come up again.
For example, when I used to train in bicycle racing
and everyone gets together, the person who was good at hill climbing,
when we got to the hill, they went up the hill real fast.
When it came to sprinting, the people that were good at sprinting
sprinted realized, what are you guys doing?
What are you doing? This is training, right?
You should train what you're weak in.
Don't train what you already know you're strong in.
Why don't you? So the sprinter.
Why don't you train the hill now? Go ahead.
We're not going to laugh at you.
We know you can't climb, but this is a training ride.
This is the time where you train your weakness and you perform with your strength.
So what's going on?
And I've been noticed that people are performing
when they're flashing all their weaknesses and their strengths.
And by the way, they're not allowed to flash their strengths,
because if you start showing that all that person thinks is full of himself.
Right. But when you flash your weakness.
Oh, that's OK. You're fine.
Oh, my gosh.
So there's a metamorphosis that takes place.
And when I say metamorphosis versus transition, because a metamorphosis
is when you see one thing in one stage and you see the second stage that it goes to,
it doesn't the second stage sometimes may not even resemble anything.
Right. Like a butterfly, a caterpillar going to a butterfly is called metamorphosis.
Right. There's no relation.
If you show someone who's not familiar with that creature, a caterpillar
and a butterfly, they cannot even intuit that it was the same thing at one point.
Right. So it's a metamorphosis.
And this is how fast change comes when you're connected to the core
or the divine or the inspiration.
And we've talked about how the inspiration, the idea, the inspiration,
the thought, the manifestation works.
And what all I see, by the way, is people's limitations
when they not. That's not all I see.
Let me take that back.
It's very easy for me to see what people are like flashing like a badge,
their limitations instead of dealing with them. Right.
Now, one thing I had a conversation similar to this with someone recently said,
well, we're technologically advanced now.
We can change. I said, no, you're not.
Just because this is the real definition of technologically advanced society.
And I'll show you. I'll prove this just because everyone has a computer
and a camera that also acts as a phone doesn't mean you're technologically
advanced, because ninety nine point nine, nine, nine, nine, nine, nine, nine, nine,
nine, nine, nine, nine, nine, nine, nine percent of the people.
If you took the phone and asked them, can you show me how to make this phone
from raw materials? They can't.
In other words, if you went to the zoo and to the gorilla monkey primates
and you gave each one of them a cell phone, would you call them
technologically advanced? No.
So why are you calling people technology?
If you went to them, you gave every monkey a cell phone,
Jim, orangutan, gorilla.
You wouldn't call them technologically.
And it's why what they could you could train them to use it just as well.
I'm sure they even have apps for monkeys now.
Now, OK, I'm sure they'll get into the camera part real quick.
But anyway, selfies especially get it.
So the monkeys with the cell phones is no different than the humans
with the cell phones.
They're not any less or more advanced, either one.
So why are you calling people?
Tell me again, how are you calling them technically advanced person?
Just shut up right away.
And this is a professional person in psychology.
Right. Shut her ass up right away.
And she got it.
She got it, though, because she's trained to form new ideas.
This is a new idea because the monkey cannot.
And then you could say, well, there are people who made the cell phone.
Yeah, we presume there's someone designed it and built it.
But very, very, very, very, very few.
So a more accurate statement would be that amongst humans,
there are some that are very technologically advanced,
so advanced that they are able to compile enough raw material
in an engineering fashion to produce this device. Right.
Wow. A very how many people can from from soup to nuts,
in other words, take the raw material and have the knowledge, even a group.
Well, I'm not expecting one person, a group of people
in the whole population that can do that.
Take it from raw plastic, silicone, glass, metal, whatever.
Silver, gold, you need whatever plastics and make a finished cell phone.
Very few people.
Very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very few people
can do that from soup to nuts. Right.
Probably about as many people could do that as as many dogs could take
an unloaded firearm, load it up and utilize. Yeah, it's very.
So why are you putting there?
Why are you bestowing their virtues on the entire population?
You see, you can't do that. Oh, right.
So so this is what's going on.
And this is what I'm stating when.
So when you're taking interest in a cell phone, am I demanding
that you know how to take raw materials and make a finished cell phone? No.
But know what you can do and can't do and express it properly.
Put everything in its proper magnitude, what you can do.
Like if you like playing golf, you may not go to the World Championships.
You like running. You're not going to run in the Olympics.
It's fine to know and express your limits, but don't do it without warrant.
Well, it's just like people tell me nowadays, you know, like people
are just generally more knowledgeable than they've ever been.
I say, no, they're not, because they have access.
Sure. A lot of people, you know, have plenty of access to, you know,
information that is beyond belief, but it doesn't mean that they utilize.
Well, actually, some of the information is beyond belief
because it just simply isn't true.
Well, you study the entire medical industry.
It's all fiction right now.
But just like you and I have discussed before, within the lie,
you can learn the truth because you can learn to eliminate what is clearly a lie.
Yeah, to to a degree.
But I'm telling you, on a personal level, I'm finding it to get really bad right now.
The level of disinformation is in the 80 to 90 percent range.
It's really bad.
Unless again, you go where old books.
I'm well, how many times have you heard me say in Sonic
that everything that could have been known was already known by the 1890s?
So that's why you've said many times
the only books of value are the ones that were printed, you know, before nineteen
hundred or before 1920, for sure, before World War One would have been the cutoff.
Some people say later, I've seen some things up until the 1950s,
but you can feel it and taste it.
You can tell something has gone wrong.
Yeah, absolutely.
Now, but the metamorphosis, my point is, even if you could put someone
in a giant library that was the size of, you know, the old New York libraries
that were huge, I don't know if they still exist like this. They don't.
Well, they were they don't.
I mean, they were large buildings that contained books
from one end to the other, books loaded with all kinds of information.
You stick somebody in there, though, and they don't read any of it.
It did no good.
You know what I'm saying?
So just because they have access to it, they have access to tools.
They have access to knowledge.
It does not mean that they interacted with it or gained any of it.
Well, yeah, they have archives, but the public is not interested.
It's kind of like the money system.
You know, you talk to anyone about the money system, even affluent people,
like, oh, no, I like all the points I get on my credit card.
Oh, my gosh.
There is no way they will.
They will understand what they're actually doing, their own destruction. Right.
A lot of the ancient texts talk about you.
Basically, when destruction comes, you brought it upon yourself.
And I see that.
But what I want to say, there's a metamorphosis, in other words,
when one understands how to relieve certain things
and approach certain things in a more proper way.
The difference is not gradual.
You literally go from a caterpillar to a butterfly almost instantly.
You transform yourself very quickly.
And by the way, it's not very popular to do that.
You do see that when certain people, let's say,
you know, you hear about some guy, you know, I'm a born again Christian now.
And you're completely and they're completely different. Right.
They from one day to the next. Right.
Oh, I went to this meeting and it changed me.
You know, and then they decide to go.
There was no transition there.
You know, right.
There was a they just changed completely and they stuck with it. Right. Right.
This is possible with all people at any time
if they allow it and they consider it.
Now, the the thing about the mind to go back to being attached to the core,
we are extremely limited in that sense that I think in one of the Sonics
I brought up the process that John Mase uses
that it's very similar to what I talked about in Greek speak.
But he made a package of it package deal kind of thing.
That we only see images.
We think of images. We only remember images.
The key, you know, you might think you remember a past event,
but you're actually it's just images.
It's just like if you're looking at a film, if you freeze it and stop it,
even digitally frames per second, it's just a series of frames
running in sequence we call time.
So there's still just images, right?
Everything is a still image.
And recently I'll do this with everyone.
Someone contacted me about
do I have a way of dealing with grief?
And and I was like, yeah, it's a very simple one.
And so we'll get in touch soon.
And I'll share this with everyone right now.
This is this is what we're going to do.
Basically, the John Mase method and also taking advantage
of how the brain simply works, just like, for example, it's simple.
It's not a mystery.
If someone drives a car and it suddenly turns off
and the temperature meter is all the way high.
And to them, they driving a car is a ritual.
They don't know what just happened. It shuts down.
Well, if someone knows that the car has some it relies on the radiator
or the coolant fluid, if it's a water cooled, that the water pump went bad
or they broke a piston rod one or the other or whatever and seized up the engine.
They can apply techno technically, very technically.
If you want to fix that, it's fixable.
Where the person who doesn't know that that's what it is to them,
they're baffled and they could spend the next 20 years trying to figure out
asking other people that don't know how it works, what happened.
And they won't come up with an answer.
But if you go to someone who knows the car mechanics inside and out right away,
he has an answer and a fix for you.
See, that's what I'm referring to with this John Mase method, Mase method.
And it's Mase, M.A.C.E.
with the brain only records images, meaning stills,
even though like the most popular thing is especially remember in the 80s
all these 1980s, late 70s,
there were a lot of these designer perfumes and colognes
becoming popular for the first time before that.
You got aftershave and Chanel number five, and that's it.
Right. There was a big boom of like Ralph Lauren and this and that.
Remember Paco Rabanne and Aramis and all these all suddenly
there was an explosion in the population for designer colognes that were
and perfumes that were accessible to the public and the public took interest.
And there was like one.
I remember that even you don't smell it much, but when you smell it now,
it takes me right back to the 80s.
The smell immediately takes me back.
And I remember where I was, what I was doing more than if you asked me
to think about that time.
It's like a stimulus or an impulse.
Now is so the smell can also be recorded as a still image,
because I didn't say it was the smell, this, that and the other.
It was just the smell that did it.
So saying that the mind only remembers and recalls still images
still holds true for something like that, because it was just the smell that did it.
Yeah. I'll give you another common trigger.
Right. When you smell a particular food
that was prepared at a special event at some point in time,
like maybe you smell, I don't know.
Let's just go with the easy thing.
Thanksgiving stuffing, stuffing.
You don't usually smell in people's houses or dressing.
If you're west of the Mississippi.
There you go. All right.
So those two things, when you smell them and it smells very similar
to like what you smelled at your grandmother's house,
all of a sudden you go back to a time.
Sure. Everything.
What I hate the most, by the way, about smells is I like to burn
frankincense and myrrh in the house for many reasons.
Frankincense and myrrh, the smoke is a resin and it will leave a microscopic
nanolayer of resin on the walls, which is extremely antiseptic.
Let's just say what I don't like about burning it is being forced
to go to a Greek Orthodox church when they burned it back then.
And it brings back that memory.
And I've worked that out.
And I'm going to talk a little bit more on how to work out these impulses,
which are stills, whether it's a smell, a smell.
Analogy I gave because I was thinking I brought up
how the brain thinks in still images, even if you remember
an event is just a compiled still images and think about
10 or 20 years, a significant event.
Try to think of that event in motion.
You will not be continuous.
You will see images, successive images.
You cannot really recall a fluid event like you would see run in a film.
It will be just successive images.
On one part of a thought, you're standing on this side of the room.
The next thought you're on the other side of the room.
How did you get there?
Because it's another still.
You see what it's like.
And it's fragmented slides. Yeah.
So the smells and other impulses and words are the same thing.
So if you, let's say, had a gang of people you hung out with gang,
meaning like the old way, a group of people and they had a nickname for you
and you haven't heard it in 30 years.
And suddenly you hear that again.
It takes you right back to that.
You know, when you were roofing, roofing was
we'd go in the back of neighborhoods and the garages were next to each other.
We jumped from garage roof to garage roof to garage roof.
Whoever got to the end of the block first that way,
we know was the challenge, you know, the one to challenge.
And it was dangerous
because sometimes the gaps between the roofs got really wide.
And if you fell, you can break a leg, right?
That's not fun.
It's not fun at 10 years old or 11.
So, you know, so all of these things, you know, again, are still it's just one word.
It's just one smell. It's it's the same as a still.
So to go back with someone who asked me, how do we deal with grief?
I said, you have a way. I said, yes, we'll get in touch soon.
So this I'll use the John Mace method application. We'll do this here.
Oh, yeah. And this works with everyone.
One other random reminder that people be able to relate to easily,
though, is the smell of popcorn or and the smell of that artificial butter.
Oh, yeah. Or a fart.
You know, whatever. Rotten eggs.
You know, yeah, I got a lot of memories tied to farts.
But, you know, when it comes to popcorn, I'm thinking that's one of those things,
though, that they actually use.
You know, when you go to I know a lot of people don't go to movie theaters anymore.
But I'm guaranteeing that if somebody hears me say,
think of the smell of buttered popcorn, you're automatically
snapped to a movie theater or something.
Sure. Yeah. But it's infinite.
Everything, everything you ever will be held this way.
And it's very sounds very reductionist to say that that everything is a single.
Yeah, well, slide.
I'm just given what it is like, not necessarily, you know, crazy, but very relatable.
I think everybody smelled that buttered popcorn deal.
Sure. But let's go back to the concept of Tesla saying that we don't really think
we access the central core in the universe.
He doesn't know what it is, but he knows he's access.
Right. Absolutely.
So we can't get any simpler than that.
And we can't we can't get more exact, really, without any difficulty
or privileged knowledge.
So we can reduce not to just say that's the truth and that's it.
It's almost too reductionist, but it works.
Just like this method here where everything is instilled is very reductionist.
By the way, it's completely rejected by the psychology community because it works
and it works every time.
If you do it well, even with people that had severe traumatic experiences
that have been going through psychologists and whatever
psychiatrists for all their life and can't knock it.
This will knock it every time if you do it properly.
And this is I'm not trained in this, but I'm going to give an example on how well
it works, because someone approached me.
Can they how do you deal with grief?
And I said, fine, we'll we'll be very quick and we'll deal with it.
This is fine. So we haven't done this yet, but I'm going to do it here on the Sonic.
So whoever's listening, if you ever had any grief
that you still hold on to or imagined or have a feeling of,
then you consider a grievous event.
Right. Think of it and what you'll see is an image.
It could be a person in a setting, a place.
It could even be pop, buttered popcorn.
And now if you have that image, when you thought of grief is emo.
Also, you know how the emo is very much the emotion of grief will bring up an image
almost like opening a Rolodex file.
And and you might jitter between one or two images.
Let it jitter back and forth.
It might be multiple images.
Let it settle in in your mind.
And what will happen is some of those images will fade away.
You'll be left with one.
Believe it or not.
Does this work because you bring up the subject and think of an image
when you bring up the emotion of grief.
Some people have a lot of images.
That's OK. Some people, you know, just let it sit.
And they're going to fade away and you'll be left with one.
Believe it or not, one kind of goes to the top of the pile.
So it's exactly right.
And it always some people, it takes a few seconds and people, it takes a few minutes.
And when you feel like you ask them, do you have just one image now?
Yes. Now we get now we get time to get to work.
You don't have to say what it is, by the way.
OK, it's all personal.
This is all personal.
I'm doing no one has to disclose anything.
Just so you know, I'm doing this one.
You should be. OK.
Anyway. Yeah, I don't mean that sarcastically, but it works more.
It has 70 percent more effect when you're doing it.
And so you'll see. So let it settle in.
And when you get a feeling that there's just one image left, you don't have to.
This is different than regular psychology where they make you talk about it.
No, this is totally the wrong way.
This is keeping a confidential works the best.
Well, it seems like if the trouble's internal, perhaps that is where you're
keeping it internal.
But you don't have the modern psychology.
They want you to let it out, say, talk about it.
No, that's completely the wrong way to go.
It has a place.
It should be kept personal because it's going to be dealt with personal.
It has a place to vent it.
It's sort of like a chiropractor.
It's nice to sort of adjust things temporarily.
But never actually solves the situation with this method.
You never ask the person what it is.
It's irrelevant, really, because this is we're dealing with the core
part of the way the mind works, not the subject matter.
Right. And so once you settle in on an image of grief, whatever it might be,
and all the other ones have washed away, look at that image and expand it.
And let it expand.
Just order it to get bigger.
Now, whatever that image is of, it could be buttered popcorn, your stepdad,
a teacher, a bully.
Let that image just ask the image to get bigger and bigger and bigger and bigger.
And you'll notice in your mind, it starts to zoom.
You zoom in on it or it gets really big.
Everyone has a different experience with it.
It's going to be some people experience it zooming in like you zoom in on a screen.
Other people feel like it's enveloping them and filling the room.
So, you know, that's the thing is I have actually two ways
I can go with this in my mind either. That's OK.
You don't have to say it. Let me let me just go on.
Hold on. I'm going to step on you.
It's important that you don't express any personal
because I'm trying to make this more objective.
Some people will feel that it's just the image zooming in like you zoom in on a screen.
Other people feel like it's filling the room three dimensional.
Other people feel like now they're in another place
out in an open desert or field and it's filling the entire planet.
That's OK. In other words.
Remember, it's just an image that you asked for it to get bigger.
And you will compile that again with another image.
You might be, you know, again, it might look like a screen
or it might be filling the room or you might feel like you were taken to another place
and it's filling the whole universe.
It doesn't matter the same image.
OK. At one point, you asked it to expand.
Now it will stop expanding and go static in that gigantic state.
It may not be gigantic for some people.
It might just be like a 10 foot wide billboard for some people.
Other people have said that it's if I'm out in the desert and up in the ocean
and the horizon and it's still the entire sky in the universe, that's fine.
That's OK. Let it go.
It could also be just looking at a screen like you were saying,
like looking at a computer screen.
And now I've just zoomed out, but it's still on the same screen.
But I've got sure.
But some people, it stays on that scale.
Other people, it can overwhelm them.
OK, because they're actually literally taken somewhere else.
Like they feel like they've been taken out into an infinitely large space.
And now the thing is becoming infinitely large.
That's OK, too.
Just let it because it'll stop growing once it stops growing and goes static.
Now that it stopped growing and it's static, you just take a few breaths.
And is it static?
And if the answer is yes, it stopped growing.
It doesn't matter how big it is,
even if it filled the entire universe from horizon to horizon.
For some people, it has.
Once it goes static and you're sure it's static, it's not getting any bigger.
Yes, not getting any bigger.
Now tell it to get smaller.
And keep telling it to get smaller and just sit back.
So what is it doing? It's getting smaller.
It's getting whether it's what appeared to you on the screen
or whether it filled the room or it filled the entire universe.
Is it still getting smaller? Is it still getting smaller? Yes.
Is it so it could take up to a half an hour getting smaller.
You know what'll happen?
It'll get so small that it will disappear and it's out of your life.
It doesn't matter if it's the most extreme trauma.
You just wait for it.
And you can't do this on yourself because we have a survival.
John May says there's a survival mechanism built in that.
It always helps for someone to guide you through it, which makes sense.
By the way, there's another whole other level to having someone else there.
But unlike modern psychology.
Where they want you to express almost, by the way, modern psychology is a joke.
It's almost like the confessionals, the priests do.
You know what? They can eat a dick.
They can eat a bag full of dicks.
Those guys, the priests and the psychologists and psychiatrists.
So here's the thing.
Once it gets so small.
It will keep getting small until it goes into nothingness.
And it doesn't matter what level of trauma you have.
I'm talking about extreme trauma.
It will be out of your life. Why?
Because you've dealt with the image, which is the only thing the mind can store.
And how did you deal with it?
You let it take over.
And now it disappeared.
And once it disappears, it's gone.
It no longer has an effect on you.
And it works.
And you might have to repeat it if there's residue.
But it's so simple just by simply using the reductionist
idea that we only remember still images.
And how do you deal with it?
Now, there are other people that might suggest,
well, why don't you just tear it up and burn it in your mind?
It doesn't work because now you're making other excuses.
That's not how the brain works.
The brain works by taking something that's really small and expanding it
or contracting it, making it go away.
What if it happens really fast?
Like, you know, when you the rate of the rate of what? Fast what?
Well, when you said, you know, now tell it to get smaller
before you even got to the point of explaining that it would disappear.
I had already disappeared that it was that's fine.
The rate of of shrinkage, the rate of shrinkage doesn't matter.
OK, if it if it goes real fast or if it takes an hour, it doesn't matter.
As long as it will.
Now, what happens is when that image is stored in the mind,
even if you don't know it, your body starts to compensate
and build your character around it because it's bothering.
It knows it's there, even if it's unconscious.
That's why a lot of people like, why are they so messed up?
Oh, well, they were raped as a child. Oh, yeah.
And everybody accepts it. No, no, don't accept it's done.
You're over. You're here. You've healed. You're recovered.
I get rid of the thing that is affecting you.
So in other words.
It's the not dealing with this image.
Let's say this is one way to do it.
The John Mace method.
That image, even though you don't acknowledge it anymore,
it still has an effect because your mind knows it's there.
The part that you don't really use consciously, it's in the core.
You're actually destroying it at the core, really, is another way to do it.
The main you know, you're deleting it out of the main part of the system,
off the hard drive completely and making it unrecoverable.
And it's that simple.
Yes, it's that simple, just like the email work.
I'm still getting emails on people that are practicing the email with success.
And I have one recent email from someone that I've known for a while says,
finally, you're able to turn off the street light, make it go off,
you know, and it took about a year and that's fine.
So this might also take repeated times, usually two times for some people.
But it's that simple.
And it's that simple to take interest in anything.
It's just a series of images.
And just like imagine someone who's had trauma all their life,
that's really bothered. I'm talking about severe trauma.
Well, you could guess I don't need to get graphic about it.
And having it disappear in one session or two sessions,
that's a really, really powerful tool.
And one of the things that I do like to bring up and I do pride
Greek speak being about is bringing up stuff that's very pertinent,
that anyone can access and is very powerful consistently.
And I think that's one of the marks of.
Greek speak.