The sonic entity known as Ocelli and the Greek.
Sonic event 13, Ocelli and the Greek rated Y. You know, I'm not even sure why I announce that
every single time. I guess I'm forming a pattern. I'm going to have to snap that one.
Anyway, enough out of my head. Greek, how are you doing today?
Hey, okay. Yeah, we were talking about trouble brewing in the Middle East and
important part first. I don't think much is going to happen because we're well into spring,
but let's bring up the topic. Let's just get right into it.
Yeah, let's do that because obviously, I'm somebody who monitors the news and all that.
And here's what's going on. Essentially, there was a rocket fire on the place that we call Israel
at this moment. I don't know about the exact point on the map. I think that that may or may
not be debatable depending. Maybe you can explain that a little bit, but I've always had a bit of
confusion about it. But either way, allegedly, and I say allegedly, because all I have are
reports to go on, I haven't seen it with my own eyes. Someone in Lebanon who was connected to
one of the two major groups that are supposed to be Palestinian freedom fighters of sorts
had launched some rockets into Israel. Israel responded after an Iron Dome and all that.
And then counterstrikes on Gaza, on the West Bank, I think. And well, now it appears as though maybe
things are calming down. But of course, all of this is occurring during this convergence of,
oh boy, here we go. I know I'm opening up a can of worms with the Greek.
A bunch of high holidays, right? You have Easter, you have Passover, you have Ramadan,
which is a month-long thing, going on all at the same time, all converging. And of course,
this is amid troubles and people learning of a bit of unrest on the Temple Mount or
the Al-Aqsa, what is it, the Al-Aqsa Mosque, the Temple Mount, the Golden, whatever it is,
this one place, which is sacred to three different derivations of a similar religion.
Yeah, there were people being beaten that were praying and all this kind of stuff because there
was stuff going on. This allegedly set the whole thing off. And by the way, there was something
that went on not too long ago called the 11-Day War. And people are saying that perhaps this is
something that's starting. Well, it is the right time of year to start a war. But what do you think
is happening, Rick? Not much unless it's, I predict, well, this year or next year, Israel's
going to go down. And I mean it, like down, down, like no aid, no help, and they're not going to
prevail. I wouldn't even say this year or next year, but that's the next major move that's going
to be happening there. Anyway, but in terms of what's happening, yeah, the spring is to start a
war, but for what? See, the wars start for gain in the springtime, and for loss or to break things
down, they start in the fall, or the purpose of starting the war is in the fall. You know, spring
is building up, fall is breaking down, the harvest, right? So if a war—well, here's my question
immediately, is if a war were to take place that was going to be fairly sudden destruction or a
serious heavy loss for Israel, a breaking down of it, that would have to begin in the fall then?
To break down, right, right, right. Okay, no, I'm just making sure I'm tracking with what you're
saying. Which is odd. Usually the wars start in the springtime to build up, to take advantage or
gain ground or have a successful campaign. Let me just preface, there are no national enemies,
right? Okay, give me an example. The Mossad that works in Japan works with the Persian
underworld. They work very well together. In other words, Israel's best friend behind the
scenes is Iran, who is supposed to be their biggest threat. All of the leaders that call
the shots behind the scenes are all buddy-buddy, all of them. So the U.S., Russia, North Korea,
China, Iran, everybody's buddy-buddy, buddy-buddy, buddy-buddy. But publicly what they do is very
different. It's not like gang wars—well, first of all, it's nothing like we're told,
and it's not like we also hear about when there are gang wars or factions that fight.
Is it a show? Yeah, it's kind of a show. It's blood sport. People, you know, when you say that
they're all friends and thousands of people die on either side, yeah, it's a blood show. It's just a
game, right, in essence. So the missiles going from Lebanon or from Gaza, from the Palestinians
or from wherever else, it's all very well known and accepted. But the people don't know it.
Now, here's the other thing. Well, when Israel goes down, it's not going to be like a fair fight
the Israeli-powered or the dominance. And they have a dominance because of their alliance with
the U.S. mainly, okay? And that's very well known, right? All of the leaders that call the shots
behind the scenes are all buddy-buddy, all of them. So the U.S., Russia, North Korea, China,
Iran, everybody's buddy-buddy, buddy-buddy, buddy-buddy. But publicly what they do is
very different. It's not like gang wars—well, first of all, it's nothing like we're told,
and it's not like we also hear about when there are gang wars or factions that fight.
Is it a show? Yeah, it's kind of a show. It's blood sport. When you say that they're all
friends and thousands of people die on either side that are supposed to be rivals, yeah,
it's a blood show. It's just a game, right, in essence. So the missiles going from Lebanon or
from Gaza, from the Palestinians or from wherever else, it's all very well known and accepted.
But the people don't know it. Now, here's the other thing.
Well, when Israel goes down, it's not going to be like a fair fight and they took out the
Israeli-powered or the dominance. And they have a dominance because of their alliance with the U.S.
Okay. And that's very well known, right? I mean, you've heard about the congressman having dual
citizenships with Israel and this and that, right? So when Israel goes down, it's not going to be
because of a fair fight or let's say whoever attacks them prevailed. No, it's because the
people, the leadership in Israel abandoned it. And one of the things I've discussed,
I think recently, one of the Sonics recently, two or three Sonics ago, is your tell on this
is going to be when things get hot and popping on the surface and the IDF, the Israeli military has
to defend, they're going to be given orders to like stand down or move into an area where they
shouldn't be, bad strategy. So they're going to be getting like really bad orders or stand down
orders from their own superiors. And one of the results, most of the people in the military there
in the Israeli military don't know what I'm saying. So they're going to say, what the hell
is he telling us to do? We need to go here. We need to go right. Our commander is telling us
to go left. So you'll have these little mutinies and confusion. You'll also see the, what they
call the Knesset or the main body of the Israeli leadership abroad or missing, like probably
underground. And then when I say underground, it doesn't mean that you go into a spider hole
or something and stay there. When you go down to a certain point, you have access to anywhere
on earth. So underground railroad kind of thing and other things. Like I'll give you an example,
any city that has a population of a million or more, especially with a military base near the city,
the capital of the city or the city's main building, or if it's a state capital or whatever,
or the city's main buildings, court buildings, police buildings, and military are all interconnected
underground. And I know this not firsthand from working on it, but secondhand from an HV, a company
that does air conditioners, HVAC contractor. And part of their stuff was to, when you build these
underground tunnels that access buildings to each other, they need air, right?
Well, you need air circulation for sure.
Yeah. So he was doing all that and he can't talk about the details, but he says they do exist.
And usually the city centers where the city, county or whatever is, they're usually called
the dome, usually call them that building. And they always do have a dome, right? If you
listen to Jordan Maxwell or even look at architecture, a minor city, their municipal
center or main building will have a dome on it, right? The White House or the capital building
has a dome, right?
Oh, yeah. A lot of state houses have them, a bunch of things. Yeah, a dome.
And that's part of the nicknames. They call it the dome and there's tunnels from the dome
and to the dome. So if you've ever heard that. So this is not just a segue back or not.
This is sort of a segue. But just to give more of how I'm viewing it is this is going to be
very obvious. In other words, the takedown of Israel, if you know what I'm saying,
and if you're watching very closely.
Well, because here's a question quickly, because you're talking about, you know,
the leadership going underground. Okay, fine. But what do we do? Well, what if the public
doesn't observe it because of something that you brought up in an earlier sonic
due to the fact that there are clones, right?
Or doubles. Yeah. But right now, it's just if you haven't heard that, you'll be scared is
Greek. What's he talking about clones? Yes, they are. There's cloning is a very
just to throw something in here, because it's also been in the chat recently. Again,
cloning technology has always been around. I think I mentioned a few years ago, I was reading
an article on the DNA of a mummy in Egypt, right? And the outcome was that this DNA is a clone DNA.
And I told people that they said, Oh, they're cloning a mummy. I'm like, No, no, no, what
they're saying is they discovered an ancient buried corpse. That was a clone ancient times.
Exactly. Yeah. I mean, it's so hard for people to mix up what you're easy for people to mix up what
you're saying. But it's weird, because if it's a mummy, look, if something is mummified, I mean,
again, I'm trying to listen to 2500 2500 year old. Yeah. And 20 cloning is something ahead of us.
Well, yes, but you could mummify something now, right? You could mummify something from a couple
of years ago, you could end up with a mummy. But the thing is, if you're talking about something
that has been mummified and been there for 2000 years, last dynasty, yeah. This means that if it
is a clone, and it's not a fake, okay, because that that's another thing. Let's say somebody
went in there took the original and then cloned it and then put a fake mummy there. Okay. But
otherwise, yeah, yeah. Well, the whole thing is was was, you know, if there's algorithms and
search the internet, the article was written, and it was not a conspiracy theory. It was mainstream
that well, not Fox News. But it was like a science magazine kind of article. I remember that too,
and going, okay, but I didn't know what to make of it. Where it was like, well, it was Yeah,
yeah, it was pretty. Yeah, it did. The hints are out there. It's very also the same technology
they use for skin grafting, they take skin tissue, and they grow your own skin tissue.
And you go to the lab, and they scrape off the excess and they bond it to the body. And it grows
back. And there was a short newscast about some newscast in Minnesota visiting, you could just
look it up on YouTube, visiting a lab that did that. And it's basically the tissue is in these
glass jars that basically slightly agitating, slightly moving back and forth in like a saline
solution with some other nutrients and the tissue grows. It's a very simple process. It's not
technical at all. It's just that you have to have certain subtleties accounted for, right?
Well, right. And you start off with some. Now look, I had a stepfather who had a motorcycle
accident. I might have mentioned this to you like years ago, where they took skin off of like, say,
parts of them that weren't burned, because he suffered severe burns throughout his body, right?
So they grafted skin on from places that weren't burned. And it looked like literally, you know,
those cheese knives he used where he kind of glided along and it creates a very thin slice of
Okay, so it looked to me as though the scarring on the healthy parts of his skin
were removed with a cheese knife. Okay. I mean, I know it sounds ridiculous. But yeah,
that's what it looked like. And they took those pieces grew them bigger, brought them back and
grafted them on to the damaged parts of his body, right? To replace the destroyed or the dead skin.
And they went through a process of removing the dead. This all sounds very real to you,
because you've heard of this kind of thing. I'm sure it's, it's kind of barbaric. If anyone is
interested in this technology or skill level, research didn't show God, the chromotherapy,
okay, in the 20s, he would show up with his lamps, very 1000 watt light bulb with colored lenses,
the yellow, very bright yellow builds the tissue, the very bright blue is a whole chart.
restores the tissue. And they would give him burn victims that all they could do for them was
morphine, because they were going to be dead in less than a week. And after two weeks of his therapy
or three weeks, they had no scars on their body whatsoever. I have personal I have firsthand
experience with the blue light therapy with burns. And if anyone lives in a place where they get
sunburn easily, or sunburns, you know, sometimes like here's a situation where the Can you watch
the children for an afternoon? Yeah, sure. And you know, the sun is burning hot, and they're
out there for three hours, and they come inside. And then an hour later, they're all complaining,
because their skin feels like it's on fire, you know, very red sunburn. So you put them in a room,
give them some sunglasses or goggles to protect their eyes with an extremely bright blue light
for an hour. And then an hour after they leave the room, the sunburn is completely gone.
I wish I had known about that. Because I had sun poisoning and lost a bunch of skin at one point
and all kinds of stuff. Yeah, being in the sun. Well, that's why that's why we're doing this
didn't show God reality. Now, if you're using blue like LEDs, or blue light you get from the
hardware store doesn't work because it needs to be very high intensity. So these are things like,
you know, people have a medicine cabinet, you know, they invest in bandages, band aids, whatever.
This is something that requires somewhat of an investment right now, because of the way the
industry is going, it's very hard to find incandescent light bulbs. So silver sodium works
okay, it gives off radiation. But you're gonna need a very powerful, incandescent type bulb that has
a filament, right? Yeah, and very pure color lenses. You could do it with blue LEDs, but you're
it's too much UV. I had I've had success with using the LEDs with several blue colored light
bulbs that whatever you could get your hands on and you will have some success. Didn't show God
reality chromotherapy. Yeah, that's for rebuilding tissue and all that I have first hand experience
and so do you if you need it, try it. But some people that have done low intensity stuff, it
doesn't really work that much, you know, that well. But we went from that to cloning to burning
to tissue development back to the stuff going on in the Middle East. Well, yeah, well, let's go back
to that. Because what I just I thought that was a good aside. But yeah, it's gonna have to tie
together with things that I've talked about a long time ago. I have gotten, by the way,
some pretty good response from people that have reached out on the uncommon radio, uncommon
sense radio one at gmail.com, the email about Greek, I can't believe it, you know, I was listening
back in 2016, with Ocelli in the Greek or other stuff, and everything you said is coming true,
meaning the West, what you're going to see after 2018, between 2018 and 2021 and a half
is a very concerted, purposeful effort to bring the Western society down, like all your values,
your morals, your entertainment, your judicial, scientific, I went specifically through a list,
what's going to come down, right? So if you look between 2018 and 2021 and a half for the judicial
come down, the entertainment industries come down, right? Education has come down,
economics downturn, society is downturned, morality is downturned, right? It's right.
So even the promotion of the ancient goddess religion, which you mentioned briefly back then
has come to fruition, I mean, entirely, as far as I'm concerned. Well, the thing, the highlight of the
ancient goddess religion is started in the 50s. It really came on the scene really, really big.
If you know what you're looking for, you'll find it. It came on the scene really big, and it started
manifesting in the 60s with the women's lip. And then at the same time, scientifically, it was
manifesting with fertility, drugs and fertility techniques and medicine, right? And then the
civil rights movement on and on and on that led to where we are today. But one thing that I've
mentioned is that in the foreground, keep in mind that you anything you see going on in the Middle
East, whether it's a war or not, or whatever, and the West coming down is to lead to focus on the
Middle East as a world power, right? And that's how we actually got to cloning. Because I asked you,
you said, Look, you'll see the leaders go underground. And I said, Well, but would we
directly because wouldn't they put doubles out? And yes, the real people will go somewhere
underground. And maybe that's not observable from a distance, right? Because you are I,
it's okay to shoot, it's okay to kill the clone. But think about it from a psychological point of
view, you can't have a dignitary laying dead on the street with enough witnesses, right? And then
him showing up three hours later, right, like Hillary Clinton does a speech in Norway. And
four hours later, she's doing a speech in Australia. Yeah, but in a time in a time where
you have things like like going a bit crazy, why not? See, this is the thing. Why not disrupt that
and have something like that happen where literally, let's just say, theoretically,
the the current Prime Minister of Israel is reportedly killed, they have some evidence of
it, you have to do that. And then he shows up again, anyway, I'm willing to bet that the majority
of the public wouldn't even flinch at it at this point, because of their their weird cognitive
disconnect. So I'll pick up on it. So it'll be that Yahoo effect, right? But that's what I'm
saying. Like, all of a sudden, if that happened, okay, you and I would say, Look, we just saw this
guy dead, because we might observe it from a distance. Or maybe you wouldn't, because you
don't watch this stuff. But I do. And a lot of other people do. And some of us would say, Hey,
there's a problem here. There's a discontinuity in what's happening, because a dead man just gave a
speech. And I think the majority of people in the world, the overwhelming majority, in fact,
would not flinch at that and would just Oh, well, that must have been wrong the first time,
even though we saw it happen on live TV. But it's all
But look, if you're going to spend time anytime at all discontinuities, you'll never have time
to do anything else. Well, that's the thing, because everything is discontinued. Here,
give you an example. Someone gave me a video, which I didn't watch. It was an analyst,
an economist, and he was quite serious. He says, Well, if money is fake, why is debt real?
I didn't watch the video, but that's a fair question. Because, well, legally, every well,
here's the thing in every court, the amount is never disputed. It's whether you owe it or not,
and then after the trial, which is summed up that you owe it, then a separate completely
separate action is a judge order to pay that much. Well, right, which has nothing. It's whether
you have a contract or not. That's why, well, every lawsuit, every headline lawsuit, like here's
the easily observable way, right? You put it your way. But I would say if you're looking at any
lawsuit where there's some kind of damage, first, they figure out if there's a damage. And if this
individual who was brought before the court, or if this group or the corporation doesn't matter,
if this defendant is liable for this, that's the first determination. The next thing is,
well, let's figure out what we're going to actually give to the person who has won here, right? I mean,
that's the simplest way to look at it, isn't it? Yeah, the amounts, well, they cannot discuss
amounts while it's in an active court case, because there is no money, no way to pay it.
It's always done afterwards. Unless you're like a TV, you're watching something on TV, but-
Well, the other thing is satisfaction too, because it's not just necessarily money. Sometimes it's,
well, I want an apology. I want a statement. I'll settle for this. I'll settle for,
you'll also agree in the future to never do this again. Stuff like that also comes into consideration,
but it's always after you determine who's actually responsible, liable, whatever.
So that's the way that works, right? Sort of, because there's a lot of metric,
there's a lot of language you have to cut through real quick. A court is where two adversaries meet
to come to a decision that's going to finalize their adversarial actions, so they don't have
to duke it out or kill each other, right? It's a place where they could go where there's non-violent
and they basically negotiate or find culpability, so the issue could be settled, right? That's all
a court is, so that's why you have two adversaries show up with rackets and a yellow ball. It's
called a tennis court, right? Golf course is a course, but you have courts in sports, adversaries
and for a winning position. Orange ball is a basketball court, but yeah.
It's kind of like when I hear people say, I went to the doctor.
You went to a doctor. I didn't know there was the doctor, like the doctor. Have you ever heard of
the doctor? Who is the doctor that everyone's going to? That is odd because you are going to
a doctor. Yeah, I called the police. Oh, really? Okay. These are metrics in language. You listen
to people. You know how they say listen more and talk less, but most people don't know what that
means. What it does is it allows you to assess what's going on and the quality of the,
should we say dialogue? Here's the thing. There's something people don't like,
the normies, they think this is passive aggressive, but if you go into a situation
and you don't take, let's say a group of people, whether it's work or play or whatever, even a
sonic, let's say, but this is just you and I, who is a group. If you don't take control,
guess what? It's out of control because you see, even the, very often someone who's supposed to
be leading the group doesn't know what the hell they're talking about, right? Right.
So whoever is listening, if someone's listening, that could rub two gray cells together. He's
going to walk away. What's the takeaway? I listened to this for an hour. I didn't get
anything out of it. So I tell people, whenever you get into a situation, take, in business,
this works very well. It doesn't mean you're obvious about it, but just make sure that
think of it on a skill level. You could never do it starting out, but it takes practice.
Think of it on a skill level. You're on a powered boat, right? It has a keel and all that. It has a
steer it and a rudder. Like you're walking up to the bridge of an airplane or a boat and you're
holding onto the rudder and the power, basically. That's what I mean by taking control. It doesn't
mean you're going to rock the boat, right? Well, right. I always look at it as steering
a conversation, which is what I often do in order to direct it so that it is a bit more coherent,
gets to the point, etc., and also to assure that we don't leave things out.
But on occasion, I also like to shake that dynamic a little so that it doesn't become
a boring sort of pattern. Well, give an example. If you start to measure the metrics that you hear
around you, they're shown to you also. Look at the billboards where it's on the side of a bus or
billboard on the street and it doesn't make any sense at all. For example,
years ago, there was a credit union that opened up here in Tucson. It says,
we lend money. Right away, I drove by. I got home. I called the controller of currency
and I said, you have a bank, a national association doing business as a bank
that has a billboard on this street. I got the billboard number. You know,
they all have numbers on them, right? Right. They're all numbered. Yeah.
Yeah. And they said that they're lending money and I think there's a problem with accuracy here.
It was a message, actually. They bumped me up to someone and said he's away from his desk.
If you're a bar member or an attorney, you have to give a certain amount of hours to the public
every year. Are you aware of that? Yeah.
I think they still have it going. Yeah.
Okay. Free time or whatever. Okay. Well, so they bumped me up to someone like that at the
controller of currency in Arizona. So, I left a very well thought out message. I thought of it
immediately as I called. I was trying to be very accurate. Within two days, that billboard was
down. They usually stay up for a week or two or three or a month, right? In two days, it was
painted white or covered with white paper. Right. Right. Sorry, Buster. Buster just chimed in. I
apologize. Oh, that's fine. Yeah, go ahead. Yeah. Another example of taking control of a
situation instead of just looking at it. And I'm not saying being... I was basically not snitching
on the bank. I was basically trying to do a public service because the last thing you want
the public to be misled that banks lend money. Right. An inaccurate statement is being shared
with the public. So, you were in the public's interest. Yeah. Right. There's personal interests
as well. When I was out in LA, I was doing a water project and I needed some parts. So,
we went to a hardware store. And it was around 10 a.m. on a weekday. And there was a line
from the cashier area going out to the front door and bending around the front door
to where the point of sales to the paint department. I'm like, wow, 30 people online to
check out. And then I went to the counter and there was five or 10 people on that counter,
another counter, five or 10 people waiting. And I'm like, oh, man, I really need to get what I
need to get here. But it's insane. Right. So, I peered all the way into the back in the stock room
and there's a clerk with a vest on, the corporate vest. He was loading some things.
I said, hey, you, you, you, yeah, you back there. Come here. I need this, this and that.
And he says, OK. And he got everything ready. I said, yo, don't leave me. Take me to the register.
Take me to the register. And he took me to the register, rang me up.
And I was out of there. And it was a neighborhood, Ukrainian neighborhood. I got some stuffed
cabbage, beef and rice stuffed cabbage. And as we had lunch and as I was leaving, one of the ladies
that had a dog and a small dog in her bag was just leaving. She was like midway online. And I
pointed out to the person I was with, remember the lady with the dog in her bag? She's leaving
the hardware store now. We went in, left, got what we needed, had lunch, drove by the hardware store
again, and she's just leaving the hardware store right now. How's that for time? You see?
Yeah, that's pretty wild.
Taking control.
Yeah. Wow.
So, but you can't, you have to do it like you own the place, though. Right? So, when I was calling,
just to go back, when I was calling out to the clerk all the way in the back, stalking,
it was as if I owned the place. Not like, oh, excuse me. No, please. No. It was, hey, you,
need you here right now. And just like, you know, you said you worked in retail and stuff when you
have an authoritative position. It's a battlefield, right? So, if you're a call, let's say, an
employee, you don't ask them, please come here. You tell them to come here. I need you, right?
So, you have to understand, you know, what energy you put out also. I just wanted to put that out
because it's very important. And this, by the way, can also be done in a courtroom when you're
dealing with these idiots, you know, the legal society. But you have to do it in a way that
they find acceptable because they will accept a lot if you know their language and their tactics.
One of the things, by the way, in a courtroom is any time the prosecutor opens his mouth,
you object. And literally. Any time, well, the, any time, well, not the prosecutor,
any, your opponent, or when they finish a sentence, just before they finish a sentence,
say objection. It doesn't matter if you're going to say objection 300 times.
Just so it goes on the record and there's someone there that, because what they use against you
is that real trashy stuff. Well, you know, you didn't object, right? Or you agreed to it. So,
you object to everything they say. Good morning, I object. Why is it, how can it be a good morning
if I'm in here with your ugly ass, right? So, anyway, these are things that are so simple.
So, I don't know about takeaways, but hey, speaking of takeaways, people have been investing
the chat, in the chat, in the ONG chat. By the way, wait, wait, wait. Before we go away from
what's going on in the Middle East, it's, can I say it's a nothing burger? Really,
completely nothing on this, you think? It's more than typical. It's more than the typical
stuff that you see, right? It looks like it's more than typical, but yeah, go ahead.
If I'm incorrect in the assessment, it'll go into what we just talked about a few months ago.
You know, a full out, right? Against Israel. Right. Here's one way to see when this is going
to happen with Israel, by the way. Where are all the dignitaries? You know, Israel,
you know, countries that have prime ministers, they still have a president. Every country that
has a credit-based economy has a president, right? In America, a lot of countries just,
that are very federalist, just happen to make the president, the chief executive officer,
the one to look at. But Israel is supposedly run by a prime minister, but they also have a
president, right? There's a president in the parliament, right? There's a president in
whatever, there's a president in North Korea, there's a president, right? Because you, if you
have a credit-based economy, it's all based on drafts and bills. You need an executive signer,
right? So the president of Israel, which is not talked about, there's a president of Russia,
right? Anyway, they all have presidents and look at, look where he, what he's doing. So if he's
in Belgium, right? And Netanyahu's in France, or I doubt it'd be in France, but you see,
and if this guy is here, the head judge is there, they're all out of the country,
right? And they just appointed some like a 32-year-old weak-chin guy as the head of the
military, right? You know, like someone deliberately has no experience, it looks like,
right? Like they're telling you, look, we're putting someone here that has no experience,
guess what? It's next, right? They do that very often, right? Like when they put Biden here,
you know, they're trying to tell you, like, you guys are really dumb. We're making it so obvious,
and you still don't get it, right? But anyway, if you put somebody who has no idea what they're
doing in charge, then you're obviously setting things up for failure. Well, it's so obvious
that they have no, that they're not, yeah, it's just kind of like when Caligula brought a donkey
into the Senate, and he made him a senator kind of thing, because the Senate wasn't quite getting
it. But either way, look at what the itinerary for the dignitaries in Israel are. If you start
to see them all being reported all over, and you have a very weak military leadership,
and this is happening, what you brought up, you know, the stuff going on right now.
Yeah, here we go. This is it. So this is the beginnings, this is like the groundwork,
if you will, for what's coming next, but it's not significant in and of itself, maybe.
I think it's going to be in an odd time, because when they did the seven day war,
six day war, that was in Yom Kippur, that was in seventh month, right? The Yom Kippur war,
which by the way, you know, was very heavy Russian, that was,
how do you say it? Let's just say that war was based, a lot of those planes, you know,
the MiGs and all that, they were not Egyptian pilots, they were Russian pilots, aces,
because one of the things was to take out the Dimona nuclear power plant,
right? And they didn't want to show the Russians doing it, right? Because they didn't want overt,
but at the time, Israel already had a few dozen nukes, they were pushing them around in taxicabs
and train cars and trucks and had them on, you know, right? Now, I said this several times
regarding, you know, what what nuclear status they had at the time. See, some people have tried
to say part of the Cold War, in other words, six day war was part of the Cold War. Right? I mean,
and they did have nukes, they weren't going to use them then, but they did have them.
There, there, there's been some odd accusations about what Egypt was thinking about doing.
But but or what they were thinking about doing with Egypt at that time. And only very recently,
have people talked about that. But it's very incongruous with the normal story about the
six day war. But that's why I found it odd that they're referencing this thing they called the
11 day war not long ago. Which war with Lebanon, right? Yeah, again, right. Yeah. Again, with
Lebanon. See, but that's why I thought it was significant. Because, you know, they're saying,
look, it's not the Lebanese government or the Lebanese military that's doing this. But it's
either. What is it Hamas? And then the other? Oh, wow, I can't remember the name of the other one.
But the two major, you know what I'm talking about? Hezbollah, Hezbollah. Thank you. So it's,
you know, it's either one of them that is doing this, but they were being very specific about
which one. And, and all that. So they struck back on the territory. And of course, the government
of Lebanon came out and said, we were not we didn't do this. We didn't do this. People did
this from our territory, but we didn't do it. And they're all they're all the power group that you
mentioned may or may not be in it, the Hezbollah and Hamas, right. But those that are above them,
are absolute friends with Israeli, right? Everybody's a buddy, buddy, everyone.
There are some countries that don't want to be a part of it, but they're still
not adversarial. How many times have I said this in the past 20 years, there are no national
adversaries at period, everyone is one big behind the scenes, all of the nations, when I say nations,
are one big happy group. And one of your main site, the two main signs are 911. No one came out,
no country came out. And you could say the moon landings to to a certain degree.
No one came out and said the Americans are fake, you know, did this is what really happened. And
the other one was the the panic, the pandemic thing. Everyone was in all the nations were
in lockstep, not a one protested. Right? So right, except China didn't want to be blamed. But other
than that, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, there was some of the, the one, the ones that didn't want to do
like this is so obviously not, not a pandemic that we don't want to put a stain on our reputation by
going along with it, really. But they're all Yeah, I think I've talked enough about viruses
and disease since the 1980s. And I haven't changed what I'm saying. It's just added to it a little
bit more. Actually, I'm taking away from it, because in the 80s, I was very vocal about it.
But unless you see as long as you have running water and a steady food supply, you're not going
to have a pandemic period. Unless it's unless it's a unless it's a real pandemic, like the
Spanish flu, or the what's the American Army flu. And no one experienced anything like that. So
well, that leads to a logical discussion about what is always brought up, you know, especially by
people like myself who object to the concept of vaccinations as they are being sold to people
right now, right? Is they always, you know, the typical argument is, well, it's the vaccines that
put an end to various diseases. And I'm like, No, no, what put an end they read? Yeah, there was
the you know, when the biggest anti vax push was, believe it or not, in history, you could look this
up 1880s. Okay, they killed a lot of people with the vaccine, right? It's, it's, it's a particular
group that took power that's doing this. It was official, well, official within the medical
community paperwork by the late 1950s, that their immunization is not a rat, it can't be done.
There's no such thing as immunization other than natural immunity. But in other words, you cannot
give anyone anything, injection pill, inoculation, anything that will improve their immunity other
than hygiene and diet, right? This was in the established in the conventional paperwork.
By the I think it was 1958. There was a convention on that. And he said, Oh, there's no more
vaccines. That's it. Well, in the 1880s, I think what they were doing was doing these limited
exposures, where they were exposing people to some part of the disease, but not a full blown
exposure to get sick so that their immunity could deal with it. That's what I thought the concept
was. Well, it doesn't work that way. Because in order to get the disease, you have to be induced,
you have body has to create it. And if you do have something that enters the body, it there's
it's not an immune system. It's an elimination system. Can your body eliminate it, there actually
is no immunity. immune system was something I'm not harping on you for using that term. But it
is a metric, by the way. In other words, there is no immune system in the body. Because if you look
at all of the immune functions that they state under the immune genre, those are not immunity
functions, not a one. All those functions are eliminated functions. Well, right, because an
antibody literally goes in to get rid of something that's in there. So there you go. And
then get it through the ductwork and organs to get it out of the body by induction again. Well,
but the thing was, they were crudely introducing this into the body. And I do say introducing,
because what they were doing is literally cutting people at certain points, right? And scabs of
corpses and things under it. Yeah. And then putting some infected tissue in Yeah, an open wound. That
was good. It was the end of the Victoria era where they were telling people it was called corpse
medicine, where they would take corpses and dehydrate them. And little pieces of the
corpses we would either be coated in chocolate, or sugar and given to people for as a health
promoter. Yeah, that was you could look this up. I think I brought it up with the old ong before.
Yeah, I don't. Yeah. And you could find it. Well, when you put in corpse medicine,
they direct you now towards autopsies. Yeah, they show you about how it was illegal to,
to obtain corpses, but somehow, the medical studies would get ahold of them. And sometimes
people were literally stealing dead bodies. And they go into all that with you if you ask for
corpse medicine, right? Yeah. But if you look at Victorian era, corpses as medicine, you get savvy,
you'll find it and it's pretty nasty. Now that's this is very well known. Okay. This is 150 years
ago or so this practice was have very heavily promoted by who what kind of a sick mind?
You know, I've looked at societies from hundreds of years back to 1000s of years back. And I
on the surface with any convention, I've never seen anything that sick and disturbing, right?
Well, right. But, you know, some people found it completely sacrilegious to study a dead body at
all. That was, I mean, I learned that with through the, you know, medical autopsy textbooks, right?
Where they presented this history, and I don't know if it was a true history or not. But the
way it was presented was, it was all about, you know, look, medical schools were kind of allowed,
but not really legally supposed to be getting ahold of these bodies, unless they were donated
by the person while they were still alive, pretty much, you know, what sort of themselves? Yeah.
Well, now it's about synthesizing, right? You don't need the body, you make it synthetics,
and they would be just as bad. Right? That's what people are saying these MNR, MNRA shots and all
that. I said, that's just a revival. I've never really gotten into it. Unless there's a call for
it. But since World War One, it was all about making synthetics, right? synthetic ink, synthetic
oil, right? All these things, instead of getting them from nature directly, what the MNRA injections
are, and the graphene and all that stuff, people aren't putting it together, because they
are still drinking the Kool-Aid. Those are they're synthesizing corpse medicine,
basically, right? That's why people are getting sick and dying. But here's the thing, there,
there is no immune system, there is no inoculation or vaccine. So it cracks me up is you have the
alternative idiots. By the way, if you know anyone who has a family member who's a doctor,
mom, usually not mom, dad, they won't say but brother, sister.
They'll usually say about, I'll talk about doctors. Yeah, my sister is a doctor, someone
will say this happened recently. Right? She's smart. And she goes, No, she's an idiot. Right?
I ran into someone recently, again, and he says, Yeah, my brother is a doctor. Is he smart? No,
he's he's a dummy ass. I'm like, so. So if you have any relatives that are in the medical field,
and I, they're dumb asses, guys. And you know that. So anyway, it's it's one of these things,
because they really, really have to beat you up. You don't have to be a dumb ass to be in the
medical field. Absolutely. Because it is rigorous. And it's not bad to go through it if you can do it
quickly. But to stay within convention with it. Yeah, you're a dumb ass. Because obviously,
what you're doing is fictional, you know, like an attorney, if I know people who are getting
attorneys, is he smart? No, he's a dumb ass. Well, but just like I said, with the news,
and you said with the news, where we talked about, you know, there's this TV show with the news,
they don't fabricate things completely out of thin air. They use things and twist it around. So
there's real information that is in there. Even with the medical practice, right? There is some
information. In other words, you know what it really is? It's the, the equipment for the practice.
Here's the thing, when society starts to downturn, which is not yet, it's won't be for till the end
of this decade. You're going to need someone to take on, if let's say your neighborhood,
where you live right now, let's say it's suburban, not rural, where you don't have any neighbors.
If you were enclosed, or it wasn't safe to go a mile away, you would have to get to know the
people that live immediately around you and get to know what they're good at doing. Hopefully,
they're not good at bullshitting, because that's not going to go very far. What I mean is, oh,
he's good with cars. So he's going to fix he's mechanical, right? He's good with cooking. So
he's going to make our meals or advise us on food. And this guy's good with fixing the body, right?
So if you need some minor, someone needs a medical emergency, what they call it, right?
Right. You go to him. Now, here's the thing. You can go into a neighborhood, and you could just
survey around. There's usually someone that takes the position of a mayor, right? The go-to guy on
the block or whatever. And he'll tell you, this guy's really good with cars. Or this guy's good
with construction, right? Or this guy is good with plants and garden, but ask him who's good
with fixing the human body. We don't know. I'm not talking about going to the hospital or the
doctor, right? Right. Is there anyone that you know in your neighborhood that would, if you had
something you couldn't handle in an emergency, let's say in a car accident or something that
could hit, do you see where I'm going with this? Or how about someone that's, he's good with cars,
he's good with plants, he's good. You got anyone who could pull a tooth who knows how to do it
safely so you don't get jaundice or something? Hepatitis, right? Do you see where I'm going with
this? Yes. Very few. Where do they say, oh, no, you got to go to the dentist. Like there's one,
you know, the dentist. You mean a dentist, not the dentist, right? A doc. Do you see what's going
on here? There's a tremendous need for that. So when you, just to tie this back to what you were
saying earlier, what they have are the toys and the tools that you need, usually, right?
Not the practices. I can give many examples. A quick one would be the emergency room. They
have people waiting in an emergency room, which is deliberate, I believe. I believe that on the
upper end they do know how the body works. For example, when someone is of health, good health,
good circulation and vitality, if a tooth is knocked out, if you put it back into the socket
immediately, it usually, it can take. Have you heard of that happening? Absolutely. It'll take
hold again. Yes. It'll take hold again. Okay. But if you go to the emergency room with it,
they'll have you sitting there for three, four hours and it won't take because the
periodontal ligament will retract. The gum will retract. The gingival line will
recede. You'll have a mucus plug build. Right. The hole begins to take care of itself. Yeah.
So that it basically tries to seal itself back up. It changes form. It will not accept it.
Right. Yeah. It will not accept the socket. We'll start changing form. The periodontal ligament,
the tooth sits on, it's like a shock absorber. Okay. So when you, someone is in an emergency
situation, okay. Just like a wound, a laceration. If you make that tight or tighten it up and line
up the, line it up how it should be like doing wallpaper, right? The seams and it's clean.
You don't always have to wash a wound, but if it's clean, you make it really tight and you go
through a procedure of very tight for 15 minutes, a few minutes to let circulate and keep that going
for a few hours and then very firm for the next few days, you guess what? It'll be completely
healed in a few days where normally it would take weeks with sutures. Sutures are not needed. Those
are a very recent thing. Well, look, on occasion, they can be helpful, but majority of situations
where people, Oh, you need stitches. You need stitches. I have taken care of that kind of
stuff myself and just said, look, you know, basically what I was taught about it was to
call it a butterfly stitch, which is all you're doing really is aligning the wound. Like you said,
make sure it's clean. You know, make sure that you don't have like hair going inside of it.
This kind of thing, depending on where it is on the body, you put it back together and it will
repair itself if you allow it to. Well, the way, well, actually you don't, what you need to do,
this is the, this is the trick. I did this on the back of Frankie's head once. Frankie's my
young child. It has to be tight, but it has to be tight. It has to have pressure. It does have
to have a lot of pressure. Well, a lot, a lot of pressure. And the reason the right amount of
pressure, the right amount of pressure, because too much is too much, but it has to be. It's not,
it's not just kind of, you know, loosely, you can't loosely put it back together. It won't set.
No, it depends on where it is. If it's on a flat surface, like the face or the head,
you, when you do bandage it, you want to implement, you have something in a block,
like a blocking, literally a blocking, a box of cigarettes filled with sand. So they're firm
and heavy. And you tie that really, really tight. So tight that it's, you can only take 15 minutes
of it. And then at 15 minutes, you loosen the bandage and then make it really, really tight.
What you want to do is put a negative pressure because what happens is when there's an injury,
when the interstitial spaces, which are the very tight spaces between the cells, decide to fill
the lymphatic fluid, it will block all of the, what people call the stem cell technology that
rebuilds, you know, the body, right? Your body develops that naturally, new cells to close it up
if there's any swelling. So if you have a negative swelling, meaning if you go the other way,
where it's completely, completely even tighter than it would be normal, the area is under
compression, extreme compression. The healing process, especially the induction, the recreation,
because the cells are not really coming from somewhere else, right?
Well, I've done this.
There's no place in the body that says add new cells here.
Yeah, to give somebody a really basic relatable illustration, I used a sealed deck of playing
cards and an ace of spades to accomplish this.
Okay, there you go.
But this technique, you need to mention that. What I mean is when you're explaining this,
it's good to mention it, everything that's needed, like line up all your ducks in a row. Because if
you tell most people, for example, not just you, but anyone, you just need to put it together and
wrap it, they don't get the idea that there's an exception here, that this is something extra
that has to be considered. I don't know if anyone rides a bike and there's a patch kit,
you can patch your inner tube, right? You put some glue on it and you put the patch.
One of the most important parts is it has a little piece of sandpaper. If you don't roughen up that
rubber before you put the glue, the patch will just peel off. You need something for it to key
and bite. In other words, I give it as an example because there's a misnomer, which I see in
emergency medicine, is they have people sit there and wait, and when they do treat them,
they have no regard for the compression aspect at all. You'll have someone with an open wound
and they'll have them sit with it and then they'll irrigate it. They'll wash it out and
stitch it up and just go away. By the way, every time they suture it, it's a new wound.
Every stitch they put through there is a new wound.
Well, of course, you're puncturing the skin.
You're puncturing the skin. Of course, it's a new wound. You're putting the needle through.
Right, so suturing is never acceptable. I can't see a situation where it is because you have
situations now where you can bond to the skin and literally, just like you have eyelets on a
shoe for shoelaces, you can bond eyelets around the wound and use something to pull it closed
together that way. There was a movie called Young Frankenstein, and they had a zipper in his neck.
I don't know if you remember that film.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay, no.
There was a zipper, okay? I always use that as a reference because there's so many techniques.
Here's the thing. Every field is completely wide open. Even nuclear energy is completely wide
open. It doesn't work. There's no such thing. But there's a way to use the string, actually.
It's very interesting. You just put it... I don't know. Maybe that went by really quickly,
but the eyelets idea... Yeah, basically, if you create an adhesive on either side of the wound...
Crazy glue.
Still... Well, that's the easiest thing.
Cryoacrylic glue, yeah. These things can be...
In a pinch, you can use crazy glue, though. You can actually use that if you need to in a pinch.
Yeah, there are people in the medical profession I do speak with, long conversations with,
and I keep bringing up what they can do that's new, and very often they shy away from it because
they would be dealt with harshly, right?
Well, the idiocy that they use there, by the way, I just want to point out something because
I saw this only a couple of years ago, is they take that glue concept, which somebody explained
to them at some point, and they misuse it because they'll turn around and try to glue the wound
together, you know? And I go, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Right, but they don't... No, you can do that, but the thing is...
You can, but that's not the wisest way to do it. What you just pointed out...
No, because the glue will act as a bond breaker and it will not heal.
Right, so that's the problem.
So, if you literally just imagine an open wound and you put just glue on either side,
you glue it together, that's great, but it's not going to heal because it doesn't allow the bonding.
Yeah, sorry, go ahead.
The point without turning into... No, it's fine, don't be sorry. The takeaway with this
is that there is no cohesive, single narrative that people are aware of that
when the body is breached or injured, even internally, that vacuum is lost,
there's swelling, and that's what prevents rapid healing, and how rapid the healing could be,
24 hours, 72 hours. Any injury, for example, that I've ever treated myself or anyone else,
if it's not 90% or 95% completely healed in three days, it doesn't matter what it is.
We didn't do something right.
Okay, we're talking about severe stuff that would be more than emergency medicine.
And here's my bragging thing. One day, from coaching women in cycling, when you coach in
cycling, you get that fateful call. That fateful call is, you know, who can you call, right?
You get a call, and this is so-and-so hospital. So-and-so is here in ICU,
right? You know, intensive care unit. That's a fateful call. You're like, oh my gosh, right?
Well, I have had gone into ICU, and the next day, that person was home. Within 24, let's say 36
hours. When you go to ICU, you're in there for a day or two, or maybe less, or sometimes more,
and they move you to a hospital bed for no less than three, four days, always. They're not going
to let you go. In this case, I went over there, I did my little thing that I've talked about,
which we will probably do something more about how to treat. It's all about compression.
And the head of the hospital, which I could give the giveaway, he was pretty famous when...
Anyway, he looked at me, and he says, I need you here. I need you here in the hospital. I said,
no, no, no, no. This is like, you know, I didn't tell him it's the devil's playground.
But he had to, when I was demanding this person leave the hospital, because they were so much
better, they didn't need to be there, they all freaked out. I said, I need to speak to the head
of the hospital. And he came and checked it all out. And he says, yeah, this person can go home.
And it all had to do with what I'm talking about is restore the body's vacuum
and prevent swelling. And the way that's done is you could be creative with it.
So how do you, when you have something that has a vacuum and it loses vacuum,
how do you restore the vacuum? It doesn't have to be just squeezing, but typically is.
So here's the thing. When they don't know what they're, no, they don't know what they're doing.
They don't. And those that do leave the profession. Here's the point. The point is,
the field is completely wide open. And it's not like there's some imaginary research that needs
to be done to develop a new way. They just need to acknowledge how the body really works. It's
internal biological vacuum and nothing goes through any tissue. It's all by induction.
Right. When you use that as a premise, then use your do your research. And it is so simple.
It's like making mashed potatoes or boiling eggs. It's so what's the complicated or making toast?
Actually, toast can be complicated for some people, by the way, because the toaster has
to be working very well. It's so simple. Right. And what you do, it's I have a dentist acquaintance
when I want to get dental work done, I'll call him up and he'll say, Oh, yeah, okay. I'm playing
basketball on Thursday night. And I'll meet you at the office at 830. How's that? I'm like, great.
I'll see you then. Right. And he has dental when he has extra dental equipment and stuff. He'll
put a bag of sizes. Can you use these? Right. So because so in other words, if the society went
down, the Greek is your dentist, right? You get it. I get it. And other stuff. Yeah. Other things.
So the thing is, there's a big shortage in this. But the amount of research that needs to be done
is no and minimal. What I'm trying to say, I brought up the dentist is this. When I bring this
up to him, I don't really understand what you're saying. It doesn't sound wrong. I can't say it's
right because I don't have experience. Listen, do you ever notice that sometimes, you know,
when you go to a dentist, not just for teeth, you know, the gum needs to be cut open to remove
something. Right. If someone has a tumor in their mouth, usually go to a dentist. They could go to
a dentist to have removed. Right. And I said, do you notice how wet tissue in the mouth heals
extremely fast? Yeah, it does. You know, if you if you've known anyone who's had a bad cut on
their tongue or the inside of their mouth in two or three days, it's it's pretty much healed up
90 percent. Right. Usually we're not talking about anything that's, quote unquote, infection.
Yeah. So that principle is demonstrated where you have wet tissue in the mouth.
You know what? You see what's going on, right? Yes. Yes. Anyway. Yeah. This is the field is
wide open. And I've I've been I've gone ad nauseum. I've spoken for very, very long periods
at length with people in the medical field and people not on the medical field. And still,
it's not enough to inspire a group of people to get together and say, hey,
you know, let's get this together and get this information out. You know, there is plenty.
If you want the best medical, let's say, from an academic or a literary point of view,
try to get a nurse's handbook pre 1899. Well, try is the operative word. There might be something
online. I think I had success finding one years ago. Either I didn't save it or I can't find it
anymore. You have a handbook pre 1899. Sorry, go ahead. Oh, no, I was just saying you had one at
one point, but I haven't seen it. There was a link for it, I think, on archive.org, where they
had it saved. Yeah. Yeah. No. And I don't I don't see it on the shelf here. But I have access to
it. But the thing is, I don't like to volunteer things that I have, because if I get requests,
then I'm obliged to scan it. Right. You know what I mean? I want to make less work for myself.
Of course, because I'm up to my eyebrows and stuff. So but the whole thing is, you know,
this is not I'm not the only one that that has this. There's many other ways to get one and just
put your eyes and ears out for it. But everything that was known could have been known by the late
1800s, by the way, even nuclear stuff and high technology and all this other stuff. The vacuum
tubes, by the way, can handle more current than any transistor. So the transistor, right, is just
a different form of the same concept of the semiconductor. So it's, you know, so here's
the other thing. We didn't go back to the chat. I wanted to bring this up because there was some
some stuff about tattoos and some requests about what do we do or how do we do or what's you know,
what's going on. And one thing that I mentioned is, to keep it short on this end of it,
there's going to come a time in history that's to come that biblical what's biblical law is
going to be implemented as worldwide law, and it's going to be very harsh. Okay.
Mm hmm. So one of the things that that are in there is that piercing and marking skin.
Now, the interesting thing about piercings is they tend to heal if you don't maintain it. Right.
Right. But the marking of skin is is not is doesn't really it does fade. It can't fade.
So there is a concern from people that I've spoken. Some people have taken
what I've said seriously and had tattoo removals from going to there will be a time where I don't
know if everyone's going to be asked to take off their clothes and investigated for tattoos. That
is possible in certain cases. But there are many people that wear them prominently. Right.
And they are to be removed. Now, what that means is to wear. Well, I can't be specific enough. But
the in the ordinance is to be removed outside of your society. Okay. So because they had a border
in an area. So you let's say you're in Israel with a tattoo as you can't come to Israel. You
got to stay in Lebanon or Egypt. Right. But my my question here is, if the entire world is under
this law, where do they remove you to the moon? There's a hotel on the moon. Unless they unless
they actually colonize Mars. Right. Where are you going? Yeah. Right. You're not going. So you're
but there's no reason to fear this, because then that means, you know, you're going to have to be
everyone's going to have to be inspected. But keep this in mind. Right. Just this is a moral reversal.
Like years ago, for example, if you were in a city and you were openly gay, you were probably killed
within a certain amount of time. Right. Usually, not always like places like New York, not really,
or maybe whatever, but usually you were hunted down eventually. Right. And it was a shameful
death. Right. So now you have a reversal of that, where you have people that are openly gay are
praised. Right. So to have so get used to these moral reversals. So you have this thing where
everyone says, Oh, I think I'm going to get this. I really like this. The flavor of this milkshake,
I'm going to get it tattooed on my arm. Right. That's how ridiculous it's gotten. Right. Oh,
I really like this song. I'm going to get this tattooed on my arm, the lyrics to that song. I
actually heard someone saying that once I was waiting somewhere. Right. So this is how trivial
it is. So they can have a reversal. Right. Okay. So the concern of having them removed the laser
tat thing removal is, is probably the best way better than chemical than the old way is to cut
it out. Right. Right. And pieces or the whole thing and have it grafted. Okay, the laser thing
I've, I have secondhand experience with someone who had that done with a tattoo on their leg,
a small one. It took two or three months with several appointments, and it was a red and green.
And it was completely removed. And I think they charge you $1 per pulse. Well, here's the thing,
I've investigated not deeply technical manuals, but it's a post. It's not the laser that removes
it alone. It's the pulse of the laser. Okay. So you need something that delivers a high energy
pulse, which is something like there's a ring ring maker or something. It's a post arc welder.
You can get them for 200 bucks. It's the power supply, the pedal, the frequency adjustment and
all that. And then you get a laser figure out the nanometer wavelength that you need. Usually it's
not going to be visible to the eye. So if you put it on the skin and it's red or green, it's not
the right laser. So you put the two together, the post arc welder with the laser, obviously the
post arc, you're going to have to change the voltage, right? You transformer. This stuff is,
you know, very rudimentary for if you're not afraid or intimidated by working with electronics,
you can learn it very, very quickly, right? You put the two together for less than 500 bucks,
you use the damn thing, and you build a nice hard case for it, right? So the next person in the
chat that might want one, you ship it to them. Hopefully they're not in New Zealand, right?
Because shipping anything to New Zealand is absurd, right? Anything that's not an envelope.
Australia too.
Right. Yeah, Australia is a little better, but yeah, yeah. Okay. So this is something,
there's equipment that's done that way. They ship it to you, you leave a deposit, right?
And you use it and then you ship it back to the company, right? You've heard of that. I mean,
I can't give too many specifics. I don't recall. I've never done it, but I hear it very often.
We ship it to you. It's like renting a tool, but instead of going down to the store
that in the neighborhood, it's done through the mail. So if you have a concerned, let's say a
quote, I don't like to use the word community, but let's say a community, let's say specifically in
the chat or whatever that is concerned about this, someone needs to get back in the days,
the smart, when you, how smart someone was, was how many pencil, sharp pencils they had in their
pocket protector, right? Right. I suppose. You know, like the nerd. Yeah. They had the pocket
protector and lots of, they had a lead pencil, a pen, right. It's a slide rule. Right. Right.
Okay. Right. The nerds, right. They lean over all the stuff falls out of their pocket. Okay.
So you need someone that has at least two or three sharpened pencils in their pocket to put this
together. I can do it, but I'm not, I'm up to my eyebrows with projects like that, technical
projects, which I could get into. And I think the project that I'm mainly focused on, I've many
people, well, some people even, I know that someone that listens to us has speakers that I've
built for them and modified and other people I've heard demos, but moving basically a coherent loud
speaker, the first and only coherent loud speaker in the world where you play it and it sounds like
music, which is also something that's in the chat with that. I'm going to take a break and you,
so are you Chuck. And we'll continue this. Continuing with a sonic event 13 on Ocelli
and the Greek rated Y did take a little break there, but let's just get back to where the Greek
was. Let's, let's build what we need. Here's the thing. One of the things that I tell people
is to stop buying things, fix what you got. If it's broken or buy it pre-owned or thrifted
or whatever, what that'll do is it'll take the demand out of the manufacturing, right?
And when the demand comes out of the manufacturing, then the prices of things should change,
even though it doesn't, we don't work on supply and demand, right? Cause it's credit, right?
That's why tip the hat off to Volkswagen. They still have a sign and drive. I think on their
commercials, they've been doing this for 15 years, sign and drive. Well, if you could sign,
you can get a Volkswagen. I mean, I mean, they can't tell you more than that. You know, legally
they'll get in trouble by the scumbag bar association, right? Right. So, cause they're
the administrators, right? It's not the presidents. It's not the guard, the guard, you know, you,
I think this one's something I haven't really driven home. The bar association has been charged
with administrating all of the countries, right? That's why you can be a president or ex-president
and you go and you get indicted, right? If you look at the new constitution of the, of Russia,
actually, or if you are not the new constitution, yeah, that one's good to look at
how much they disclose there. They discern the difference between a man and a person
in the constitution, by the way. Really? Yeah. Yeah. So should anyone, right? Well,
they should, but I've never seen that in a constitution myself. So yeah. Well, it's fairly
new. It's not, it's not from, you know, it's recent, but if you go to the president of Russia,
his webpage, Putin on the front page or somewhere, it says, do not contact him regarding legal
matters. Cause basically the government has nothing to do with legal matters is what, get it?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Cause they're not legal. I mean, how much more, they're not a legal thing.
They do have this thing where the president can issue a pardon. That just means the discharge.
They do give a few things like that to give the illusion to some people.
But if you think that the legal society in your country, wherever you are, has anything to do
with your country, you're an idiot. It is a, it is a, a world-based concern that is to
administer the, the bankrupt, all the bankrupt societies. Basically they don't speak about it
this way. I think up to the seventies, that word bankruptcy is a bad word or bankrupt.
I don't know if people are here old enough to remember, but up until the seventies, early
eighties, that word was commonly used, not referring to the government so much, but not anymore
because there's, there's no need for it because it's all credit. So, but anyway, start building
things and fixing things. I always tell people, fix it, you know, and, and buy or buy a quote
unquote, use thrifted or pre-owned. Don't stay away from the primary market. Get out of it.
The other thing that I'm not going to lean much on, but as we go down into the future,
sonic events, I think it will help people because I'll get very specific.
I'm saying this with, I don't know how to say it, but I'll just say it.
I am disappointed. Well, you know, I've said I'm embarrassed to be human, right?
But the more I interact with people, the more dismayed and disappointed I am at how
lack of skill people have, right? And meaning,
most people that I've met in the past decade, I'm not super well-traveled, but I've traveled,
don't have the skills that I would expect an average human in a society that we live in right
now to have, right? An example of that, someone who has what they call a engine driven wagon,
which is called an automobile or a car. Most people still, when something goes wrong,
it's customary to pop the hood and try to start it again. And then they throw their hands up
in the air, right? Most of the time, right? Or check the gauges. You know, am I out of gas?
But they don't know what's what, you see? Not only that, but can they fix it? Most people still
cannot. It's a small minority that does even maintenance, right? Someone's listening to me.
I know someone's listening to me that can pretty much take an engine apart, put it back together,
get all the valve timing correct, right? And all that. Yes, I hope there is, by the way.
But there's a lot of people, I'm sure, that change their spark plugs and change the oil
and the coolant if it's water cooled, right? Can do that kind of stuff besides washing the car,
you see? Giving that as an example. This has to do with cooking, has to do with just fixing
shit in general, right? I had something go through a new laptop. It's a Lenovo ThinkPad
E15, right? It's like right down from the top of the line. Anyway, I had a drywall screw gun go
right through the laptop screen, right? It just happened to be in the bad spot and the screw gun
fell over. Okay, so my wife says, oh, that's too bad. It's a new laptop and we'll have that
professionally done. I'm like, yeah. So I go and order a screen for like 40 bucks and I put it in.
Do I know anything? If you ask me how many laptop screens I've changed in
recent lifetimes, none, never, right? But you go to YouTube University,
right? There's two YouTubes, right? Actually, I call it YouTube University. It's great for like
if you want to change. I think I gave an example about changing a water pump in a car video.
Right. And the guy says, I'm not going to do it. My girlfriend's going to do it. I think that was
great, right? And she did. It was easy, right? Okay. So I went to YouTube University, didn't
find the exact one, but I got a hang of it. Okay. Changed the screen. Called around, they wanted
250 or 300 bucks. Okay. It's not the money. It's not the money, right? It's not the funds or the
credits. Can you do it, right? And it builds character. So what I recommend to people to do
is try to pick up a new skill every week. Well, not completely or entirely, but try to do something
that, but don't be foolish, but try to do something that you haven't done that you wish you
can do or wanted it to do and attempt it. And sometimes it might mean getting the tools for it,
right? Okay. And improvise and just try it out. But because of YouTube University, you can educate
yourself by actually sharing. If someone says, I have no experience doing, I have no experience
changing laptop screens, but if I see a few being changed, I see what they have in common. And you
do have like a virtual experience, right? You don't have the tactile feeling. You don't know
what it feels like. No, you can get an idea. Yeah. You don't smell it either. No. Right.
So here's the thing. I really would like to see people building up their skill level and especially
in the medical side. I hate to use that word medical, physiotherapy,
or physiotherapy, the physical terrain, learning about dentistry, learning about...
Here's the thing. To go back and learn about the human body, you know how they say, I just
look at the pictures? That's what you should be doing unless the book is more than 100 years old.
The minute you see immune system absorption and this and that,
delete, right? It doesn't exist. Right in front of you, it's like saying jet fuel brought down
the towers, right? Oh my gosh. It doesn't work. You know, if you had a swimming pool full of jet fuel
or diesel fuel and went into the house, tore out a sheet of aluminum foil, the kind that you
wrap baked potatoes on to put in the barbecue, right? Throw the aluminum foil in the swimming
pool full of diesel fuel and light the swimming pool diesel fuel on fire. And after about two
weeks, it'll be completely burned, right? All the diesel. Well, at the bottom, you're going to see
the aluminum foil still be all charred, but you take the aluminum foil out and you just go inside
with the sink and a sponge and just wash it off. It'll be nice and shiny and you could use it to
wrap your baked potatoes. Yep. So this fuel that's burning for a week or two weeks or a month
doesn't melt. Aluminum is going to melt four inch thick steel. Now, in order to put out a story like
that, you have had to conditioned the society to be so idiotic and moronic that they count as
zero, right? Okay. This is what's going on with the medical stuff also, right? Science. What was
the thing they're pushing with the pen? Oh, let's trust the science. Ah, trust the science,
not trust science. Trust the science. That's like the doctor. Everybody says, I went to the doctor.
I want to find out who this is. Is it like Santa Claus who goes on everyone's chimney? You know,
Santa Claus is told to children that brings all the toys and all that, right? So it's the same
Santa Claus, right? For everyone, isn't it? I guess so. Yeah. Well, it's like I never heard it
mentioned that there was Santa Claus A, Santa Claus B, one in the North Pole, one in the South
Pole, right? So it's the Santa Claus. So I hear people saying, I went to the doctor here and that
person over here, maybe on a video says, I went to the doctor. A person down the street here says,
he went to the doctor. I said, oh my gosh, is this the same doctor? This guy gets around like
Santa Claus. Anyway. I got you. Yeah. See, this is a metric. So now you know, look, if you want
to know what I'm thinking about, listen to what I'm saying. Okay. It's exactly what's going through
the mind. One thing that going back to the chat, by the way, I get very, before we went on this
short break, if it's still in there, we talked about making your own laser pulse, uh, pulsing.
One thing I did for removing tattoos. One thing I didn't mention is that nitrogen in the air,
which is more than 70% doesn't like high energy. It turns into nitrates and things like that. And
it could cause problems. So purging, if you purging the area with a gas that's inert helps
CO2 maybe, and which is also cooling. I just want to throw that in there. Um,
going back to the chat, someone says, Hey, uh, uh, I think it was ed. What do we talk about?
What do you think about music or whatever? Uh, and someone second that I think phase shifter
second, that idea. It's very simple. What is music, right? Right. I know Chuck. Go ahead.
What go ahead. Cause you, you did, uh, some genre of rock or something maybe beyond tell us.
Well, I did, I did, uh, lots of different stuff actually, uh, musically. And I mean,
I would just, uh, I would create mostly original material, but sometimes we would,
you know, play, uh, cover tunes, this kind of thing. I mean,
I did all sorts of different work in the music business, uh, and then wound up,
you know, making money actually, uh, by, or, you know, making a living for a bit anyway.
Uh, being a bouncer, a booker, et cetera, as a vocation. Yeah. I mean, I worked in studios.
Here, here go the dogs again. Uh, all that, but, um, yeah, uh, no music is something that's very
interesting to me though, because it is often a cultural vehicle. It's often a very spiritual
feeling thing one way or another, whether you're expressing, you know, an emotion,
see, it's also very emotional. It just seems to cross into so many different things
that are part of our experience that I, I find it to be, you know, one of these unique pieces of art
that is out there, you know, uh, it is, it is similar to replicating an image, you know,
because you're replicating an emotion sometimes, and you can transmit that, uh, through these
different, you know, people tell me, oh, it's about the frequencies and so on. And in some ways
it is, but in other ways that there's, there's kind of intangible things to it. I think, uh,
you know, you know, the idea of like, I don't know necessarily how to tell you how to write a hit,
but I know one when I hear it, you know, you've heard that a lot from these guys who were
successful producers and stuff. There is a, there's an element that I think there's not even
language for outside of it. It is a language in and of itself. Now, maybe that's a silly notion,
but yeah, go ahead. No, when you say a hit that the whole industry has been in lockdown since Clive
Davis, uh, uh, you know, since the 60s, since Motown it's in lockdown, unless you know how to
work the system and then, then you'll get sucked up by it. But what I wanted to say is, you know,
you could ask a thousand people that they're, that is into music on whether they're playing
an instrument or whatever involved in the music business. And they'll all, all thousand people
will say something different, but the commonality is pretty much the same. It's, you know, it's
something that, uh, is, uh, people need and want and they produce it and they make it because people
need and want it. Right. And it's been around in history. What, what I want to give about that
is, um, it's kind of like a name, you know, when you ask someone, what's your name?
And, uh, if they don't hear you, right. They're like, what? I'm like, uh, what sound do you
answer to? Right. What is the name? It's a sound that you answer to, right. It doesn't have to be,
it could be like something like the Greek, right. Which is like a nickname kind of thing. I answer
to that. Right, right. So it's a sound that you answer to. So what's happening is, uh, this music,
we answer to it in a contemplative way. We hear it and we either like it or we don't like it. And
if we like it, we accept it and we try to take in something. Right. What I say about music also is
that, you know, people think they see with their eyes and they hear with their ears. We actually,
you see with your brain and you hear with your brain and magicians know this. That's why they
can distract you and do what they do in a ledger domain or press the digitation,
because they know that it's not your eyes that you see with, it's with your brain. So if they
can occupy enough of your brain, the, uh, you will see what's going on, but you will not acknowledge
it. So when someone hears a certain kind of music, they don't like, they acknowledge enough
of the parts that they don't like, and they turn it off. Someone hears enough of the music that
they acknowledge that they do like, then they open themselves up more to it. So that's where
you have, you know, I like it or I don't like it. Um, this is where, this is the point I want to
make that I'm sure many people or no one has heard because this is a very unique, as far as I know,
I was the only one involved in a small group of people back in 2009. There's a company called
ProSonic Formosa, ProSonic, they're in Malaysia. They're a very large, um, they make all your Sony
stuff and speakers, uh, home theaters, all kinds, they're involved in all kinds of stuff, right?
Well, we came up even back then with a counter space, this, this module that you put in an
audio dynamic speaker and it makes it coherent. So there's no distortion. What I mean is, you know,
you go to a drive-thru and you sound like this, right? Right. Okay. That's because of the
enclosure of the driver. There is forcing a driver to move in it, in an enclosure, a box, a speaker
box. And if you cut anything open in nature, you're going to see there's a secondary geometry
inside of a piece of fruit, right? You don't cut an apple open and just see apple flesh. There's
actually a geometry inside, right? The core and the seeds, uh, a watermelon, any, anything in
nature, an egg, the human, but anything in nature that grows or is alive, when you open it up, it has
a secondary geometric layout inside, right? It doesn't resemble what's on the outside at all,
right? Like when you cut open an orange and you see eight pieces, you know, the eight sections inside,
you don't see that one. It's hanging on a tree. You have to open it, right? So you have a
complimentary geometry. So we made these modules, you put them in a speaker and suddenly it sounds
clear, right? Because we're, we're just completing the project, right? We're completing the
manifestation of reproducing sound. Okay. So the idea was, uh, when the module is in the loud
speaker, it sounds really coherent and clear. And when it's not in the loud speaker, it sounds like
this, right? Okay. So we found what we did was, um, uh, I did this remotely. I was still in the
experiment. This was in 2009. It took about six months and there was about 75 people involved.
Half the people worked at prosonic and the other half didn't. What they did is they set them up
with various EKG and ECG equipment, you know, where they scan the, um, what people that have
equipment were brought in, let's say that scan the stress levels in the body, right? They have things
that they stick on your skin and they have various factors that they look at, including brainwaves.
And when, uh, they, these people are there to tell, it's kind of like lie detector kind of
equipment, right? But what they do is they developed an algorithm which shows someone
is experiencing a higher, uh, stress or normal or reduced stress relaxation, right? Points.
So what they did was they played the speakers without the module and they had a certain
stress level. Then they played the speakers with headphones and speakers in the room, both
with the module and the stress was reduced, right? But here's the thing. Okay. Why is he saying this?
What is he? Why? Okay. That's good. Okay. But here's the thing. It didn't matter what kind of
music it was. They had heavy metal, right? Like I call it love songs. They're really, you know,
really strong, heavy metal. It sounds like a Viking battle cry, right? Okay. Right. They had
acid, heavy metal. They had heavy disco. They had classical music. They had a funky jazz and
mellow jazz elevator music, right? And just vocals. So they had all the like five, six genres.
So they played, um, all the different genres. So you would think that most people would have,
that people would have a higher stress level with the acid metal or whatever, right? Or the
hard disco than the classical. And they found out that it wasn't the type of music.
It was this, how coherent it was to them. So the stress level for the elevator music was the same
with the heavy metal. Ultimately, when they're listening just for stress levels,
they told people to relax and they would measure the stress with the module or without the model.
So without the module, the stress levels were higher with all the music equally.
And with the module, the stress levels, you know, with the speaker sounding clear,
were lower. So when I found that study out, it took me like a few days to digest it. Because
let's say I don't like heavy metal. I'm not saying I don't, but let's say I don't, or I don't like
disco, which I did that for a few years, by the way, specifically, I did heavy metal stuff. But yeah,
good. Yeah. But what I'm trying to say is, let's say, let's just take as a given, I don't like
disco and heavy metal. Let's say I'm not, that's not true. Well, but let's just say you did. Right.
Okay. Let's say, right. So I, if I'm in doing a test and I'm listening and I agree to be part of
this, I'm expecting myself to have elevated levels of stress listening to those genres, right?
Simply because you don't like it. Right. But the test shows that was not the case. And these
were people between 18 and 80. Right. So they found out that it was not the type of music,
but it was whether it was coherent. In other words, the more clear it sounded
and more coherent and less distortion, the less stress the organism
experienced. And when I say organism, you know how they say, these are like the crazy
rich people on park Avenue. Make sure I know a lady has a duplex on park Avenue,
penthouse. Make sure I watching the apartment a long time ago.
Make sure you play the classical music when you're not here because the plants like it.
Have you ever heard? Yes, I have heard that kind of thing.
Okay. All right. Very important. Okay. So that's why I said organism. It is true. There are plants,
there's the secret life of plants, right? It's true that plants do react to these things also.
Now this, but this whole study, it has nothing to do whether it's classical music or not. It's
whether it's coherent. Okay. Here's the other thing. People say, uh, Greek, let's go listen
to some live music. And I know what's going on, but I don't want to be an asshole. So I go with
them and I know what's going on. Meaning we're going to go to a venue where there's a live
band playing, but it's going to be amplified with these stage speakers, right. Which is
or the PA system in conjunction with stage speakers. And it sounds like crap, right?
A lot of times. So I show up and I know what's going on when they invite me. I know I, you know,
I show up and after a few minutes, I'm like, guys, I'm going to be outside having a smoke
or something. Cause this is too loud. And it sounds, doesn't sound good to me, but it's live.
I'm like, yeah, I know it's live, but it sounds like crap. Right. So usually people that enjoy
that kind of thing in a venue just want something different. They don't even care if it's good or
anything. They just want something different. Exactly. But what I'm saying is even though
they think they're liking, they will have an elevated stress level because it sounds like crap.
So when this music thing was brought up in the chat, I wanted to interject what I'm saying,
because most of the time we go around within a, from a cultural perspective,
from a heretic or heresy, meaning like, what do you, heresy means to prefer something,
what you prefer preference. And because something is not of someone's preference,
we feel that that will inconvenience them to the point where they will be stressed, right?
Okay. So, but we found out objectively, that's not true. So it's the incoherent sound that stresses
people out, not the genre of music. And I just wanted to share this with everyone because I
know this is not public because right now you can go around and ask pretty much everyone on this
planet, what do you think happens to people who are listening to music of a genre that they don't
prefer? Oh, they get stressed, right? No, the answer is no, they don't. It's the way that they,
the quality that comes to them, if it's incoherent, right? Listening to a shower radio would be the
least incoherent, right? Or a cheap radio, right? Oh, yeah. No, yeah. Think about that for a second.
The little tiny, like old transistor radios that had the terrible speakers in them.
Well, it's such, yeah, it's the whole system was, but even now, if you look even in high end audio,
a lot of people say this is too fatiguing, even though it sounds crystal clear, because
it's not coherent. So I just wanted to throw that in there about music, because that's something
that is completely wide open. It's like food, right? And I feel really good to be a part of
something that is, for the first time, other than live music, can be reproduced and be coherent.
I think I sent you a video sample of the loudspeaker, right, on a bench. Right. And
then I sent you the source that you could listen to directly from the file. And there was no
difference, very little, if not any noticeable between the speaker playing in the room and the
file being played on whatever you listen to on the headphones. Right, right, right. That's not
possible, because you're right. Okay, so what I'm trying to say is we can go, okay, let me put it
this way, in a general sense, we could spend most of our lives with preconceived notions of things
that we've borrowed from academia, culture, TV, or listening to other people. And it's just not true
when you find out by objectifying what's really going on. And I just wanted to bring that up with
the music, because it's not the type of music, it's whether it's coherent or not. In other words,
is it natural? Another example of that would be bird song. You know, birds communicate really,
really from great distances and echoes and sound reflections, and they still get the message,
right? And our hearing is more sensitive than our eyesight. Give an example. You're walking through
the forest with a group of people, and it's really late at night, and it's really dark. It's a dark
moon. You can't see much. And you hear something unusual. What happens? Immediately, you want to
run the opposite direction, right? Let's imagine we're making a bee horror movie, okay? And you
hear a growl and a screech. Behind you, everyone starts speeding up, going in the opposite direction.
So your ears are more important for your survival than your eyes.
Well, they can be, but there's other things going on there outside of your ears. That's just the
one that's easy to interpret, right? Yeah. Well, the thing is, you'll pick it up with your skin
also. That's why headphones don't really give you... When you're listening to music that's
reproduced, let's say, with a hi-fi system or live, the tactile sensation, it's almost haptic
through the entire body and the ears, right? I know people that are into headphones.
Yeah, I hate listening to music on headphones because it feels like a half an experience at
best. That's right. And I wanted to say something, but maybe I won't be lascivious in this,
because it's pretty lascivious. So anyway... Well, why not? We're all adults here.
Yeah, well, we'll skip it. Yeah. So what I've suggested to people that have invested in
headphones and especially high-end system, I said, well, why do you listen to headphones? Because I
don't want to disturb anyone else. I said, well, okay, how about you put the headphones on the
jack and have the main amp put the loudspeakers on very, very, very low. You could test that for
yourself. Just close the door and go outside of the room if it's a closed room or whatever.
Some cases you can't do it, but still have the loudspeakers on in the room, very, very low with
the headphones on, and then tell me how the experience. They're like, much, much better,
not disturbing anyone because it's too low of a level to disturb anyone. And I could turn up the
headphones, but I still get that ambient perturbation in the room. You see? Yeah. That's
actually a really good idea. Yeah. And that brought to life because I've had people, I said,
yeah, man, I'm trying to get into this headphone experience. I started off with some $100
headphones, another up to $3,500 headphones, electrostatics. And they thought if they got
those that they were more... I said, no, no, it's just in your head. You're just putting your head
in a vise. Was there a movie that put the guy's head in a vise? Casino.
Yeah, or something. So it's like putting your head in a vise. Think about it. What is a headphone?
And you're trying to get an entire emotional experience out of that. No, it's not going to
happen. You need... Right. Okay. So I just suggest to people, if you do listen to headphones and it's
an inconvenience, have a system in the room also playing very, very low. Because I have actually
experienced where, let's say I'm sleeping in one room and someone else is sleeping in another room
and I want to hear something. I could put it on so low that you don't hear it outside the room at
all. Right? Even with the door open. You know what I mean? Right. You just got to play around with
it. It's very important. The headphone thing, I think is... That's why the incidences of hear loss
have gone up since the 80s with the Walkman, you know? Yeah. In the 80s, the earbuds. Well,
it was by the end of the 80s, they were sticking the earbuds all the way down the ear canal and
you were pressurizing the ear canal where... See, with the over-the-ear headphones, you have some
airspace around the lobe, right? Right. You're not directly pressurizing. Oh, that's why I refuse to
use those. And still, people think I'm nuts. They're like, why are you using a big old pair
of headphones when you do your radio stuff? I'm like, because I don't want to damage my ears.
And you guys are sticking these things in your ears. I don't want to do that.
It does something. I don't know how to explain it, but I know...
Well, what it does is you're vented. The ear canals are vented in the rest of the head,
right? Yeah. That's why when you go up in an airplane, they tell you to swallow or chew gum
so your ears don't... Your ears pop, altitude change. You have vents that go into the throat
mouth area, right? Right. So it's not totally pressurized. It's almost like a reflex system.
But when you close off... You see, when you have the over the ear headphones, the shape of the lobe
offers a valleys and peaks for air to move around in there. You're not directly pressurizing.
It's kind of like if you want to blow up a balloon, you put it tight on your lips. That would
be the high pressure situation of the earbud. Where imagine trying to blow up a balloon with
one inch away from your mouth. You're not getting that pressure in the ear, you see?
Right. You're not going to blow up a balloon. So the over the ear would be
the way to go. And also the larger the diaphragm, the safer it is because the larger the diaphragm,
it doesn't have to move as much. The smaller the diaphragm, it has to move more to produce the same
volume and that creates distortion. You notice it sounded like when asked about music, I went
away from directly discussing music from a romantic point of view to a more, let's say,
technical point of view. I wanted to show how it's not what you like that makes you feel good
or don't like that doesn't make you feel good, but it's the quality of the music,
how it's being received, that makes you feel good ultimately.
Ultimately, I appreciate lots of different types of music. I've always found it interesting. It is
about the quality. It's what's good is good. All the different types of music, when it's
objectified, one shouldn't make you feel stressed and the other one doesn't. That's what I'm trying
to say from this study. See, but that's what's weird. I want to ask you a question about that
though, because I'll tell you that I get a stress level from this like pop crap that is just like
really very artificial sounding. And I know I get stressed from hearing that nonsense. I'm sorry
about the chair noise there. By the way, I need a new chair. But the thing is that there is,
I don't know, there's something to that where it's like the,
oh, who's even really popular now like a Cardi B, right? It is coherent. The sound appears to be
coherent. But I am absolutely disturbed by it. I it's just annoying to me. I don't find it.
And it's super popular. It's like, oh, it's but it's very, you know, it's very consistent. A lot
of people basically are saying it's very consistent. They like the beat. They like this.
And I go, I don't know, for some reason, it's very disturbing to me.
Well, I'm going to have to lean. That's preferential. But I'm saying that the organism
from what I mentioned earlier, we'll accept it just like music that you like. And then we
rationalize it that, you know, I don't want to play that again. Or I won't buy that CD. What
is it? Was it Cardi? Cardigan? Cardi B or whatever. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. All right. Oh,
you won't buy the CD, right? You're not going to go to a concert. And if it's on the radio,
you might find something else. Right. Right. Right. So that's that's so maybe
if you're enterprising away from it, that could cause stress. But what I'm saying is I.
So this secondary study, it's a secondary action, though. It's a secondary action.
Yeah, it's a secondary action, right? It's like you're going to make a move to get away from it
or critique it. But see, that enlightened me to the point where there is a genre of music
called lo-fi. I see it sometimes coming up on YouTube where they add distortions and things
like that. And I don't know what that does, but I still think if it's being reproduced coherently.
But I don't think it is because there's an attempt to make it lo-fi. You know what I mean?
Right. So I just wanted to throw that in. But, you know, there's a lot of sayings about music.
Soot soothes the savage beast. And it's the silence between the notes that makes the music.
People talk about frequency. Frequency is a vibration per unit of time. That is
almost like blood pressure. It doesn't exist, you know, only for a certain it can only be
used for a certain parameter, which is the time between heartbeats. Right.
Or when the heart's expanding and contracting, there's no pressure. So what I'm saying,
the frequency is irrelevant. It's the vibration that's relevant. And when you're listening to
music, it's not just a frequency. It's many vibrations in time. Right. So that needs to
be considered as a whole. It's kind of like when you I had a bowl of soup for lunch. Do you think
it was just hot water or it had other ingredients in it? Right. Otherwise, it wouldn't be I wouldn't
call it a bowl of soup. Right. Right. So when you say you're hearing music, it's it's it's
a vibratory effect of many frequencies in time. No pun intended, because when you're learning to
make music, it's timing, isn't it? It's all about in time, right? Timing. Yeah, exactly.
So the frequency part, it maybe is important there. There's an aspect of the four thirty
two and four forty. Yeah. People talk about more needs to be it's kind of narrow. That's
for the tuning of a K. Whenever I see something being brought forward as a cure all, I'm leery of
it. You ever that's been going on now for more than 10 or 15 years. Oh, they went from this to
that. Well, they're not talking about that. It's the tuning of a and have they mucked about with
the tuning of C and D. Right. And they have there is. So to me, that's like a lot of the flat
earth stuff. The flat earth stuff, by the way, I was going around and like I remember from like
1986, 1987, talking about talking to people, you know, the earth is flat logically and rationally.
But when I do surveying, it's round. So it must be both depending on what you're focusing on. Right.
And I would bring up the earth is flat often. There was also in the 80s, the concave earth
that we're actually in a concave section. Now, that's like the plate issue, right? Where like
it's almost like a plate where there's a. Well, no, it's kind of like imagine we're not on the
inside or not on the outside of the globe of the basketball, but we're on the inside.
And when we're looking up, we're actually looking at the center.
Oh, so these are all different perspectives. That one was brought up because when you dig
two parallel holes, they start to diverge. They don't converge. They go further apart,
which means we're right. So anyway, because they're actually tangents. But here's the thing.
Talking about all this stuff for many, many years and seeing it come up again.
Right. Like most people, the flatter thing is a new thing. Right. And I'm like, oh, my gosh,
I don't know if you remember me addressing this a long time ago as a flatter thing. I was doing
that. Everybody's doing that. Not everybody, but I was amongst people that made it a serious point
of research. Right. Right. So these things are revived over and over and over. All these
things are brought back. And I think the the a. Tuning. Yes, most people I went forth,
they don't even know what they're talking. They don't even you know, I've heard the difference.
I could hear the difference slightly. I'm not I'm not into the fine tuning of instruments.
There is a slight difference. But I think I think you need to be if these points are brought up,
they need to be more well rounded, because most people, when they argue the 432 and 440,
they don't even know of what tuning of what what's tuned. They don't know it's a right.
Most people, they just say preferred, because this is like, what do you say,
tell people what to think, what to say, what to be a part of, right, what to have interest in,
they don't know. So what I suggest is a more well rounded approach to anything. So when you see the
next new thing, which is actually an old thing, brought up as a controversy or whatever, learn
more about the subject more well rounded, and you'll see if you're being played or not, you
know, or it's a what do you call it when they just distract your take your attention away?
Just that right? Distraction. Distraction. True. Yeah. Because I found most of the things that
the majority and I'm talking about even alternative, which is still part of the majority.
When I say the majority of the mainstream, I'm including 99.9999% of the alternative also,
of course, right? Yeah. Essentially, what I suggest like recently, I saw someone I haven't seen in a
while. And they said, What are you doing? I said, I'm doing this thing called a Shelley in the
Greek. And it's basically an audio guidebook for anyone visiting Earth. Because if you're from
Earth, you won't understand anything I'm saying, and it won't make any sense to you. But if you're
not from Earth, you'll get a pretty good idea of what's going on here. I know what to watch out
for. And they're like, that's freaking cool. I like that. Yeah, well, you still often say,
look, I'm just here taking notes, which I thought was, was a great way to explain it. And just
there you go. Not really claiming, although you are here, you're, you're, you're among us,
you're not claiming to be another species or anything. Well, you're neutral. When you're
taking notes, if the situation is going bad, your interest is to just write it down, right?
If the situation not to take part of it. And if your situation is going the situation Jones going
good, you're just to take notes. Well, much like what a reporter or a journalist was supposed to
do, they were supposed to journal what was going on, not interject their opinion, not interject,
you know, a certain slant. It was a matter of journaling. In other words, just recording
what is happening. They were in turn supposed to relate that to other people. But still,
the idea was to journal it, not to influence the information, but just to,
again, take notes or censor it. Yeah. And unfortunately, I am embedded still here.
You know, there was an odd question that came up just really fast before we,
because I have this feeling we're about to come to an end here for this sonic 13. But there was
this odd question from somebody that I don't know if they're going to keep their subscription. But
they asked me something that about something you said elsewhere. And it just came to my mind,
for some odd reason here. Well, I know what the odd reason is, but nevermind.
They said that you had said something about being from another time.
Absolutely. Yeah. Now, another time. Do you mean that your ethical construct is out of place in
this time period? Or do you mean literally, from another time out of no ethical, moral, intellectual,
social, all of that? Okay. Well, I just in other words, the way it happens is I keep
explaining how it works. I think the concept of time, you know, everything that's happened
is happening still, but it's in fade, a very faded wave, like water hitting.
You see the surfers that try to catch the waves behind the freight ships, and they're like two
miles away, and they still catch the wave, right? And it gets smaller and smaller. And if something
to happen in the future, there has to be a primer or the possibility of it happening already set up.
Otherwise, it would not happen, right? In other words, the allowances, all of the physical,
spiritual, energetic allowances have to be there for it to happen, even if it's way down the future.
So, what I am doing here is I am in resonance, literally, just like CB radio's message to each
other, or walkie talkies, you know, you could have, you know, just like cell phones that work
on independent frequency, right? The SIM card, right? You can have 100 people in a neighborhood
will have walkie talkies, but only the ones that are tuned in, right? Only the ones that are tuned
into the same channel, actually hear what's happening on that channel. Yeah. Right. So I found
out a long time ago, that what I am interested in and what I am most effective in communicating
are things that are not of this time. Meaning time, meaning the way things, the events,
of these events. Now, what makes it even more absurd is the absurdity of it. Not what I am,
my position here is, but what I see going on around me. I see people wondering about things
that are already been referenced, right? And provable. People hoping for things that are
been shown don't exist and cannot exist, right? People asking about, or thinking things are a
certain way, when in their references, it's already shown that it's the opposite, right?
So you have a society that is living in this imaginary dream state, right? And that's why
things are the way they are. I mean, how easy would it be to take control of a million people
that are all asleep? You've heard that term, and I mean literally. If you went into a hospital
where they have all the beds open, or a military place, if you have, let's say, a hundred, a
thousand, a million people, and they're all in their bed, sound asleep, and you're walking around
through them, it's like, you feel like, what the hell's going on? I'm the only one here, right?
You see? Might as well be.
Because they're all asleep. Yeah, might as well be. And you have more control than they do,
because they're asleep. So in essence, I am definitely not from this time. Not at all.
Can't be. Just like the resonant and the frequency and all that, with two CB radios, two walkie
talkies, or two cell phones, right, on the tower, they click into the same frequency. No, I'm
definitely not from here. Can't be. That's from a rational thought. It cannot be shown directly,
but just like the poles in a magnet cannot be shown. You know, the magnets don't attract or
repel, right? It's like a screw. The top, one side of the magnet is clockwise, and it's clockwise
through the magnet, but if you flip it upside down, it looks counterclockwise, right? Or when
you have a right-hand screw, it has to go in a right-hand nut, a left-hand, and a left-hand
nut, right? Left-hand thread, right-hand thread, right? We can't see a lot of these things.
Yep. But it's a rational way that I used to express it. Absolutely.
Okay, fair enough. I thought that would be a great question, and I meant to get to it last
time we got together, and I forgot, actually, because we wound up on a different path.
Yeah, and time is events, right? So in other words, I am not from these events, and I've met
very few people in that sense. So time, from this time, would be events, right?
Mm-hmm.
Right? It just doesn't make any sense at all. So how can, if you see something, by the way,
that makes no sense at all, and it shouldn't make sense, but it's still continuing,
how can you be from there, right?
Well, in that case, I got to say that although I'm not seeing the same things you are,
I concur with you. I see things all the time that make absolutely no sense. I hear people speaking
where the language, I think I understand the language, but apparently I don't,
because it doesn't make sense what I'm hearing said. This is a constant for me.
Well, look, it goes beyond that, because if you ask, for example, someone who's religious,
it's a feeling they have from belief, right? I don't even, I don't understand,
I can't sympathize or empathize or feel that at all.
No, it's not about belief. It's just about what doesn't seem to make, it's just incongruous. Look,
if you tell me that there is an order, right? And I say, okay, look, I understand, let's count one,
two, three, four. And somebody says, look, one and three and five, they don't really matter.
Just use the even numbers. And this I'll go, okay, your system makes sense, you know,
because at least we can incrementally count by twos instead of one, two, three, four, right?
And I can say, all right, well, we can count by fives, whatever. I can look at that objectively
and say, well, this is a way of accounting and we can do it that way. And that's faster.
All right. I don't have to count one, two, three, four, five. You know what I mean?
That's okay. But when you have something where you say, look, you can go one and then six and
then two, and then I go, whoa, whoa, whoa. Well, that's actually sympathetic. And I
mean that in many levels. You have the word sympathetic that we use socially and culturally,
but then there's sympathetic and vibrations, right? That are harmonics that are formed.
And there are odd harmonics, but here's the thing with harmonics, they all have use.
Because if you understand odd harmonics enough, you could knock a wall down with sound, right?
Right. It's true, but there is always an order to it. Even when somebody explains something
odd like that, like, you know, the sonic weapons and things. I say, look, generally speaking,
most of my experiences don't line up with this, but that's not what it's about. It's not about
my recognition. It's about, at least you can provide me with an objective sort of sense of
how the order goes with things, right? Well, that's why it's beyond rationale,
Chuck. It's beyond what you're saying. Like if you ask someone how many cats are in the room
and there's three cats and they count three cats, or maybe they don't know how to count,
but if they insist that there are only two or one, is that what you mean? Like there's a problem
there? Yeah. I look at it and I go, well, how do you not see that this is happening? Look,
even if you and I don't understand it the same way, how do you not see that something is
happening? I'm telling you that it's almost like somebody sets off firecrackers in your living
room. You're in your kitchen, okay? And look, I didn't see it happen, but I know something
happened in that other room because I heard a noise. Something is observable here. We should
have all heard it if we all were able to hear. Okay? And you go to that room and they say,
no, nothing happened. No, no, I get you. Well, there's a lot of sayings about that,
the 800 pound gorilla in the room and all that too, right? But what I'm saying is it's very deep.
If you read, for example, there's stuff in what they call the biblical texts and there's stuff
that Socrates and other people wrote that I used to take out and show as a quote to someone. And
I would say, when was this written about society? And they said, oh, this sounds like what's going
on right now, meaning past month or two weeks. I'm like, no, this was written 2,500 years ago,
or this is from the book of Numbers, or this is from Psalms, or this is from Socrates,
right? And I'm like, wow, how can it be so accurate about what's going on right now?
Right? Because what it's doing is it's not shining a lot. This is a mistake people make.
It's not about, you know, they say we've got to shine a light on it, put it, take it out of the
dark, put light on it. No, that doesn't necessarily do it. Right? Putting something in the light
doesn't, I mean, they have cookers that work with light. It doesn't do it. There's an underlying
substrate. Although we did learn earlier that a particular type of light can be advantageous,
depending on the effect that you wish to create, right? Yeah, it can. But that's, again,
it's sympathetic. If the light has to be incandescent, it has to have a very pure color filter
also. By the way, we'll just recap that Dinshaw-Gaudi-Aldi chromotherapy,
there's other people doing it, but the thing is, you don't have to get complicated about it.
Theatrical gels work, and you have to have a very strong incandescent bulb. Incandescence is
important. But what I'm saying is that there is a very, very deep, call it spiritual, it's a
non-material thing, like magnetism is non-material. It's the quality of a thing, right? If you look
at a hunk of iron, that's just a hunk of iron, and a hunk of iron that's magnetized, they're
exactly the same, except one is magnetic, the other one's not. That's not a material difference
or something. It's immeasurable from a material sense. It's energetic. It's a quality. One has a
magnetic quality, the other one doesn't. Same exact piece of iron, right? Right.
It's the same thing. There's a level where I'm telling people on the emo stuff, especially,
very important, that this time concept of events is all connected, all the way through,
backwards and forwards, just like the example of when you're in a bad situation and you hear a
little voice say, is it going to be okay? That's you recalling, I'm suggesting, that is you
recalling the event. If you don't hear that little voice, it's probably the last time you're going to
have a bad event or any event, or you forgot that event. You didn't recall it. It doesn't mean
that it's the end when you don't hear that little voice saying everything's going to be okay,
if it's a really bad, you're in a tight spot. It just means that you won't recall it. It'll
be forgotten. This is an explanation, again, just another thing on the list. Consider this,
because that gives you, okay, some people will say to me about that, great, that's really
introspective. I like the ways, yeah, okay, so you like that analogy that I gave, because it still
leaves you two possible things. One is, it's the last time you're going to be in a tight spot.
It means that you're done, or you're going to forget it. Okay, so let's take that and go to
the next level with how we operate in time with our consciousness, backward and forward, you see?
That's what I'm talking about. I'm not from this time, for sure.
I don't think many of the people listening and continue to listen to this
and enjoy it and actually use it are either.