Rated Y, Sonic Event 125, or 125, whatever it is you want to call it, anyway, here it
is.
Greek, how are you?
Yeah, yeah, this is going to be a good one, I think.
I'm doing alright.
We're bringing up a couple of questions before we hit the record button, and one of them
we just finished off with, we were talking about free phones, you know, or they're not
really free, whatever, Federal Reserve Notes, whatever country you're in, they're a form
of Federal Reserve Notes.
You know what they're talking about back in the 90s or 80s, they bankrupted the Soviet
Union, that's why, you know, it fell and all that, that's total, do you know that the Soviet
Union and the whole, it's not just the Union, let's include the bloc, you know, right, Hungary,
East Germany, keep going on and on, right?
Right, the Eastern Bloc, sure.
Eastern Bloc, yeah, all of that went through the Federal Reserve in Washington, D.C. and
New York.
You could look that up, it's hard, you know, they didn't have their own money, right?
Well, on their paper money, though, it said, you know, Bank O.D., whatever, right?
That's right, all the central banks are part of the, they were part of the International
Monetary Fund, and all of that goes through the D.T.C.C., which is in Manhattan.
You could look up the D.T.C.C., and they have a sheet, maybe they don't anymore, but they
do 24 quadrillion, quadrillion, a year in transactions.
Now, let me just put that in perspective, that's 2.4, 2,000, that's the one after a
trillion, that's 1,000 trillion, 2,400 trillion, 1,000 trillion, all right, now the Earth has
been, you know, when you get an appraiser, right, to appraise how much something, whether
it's a ring or a house or a watch, okay, the entire Earth right now is less than 250 trillion
appraised, and they're doing 100 times more of that in transactions a year, okay, just
the food for thought, it's a tangent, right, but just how ridiculous this is.
By the way, when the shit goes down from cosmic forces, let me just say it this way, do you
think the cosmic forces, the ones that we allegedly get proper law from, view this unlawful
activity and the trading and all that as acceptable behavior or unacceptable behavior?
Well, obviously, it's supposed to be unacceptable.
Unacceptable, right, but you're given a chance to do it, to see what it's like, because you
don't want to be totalitarian, and then you let them go, and if you see, they know that's
the wrong thing to do, but if they keep doing it, then you got to come and slap them across
the head, right?
Okay.
And destroy their entire society as a side effect, right?
But the big question comes into play here, if that is all the case, then why, right,
here we go with the why, why does this get allowed to occur in the first place?
Well, I just, the reason I mentioned, because if you enforced it, if you did prohibition,
if you prohibited and enforced that prohibition, you would seem tyrannical.
Yeah, but why allow it to even begin, like, in other words, at the inception?
Well, okay, that's a matter of time.
For us, it's been going on more than our lifetime, but from the other side, it's only a few seconds.
I know, for you and me, look, it's impossible, because we got here, this is the way it was,
right?
But at a certain point in time-
Right.
By choice, though.
Yeah.
Okay, but-
It's still by choice, but if you choose not to run in this way, you're going to not be
able to get a lot of stuff, let's say.
But this is the condition of things when we arrived, as far as I'm concerned, right?
Right, but what I'm saying, it's a factor of time.
Okay, for example, the ancient Greeks had an idea that the meaning of life, which I talked
about last week-
Yeah.
The last song.
The meaning of life was on the last song, I guess.
Yeah, we're all basically here to waste each other's time, just passing the time.
Right.
And this might add a little more to it.
I don't know if I mentioned it, maybe I did.
The ancient Greeks, there was a school of philosophy that believed that in the world that we came
from, we actually died, and this is in the between time, like your whole life flashing
before you, or the time in between, like the Bardo, the time in between going to another
existence is what this life on Earth is.
So you're actually dead, which is actually backed up quite a bit by, if you read what
the Christ allegedly said, let the dead bury the dead, and the walking dead, and all this
stuff, right?
Yeah.
That we're actually all dead, and this is an in-between experience, so how long should
that be, right?
So it's not a matter of time.
So you never discuss time as being a, it's a matter of purely, purely observational when
you discuss time, right?
You cannot say, well, why is something, when you're speaking on a cosmic level, and even
on a societal level, because all societies, as you know, companies usually last 20 years
and they go lose their peak, and you know, countries go two or 300 years, they lose their
peak, right, and all that stuff.
So all that stuff, within those contexts, you could say, why is it happening for so
long?
But when you're having a discussion regarding cosmic forces, time is left out, completely
out of the equation.
I was not asking why it's happened for so long.
I was asking why it was allowed to begin, is the biggest question, like, why was this
even...
Well, that's the rated Y part, and the rated I part, I think, well, I...
But look, just a quick example here, right?
You start noticing your neighborhood going downhill, right?
You got to block...
No, no, no, but let me say, why?
Because if they prohibit it, and certain things are prohibitive, by the way, okay, let's just
work it.
What are we not allowed to do?
And this might answer, okay, we cannot see into the spiritual realm on an individual
level at will, full vision, cannot do that.
Not at all, not at will.
At all, not at all at will, yeah, and even little glimpses, you know, a little dark,
you know, seeing through a glass darkly, right?
Glimpses, they occur accidentally, just like the randomness of...
Right, so we're not allowed to do that, okay, there's a prohibition, okay, but we can't
fly, in other words, defeat gravity, you know, and within our box.
We cannot physically fly at will independently, yes.
That's right, yeah, most people can't, as a matter of fact, I'd say no one can, with
the exceptions that we don't know of.
So there are many prohibitions, like overcoming gravity, seeing the mind, where the mind comes
from, right?
There are prohibitions.
Okay, directly reading, hold on, directly reading someone else's mind is not something...
Yeah, yeah, all that stuff, anything in the mind, the non-physical knowledge and all that,
okay.
So do we feel that not being able to conquer gravity and go into the spiritual and fully
into the intelligence and information realm, if you start dwelling on that, you're going
to feel like you're living in a tyrannical environment.
You will feel like you're living in...
There's an interesting book called Etta Darpa, which is, it's actually a true book, it's
Aphrodite spelled backwards.
Okay, but I don't think anybody sees the lack of ability to fly at will as tyrannical,
right?
But hold on, Etta Darpa, which is, they have it as a fictional book, but it's actually
a true book, because the level of science in there that contradicts the science experiments
of then and now are all true.
Anyone can do simple science experiments in there and show that what we're being taught
is contrary to what it can really be.
In that book, towards the last part of the book, he kept repeating on how gravity is tyrannical,
because he went to a place where you can make a minimum effort and leap 30 feet across, right?
So he started noticing, when you dwell on a subject, for example, we're going to bring
up the Bible also, so when you look at the way people look at what's in the Biblical
text, and when you research it a little bit or have enough Greek speak under your belt,
you will view that subject by the populace and the authorities as being under tyranny.
Because there's absolutely no reason why we can't have a translation of it, instead of
versions, there's no reason why anyone should be going to these god-awful religions that
are supposedly based on it and are contrary to what's written, there's absolutely no reason
for what's going on.
So if you actually study what could be on any subject, I've just brought up gravity,
the Bible, mental capacity, and all that, if you focus on certain things, you will see
we are under a tyrannical rule of prohibition into these things, yes, you will see, but
when we talk about the money system, hold on, the money system is different, and I'll
explain to you why.
Because if you read in the Biblical text, it's the love of, a lot of people say, oh
yeah, I see it on comments, by the way, the reason I don't do a YouTube channel, I think
I've mentioned this briefly, but I have never given a solid reason why.
The reason I am against YouTube is because I've been looking at YouTube often for things,
and whenever you go to the comments section, I just want to throw up.
In other words, if this is the audience, if you read comments, if this is the audience
of YouTube, I want nothing to do with it, and I still hold that, right?
But that's only a minor representation of who actually...
No, no, go look at, for example, a big channel with a million or whatever subscribers, they
have 1,300 comments, go read through the comments.
Yeah, but that's my point right there.
You just want to blow your brains out.
But mathematically, right there, it's a simple, provable fact that that is a small fraction
of the individuals who actually engage with that material, because if you've got a million
people...
No, it's enough of a fraction to pollute the entire thing.
Okay, so let's go back.
With money, it's very different, Chuck.
Because in the Bible, it doesn't say money is the root of all evil, like a lot of people
like to comment.
It says the love of money, right?
So what they did was they took money away, and it's very clear that money has to have
intrinsic value, right?
Okay.
Now, there was...
Let me just give you what this is.
There's a movie called Brazil in the 1980s, it was like this dystopic future, De Niro was
in it, you know, it was like this dystopic futuristic scenario, where if you needed something
fixed, like plumbing or electrical, you had these guerrilla type guys would come in, so
you didn't have to wait for the state.
But if the state found out you used one of these guys, they punished you, right?
It was kind of like a 1984...
Anyway, they go to this fancy restaurant, and the menu has pictures of the dishes, what
beautiful prepared presentations, but what you get is a pile of mush, either green mush,
brown mush, or whatever, right?
So it's a picture of what this mush supposedly is like, and that's what the money...
Right now, you do not have money anywhere in the world, it's all based on promises to
pay, right?
Notes, right?
Okay.
And they're not redeemable.
So hold on, people still want that.
All of the laws in every country basically define money, especially in the US, and what
we use is not money, it's all credit.
Credit is deferring payment, right?
So how many people, how many times, okay, an idiocracy, I love money, remember the attorney,
I love money, right?
I run into, because I'm less and less and less in many circles, whenever I get into speaking
in groups, especially in industry, when you get to know these people privately, you'll
bring up something that seems quote-unquote profitable, and they're like, oh, I love money.
I'm like, oh my gosh, it's like these people, there's no money, guys.
There's no money.
And you see, so what it is, there are people that still love money, and there is no money.
So what do you call someone who wants and desires something that doesn't exist?
Delusional.
Yeah, well, it's like masturbating as opposed to actually having sex, look.
Yeah, well, I think masturbating is less delusional, I call that self-service, self-serve, it's
a self-serve aisle of the self-serve, right, the self-checkout, whatever.
Self-checkout would be more like suicide.
Yeah, but you get none of the products.
Yeah, so now here's the thing, it's so easy, like, for example, if you go to the GAO, which
is the Government Accounting Office, and look up the IRS, they have nothing, nothing.
But they have plenty on everybody.
Where does your money go in taxation?
Even on a city and state level, in every country, they cannot report.
Now, if you ask them, they'll send you a letter that says, it goes to the jurisdiction of
the schools, goes to the jurisdiction of the roads, okay, jurisdiction, there's no such
thing as that.
So it has to be done that way, because there's infinite money creation.
Again, I don't endorse him, but Brandon Joe Williams, I've been mentioning him on every
Sonic now for the past four or five times, very impressed with what this young man is
doing.
It's funny, when you get to about 60, you call people in their 30s a young man, right?
So you go and see how delusional the society is, but is it still working?
It's working to a certain point.
Now, this is, by the way, the way the money system, the legal system, and all that other
stuff is set up in the US, was designed to implode when the moment enough people found
out about it.
Where did we find out about that?
Henry Ford is a famous saying that they've been putting out since he said it, allegedly,
if the people ever found out how the money system works, there would be blood in the
streets in a day or 24 hours, right?
You've heard that saying, right?
And that's been out there now.
So basically, there is a timed cosmic thing that these systems, whether it's the medical
system is the same, it's worse than Dr. Frankenstein, because Dr. Frankenstein was able to piece
dead people together and animate them, which is what Ben Franklin was doing, by the way.
He was buying slaves and chopping them up and putting them back together, trying to
get electricity to revive them.
That's where Mary Shelley got the idea from rumors, right?
But anyway, you know, there's enough evidence to collaborate what I said, if you look even
on the Internet.
So there was even people experimenting like that lady in Louisiana that they caught where
she was sewing people together and doing all that other stuff.
You know, yeah, whatever it is.
But here's the thing.
A lot of these systems, the medical system, the legal system, the money system was set
up to implode.
In other words, whoever adopts this system will go down with it once enough people find
out how it works, that have morality or wake up to it.
Now, it's so easy to find out that lawyers don't know any law and doctors don't know
anything about the human body and any field.
You know, recently I had a discussion with someone who was very proud that they come
from a family of academics and they mentioned all these different industries and fields.
And I was like, yeah, between you and me, it sounds between you and me.
Thank you for telling me. And if you go out and tell people, they'll commend you.
But I'll tell you, OK, so let's start here with this person.
What field were they in?
And he mentions this.
I said, you know what? In reality, in reality, they didn't know anything about that.
Right. You could work in a field for 20 or 30 years as a professor and just do what
you're told to say. And they really don't know what they're talking about, but they
sound right.
And I went down to the other one, the medical one definitely didn't know what is the
chances of someone being a doctor for 35 years and not using a blood pressure cuff and
tell it right now is zero.
They know nothing.
I notice that all the time, even.
OK, so I do my broadcasting, you know that.
But when I listen to other broadcasters and I go, it's interesting because they use
the right words, they say the right buzz phrase.
But I'll tell you what, the second you try and test to see if they actually have any
knowledge of the thing that they're spitting out this stupid phrase about, they know
nothing. They never read the book.
They never actually investigated.
They're sitting there talking about, well, scientifically, I know this.
And meanwhile, what scientific study have they even bothered to partake of or to
participate in?
Did they ever bother to even read somebody else's scientific study?
And you know what the answer is?
No, no, of course.
Well, it's not even that they're OK.
And that's what they're doing.
Is they're filling a position and they're asleep and they're sleepwalking.
And meanwhile, that's the most, quote, unquote, successful guys I see and hear.
It's like I listen very carefully and I go, OK, that means.
To make that statement, you would have had to have studied this, this, this very, you
know, you know, the kind of stuff I study and I listen carefully.
And guess what? I discover they know none of it.
Well, here's another example.
I could go another way. No woman.
She's a professor at the University of Arizona.
She has three sons and none of her sons barely graduated from high school.
And they all work in different fields.
One is like a I shouldn't give too many.
One of them is one of these MMF MMA fighters.
OK, that could be one billion people.
But, yeah, I got you. And then, yeah.
And then one is this and one is that.
And they're each one is successful in their field.
And and I'm like, oh, that's so good.
Mom is a professor, tenured.
And it's great that it's like she did the right thing.
She didn't make them go.
They, you know, because they could have gotten a free ride, you know, all next to free.
And she did, even though she works in a because she's locked into that, but she can't.
You know, she likes the life they give her.
So she's like a working form of welfare.
Sure. And they automatically provide that you can bring some.
Yeah, she doesn't have to do anything, really.
And she gets, you know, twice the salary of all the other professors.
So but the children did not get any kind of that stuff at all.
And they went off. And so there's an example of a well-done kind of right situation.
Right. They went down thing.
Yeah, they went through other thing with no academic, no college, anything like that.
Barely did high school, whatever.
And because it shows you that the breakdown, you know, the one of the worst things you'll ever see is run into an attorney or a doctor.
And you find out that their dad was a doctor.
Their granddad was a doctor.
Their uncle was a doctor.
Their mom was a doctor. A family or a family of attorneys right there.
Those people are very dangerous because they're all sleepwalking.
Right. And they're carrying on.
That's that's the culture.
You know, that's the culture that they form.
You know, the Klan.
Right. They come out of a clan.
So what you have, because the society, let's say, from the 20th century, let's say World War Two reshaped all of Europe, you know, in a way that, you know, if you're in the US, Canada, Australia, and you wanted a government document or something during the war, you can pretty much get it.
But a lot of places in Europe during the war and after the war, you couldn't get anything official.
It took years to rebuild everything.
Right. Right.
So there's a lot of things were redone and a lot of puppet.
All the puppet governments were finally set up on whatever the agendas were put in.
A lot of the agendas that you hear of that are supposedly in place now and were for 10 years, it started with Obama and continue to 2030 were all put in around World War Two, if you research their history.
So basically, you had an unfettered continuation of life in the US, Australia, places like that.
Right. The continent of Africa, of course, you know, pretty much continuation.
But the war and all that stuff, World War Two is a good demarcation line where you could say anything after that is the same society.
Right. Generationally, if you take so anyone born or anyone, let's say, acting in society, living after the 40s till now, it's pretty much the same society.
Pretty much. You have some exceptions with the war in Kosovo.
Right. And now supposedly the Ukraine, where things were dead because they really remember that there used to be a country called Yugoslavia.
Right. Well, I have one minor objection to this, and that is that I, I believe that you're correct up until 2001 because we have a serious change.
Once again, I think the society is actually different.
Again, you can segment it.
Well, no, it didn't break continuity, though.
It didn't break continuity.
You sure about that? Because.
Yeah. How would it break continuity?
2001. Because now a different reality emerges where you have a surveillance system.
There is no longer any privacy.
Yeah, but that doesn't continue.
That changes a lot of the behaviors of a society in general.
It was mental. It was a mental mind.
It was a big propaganda mindfuck.
Well, which I see why they did it.
But beyond that, it changed a lot of behavior patterns.
A lot of things were eliminated and a lot of new behaviors were introduced into the society, which altered it.
Here's how 9-11 was predicted on many fronts.
First of all, you didn't have an enemy anymore.
Cold War was over.
So you need the enemy.
But you got a new one.
Right. The other thing is you want to you know that the end is near.
And what in order to control people, you cannot allow them to have free travel, you know, freely travel.
Right. And yet the heightened.
So you have to install that.
Yes, but also the heightened discussions of the apocalypse, the Armageddon, all that.
That's right. You notice which they thought was going to be around 2000.
Yeah. See, that didn't come.
You see that change because you had this time.
The world ending thing was all very big.
It was amping up all the way up to 2001 and then culminating with the 2012 deal.
Because my calendar, Greek, you know that my calendar is 2046.
Yes. But back then they were saying what?
2012. And it was what?
December 21st, 2012, I think.
Right. Something like that.
Like the whole world was supposed to end because the Mayan calendar stops.
Well, because the Mayan calendar is based on a 360 day.
Well, I'm not talking about the truth of it.
I'm talking about the way people.
But the same thing holds off, you see, because 9-11, you're going to have more 9-11 coming type stuff.
But it's going to be, you know, like, you know, what the first 9-11 was was was not Waco.
The one in Oklahoma City, that was the first mini 9-11.
We know where they declared the domestic terrorism and the buildings being blown up.
Of course, there's your OKC thing, which happens.
But there's a huge change there between in that time period from 2000 to 2012 where the world is going to come to an end thing.
That's right. And it wore people out.
It's not coming to an end like they're saying.
But do you hear people talking about the end of the world?
No, that's no longer the big thing that's coming.
Yeah, but there's no change in continuity.
What I mean by continuity is when you had families of doing a Klan, like a medical Klan fight or legal Klan or industrial Klan, there was a big interruption around World War Two where they physically didn't follow it.
And just like I gave the example of this professor with her three sons, right?
You don't think because of the change in travel, the change in freedom, the change in the continuity too much?
Because if you have to travel somewhere, you're going to travel there, right?
You're going now.
It's a difference between doing on a steamship or a jetliner.
Not necessarily.
No, because it changed a lot of that.
And see, those behaviors were very different.
Well, if you gave me the offer, a Learjet or Skype, which one am I going to take if I had to do business meetings?
Well, I would say, depending on the circumstances, I would do Skype.
I would not fuck the Learjet because you can get up to 90 people or 80 people or whatever on Skype anytime of day, anytime, anywhere where Learjet flying around the world to meet them is not right.
So if you told people before COVID that they would think you're nuts now, most people would say, yeah, absolutely.
I would do what they call network video conferences and all that.
Even a lot of court, you could record what they're not really courts, but what they call court, you could request video conference instead of going in person.
Right.
Well, if your business meeting is based on something of seriously high significance, I would say that, no, I would not restrict it only to.
Well, that's a matter of culture, because if the meeting is to exchange meeting of the minds, of course, the video is superior to the time that you'd expense.
But there are certain when I was working with water internationally back in 2010, 2011, 2012, 2013, if you did any work with people from Asia, they had to come and meet you.
And some did. They would fly over.
They even came over with a Russian guy once.
And I never met the Russian guy because they said he had such a bad hangover.
He drank so much on the plane that he slept the whole time that their time.
Anyway, yeah.
Between that and jet lag, he probably couldn't get himself together.
Yeah, I never met him.
Yeah. He took him.
Yeah. So so they had to come over and meet me face to face, which was like a three hour thing.
I'm not going to say hello.
Goodbye. You know, three hours.
And that's it. That's they're from Taiwan.
And they have to do that.
That is a necessity because it's so it's cultural.
It's so it's cultural.
Yeah. So depending on the culture.
But now the culture is more uniform.
But if it's a minor thing, right, then you don't necessarily need to see somebody in person.
It's not that big a deal.
It's a small deal.
But it does need to get done.
But if you got something of heavy significance, do you want to just take the word of whatever it is you receive?
Yeah, of course. You can do it all digitally.
I would not travel.
And as a matter of fact, I don't get on airplanes or anything like that, even though I do have privileges and other paperwork.
But you're clear. I don't.
But I have a different type of complete situation, which I've never discussed publicly.
The people that know my status and situation and the State Department paperwork I have in this and that.
But that's another story.
But the thing is, you have to admit that you are not typical.
So I'm talking about.
No, no, but this is an atypical sonic event also.
But here, let's just.
So the point is that we were discussing the only thing other than 9-11, I would say 9-11 and the Corona pandemic thing was another.
Because you're still seeing the repercussions of it four years later, just as much as you saw the repercussions of 9-11 four years up until 2005.
These are what we call watershed events.
OK, and that's fine.
I get exactly. And you're going to have more coming.
Yeah, very similar.
They're going to be religious based, by the way.
Again, coming.
So so all these things and continuity were again, all this again leans on what you it's all transactions.
Right. And all the transactions right now are being done by in a way that people don't understand that it's even it's even it's OK.
Talking about how the money system works in general is like asking people, what are their most secret sexual proclivities?
They will not disclose.
They just don't want to talk about it.
So to me, that shows that there is a strong cosmic veil.
Again, that's why I give big kudos to Brandon Joe Williams, because he's putting a lot of his effort properly done.
And he's getting thousands and thousands and thousands of people, hopefully to clog up the court system and the State Department system with, you know, using their own paperwork.
And he's has experiences where he goes with a form D-11, which is for passport and all that, and fills it out a certain way.
And you can't do that. Like, what do you mean?
And this is the law right here.
And there are people working in the State Department 25, 30 years that don't even know their own paperwork.
And they go look it up and like, oh, shit, you're right.
How can I be here for 30 years and not know this?
Right, right. So it's every field is like that, you know, same with the DMV.
So you see, again, look, when you were talking about the love of money and that's what the problem is.
Well, here's the problem altogether.
And we solve it real fast.
How do you have the love of something that doesn't exist?
Right. Well, yeah, it makes you delusional.
There's plenty of people that do that with many things.
Right. But, you know, like, for example, I'm delusional in a way that I'd like to live in a more perfect society.
And I didn't say perfect, a more perfect society where people can communicate reasonably well.
Right. And they're not annoying.
That would be wonderful.
That would be nearly perfect for me just just to be in the presence of someone for more than 10 minutes.
Anyone that is not annoying and can communicate reasonably well, not great, reasonably well.
That would be my more perfect society.
Right now, by the way, when I say annoying first is because that comes second when someone doesn't communicate or noise the hell out of me.
Now, there's no reason for that.
If you can if you want me to learn sign language, I'll learn sign language.
But anyway, the whole the whole thing is cosmically ordained to be this way.
And that's why on the last Sonic I said it's strictly very simple and strictly that we're here to waste each other's time.
That's basically it.
There is no other thing going on, just like there's nothing new going under the sun, nothing new under the sun.
If you look, if you don't think that we're here to waste each other's time, go look at the horse and carriage, how long that's been around as a main form of locomotion.
Right. Don't think that the automobile and all this stuff that's being used in all the way to whatever you want to call it now, electric cars or whatever.
That form of travel was not known of.
And right now, all this stuff, there are things still that if you have a proper library, which I don't even couldn't say, I mean, who knows what's going on?
Let's say the big New York City Public Library, because I remember by the late 1990s, they're already packing books and putting them away out of public view.
But if you have access to stuff up until 1895, 1896, you will see stuff in there up to the 1920s that still is not discussed by science, that by then was shown to be probable and very possible.
As a matter of fact, in one of the Eric Dollard YouTube videos, the National Electric Engineers Society leader stood up and said that pretty soon we're going to have electrical generation without a primary mover.
What a primary mover means, you know, when you have a generator, you got to move it with a primary mover like steam or waterfall or wind, right?
You won't need any of that.
We'll be able to have something that creates electricity or makes the electrical voltage and current we're looking for without feeding it steam or water or whatever to crank it to move.
It'll be static.
So what happened?
Yeah, something that sources from a continuous and just existing thing.
But hold on.
What he was referring to more was not like airy fairy stuff, like pulling out of the ether or something.
That's what most people would say, because the reason I'm referring to pulling out of the ether is airy fairy is because it's very, very slow.
Trying to pull electricity out of the ether is too slow for the demand that's required to even today.
What we can't do is pull out of ether.
Just like solar power.
The problem isn't with the concept.
The problem is with the amount that is required.
Efficiency.
But what he was saying was something different.
Now, the way Tesla was doing it, by the way, most people don't understand it.
He was pumping a lot of electricity into the ground and he was getting more back.
There was no free energy there.
You still, if you study the Colorado experiments, which are the most widely easy, accessible, actually the only 10% of those papers really made it to the Internet.
I've seen the more elaborate.
I've seen 50% of them.
His main problem was to how to generate enough power or create enough power and voltage to send it deep enough into the ground so he could get that return.
Right.
So it's it's kind of like what people do on the stock market.
You want to put a dollar in now.
So you get five dollars or two dollars later.
That's what Tesla was doing.
It's not ether stuff.
It's just he explained it as the ether.
But power can be the only way to get instant power from the ether is very, very dangerous is what they call nuclear detonation.
Right.
And there's a lot of stuff out there about nukes don't exist.
Yes, they don't exist the way that you're told, just like blood pressure doesn't exist.
And just like, you know, you don't absorb anything.
Right.
But nukes do exist, but they're not.
They're an electrical phenomenon.
They're not nuclear, their own category.
So to go back to what this engineer was speaking about, the head of engineers is he was discussing about making a device that would create an impulse that once it starts, it doesn't stop.
Right.
It's perpetual motion.
It's got a bad name.
Right.
Perpetual motion is something that's like a bad term that you tell someone that what you're working on is futile.
Just like excuse me, a conspiracy theorist, a conspiracy, calling someone a conspiracy theorist is a bad term that just means that you're not insane.
When someone calls you a conspiracy theory theorist, that just means they're telling you in a bad term that you're not crazy like the rest of us.
Right.
So right.
So so anyway, these things all existed before.
So what's happening?
There's a cosmic veil that's keeping everything covered.
So, again, look how long the horse and carriage was around.
Right.
And now we have this.
So what were the for all those hundreds and hundreds of the horse and carriage?
Don't you think people are wasting each other's time?
Absolutely.
And also there's the timing.
So what a better way to limit a society or let a society advance is the limiting component would be just have them waste each other's time.
And they don't know they're doing it.
They just don't know they're doing it.
How long can that go on for as long as you can?
And it's still happening today.
What will happen eventually, as perhaps in our lifetime, is there'll be a quickening, which that term is used to apply to extreme measures, by the way.
There'll be a quickening where people will realize we cannot waste each other's time anymore, meaning husband and wife, father and son, co-workers, boss.
And where all these people, everyone you interact with is wasting everyone else's time to keep things stable.
There's going to be a time where this will be lifted and people will wake up and say, what the fuck?
What's going on here?
Why are we doing this this way?
Just OK, I see what you mean.
Right. Not like show me what you mean.
I see what you mean.
Right. And everyone starts going into agreement and starts putting things together more properly and more properly to the point you realize that what the hell we've been doing here for all these years.