I think it's Sonic 117, but here we are, Greek. How are you? There you are.
Yeah, I'm here. Yeah, I just want to say I got really impressed by a fellow who sent me a PayPal,
which I don't have by the way, it's just sitting there, and a message about what he's been up to.
And it's very rare that I get impressed.
And I say, well, I get impressed by a lot of stuff. By the way, have you noticed that people that you know,
and don't know are getting dumber, by the way, and worse and worse?
Yeah, it's a little, you know, it's like they're a little worse today than they were yesterday,
but not as bad as they're going to be tomorrow, right?
Anyway, and I'm talking people you know, not strangers. Yeah, something going on.
And I want to talk about a few more things, but this fellow was not in that category at all.
He made a list of all the things I've discussed.
Many things that I've discussed that he's working on.
Quite impressive. Kudos to you.
And I reached, I just gave him my personal phone number if he needs anything.
This week is over. Super busy.
Sent me a PayPal for an hour's worth of my time.
And I don't have a PayPal account.
So this is what I want to, it's very simple. It's basically an email thing.
Someone, I brought this up about a year ago, and someone dropped a video about how to get into code.
I didn't get that video. I didn't get what, there's a thing on how to set up a PayPal account, right?
Okay, what I'm trying to do is a conditional endorsement where somewhere it's evidenced,
like if you were to open a bank account, they have a bank card that you sign.
Now it's done digitally, right?
You ask it for on paper for tax purposes.
They like it when it's for tax purposes, just to print it out.
And he says, well, we don't have it. Just go to the computer, press control P, right?
That's getting a little sarcastic.
But what you do there is you want it on paper so you can give it back to them with your signature on paper with a conditional endorsement.
By the way, banks do blank contracts.
You know, whenever you sign anything on a bank, they take your signature and put it on things that you're not aware of.
They're allowed to do that, right?
Wells Fargo was busted a few years ago for opening a quarter of a million credit card accounts that were, you know.
Yeah, it seems like fraud to me, but yeah.
Yeah, well, it's unlawful. They're not lawful.
So fraud is something in law.
That's why if you go to any attorney regarding fraud, it's very hard to prove.
No, it's actually easy, but in the legal it's hard to prove because fraud has nothing to do with anything legal.
Everything legal is a presumption.
Fraud is where the law is competent, right?
And the law is not competent in the legal, right?
And the legal is not competent in law.
There's a problem, yeah.
Yeah, anyway, I was very impressed by this fellow.
Again, I don't know how many times I can say it.
I could just be here for another 20 minutes saying I'm impressed by this fellow.
And AM are his initials.
And what I'm asking for publicly, if anyone knows how I could pretty much, when you initially sign up for PayPal,
they want address or whatever information they want.
I need to stick in the verbiage lawful money only or demand for lawful money, 12 USC.
You got to put the 12 USC, 411.
This is so important.
A lot of people, I once talked to someone and I said, oh, you want to do that because you're afraid of the IRS, right?
I'm like, what?
That's so stupid, right?
You know, that's like someone that shouldn't be listening to Greek speak.
Well, can't you just put that out on the button so that when people enter or go to actually offer something?
No, stop.
You're not listening.
Sorry.
Because the button is way after signing up to them.
You put the button, you put a bumper sticker on your car.
It's not going to help you with your bank account.
You have to do it at the initial signing point.
You have to show it at the beginning.
This is just a matter of being impeccable, right?
So most people will never get this, by the way.
So if anyone knows how to do that, because usually the easiest way to stick it in is the address columns,
the address areas where they ask you to put an address.
There's usually several fields.
Yeah, there's definitely a lot of fields you've got to fill out.
So maybe in one of the – is there a possibility that –
Yeah, but the AI checks it out in an algorithm that says that's not a legitimate address the moment you put lawful money,
only 12 U.S.C. 411.
Not because you wrote lawful money on it, it's just because it checks it against all the addresses.
Do you ever go to the post office and drop something off and you just put down the most rudimentary amount of information
that gives you all the other data that supports it?
There's networks that pull the data.
So if anyone knows how to manipulate – if there's a video personally wants to –
UncommonSenseRadio1 at gmail.com.
That's the number one, UncommonSenseRadio1 at gmail.com.
I need some help with it just – because once you do it, you can't undo it.
So yeah, I need some help to just start – I'm totally still – OK, totally against all this stuff.
One thing I wanted to go into is – did I mention I was very impressed by someone who sent me an email on the PayPal?
You certainly did.
So what I want to mention is what GreekSpeak does is it shows you very often –
by the way, did you want to add anything else to that, Chuck?
No, I'm just thinking about the problem and saying to myself, well, why not –
No, it's not a problem. It's a condition.
OK, the condition that you want to apply here.
That's right.
And I'm thinking to myself, why not just create a secondary situation where it comes out of this PayPal,
which it gets delivered there, whatever it is it is,
and then it gets delivered to something else that does take it in as a lawful transaction somewhere else,
and that way at the end of the transaction, it's clean. No?
Middleman, you can do that.
In New York, we knew a guy that ran – whose brother ran a bank.
They'll take any check.
He took 5 percent cash, any check for anyone, which was important if people were in the country.
Or you could actually get a check for selling someone a kilo of something.
You could actually pay you in a check because you don't care who they write it out to, right?
And the banks don't care anyway.
That's all Dog and Pony shows.
So anyway –
Even though they've ended –
The conditions –
Yeah, they've ended that –
That's a middleman.
What are you talking about is a middleman?
I already have several people that would do that, but this is direct to this email.
This is an email that I have control over, which is UncommonSenseRadio1 at Gmail.com.
Yeah, which means there's a way to set up a PayPal.
You can set up a PayPal with any email address,
but you're looking for a way to set it up so that automatically as soon as it enters into that –
It shows that there's a conditional endorsement.
This is very powerful, by the way.
I've seen a letter where someone was arguing with an ex-wife.
When there's a divorce, she should always file a divorce because if you file a divorce, you've got alimony, right?
So when she files it, then you kind of freeze up from them scrutinizing that.
OK, anyway, and it's different with children, but he had children.
She was a lot wealthier than him, still demanded the $1,200 a month or whatever.
Oh, boy.
He opened a bank account with a 12-USC411, and he got a letter because the state came into the bank account
and wanted to pull money out, but the bank sent a letter back to the state saying,
well, you can't do that because he already created conditions where that cannot be done.
Sorry, and he sent a copy.
If the bank does an interaction with an agency and they interact back and forth, they send you a copy of what happened, right?
They're supposed to.
Yeah, they're supposed to, and he got a letter like that, and it was like, wow, that's so powerful.
But then they closed his bank account because he was doing like $10,000, $15,000.
He was selling Harley-Davidson.
To make a long story short, I just want to say that it is very effective.
Also, I have a letter from someone that does the 12-USC411,
and the IRS basically did a tax return.
They took out like $30,000 in income taxes, and he wrote his income was zero, which it is because he showed it.
He got the full amount back plus 5%, and a letter that said basically your account is at zero with us,
meaning when your account is at zero, it means you don't owe the IRS anything.
No one owes them anything, but this is very powerful.
Instead of complaining and doing all this stuff, they're giving you the remedy.
Like poison ivy, the remedy is the white oak that grows next to it.
There are other things too.
So when they did the Federal Reserve Act, by the way, it's in the 16th Amendment.
It says demand for lawful money.
It's in the 16th Amendment, right?
They took out – they've been changing digitally some of the wordage.
If you have one in print, you'll notice the verbiage is slightly different but still just as effective.
OK.
The thing I wanted to get into is the Greek speak is a simple approach on how you could fix any problem by listening to the stuff we discuss here, right?
Any problem.
But what happens is you might expect drastic changes.
I want to give – since we're on the money subject, a real quick one.
If people demanded lawful money, there would be less fractionalization and all that.
But then you go to the next level and say why are you doing fractional banking?
And there are starving people here and people with families with children being thrown out on the street because they don't have your fiat currency.
Why don't you have them come over, sign their name, and they have enough currency for everyone and there's no more poverty?
Well, then the people that have stored billions and millions in personal wealth, that's not worth anymore because anyone that doesn't have it can go write a number on a piece of paper and they give them that amount.
You see?
Ferrari would go out of business, right?
Right.
So if a Ferrari – what is – we used to say like a Ford in the 70s, Ford Pinto or a Yugo.
I don't know what you would say now is a real basic car.
What would it be?
I don't know.
What's a real basic?
There aren't anymore.
They're all about the same level now.
It seems like that.
Yeah.
Still some Toyotas and Dodge vehicles out there, I believe.
But what – it's too specific.
If you said a Ford Pinto or a Yugo, you know exactly.
It was like the most basic.
Yeah, a Toyota Yaris or something.
So a Ferrari next to a Ferrari Yaris.
It's no longer the money that separates them because if you can afford one, you can afford the other because it's just – OK.
So now we end up going into more of a Star Trek environment where – remember in one of the Star Trek episodes, more than one, the movies especially when they brought someone in from the past.
What do you do for money?
We don't need money anymore.
Everybody just does what they're interested in.
You have replicators.
So all of your basic needs are met.
There is available everything.
Well, there's a whole string of stuff, medical stuff.
Yeah, but I mean the issue of money.
There's no more money.
So now it's kind of like – I was listening to Warren Buffett recently, who I don't like by the way because he's just a total con man.
But how can he be a con man?
Well, anyway, it's a long story.
Yeah, and Jacque Fresco was reaching for that with that idea about designing the self-contained cities that grow things and you don't have to – and therefore you can just pursue your art or whatever.
Yeah, but let me just say Warren Buffett is a con man not within his own group, which he tries to keep integrity, but within the public air.
He never talks about fiat currency and he talks about taxes and things that must be done.
But yes, they must be done if fiat currency is the entire universe.
But the people who created the fiat currency said you have a choice and the choice is clear.
People want to go for the fake stuff and suffer what they have.
But anyway, go back to the Star Trek.
Even in Star Wars, they had money in Star Trek where they built a federation.
What's interesting is doing what you're interested in doing, not a job.
Find what you're interested in.
One of the things that Warren Buffett said, he got picked up by a Harvard student to take him to a lecture and the Harvard student was asking for advice.
I want to work here. I want to work there. I work there.
So I have a good resume after a few years.
He's like, well, are you doing what you're interested in?
He says, no, I'm not. I just want a good resume.
He says, well, what are you waiting for?
Waiting to do what you're interested in is like waiting until you're an old man to have sex, right?
You don't do that.
You have it while you're young, right?
You want to start what you're interested in.
You'll always succeed if you do what you're interested in, right?
That's why so many people are unhappy.
They hate what they – let's not use the word job.
It's a vocation, what they apply themselves to every day to get fiat currency.
Hardly anybody enjoys what they do to do that.
There's very few people that do.
I mean we've all heard that you never work a day in your life if you enjoy what you do, which by the way, the Star Trek thing, I got to tell you, one day you and I need to talk about just that.
Because you're oversimplifying it a little bit and I'll tell you why.
No, it does – hold on.
Once the fiat currency notion is applied with ethics and morality, it will become – everything will become oversimplified.
Yes.
That's what I'm trying to say.
And we can do the same thing with health.
Go ahead.
Well, but the fun thing about the Federation deal is that once you go outside of the Federation, there is money in that universe.
Right, right.
Especially later on in the series, there's some extremely greedy races that try to – will do anything for a coin, right?
Right.
You got your Ferengis, right?
Yeah, that's what I'm referring to.
Yeah, which it was hard for me to watch that.
But yeah, I understood that they were like the –
The hyper-capitalist.
The Ashkenazi businessmen, a garment district.
Yeah.
They're building a garment district on Glancy Street.
They're sort of hyper-capitalist.
They live by literally something they call religiously the rules of acquisition.
And they believe in the great continuum of the material world that is out there in the universe that there's sort of a flowing river of goods and wealth out there that you get involved in.
That's literally how the universe works to them.
Well, it's like gamblers.
It's not the actual wealth and material itself.
It's the act of getting it, right?
It's the thrill.
Right, right.
Yeah, like sex is more exciting thinking about before you get to the point, right?
Well, what's more exciting, the girl that's the girl of your dreams that you never quite get to or the ones that you can get that are low-hanging fruit all the time, right?
But if it's the girl that's in your dream and she's in your dreams, you can get to her.
But anyway, let's talk about the health.
The same thing happens here.
Yes.
If people were taught that the body is a biological vacuum, which is easy to prove.
The heart does not pump, right?
Eat seasonally.
It doesn't have to be seasonally if you can control your environment even more.
By the way, if you oversimplify your diet, seasonality goes away because you only have three things that you can eat, right?
Let's say you could just eat brown rice, plums, and kale, which kale could be toxic to some people.
I've known people that—
It causes stones, kidney stones.
But anyway—
But that's the trouble is I've known people that do that and they break it down to about like three, four component foods and that's it.
I mean their entire diet is based on those things.
And almost inevitably what happens to them is something goes wrong.
Because you need variety.
We could have another discussion on how to create variety there.
But what happens now, once you understand like if there's a wound, you squeeze it tight.
By the way, you can actually do a surgery operation, a pretty big one, and not use any stitching at all or anything.
Actually do the compression deal again and it will heal very quickly.
Absolutely.
And other things like that and understanding the energy of foods and the left side, the movement of the energy on the right side.
What will happen—
And you can limit incisions or cuts.
An incision and a cut is two different things.
But you can limit incisions—
You mean surgeries or injuries?
No, actual incisions during surgeries.
Well, an incision is a precise type of cut and a cut could be—
So a surgery.
Yeah, but the thing is you can eliminate the need for a lot of those cuts by utilizing—
Yeah, just like hernias.
They used to cut open the whole front of the abdomen.
Now they just go underneath with two probes through the Canadian method.
Well, there's the arthroscopic thing and that's great and all, but there's also the use of pressure.
A lot of people don't realize just the simple use of pressure.
You can eliminate a lot of stuff even when you have to extract foreign objects that have somehow gotten buried into the body.
That's right.
Yeah, of course.
Like I've extracted—
I mean the technology is there.
Like I've extracted a bullet before pretty deep in somebody's body without cutting them at all, okay?
Isn't that funny when you try to do that?
It seems like it's moving.
Oh, yeah, absolutely.
You're like right there.
I got it.
And then you go back and it's gone.
You let it go.
But that's the thing is if you direct the pressure properly, you can generally remove almost any foreign object from the body without cutting it.
Do you know what the biggest complaint of people who've been shot—I've been around several—is?
You tell me what you observe.
Go ahead.
It burns.
Yeah, it does.
But that's usually when you're shot close up.
Yeah, definitely.
And that's the chemical reaction of the deposit of the gas on the skin.
That is usually what goes on, and that's usually the thing that hurts the most.
But you've got to extract things out of there because leaving lead and antimony and things like that are not positive things in the body.
So you've got to—
Your body will actually deal with that, believe it or not, very quickly.
Let's get back to the point.
Yeah, go ahead.
The point is, let's say the stuff we discuss on how the body works, which we can elaborate, I think, on the last Sonic.
I said we can get into several eight-hour Sonics.
But the thing is it has to be more focused than just general, quote-unquote, medicine.
Once the people understood that, obviously the current system of medicine goes away completely.
The idiots they call doctors and whatever and lawyers, whatever, go away.
They're actually put into more useful positions.
But what will happen is the individuals will be so empowered because not only that they have better health and not susceptible to the malady of an injury or whatever, but guess what?
Now they have the mental understanding that the body creates things like the replicator you kept mentioning earlier on Star Trek, right?
Right.
And now if children are taught that your body can replicate anything that it appears to need, why don't we do that on the outside?
And voila, we have again the Star Trek universal replicators, right?
Well, yeah.
We'll have that in a very short time just like we went from horse and carriage to airplane very quickly.
So I'm not talking about hot air.
Hot air balloons have always been around and airplanes were around a long time ago, but I mean in recent history.
So we all have that technology.
And then what will happen is people will become generally more intelligent.
And what happens when people become generally more intelligent?
What happens to the birth rate, especially when having a good time is promoted?
What happens to the birth rate?
Goes down, can go to zero, right?
The more intelligent the people, the fewer or no children they have.
This is proven throughout history.
So what happens then is you have a population decrease, but people are living longer, right?
So having a child is going to be a big deal.
And everything changes now because do you think when people have a child in a world like that,
they're going to go to defunct toys or a toy store and buy them little kids toys?
No.
Ain't going to happen.
There's no need for that, right?
So the entire society will change and it will become extremely simple.
And then people will actually be looking for things to do.
And I mean beyond what we've ever been looking to do, right?
So that's how it will change.
And this is very simple to do, but it cannot be done within – you need three generations to do it.
Kind of biblical.
You have to bring the notion with – not revolution.
You have to bring it in forcibly in the current situation.
Imprison or eliminate those that resist it.
And then the new generation that is born, they are isolated from those who resist it.
Completely isolation.
Even censored, like those people don't even exist, right?
They're mythological, any resistance to it.
And when they are raised, completely isolated from the resistance to what we're talking about.
Their children are similar protected, but the people that are resisting it are much older and have died off almost to the point where they've died off.
And then the people will be intelligent enough that you can actually give them the real history and why this was done
instead of just hiding it from them like what's being done now.
You see the difference?
And it's very brutal to do this.
I don't really want to be around – actually it would make me – it would give me a pretty good shit-eating grin if I saw a lot of these whatever being rounded up into camps and stuff like –
the ones that are promoting what's being promoted now, you know what I mean?
Yeah, but at the ages that you and I are at, we're not likely to see it.
No.
I mean like here in Tucson, it's very well known.
The administrators know that one of the hospitals, they killed over 2,500 people by putting them on certain treatments and ventilators.
They know it openly and they don't mind.
No one's rounding them up, right?
And the cops and the FBI and the judicial is totally behind them, right?
It's all money.
Now would you feel bad if those administrators were rounded up and put into a camp?
Not at all.
Given just bread and water and one bowl where they have to – the same bowl they eat in is the same bowl they shit and piss in.
I got no problem with that.
Yeah, that's – this is beyond forgiveness, right?
They were talking about some evil scum.
It's just like Cuomo there.
You know what?
He disappeared.
I mean what was it, 100,000 old people or whatever?
It's OK.
And then what do you have to do?
He resigned from being governor.
Goodbye.
Oh, yeah, because supposedly he was sexually touching people but whatever.
Yeah, talk about equality.
They went real hard on the Nazis and they're not doing anything to the people now.
Wow, it's even worse.
So, yeah.
So, yeah, this is how Greeks speak.
It's very simple, very simple.
But it will flip everything over.
It won't work.
We could go on and on and on and on.
Imagine just getting rid of the Catholic Church.
How many ales would go away from society just there?
Turn it into a museum.
Turn it into a nightclub.
A lot less people.
Whatever, the Vatican.
A lot less pedophiles right out of the gate.
Well, they talk about Peter Blake in Thailand.
They talk about Westerners go there and have sex with little girls.
Well, the age of consent, I think, is 14.
And the Vatican, they say, well, they had sex with an altar boy who was 14.
Well, the age of consent in the Vatican, someone could check, is 12.
So, having sex with a 13-year-old is past the age of consent.
Yeah, it's actually not a problem.
These little things are left out.
And I don't agree with that.
I don't agree with that at all.
For me, the age of majority is 20.
So, when you become 19, you're in your 20th year, right?
It's 20.
It's old school.
So, you know, some states, it's 18.
Some states, it's 21.
Right.
It's funny how it's kind of.
But when you become on the Western side, you know, on your 19th birthday, you're in your
20th year, age of consent.
Simple for both men and women.
And that's very, very simple to do.
And that's what I believe would be optimum.
Well, taking a look at neurological structure, I would almost argue that 25 should be the
proper age of majority.
You know, that is the age at which you have.
Are you trying to say that it destroys my chances of ever hooking up with a 21-year-old
now?
Oh, did I just say that?
I would say that.
Okay.
I can't even look at a 20-year-old.
No, they look like children.
They look like children to me.
Exactly.
Now, you know, look, when I was 20, they did not.
You know, a woman looked like a woman to me.
I mean, when I was 15, a 20-year-old looked great.
And by the way, I said a 21-year-old should be in her 22nd year, right?
Sure, sure.
And look, you know, a 40-year-old didn't look great to me when I was 15.
I'm saying they all looked good when I was 15.
No, I wouldn't say that.
Actually, sometimes when I go down to the university, I'd stop at a light and all the
children are crossing the 20-year-olds.
And I say to them, I say, look how unhealthy they look.
Oh, yeah.
Most of them, they look really unhealthy.
Nowadays, yeah.
Small ears.
By the way, just maybe one day right around after this.
Sure.
Constitution of the body is developed around the ear.
So do me a favor.
Go look at people on the Internet or TV or whatever that live to their 90s.
Look at the size of their ears.
They're huge, like Dumbo.
But they're in proportion.
So, you know, you don't look and say, hey, there's Dumbo, you know, with the big ears,
flaps him and he takes off.
But they're in proportion.
There's a strange proportion that happens with the size of the head, the size of the
cranium.
But they have huge ears.
People with small ears don't live very long.
So when you see people that have well-formed, large ears and their ears keep growing as
they grow in proportion, but they're typically larger than normal.
That's what you call a strong constitution.
They'll probably live a long life.
Biblically, living a long life is, you know, treating your parents, being in a good relationship
with your parents.
But physically and constitutionally, I always point this out.
If you go to watch black and white movies from the 20s and 30s, the general public,
they typically had larger ears than if you go look at what's in Hollywood, you know,
people they put on TV now.
The proportion of the ears are much larger.
And those people had a longer lifespan and more robust.
What I mean also by stronger constitution is that if they get hit with, let's say,
an incident, an injury, they'll recover fast.
If they get hit with an illness, they recover faster.
That's what I mean by strong constitution.
And it's the chemicals introduced in society and this lifestyle, and just the chemicals
in the water itself, you'll notice children and younger people.
We're talking about people born after 1960 predominantly, especially after 1970.
You will not see people with larger ears unless you go to countries that have not been
westernized like on the continent of Africa and Asia.
But yeah, let's leave it off with that.
I think the big ear syndrome, we'll talk about it again sometime.
Right.
And you know, in the future, one thing I do, you just struck on something that curiously
I was thinking about this week that you have never addressed actually on the Greek speak
that I've done with you.
And that is the treatment of one's parents.
What is fit and proper in that case?
You and I have never had that discussion because I have no...
Yeah, we could do that real quick.
It's real simple.
When you read all these things you have to do, and let's say if you're an Old Testament
guy like me, right?
And actually, the underwriting element to remember in that is that that's when you're
all living under the same law or rules, right?
So let's just use a very simple whether you believe it or not.
Abraham left his parents home because he didn't want to practice their religion.
Right.
And he abandoned, he just got away from them.
And others have done that too.
Right.
That's why he went out on his own, tried to establish himself with these other people.
Look, I'll work for you.
I'll marry your daughter.
This and that.
Beyond that.
In other words, it's better to like personally have a terrible, when they were alive, relationship
with the parents.
And instead of fostering a terrible relationship, I just avoided them.
So if I spent on the phone more than 30 minutes a year with them, that was a lot.
And it was just cordial, polite.
Hello.
Goodbye.
Because if you spend more time with them, you're going to be disrespectful.
Very easy to.
So it's the same thing.
Like if you run into someone you don't like, what do you do?
You go have a drink together and go have dinner.
No, you just hello.
Goodbye.
And anything more than this may get ugly.
So let's avoid, you know, avoid them is the best thing.
Right.
Exactly.
Avoidance.
So if you cannot have a good relationship with your parents, avoid them.
Don't go back and argue and do this.
And the other is my recommendation on that.
If you do have a good relationship with your parents, then, of course, and then you go
into what's one of those 1950s TV shows where I have to go.
Look, everybody was just fine.
Leave it.
No matter.
Leave it to beaver.
Yeah.
Then you could live that life, whatever, and you'll be fine.
It's very simple.
Maybe.
But a lot of the things you read about in the Old Testament in terms of the law has to do
with people living under the same covenant.
Right.
It's the same in every situation.
What covenant?
Remember, in early Greek speak, I used to say, when you want to get to know, ask them,
what covenant do you live by?
What set of rules do you live by?
It really shocks people because they don't know.
So if they say they don't know and they don't have one body of rules that you can go and
look up and see, it tells you a lot about them.
Tells you like, well, they're at large.
Right.
They can do anything at any moment, depending on what's on TV.
So you can pigeonhole that person very safely and make them very predictable that they're
unpredictable.
By the way, when someone is very unpredictable, that actually makes them predictable.
It's predictable that they will be unpredictable.
Right.
So you want to avoid them, you know, when you see them like running with the scissors
or anything.
Right.
So unless you live the same way.