Hey, Rated Y, and what are we on,
193, Greek, how are you doing?
We're going to hear some noise because you're
outside, maybe, we'll see.
Yeah, I'm building a deck sort of thing,
and I'm trying to make use of all
the daylight.
When you're in a swing of things, you
don't want to stop.
Yeah, ladies know about that.
Don't stop now.
Yeah, kind of thing.
But yeah.
You know what's funny?
I have a strange question that almost fits
exactly, dovetails perfectly with where you're going right
there.
So let me go there first.
Go for it.
I was going to save this for last,
but I'm going to reverse it because things
change as we're growing.
Somebody asked about emo work, right?
And they asked about masturbation.
Okay, now, you're obviously doing something that's emotional,
and if you're picturing things, you know, in
the old days, not using the Internet, etc.,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Does that relate to emo work?
Because does that do something?
Yeah, remember that.
Yeah.
That's what there is.
Remember that.
There's an emo there.
What is it?
You know, you could do your own diagnosis.
Is it giving?
Is it taking?
Is that a part of...
Well, it depends on what you're picturing, doesn't
it?
I mean...
Is it...
You know how the animals do things from...
It's the animalistic nature that wants to procreate,
right?
Is it that?
You know, because...
Right.
Wilhelm Reich showed there's a separation between the
emotional release or the mental release of that
versus just the bodily fluids and the procreation
aspect.
Right.
Is there a mix there?
I personally, this part of my life, sex
is for having babies.
There's other aspects to it.
You know, you could have a sexual arousal
and all that.
It has nothing to do with wanting to
procreate.
Right?
So it would be that aspect of it.
I don't know.
I haven't really dealt...
I haven't given it a lot...
I haven't done much mind work on it
to see how to direct such a question.
But there is a separation between the mental
health of an individual, let's say, and the
need to procreate, right?
So there's a separation there.
And then how much is the need to
procreate really separated from who we really are,
from the emotional needs?
That needs to be worked out, I think,
more than what William Reich did, because he
used it as a form of therapy.
And of course, I don't know if I
would say the times back then were more
like sexually restrictive or pent up.
I mean, that's the propaganda we get.
If you watch stuff from the 1930s or
whatever, man, are they suggestive, you know?
So I don't think they were that repressed.
I don't think there's much repression.
I think that's propaganda.
And it's more individual.
Yeah.
And that's the thing, is that the culture
shifts and propaganda shifts, and the reality is
always a bunch of crap.
Because, you know, they tell you all about,
oh, gee, you know, back we were much
more repressed in the 1800s and this and
that.
Meanwhile, if I read very carefully and just
take a look at, like, the history of
the Civil War, what they preserved, I mean,
there's a whole lot of action taking place
where people are trying to tamp down all
sorts of STDs.
People are getting the clap left and right.
They're having issues because of the prostitution.
There's huge prostitution rings.
Whole cities were taken over by prostitution rings
during the Civil War.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, yeah.
Of course, mining towns and, you know, game
towns.
But it's not, you know, look, if the
prostitutes, it's like saying they got food poisoning
because they ate at restaurants.
But I'm not making a judgment here.
I'm just saying, just think about this, because
this is part of the propaganda, not that
you're putting it out, but it is laden
with it.
Like, well, they had STDs because of all
the prostitutes.
No, that's like saying they got food poisoning
because they ate at restaurants.
You get it?
It's the same exact thing.
So in other words, the reason why you
get food poisoning in restaurants is because of
how the restaurants manage themselves hygienically.
The reason there was STDs because of prostitutes
is because they're dirty hoes versus clean hoes.
No, I get it.
Right.
I was just pointing out what I found
in the documents, what they were saying.
The Department of the Army was saying this.
The whole thing.
Yeah.
That has to be rethought.
And I've never really given enough perspective from,
let's say, what can be said about the
entire sexuality thing.
I've just lately just put a cap on
it and say, hey, if you're not interested
in having babies, get away from it.
It's not necessary.
But there is the arousal part.
There is all these other things.
Yeah, that has to be considered.
Because we live in a society that promotes
sex, which means the birth rate will go
down.
And it is, right?
But that's the thing.
It is a serious consideration in emo, though,
because there is a strong proclivity toward this.
I mean, I know that nowadays there are
people that claim to be asexual and this
and that and blah, blah, blah.
But the thing is, it is a key
component to somebody's emotional structure, I think.
Well, the ones that are like that are
the ones like protect the children.
And it turns out they're the ones that
are actually molesting the children.
If it's put out in the mainstream, it's
the opposite.
The moment I see somebody screaming about, you
know, pedophiles over and over and over again,
it's like either they're the ones that are.
Yeah.
Either they're a victim.
Right.
Exactly.
That kind of thing.
So, you know, they say, well, I'll just
throw something in there.
I don't even know if it's online anymore.
Oh, the Vatican molested a child or whatever.
It was a boy was 15 or 16
or 14.
You know what?
The age of consent that the Vatican is.
I think it's twelve.
Thirteen.
Okay.
I was thinking thirteen.
But twelve or thirteen.
Yeah.
So, you know, these things are propaganda.
There's by the way, I discovered a YouTube
channel looking at it.
I don't really fully endorse him, but he's
a good listen.
If you're familiar with stuff I've spoken of,
it's called Middle Nation Shaheed something.
OK.
Used to be a professor or something.
And he talks about Middle East and how
the world is abandoning the West and all
that stuff.
I talked about 15, 20 years ago, how
it's coming into fruition.
I mean, he's new on this and he
can make some very valid points from a
good, fresh perspective against the propaganda.
So because it's not right or left.
And he is correct about, look, you want
to clean up a society, make them Islamic.
I didn't say they should be, you know,
clean them up because religion goes into every
aspect of your life if you take it
seriously.
Now, recommending someone to become Christian is just
ridiculous.
That's just like everybody go get a lobotomy
and get on that.
So my stuff, you know, whatever.
No, that's just that should be like never
even considered or done.
Now, if you say from a social perspective,
convert people to Judaism because they have laws
and rules and all that.
No one face it.
No one wants to be a Jew in
this world.
Still, you frown down or whatever.
Now, the propaganda shows that, by the way,
most people think I'm Jewish because I say
I'm an Old Testament guy, including most of
the Greek people that I meet.
They equate it all the time because of
your mentions of the Old Testament.
They say, oh, you must be, you know,
a pseudo Jewish.
And yeah, he thinks that a lot of
these Greeks I've spoken to, which is like
two or three, say that I'm a Jew
that just happens to know some Greek that
calls themselves the Greek to hide it.
And it's the opposite.
Right.
I'm not hiding that.
You know, I'm not Jewish.
I don't have to hide.
Anyway.
So beware of Greeks bearing gifts and beware
of Greeks bearing comments.
But anyway, beware of anybody.
If you go Islamic, you have the rules
and you have a certain composure where there's
a priority on your behavior.
Actually, it's very misunderstood, you know, and it's
actually not bad.
It's very submissive.
You know, the word Muslim means a submissive
right to be a submissive, submissive.
So that is a good thing for a
temporary fix.
I don't know how you could put a
religion.
Has it ever been done?
Put a temporary religion on people.
You got to do this for 10 years
or 20 years to fix your society.
I don't know.
Probably.
Yeah.
It seems like people personally do that a
lot of times, you know, they go through
a time period where they're kind of hell
raisers and then they find, you know, religion
for a little while, they always say.
And and then after a while, everything sort
of levels out again.
And it's not all about the religion and
AA and everything else, whatever.
I've watched people go through that cycle.
Interesting.
I looked at this Middle Nation channel.
You're talking about the guy who looks like
I hate to put it this way, but
I hear I think of it as part
of black YouTube at this point.
He looks.
No, no.
He looks like the architect in the Matrix.
Yes.
That's the guy there.
But he uses the symbology here of like
with the the black, the black, the red
and the green and white all together.
I'm not familiar with that.
That's a that's a West Asian, African, what
do you call Southern world colors?
Yeah.
But anyway, I just want to throw it
out there, because a lot of the stuff
is stuff that I spoke about a long
time ago and he fills it in with
current affairs.
Look, I'm not endorsing being Muslim, but but
I'm not endorsing being any religion.
But his point of fixing and cleaning up
like, you know, you don't get him.
You don't get impoverished becoming Muslim, actually, because
it's a form of communism in a way.
Right.
The no interest in this.
That right.
OK.
Well, shouldn't you say that?
That's not true.
It's not a form of communism.
I was going to.
If you turn Christian, you're going to be
impoverished because the Christian religion is a rich
man's religion.
I was the rich people funded because the
main point is you can do anything.
All laws are done away with.
And guess who you get?
Where are you going to get your laws
automatically from the rich people at the state?
Also, it tells people, don't worry about acquiring
wealth here because your wealth is somewhere else
up in the sky.
Right.
So it's perfect.
So they don't have to invest in control
apparatus.
The Christianity is so that the minimum investment
in the protection apparatus for the elite minimum.
Right.
So and it's the most hypocritical, totally hypocritical,
hypocrisy.
So when the elites say the absolute something
is absolute in the next day, change it.
They're not called them hypocrisy because the people's
religion is based on it.
So anyway, if you want to degrade and
demoralize the people, it's Christian.
Right.
Well, look, what did they do to the
native cultures in the state?
Right.
Right away.
Make them Christian so we can get rid
of them.
Right.
Very interesting.
Because you get rid of you basically wind
up surrendering all possessions because your real possessions
aren't here.
They're in the next life.
So don't worry about this.
Well, the main thing is that there is
no law.
There's no law.
But, you know, you have to have some
order.
And because the law has been done away
with subconsciously, they put in the state's laws,
which is all commercial.
Anyway.
And, of course, you've got to do what's
Christianity without Sunday.
You know, there's the Seventh-day Adventist and
all that for Saturday, but it makes you
a strict adherent to the Pope's work schedule.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
It's terrible.
Well, here in the South, not necessarily because
you're going to church all different days here
in the South.
I mean, you got church Wednesday, Thursday, every
day, all the time, you know.
Yeah.
But that's that's because, again, the hypocrisy.
You know, you got to it's about people
have a lot of energy.
And if you don't give them something to
do, they're going to do what they they
might actually educate themselves.
So what else you got?
There you go.
OK.
So somebody did.
Here's a random thing.
If they asked, have you checked out any
of the Zen cooking books from the Oshawa
Foundation?
I don't know what that is.
Do you?
Never heard.
I've heard of Zen and that is actually
a pretty good mindset, but not the not
one that gets advanced in for Western cultures,
which it is more of a Western thing.
But no, I haven't checked out those cookbooks.
OK.
The main thing about food is think about
it as a car.
If I put this fuel in the car,
is it going to gunk up my engine?
Is it going to give me the power
that I need?
Is the engine going to run rough?
Is the engine going to run smooth?
Right.
Is it contaminated?
You know, water and fuel is a contaminant.
Right.
So think of it, not that you're burning
anything.
People think of food on the daily, even
on a park daily, like, well, this is
what I have for breakfast, what I have
for lunch, what I have for dinner.
And that's it.
But, you know, what you ate yesterday for
lunch is still mixing what you're eating today
for lunch.
Right.
In some capacity, energetically.
The main thing.
Let me just make a little interjection here.
Total segue into something.
Laundry.
I've been a laundry buff my whole life.
And if anybody here, especially guys, well, women
also, if you notice that your clothes, even
though they're clean and dry, you put them
in the closet, you think they're fresh and
you get this sense of B.O. and
you use more soap and the B.O.
is still there and all that.
I've done some experiments because I've been playing
around with soaps and this experiment lasted about
two years.
And there's something about biodynamic emergence where things
emerge.
Now, they say they find bacteria that cause
these odors.
So the body odor, which is the bacteria
are found, but they're now come from somewhere
else.
They emerge from the chemistry and the energy.
So when you use a particular soap and
you like it for a long time, the
chemical constituents in that formula is going to
breed a particular bacteria that's going to give
off a certain smell.
So the way you fix that is by
changing soap simply like, for example, give an
example.
I have like some dress shirts that they're
casual shirts, you know, button up and all
that long sleeve, you know, and no matter
how much I washed them, they had B
.O. And I said, OK, this is an
emergent.
In other words, something is starting to grow
here that it gives me an unpleasant smell.
It's, you know, it's just like it's supposed
to smell fresh and it doesn't smell like
body odor even after doing a triple wash
on it with extra soap and rinses and
all this other stuff.
Immediately, as soon as I switched to soap,
I went from powder to a liquid or
a different powder or whatever.
The B.O. in the mildest clean went
away and it's gone and it probably be
gone for a few months to a year.
Then it will return if you continue using
the same soap.
So my advice to fresh smelling laundry is
it's not one of those things, you know,
like a cigarette brand.
You know, I've been smoking camels for 40
years.
It's the only one I like.
OK, laundry, you know, or I drink just
Pepsi or Coca-Cola because that's what I
like.
I'm a, you know, I'm a Miller guy,
you know, my whole life.
No, no, no, no, no.
That doesn't work with laundry soap.
You must change laundry soap brands now.
It's important.
I'm saying brands because each brand has its
own distinct formula that even though they seem
the same, they're slightly enough different that each
one will emerge a different type of condition
where you will have a body odor in
the clothes that does not go away.
And I am so happy.
I am so happy because I got to
the point where all the clothes were clean
in the closet and I have a pretty
good ozone machine and I kept ozonating and
it just made it worse.
I was like, what am I going to
do here?
You know, I don't know what I ever
said.
Hey, your clothes is B.O. I smell
it.
That's enough.
Right.
So and I just want to share this
with people, because if you do notice a
closet of someone or yourself, the clothes are
all fresh and clean, but you still have
this body odor.
Just change your soap.
I think every three to six months, go
to a different soap and that will go
away immediately.
That's why this is a big achievement.
I mean, it doesn't take much to make
me happy.
So this made me very happy.
Oh, fair enough.
Look, sometimes the smallest things.
Right.
Oh, my gosh.
Yeah.
Anyway.
So.
All right.
I did the thing about the cookbooks.
Home clean.
OK.
Home cleansing.
The idea, you know, people that burn sage
and, you know, do prayers and this and
that.
Well, they're not.
That works.
All that works.
But.
OK.
It's just like the laundry soap.
When you do something, you ever go to
an old person's house, has that old person
smell.
Right.
Guess what?
Because they're always doing the same exact thing.
They set the clock.
They have to eat the same food at
the same time.
Right.
And they do all the same stuff.
And that from that condition emerges the stale
whatever.
And the things that are happy in that
stale custom environment will stay there.
So when you burn sage, it's like the
laundry thing.
You just change the entire condition and whatever
made itself at home now has to leave.
Right.
Now, you might say a logical mind might
say, well, now you're inviting the entities that
bring the sage.
Yeah.
That, too.
But at least you're not in stagnation.
It's really to stop stagnation, stop mental, spiritual,
physical.
Well, they were spiritual stagnation is bad also.
Of course.
And they were asking a couple of things
like, is there a particular time of day
that's best to do this?
Well, think of it this way.
The time of day when you ask that
question, it's a loaded question because the day
ends at noon.
Mm hmm.
All right.
Right.
So time of day is do you want
to do it at the end of the
day, at the beginning of the day?
Well, if you want to do it at
the end of the day, you do it
right before noon.
You can start.
You want to do it at the beginning
of the next day.
You do it just right after noon.
Well, I was just going to say you
could do both and cover it because it
could take you, you know, say 10 minutes
if you start at five minutes.
And you covered both.
Yeah.
Then you cover both.
Would that not be a good way to
go?
Or that would be the best way to
go because you've covered two days in one
shot in 15 minutes.
So you actually it would be an hour.
It'd be the first hour, last hour.
Yeah, I would do it.
I would do it around then or at
night when it's dark out late because that's
when the ether is the most compressed and
you're going to get more bang for your
buck.
Well, see, that was the thing I was
going to ask you about, too, is that,
you know, would it be better to do
it then?
Because this is when spiritually things are more
quiet.
I hear you.
It's all right.
Oh, yeah.
Let me let me move around here.
No problem.
We have someone that's got dogs that doesn't
know how to take care of dogs.
They don't know that dogs have different voices
for different communications.
So you get the most bang for your
buck a little before noon and into a
little bit afternoon because that's covers two days
and also at nighttime, late at night when
the ether is the most compressed.
Well, see, like, you know, for most compressed,
but also we talked before about there's sort
of less traffic because there's less, you know,
going on.
So people are more.
Yeah.
The airwaves are cleaner.
So that would that would be another time.
But what do you think?
Later noon.
Yeah.
Late at night.
And late at night would be midnight.
Ten, eleven, twelve.
One, two.
OK.
Anywhere between there.
And some people, if you work in a
live in a community that people get up
early to work, they might wake them up
in the middle of night, call, you know,
like, what the hell is burning, you know?
So you have to adjust it for where
you live.
And also, you're not I'm not at home
at noon because I got a job or
you're either way.
Yeah.
So, yeah, that's what I.
Oh, by the way, there's research that's been
done.
I have to dig it up.
But when the spirit leaves the body, it
takes longer to leave at night, right, because
it's denser.
Everything's compressed.
Right.
Then someone who dies in the morning or
around noon where it would just fly out,
right, because everything's expanded.
More suction in the atmosphere.
Yeah.
I know ether.
It covers physical and spiritual, you know, mental
and physical.
Right.
Like I noted, quite honestly, that in the
single numbered hours of daylight, right in the
early morning is when I would know most
of the time this is when people died
of old age and things.
Well, regardless of when you die, this the
the the spirit leaving the body, like if
you study, like, for example, this is a
hypothecation and ease.
The people that had most more detail are
the ones that died when it was nighttime
because they hovered over the operating table or
wherever, saw themselves and the ones that had
less to say, because they really flew away
and had stories where they were a way
away.
It was more when they died during the
day.
OK, very simple.
This is all simple.
Universal principles apply to everything the same.
So when something is expanded, what are the
qualities of something expanded, what a rarefied right?
Thinner.
What are the qualities of something compressed and
condensed, denser?
It doesn't matter if it's physical, mental, spiritual.
The same thing goes with thought, spirit, everything.
Universal principle is just that universal principle would
be someone who is a technical software and
hardware guy for video.
He knows everything about the program, the digital
video, including how it's going to manifest on
the screen for people to view.
It knows everything about that.
That's how he knows how the machine works
and the code.
And he knows how it's actually translated into
an image.
That's right.
That guy.
That's what universal principle.
That guy's the most people I know.
I just do software or hardware, you know,
some hardware.
Right.
And the guy who does hardware doesn't know
software.
See that?
That's the slave stuff.
Right.
So.
That's that's how you keep it compartmentalized like
they do in intelligence work.
OK.
So with that, you know, it's kind of
funny.
I have one other question, but just one
weird thing.
Yin and yang.
Right.
Is there a particular like to apply that
to the time of day?
Well, how about that?
Expansive and contractive.
Yeah.
So during the day, it's expanded at night.
It's contracted.
So nighttime is young and daytime is that's
I mean, I'm just pointing it out is
that I'm just right.
I mean, because we were going to give
it to you and it's lean because the
sun is very young.
So it creates a yin effect.
Right.
Just like, for example, fire is very young.
But when you heat something, it expands, which
is yin.
Right.
And it becomes something that's becoming right.
And because it has heat in it, but
it's more young, even though it's a balance.
So when you put fire, which is young
on a piece of metal and it expands,
that's a yin reaction.
But the metal takes on that heat, which
makes it more young than it was before.
But it's also more yin because it expanded
state of balance.
And that's when you work with metal.
That's why, for example, people that cut copper
all day and plumbing or whatever, I said,
you know, if you have that copper at
86 degrees, it'll cut so much better.
They're like, oh, come on, it's 78 in
here, 86 degrees to make that much of
a difference.
I'm like, yeah, try it.
They're like, oh, my gosh, that's a big
difference.
Right.
Because everything has this little sweet spot.
That's true.
Right.
So.
OK, so I have one more universal question,
but you had something else that you wanted
to bring up outside of the laundry or
just the laundry.
That's a major thing.
I mean, that thing is like if you
ask me, what's the most exciting thing I've
discovered in the last six months, it's that.
Well, another thing, though, just about the laundry,
quick question is I had this problem and
I threw a bunch of different things at
it and I'm not even sure what finally
solved it.
But the machine had a smell that I
couldn't get rid of that was putting it
on all the clothes for a while.
And it wasn't B.O. It was something
else.
And I don't even know.
The machine itself is not self-cleaning.
They get very dirty.
machine that you have changing the bearing where
you have to remove the drum and disassemble
all the wet workers and see how scummy
and shitty it is.
I have made a small high pressure nozzle
hose, quarter inch hose that goes between the
inner and outer drum.
And I spray just toilet bowl cleaner.
You don't want to use acid.
It's a strong acid, but you do it
quickly.
If people that put vinegar in their in
their wash, that's OK.
But if you do it often, all the
rubber hoses and seals will disintegrate very quickly.
I discovered this a long time ago when
I used vinegar and a pressure spray bottle
was pump spray bottles and it dissolved the
diaphragm in three days, turned it into black
powder.
Oh, crap.
So good.
The washing machine people don't tell you that
because it's a three to five hundred dollar
service call.
They like doing it.
It's an easy job for them to change
the drain hose, the internal one.
But yeah, you have to clean the washing
machine.
I use steam.
I have a very hot water and a
very fine nozzle that goes through the tiny
little holes in the drum front loader, top
loader.
Top loaders always work better because of gravity.
You think.
Yeah.
So I'm very I'm disgusted at washing machines
because when I grew up, washing machines were
30, 40 years old, still working now every
five years.
You've got to get one.
It doesn't matter if you spend five hundred
bucks on one or two thousand.
Yeah.
And that's the consensus.
Someone would say, oh, I have mine for
10 years.
Well, that's a rarity.
Right.
Yeah.
At this point.
Right.
It's like someone saying they're married for 20
years.
You know, it's a rarity.
Right.
You look back at grandma.
Grandma had her, you know, her knives for
for 40 years.
No problem.
That's different.
The reason why.
Well, knives could last a thousand years.
But what I mean is the washing machines,
they've decided to really work with the big
department stores.
Yeah.
So it's a it's a it's a long
story, but it's pretty easy to figure out
once you do a little research.
It's another story of planned obsolescence.
Right.
I mean, like you and I.
Yeah.
It's definitely planned obsolescence, like the printer that
stops working because you made too many copies.
Yeah.
Like you and I.
It's an electronic command of the iPhone that
I'm using.
Yeah.
Like you and I talked about the iPhone
just before we started recording and it was
like your iPhone's not working now too well.
So yeah.
Anything other than the telephone will not give
me it will not give me a tone
no matter what.
And if you go to adjust the tone
setting, the button is disabled like it has
no effect.
They're pretty shitty company.
I mean, pretty bad.
They're all pretty shitty.
They're all, you know, there is no Apple
or Android or Microsoft or whatever.
Samsung.
They're all the powers behind.
Once you have a business that goes over
one hundred and fifty million dollars a year,
you've surrendered it to the the oligarchy.
They take control of it.
Complete control.
I heard from someone who's been in business
for a while now, it's as little as
five to ten million a year.
You make sure that they got a pretty
good sense of what you're doing.
I'm talking about full control of the company.
Wow.
So so, you know, everyone's on board.
Right.
So so I've only got one more piece
of feedback input question here, and it's kind
of a weird one.
But they were listening to some of the
early ones and you talking about, you know,
I'm just here taking notes and this kind
of thing.
And we talked in early on about what
would you do if an alien showed up
or this or that?
And they didn't get an answer in this
in this listening to that about, OK, what
would you say if someone did literally show
up and they just happened to drop in
front of you particularly?
They want to know.
And they said, look, we just discovered this
place and we want to take notes.
We want to observe what's going on here.
Where would you send them?
What would you tell them?
This is the question they have.
Well, can you hear me?
Yeah, I can hear you because there you
go.
OK, I just lost the head for a
moment.
Sorry, you're good.
You have to rephrase.
Just paraphrase it.
So if someone showed up and like I
said, as a rescue mission to get the
Greek out here, I mean, no, if somebody
showed up and all they said is, look,
we just discovered this place exists.
Oh, you mean a real I mean, someone
who actually saw the advertisement I put out
and answered it and we just found this
place.
What do you want to tell us?
Well, what do you want to tell us?
And also, where should we go and what
should we see to take no place?
So where'd you come from?
Wherever you came from, go back and leave.
You know, it's easy.
I said that before.
There's a billboard on the back of the
moon.
This is your last chance.
If you pass this, if you see if
you can read this, you'll probably be visible
by surface-toiling earth inhabitants, which are morons
with very little exception.
So our recommendation of the council, Intergalactic Council
or whatever, as we found through many years
of experience with these idiots, that the best
thing is to turn back and do not
engage in anything.
If you do engage anything, you say we'll
confuse them.
So you can enter at your own risk.
Yeah.
They have a very toxic environment.
Kind of like they don't.
Yeah.
So kind of like a warning beacon they
put out in Star Trek, right, where they
go, OK, we don't want anybody to go
near this planet or the system.
We're going to put out a beacon here
that says this place is dangerous.
Don't go.
Yeah, there wouldn't be much.
The first thing is leave.
There's nothing to learn here.
And you want me to prove that?
Look at the ask the inhabitants what they've
learned here.
And it's kind of like if you want
to know whether you should vote or not,
have a five minute conversation with a voter.
You've heard that something like that.
Yeah.
You know how dumb they are.
So the same thing.
There's not much here.
No, no.
And don't be fooled by the beauty.
Like the people.
You're not being fooled.
You take it in.
That's why, like people go to prostitutes.
It's a momentary whatever.
And then you go on.
It's a moral.
There's a moral issue.
There is no moral issue with saying, I
like how beautiful the flowers look and smell
and how beautiful the sunset is and all
that and the beautiful things or whatever here.
But that's just small and temporary extraction, like
a snippet or a thumbnail of what's going
on here.
The the real truth that I keep saying
this is I've spoken to several people and
advise them.
In other words, people, especially during the Obama
age, they were retirement Obama age.
Yeah, it was the Obama years to go
off the grid.
They thought the country was going to tank.
And I said, no, it's not going to
take.
It's actually going to get a resurgence and
get ultra conservative.
And it's going to the Middle East is
going to be the anyway we're going to
be more isolationist.
And they said, if you go off grid,
everything's going to cost five times as much
all your fuel and energy.
And you'll notice that everything in nature wants
to kill you.
Yeah.
And like two or three of them came
back and said, yeah, it's just like that,
man.
It was beautiful, but it sucks.
Everything wants to kill you, everything, the bugs,
the animals, the environment.
Yeah.
So it's a constant thing.
By the way, one thing I want to
interject that I haven't gotten into much is,
you know, the seasonal attitude or the seasonal
outline of how affairs happen, like spring is
building up, planting, planting, planting.
Summer is building up and growing.
Fall is tearing down.
Harvest winter is a time where you don't
plant and grow and tear down.
It's an in-between time where you do
things that you couldn't do or didn't shouldn't
have done while you were planting, growing and
harvesting.
Right.
So give an example of that.
You know, spring, you plant your seeds.
Summer, you grow and have some summer harvest.
Fall, you have your main harvest.
You take care of all your of your
business debts and income, whatever.
And then the winter is when you put
a new roof on your house, you fix
your wagon, you go on a long trip.
Right.
This is the agricultural basis for life.
So from a basic societal point of view,
stuff that happens in the spring is planting
something that will probably grow in the summer.
And things that happen in the fall are
tearing down events.
That's why every financial crash is always in
October or September.
And that's also when people are harvesting, because
that's when the financial crashes happen.
That's when people really make their money.
But yeah.
Yeah, that also it's also tearing down.
Right.
Wintertime is when the really weird shit comes
up.
Like, you know, somebody did something weird.
Like, you know, India launches a satellite into
space like India.
I mean, they they still have a caste
system with untouchables and the curry.
And how the hell do they sell a
satellite?
What?
So anyway, you'll see these patterns throughout.
So I didn't talk much about the fuckery
going on this spring.
I didn't get a sense, like with covid,
they announced the Federal Reserve and the treasurer
announced covid on the Passover, the biblical Passover,
not the Jewish one.
And like 9-11, the one that happened
in 2001 happened on the Day of Atonement,
the biblical one, not the Jewish one, meaning
the 10th day of the seventh month.
So covid was announced on the on the
13th day, the end of the 13th day
of the first month.
And that's not January 13th, dickheads.
I mean, the people are trying to tell
me, well, that means this.
I had a message from someone who's like,
you know, the Bible says what it means
and means what it says.
If it's the 13th day of the first
month, it's got to be January.
I mean, total retarded shit sometimes I get,
but not much, by the way, for the
thousands of messages I've gotten, I've gotten maybe
two or three memorable, really dumb asses, which
is excellent.
That's like point one point zero one percent.
That's pretty good.
I wish I could say that.
Yeah.
Oh, my gosh.
I'm actually blessed completely.
Like, you know, I shouldn't use that word
either, but you know what I mean?
I endowed with a very responsible listenership, but
the fuckery going around this spring, we're in
the middle of spring now on summer.
We had 100 degree temperatures for two days
in Tucson, broke a record like 10 degrees
above the historical record.
I wonder if anybody's doing weather work in
California.
But anyway, I'm not.
I could be to mitigate it.
But the fuckery going around in, did I
say fuckery?
Going a medical term, going around this springtime
and all that.
The main thing I didn't notice anything threatening.
But I did notice that the there was
a big move to do this tariff thing.
Right.
A middle nation does talk about the tariff
thing.
It's just to isolate.
And, you know, it's really interesting in how
stupid people are.
Manufacturing, it supposedly protects the American wherewithal and
resources here nationally.
All those were cut.
All the.
What do you manufacture?
Well, all the factories began to be shut
down in the late 60s, for sure, in
the 70s and 80s.
Yeah.
And the only thing is little cottage industry,
a little mom and pop stuff, which is
what Covid was supposed to get rid of.
And the tariffs are going to make it
even harder because the big businesses know how
to use bills of exchange.
The little business guy does not.
So if a little guy that does a
quarter of a million in business a year
gets bills that are 50 grand, he's out
of business.
He doesn't know how to handle those bills.
He sees it as something he has to
send out using from the earnings from his
business.
They don't understand that the big corporations, they
have private accountants and attorneys that know how
to use bills of exchange.
You know, there's no money.
Right.
So just the way you write a certain
paper makes it money.
That's why I keep saying, how can Apple
be worth a trillion net?
Because that means that everyone on the planet
would have to buy at least a thousand
dollars worth of Apple products every year.
I sure as hell I don't.
I don't.
So it's all bills of exchange, negotiable instruments.
So combined with the high tariffs and the
small business, people don't know how the money
system works.
So when someone sends them a bill for
a thousand dollars, they think they have to
take it out of the income that they
earn.
They don't know that that bill is actually
a check.
You know, I mean, it's ridiculous.
So for their own ignorance, we'll put them
under.
Yeah, I just see a slow turndown, more
more of the what you saw COVID do
is what the tariffs are going to do.
But in a different way, it's a small
business to business in general.