Rated Y 131.
That's the number.
That's the time.
I guess.
Anyway, what?
You know what?
What time is it?
Greg?
What is the proper day?
Oh, well, the time, the day, you know, I'd have to I'm kind of losing count.
We're into the first week already past it, I believe.
So I could I could do my I could show you my account right now.
That's fifth month.
Fifth.
Right.
Yeah.
What do you think it is?
I shouldn't hold you to it.
You don't.
I believe it's too much.
Let's see.
I think it's the fourth day, but I could be wrong because it's the sixth.
It's the sixth day.
See, I'm wrong.
OK.
Yeah.
So rough.
No, it's not the wrong.
It's a matter of observation.
Who has a better observation and not knowing is fine, it's just basically that's how it
rolls.
I reckon the the full moon was the last full moon was Saturday, Sunday.
Right.
Night.
So.
So basically the.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
So Saturday noon was the first day of the month.
So it is still the sixth day.
It's so it's the sixth day or seventh day.
I really do give you a count right now.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Actually, we're in the eighth.
We're in the eighth day right now because it starts at noon.
Sorry.
So it's the eighth day.
Wow.
I was way off.
OK.
And I went and I was a day or two off because I was I wasn't, you know, it's what they call
the weekend.
And I thought it was Wednesday.
Oh, wow.
And I went to go to some industrial supply places.
They're just Monday through Friday, like the real hardcore places.
They open at six and close at four.
You know, it's just for.
So I'm like, oh, my gosh, what are they going out of business?
Why are they closed?
It's like it's Saturday.
Yeah.
I had no idea.
It was Wednesday.
I'm like, oh, my gosh, this place didn't go out of business.
It's only nine a.m.
They should be kicking.
Now, you know, they've been open for three hours.
Why are they going out of business?
And I asked him, are they out of business?
He says, no, they were open yesterday.
So, you know, what they started doing is determining if they weren't making enough business.
They didn't want to keep the overhead there.
So they started cutting down on employees being present.
And then therefore, the hours have to come down.
So, yeah, these these places that I go, they supply to the trade.
So let's say it's a welding shop that supplies welders and ironwork.
Not too many people go there to browse.
If you're there, you know exactly what you want.
And the other thing is a lot of that's going to be, you know, phone orders or over the, you know, over the internet.
Exactly.
When you want to check out, you go to the service desk.
It's called.
Not the checkout, right?
Yeah.
But I mean, you go there and you can call them up and then pick up your stuff.
You know, which is something if you're in the area.
So, yeah.
And, you know, this stuff.
Here's the thing.
Living in Tucson is way better than any place.
It's the biggest little city I've ever lived in.
In other words, I'll give you a quick story.
When I was doing Spring 2.
Oh, actually, I found the Twitter and Facebook stuff that someone else set up back in 2011.
So we're hanging around Spring 2.
Oh, yeah.
And it is a water bottling.
We were selling an arrow one and a whole bunch of other places.
Rossum.
And then I stayed out there almost half a year.
And that's when you were like the $20 bottles of water.
Right.
Yeah.
I was at an apartment off of Romaine and Santa Monica Boulevard.
Nice.
But, anyway.
It's too bad.
But, yeah.
So, what was interesting with all this is we needed what's called a diaphragm pump.
A Flotec one liter per minute high pressure diaphragm pump.
So, a guy I was working with.
Anyway.
He's like, yeah, I've got one.
I did my research.
Found it on the phone.
So, we get in the car.
We get on I-5 for like a half an hour.
And I'm like, where the fuck are we going to get this pump?
You know?
And he's like, oh, we'll be there in another 20 minutes.
I'm like, where are we going?
Why does it take so long to get anything here in L.A.?
You know?
And I finally end up near Pasadena.
And you walk into the place.
And the guy wants $300 for it.
We're like $275.
I'm like, you've got to be kidding me.
And he says, let me show you.
You know.
I said, no, no, no.
I get that for $90.
There's no way.
It's more than my cost.
So, go check your cost.
So, he goes and he brings his wholesale book forward.
And on the cover of the wholesale book, it's Tucson Wholesale Pumps.
Which is the place I go to and get it for $90.
So, I understand.
He says it costs $150.
I understand he has to cover.
It will cost him that much with the shipping and all that other stuff.
I walk into Tucson Wholesale Pumps and walk out the door.
Right?
For $90.
And how long does it take for me to go there to get that pump from where I am?
15 minutes tops on a bad day.
Right.
Now, from one end.
You know, from the part where people lose the industrial side to the industrial side.
I could find anything here.
It's an anomaly.
Within 10 or 15 minutes from where I live here in Tucson.
L.A., it was like either you can't get it or it's a two-hour drive and it's four times the price.
So, that really nicks.
L.A. and California is not a good place to live if you are an inventor.
You do research and development and all that stuff.
Unless you do it for the government.
You know, some base.
You know, whatever.
Oh, yeah.
Somebody doesn't care if they're shipping things in from everywhere.
And it doesn't matter.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
But California is not good.
It's not good for an inventor or somebody who's researching and needs to get stuff all the time.
And there's a line of work that I do.
There's various things that I've discussed.
And it's also not like New York.
Because in New York, it's just a matter of do you know the right person?
All you got to do is know the right person.
You can get anything in New York.
And it's only 20 minutes away at most.
In New York.
Right?
I mean, even the worst of the worst stuff.
If you had to go to Jersey.
Well, if you needed stuff like that.
Like Brooklyn, Navy Yard area.
Lower West Side of Manhattan.
Yeah.
Because that was where the docks were.
Oh, you go over by the.
Supplies and places like that.
Yeah, you go over by the fish market.
And there's warehouses over there.
You can get anything.
Yeah.
You just got to know.
Fortunately, I never had to go to Jersey.
I went to Jersey a couple of times.
Actually, bike racing and other visiting stuff.
I like the better parts of Jersey.
The parts that are far away.
The parts that are closer to Pennsylvania than New York.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
Like Morristown.
Not Morristown.
Tom's River.
Well, Tom's River is actually on the eastern side of the state.
But here's the thing about Jersey.
You can drive across the whole state depending on where you are.
In 45 minutes maximum.
30 minutes on the skinny part.
You can go from the ocean to Pennsylvania.
No problem.
Yeah, that's what I mean.
It's a small state.
But Tom's River is actually on the eastern side.
It's over there right by the Atlantic Ocean.
Next to Long Beach Island and Seaside Heights.
But when you just get over the tunnel or the bridge.
You know, George Washington Bridge or whatever.
Right.
It's all right.
Yeah, I mean, it's fine.
A lot of Jersey.
The coast there in Jersey, by the way.
I do remember this from back in the 90s.
You see, you know, the Palisades right from Manhattan and all that.
Those neighborhoods tucked in.
There's all intelligence agencies from all over the world.
Yeah.
And allegedly, you know, in little safe.
I'm talking about safe houses.
It's not like a center.
You know, it's not a campus.
No, no, no.
But that's true.
Yeah.
They have safe houses.
Like in other words, every intelligence agency in the world has a safe house somewhere along
that Hudson River.
You know, George W. Bridge or whatever.
Yeah.
Very interesting.
Well, you know, I won't say it out loud, but the reason is because you can meet up with
the criminal element and the intelligence element right there in Jersey.
They happen to cross over.
Did I say that out loud?
I think I did.
But yeah, that's the truth of it.
That's a matter of fact, even the guy that they caught like afterwards and they couldn't
figure out why this criminal was nearby when JFK was killed.
He's got a Jersey connection.
It's hilarious.
And these guys all end up in Jersey at some point because it's funny.
Yeah.
Anyway.
So you got any questions for tonight or nothing really flying by?
Well, you know, I didn't see any heavy questions.
I want to thank Mr. McFadden, though, because I meant to thank him last time and I didn't
get to it.
And I just wanted to say thanks a lot because not too often do people even acknowledge me
and I appreciate it.
So I wanted to acknowledge you.
All right.
And moving forward.
I did notice it in the chat.
Somebody mentioned something about aliens.
And I know you and I had to talk about this a long time ago, like about these concepts.
And of course, it was in the news just like it was last year, the year before.
Maybe maybe it's been two years now where that guy went to Congress and said, look,
you know, we got aliens and this and that.
And then everybody.
It's not what.
No, no, it's always going to be the opposite.
The reality of it and what you what they're talking about.
You know, government.
Who are you from the government?
Government.
Yeah.
They don't know.
It's always going to be the opposite.
It always was, you know, up until FDR, FDR, maybe a little after they were quite honest.
Like, you know, when the U.S. was bankrupted, FDR did his fireside chats on the radio every
night.
And if you listen to those fireside chats, he's asking, he's pleading with the people
to participate in the new system.
We need you know, we need for you to volunteer.
Right.
That's why when you're 18, they send you a W-9 form.
Everybody.
Oh, you have to fill out.
You don't have to do any of it.
So after FDR, where they captured most of the population, they got very comfortable about
just flipping everything.
Like I said, it's part of the control mechanism.
If they put out a bunch of bullshit, most people believe it.
How much do you have to invest in the control system?
You don't.
They're getting the quote unquote powers that be have it real cheap.
You know, even though they're spending billions or trillions on the propaganda, they don't
have to put out a Stasi or secret police so much, you know, or, you know, enforcers like
like other times in other places.
You know, the control apparatus is very cheap for them.
Just the media.
Yeah.
Just put up bullshit.
You don't have to put out brown shirts anymore.
I mean, it's just not necessary.
Brown shirts or black shirts.
Right.
And yeah.
No, none of that.
But, you know, with the brown shirts, actually, they were gray shirts first, the technocrats.
Right.
And they swear.
And they lost just like the Russian revolution.
It was a white revolution and became, you know, once they were done, they got rid of them
with the red revolution.
Right.
You know, it's just like now it's going to happen with all this woke stuff that they
did to unsettle everyone.
They're going to go after them.
You know, the actual same.
It seemed like the establishment was going woke.
Now the establishment is going to go anti woke and very racist.
Right.
With a religious flair to it.
You know, of course, I've always said for years that we're going to go into an ultra
conservative viewpoint because eventually, you know, use biblical law as the law
directly improperly.
So you're going to see that.
But you're going to go through a type of almost almost almost as bad as when you go
to a donut shop, they'll have two windows, one for blacks, one for whites.
It's almost going to get that bad.
And you're like, that sounds really crazy.
Those, you know, like the days down south, you know.
Yeah.
It's going to get that.
They're going to create a not race war, but animosity.
You know, you know, war.
You can have animosity and not have war.
And you can have war without animosity.
Just propaganda.
We're going to start seeing a lot of racial stuff coming up now.
Big time again next few years.
We got it now.
I mean, it's really right now.
It's just that it hasn't.
It's not in your face.
See, like the woke stuff was around since Obama.
People don't realize that.
Of course.
Yeah.
So so maybe when you say we got it now, maybe in that sense.
But no, it's going to get pretty bad.
That worse than it's been in, let's say, 50, 60 years.
Look anymore.
There's a big difference between what is on the ground in most of places.
OK.
And what they're telling us is on the ground in most places.
That's the thing.
You know, like the impression they keep giving about, you know, there's crime everywhere.
There was always crime everywhere.
But in fact, it's actually not as bad as it used to be.
And they're making it sound worse.
You know, this is always the manipulation.
Right.
You get people nervous.
You get them worked up about stuff.
You point to a couple of bad examples and you make it seem like it's happening everywhere.
It's like, you know, the summer of George Floyd, the whole country was on fire, according to some people.
And it was not.
It was not.
And look, being in Brooklyn, like off of Vanderbilt, Pacific and Underhill Avenue there back in the 80s, I had a shop where we did industrial.
We did artistic sculpture and stuff.
And the landlord pretty much let us stay there for free because he was like a white landlord.
And he knew that if no one occupied the building, the chances are someone will throw a brick through the window and light the place on fire.
So it was better for us to have one of the top floor and make it look like it's called occupied so that people don't burn.
Anyway, there was every week there was someone being gunned down in the street or like some serious stuff.
Like a guy walking around with a knife sticking out of his side for like half an hour.
He couldn't pull it out.
It was that deep.
None of this, by the way, none of this stuff made it to, quote unquote, the news at all.
Underhill Avenue.
And yeah, this is called the border of Brownsville and Brooklyn in the 80s.
And very, very rough.
I have a quick story I'm going to count.
I could tell you back in the late 70s, early 80s.
Actually, I'd say it was 1980, 1980.
I kind of left home.
I was 15.
I went on my own and tried it out.
And this guy, Richard, a Jamaican family, took me in.
It was actually him, his brother and his mom, single mom.
And it was off of 140th and Convent Avenue in Harlem.
But you and I were in the same neighborhood in 1980 then.
Because, yeah, OK.
And I stayed there for about a month.
But this is the interesting part.
When I came back to Park Slope or other parts of Brooklyn and I told people where I lived,
they thought I was going to get killed because I was living in a black neighborhood in Harlem.
But I used to go to the Boys Club over there.
I used to go to the Boys Club over there because that's where business got done.
Anyway, please, go ahead.
So it's a big hill on the side.
Everything is...
It kind of gives you a feeling.
You don't even feel like you're in Manhattan when you're there.
No, not at all.
It feels more like the Bronx or something.
So anyway, the apartment off of there was a huge apartment.
And when you go through the long hallway to the entrance to get back, to get up,
I found that if I...
Instead of going on the front of the street,
if I went through the back of the other street, through the alley, real short,
I could go through the back door and the elevator was right there.
It was really quick instead of going through the entrance way.
So one day I'm going where I was staying.
And I go through the back door and it was never really locked.
And I opened the door and there's about three or four guys, black guys,
I'll just say it that way, melanated,
sitting at the step.
They were rolling an L.
And they saw me and they dropped the L, they dropped the weed,
they dropped everything and ran.
Because they thought I was, you know, Tracy or something.
I got you.
By the way, the nickname for 5-0 or police was Tracy.
Right?
So...
Even...
When I went over to the more Jamaican neighborhood,
what was that?
It was sort of like a Jamaican enclave in Harlem.
It wasn't Harlem proper, as they told me.
But...
Some people called it Little Haiti, but yeah, that too.
Yeah, it could be.
And when they saw me walking down the street,
you hear the Jamaicans,
they go, John Wayne in the area, man.
John Wayne in the area.
Right?
That's a white guy.
Yeah, meaning me.
John Wayne is to the Jamaican crowd,
is the police called John Wayne.
And he's the white guy, he's the sheriff.
Yeah, the white guy, yeah.
So I'd walk by them,
John Wayne in the area, man.
And by the way, I know it doesn't make sense to call Little Haiti
when there's Jamaicans around,
but trust me, that's what people did.
No, that's rough.
So Haitians are very rough.
Yes, they are.
And you can't tell.
I mean, I remember I met some Haitians
and the guy was like, you know,
kind of like olive toned, green eyes,
you know, kind of brownish hair.
Yeah, very mixed.
Very mixed.
And he introduces me to this guy
who's really dark skinned and tall
as his brother.
And I'm like, how could that,
you know, you guys don't look anything alike.
You know?
But anyway.
So, yeah.
So here I am.
My white friends think I'm going to get killed in Harlem.
And the people in Harlem think I'm the police.
And I mean, these guys,
they just, you know,
they drop the weed, they drop the L.
The L is a joint or a blunt, you know,
people, I don't know if you,
that's old school.
I don't know, do they even use,
do you ever heard that terminology,
calling it L?
Well, I used to hear it called a J a lot,
but L, I guess.
Drop the L.
Yeah, anyway.
You could roll a L, right?
Or a Dutch.
Or a White Owl.
Can you skill me in L?
Yep.
Yo, son, can you skill me in L?
That's because it's a loose L.
E-L-L.
It's because it's a loose cigar is what it is.
And then it ended up being, you know,
but then Lucy's ended up being the cigarettes.
So why would I walk by
and they dropped everything and run?
Right, why?
Because they're going to kill me?
No.
So in other words,
I'm bringing this up.
It's an account.
And these are stories you can even create
off of these accounts and expand on them
in several instances where
I was like, oh, maybe I'll get killed,
but I don't care.
If I get killed this way, I deserve it.
I must have done something stupid
and I shouldn't be stupid.
But I noticed that, quote unquote,
they were afraid of me,
who they are.
Melanated people, the Jamaicans
and the American black people
were not afraid,
but they didn't want.
It's like, you know,
we're doing something that you
shouldn't do in front of the popo.
You shouldn't do it in front of him
because we don't know.
So, oh, my gosh.
And, you know, and I went that was a
really that was a very good adjustment
for me coming from, quote unquote,
middle class, upper middle class,
almost white neighborhood
where, quote unquote, dark people
were dangerous.
I found that when I went to their
world, I was dangerous.
Right.
Oh, my gosh.
And that was good at 15.
I learned that was that set me
better off because most people
quote unquote white people will
never, especially mid suburban
America, whatever, will never
figure will never figure out what
I just told you.
Ever.
They'll go through their whole
lives thinking you go to a
neighborhood of dark skinned
people, you're in trouble.
See, they that's how they spend
their life.
So it was a very good adjustment
and I would very often share this
throughout my life with people
when they ask me about race
relations and things like that.
So, no, it's the misunderstood
part of it, you know, at least
that's the way it used to work.
Now, I got to tell you, things
have shifted.
It doesn't quite work that way
anymore.
This is before rap culture.
Right.
In other words, there was no
thug. There was rap called his
grandmaster Flash.
Right.
The Furious Five.
That's about it.
Yeah.
But I mean, this is just guys
talking about how great they are,
you know, with a record.
I mean, there's no subculture
didn't come out yet.
We're just to be, you know,
because.
Yeah.
It was just straight up going to
beat somebody down, going to
grab some.
You know, it wasn't that it was.
I knew.
Yeah, I knew it was going to go
not to blame Wu Tang, but
they made it really dark.
We were riding our bikes on
Canal Street going across to go
to the east side, get the
Brooklyn Bridge.
This is about 1990.
And says, yo, let's go down and
get some tapes.
Wu Tang.
They're there tonight.
You know, whatever someone
tapes and sell tapes every
Thursday or whatever.
So I heard a sample sounded
terrible, you know, like no
fidelity.
And I don't know one of the
guy.
He's like a guy.
This is how it sounds.
It's good for you.
It's good for you, man.
You know, and this is before Wu
Tang was anybody's
anything.
You know, you were selling tapes
on Canal Street for ten dollars.
Right.
And I had one up until I moved
to Tucson, original from them,
because I don't think they hit
the scene till ninety two,
ninety three, something like
that, maybe even ninety four.
I don't know.
That's when they got big, you
know, but they were on the scene
around 90, 89, 90.
Yeah.
But prior to that, the L.A.
thing was bigger.
The West Coast, you know, was
bigger because they had better
production.
Bottom line, they did.
They had better sound.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, they did.
Yeah.
It's about for me, it was sound
quality.
And, you know, was it something
that had, you know, was it
cogent?
You know, it was understandable
and pleasant.
You see what good music is, what
sounds good.
If it doesn't sound good, it's
not.
It's genre comes second for me.
If it sounds good, it is good.
But anyway, we got off on that.
I think because it's going to be
some bizarreness coming in the
future, it's all unnecessary.
Pretty much everybody gets along
just fine.
And I think I've also mentioned
in terms of race relations in my
life, I've run across some
prominent, but fairly prominent,
quote, unquote, black people
that were wealthy, well
established engineers
and things like that.
And they've told me the
other side of what is it?
I think I've gone over this
before.
The affirmation.
What's it called when you have to
hire minorities?
I don't like that word, but
not for me.
Not
affirmative.
Affirmative action.
Yeah.
That was not because they were
disadvantaged.
It was because they noticed that
the white middle America,
middle aged white man running
industry and all of business was
kind of incestuous in terms
of that culture was going to fall
apart and they were going to lose
their edge.
You know, the banking, the
industrial, especially industrial
design, engineering,
all these white guys
working and running everything.
You need cultural infusion.
So they wouldn't do it.
They wouldn't hire people
that weren't white.
You know, big engineering firms,
engineers in Detroit, you know,
big insurance companies, you know,
all this stuff.
The tops of, let's say, the tops
of industry, you know, they just
hired white guys out of, you know,
good schools and never hired
people from, you know, East India
or melanated people or,
you know what I mean, or Asians.
Never.
So when the affirmative action
came out and gave incentive,
people think it was to assist a
disenfranchised group of people.
Right.
This may be one way it can be put.
Yeah.
And it has nothing to do with it
at all.
What it had to do was preventing
this white culture from imploding
on itself, put in some extra,
extra, let's say,
extra cultural,
extra traditional values
and ways of looking at things.
And it did work.
And I got this from a guy who was
a civil engineer.
He's one of the two or three guys
that designed, which I'm not happy
with, was the I-10,
that big route around Georgia
and Houston, Texas, all the
highways there.
OK.
They laid all that out.
And it was a big project.
You know, like if you go across
and you have to go through Houston,
you have to go through Atlanta.
Right.
So when you're driving.
So it did all this stuff.
And he made me aware of how the he
was no.
He was in his late 70s 10 years
ago.
But he let me know basically how
white America and industry and
business was imploding on itself
because it needed some flavor.
You know, it had.
Right.
Just a bunch of white guys
couldn't figure something out.
That means it can't be figured
out. They need to bring in a
brother or somebody, you know,
somebody from another culture
that has a different way of
seeing things.
And it does.
It is important.