Rated Y, Sonic Event 34.
That's the way we mark it.
And Greek, how are you doing?
Hey, pretty good.
You know, I was thinking about the 33 Freedom of Sonic reference, so I just want to bring
that up.
I think we're going to talk about sex, computers, and free energy.
That's what's on the mind.
Nice.
I saw in the chat.
I saw in the chat, somebody said, oh, you guys like they had the idea that you might
skip 33, like, like, you know, how they skip the 13th floor in hotels.
I always find that funny, by the way.
Yeah, they're actually they're well, yeah.
But that's another discussion.
The 13 there is OK, the 33, by the way, is free Masonic.
But there's really three levels in Freemasonry.
And I might have to be checked on this.
But once you become a master mason on the three levels, then you go over to what's called
Scottish Rite, where they have the 33 plus levels, right?
So it's really Scottish Rite when they talk about the 33, not Freemasonry in general or
the craft or what have you.
I just want to bring that up.
We didn't really touch on that much because, believe it or not, the most of them are just
there to get together and take photographs with stupid aprons and have pork in the springtime,
you know, big pork roast and all this other stuff.
It's just a social club now with the Freemasons, I've noticed typically we see a well-dressed
person or whatever.
It doesn't hold the door for anyone, doesn't ever smile in public.
You follow you notice to get into the car, don't follow them.
But if you notice they get into the car, they got the little G with the compass on the bumper
sticker, right?
Another Freemason, right?
So this is where it's become where it used to be helping people.
So well, to a certain degree, see, because years ago you had guilds.
So if you're a carpenter or a plumber, painter, whatever, and you were hurt, you couldn't
work to support the family.
Everyone else chipped in the guild, right?
And it wasn't only for that.
This is very commonly known.
What the guild also did was it upheld the reputation.
What I mean by that?
Let's say you're in the carpenter's guild and you hang a door falls off and you refuse
to go back and make it right.
It's not just that one carpenter or a mechanic or whatever that you hear now, watch out for
this guy.
It was actually a stain on the entire guild.
So when the guild got word that this carpenter didn't hang the door right and didn't go back
to make it right, they went back and made it right and admonished the one who didn't
do it.
Right?
Right.
It is cut both ways.
It's like a social insurance.
Yeah.
And it also cut both ways.
I mean, this is like I used to know guys who did house painting and they had a general
place where they would gather on occasion and you know what?
Some guys found more work than others for a while.
They might split work and go, okay, you know what?
I got jobs I can't do.
How about you do them?
And when you have extra jobs, you come back here and you drop those off here for other
guys too.
They would do that.
And that's like the more common use of something like that.
Well, this is different.
This is very, very, very different.
What's common now is just each man for himself because it's what people don't realize that
all the countries are running under state of emergency, right?
Because in their laws and bylaws and codes and statutes and rules, when there's a declared
state of emergency, they can bypass certain procedures and do certain things.
And the state of emergency is essentially that the, how would you say it?
All the government's ability to issue currency has gone over to a private group because the
government screwed up.
And it was, of course, deliberately.
Now, here's to go back to the guilds.
What's interesting about that is now, like you were doing some stuff with mechanics,
right?
Yeah.
Or I know someone who was doing stuff with plumbers.
And it didn't work out very well.
That would have been very different in certain societies in the past.
The guild would have made it well.
And that person who did whatever trade represented the guild would have been, let's say, sanctioned
for it.
Right.
So this is way, this is way off the way we think today.
Now we look for they have like Angie's list, you know, for hiring people, you know, go see
if this guy is good and who is and who's not, you know, Yelp or whatever.
You know, to rate tradesmen, let's say.
This was that system back in those days, but it was active, not passive.
What I mean now, the system is passive where, you know, you look up, like you mentioned
a painter, a guy's got one star and there's 20 people complaining.
People now say, oh, avoid that guy, right?
Avoid and find one that's rated higher.
But that's not.
And they ride.
They just let it ride out like that.
And it's OK.
People don't understand how these guilds had structures.
And they were indirectly associated with people who did the craft.
But you mentioned a couple of things that when you were speaking about the painters
and the work and all that, a few things flashed through the mind, by the way.
You know how I feel about attorneys or because I know them.
I.
Well, here's the thing.
Many people form opinions on things they've read, seen on TV, right?
That's why they have all those government and cop shows on TV.
You know, so people think that that's how it works or court shows.
Judge Judy, whatever.
Oh, yeah.
Of course.
Yeah.
And it's total opposite.
It's because they know that they're there.
They get impressions from that.
But long story made short, I know a billionaire growing up when he was growing up, he he's
actually an oil and gas and controls a large amount of helium production and other things
like that.
He was a depression baby, post-depression baby, like in the southern part of the U.S.
and to the point where they had to go through the garbage and find old shoes and boil the
leather to get something to eat.
And as he became adolescent, he decided to start doing some paint work.
So him and a friend of his and another friend of his, another friend of his restored this
big Victorian house.
They worked on it for three months and the job came out well.
And the the owner was an attorney.
And the day he came to settle with on the project, the attorney comes out, says, you boys did
a great job, greater, better than I expected.
But I'm not going to pay you one dime for what you did.
And I'm not going to pay you a dime for anything you did for it to be a lesson to you in life.
Hmm.
Interesting.
I just wanted to share that, by the way.
Yeah.
Because, right.
It doesn't make sense to most people today.
Right.
But back then it made sort of sense.
It's like, well, on several levels.
Right.
You could think about it.
Yeah.
No, I get it.
But like I said, you know, there were times I saw this, you know, some years ago, a couple
of decades ago that there was still kind of an active element commonly with people that
would share work, like I said, and actually did behave sort of like the guilds of old.
But they're not really the guilds of old.
They kind of had some of that stuff still going on, but I think it's been just about
completely eliminated now with the age of, like you said, Angie's List and Craig's List,
you know?
Well, before that, like you said, that age is over.
Yeah.
It was in The Mob when you had a problem with someone, you went, you didn't deal with it
on your own.
If a certain family organization had jurisdiction, you went to them.
Right?
You see it in the movie, The Godfather.
Yeah.
I used to see it in real life.
It was very simple.
Well, yeah, exactly.
I've been around it.
I'll give a story.
It's a true story.
I opened a bike shop in Brooklyn, and it was a high-end, whatever.
And of course, you need garbage disposal.
Here we go, right?
And waste disposal.
So I call up.
There's only one, you know, no matter who you call, they're all going to send the one
who does that neighborhood, right?
Right.
Yeah.
So this guy gets out of a car.
He's like six foot four.
It's springtime.
He's wearing a leather coat.
Goes down to his ankles.
Hair greased back.
Vinny bag of donuts.
Hey, Vinny, get the IROC, kind of guy, right?
Okay.
He stomps into the shop, and he says, it's 700 a month for garbage.
That's it.
And he stomps out.
And I'm like, oh, I remember the people before paying like 150.
Right.
So I knew someone who knew someone who knew someone, and I told him what was going on.
And he says, what kind of store?
A bike shop?
Yeah.
Listen, I got a I got I wanted to get back in and riding my bikes for my wife, my family
children.
I'm going to bring us some bikes over.
You take care of them for me.
So he brings over like four or five bicycles are completely dusty, like they haven't been
touched flat tires and everything.
Right.
So leave them here.
The next day, the tall guy with the leather trench coat storms in.
He says, OK, I'm really sorry.
It'll be one hundred and fifty.
One hundred and fifty.
OK, bye.
Yep.
Right.
So you see, like the typical, quote, unquote, America, oh, I got to call the Better Business
Bureau.
I got to.
Oh, whoa, whoa.
It doesn't work that way.
I was just thinking of that.
That used to be, again, when when you and I, I mean, again, we're similar in age.
So, you know, when when we were kids, that was a common thing.
Right.
Oh, you got to call the Better Business Bureau.
And yeah, that's not.
That's part of them.
You ever see.
What was the movie where the fight club where he goes to the police?
Oh, yeah.
And I don't know if you remember the film when he says, you got to stop this guy or
whatever.
And then the police run around.
They said they said you were going to say it, say this, whoever says this, we have to
cut off their balls.
Right.
Police now are holding them down.
This is an amazing sacrifice, sir.
We can't believe that you're doing this to test us.
Yes, we'll take care of it.
Yeah.
It's even the cops.
You see.
So this is exactly how it is.
The military is for hire.
Private.
You have enough money.
You could call the who runs the military bases.
Each military base has the oh, gosh, name escapes me.
It's not the big quartermaster or whatever, actually.
Yeah.
It's the provost.
Marshall.
There we go.
That's it.
Yeah.
And and you give him enough money, he'll send an F-16 to drop a bomb on someone's house
or shoot it with a missile.
And then what you'll see on TV is there was a gas explosion.
And if the cameras get there too soon, you see the gas company unloading old, dumping
old pipes on the ground.
Right.
To make it look like.
Yeah.
And this is actually from a real event that happened in San Francisco more than a decade
ago.
Well, sometimes you get a warning like, you know, you could persist with this kind of thing.
Accidents do happen, you know.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Speaking of accidents do happen, we're just talking about computers.
You know, you got a wonderful family.
It would be a shame if something ever happened to them.
You know, just saying.
Oh, no.
Of course.
But speaking of accidents, computers, I wanted to just bring that up.
I was saying speaking people that are into computers don't get anything for the past
six years.
Don't get anything that has a hard drive.
You have an SSD solid state, all solid state.
Right.
That's the way to go.
Because the reason why is you mentioned also having backup.
Well, if the safety mechanisms and protocols sense that the hard drive is not up to snuff,
you won't won't be able to turn it on to access anything, the external drives or anything.
So the hard drive is the thing to avoid anyone buying computers or whatever.
And the other thing was data, how to protect it.
Well, many places in Europe, they don't send data through a different line.
They send it through the power plug.
It's called broadband.
Right.
I said, let's let's talk about this before we started recording.
So we are now.
Well, right.
Because actually, I just had to swap out the, you know, the little electrical plug that
I have for my mixer.
Well, it finally burned out, you know.
So I kept the past couple of times I bought new mixers.
I kept the old the power plugs that were never used.
So I just came in.
You're on the side.
Yeah.
Because.
OK.
The mains cord.
Every so often they burn out, you know.
So.
Yeah.
It means they're not.
You should always.
If they tell you you need a certain gauge wire, go one gauge heavier.
And also the equipment.
Last year, I see someone running a power tool, a thin extension cord that creates excessive
amount of arcing and damages the brushes and the motors.
It's even worse with electronics.
If you're into high end audio, there's a craze now with power plugs like just the six foot
power plug that goes from the wall to the amp.
There are four or five thousand bucks.
Right.
The way they're made.
Well, I don't have a bunch of those, but I do have the ones that are, you know, actually
matched up correctly to the manufacturer's specs and all that kind of stuff.
And I've got like three of them.
You got to do better than manufacturer's specs, usually is what I'm trying to say.
It's kind of like the nutritionist specs, right?
Oh, I got you.
Think of manufacturer's specs as like nutritional information.
But I've got them here so that one day I'm not just caught like, oh, that burned out.
Now I can't do anything.
You know what I mean?
So I do have backup parts, so to speak.
So I just had to get one of those off the shelf.
That's all.
Yeah.
So so on the computer thing, when the power sent broadband like that, I had found out
about that a long time ago when there was a big push for fiber optics.
And then they said, well, why do we need fiber optics?
We could just keep the old copper wires, just do broadband.
Right.
In other words, increase the frequency sees an actual and other things have to be increased
as well.
So this is the the aspect with computers.
It's very, very simple.
They're serving as garbage technology as usual.
And you have to make a choice.
Well, no, you have to make a decision.
Many people think decision is they have to make a choice.
It's the decision.
The choices are many.
The decision decisions are few or singular.
So I just wanted to put this out because I also have an SSD now laptop for about a year.
It's a pleasure.
You turn it off, goes off, turn it on five, four, three, two, one.
It's on.
Right.
Ready to go.
None of that stupid stuff with the magnetic hard drive and whatever.
So I just wanted to bring that up.
That would be, you know, instead of just looking for a computer like I am right now for someone
and maybe for you as well.
It's much harder.
You know, if I just wanted a computer, I would have had five of them for, you know, 50 bucks
each, you know, fairly new computers.
But they have hard drives and it's like shame on them for still putting that crap out.
Right.
So anyway, I'm looking for that.
The so I mentioned sex, didn't I?
I want to get into that again.
Well, you did.
I have a question about emo stuff, though, because it came up in an email, if you don't
mind.
Go for it again.
I like to feedback.
And by the way, we are checking the chat as well.
The chat's very interesting.
Somebody recently talking about the Sabbath and how they observe it and things like that.
A bunch of things going on.
And also, our friend who likes to cook potatoes on the stovetop appreciated that he was mentioned
in.
He said, Sonic.
Oh, cool.
Yeah.
He's been we've been in touch be through Skype texting and all that.
I enjoy him very much.
He did do the blue tape around the light and keeps the bugs away with a little bit of blue.
Yeah.
I don't know if you got that.
But yeah.
And also, I have got feedback from him and others regarding the driving.
When you pull on the steering wheel slightly, it changes the entire feeling.
One message was it went from an SUV to a sports car just by pulling a little on the steering
wheel.
Well, that's interesting.
I can't share that because I don't drive.
But anyways, the interesting thing, though, was that somebody asked about preparation
for emo work.
What do you do before you do the emo work?
Is there a general sort of way that someone should, you know, prepare?
Because most people that that's, you know, attempt to talk about this kind of stuff will
tell you about.
Well, first, you got to get yourself ready.
And this is what you do.
And they often tell you about meditation and blah, blah, blah.
You know, so it's not necessary.
I'll tell you why.
Oh, no.
I'm just relating what's in the email.
That's all.
But go ahead.
No, I get it.
I get it.
The the whole thing that I want to lean on very heavily, a double underscore emphasize
and air quotes, whatever you want to say is very important.
The way that I discuss the emo and what it is has absolutely nothing to do with anything
else out there at all.
The reason why is because what I'm trying to emphasize is the purpose of emotions.
That's it.
Now, if anyone wants to attach preparatory elements, ritual or whatever to it, that's
fine.
But what I'm saying is it's amazing how we live in a society that everyone sort of talks
about it.
But no one acknowledges its purpose.
And and it's and the way we do that is by looking at its effects.
I mean, I don't really know.
But what I've surmised is thus about the emo work.
Now, just to fast forward about prep, though, a lot of the techniques and things that I've
mentioned that you can implement when doing the emo work is independent of time, independent
of distance, right, independent of many, many things that we consider to be psychophysical
or just purely physical.
Right.
So if the emo works independent of time and distance, there is no preparation necessary.
It's sort of like prayer when you do it properly, right?
Prayer can be done ritualistically and also with intent to whatever deity you subscribe
to.
But it also could be done with none of that.
Like you fall off of a ship and you're drowning and you say, help, I'm perishing.
Right.
So it can go either way.
I wouldn't say, no, you don't have to prep on that.
But I'm saying that it's not necessary because it's it's it works beyond time.
It works beyond distance.
And it's sort of like it affects the psychophysical first, meaning the spirit, the mind physical
together first, then to the physical.
Right.
So we'll get more and more into it.
But I wanted to anything else on that, because I wanted to just fill in a couple of things
on the subject and bring up a new subject.
Yeah, there was one more thing and then and then I'll shut up.
But it was pretty simple about manifestation.
Right.
And, you know, look, sometimes emo is just about changing a general circumstance.
You create an atmosphere and you don't have a direct intent necessarily.
You just want to improve things.
They were saying.
And then in other cases, it's not going to work.
It's not going to work.
General general statements are generally ineffective.
OK.
It has to be very specific.
Once, you know, everyone is going around, you know, everyone's doing the emo work constantly.
If you watch like a frog trying to get a fly, right, he's like, I got to get that fly to
hold still just for one second.
Right.
So they're all everyone is doing.
It's just that no one is acknowledging it as it is.
Right.
It's much like water.
Water is involved in everything, even if you're not focused on it, you're dealing with.
You know what I mean?
So, yeah.
So back to it.
They were saying, you know, OK.
So general, you address done.
But when you're attempting to manifest something in particular and let's just say you're you're
you're wanting to attract a particular individual into your circumstances.
This is what they asked.
And this isn't about, you know, relationships or trying to, like, you know, cast the love
spells like there's a whole bunch of people on the Internet to try and tell you about that.
Right.
How do you attract the proper mate?
Well, here's what you do.
And they give you this whole, you know, very, very there is no attraction either.
That's the whole thing.
Everything is a push movement.
But go ahead.
Well, I'll get into that.
But that's the thing is, how do you push from a distance to sort of attract something, for
lack of a better word, to attract someone into your life from a distance?
How do you do that?
Easy.
That's very easy.
Imagine that they're already there and you're feeling and living as if they're already there.
And that's that's very simple for a lot of people who are older.
Let's say they've been in several relationships or have more experience.
They infatuate, fall into infatuation with someone.
They feel great.
They're on cloud nine for whatever.
And then after a while, it's kind of like this person's annoying.
Right.
So or you don't think about them that much anymore.
On and on.
So when you understand that and you understand that possibility, let's say, when you want
someone to, let's say, attract to bring someone in, you imagine as if you're already living
that way with that person there without the annoyances, without the negative aspects that
would lead, you know, to another desire, which would be, you know, another person now.
Right.
So what what makes bringing another person into your life satisfying for you not only
momentarily, but also long term, how it has to do with how you live, what culture, your
mindset and what you're doing.
And the thing is, what you're doing should always be based on what your goals are and
your goals should be minimal.
By the way, I know this sounds crazy, but you know, it should be minimal.
You know, big goals like I want to make the world a better place.
That's that should be absolutely minimal.
Right. Right.
Of course. And that's the thing I'm trying to address this because they did ask a specific.
So I'll drop the last part of this with a specific piece where effectively there's
someone that they had in their life at one point and they are now no longer really in
contact with them, this kind of thing.
And what they want to do is draw them back.
And, you know, a lot of people experience that, as you say, you know, you get old enough,
you've had someone in your life, you've lost track.
There was a problem, whatever.
There was some sort of struggle between you or there was a difficulty and they've gone
away. Now they've been away for a while.
And you'd like to bring them back.
And they were talking about using the email to say, you know, reintroduce somebody who
was an old friend or who was a family member who now, you know, the two of you, because
of geographical changes or whatever, are drifted apart physically.
But you'd like to bring them back into your your sphere, your daily.
And I got you.
That's more extreme than someone that you don't know yet.
You try to stay in the middle, because when you get in touch with someone that you are
that is not with you deliberately, it'll get more extreme.
It could be extreme, like extremely subtle.
Like if you haven't spoken to them a long time, you get in touch with them like, oh, I
was thinking about you for weeks and months.
I'm glad you called. Or it could be I told you I'm with someone else.
Leave me alone. Right. It's no more this moderation in the middle.
Right. Like, hey, let's meet for coffee at three o'clock.
Right. It's not like that anymore at all.
Right. Oh, yeah. You know, we're just going to have a coffee, even though we have no
relationship anymore. We'll catch up, you know, this.
But yeah, once you've had a relationship, it's now it's going to be on the left swing or
right swing. It's not going to be in the middle.
You know, like when you first meet someone, you know, you try to be in the middle.
Right. So how about coffee?
What do you like when if you already know those things about that person?
So it's going to be extreme.
So the first question is, are you prepared for extremes?
The second thing is, what are your options?
Right. In other words, you have options, choices.
And one of the choices, have you decided on absolutely bringing this person in?
Right. Because here's the thing about the emo.
If you're wishy washy or doubtful, it doesn't work at all, at all.
You have to be very sure.
And sure is, again, more emo work.
In other words, when here's an example of it.
There's you know, if you've when certain perfumes and colognes were in vogue 20 years
ago or whatever, and someone now wears one and you smell it brings you right back to
20 years ago, listen to 80s music or whatever.
Right. Yeah. OK, so.
All right. So you have these attachments, that's all emo.
In other words, the the this remembrance of that scent is not the emo.
The what the what the remembrance does is the emo you see makes you feel like you're
back in that time. Oh, yeah.
Like, you know, every once in a while I catch a whiff of this is going to sound funny,
but I bet you you'll know what I'm talking about.
I catch a whiff of something that reminds me of remember that aquanet hairspray crap
that a lot of women had on, you know, in their hair in the 80s, like it seemed like it
was everywhere. I can't say for sure, but yeah, I get it.
Well, I was like a cellophane chemical kind of plastic smell, but it's sort of
fragrant. But it also had me.
Yeah. It also had like almost a fragrance to it that was almost perfumey also.
Well, what's weird about it is that that reminds me of, again, being in the late mid
to late 80s in Jersey, you know, women with big hair in Jersey in the 80s.
Yeah, of course. You know, also the sunrises.
So, you know, that was just the circumstance.
But I smell that every now and then I think back to that.
It throws me immediately emotionally back to being a teenager and going, oh, I remember
this when, you know, women wore sandals and, you know, you know, the example is not
remembering the smell.
Not at all. Right.
The example here is that the smell triggers the email, right?
And when the email is triggered, you're there.
Really? You're back. You're like, you know, whatever.
You know, Jersey in the 80s or whatever.
Yeah, I feel it all of a sudden.
It's like, yes, that's the email in reverse.
Right. So it's the email in reverse.
So you do it that way again in reverse.
So in other words, when you're doing the email, it's in reverse instead of, OK, you
get the smell, you remember the smell and the email takes you back to that era as if
you're living it again for a moment or whatever.
Now, when you do it the other way, when you do the email first, it has to create you
create the remembrance and then the presentation.
In other words, so you go email to remembering what you'd like to have.
Right. Because you could actually remember the future if you're structuring it.
Right. If you make plans for next week and you write them all out and I said, do you
remember what you wrote for next week?
That's still remembering, even though it hasn't happened yet.
Right. I don't I don't need to say that again.
It could be it could be confusing.
Right. And then once all that is set, then the manifestation occurs.
You don't have to worry about how it's going to manifest.
Just set up everything else for it.
Right. In other words, when you smell the whatever you did and you remembered the
smell, you didn't have to set up going back to the 80s.
It happens automatically.
Right. So you do it in reverse.
You set up, you see how it will be by remembering it, even though it hasn't
happened yet. And then it manifests.
If you over plan it detail by detail, it'll be sort of like, hey, you got this on
your own. You don't need the rest of the milieu that's out to do these things
because everything is manifested.
Right. By other beings and other things.
It has it takes life to manifest things.
Right. Even when the Grand Canyon is formed, it's living water that does it, you
know. So everything has to have some sort of life impotence to manifest something.
Yeah. We'll have to do more of the emo stuff.
The solo sonics are starting, by the way, at Greek speak dot com.
Right. And not necessarily want to plug those too much because people who already
found out, I think I just wanted to bring that up again because these things will go
into depth. But basically, I laid it all out in terms of an outline.
Hopefully it wasn't too confusing.
You could always hit pause and go back.
It's all in reverse.
And I think bringing up the smell to remembering the smell to reliving the past is
the emo in reverse.
The emo came last there.
So here the emo comes first, then the remembrance and then the manifestation.
Right. And that's basically how it works.
And don't be attached to it because here, you know, a lot of people get attached to
their hopes. I hope it comes.
Maybe it will. Maybe it won't.
All this stuff. Okay.
If you act as if it's already happened, what are you hoping for?
It's already done. Right.
There's no hope needed.
There's no belief needed.
Right. Well, I've never known how to articulate that.
That that is specifically like, no, you don't say you want this to come.
You say this is this is happening.
It is.
Well, well, you can only say you want this to come with the words in the cycle, cycle
materialistic. But in the emo, it's the feeling as if it's already come.
You see? Well, but that's the thing.
There's a huge difference between I want this to come.
I want this to come. Come on, bring it, bring it, bring it.
And yeah, that's not going to work.
This is already happening.
This is coming.
Like, in other words, if there's exactly so that that's done, it's already done.
That's the way you got to go with it.
That's always hard for me to kind of articulate.
But I think you just laid it out.
But it's not just saying it.
What does it actually feel like when it's actually done?
And then act accordingly.
Right. Because you must you must perform something in the psycho material world.
I see psycho meaning spiritual.
Right. That's funny, because most people, you know, say psycho.
What do you think keeps using that word psycho for you?
Well, spirit, spirit world, you know, either.
Right. But the ether is a substance used by the spirit,
just like we would use material here.
So fair enough.
So now that you've addressed that, let's see on your checklist sex.
Yeah, I wanted to bring that up because it's such a big deal.
And this is for immature audiences, not only.
But, you know, I say for mature audiences, right.
This is also for the immature.
And because you could be 90 years old and be immature, just look around you.
Right. Yeah. Well, maturity is also relative to what you consider to be mature.
You know, it depends on where they're stuck.
Most people, you know, in their later year, even till later on in life,
are still stuck in that high school mentality.
Yeah. Or lower. Very, very weird.
But but it is also in the eye of the beholder.
You know, I've had people tell me that somebody is very mature and all this kind
of thing. And I said and I look at him and I go, how?
I don't understand how exactly.
Well, sorry, I don't know if you heard that siren go by.
That was weird. But yeah, go ahead.
So it's just like, you know, I see people are dumbed down.
Well, look, even the most dumbed down, whatever.
Now, if you ask them what city or town or what month it is, they'll pretty much know.
There are plenty of plenty of authors and writers from the 16th, 17th, 18th,
19th centuries that made commentary on the public that if you were, let's say,
in the 1700s in Paris, France and asked anyone or the majority of the people,
the normies, let's say, what city you're not.
Well, I should say there were people that if you ask them what city you're in,
what country, what year is it? They wouldn't know.
That's how dumb you see.
So we're much better off in many aspects like that.
So in terms of maturity, it's possible that they're more mature
than the immature ones from back then.
It's something in scripture about, you know, don't romanticize the past
because things are actually getting better,
but they're going to get better for those that are not doing good.
And they're going to lead you into that.
And the whole thing has to be redone.
So with sex, this is also for the immature.
The reason I'm saying this is in age also is because,
you know, the food, clothing, shelter and all this other stuff.
Sex is one of the most powerful tools and motivators
that's used in society.
And what I mean by that is they're actually business deals
that are not, quote unquote, consummated until a certain, you know,
you have this businessman who wants to invest in a company
and he tells the person in the company, hey, your secretary's built like a B-52.
I'll have a night with her and you'll get your money.
Right. So it's not just between two people.
Now, the the boss has to convince the secretary
that if she doesn't have sex with this guy, the company doesn't.
You see what I mean?
Yeah, well, that's definitely a taboo thing nowadays.
Well, this is going on and on.
And also the children are used, you know, the pedophilia,
which is always talked about.
But there's not much talk about pederasty.
Pederasty is where older men with a younger man,
younger, usually adolescent pedophilia
usually means like infants, you know, very young, formative years.
But pederasty is when you would have a teenage boy with an old man.
Right. This was that's more common, believe it or not, in other cultures.
So this thing about sex is that it's a very strong power.
You know, they say, what do they say, sex?
And even in Scarface, first you get the money, then you get the power,
then you get the sex, right, or something like that.
So it's this thing that denotes it's more than just a bodily function.
It's more than just like I keep bringing up Wilhelm's Reich,
Wilhelm Reich's association with it, because he dealt on the function
of the orgasm much and on how it was very similar to people
discharging emotional armoring and such.
What I what I'm saying is that no matter how much the the society changes,
that seems to still remain the same.
There's still pederasty, pedophilia, a coercion, right?
Business deals being consummated, all this other things.
Relationships, relationships over sex.
Right. For example, personal relationships, husband and wife,
boyfriend, girlfriend, whatever, whatever.
They focus on it as a leverage point, pro or con or whatever. Right.
Too much sex, too little sex.
It's never just right. You know what?
What's at the party?
Healthy sex life.
Do you have a healthy sex life?
They all can do that, too. Right. Right.
And then there's you know, if you over sex a population,
the popular the you have less population growth, by the way.
Right. Because then you could start introducing other things
in it that focus more on not having children.
So what's interesting about this is
all of it is relevant to a level of spiritual immaturity,
because once someone decides what it's for,
even on the Wilhelm Reich aspect, what it's for is for having children procreating.
Even on the Wilhelm Reich side, he was kind of made fun of a little bit.
He was a little eccentric, a little actually.
Anyway, one of my mentors, Joe Blankenship, was his driver,
personal driver when Wilhelm Reich spent four years here in Tucson.
OK, I'll just give you a quick thing.
You'll never you won't see this on the Internet.
So Joe said, how was it being around Wilhelm Reich?
So I couldn't stand it because of this. I'll tell you what it is.
We go around town, pick up whatever he needed and we go back to the house.
So Wilhelm Reich gets out of the car, opens the door, goes into the house.
Joe Blankenship is unloading the car, you know, about a minute later,
walks into the house and there's Wilhelm Reich stark naked
laying down on the couch having a cigarette because he was he was a nudist.
He liked being naked all the time.
And, you know, I mean, you know, a guy in his 50s or 60s, you know,
I don't know any. I mean, I don't know.
I guess maybe it's personal taste or whatever.
It makes some people uncomfortable.
Others are just, you know, unfazed by it.
Everybody's got their own.
He didn't like that about him. You don't hear maybe this anyway.
So there's the Wilhelm Reich aspect.
But I'm suggesting that once you mature about it and
and you see what it's for, even from the Wilhelm Reich perspective,
he says it's important to the orgasm and the discharge
of discharges, extra energy so it doesn't create armoring and harm in the body.
Yes, I agree to that.
Many aspects, but also a brisk walk or jog around the block
about 3000 times might do it also. Right.
I'm just joking, but cold showers next.
Yeah. Well, here's the thing.
It's kind of like when you're fasting,
you get more hungry if you admit that you're fasting
than if you're having a busy day.
You'll say, I didn't eat today.
You don't even think about it. Right.
So if you're focusing on it, it'll become more difficult. Right.
Now, I'm not saying to abstain or whatever.
And this is other stuff on the Internet.
There's the piss drinkers, you know, drink urine therapy.
Then there's like semen retention.
Oh, yeah. The tantric.
Yeah, that has nothing to do that.
You look when you look at Buddhism and I've been saying this for 25, 30 years.
Actually, I found out about it in the 80s, what Buddhism was really about.
Everything that you hear about Buddhism is what Buddhism is not.
If you study the Buddhism, just like the scriptures, for example.
Right. Or just like anything.
I mean, like everything.
I was going to say, just like anything, it seems like whatever it's labeled as.
That's wrong. Period. Right.
So like, you know, like I've said, if you understand the Bible,
you'll never call yourself a Christian.
If you understand the Koran, you'll never call yourself a Muslim.
You see how it goes on and on and on.
So those are just labels.
Those are like catchphrases.
Those are things to identify
people and say, oh, this guy says he's a Christian means he knows
absolutely nothing about the Bible.
He's just following along what we set for him.
And the same with the Buddhist, same with them.
Right. And what's interesting was very refreshing.
There's a young man in his early 20s
who talks a lot about the Koran on YouTube by Congress.
And he says, don't I'm not Muslim.
But he knows more about the Koran than any right Muslim does.
Right. He has very good commentaries.
And I found out about him through the one of the archaic interviews.
You could look him up. OK.
Wonderful young man.
But he's not Muslim. I love that. That's great.
Like, you know, a true biblical scholar would never be considered Christian
himself. It would be insulting. Right. On and on. Right.
Someone who knows about the human body would never be called a medical doctor.
Never, ever.
Someone who knows about the law would never have been called an attorney.
Well, some of the best students study something objectively as well.
You know, they don't have an emotional attachment to anything.
So they actually look at things as they are, as opposed to trying to shape them
in a particular way to fit their particular belief. Right.
Well, it's not personal.
I'm saying the society is set up that if you're going to take on a trade
or a label like that, you have to do it their way.
And their way is always corrupt. Right. Of course.
It's very simple that way.
So with the aspect of the sex also, let's say within relationships,
when it becomes a point of contention,
it's sort of like it can go to the level I've seen people who are alcoholics.
It's the same way branded as society.
You know, go to AA or whatever you should. How about this?
You should never drive a car anymore because you are alcoholic.
Ten years ago, that doesn't make any sense. Right.
You're not right now. So so there's this aspect.
It's basically sex is also a form of communication.
Right. The better the communication, the better the interaction.
Now, here's the thing that most people, when you say sex, thinks what it's about.
It's not just the penetration and all this.
There's a level of when people are communicating well
and they feel close to each other.
It's just being close with each other. Is that sex or not?
You know, well, no, it's not because sex, again, is defined by procreation.
Right. And if there's no orgasm in the male
to deliver that, right, are they having sex?
You see. So intimacy.
I don't use the word romantic, by the way.
You know, that's a television thing, right? Yeah.
Because what does that even mean anyway? You know.
Yeah. So so there's that aspect as well.
I mean, there's people you can be
intimate and not have the penetration
and can be just as satisfying for many
if the emotion and the communication and spiritual level is there.
There's not much talk about it in a sense of how broadband this topic is,
because it's always this or it's always that or, you know, like we just mentioned,
all the modalities, even from urine drinking all the way, which is not sex.
But I'm saying it's kind of like they're with the semen retention on
whatever the tantric
or some level of your head spinning.
Yeah, it's some level of intimacy, but it doesn't mean that it's sex.
I mean, you know, so I mean, you can have different levels of intimacy
that are not necessarily sex, you know.
So, I mean, it's just there's many different ways to go with it, right?
Well, it's no, it's not really because the actual basic sex is to procreate
for the sperm to reach the egg somehow.
And the thing is, that could be actually done without any intimacy.
Right. But the aspect of it, in other words, what I'm saying, it's like love.
Sex and love are not making love, making love.
Love is to do the right thing.
Right. Well, you should do the right thing.
But but either way, again, it has to be it's based on communication.
But you have to understand this topic is so heavily
subjectively dependent on the culture that you were raised in
or you have accepted because you could be raised in one culture,
transplant into another and fully adapt. Right.
So it's very much that way.
But but what it will lean on very heavily is the purpose of sex
is strictly to procreate.
That's it. And then there's all these other things that lean over.
Oh, we're making love or this or that or pornography.
Right. Which is the sale of sex or prostitution or whatever.
The sale, the commercial aspects of it. Right.
With one package, you can put it in. Yeah.
Yeah. So but in essence, it's strictly for having children.
The rest of it that they call sex is basically levels of communication,
intimacy, fellowship,
on and on all the way to Wilhelm Reich's idea where it discharges.
So there's this mixing.
Making love is one of the worst things that you could say
about sex is because, again, TV, you know, the word romantic, making love.
All this stuff is borrowed from the Western culture. Right.
Right. Because love is doing the right thing.
So then that can't happen unless there's communication.
All right. So communication and openness and the people have to be intimate
and all this other stuff.
So, again, I just want to lean on it again.
There's so many things that are attached to it that are really not
much to do with having babies, especially where I started off.
The man won't invest in the company until the company boss
has a secretary, have sex with him. Right.
This kind of like thing that goes on, it's still going on
and will always go on in this society.
It doesn't matter if it's Eastern or Western or whatever.
That seems to be a human thing.
So I just wanted to bring those things up again,
because I was thinking, you know, talking about sex, we're going to talk about.
I mean, it's just about having babies.
And the rest of it is intimacy, relationships, communication and culture.
That's pretty much it.
And then once discipline on it.
All right. Free energy was the next thing I wanted to get into. Right.
I think that's the last thing, if you will, on your agenda
as you laid it out at the beginning here.
Yeah, I was thinking about that.
You know, what's interesting about that?
It's again, another topic you see online
and it's just running all over the place or whatever.
I don't know. The popularity seems to have kind of slowed down as a blade.
It seems to me like about five or ten years ago, somewhere in there.
It was it was really everywhere.
Yeah. Nowadays. Yeah.
Very much like, I don't know, sort of suppressed in a real way.
Well, it's remember all this stuff, all this alternative stuff is not really
these people like if you meet people in the alternative media, you look at them
and they're just like me.
You know, oh, I woke up in such a year and I'm going, you don't know.
Anything, you know, they really don't.
I mean, yes, they might have a specialty in something that they're specialized
or no experienced in or studied or whatever.
But it's like, wow.
Overall, generally, it's like, oh, my gosh.
Can you know, it's just like, what do you do?
You're all saying the same thing.
So, you know, here's the thing with the Greek speak.
What I try to do is like, OK, just stop.
Everybody stop.
What's going on? Let's just start right here.
What's what's in your pockets?
You know what's in the room
when you walk down the street, what do you see?
You know, real basic stuff.
Just forget about everything for for a little while.
Let's pay attention to what things mean.
What? OK, all this.
All right. So there is no free energy in a sense.
But in other words, what you're actually talking about is hyper efficiency.
And here, actually, with this next little bit that we're going to get into here,
I'm going to show you how anybody listening to me can grasp these concepts
and move along and develop, quote unquote, what they're calling free energy.
Quite simply.
And if you've grasped the concepts of the pope's work schedule being false,
how the human body works.
I mean, it's pretty obvious.
You're looking at anatomy that nothing gets absorbed
and calories have nothing to do with it.
And those things are so obvious and regardless of,
you know, how many people don't think so or don't pay attention to it,
you're able to if you're listening to me, you're able to grasp this.
It's very simple.
So what they call energy, the energy is there's many definitions,
but generally it's the ability to do work. Right.
They very it's very difficult to define the word energy
without using the word energy again. Right.
Something providing an impetus force to do work. OK.
All right. So what what are we doing now
when we talk about energy?
Ninety nine percent of the time people are going to go to electricity, right?
Electric motor fan or whatever. Yeah. Turning that motor.
OK. And then from that, they think about an electrical generator.
Right. Go to a construction site, whatever.
Someone has an emergency backup. What's that?
Oh, it's an electrical generator where that thing doesn't generate
any electricity any more than a water pump generates water.
And what I mean by that,
you have here in your mind anyone, you know what electrical
what they call an electric generator is now put in your mind a water pump.
Do you expect to go out and buy a water pump?
Just leave it in the box. Plug it in.
Just open the top. Pull the cord out. Right.
Plug it in. Do you expect water to start shooting out of it?
No, only if you're an idiot. But yeah. Right.
Well, so that's why they're calling them generators.
They're not what the water pump is designed to do is have an input and output.
Right. And the input is a static body of water or a certain pressure or volume
or rate. And depending on the design of the pump, how big it is,
how fast it spins, the impeller is the output, how much pressure.
Right. And all this.
They all have different ratings, just like generators do.
They all have different ratings.
Now, simply what the generator is doing, it does need a prime mover.
You could crank it by hand.
You can have it to a gas driven engine or on a waterfall.
You know how they do the the dams is to drop water on a spinner.
The hydro hydropower or heat, you know, you boil water
and you turn the steam turbine using whatever, you know, burn garbage, coal,
oil, nuclear, whatever.
OK, so what they're doing
is that they're rotating a magnet with an electrical field coil.
And as the magnetic poles, as they state,
pass and cut the wire.
In other words, the field of the of the
the magnet goes through the wire.
It generates an impulse is what they're telling you.
It's actually what it's doing is the same thing that a water pump does.
If the water pump isn't moving, how much water is moving right through it?
Nothing. As you start to move the water pump faster, more water pumps
through based on how it's designed, the same principles happening
with the electric generator internally.
Right. But it needs a prime mover.
In other words, you have to turn the generator with something.
OK, so the idea here is if you move a little bit further,
while the easiest thing then, Chuck, would be to hook up that generator
to a windmill, right?
Or hook it up to a water, a river like the water wheels, you know.
And back in the days, you know, the windmills were used to grind
to make grain flour and grind things right.
Or even as water pumps as as they turned.
And the water wheel was used for whatever.
It's been used for thousands of years, literally.
OK, so that is the prime mover.
But here's the concept now where we get into the free energy part,
because it's very much in line
with all these things and the metaphors and examples
and analogies I just gave.
It's exactly the same thing.
It's not this mysterious whatever. Right.
So here's the here's the you said it's died out a little bit.
We go online, whatever, because it's always this mysterious thing
that you're looking at.
You have to lay out the premises of what you have, what's really going on
and then move into that category. Right. Yeah.
All right. So we have the idea
that let's say if you go to this, the regular academic, academic science
that everything is moving, you know, like magnets
even have a rate, a little more frequency. Right.
It's magnets are actually moving at a frequency.
People talk about the speed of light.
No one talks about the speed of magnetism. Right. True.
You know, you could sense it. Right.
So you have the idea of like they tell you these little electrons
are running around the inside of an atom.
You know, it's the proton and he's got a lazy cousin, the neutron. Right.
And all this other stuff's moving.
They tell you the planet's moving around the sun,
the planet's spinning a thousand miles an hour,
six thousand miles around the sun, but all these things, everything's in motion.
Right. OK, so.
But it seems to be static at the at this time.
We don't sense all of these movements. Right.
OK, what's happening is very simple.
Let's say you have two cars on the highway
and they're both going 50 miles an hour.
As long as the windows are rolled up, I could look over at the car next to me
and it doesn't look like they're moving at all, does it?
I'm not looking at their surroundings, just the inside of the car.
We're both moving at the same speed. Right.
If you're traveling at the same rate of speed. Right. Yeah.
But if I carefully open the door and drag my knuckles on the road.
What happens? I'll tear my arm off.
No kidding. I mean, look, you can see this in movies all the time, right,
where you see that a car is moving
when they actually would drive a car next to a car so they could film
people sitting in a car while they drive.
That's the idea. They're usually on trailers.
But yeah, of course, that's the way.
But what I'm saying is the concept is the car is moving down the road.
You put something next to it that is outside of the car and you can shoot
from the outside of the car and move the car, move the surroundings.
Yeah, it's the same sense of motion. Yeah. Yeah.
Well, I'm giving the sense of motion because we're told that everything
around us is moving.
Right. Right. And but we don't sense it.
I mean, do you sense that they're telling us, which I don't believe for a second,
that we're moving 66,000 miles around the sun per hour
and the earth is spinning a thousand miles an hour.
Eight hundred to a thousand miles an hour.
If you were on anything that was spinning at that rate of speed,
you figure you'd feel it. But yeah, right.
Yeah. But let's say it was true.
Let's say all these things are in motion, which I suggest they are.
In other words, another in previous Sonics, I've talked about another
for something to appear solid in the matrix that we're in.
The ether that we're in, it has to be in a state of motion,
just like putting your hand through a fan or a bicycle wheel.
If it's not moving, you can move freely.
But once it's in motion, it appears to be solid.
Right. The area that it would be moving it.
And this is true. This has been shown many times with certain frequencies
and impulses on materials.
You can actually put a, you know, a regular lead pencil through a steel beam.
Right. It's not very popular, but the stuff exists.
You can see it. Also, people with the loud subwoofers in the car,
you can see the window if the camera picks it up with the flicker rate.
Much better. The glass is flexing like it's made of jello,
but it doesn't break. Right. Right. Because of the sound waves.
You could look up how car bodies ripple with subwoofers.
It happens in real time, but you don't notice it until you put a camera
that has a certain flicker rate on it.
LEDs, if you ever look at a someone's YouTube of a new car,
it looks like the headlights are on and they're always flicking, flickering.
But you don't notice the flickering with a regular high because the flicker rate
the camera picks up.
So there is evidence of oscillations and movements.
Now, let's go back to the analogy where the two cars are
next to driving next to each other at the same speed.
There's no apparent relative movement until you somehow adjust or make
an adjustment and notice how if you stick your knuckles down on the ground
and drag them on the road, they're going to it's going to pretty much not just
damage your knuckles, but rip your arm off. Right.
That's an extreme example if you're going at highway speed.
But relatively, as you're next to the other car,
perceiving the inside of the car, there's no relative movement.
By the way, I'm not this is not going to anything Einsteinian
with his relativity garbage, which is a theoretical,
philosophical, never science, because he he got that from Pankare,
a French physicist way before his time, but
actually not way before, but decades.
So here's the other misnomer.
Now, if you understand what the analogy I gave, that there's no movement,
but you can actually feel the effects of it.
We move forward into what if you why reinvent the wheel?
This is a statement that's constantly being made.
But, you know, is there anything that we need to do
that hasn't been done by nature already?
And the answer to that is no. Right.
Because when I say that, let's say even to the stars,
that's already everything is pretty much done naturally.
So let's move to another analogy.
And everyone, I'm sure, that's heard Greek speak is very well primed
in this or primed enough that the heart does not pump any blood ever.
It's a breaking mechanism. Right.
So what is happening is that the there is a biological vacuum,
a slight negative pressure right in the body that is
a the condition, the overall scale or condition of the body.
And the movement towards the heart
is already provided by the capillaries. Right.
And I don't know if I've ever gone into the biology of this very much,
but essentially it's the capillaries that are moving everything
because it's impossible for it to be the other way,
because you have 2000 miles of blood vessels in the body.
You're an adult, 50 percent solids, 98 degrees or 37 Celsius.
Would it be that much, that length?
2000 miles if you laid it out straight. Really?
All the blood vessels. Yeah.
A little bit more. It's more like 2400.
I'm being conservative. Really?
I don't know. I just see.
I mean, I often remark about how, you know, the length of intestines
are pretty extreme.
You know, I tell people there's 50 feet of that on the one
the one part of the intestine.
Yeah. All the blood vessels in the body are around for an adult.
Depends on the size.
But between 2000 and let's say 3000. Wow. Right.
OK, no, I just think it's kind of mind blowing to consider that.
Yeah. Average diameter of half a millimeter.
Right. There's you would need.
We did this on a computer a long time ago, a university computer.
It stated that you would need 1200 horsepower pump
and it would only go 200 miles.
So a 1200 horsepower pump only 10 percent. Right.
So you would need 12000 horsepower to pump, you know, the blood.
And this is totally ignored.
In other words, they're giving you an engineering
structural analogy of the heart.
But if you go to engineering and structures, none of it makes any sense. Right.
So here's the interesting thing.
The heart is actually acting as a breaking mechanism. Right.
So and this is already happening in nature. Right.
Because when you have induction in anything,
whether it's a plant, animal or human, there has to be regulation and control.
This induction is happening from an energetic point of view.
So we have glands and organs and circulatory systems, the heart
and things like that, that move not to create movement.
The movement's already happening.
It's to constrict it and restrict it and regulate. Right.
So in essence, if you look at the heart as a breaking mechanism
and it's a it's a natural occurrence.
Why don't we start applying breaking mechanisms
to the energy modalities that you're seeking?
In other words, if you're looking to make electricity
instead of providing a prime mover to move a field coil and a magnet
to pressurize the ether, the static. Right.
You end up creating electricity of a certain type. Right.
You know, for example, when you're producing, let's say, consumables like oils,
you have cold press oil, regular pressed oil. Right.
So the way that the oil is produced, how things are fermented,
how things are prepared, you want it fried, baked or steamed. Right.
The same thing.
Different methods of preparation will yield a different almost thing.
Like if I steamed a hamburger or I fried a hamburger or I grilled it on the fire.
It's like having three completely different meals. Right.
Oh, yeah, absolutely.
So the type of electricity that we're used to, that we would like free energy
to replace is for, let's say, a steamed hamburger.
It's it's it's this type of electricity that's produced
with a prime mover that moves a magnet or coil
in a field situation to take the electrostatic field
that it's static field again, like the water pump. Right.
We're trying to find things that are static and get them moving at great expense.
Why not looking at things that are already moving
and instead of trying to get things that are static moving,
why don't we get things that are already moving into a braking situation?
What happens when you I don't know, I've done this several times.
Someone pulls up to me to check out their car and it's about brakes
and they just drove around and drove around and you take the wheel off.
You want to check out the brake, touch the brake.
Ah, really hot, like a really hot pan. Right.
Lots of energy going into the brakes.
The brakes uptake mechanical energy and dissipate it right into heat.
Let's say typically it's more than just heat.
There's a lot of torsion, internal torsion that develops as well and electricity.
So instead of trying to create these prime movers to move things,
to get something out of something that's static, that we won't be able
to get it out of it unless we already start something moving.
Why don't we look at all these things are already in extreme motion.
The thing is that the if the motions are relatively,
I would say, moderate, we already use them like running water or wind or whatever.
What if we start going to motions that are extremely fast?
Then we just need a subtle braking mechanism.
We don't need such an extreme breaking mechanism
because it's already very high energy.
We just need a little bit of it. Right.
Tesla talked about that when they told him about nuclear energy.
He says, oh, that's nothing but an infant's
consumptive breath compared to capacitive discharge.
Now, I'm not preparing.
I'm going into the technical aspects of this.
But I just wanted to create an introduction to understand
that what is being put out there again?
I not at the fault. OK.
You know how you have disinfo agents.
I believe that the majority of these disinfo agents don't think
that they don't know that they're disinforming.
That has been led to do so. You know what I mean?
Right. They're they're producing that they're producing disinformation.
But to their minds, they're producing good information.
They're doing the right thing. Yeah. Right.
That's yeah.
And I think you definitely would have seen that or realized that
what the research you're doing with JFK.
Well, I encounter it constantly.
You think you're doing the right thing, but you're not.
Yeah. I see it all the time.
Look here. Yeah. Look at this.
You know, this completely undoes what you've been promoting, let's say. Right.
Right. So and then, you know,
they either do two things, one, argue about it
or they just completely negate it like you never told them. Right.
So, right. It's either ignore or or possibly confront it.
And, you know, they yeah.
And then, you know, hopefully hopefully there's a tie or or they prevail.
So this is very much what's this is what people have.
I mean, look, I've said this many, many, many, many years ago.
If well, maybe just many years ago, not many.
I'm not many, many, many years old.
But if there's anything out there that, you know, worth listening,
I wouldn't be doing Greek speak at all.
It's just that I keep discovering things and looking at
and thinking about things in a certain way.
And I'm like, OK, let's go ask around and see who else is.
And I find that no one else is.
I'm like, OK, all right, I'm not going to keep it to myself.
You know what I mean? Right.
So, OK, just to go back to the free energy.
So instead of looking for these prime movers,
why don't we just go over and find things that are already moving
and already have what's called a difference in potential?
Here's a very simple way to look at it.
Again, free energy.
First thing that comes up is a light bulb electricity.
The type of electricity that they're using, by the way,
is not going to work with the free energy system.
It's going to be different.
If you're used to like a charbroiled hamburger
and now you're going to only have a steamer,
you'll never have a charbroiled hamburger again if you only have a steamer. Right.
So the variety of preparations and the energy is going to be very different.
But nonetheless, it will still be energy.
So to give an example, when you think of free energy,
the first thing that comes up is electricity.
OK, well, how do we what are the most rudimentary things?
You know, if you're a carpenter, you use a tape measure or a ruler. Right.
Right. When you're working with electricity,
the first thing you're going to have to get is a voltmeter. Right.
So what is if you look up a definition?
Actually, I haven't done this in a long time.
Let's just just bear with me for a second.
I'm going to open the browser and I'm going to put in how does a voltmeter work?
Is that right? And I haven't.
Let's let's see what they say, because it has to do with the.
OK, I'll show you how they're showing what they want you to see.
But and not not ask any questions.
Let's see. Conceptually, this is why I used to like the concept of solar energy,
because it's taking something that already exists,
is already abundantly happening.
And you just simply redirect it for now, redirect it and gather it.
You know, I see nothing wrong with the concept.
As long as your panels are less than 15 percent efficient,
they had 30 and 40 percent efficient panels made with molybdenum
and other alloys back in the 1800s.
But you can't have those just like the 100 mile per gallon carburetor.
You can't have that. OK, here we go.
Voltmeters. How does a voltmeter work?
Voltmeters operating on electrostatic principle use the mutual repulsion
between two charge plates to deflect the pointer attached to a spring.
OK, let's OK.
OK, so here the the electrostatic electro, what is static mean?
Not moving. Right. It's ever present.
And electro. OK.
Again, you see it's about electrostatics.
But again, why is electrostatic not moving here?
Here's let's see how does the electronic
that's going to have to do.
Let's see if it talks about rectification on tronic
because most of the voltmeters are electronic now, digital, right? Right.
The electronic voltmeter uses amplification or rectification or both
to measure either alternating or direct current voltages.
The current needed to actuate the meter movement is not taken from the circuit
being measured. OK, so these are all pressure devices.
In other words, you have to give it power for it to work.
The analog, sometimes the old analog ones didn't.
They had Leyden jars. OK, but this is where I'm going with it.
Let's say people have been playing around with the silver,
the aqua Sargentum
and or either way you want to say it.
But it's not colloidal silver, but let's just call it the silver.
Have you been getting feedback on that, by the way, since?
Tremendous. OK. Tremendous.
I've been getting feedback on that for decades.
So no, I'm just recently from the rated Y.
Yeah. From rated Y.
Because I haven't gotten any on that.
So I was just curious.
Fair amount in the chat.
Fair enough for what it is. Yeah. OK. Fair enough.
Yeah. It's you know, here's the thing, just like with anything.
If you just learned how to cook, don't expect to be a chef right away.
You know, the more you use it, the more you get and the more you use it
and the more you make it, the more you'll discover about it.
Right. Of course. Yeah.
Especially if you have experience with commercial colloidal silver.
It'll be radically different.
So, OK, so people have been working with silver.
You'll notice that if you do a little bit of experimentation
with metals with a voltmeter, if you, let's say,
put different metals, let's say copper and iron or whatever,
two different metals in water and you put a voltmeter across it,
that's just a voltmeter.
You'll notice that there's a little bit of an electrical charge
coming across the two dissimilar metals.
And one always assumes a positive, one always assumes a negative. Right.
Typically, the larger elements will tend to be more negative
than the smaller metals, meaning on the periodic table will be more positive.
Right. Yin and yang. Right. Again.
So what's interesting here?
If you're going to take a level of potential differences,
what about if you have access to the equipment or the materials,
start collecting materials, all the elements you can
on the periodic table that you know,
let's say, divided, that will always show up positive.
And then try to collect as many materials as you can
that you always know will show up negative. Right.
Because you need positive and negative
to make the circuit for the type of electricity that you want to do.
So you take all those metals
and you grind them up into an extremely fine powder and then center them,
which is compress the powder so much that, you know,
in neodymium magnets are centered, by the way,
you know, that they have the shiny coating.
It's just compressed powder.
That's why if they're in water, they just dissolve, they break up. Right.
You know, when you have one aspect of
sintered material that, you know, usually strikes positive
and another aspect of material that's always strikes negative
in a powdered form, why a powdered form?
You could do plates, but powder gives you tremendous surface area.
Right. You grind everything together. Right.
And what happens if you put those together in water or not?
All of the elements you could possibly get on the periodic table,
put a voltmeter across it, what's going to happen?
You're going to blow up the voltmeter. OK.
I was going to say, I don't know, but OK.
Well, yeah, it will be so much current and voltage going through that.
Right. So why? Why? What's going on?
Well, why? What's the big mystery?
We're going to get into more of this in the future.
But at least the primer, I think we've laid out.
Fair enough.