The Sonic Event 191, here we are, Greek,
how are you today?
I'm tired, I'm going to go to sleep
soon as we finish this.
Yeah, it's just very windy, doing auto mechanic
stuff today and all kinds of stuff.
Been up since four in the morning.
You just replaced your transmission or just had
your transmission replaced?
Yeah, but I'm doing something else.
I haven't done anything on it in really
a decade other than basic coil changes and
I was like, oh my gosh.
Hey look, if you don't have to do
a lot of work, that's great, outside of
general maintenance, right?
I mean, that's the whole point.
No, I did, I do a lot of
stuff, mounts, all kinds of stuff.
I usually prefer to bring it to someone,
but mechanics suck.
Even like really good mechanics, they're not very
good.
I hate to say it.
Well, you know what it is.
It's like going out and eating in a
restaurant, you know?
There aren't any good restaurants anymore.
They do have those computers nowadays, though, that
for the past like 10, 15 years, they've
had something they can just plug the computer
and the computer tells them what's wrong, right?
Isn't that like the general?
Well, that's the OBD system.
We've kind of brought that up.
OBD is onboard diagnostics.
Yeah.
Yeah, sort of.
That doesn't tell you much, just a bunch
of sensors.
I'm talking about the workmanship, really.
Oh, okay.
Workmanship is poor.
Absolutely.
Well, isn't it poor on everything?
So look, I've got a bunch of oddball
questions this time, and I'm grouping them together,
and I got one stupid one to open
up with you just real fast, just philosophically.
I'm curious about this myself, and probably you
don't do this, but you ever have one
of those like days where you do a
couple of really just dumb things and you
can't figure out why?
You know, the day where you press the
coffee maker and you're sitting there going, why
isn't my coffee brewing?
And then you realize it's not plugged in.
You know, like that kind of stuff you
do a few times in the course of
a day, and you're just like, man, I'm
off this day.
Do you do that ever, or are you
immune to that?
I'm immune to that.
Okay.
I got a lot of radar around me.
I got you.
You know the Terminator?
When you see it from his point of
view and he's got these...
Oh, he's got the analytical, here's the responses,
here's all of the vectors.
Yeah, that's how I function, yeah.
Oh, that's cool.
Yeah, that's cool.
Well, I don't, obviously, but I was just
curious, because I notice that those things sometimes
come in batches, and I was just thinking
about it, and it doesn't matter what my
physical being is.
Anyways, so like I said, there's weird questions
here, and this one, they actually make a
reference to a biblical passage, and Ezekiel 34
and 35, excuse me, and no one talks
about this.
Can the Greeks talk about it?
Okay, it was the prince of Israel, okay?
Will he be ruling in the next society?
Is this person someone who is coming in
the future that is referred to in Ezekiel
34 and 35?
Okay, how about that?
Yeah, it'll be coming from the future, but
it's complex, because most likely things like that
you read in what they call the Bible
are like hyperlinks.
In other words, you have to look at
the phrase as something that's a directive or
a strong subject matter to be defined in
other places, typically.
That's just the style that it's written in.
And like most hyperlinks, it's got some of
the information that's relevant in the hyperlink, but
you have to actually go to the page
to get the whole thing.
Yeah, you have to know it all, and
you can't just read.
That's why in religions they just have you
read one verse, you know, because it's understood
that you cannot read it piece by piece.
You have to read the entire thing, really,
even though it was written over a big
time span.
That's why people don't understand it.
When you read it all, let's say you
were to read all of it in one
shot, the entire Bible, right?
You would understand it way better than if
you spent 20 years reading it the way
people read it.
It gave me two different versions of it,
reading this thing they call the Bible, reading
it cover to cover over the course of
about a year.
I just read it like that.
It took me a little time, you know,
eyesight and everything.
And then other times I read it in
pieces and this and that and finished it,
but didn't actually dedicate myself to reading it
every day.
And it gave me two different perspectives on
it, for sure, even though it was only
a few years apart.
Try to read each book in a day.
So read Genesis in a day, the next
day read, right?
So in a month you'll have it done,
or a month and a week or whatever.
Yeah, I did that temporarily and then kind
of got off track and then had to
go back to it.
That was that other time, outside of when
I did it.
But if you actually read it, see, everybody
says they read it.
No one wants to say they didn't read
it.
They're like, oh, yeah, I read it, too.
And everybody says, oh, good, you read it,
too.
Nobody read it.
Nobody's really read the Bible.
I hate to say it.
Nobody.
No, I read that book.
Even people who say, not nobody, there's very
few exceptions people actually read it.
Yeah.
And can retain it and comprehend it is
completely off.
Well, retaining it and comprehending it is another.
There's got to be fewer than 1,000
people on the planet who have actually read
it and try to comprehend it.
I mean, it's one of those popular, how
would you call it?
You have things like that in culture where
everyone just passes things off as a given.
Like all the people.
I've only met two people in my whole
life that actually read the Bible.
Well, I've read a lot of people that
say they read it 50 times and all
that.
So I come up with stuff like, oh,
like, how can you put that together?
Well, I've I've read it, but I've read
that version of it that, you know, obviously
I've read a version of it.
And I read the common English version of
it or whatever they called it.
I can't remember what they even call it
now.
But, you know, where they put it in
more plain American English.
I read that version of it.
I read the King James with the, you
know, the those of the these and the
thousand, all that.
I read both of those things, but it
doesn't mean that I actually retained at all.
Maybe it was a mistake to write the
Bible, because like I say, if you write
a book, you're presuming that the readership has
comprehension.
That is the problem always.
And I was thinking that when I watched
the Capitol Hill hearings today on the JFK
case, it was kind of funny.
But anyway, maybe I'll talk to you about
that another day.
That's fine.
Here's the thing.
Yeah.
These presidents, they're either read in or they're
not and they don't care.
It's a really shitty.
You got to feel sorry for them, whether
they've been assassinated or not.
Right.
But they're real shitty people because for either
either way, it's like what I'm trying to
say is, have you stopped beating your wife
yet?
It's that kind of thing.
Whether no matter how you answer that question,
you're admitting to beating your wife.
Right.
The basic history.
They're presuming that no one knows the history,
which is pretty good presumption that it's a
corporation.
It doesn't serve as a government as as
it was created.
It's a business.
And what they do is for their shareholders.
So to be a president of such an
organization, I mean, that's you got to be
like a real scumbag, you know.
Now, here's the other part that's even more
damning.
If you don't know any of that, you
believe the propaganda that the lady has been
told.
Well, you're even worse now because what are
you going to leave?
It's like the blind leading the blind.
You know how they say, right.
Or the dumb leading the dumb.
So either way, it's damning to be in
any of those leadership positions, any country because
of the state of affairs.
Yes.
Just a very dirty, very, very dirty.
I've kind of looked at it this way.
Every once in a while, some fool gets
in there and thinks he's actually going to
be in charge and be able to do
something.
You know, we don't know what's going on
in the background.
Right.
No, we don't know.
But they're all it's all very bad.
It's it's been very bad for over 150
years because it's not it doesn't have it's
not very bad in the overall cosmic sense
because it's just a corporation.
There's plenty of bits.
I don't know.
Someone was going to put together where they
say the US government's a corporation.
They had generals, people.
Yeah, it's just a corporation.
It's just a corporation.
You know, it's just a God is G
.D. piece of paper.
You know all that stuff.
Right.
So I think that it's they're they're all
bad either way, no matter.
You can give whether they know what's going
on.
They're bad if they don't know what's going
They're bad.
Right.
Because they should know.
So it's just really bad overall.
And it's it's also the the populace's fault.
No, I understand.
Look, you know, it's not like you're going
to have good and bad people working at
the crack slash whorehouse.
You know, it's they work at the crack
slash core, you know, the whorehouse.
So that's it.
I mean, it's not it doesn't serve.
It doesn't serve what it was intended.
It doesn't work wherever.
Here's an example.
Wherever you have influence of the corporate government
versus low influence of it, like in places
in rural places, you know, you don't have
much influence.
You'll notice the culture and the society go
down very quickly.
You wherever you have corporate government, like all
the cities or whatever, crime goes up.
Poverty goes up.
Drug use goes up.
Corruption goes up.
I'm not saying that minimal corporate influence has
none of that.
It also has it, but not as much.
So you look at all your big corporate
cities, L.A., Philadelphia, New York, whatever, Jersey
City.
Keep going.
Right.
Or even the shore, Jersey Shore.
Those, you know, they became popular recreation, the
government regulation and went down to shit.
Yeah, that's exactly because not because of the
government.
That's what people are saying.
It's because it's a corporation and they have
investors.
And one of the definitions of investment is
to gain from the efforts of others.
Of course.
Right.
So it's it's pretty bad.
But, you know, you I used to be
naive thinking like I wanted to get out
of New York because everyone around me sounded
dumb.
And I went to other places.
They didn't sound so dumb, but they were
just as dumb.
Then I was like, well, it's got to
be Americans.
And then I met people from Iraq, people
from Tibet, people from Russia, people from Japan.
I said, oh, they're dumb, too.
Oh, my gosh.
It's planetary wide.
This is a surface dwelling earth inhabitant issue.
You know, along these very same lines, somebody
asked a question, actually quotes a bunch of
stuff that you just said, OK, in their
longer message.
But to break it down, they're asking, you
know, if there is a spiritual purpose or
if there is a weaponized purpose in the
spiritual realm to the fact that so often
people like that in the government or in
the culture or whatever capture a large portion
of the imagination.
In other words, a lot of people's thoughts
and a lot of people's discussions are taken
up with these people, their actions, their crap.
And isn't that a form of manipulation in
and of itself?
If everybody is talking about this person, thinking
about this person, you know, against them or
for them, it's irrelevant.
OK, let's say it this way.
Yeah, you could you could do an overarching
in respect to any question.
There's an overarching aspect that's not really brought
up or emphasized.
Right.
And what I want to emphasize is that
we have an evasive species that is negative,
invasive or evasive, evasive and invasive, but more
evasive, evasive and invasive.
No problem.
OK, go ahead.
Evasive meaning you can't see them, but they're
negative.
Right.
And they basically benefit and feed off of
what we call negative behavior, negative thoughts, negative
whatever.
I'm not going to say loose or whatever.
That's that's more extreme.
You know how that term became popular about
15, 10, 15 years ago.
Right.
But in other words, if you go to
find swamp creatures, they tend to need like
a high sulfur diet, decaying, decomposing things to
thrive.
That's an analogy, right?
OK, got it.
So they need a decaying.
You'll have things go really well in generally
in many societies here for no more than
a decade or so.
And then it goes into a long like
century of decay because they need to breed
decay and strife, but not enough to kill
the victims, but enough for them to survive
it and propagate it.
Right.
Well, most parasites, most parasites don't kill their
host.
And quite frankly, look, mushrooms grow very well
in the dark and the muck and clams.
You know, a lot of people love the
clams.
Maybe that's your thing.
They go where they harvest clams.
It really stinks, doesn't it?
Actually, the best places to harvest clams in
a lot of places are what?
Near the sewage where they dump the sewage,
to be honest with you.
So what does that tell you?
Well, yeah, so we're but at the same
time, you know, we have a short it's
good to have a short life to pass
through here or whatever.
Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
It's not a positive place, no matter how
you cut it.
Just like I mentioned recently through the years
of people, what do they call them?
Survivalist preppers or whatever, like, oh, I got
to get out of the city.
I saved up one hundred thousand bucks.
I got this place out in the middle
of nowhere, off the grid, whatever.
I talked to him two years later.
I'm like, oh, man, it sucked.
I was like, I told you, it was
like five times more expensive living in the
city.
And then in nature, you'll find out that
everything wants to kill you, right?
Whether it's a bug, an animal, anything, everything
wants to kill you.
And he's like, yeah, I was like, I
can't go live in the city.
Like the city is the pinnacle of human
existence.
Besides that, I mean, here, let me just
take it further.
Unless a doomsday comes, a doomsday prepper is
kind of useless.
And by the way, who the hell wants
to eat beans and rice for the next
15 years?
Because that's what they always stop.
Well, here, let me continue the logic train
on this.
So if you really if you lived in
a city and you didn't have a corporate
government with investors, or really just, you know,
they can't tell.
See, the corporate government, again, this is a
tangent.
Can't tell people what's going on because they
don't have to.
You could just look it up yourself.
It's pretty crazy.
I'm still reading like statutes at large and
stuff.
And some of the laws are insane.
You know, I mean, like in our favor,
all the laws are in our favor.
All right.
Except for, for example, a U.S. citizen.
The only rights they have is to live
in Washington, D.C., basically.
That's it.
And they're a debtor.
And they have everything they can do as
a privilege.
Right.
That's the all caps name.
So it's like a credit card, you know.
But so if all that was known, people
would it would just dwindle and become nothing.
So they rely on deception, the corporate side.
Right.
So it's just like when you go to
a Ford dealer, do they say, well, you
know, Chrysler's got good cars, too.
They never say that.
So they can't talk about anything that is
not in accord with their fiduciary responsibility to
their principles.
Meaning the United States government and all the
state governments are also part of the since
the Civil War were planted and put in
by the federal government.
They were all dissolved.
Right.
OK.
This is easy to find in the statutes
at large and places like that.
So so when you're dealing with, say, state
of Georgia, that is a political subdivision out
of Washington, D.C. That's where its home
is, not Georgia, because there's Georgia state, there's
Florida state, Arizona state.
But state of is the is the Washington,
D.C. thing creature.
So but they don't have to disclose anything
because it's already written pretty clearly.
Right.
But let's say everything was disclosed.
Everything was hashed out with government, religion, all
that stuff.
You would have a city that would function
optimally.
The people's fitness or health would be very
high.
They would determine collectively direct representation how they
want to see the society go.
They would also have a science that allow
them to fully manipulate all material world around
them.
What that would lead to is what do
you call it when you eliminate eradication of
animals and insects?
You don't need them anymore.
You might have some pets, whatever, but you
would eradicate all the wildlife plant, all the
things that, you know, are unnecessary because you
don't need animals and plants and bugs and
stuff.
You have full control of your environment.
Right.
That transmutation Star Trek type stuff.
Yeah.
And then eventually you take over the the
entire planet.
You put a Dyson sphere around the whole
planet.
Right.
Energetic one.
Nothing can come and go.
Yeah.
That's that's the future, by the way.
If you were to continue in an optimum
way.
Now, what I just mentioned, like if I
talk about eradication of all the species, except
for humans, people are like, oh, my gosh.
Yeah.
Sounds pretty horrible, doesn't it?
But that's what happens when you optimize the
human culture.
Sorry, I don't mean to.
So how many creatures were in the world
when people were more primitive, primitive?
A lot more creatures as people became more,
let's say, advanced, the number of creatures declined.
Well, they talk about the logic train.
Yeah.
They talk about the extinction of thousands of
creatures.
You know, over the course of time, it's
because, yeah, they get eliminated.
And I guess, yeah, if you don't want
to maintain the balance of the natural existence
and you don't need to because you can
simply replicate.
Yeah, you can do anything.
For example, when I had the bike shop
and the reps would come in to sell
parts for me to sell to the customers
retail.
Right.
And the guy, you know, let's say they
have high end saddles.
They're not called seats.
They're called saddles on a bike.
Right.
OK.
And he had a really high end stuff
like, you know, you know, 100, 200 dollar
bicycle saddles.
And I would always mess with them.
You know, I got anything else.
What do you mean?
This is like the best stuff in the
world.
I said, no, I want some bicycle saddles
that have leather and skin made from endangered
species.
You got any of those men?
And they would look at me like I
was just like I said, I wanted to
go home and F his sister or something.
Right.
I was just joking.
So what I'm trying to say, one guy
got really in my face and said, I
want saddles made from leather of endangered species.
He wanted to kill me for saying because,
you know, you know, the brainwashing of the
right environmentalists.
So you want white you want white panther
coated bald eagle feather stuffed.
Yeah.
Like if there's like one white tiger left,
I want it dead and I want it
skin on my bicycle.
Right.
And and if there's enough left over, you'll
make a holder for your water bottle.
If it's the last one that that's even
better.
Now, that freaks people out when you talk
that way.
Now, do I really believe that?
I'm not going to confirm or deny it.
I'll let you decide, because I know I
know that you're not going to hear anybody
else saying that.
So, yeah.
Screw the animals.
I mean, don't screw the animals.
Let's be silly.
No, I have no regard for them other
than whatever.
Because if you're going to if you're going
to think about the big picture, like I
just said, moving forward.
Right.
That's what dictators did.
They get branded really bad in history.
But they were to eliminate huge amounts of
their population because they were like, we need
to clean this place up.
You ever you ever see people like a
young couple move into a neighborhood where some
old people lived?
And like for weeks they have dumpsters outside
throwing everything away, tearing stuff out.
You're like, my gosh.
It's like, well, this person had a lot
of crap in here.
You know, we had to gut the place.
Right.
So gut the damn place.
And yeah, creatures and everything and just make
a human society.
But you can't do that if you don't
have full control of your environment.
Right.
You have to be able if you need
gold, you go to a machine.
Boom.
You got gold.
You need you know, right.
You make everything is made.
You know, there's no mining.
There's no farming.
There's no right.
This is possible right now.
This can you can look.
I do the stuff that I'm talking about
in my kitchen.
Right.
And I need to start maybe doing some
videos or seminars, free seminar and say, hey,
look, guys, there's a camera.
Nothing fake over here.
Look, this is carbon.
I'm going to turn it into iron.
You can do this at home, too.
This is how you do it.
Right.
It's no fakery here.
Look, I'll even do a topless.
No shirt.
Don't show whatever.
I'll do it naked.
Don't show them how to make.
Yeah.
Don't show them how to make gold, though,
because somebody might come and try.
So we will show how to make gold.
I've gone over it many, many times.
It's biological gold that it has to be
taken to another level.
Quite a bit of confirmation with that.
It's not difficult.
There's a logic train there.
And you do use organic materials right now.
But, oh, my gosh, you know, it's people
don't want to hear.
They only want to hear the stuff that
they're being conditioned to hear.
Right.
So, you know, you know, here's a question
that kind of goes along with that.
But let me just say one more thing.
You start talking about eliminating all the animals
and insects and plants, all that stuff.
You can't do that as you are right
now.
You it will not work.
It'll be total havoc.
Right.
It's kind of like saying, let's get rid
of all the gasoline cars tomorrow.
That won't work.
You have to transition.
Right.
And then when they're almost all gone, then
you're like, oh, my gosh, I'm glad we
transitioned.
Right.
So anyway.
Well, yeah, if you're in the place and
it's, you know, been gutted, been redone, everything
is shiny and new.
Yeah.
Anyway, Greek has left hints on the power
of intent to create our reality.
Could you speak to whether it's about.
See, they're asking for technique here.
Do you write these things down?
Hold on.
You can't intend.
You have to have technical.
You have to intend to get technical access
and know how and where we're going to
do it.
Intention ain't going to do much.
Right.
But you can sit around a day and,
you know, people hope for a lot of
stuff there.
Their their their day is going to come.
And before you know, you wake up, you're
seventy five and nothing's happened.
And you're like, oh, shit, I should I
should have done something more than just waiting
around.
Right.
So, no, the intention is is doesn't intention
is is a variable in a very big
equation.
And if whenever you hear culturally, societally, whatever,
people just focusing on one thing like positive
thinking or and that's it, that'll get it
done.
No, it doesn't get it done.
Positive thinking is part is to be thrown
into a bag with twenty five other things.
So is intention.
So is the emo.
So is everything.
Nothing.
Right.
No monoculture of thought or spirituality.
It's all even in spirituality.
You have to do works.
You have to do things.
You have to.
Right.
And like you said, you got to first
get the tools in hand.
I mean, you know, here, build a bookshelf.
Here's a Phillips head screwdriver.
Not going to be the only thing you
need.
First, the tools.
They all have to come within a very
close time within each other, because if you
have one or two or three parts and
the other ones are taking too long, you'll
give up.
Right.
So you have to play.
It's planning.
You can actually be a real like sorry
ass fuck of a human.
And at the same time, while you're in
that state, start planning a great future or
a great reality for yourself.
But cover all the bases you cover.
Let's say you need money for this.
How am I going to get all the
money I need?
How's my outlook going to be?
How do I get myself better outlook?
How do I get my fitness level up?
Because I need energy to do this.
How do I find people around me that
will support what I want to do and
help them also?
And then the tools.
Right.
And the location.
All of that has to be planned.
So that comes.
There's no evolution.
One thing.
And then hopefully the next thing will come.
No, it doesn't work that way.
That's how you have a divided kingdom.
That's what you live in.
OK, well, here's another random strangeness.
And then I've got just one more thing
after this.
What is the Greek speak on Eden in
Florida?
In quotes, hypothesis.
A man called LV Edison Calloway in the
1930s, I think, researched and wrote about it.
Pre-flood civilization being in America.
Giants.
Yeah.
And reported in old newspapers all across the
land.
So what do you know about that?
Not much, but the archaics gets into that.
Everything really started here.
The modern society, people were everywhere all the
time, just like electricity has always existed.
Everyone in every culture knew about electricity, but
they didn't use it.
Right.
And then you had different levels of culture
that use it and others that knew about
it and didn't use it.
It's just like that.
You had very advanced cultures here.
But the thing about places that are heavily
desert, barren, flat land.
Yeah, we're different at one point.
And like, for example, like archaics gets into
a lot of this.
Most of the U.S. was underwater.
Not most.
A lot of it was.
You know, if you drive through, you don't
see any old trees through Arizona and Texas
and parts of California.
All these that this was all underwater.
That's why you can find fish fossils.
And if you dig deep enough in a
lot of desert, you'll actually find fish fossils
where you think there was never any water.
I find seashells.
What if I go down one, three, four
feet?
OK.
It's high desert.
It got pushed up.
But Charlemagne, there's they're constantly finding encampments here
where King Charlemagne is around 800 or ninth
century.
He had a colony here near Tucson and
they sailed here.
Right.
The water.
I mean, by car, you have to drive
three hours to go to the beach.
So they sailed to Tucson.
So it was very different.
It was an inland sea that connected to
the ocean to what they call the Gulf
of America now, I believe.
Right.
And all this.
So, yeah, that's only recent.
A very recent big geological changes everywhere.
But no, nothing about Eden in Florida, Florida.
Imagine that extending all the way down to
wherever you want to extend it.
You know, it was much more much different
than you mean.
The land was bigger landmass.
Yeah.
OK.
No problem there.
All right.
So let's start right off the coast of
Florida.
Florida, Cuba, there's underwater.
There's cities under there.
Yeah, there's all kinds.
They're all submerged remains like the Bimini Road
and.
Yeah, exactly.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Hemingway and all I got into.
Yeah, exactly.
OK, so look, this is the last one
here.
And let me just get that note up
because I put it on a text document.
I wanted to save it for a moment.
Where is it?
There it is.
Right.
OK, so this person went through the process.
They kind of argued with themselves for a
little bit and went through the process of
making that process, that voice inside their head.
Silent.
Oh, so they got rid of that.
And what resulted is that they started dreaming
differently and they're a little bit disturbed by
it.
Now, here's the thing about these dreams.
I get it.
Go ahead.
Probably things that I've experienced when I experimented
with that.
It's not like scary dreams or anything like
that, but literally the rules of reality change,
like to the point of you can walk
upside down on surfaces like you don't have
to worry about, like you can walk up
a wall and this kind of thing.
The rules of reality literally are changed in
these dreams.
And this person is wondering, is this another
trick by those entities to try and break
them in some way?
OK, yeah, I get it.
OK, you leave.
You live in an agreed upon reality.
Like everybody will pretty much agree.
You can't walk through walls.
You can't fly.
Right.
You can't dematerialize.
You can't be invisible, you know, physically or
all that.
So that's an agreed upon.
All of that is without a machine.
You can't travel over 10 miles an hour
or whatever.
Like, you know, yeah, et cetera.
That's agreed upon reality.
All those limitations, your perception or limitations.
The reason you see what you see is
because if you saw everything, you couldn't handle
it with the capacity, mental capacity that you
have.
So what's going on is if you're in
a dream state, if you train yourself, if
you can see your hands and move your
hands, you're not in a dream state.
You're in like a mid reality.
Right.
If if you still see a lot of
people say you dream in black and white.
That's just to satisfy a juvenile mentality.
Don't even ever think of that.
But another thing is, if you notice, if
you're dreaming and people are their speech, their
mouths are never moving.
Right.
But if you notice their mouths are moving
now, you're not in a dream anymore.
You're actually conveyed into a different in between
channels, let's say.
Right.
OK.
The other thing about that agreed reality that
I mentioned, you could.
Yeah.
The laws of of agreement that we have
here don't don't apply there.
So now they would be if if you
hear if you see if you hear speech
and you see the mouths are not moving
and you can't really have control of your
hands and see your fingers moving intentionally, it's
probably an implant again by those entities that
give dreams.
Yes, it's an implant.
But if you have control of those things,
I've had a dream, for example, I've asked
myself to dream.
And I went into a community where there
were sharks and horses like people.
And they honored me.
The horses honored me that a huge table
and there were horses.
They sat down and they grabbed beer mugs
and I saw my hands moving and their
mouths were moving and they were all talking.
And they were there, had these big steins.
And I don't recall exactly how they were
holding them with hooves.
But they were upright.
That's funny.
They were glad to meet me.
And there were some sharks there to be
careful.
The sharks are, you know, they're OK.
Just don't get too close.
And I was like, well, that's a real
fucked up situation.
It's got to be a dream.
Right.
But no, it passed all the tests.
But I saw their mouths move and my
hands were moving.
I was able to articulate.
So that was really cool.
I mean, you've heard of DMT, right?
Yeah, of course.
Yeah.
In literature.
You know, actually, that's kind of funny because,
you know, Gulliver's travels, right?
Everybody knows about the one where he shows
up and he's a giant because that's the
one they always show you in the cartoons
or the movies or whatever.
And then and then he's a microman.
And then he.
Yeah.
But there's actually the least known book of
them all is he's a horse.
People, the whole Williams, the horse people.
Right.
I was just going to say that.
And I was just wondering if that was
connected, if that was connected.
Yeah.
And no, that did not come to memory
till I gave this account to someone about
a year ago.
OK.
No, I was just curious if maybe, you
know, it was a very Tudor setting.
Tudor would be like sixteen hundreds, fifteen hundreds
village type thing.
Very rough hewn, using pretty real and smells.
If you get very strong smells and tastes.
But if you if you don't, the criteria
that I use is if you don't see
the mouths moving when their speech or you
can can articulate your hands, you're still being
fed a dream.
Now, remember, they depend on them, the inner
voice and all that.
Right.
OK, well, first of all, that's a success.
That's testimony on what I'm putting out, because
if this person worked on and he had
results about quieting the voice, that's another box
we could check off.
Another one that's that's advancing beyond the shit
that we let's put on us.
And that's only that's only the second person
who's written to me and told me that
they were able to do that, by the
way.
So, oh, there's more.
I've spoken to a few.
I believe you.
I mean, I did it, too.
But I'm just saying it's just funny to
me because it's like that's the second.
That's only the second person people have written
to me about over and over again, about
a lot of things.
But this is one of those things that
I've only heard twice, you know, coming back.
But the first thing here, look, it's an
open adventure.
I'm the only one really talking about that
voice in your head.
It's not you.
Well, actually, I did come across it in
Castaneda, something similar.
And you talk about the second attention and
all that.
But I'm the only one that's, I think,
taking it out of context that it's usually
given in some novel or whatever.
And I'm saying this is real.
And go ahead and work on it.
And you'll see your life change.
Your perception will change.
You'll be you can't be better off here,
by the way.
You know, when someone tells you do this,
you'll be better off here.
No, this is this is you can't be.
This is a place of compromise.
And but this sounds like something you should
test this whole dream thing, because he talks.
Yeah, but it's more than the dream thing.
Look, remember the dream thing is that dream
experience and all that is tied into calling
the voices, let's say.
Right.
So, yeah, of course, it's going to work
that way.
But also, they could take you down that
route where they show you instead of focusing
on this world, they make you focus on
another world.
Right.
That they they can assist you to do
that.
And it's still mess with you.
But there's also a series that I've noticed
that if you if they try doing a
replacement voice on you, one of the final
ones is prescience.
Like they give they make you psychic eight
seconds, two minutes into the future.
And most people, like I said, fall for
that.
Right.
Yes.
And then they work.
They go work with the police and they
find, you know, right.
And they say, I'm psychic.
No, you're not psychic.
You they replace the the typical entity with
one that does that.
And you believe it.
Oh, my gosh.
I mean, that could be anyone could be
right.
They gave you an entity that actually has
that knowledge and therefore gave you less work
to do that than to keep you occupied.
Right.
Otherwise.
So they they're very efficient at what they
do.
Yeah.
But here's the thing, like just like people,
they're not that smart.
They're lazy.
Right.
So, you know, once you understand that, you're
not going against a formidable enemy.
They're under you can consider these entities and
nonphysical entities formidable because they don't have physical
limitations.
But on the other hand, they wish they
did because there's something about having a physical
body enjoying this realm.
Right.
It's always like you're never happy with what
you got.
Right.
Like the humans want to be spiritual and
get out of the physical and not the
spiritual ones want to be physical.
Is that funny?
The grass is always greener.
Greener.
Well, the whole thing, this whole system is
screwed up.
You want to get out of the system,
not whether you're spiritual or physical.
You see what I mean?
Yeah.
Just to finish this question, though, just real
fast is the last part of it.
He mentions that he got rid of one
voice.
It seemed like it was gone for a
little bit.
Another one seemed to start up.
And then when he got rid of that
one, that's when these dreams started.
And the weird thing is, you know, besides
this sort of like defying the rules, like
you said, the agreed upon reality here is
that it also gave him like choices, like
he could decide to walk on water or
not in this other reality where, by the
way, there was fluid in strange places that
it wouldn't have normally been.
It was a very kind of almost seemed
chaotic, but he started to understand there was
an order to it.
And these things have rapidly and been constant
for many days afterwards.
Yeah.
Well, be careful because they might want to
drive you nuts, too.
Right.
So you might want to get rid of
that the same way you got rid of
the voices.
Fair enough.
So some of the most interesting people I
ever met was in the loony bin.
Not that I was there, but I knew
how to visits.
You know, someone said, hey, let's go visit
whatever.
They're in the psych ward.
Right.
And once a week, the ones that are
not dangerous, they're out.
They're out like a public room.
They can't leave the building, but the public
could go and interact with them.
OK, well, usually you sit next to me,
talk to me like they seem pretty normal.
But after like 30 seconds, like, oh, shit.
Now I know why you got your ass.
It's like if you go on the you
know, you go into the on the wrong
train on the subway one day and you
end up in a part of New York
that you don't normally go to.
But that seems to be.
Well, it depends.
It depends.
But also some of the most interesting people
like very well, like Tesla said, an insane
person can think very deeply.
But an insane person cannot think clearly.
So you get a lot of deep thought.
And first of all, if you were too
progressive in your let's say your level of
intellectuality, if there is such a word, the
powers that be want to see you either
like addicted to drugs, homeless, living on a
park bench, eating out of a garbage can
or an insane asylum or jail.
They don't want you in the public.
Look, fair enough.
And, you know, one of the coolest things
I ever thought I saw when I was
younger is the first guy I saw with
one of those, you know, five gallon paint
can drum sets, you know.
And I love that guy.
But was he sane by standard concept?
Yeah.
So that was in Times Square in the
80s, really late 70s, 80s.
Exactly.
But the first time I saw it, it
was amazing to me.
And that guy, when you talk to him,
though, you know, yeah, it would take about
a couple of minutes.
And then you realize this guy's probably not
going to hold any other kind of job.
So probably good.
He's making paint can drums.
Well, you don't want a job.
You should have a job.
Quit your job.
Learn how to use revenue.
Right.
Fair enough.
We're having a lot of fun with that,
by the way.
We've like I said, we've made the group
more private.
The chat groups will just take you to
the old one.
We're going to nuke that pretty soon.
But we're just moving along.
We're just moving along.
It's it's such a such a cool thing
to wake up to stuff that has been
around for over 100 years.
Let's say we're just about 100 years and
has been taken advantage of by those who
know about it.
And they're not hiding it because you can
find out just by reading.
Right.
Cool.
Yep.