The Sonic Event 26, rated Y, Ocelli and the Greek.
So trying to break the pattern, put a few things out of order, and who knows what will
come of this one, because there is no script.
We might talk about things just a little bit ahead of time.
We just did that before I pressed record.
So here we are.
Greek, how are you doing tonight?
Yeah, I keep telling you, man.
Let's just hit record, because we don't want the best stuff to just go into the ether,
right?
You know, I'm in my 50s.
I can only go once, you know?
But anyway, so yeah, you were saying – go ahead.
You start, man.
You start talking about – you were saying something – you brought up something.
So bring it up again.
Well, okay.
All right.
Well, I didn't give you the whole thing because I wanted to record it and just get your reaction
and your thoughts.
Look, I had a strange thing go on this week at my house, right?
And I know you don't like personal stories, but it got me thinking about other things.
And here's what happened.
We had mice all of a sudden and kind of invaded the house.
And I was getting irritated because, you know, look, the mice, what do they do?
They poop.
They chew on stuff.
I mean, they cause problems.
Everybody talks about disease and whatnot with them.
I don't know.
I don't have firsthand experience with that, but you don't want mice in the house, okay?
So what did I end up having to do?
This week I killed three mice by hand.
Well, by hand, by hammer, and by toolbox, because I encountered them.
And when they were out in the open, I just grabbed what I could and I smashed them.
I set traps before that, trying to get them and everything else.
Now, what is the point of this story?
Well, it got me thinking, actually, about the hierarchy of creatures on the planet.
Now, why?
Okay, look, I go back to the old biblical story as it was related to me, right?
And the garden, and here's the animals, why don't you name them, et cetera, et cetera.
And I think about all that, and now you're the steward of all the animals.
There's a lot of things going on here.
First of all, did the Adam see fish?
Did he see bugs?
Did we have to name all the bugs?
You know, look, there's a lot of living things here on this rock, whatever shape you think
it's in.
There's definitely a hierarchy.
We even talked about pets, right, and how dogs and cats are higher level animals than
maybe some others.
And we talked about the order of things about what you can eat and what you should eat,
what you should not eat, et cetera.
I don't know, it's just that we've always touched upon this, and I've never really asked
you about, well, look, I may remember talking about bugs a few times, and we talked about
different entities that might be in charge of them, et cetera, but we're all sharing
this planet, right?
So, yeah, go ahead.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, no, just real quick.
Do you need to rent a cat?
I used to do that back in the day, not here in the Southwest, but when people had a mouse
problem.
You know, you've heard of bodega cats, right?
So yeah, you need to rent a cat.
That's anybody listening, you're free to use that.
I don't know about the animal control people, the animal rights people, but yeah, rent a
cat will take care of that.
If you've got mice that are bold like that, it means they're breeding.
When I had, before I had cats, I have a big area outside where I plant things that I call
tree rings.
Everywhere there's a tree, I get these terracotta chimney pipes, and I put them all around and
fill them with soil.
I'd go out in the morning, and it was just like a Disney cartoon.
One mouse is on top of the terracotta pipe, you know, two feet off the ground.
He's telling a joke, and all the other mice are listening, and when he stops talking, they
all start laughing and rolling over, and then they see me, they're like, oh no.
A lot of the Disney stuff was based on people watching animals, you know?
Especially, you know, you've seen a dog run in place, right?
Because he has no traction, you know, you watch the cartoons, what does the dog do?
Run in place, right?
Yeah, I love that.
When they go doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo, and they start slipping, you know, that's a funny
thing.
Or a spike, yeah.
I don't have cats.
So you watch Disney?
Yeah, so I don't have cats.
I do have some little dogs, and the little dogs are not good mousers.
There's a couple of stray cats wandering around outside my house now a little more often.
Seems as though I'm being invaded from somewhere, so I don't know if they're breeding, or if
I'm just, you know, suffering a general invasion.
My little dogs are only good for, well, the oldest one anyway, is good for finding them.
A few times where she gets obsessed about an area or something, and I discover that, okay,
there was a mouse there.
That's why she was obsessed with the area.
But she doesn't catch them.
The pups who are less than a year old, they don't catch them, but I have a couple times.
Okay, I don't know if you remember, I don't know if it was with you or others, I brought
up something, and only two people, which I consider very deep thinkers, brought it up
again, and I've never brought it up.
No one else has brought it up, but animals have been coming up a lot lately, and I said,
you ever notice, I think I was doing the Solosonics on AFR, humans, a man, has a vertical
spine.
Animals have a horizontal spine, meaning their spine is parallel to the Earth, ours is perpendicular.
Why is that?
Right?
And I never really got into it, and the reason is, I could get into, it's a long explanation.
I've tried to make it short.
The shortest I can say is because we perceive things differently.
The way we, spatial perception and sound and sight is ether, so the way ether flows, we're
very dependent.
The way we see things, like when we are approaching, let's say we see a wall with a hole in it,
let's say in nature that would be a mountain with a cave opening.
As we walk closer to it, we're perceiving it as, look, we're walking closer, that's
why the opening is getting bigger, right?
Perspective.
As we get closer, it gets bigger.
As you walk further away, it gets smaller.
Animals don't perceive it that way.
As I'm walking this way, I'm not really moving, the Earth is moving around me.
My whole life, I'm stationary.
So look, the Earth is moving, the mountain is moving towards me, and the hole is moving
towards me, getting bigger.
You see the difference?
It's kind of like on a treadmill.
They spend their whole life thinking that they're stationary, and everything around
them is moving.
Yeah, perspective-wise, it's almost like one of those video games where you've got
a person walking, stays in the center of the screen, but the rest of the world moves around
them.
Exactly.
It's more like a video game for them.
Very good.
That's a good analogy.
So their life is more like...
And then we go to the plants, which is dream world, right?
If you're in a dream and your arm gets cut off, eh, fuck it, I'm dreaming, right?
Yeah, it's just a dream, yeah, sure.
Yeah.
When you go and cut a branch off a tree, eh, what the fuck, what's going on here?
I'm just dreaming.
Hey, by the way, these things called natural hallucinogenics, they modify them from plants
anyway.
Where do they come from?
Plants.
Guess what?
Because, right?
Right.
They're always hallucinating.
It's just the ones that transfer over to humans.
Yeah.
So I wanted to bring up a couple of points, and the chat usually we bring up.
Oh, yeah.
But we always, lately, the hot topic has been the magnetic water, and yes, that's good.
And I've been very active in the chat about it, because if you're excited about it, you
should be, because I keep saying, I keep giving hints.
If you're an enterprising individual, whatever that means, wink, wink, you know what this
is, right?
Okay.
This is like saying, hey guys, there's this stuff that just came out, Bitcoin, and it's
25 cents.
Are you an enterprising individual?
Get it?
I'm not going to say buy it.
You know what I mean, right?
Yeah.
No, look, there's some way to get involved in this, in a way, before the whole world
knows about it.
Do it.
Yeah.
So I don't want it to come off right.
I really wish, I mean, look, I remember when people were trying to sell me whole Bitcoins
literally for $80, and I said, I can't, I couldn't see.
It was 25 cents three years ago.
Yeah.
Well, it made no sense to me, because it's like, well, I'd rather have a silver coin,
because I know that.
I've had it in my hand before.
I'm familiar with it, and that wasn't me being enterprising about that.
I didn't think about it the right way.
Right, but this is like that, because, okay, and we're not going to talk about this anymore,
but let me just say this thing.
What I've been working on now, and I'm going to share also, most likely in a solo, is the
technical aspects of it, and it's so simple that anyone can easily reduce what's in the
water by 30% to 40%, no exaggeration, right?
But one thing I'm just going to say, I saw someone in the chat using an RO, and RO requires
a lot of pressure, a lot of time.
I have done, doing, and will do more tests, but if you have a pump, let's say that's running,
and before the water goes into the pump is treated, you're going to use 10% to 30% less
electricity to move the water, right?
So if you talk to anyone who has a large commercial business that requires RO water, car wash,
soda bottling plant, whatever, whatever, you ask them about their electric bill, they kind
of joke and hem and haw, because they don't want to tell you how much.
It's embarrassing.
You know what I mean?
It's so high, right?
Right.
And that's because of the reverse osmosis pumps.
Well, what if I said you could shave that by 25%, would you be interested in your electric
bill?
That's a lot.
That's a salary.
Then you have bigger projects, and so on and so forth.
So that's all I'm going to say about that, but what I'm working on is I know for sure
20 years ago would get you killed.
A device that you run dirty water through, and there's no guts to it.
The device, in other words, take the device out of the system and just hold it.
You can look right through it.
There's no guts.
There's nothing in there, right?
It's just straight through.
Yeah.
So it's not a machine.
It's not a filter.
It's just a pipe.
Yeah.
Well, let's say it's a box, but you can see right through it, right?
This is like a magic trick almost.
You put dirty water on one side and clean water comes out the other, and that's it.
Story is done.
I think we talked about this already, right?
Case closed.
I've been working on that.
I ran some turbid water through, and it went from 590 parts per million to 340, and it
did get a little clearer, and this was just putting stuff together with hot melt, right?
So yeah, now I heard we've discussed this or whatever.
I think we brought it up the last time.
I think that if you did the 100-mile-per-gallon carburetor, there's no carburetors in cars
anymore, or this device or free energy or whatever, I don't think they kill you anymore,
do they?
I haven't heard about that in a while, to be honest with you, so yeah.
I don't think the suppression is that much because they're going after food and water
and energy, right?
Okay, so that's all I'm going to say about that.
The other thing I was – there's more on that, people.
There's more on that, and it will be shared, and whoever's listening now will know how
to get it in the near future when I talk about it some more.
The thing is, by the way, it's all open-sourced.
Once these devices come out or I have success and it's reproducible, if you want to know
how to make it, I'll tell you how to make it.
It's no big deal.
Someone posted – Harry, I think it was Vandy posted Harry, who's a guy that called me
for a while about weather devices.
He's very active on YouTube, and he says he wants to tell the whole world about it.
I said, well, I can't really talk about how to do the newer stuff because Trevor was
still alive.
I didn't say that.
I just – I know how to make stuff that – whatever.
When Trevor passed away – Harry, you got in touch with me again a few months later.
I said, well, Trevor passed, so guess what?
Get yourself some silk.
Get some double mirrors and do this, and he's been very, very, very public.
I was very, very happy that someone asked him, so you got this from someone who worked
with Trevor?
He says, yes, someone worked with Trevor.
I said, who is it?
But he doesn't want his name known because I said, look, you plan on going public.
His whole thing is to be on CNN, right?
I don't want him to say, you learned it from me, because what does that do?
That makes me an accomplice, right?
Well, somebody got his YouTube video.
Yeah.
So I don't – this is – I never wanted – like if CNN – I know one of the people
here in Arizona.
You remember the Iran-Contra affair, the main thing?
The Army Air Force always sells old planes, okay?
And they put in the clause that once you buy the old plane, it's salvaged.
You can't resell it.
It has to be torn apart, right?
Well, in this particular contract for Iran-Contra, they left that part out so he could resell
the plane, right?
I know – his first name is David.
He lives here in Tucson.
I've known him for a long time.
I haven't seen him in a while, but – and when the Iran-Contra thing went down, they
exposed enough that they found where they got the planes from.
So he lives here in Tucson, and they – this is in the probably early 90s, late 80s when
the thing went down with the Oliver North stuff, right?
Late 80s, yeah.
Late 80s.
Well, they knocked on his door early in the morning, and he opens the door, and he sees
all these spotlights on him, and he's like, what the hell, you know?
I'm not being arrested.
This is the news.
This is nothing.
So he kept talking to the news, right?
You don't want to do that, right?
You don't want to talk to the news people.
And I learned that from there.
Everybody was like, yeah, you don't talk to the news if they come to your house, right?
Never.
Never talk to the news.
It's usually not a good thing if they find you and they come knocking on your door, yeah.
Yeah, because they can edit it and make it say like you said anything, right?
It's how they piece it together.
And they did that famously to Jim Garrison, too, by the way, which was a really funny
thing.
You know, JFK stuff, of course.
I was just thinking about it because I was working on something this week, but they did
that to him where he had an interview with an interview guy who was like totally friendly
to him.
He got out a bunch of stuff, this and that, and then they turned around, re-edited it
and made him sound like a lunatic.
Right, right.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Because plausibly, you know, we're putting this on front, you know.
So when you hear about this guy again, you can see, obviously, he's a nutcase.
That's what they do.
Yeah.
So, yeah.
So when Harry told me he wants to bring this to the world in every way he can, I'm like,
oh, no, you just leave me out of it then.
Yeah, that's up to you, but leave you out of it.
Yeah.
Yeah, he did, which was good.
Fair enough.
And I'm just saying this because it's funny because he's, it's nice to see people, well,
let's just say when you do something and someone gets really, really, really excited and makes
it sort of a lifelong thing, it's kind of good.
You feel kind of, you know, hey, good, you know, where would this guy be if he didn't
have this, right?
Right.
It'd be boring, right?
At least he's getting some excitement.
I got a couple of guys started with, like, podcasting, believe it or not, that had no
design on doing it and then decided they wanted to and came to me, asked me how to do stuff,
this and that.
And the third thing, and it's kind of fascinating to look in on them a couple of years later
and it's like, that's their, their whole thing now and they're, you know, completely into
it.
That's what they do.
You know?
Yeah.
The only thing about Harry is, is my advice to people, if you get into the weather work,
just make bad weather.
Forget about sunshine.
I mean, yeah, look, whatever.
Make bad weather, help out the Aggies, help out the farmers, you know, but other than that,
make bad weather, you know, because that's what people want.
They want disasters.
Speaking of disasters, what I was also saying earlier, this changes, let's get into it a
little bit.
You go down to a Jewish community in Florida and there's a restaurant, I know there's at
least one now left, it's called number 26.
This is episode 26, right?
Yeah.
Masonic 26.
And if you ask them why do you call it 26, because they say it's the name of God, right?
That's what they say usually, or, right?
Because the numerology, the mantra on Yahweh is 26.
I just wanted to bring that up as trivia.
The Asians do 88 a lot, like Pho 88, you know, Pho 88, this is the Vietnamese soup, or Chinese,
they like the number eight.
But anyway.
Which is odd, too, because, you know, 88 for a while, at least early internet, as I understood
it, was supposed to represent Adolf Hitler in some way, and I forget why, but there was
some reason for it.
You know what I'm talking about?
Talk about getting the shit end of the stick in history.
Yikes.
But, I mean, just saying, yeah, well, ask Gaddafi about that, but, you know, I'm done.
I'm just saying, it's like, it's very weird when people attach things to numbers, because
on the one hand, it's a valid thing, numerology, and on the other hand, I don't know, sometimes
I just, I listen to people run around in circles with it, and I go, you have tortured yourself
with these numbers, you know?
Yeah, well, don't overdo it.
Just like with words, you know, they say, like, history is his story, television is
telling lies on your vision, and the son of God is the sun in the sky, right, only works
in English, you know, you hear this all the time, the George Maxwell, Jordan Maxwell's
and, oh wow, sorry about that, and the Bonacci's or whatever, they try to play these things
on people that don't know.
Look, if you're going to try to play people that are ignorant, you're going to have a
lot of followers, you know why?
Because, anyway, I don't want to get into it, right?
Stuck on stupid, so, anyway, where was I with this, the play on words?
I put in the chat, I was in a response, if you're good at math, you're going to be good
at language, because they're both forms of communication.
Math is just communication.
Now, there's a lot of people, I think I went over the psychological aspects, when you say
you're not good at math, it's simply because when you were young, you heard someone that
was sort of respected for saying that, so you said, oh, I could be lazy, right, I don't
have to learn math, and I could just go around in life and say I'm not good at math, and
everybody pats me on the back, that's okay, right, you see how it works?
You can learn good and bad things by example, right, because, I mean, look, the example
given there is that somebody gets themselves out of having to do some sort of little bit
of work, or having to think their way through something, which is a form of communication,
don't think of it as math, is the point, right, so you're cutting yourself off from a form
of communication, right?
True.
That's all it is, people say, oh, I need to do the math on that, I said, why, you just
told me about it, and they're like, huh, I said, well, math is just another form of communication,
you ever hear that a lot, oh, this is how this works, but I haven't done the math on it,
yes, you did, you just told me, that's why I like the five percenters, you know, in New
York, you know, word is bond and all that, because they say, that doesn't add up, right,
whenever something, instead of saying, that's untrue, or that's whatever they say, it doesn't
add up, do the math, they're correct about that aspect of it, you know, so math is just
another language, and it's a universal language, Jack Fresco mentioned this before, like, if
you talk about sodium as an element, why do you have to call it different things in
different languages, just give it a number or a symbol that represents sodium, and everyone
will see it as being sodium, right, that's what numbers do, and yeah, so you learn a
lot about people by them telling you, that's why I say, listen, be a good listener, they're
telling you what shortcomings they've decided to adapt, you know what I mean, I'm not good
at math, all right, that means that you just, right, get it, so, doesn't mean you have
to be good at math, but typically, whoa, that sounds like a cherry bomb, you know, it's
a straight pipe, yeah, so, I'm near the street right now, actually, so, but the whole thing
with math is, it's not universal enough, but the idea is there, and a universal language,
there are people trying to do universal languages like Esperanto, I don't know if you remember
that, it started in the 50s, Interlingue is another one, it's a mixture of Latin, Spanish,
the whole world's gonna speak one tongue, it didn't really work for them, the UN wrote
a thing about it, anyway, math is not as good as that, you know, how do you say I love you
with numbers, right, you see, it's not very, quote, unquote, romantic, but the reason I
brought all that up is because it's number 26, and I wanna talk a little bit about the
spiritual side of stuff, you know, but in a technical way, should we say, where you
can actually use it, if that makes any sense, you know, because people, you know, say, oh,
this guy's really spiritual, I said, spiritual just means non-physical, is it good or bad
spiritual, right, they're like, well, it's spiritual, of course it's good, right, you
know, I never understood that at all, either, where it's like, oh, they're very spiritual,
it's like, well, what does that mean, exactly, that doesn't, well, yeah, spiritual just means
non-physical, so are they in the dark or are they light, and by the way, there's no problem
with the dark or the light, you have to have them in balance, right, in this structure
and construct that we have, you know, like I keep saying, the Star Wars, the whole thing
about Star Wars is not the Jedi defeating the self, no, no, no, no, it's putting it
back in balance, because the Jedi got caught out there with being eliminated, and now the
self are over overcoming, right, and it's just to put them in balance, it's not that
either one, one tried to get rid of the other created an imbalance, even here, it's an imbalance
in the force, you know, so having the balance both ways, you know, like I said, some of
the best quote-unquote religious or God-type conversations I've ever had are with atheists
and Satanists, right, because one is abstracted from the whole thing, and the other one is
anti, right, and I'm showing them that, you know, he's just a revolutionary, you know,
this Satan, that's, right, the adversary, he's a revolutionary, he's not this thing that
Hollywood shows you, right?
Well that's when you get into that type of Satanist, and then there's the other types
who effectively have decided that they are God, they are their own God.
Oh, yeah, yeah, well they are, actually, this is his world, by the way, and the thing is
calling it a construct or a simulation, I don't like doing that unless you really, really
see what's going on, and then you'll see that it is, right?
Well, see, now, that's strange too, because to call something a simulation, it means that
it would be mimicking something else that is known.
Right.
So what is the simulation mimicking?
There is the open question I have for anybody who brings up the simulation theory.
Yeah, go ahead, I'm sorry, yeah.
But it is a simulation because it's a physical counterpart of something that's non-physical,
right?
Well, okay, that's fine, but still...
That's where it's a simulation.
Okay, but isn't that a serious missing aspect of that when somebody says, oh, this is all
a simulation?
I go, yeah, but a simulation of what?
Because anything that is a simulation has to represent something else, right?
Yes.
So what is the else, you see?
Have you seen or heard, back in the 50s, it was more popular in the 60s or 70s, when Westerners
with tech in the 60s that went to indigenous peoples and they didn't want to be videotaped
because they believed that it captured their...
It would steal their soul, and yeah, right.
Yeah, yeah, right, right.
So when you saw a videotape of yourself, doesn't it look, for a moment, aren't you captivated
and that's me, right?
Then there's a part of you that says, oh, this is technology, right?
That's literally a simulation of yourself watching a movie, and the better, the more
it's done, the more, right?
If the movie's not good, people...
If you start...
You know how you find out if people are enjoying the movie, you start making a distraction.
If no one tells you to shut up and sit down, the movie sucks, right?
So anyway, it's actually good etiquette.
So to not do that in a movie theater, I don't know if anyone...
I can't go to the movies, by the way, because the sound and the picture that I have here
is way better than any movie theater I've been to, even the IMAX, believe it or not.
So the simulation, just like the indigenous, let's say, non-technological people do not
want their...
They don't want to be videotaped.
Really it was photographs, especially a land camera, a Polaroid or whatever.
Why did their mind go to that point, so extreme, right?
They don't want to be copied, they don't want to be captured, right?
It's called a capture anyway, when you do a screen capture on the computer.
Right, right.
So you have the real thing, which is existing in one domain, and then you have the capture,
which is in another domain.
We are in the physical capture domain, okay?
So that's where the simulation tests out, you see?
Yeah, but I'm still failing to recognize where the original is.
Oh, if you have a concept of what they call time and space, which neither one has any
attributes, right?
Space has no attributes, that's why it's called space, and time is just the recordation of
events, so it doesn't exist really, unless you make it.
It's a record.
That's where it exists, and the way you see that is from life and death.
I keep saying, don't worry about doing anything here.
It's all pre-scripted, right?
People say they want to be successful.
The presidents are pre-scripted.
You know, in America, you grow up and be president, right?
Or these Jeff Bozo and Elon Musk or whatever, those guys were put in those Bill Gates before
they were born, or those things were structured for them, and they fit it.
They had no choice in the matter, to a certain degree.
The only choice they had was dancing between the raindrops at some points, you know?
Wherever you are is where you are, and you have a certain thing, like being on the cruise
ship.
It's all predestined, but while you're on the cruise ship, you can go into your cabin,
you can go up to the deck, you can go to the movie, you know, but a cruise ship is like
a small city, right?
You've got a little choice.
That's the freedom, but everyone's going to a certain place, but if you're in uniform,
you don't have that kind of, quote unquote, liberty, no pun intended, because liberty
is a naval term, so you don't have those freedoms, right?
So the people that people see that are successful and noteworthy are in uniformed in some way
to be there, and they have no choice.
So I've also said and imparted that it takes 50 to 100 years to master something, a skill.
You don't have that much time to grow up formative years, adolescent, start a skill, and 100
years later start producing what that skill is.
It means you have to live to several hundred years, right?
So imagine you're walking at a flea market or an open air market, and you're negotiating
a rug, you know, and the guy says, it's this much, and you're like, oh, I want to give
you that much, and he says, come on, I've been making this for 50 years.
Imagine that?
We don't have that now, right?
So this is out of our concept, so that's what I mean about these concepts of once you start
going outside, where is it, what is it?
We can only relate to it based on what we know.
That's why I use that long metaphor.
It takes 50 years, and things are scripted, so where is the other one?
The other one is not limited by things like that.
It is more open.
Look, you don't like this place, go to another world.
In other words, you hear people, I don't like this country, I don't like this neighborhood,
I've got to go somewhere else, but it's difficult, I can't afford it.
Or whatever, whatever, political situations.
In the other world, you don't have that.
You want to go somewhere else, you're there, and it could be anywhere.
I wanted to give several examples, and you started off with your personal thing with the
mice and whatnot, right?
I'm going to give a personal example, because also, it's going to be interesting, hopefully,
and let me just recap.
We had a whole thing that, remember the call-ins in Ocelli in the Greek?
Oh, yeah.
I was like, if you call in, we don't want to hear personal stories unless it has an attribute
that we could get something out of it that everyone can use, right?
I think we're the only ones that ever said that.
I don't want to hear what you think about your opinion or your personal stuff.
Give us something that everyone can use.
Make it useful.
Right.
It's got to be applied to everyone.
The only way I could, let's say, move this forward is by giving a useful story.
Years ago, this is like 15 years ago, man, when you tell someone 2003 on the Pope's work
schedule doesn't seem like a long time ago, you know how you get, you're old, right?
You tell this to a 20-year-old, they don't...
20 years ago is almost their whole life.
I mean, what are you going to do?
Yeah, right.
Exactly.
So for me, 2003, I could tell you 2003, 2000, or 5, 6, 7, seems like a couple of years ago.
So some guys that I knew, enterprising young men, they said, you know, someone got a property
in Safford, which is like 100 miles out of Tucson, and they got some people, they got
to dig a well.
Safford, by the way, Arizona, the grass doesn't grow more than a half inch tall because that's
how windy it is, right?
And they want to dig a well, but we know that you can use those dowsing rods and find water
in the ground.
So let's go out there.
I'm like, all right.
So we go out there, and I walk around the property, it's like basically a mesa, and I'm walking
around for half an hour or so, and I said, give me a piece of paper, I'm going to mark
where I'm at.
And a couple of times I went back to the same spot, and I called the guy over, and I said,
this is where you're going to dig, it's going to be around 3,000 feet.
And he makes this really strange looking face, like he's almost upset or mad at me.
He says, hold on a second.
And he backs his pickup truck, drops the bed, opens the box, takes out this roll of paper
or whatever that he got from the welding company, and he says, give me that sheet you got.
I'm like, okay.
You know, where I drew the thing, and he says, this is the property, pretty close.
He puts it over, he says, this is where they told me to dig.
This is where the well's going to go, exactly right here is where they figured out with
their radar and all that stuff.
Because he was skeptical, right?
So I was like, okay, cool.
So my office says, no, you're right on.
I'm like, okay, all right, well, why the attitude, right?
Why the tood, right?
I remember that very strongly, this was a long time ago too, let's say.
So we're driving back to Tucson, and they pull over into this, between Safford and Tucson
into this place, little street, you know, one store, one light, what are you doing here?
He says, oh, they have good Mexican food here at the gas station kind of thing, right?
And I'm like, but this is, I said, I'm not hungry.
He said, well, we really didn't come here for this, we came here for this.
So they call someone up, and he meets us there, and he says, is this the guy?
And I'm like, well, are you guys going to let me in on this?
What do you mean, is this the guy?
So we drive about 10, 15 minutes in north-south direction.
They take me to this abandoned house, and they said, this house here, everybody says
it's haunted.
A little girl died in a fire, or the family, it was a fire or something, or whatever, and
the little girl died years ago.
You could see it was scorched and some other things broken, partially broken down.
People that are in the neighborhood hear the little girl screaming, and they see the little
girl on the top floor sometimes, right?
So go ahead and do your thing.
I'm like, oh, what do you mean?
Because I'm talking about how these spirits don't work the ways.
Yeah, go ahead and do it.
I said, I can't do it.
What do you mean?
No preface?
Nothing?
You just drive, give me like five, not even two-minute introduction?
Drag me in here, and here's a beat-up house, somebody died here, do your thing.
Yeah, and they drive away, I said, all right, give me some time.
Right away, without even thinking, I said, okay, this is nothing special, let's see if
I could walk the talk and talk the walk, right?
So, I faced the house, and I basically, I'm going to preface here, paraphrase, basically
talking to the house, and I'm saying, why are you taking advantage of these ignorant
people that think it's a young girl?
Why are you doing this imagery and this show?
Go somewhere else and do a show, don't do a show here.
See, because the little girl is dead, she's done, it's just, you know, right?
So, a spirit, quote-unquote, one of these intangibles, that deals with humans, this
is the type of spirit which I'll get into, that also brings dreams and thoughts and inner
voices, a different part of the group, but one of them, decides to play a joke on humans,
right?
Like they all meet at a bar, and they say, oh yeah, I'm going to go haunt this house,
and watch, and everyone's going to think it's this person that died, and they all high-five
them, and one guy says, oh, I'll bet you they're not going to believe it, and how much are you
going to bet me?
I'll bet you like a beer, you know, and they leave the bar, you know, the spirits, right?
And the guy's playing the thing.
So anyway, I'm basically saying, these people are ignorant, you're taking advantage of them,
and you know it, stop taking advantage of the people.
Okay, so basically, that was my exorcism and my unhaunting, and it worked, from what I
found out, and I kept, I was like, I need feedback, I need feedback, I need feedback,
and I need feedback for a couple of years later, yeah, there's nothing been seen, and
it was frequent, you know?
So what I just said was very simple, and it seemed very uneventful, it wouldn't make
a good ghostbuster, what is it, house haunters, or whatever, TV show, where it would, yeah,
they got a few, they got a few of those, the ghost hunters, and the, yeah, yeah, that
would be very uneventful, right, it wouldn't be, yeah, you know, now, right, so, but here's
the other thing, for me, it didn't look like anything was going on, but for the people
that were, I needed to be left alone, they were saying there was some interesting stuff
going on while I was talking to the house, interesting like what?
Well, it looked like the house shook a little bit, they heard a noise, this and that, right?
I didn't hear anything, but what I just went through, you notice, I just paraphrased, but
it was like, eh, meh, doesn't sound like much, that's an unhaunting, or an exorcism, quote
unquote, thing, very uneventful, doesn't make for good TV at all, but it works, because
you, if you, what are the, what did you call them, ghost hunters, whatever?
That's one of the big ones, yeah.
Yeah, oh, what do they do, if you call them, what are they going to do?
They're going to address the little girl.
Yeah, they go in at night, and, okay, we're going to find this spirit, they show you a
picture, and they go, okay, this person died here, so we're going to find, if it was the
little girl, yeah.
Yeah, so they're going after the person who died, which is a waste of time.
Right, no, absolutely true, you and I talked about this many years ago, actually, like
during the first run, I think, of O and J, and yeah, exactly, this is, you're
exactly right, this is the way it actually works, all that crap they put on TV is a bunch
of, yeah.
Here's the thing, yeah, but no one knows it, because the TV is messing them up, you
know, you know how I've talked about, as seen on TV, people, when you talk about, you
know, you listen to people, it's like 99% of what they, well, most of what they say
is they got from watching the tube.
Oh, yeah, I mean, and there's a whole thing now on the Travel Channel, by the way, which
is hugely popular, and I don't remember the name of it, but several people have been
like, you got to see this, because this is amazing, and the one guy goes in like a
regular detective, and he does like a history on the place, and who owned it, and who
died there, who lived there, etc., all that stuff, and he does it separate from the
psychic, right, so then the psychic goes in at night, and they film the psychic going
through, and she goes, oh, I'm feeling this, I see this, I hear this, and you're
watching her, you're not seeing any of this stuff, you understand, all this stuff that
she says she sees that's happening, and whatever else, you're just watching her
describe it, and then they get together, supposedly with no communication, maybe
you've heard of this thing, have you heard of this?
Yeah, but is it good TV or not, that's the point.
It's kind of interesting as a TV show.
Yeah, that's right, but in reality, they're not addressing anything, you know, but the
thing is, eventually, it will, you know what that will do, if they don't address it
the way, let's say, I did, I'm not saying my way is the only way, that's going to
invite more haunting.
Well, see, that's the thing, is that somebody else who wants to go put on a show
is going to go, hey, I can go put on a show, and I can get on TV with it, too.
Yeah, exactly, just like I hear some of these sci-fi, they're real alien, they put
a real alien there just to hear what people, if they could pick them out.
Yeah, right.
So, you know.
Why not?
That makes perfect sense, actually, and it's exactly that, so now that meeting at
the bar where somebody goes, hey, I bet I can get a show going over here, now they
can go for an even bigger game, you know what, not just freak the people out in the
neighborhood, how about we'll get the whole country looking at this, it'll be a
famous one, you know, like what was the biggest one you and I would know about,
Amityville, right, Amityville's the biggest thing ever, remember the Lutz family and
all that?
That was boosted, yeah, big time, that was a huge franchise in the 80s for a while.
Right, right, huge franchise, now, as for what really happened there, I mean, there
was a legitimate thing that historically happened there, but honestly, what are your
thoughts about that, though?
I mean, you know about that, right?
Yeah, I do, but I never, that would be people who are in the investigative capacity on
that subject, and I'm not.
I look at it from an overall general, just going like the magnets, you know, for
everyone's, keep it strange, but everyone says put the water where the magnet is
effective, I say put it where it's not, and watch what happens, right?
Well, let's go step by step on the bullet points of that real fast, and just let me
get your input on it, okay?
Because you have the whole situation that goes on in the 70s, right, which is this
kid, you know, takes a shotgun and murders his family, I mean, that happened, okay, so
that was a thing that occurred.
And he claims, or there were claims that he is possessed, and this and that, now, what
are your thoughts on that, a guy who just, you know, wakes up one night, he's got his
problems, whatever, he was, you know, smoking too much weed, drinking too much?
Well, okay, real short.
It was an Amityville horror because it was done, supposedly, by the undead, right?
Well, the undead influencing the younger guy who kills the family, first start.
Oh, that's, okay, that's when it ends, right?
That's when it ends.
That's, yeah, that's legit, and then when it continues, it's still, it's not the,
anyone who died, it's another spirit coming and doing it, you see how I anthropomorphized
it by saying the spirits meet at a bar?
Right, now, here's the thing about this, right, now, that's the first stage of the
story, and that's the backstory to the franchise.
The franchise comes about because of the Lutz family who supposedly moves in afterwards.
And now, they're being, they're, they got poltergeist, they got the room from hell
in the basement, they got the whole, all kinds of crazy stuff we're seeing up ahead.
Yeah, that's legit, that's legit, but I'm sure it was boosted big time, exaggerated,
that's legit, but it's not what they think or have been told it is, it's just opportunists
on the other side using it, just like they have a network, the spirit beings, they can
be like a hive, right, and they can actually, if you watch a lot of that and believe it,
you could actually invite them into your own house.
Like, for example, when, this is kind of a diversion a little bit, but let's say one
of these spirits runs across someone on the planet, and all he has to do is be, anybody
got anything on this guy?
And they all, all the ones that are tuning in, no matter where they are, let's say,
they'll, yeah, I know he had a grandpa that told him this, and he's the only one that
him and his grandma's grandpa's dead, so if you tell him this, he'll believe you.
Okay, thanks.
Almost like, you know, like the cop on the radio, right?
Okay, gotcha.
Yeah, yeah, they have a hive mind, so they could exchange energy, communications from
anywhere, in the physical realm, you know, like, right?
So they, it's not that particular spirit, but they're very good at that, and they don't
want themselves known.
Yeah, but what's useful to the listener, though, is to understand that if you start to steep
yourself in this stuff too much, okay?
Yeah, they'll use the hive thing on you.
You got anything on this guy?
Yeah, well, he believes.
This guy watches Amityville Horror, and a spirit comes around, and he says, hey, this
guy watches Amityville Horror, he bought that, so you got anything on this guy?
You see?
So, preconditions, here you go, you're a waiting audience, waiting to be served,
pretty much, right?
It's not, yeah, it's not like the Amity, you invited the Amityville thing, specifically,
over, a lot of the Christian, whatever, say, oh, yeah, you watch this stuff, you'll invite
that in your house, no, yes, yeah, you'll invite a similar thing, but it's not them,
it's someone else, oh, they go, they do an APB, right?
Mm-hmm.
Right?
Okay.
What is it, All Patrol Bullets, or whatever?
Yeah, points, points, I mean.
Across the whole radio, yeah, I got something on this guy, even though he's working on
somebody else.
They come from a group that also gives you dreams, and also gives you the inner voice,
a different group, a different category.
What I mean by this is like, okay, let's say you go to a municipality, right, the city,
they got the water guy, the electrical, they got the garbage man, they got the cop, they
got the one that's in the meter maid, right?
Mm-hmm.
All those things that I just mentioned are very distinct from each other, but they all
work for the city.
Okay.
That's how these spirits are.
So one does dreams, one does inner voices.
The inner voices one is probably the biggest group, right, because they keep changing those
inner voices as you change, as you change in age, and as you change in what level your
spiritual and mental capacity is.
Right.
And if you get too advanced, you know, people say, I just woke up, I found out about this
and that.
Well, you got to get another one, because his inner voice is different.
Now, we can't give him the inner voice, right?
Fortunately for them, the majority of people on the planet, they're still using the same
inner voice that they got when they were nine or 10 or 12.
That's why how many times you heard me say, most people do not mature beyond nine years
old or maximum 12 years old, like you're, like, who would you consider a pillar of society?
I don't know, a politician, most people that they like, or professor or doctor.
I'm telling you, I could show you that that person has a 12-year-old, nine to 12-year-old
mentality, maximum third grade, right?
Okay.
They don't go beyond, they're not, how do I say this for sure?
It's because if they wouldn't be known publicly if they were, you know, actually advanced.
So they have to change.
So let's say someone's, oh, I woke up in 2003, right?
Sometimes you heard that.
I woke up, I found out about the Illuminati, blah, blah, blah.
Oh, they got a, you need a new one, you got to change his inner voice.
And you have a period there where they transition.
It could be a few seconds or a few weeks where they bring in another one to give you
a new inner voice.
And that's where you actually, some people feel really, really different when they transition
from one thought to another.
If you get really advanced, I'm talking about the humans, they have to bring in a super
big one and they're more limited.
Even in scripture, there's a metaphor where the Christ says, once you get rid of one demon,
then he'll come back with seven worse ones, right?
You see?
So if you get really, really advanced, then they try to anticipate your actions before
you do them and mess you up.
That's why, quote, unquote, a lot of people that are, quote, unquote, geniuses seem crazy
or irrational.
Oh, by the way, you know what the difference between genius and stupidity is?
Go ahead.
Genius has limitations, right?
No limitations on stupidity.
That's the punchline.
No limit on stupid.
Wow.
Yes.
Right.
Yeah.
So anyway.
By the way, that's a t-shirt right there, by the way.
Speaking of enterprising individuals, I got to tell you, that's a t-shirt.
The difference between genius and stupidity is that genius has limits.
And I just end it right there.
And that's it, hopefully.
Yeah.
So this is the other realm that here, there's many ways.
Well, Greek, if you start asking me questions more about the context and fabric and structure,
I don't know.
I can only know it's like if I said, what is a bear?
You'll say, do you know what a bear is?
Yeah.
Well, this is how you want me to tell you how you know what a bear is by watching what
they look like and their behavior, what they might sound like.
That's it.
Has anyone ever sat down and did an eight-hour examination conversation with the bear for
the bear to tell you who, what it's like to be a bear?
No.
Right.
Yeah, you might have the bear whisper, but even then it's limited.
So we know about things by watching, perceiving, observing, and then communicating that body
of knowledge.
That's what I'm doing here.
So observation, recording, and then, you know, you.
Collecting the data.
And you distribute that.
Searching it.
I don't believe in research because research is to research.
But if you search something out well enough, you don't have to go back and do it again.
Go to another thing, go search another thing.
See, I do search, I search, and I search.
I rarely do research, go back, because I try to be methodical and complete.
Yeah, well, see, unfortunately, bodies of data can change.
In that case, you have to do research.
You have to go back and re-search it.
Right. For instance, I mean, look, again, you like to point to the JFK stuff.
I have to do research there because they add to the documentation.
Sure, but that's a good example that you brought up.
What do all assassinations have in common?
It's not a joke, is what you also find.
All big public assassinations, because there are private ones that you hear about later.
But the public assassinations, meaning it's almost in real time or same day.
What do they have in common with JFK?
It's not a punchline, it's a lot.
The security is pulled, right?
It's hinted at, blah, blah, blah, Patsy.
Look, I point out all the time, if you go anywhere from the JFK assassination to
an attempted assassination or a successful one in North Korea, it's the same crap.
Anyway, it doesn't matter, the culture, the language, all of it, it's the same thing.
Yeah, so we go back to the animal kingdom.
People are trained, detectives, forensic people, parks, rangers.
They find a body, they know what animal ate the human body, depending on where it was.
If it's the face that's eaten off, it's most likely a lion.
If it's the groin, it's most likely dogs.
If it's the center area, it's a bear.
If it's the toes and the fingers, it's another animal, right?
So you can judge, right?
There's someone called the maggot man, and he knew, he could tell how long a body's been dead
by counting the maggots, because maggots produce very linearly.
So if you count all the maggots, you'll know how long the body's been infested upon, right?
These are just measurements.
Well, a couple of things go into that, too.
They got to know what temperature was going on and things like that,
because that varies a bit.
Yeah, they do.
That's easy to find out, I mean, to a certain degree.
By the way, since I've been doing weather work, which is two decades now,
they lie about the temperatures and the rains and all that, too.
You can't trust the records.
But I guess for them, they might have their own little weather station.
So here's the thing.
I don't like taking too many questions on the spiritual world, because I don't know.
Just like I don't like taking questions on what a bear is.
I don't know.
I don't know any more than the next human.
You know who knows what a bear is?
A bear.
Unless he's got a really low self-esteem, right?
You have to check their self-esteem, by the way, before you interrogate them, let's say.
Yeah, you might want to be something else.
I don't know.
There could be weird bears, you know, just like we have guys that want to be girls.
I mean, it could be a bear wants to be a wolf.
I don't know, you know.
Well, here's the thing about human perception.
We can rely on the perception, and it's repeatable.
Just like if you took a circus bear and put him in the woods, you know,
all the other bears say, what a dummy.
What a dummy.
We think the bear is really smart, but they would look at him as an idiot.
So what the hell are you doing that for?
Right.
You see the difference?
I'm not, you know, I'm just you're hungry.
You'll catch a fish over there.
Don't you know where the fish are?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, exactly.
He would be a total idiot compared to the, but the humans view the one that's in the
smart, right?
So you have to leave all that stuff aside and to go further.
So to go further on this spiritual thing, there is a collective.
And here's the thing.
I'm surmising that they were here.
We're in their territory.
The earth before the earth was put here, moved and parked here.
Think about a parking spot.
You know, you ever go to a corporate office parking lot, it says reserved, you know,
for the employees or whatever kind of thing.
Well, they were there like that.
They were here, meaning in the Greek would be topos, or it was where you get the word
topography in the topos or horos, which is field.
Let's say also means dance would would be.
In a nonphysical world, so you could park the earth here, whether it's flat around,
it doesn't matter.
And we're inside their world or they're they're walking through us, you know, where
they do show this in Hollywood, where, you know, ghost comes through the wall and walks
through someone that's standing there.
Right.
I think I saw something like preview something recently, recently, a few years ago, where
the ghost just walks through the person.
They don't present, right.
Very like one who could see the ghost.
Common from.
Yeah, common.
Yeah, yeah.
Just like that.
But so they struggle to affect this world, but they don't have to struggle.
They know they could tune into the perception and the mental aspect of of ourselves, you
know, through thoughts, inner voice.
The apparitions, I'm sure I don't know how they do it, how they transfer over to this
world and start moving physical things.
Exactly.
It would be just like us doing PK and us doing telepathy, you know, in their world.
Right.
We have humans that could cross over.
I've had PK events happen.
I just can't control them.
They just happen.
So I think I've shared them on Sonics so we can look at all these things, the hows and
whys and the mechanics.
I don't know.
I mean, even again with the magnet, I've been looking at this for a long time.
So I'm going to finally do a deductive result and put the water where everyone else is not
because it makes the most sense.
And guess what?
Right.
So this is I've been adjusting the way I look at things now because I say the stranger,
the better, you know, at this point, because if you start saying things that are not, let's
say, comporting to what the academics are saying, that's strange.
Right.
Isn't that strange?
Well, look, very much like talking to water, you know, and they go, well, what the hell
is that?
You're not doing anything.
Well, Veda Austin would be the one for that.
She does.
She'll put the water on the photograph and then partially freeze the water and you get
many of the elements of the photograph.
And it's not coincidental.
You know, it's direct.
You can see it.
Well, so on the spirit side, that's why I have been bringing up the inner voice.
And I brought this example tonight and also how these things are a community or a collective
on their own.
It's an entire other world.
When you the next thing I know some people might be thinking is, does this have anything
to do when you die?
Well, death is the reverse of being born.
So just think of being born in reverse.
And that's what your effect would be there to a degree, but without the experience here.
Right.
So that's another subject.
But the subject I wanted to just work on a little bit more is the spiritual side where
we, like I said earlier, oh, he's spiritual.
You know, it's always a good or bad.
What do you mean?
He's a good or bad.
It's spiritual.
It's like, that's not telling me anything at all.
So is there good and bad in this?
Well, yes and no.
Right.
You know how I say, you know, people say, well, I give different, I try to explain good
and evil.
It's not good and evil.
It's good and bad.
Evil is brought upon someone who doesn't do good, does the opposite of good.
So when you have people that are doing bad things and things are going out of balance
because of it, and they could be doing these bad things for a really long time, but eventually
it's going to, right?
Eventually it catches up to them, they say.
The way it catches up to them is by putting evil on them.
Right.
So when you say someone is good and this guy's evil, I'm like, well, to me, they're both
good because the one that's evil is out to get back at some, to put something in balance,
you see?
So that word's not being used the way, right?
So, you know, it's like the cops and robbers, for example.
When the robbers get caught by the cops, guess what?
The cops are evil, aren't they?
To the robbers.
To the robber, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
But you see what I mean?
And vice versa.
So it's not just a matter of perspective.
It's not even cause and effect because you'll have a group of people on the planet been
doing bad shit for hundreds and hundreds of years.
It's like, when is it going to end?
We've talked about that, too.
Mop-up crew is going to take care of that, but it's also going to take their followers.
The interesting thing about the spiritual thing, it's intent and it's also what you
subscribe to, right?
So let's say, okay, when you have a mentality that's part of the collective, you just
screwed yourself when the mop-up crew and these retributions on this world take place.
Doesn't matter if you think you're good or bad, or you may have never sinned in your
life, quote unquote, right?
You're not a smoker, not a drinker.
You got a church, blah, blah, blah.
You vote, blah, blah, blah.
You just screwed yourself, dude, because when they come back to take out that system, you're
part of that system, you see?
That's how they view it.
It's kind of like, let's say the CCP blows up Beijing and says that the U.S. did it and
they send the Chinese troops to attack the U.S. and the Chinese troops come to your
neighborhood, and it's an obvious false flag.
You're going to go to the Chinese troops and say, hey, man, it was a false flag.
You know, leave us alone.
They're going to shoot you in the head.
They don't care.
It's already done, right?
So when the system is here, the conventional system that everyone goes by, that will be
taken out because it's with evil, because it's bad.
And if you're part of it, even though you just subscribe to it, you see, does that make
any sense so far?
You see what I mean?
So if you're part of the collective, you just screwed yourself because you've subscribed
to a system that has to be eliminated, and that system is not just the ideology.
It's the people that follow that ideology, just like the analogy I gave with the troops
coming over here thinking that the Americans blew up Beijing.
Look, they were telling, look how dumb they are also.
This is a military town.
There's an Air Force base here, and the largest army intelligence is less than 50 miles
southwest, southeast.
I've seen military people out, and I'm like, you guys in military, how's your military
history?
Oh, I know a lot.
So when was the last time the U.S. declared war?
Oh, 9-11.
Like what?
No.
And do you know that the president is not commander in chief unless the Congress declares
war, right?
Right.
He's not commander in chief of the military, and they still say that.
I'm like, what are you talking about?
You know, so that's where it says, just leave things be, right?
Leave them be, because it's too far gone.
So on the spiritual end, I don't know exactly enough about these beings, but I see enough,
I've heard enough, and whatever, that we can speak on it this way.
And you'll notice like half the things I've said is to correct things that are just way
off, like good versus evil.
Why?
If evil is coming, it's because someone was doing bad.
It has to, you know, it has to follow through.
You mean good versus bad, right?
But if everything's bad and you call it good, wait a second, that's in Scripture too.
Whatever is bad, they call good.
You know, so whoa, it's like the word nice.
You think you'll ever stop having the people use, like, have a nice day?
That'll never stop until it's redone.
Yeah.
So you got to leave it alone, but doesn't mean just because you know you got to do something
about it for them.
Right?
It's like the money system is another one.
You know, the money system is the easiest one to deal with, and still no one's doing
anything about it.