I have a couple of thoughts at the beginning here and I'll try and shut up and get out
of the way as fast as possible.
Because I think I'm going to have to this time.
You know, Greg, how are you doing, first of all?
You're outside tonight.
So maybe we'll get a different type of feel.
Yeah, I'm out here by the patio garden slash cat area slash work area slash all that.
Yeah, before we started recording, you asked me when we ended the last time, you got some
more you want to talk about.
You brought that up.
And I was like, you know, I forgot.
Right.
Well, it's kind of funny because you were like, look, I got a whole bunch of stuff on
my mind.
But I don't have time right now.
I got to go.
And you were like, really in a hurry.
And I was like, OK, cool.
Yeah.
Great.
That's that's what happens lately after me.
The past six months, let's say, were really nothing to do with what we're doing.
And no, no, it's actually the water projects and other things that are just right.
Well, you and I only do this a couple of times a week.
Right.
So, I mean, the thing is, we have we have other things to go on during the week, during
the time in between.
And look, I get it.
But it's really funny to me because I never think of you as a guy who wouldn't keep something
in your memory because you have this astounding memory for certain things and certain things.
Yeah.
Well, you notice I did say.
And I have odd memories for certain things as well.
Like I remember fragments of conversations, like literally like as if I recorded them
sometimes.
I don't know why that is.
I don't know why.
It seems that different people are equipped differently.
Different people train themselves differently in memory in and of itself is kind of a fascinating
aspect to this.
Well, let's just call it the creature I'm inhabiting at the moment, because as far as
I can tell, I'm one of these human things here on the surface of this rock.
And I got to say, it's one of those aspects that everybody talks about.
Everybody mentions, you know, from from the dumbest, dullard possible to the most intelligent
person.
They always go to their memory.
They always talk about memory.
Everything, you know, really revolves around memory when it comes to conversation.
What information you retain, what it is you're able to do with things.
Do you remember?
Do you remember whether it's emotional, too?
That's another thing.
Also, is it worth remembering?
Well, there you go.
And can you remember everything?
Like when people say to me, well, this is actually hold on.
Yeah, you do.
You actually do.
That's the crazy part.
Everything is recorded because it's a tiny fraction of one's ability.
Well, and even physiologically, there is the difference between the endemic memory and
the other one.
Right.
So you have one that you can recall.
And then you have another psychologist, the academic, because it doesn't work that way.
Well, I'm not bringing the academic in.
I am.
I'm only bringing something that I was able to observe.
Everybody else is non-academic.
Yeah.
No, no.
This is not the way an academic is going to describe this, I'm sure, because I've gone
through that stuff.
I've read that stuff.
And it's foolishness.
It's really foolish.
But one thing they do kind of have right, but I'm not referring to them.
I'm going on observations here is, you know, we have memories that started like if you
think back, what is the first thing that you can recall?
You're not going to recall your birth.
No, I don't.
I mean, you know, some people, by the way, but but it'll be extremely difficult because
your physiology, that is that memories from that point of your life.
Right.
Until about three or four is super reliant on your physiology.
What do I mean by physiology?
Well, you're small, you're underdeveloped.
You're very flexible, very fluid, both in the descriptive mechanical fluidity sense
and in the chemical fluidity sense.
Right.
So, well, as a creature, we're still sort of incomplete there.
Now, here's where I do agree with the academics and maybe you could correct what I was going
I just finished off the thought is this is where the ham radio guys come in, OK, because
the ham radio guys know all about, you know, antennas, you know, sizes and measurements
and frequencies.
Right.
So it's not that we forgot.
It's just that we are in such a radically different body, but it can be tuned in.
We'll talk about more of that in the future as I'm making more discoveries as we go along
on, you know, what I'm working on.
So well, the fact is, without adjustments, you can't take an FM radio and say, pull in
radio free Sweden, you know, not so easily with the standard construct.
You have to make some, you know, adjustments to receiver, don't you?
That's another that's a simple discussion.
You'll have more efficient radio transfer if you learn to build radios to transmit and
receive through the ground and not the air.
Yeah.
It's a big mistake.
Eric, look up Eric Dollard stuff.
You could find it.
I haven't found too much of it where you can pick up any radio station anywhere in the
world at any time.
If you design the device to do so through the earth, not the air, which makes more sense
because the one thing that is always common, OK, because it doesn't have constant rushing
storms changing it and things like that has nothing to do with that.
It's actually a non material phenomenon.
Real quick, everything in nature wants to form a sphere.
Why?
Because the sphere is the smallest surface area to to close the volume.
Right.
So you might think a cube is, but a cube has more surface area than a sphere.
And this but the sphere will end up with a smaller volume ultimately.
But it is this the smallest ratio of surface area to volume to on that for a while.
What does that have to do?
What we're talking about?
But good.
No, I got it.
You know what?
You have something where you have an equivalent ratio going in all directions with a sphere.
So it makes sense.
Yeah.
Twenty two over seven is the ratio generally.
But no one could figure that out.
Well, I can see it.
I don't know how to articulate it, but I can see it in my mind, which is interesting, too,
because it almost seems to come from some other memory back to the memory.
Right.
So, look, you start out with a different body.
You can't argue that because we're not like horses.
We don't get right up and are able to walk.
It's not something that happens automatically.
I, you know, I have raised a few children and know what what condition they are when
they come in the world from a different, you know, from an adult perspective, not just
my own.
Right.
They're not quite complete.
I think their wiring is not quite all the way set up just yet.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
It is for that society.
I was at a I was at a house when I was peddling, trafficking in high end water.
And it was one of these split levels at the boo.
The boo is what Malibu is called, right?
Oh, yeah.
Is this when you were selling the twenty dollar bottles?
Yeah.
Right.
OK.
Spring water basically reprocessing tap water into spring water.
And it was going against the best spring waters in the world and matching it.
So, of course, I just try to it was it was I think at that time I was the only one in
the world that actually reproduced Victor Sharpe of his device.
And that's a great that that would be a good little book, you know, like a hundred page
hundred twenty page book novella.
But anyway, we were at a house.
You drive up, it looks like one level, but the back of the house is three floors.
You know, it's built on a hillside.
Daryl Hannah and a couple of other people were there.
Some of the David Wolf, the guy that's into health food and avocado boy.
And oh, you don't you don't mean the TV guy.
You mean the the health guy?
Yeah. A whole bunch of other people.
There were some TV people that movie people.
So anyway, bored out of my mind and as one would describe it, even though I wasn't
bored, but on the ground level sliding doors where the whole wall opened, there were
like two nannies there and there were about six children and two of them were on the
couch and the rest were on the floor.
And they were all paying attention.
The five of them were paying attention to this one who was doing this elaborate baby
talk. And he finishes the baby talk.
There is a moment of silence and then all the other babies start breaking out into
laughter. And I looked at that and I said, look, he just told a joke.
He just told a joke the way adults do exactly the same way.
You know, everybody listens to the joke.
Punchline comes moment of silence.
Laughter. Exactly the same way you would direct the film for the cadence of the
interaction. Like, yeah, like in Goodfellas, you know, when someone cracks a joke and
then everybody laughs, right?
Right. Or something. He was choreographed.
It didn't look. It was so surreal.
And I was like, so I was like, look, this baby just cracked a joke and baby talk and
it was complicated and they all got it and they all laughed and they thought it was
good. How come we didn't understand a word of it?
Right. That's a very good question.
Yeah. You see. So they have their own culture and their own society pre downloaded
because remember. I talk about everything is not downloaded, but there's a small
exception in the baby talk world.
Right. Where it is pre downloaded, you know, to a degree.
Well, enough to the degree that I just explained what I saw.
Well, now, you know, maybe I'm imagining things, but I need you to.
Yeah, I need you to bridge something here then, because I get what you're saying.
And I it's hard for me to understand this because I don't have a memory of it.
I've never observed it, but I believe you.
Here's the thing, though. I take note all the time that there are people that seem to
have preloaded talents.
They take to things very easily.
It's just it's you know, like you have a bunch of things that you're able to do that.
It seems to me like I don't think all of it was what you learned.
Some of it seemed to be what some people call intuitive external.
It's all external. It's all external.
But some people receive more than others.
I'm just saying, like, you ever know a guy like, OK, for instance, Randy Rhodes, who was
an excellent guitar player.
It's said that he only took nine months of guitar lessons.
Now, there are people that study five, six, 10 years and never achieve any of the
sophistication that this guy was able to get at.
Right. And you'll see people like this.
Some people are just talented when it comes to certain things and everybody's a little
different. Well, hold on.
There's two things going on there.
That's one thing is if you do a tutelage under a master and you ask him, show me, he's
going to kick you out the door.
In other words, if you ask him, give me a lesson.
Sorry. If you ask him, give me a lesson on this, he's going to throw you out.
But if you ask him, tell him, show me, he'll be glad to do it.
OK, when you are working under a master, I'm not talking about like a bullshit
apprenticeship that, you know, whatever some whatever someone that says they're good at
whatever, but a true master like the kind you see memorialized in Hollywood movies.
Uh, what they do is they teach by having people around them that are astute observers
and learn that way. And what he will do is he'll perform what he's doing.
And it's up to you to learn by watching him in real.
How would you say in earnest?
In other words, he's not going to pause.
Masters are looking for people to teach that will not allow the interruption of flow of
what they're doing to demonstrate, you know, and what they're demonstrating, because
actually when you are doing something and you want you have apprentices to learn from
it, the moment you stop, begin to pause to explain, you have you have diminished the
entire performance. You've taken away the flow because there are small little fine
things that are done in time.
So this whole thing about, OK, this is how we build this and we show this.
Any questions? This is how we build the next part.
No, no, no. Doesn't work because the pauses break up the flow.
There's a rhythm, there's a flow, just like instruments.
Right. So what I'm trying to suggest here is what I always tell people.
Recently, I brought up someone that, you know, when you cook poultry, use lavender and
sage. Right. Still, she goes, oh, I learned about that.
So you learned about it.
Yeah. I took a cooking class.
I said, from where? From a chef said, oh, that doesn't mean anything.
She says, why? Because anyone who goes to a good chef school does not say I'm going to
a good chef school, paying all this tuition and time so I could cook to do cooking
classes. What they want to do is work in a restaurant, get their own restaurant, have a
partnership. Right. But if they fail at that, guess what?
They default to so teaching.
So I said, you actually learn from a failed chef.
Mm hmm. You see.
So the same with judges.
No one goes to law school saying I want to be a judge.
They want to be a partner in a law firm and make one hundred twenty thousand a month.
Pretty much, you know, feeling important.
Well, it stands the same with a guitar teacher, too, by the way.
You're not learning from the greatest guitarist.
You're learning from you failed, probably trying to be a rock star.
That's what his intent was.
And now he's trying to make a living.
If you can't be a partner in a law firm, you default as a judge.
So you go in front of a judge. It doesn't matter if it's the Supreme Court.
It's a failed lawyer.
So what I mean by this is things are not taught the way people are taught, the way
things are taught. Say that three times fast.
In other words, people that learn by watch being there and expect.
All right. How many times have you heard someone come into a situation and say, I
can do that. I have a lot of experience in that.
They don't say I got lessons in that.
Who would you trust more?
The one who said I have experience, the one who says they did that, well, the one
who did it and the one that I'm certain did it.
Yes. Yeah.
OK, so this goes back to the memory because they really don't teach.
They teach you how to memorize in a poor way.
So just to go forward, you're saying about instruments and all that.
That's a that's complicated, by the way, because it's really numerics, but not
numerics as we are taught.
Twenty two over seven is pi.
That is a indicates a whole relationship between the circumference of the diameter
that is a whole number.
Right. Well, it is a number that is contained.
It's finite. But once you start going just to numbers, if you divide 22 by seven,
you'll have super computers running that division for years and years and still
can't figure out what it is.
Right. It seems to go on for infinity and it never repeats itself.
But if you if you represent it with a circumference, just a drawn circle with a
line across, meaning the diameter, that's the representation of the proportion.
So how come it falls apart when you try to do it just numerically, meaning you'll
never find the end, but you can represent it geometrically.
And that's how the memory actually works.
That's why when you do rudimentary search, the most popular thing they're promoting
is memory palaces.
Right. So when you when you encounter something that you deliberately recall to
yourself, this is worth remembering or I want to remember it.
There's techniques for that.
I don't use that.
I do use that, but not in the directly.
You have to custom tailor.
What I use is a song and it doesn't mean what it's so simple, it's hard to
comprehend. I'm doing some gardening and I got some rice cooking, you know, by
the way, whenever there's a comment on Greek speak, you know how to cook perfect
rice is one of like the most sarcastic comments out there.
Right. I've seen it over and over.
Right. OK. All right.
So because I kept pushing that and, you know, believe it or not, anyone who did the
directions, I make perfect.
Right. Here, cover your ears.
But most white people can't cook for shit.
Right. Oh, did I just say that?
I'll take that back. No, I don't take that back.
Because I don't know.
All right. But but cooking rice.
Oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh.
That's like threading a needle at 100 feet.
So what do you do?
You go to the stuff that you know they're going to fail in every time, every one of
them, pretty much. And you put that out in a way that is orderly.
And all the semantics and syntax are there.
You can't screw it up.
And everyone admits that now they're making perfect rice.
What a great achievement on something that is so minor.
But it's not even a white person.
Americans House with rice being served.
Oh, my gosh. It's like, oh, my God, it's not.
I mean, it's animal grade.
Yeah. It has to do with technique.
OK, so I got a pot of rice on.
I can't hear the timer.
I'm not doing some gardening.
I know I got to return in less than 10 minutes.
So I tell myself, all right, you got to sing the rice song and I go back to the
gardening and I come back with two minutes to spare.
Now, hold on a second.
What do you mean the rice song, Greek?
All right. Am I actually writing a song or singing a song?
No, there is absolutely no song stuff going on at all.
All it is, this is why it's so simple.
You'll never figure it out, I tell people, until you figure out to appreciate
things that are so simple that work like I'm out here in the portrait.
I have a little bit of blue tape on the lamps and there's no bugs on the lamps.
It's amazing. A little dot of blue tape.
OK, so simple defies the mind.
Just telling yourself you have to sing a song of, you know, the rice song or
whatever, whatever, wherever.
I got to go pick up my daughter's song.
You just tell yourself you have to sing a song and mention the thing you want to
remember. And it's remembered and it keeps you alert.
There's no singing. There's no song.
You just tell yourself, OK, there's a song involved.
That's all it needs.
That's all the psyche needs.
It's amazing. And I've been playing with this with myself for more than a dozen
years. And I've showed it to other people.
About half the people can do it, half can't because they think if you're going to
sing a song, well, what are the words?
What are the lyrics? What's the music?
What song is it? You know, I don't know a song about rice.
See, that's it gets in the way.
Their own mind gets in the way.
Right. And by the way, I wouldn't recommend playing with yourself too much.
They say you will go blind and.
Yeah, it's possible. Sorry, I doubt it.
I had to play with you.
So we call it self-serve.
I had to say it's self-serve, self-serve.
Good. Yeah, I don't play around.
That is a great way to put it.
Actually, self-service.
Go ahead. Sorry. Yeah, like, you know, when you go to a buffet and they got the
salt. Anyway.
Yep. So if you use anyway, I'm not going to get into that.
It's so. All right.
So the concept of a song.
Well, OK, let's go back to Homer's Iliad Odyssey.
Guess what? The Native American history.
Guess what? When you look at a lot of other things with big semantics in it, guess
what? They're all oral traditions.
Everything I mentioned was basically held in an oral tradition, not because writing
was bad and they didn't have writing.
They did have writing, but they lost it.
So there's something about the oral tradition
being mental. It's a song, iambic pentameter, right?
The Greek structure.
So the simplest thing works the best
because if it evades rationalism, the rational mind doesn't get occupied
with it. And the rational mind actually needs things to remind it.
Right. Because it's right. It's a metric.
So if you if you subscribe to things that are very, very simple that work
and learn how to manage those things.
Right. Then you'll be more successful with your memory.
And I know that's a big statement.
But in giving the little song, some people say this is ridiculous and some people
have. But whoever has adopted that find that it works.
And by the way, there's no time scale.
You can say, I have an appointment in two weeks.
I have to sing this appointment song.
That's all you have to do. And guess what?
When that time approaches, you're like, oh, yeah, I remember that.
It's amazing how it works.
Now, there's other techniques, but I just wanted to put that out because you won't
find that anywhere. This is maybe a homegrown Greek speak thing.
Yeah, I guarantee you, I've never heard that before.
Yeah, it's homegrown then.
OK, good. Homebrew.
So, yeah, I wanted to go back.
I actually forgot we were talking about the babies and how they're downloaded.
And but they're not we're not we don't rely on those downloads because we change so
radically that it doesn't work anymore.
Right. And you told us a story about the baby on the couch telling the joke and all
that. So they all left. Yeah.
And it was choreographed as if it was a I think they once did a baby movie.
They were acting like adults or something.
And it was fascinated by that because it allowed me to see into their world.
I didn't understand anything he was saying at all.
And it was complex, obviously, by the you know, they're all listening intently.
Eye contact, gestures, just like you would choreograph someone telling a joke.
Right. And a mob film.
Sure. Yeah.
And I found that to be incredible.
Now, the thing about the body, the body size sounds like someone's working on their
trailer. I'm going to go inside.
No problem. I'm surprised we didn't hear from Ivan.
Yeah, I'm on the stupid rectangle, by the way.
You'll hear an audio change probably in the background.
So so what's going on is with memory, by the way, I'm not sure if the if you were to
loosely look at the etymology, mem is water and order means light in the Hebraic
vernacular or, you know, the cognates.
Right. So it's interesting how it's water, light, water and light put together.
But what I would suggest with the memory, it's external as well.
Right. You know, you've heard of people.
Actually, they're very good at covering up stuff in terms of, you know, there are
people that don't have a brain, you know, function, you know, this might be some
left, you know, from an accident, you know, or something.
And they're still pretty functional.
You know, I was trying to explain someone the other day.
You know, when someone's in a coma, they call them a vegetable in a vegetative
state. But, you know, this is a little diversion here, a tangent.
But you notice how they stop there.
And someone brought that up and I was like, OK, so you have a vegetable, someone in a
coma is considered a vegetable, a vegetative state.
Let's continue. What do you call the average normie people in the collective, the
people? And I'm talking about, you know, your family, your friends, the people you
see on the street could be in this, too.
Right. What's a step up from vegetable animal?
Yeah. Yeah. And what's an animal?
Livestock. Oh, perfect.
So now we got the vegetative state, the vegetable, which is the few.
And then we go to the livestock, which is I call them that before, you know, the
normie, the NPCs, whatever.
Right. And then what do you get after that?
Then you go to man and woman or human.
And a lot of people, the Jordan Maxwell's and the others have really ruined that
word. They said told everyone it means monster.
It was in a legal dictionary as a side note.
So anyway, I just want to bring that up, the legitimate use of the word livestock
to mention most people because they're like animals, just as someone who is, you
know, just breathing and have a just basic soul.
Right. Metabolism is a vegetable.
I thought it was kind of cute to go from vegetable to animal.
Right. We never we never dogged on the minerals ever called.
I know. Well, actually, in the British said that you have the minerals, meaning like
you have the balls. Right.
So later, the stones.
Right. So the stones.
Yeah. So, again, it's very, very tantalizing to think about the structure being so
important to them, to the function as a child, having a complex language and social
structure potentially changing very quickly.
And then how does that connect to memory?
And that's the first thing I brought up is that it's not it's some parts of your
memory, if not most of it is based on what the ham radio operators talk about.
Right. So so what do ham radio operators talk about?
Right. That's not fair.
I I haven't been one, but I've been around them.
Frequency, antenna length, right.
Power. Oh, yeah.
I used to have shortwave longwave radios and stuff, and I never talked on those, but
I could pick them up.
And oh, my gosh, it's critical to some degree.
But once you get into the very forgiving as well.
But if you want, you know, best signal.
So so there is something.
So what do you do with the adults?
Let's say we're presuming most of the people listening to this are adults.
What do you do? Right.
Well, the the easiest thing to improve memory is to pay attention.
In other words, don't take don't take things for granted and avoid idle chitchat
and things that annoy you.
But how's that?
Because annoyance is a form of trauma, by the way.
Right. It's a slight trauma.
You know, it's kind of like the drop.
What is the old famous saying?
The Chinese water torture.
Right. It was just drop, drop, drop.
Right. Oh, yeah. Right.
Yeah, it's cumulative.
So those are very simple hints.
What I've homegrown is the song.
Just tell yourself, you know, what you want to remember as a song.
There's no song, by the way.
I don't have to go over that.
It's just it's so simple.
It's it's unusually simple, but it tends to jog the mind.
And what do they call like a sticky note kind of thing, you know?
And it kind of works for it works for me and whoever pretty much got it.
The other thing is those that are good observers are good.
Memory have better memory.
I've noticed in life.
In other words, if you're in a situation that's let's say you were three people
and the three of you go somewhere and see something that you've never seen before.
And it's an action.
And the one that is the best observer.
We'll have we'll be able to recall more of the event
because of the input, more input right now, here's the thing.
The body will not.
You know how they say the universe doesn't give you more than you can handle.
Right. OK.
People that are good observers have good memories
and people that have good memories are good observers,
because if you are a good observer and you don't have the memory to handle it,
it's a waste, isn't it?
And vice versa.
Well, this is true.
And some people fool themselves.
And I know they do it.
I've watched them do it where they start to add information to something
based on something that's erroneous, not their observation.
Plus confabulation.
But they yeah, they begin to add in because look at all times.
Memory is malleable. I agree with that.
You can always add information to it and then skew the whole situation
and screw it up.
Because if you start to interpret something, this is where the problem comes in.
If you simply observe it and take it in,
you can learn a great deal more by objectively observing it
than starting to add your own information to it. Right.
Well, you see, it's not just yes, it's not about memory.
Then it's like, what does it take to be a good observer?
By the way, they're in what they call in air quotes
and the jerk off hand sign at the same time.
And if you can imagine that law enforcement supposedly has trained observers,
right, they train, you know, and they bring up someone as a technical
whatever, they say he's a trained observer. Right.
You hear the military or law enforcement. Right.
Yeah. Yeah. Stuff like that. Yeah.
So and I that I'm not that's not what I'm talking about.
But there and I and I don't like to say it's
there's a natural proclivity towards it.
But it seems like some people tend to be better observers than others. Right.
Yeah. And by the way, that training does give them an upgrade
from the average upright walking individual around.
They are a little better at it than, you know, common person.
But are they doing it right?
I don't think so. Oh, yeah.
And by the way, did they did they learn that by taking a class
or did they learn that by actually being a good observer? Oh.
Oh, wait. Yeah. When they're actually good at it, it's because they've done it.
Right. Yeah. Right.
Or if you took a class in it.
Well, you know who taught it?
There's so many factors. Why did you have to take a class in it?
And right. So that's why whenever I've had to teach anybody anything,
I've told you this before.
I always, you know, made them do it.
Look, just do this. Start to do this.
Here's the basic thing you need to start with.
I'm going to do something that they can get hurt and that they have no knowledge.
I don't know what to do.
You say children all the time.
Yes. You safety the issue so that it's not a big deal.
But you have them do it.
That's the way I disagree with that in a big way.
It's just like when you see you go to someone's house that has children
and they have the crayon drawings on the refrigerator and they
because I think they should all be thrown away.
So you don't give someone that has no skills, no skill in expressing themselves
and to draw and say how good it looks.
It looks like crap.
But you got to give the children at least maybe a few hours
and how to draw proportion.
Then they can express themselves better.
You know, I'm talking about the cheesy drawings, stick figures
and the size of the house.
That's garbage. Don't do that to a child.
That should not be done.
No, no, no. Look, I let them do that to start with.
And then I say, OK, well, that's here's what you're doing.
Here's what you're not doing.
And now let me instruct you a bit.
Now take it and do it again.
By the way, this is part of the kids culture.
This is very carefully crafted, like the Skinner system, Skinner boxes,
psychological stuff and, you know, Bernays all at that time.
You know, after the 20th century, the whole Bolshevik movement, you know,
which I'd like to do a tangent on that real quick.
There's a lot of people I've been running into lately
that don't know about the money system and don't care to you
because they say, oh, I'm a craftsman or I'm an artist or whatever.
All right. Well, what they fail to recall
is that at the turn of the 20th century, the Bolshevik movement,
which basically came out of Wall Street in Brooklyn, a bunch of Brooklyn guys.
It was nothing to do with the Russians.
You could look at the history.
The people that revolted and killed the czar,
then they were killed for another revolution, right?
It's systematic, right?
OK, that happened there to reorganize the culture
based on what that culture can understand the communism thing, right?
In America, they did the same thing,
but they didn't do it that way.
What they did was they
they took the money system away and made it fiat currency.
In fact, they started with fractional banking and then fiat.
So someone who says they don't understand the money system
or not interested in it is like living in Soviet communist Bolshevik
Russia and saying, I don't understand communism
or don't care to or whatever.
You're going to run into a lot of problems, right?
Very quickly.
So not necessarily if you're in the outskirts, but, you know,
when you're in in the collective.
So what they've done with the Americans is much, much worse.
It's much more insidious because guess what?
In 89, the wall came down and they reorganized it and opened it.
But in 89, did anything happen?
Reorganizing the financial system here is getting worse and worse,
getting worse and worse.
So that was the tangent. So
let's go back to what we were
we were saying about learning things and experiences and all that.
That's very that's a big, big, big thing with the children and the drawings.
What you don't give children crayons and say, draw and then say,
oh, look what they drew up. Beautiful.
Looks like crap. Throw it away.
Did the child get any instruction how to express themselves in that?
Just like a four year old banging on a piano.
There's no experience, right?
I mean, if they start playing Chopin, that's like maybe one out of a billion.
Do you think you think one out of a billion four year olds
can just jump on a piano, start playing Chopin? Is that possible?
Yes, it is. Probably. Yeah, that sounds about right.
That's right.
So the same thing when I see these children's drawings that the parents
hang in the house, on their office or on the refrigerator, as you throw that away.
It's terrible. Would you record the four year old banging on the piano?
So listen, how beautiful. It doesn't sound beautiful.
So when it's a self-denial, what is it to take the ugly
and the misinformed and the uninformed and the unskilled and saying,
look how beautiful it is, it's an effect on the mind.
The other thing is to show the children, just go out and do stuff,
because the more you do stuff, the more we have attorneys
that could charge you for doing it now.
You get it?
How many times have you seen attorneys charge people?
Well, you got all these charges, right?
You know, because why?
Because they don't understand what they did to the Bolsheviks.
They did over here, but using the money system. Right.
So this is a complex thing.
But this is this is, again, in other words, there is a certain amount of order
and a certain amount of instruction that is necessary before
someone starts on anything.
Well, I understand. But, you know, look, because I had to transfer
the ability to do certain tasks.
OK, I'm not going to describe specifics here, but I tried.
Look, observe me.
And it was it was just impossible.
I seem to be confronted with a good observer or not.
Like my wife. She's not a good observer.
I've been working with her for 20 years.
No, she's not a good observer. Right.
But I didn't make her bad.
No, no. Does it make her good? No.
But it means in order to teach her to do something,
you can't just ask her to observe something, probably. Right.
Yeah. Yeah. So yeah.
So what happens is you start seeing these things.
And when you get later on, you know, I'm in my sixth decade,
you start realizing, OK, that will probably never change
in the ever we have left.
But if we live to a thousand
by the time this person is not a good observer,
it might be around 450 years old.
They might pick it up then.
Well, we don't have that kind of time. No, we don't.
So what that what that makes is it makes things that people do not improve in,
even over long periods of time, it makes it more pressing.
And then when you make it more pressing, then you have conflict.
So what do you do? You have to leave it alone.
Right. And that's the world that we live in.
But here's the thing.
There is a subtle line between pressing someone into
they have to do this better because of the time they have left at the rate
they're going, they'll have to live to a thousand to catch up.
And that, you know, some people feel like they have that luxury, by the way.
Do they act like it?
They do act like it's in the DNA somehow.
I you know, I can't disagree with you there because I see that.
And I say to myself, look, and you know what?
Some people, if they live to be a thousand,
I know they wouldn't master what it is they're trying to do.
And it's really sad to me.
Anyway, it's interesting.
I have another idea, but I also want to address the speed reading,
which was the other part of the question in the chat, if you don't mind, real fast.
But perhaps we can talk about identity at a certain point
because I had this weird idea and maybe I'll get into it with you on the next
Sonic, but speed reading or finish out with the memory thing.
But it's interesting to me.
You have you have a very
yeah, you have me considering something very interesting here.
I think I think I'm starting to change my mind.
I don't have much. It's just like driving a car.
Would you give someone I'm using the regular vernacular, OK?
If you give someone some keys, they just they started.
They started driving a week ago.
Is he here? Go to the race.
Go to the race right now with the car. Go ahead and race it.
Well, no, it's not going to work. Right.
Actually, most people think they'll crash.
Actually, they'll be so terrified they won't do anything.
They'll just sit there, you know, as if they're out of gas, you know,
or the engine died.
Believe it or not, because being in a race is very intimidating.
It sure is. Yeah, they probably won't crash it.
But the chances of them crashing is extremely high as well.
So the same thing with speed reading.
What I suggest with that is the typical textbook
before you even do that, just be a good observer.
What I mean by that is when you get a book,
especially something that's technical, even this works with novels.
The author usually when you write a book and publish a book,
if something is really important, guess what?
Not only do you write a little bit more about it, you might give what?
A picture, an illustration, a graph, a chart. Right. Right.
OK, so you just do what you do, whatever the subject is.
It doesn't matter how big the textbook is or technical book.
Let's just stick with the technical book, for example. OK.
You look at the front and back cover.
Very obvious.
And then you go to the table of contents and just browse the table of contents.
That gives you an idea.
I mean, have you ever seen a table of contents like 15 pages long?
I've seen that sometimes.
Oh, my gosh. Yes.
The divisions in here.
That means there's a lot of divisions, a lot of multitude
of various topics and things. Right.
Right. A big, thick book with three chapters. Easy. Right.
I mean, you know, the same thing.
They just talk more about the same thing.
You know, 150 chapters. Wow.
That'll covering 150 items most likely.
And then start going through the chapters page by page very quickly
and look for graphs and pictures. Why?
Because if they actually invested in putting in an illustration or a graph,
guess what?
They want to emphasize that point or it must be important.
Don't worry about learning or memorizing that.
Just keep going. Keep going. Keep going.
Let's get to the end.
There's glossaries, appendices, footnotes, credits,
you know, that they give to others. Right. Right.
And if there's none, you might say this is either plagiarized,
heavily plagiarized, or this person has really done a lot of research,
authentic research. Right.
It's got to be very original,
especially if you don't see like a bibliography where they write a bibliography.
Right. So if you don't see that, you're like,
whoa, this who this is incredible.
You know, if it's worth looking at the subject matter is interested to you.
And it's not bullshit.
Also, also an index at the end is an interesting indicator as well.
Yeah. Good.
Then when you go back to the chapter beginning,
look at what each chapter introduces.
But believe it or not,
even if you don't read the introduction to the chapter, guess what?
It's usually in the title itself.
You don't have to do much reading in the beginning at all.
Go to the end of the chapter and usually basic essay writing classes.
They give you you must come to a conclusion.
You already know what the chapter is about based on just the title alone.
Mostly you could read the first sentence or to read
the closing of the chapter last two or three sentences.
If it tells you, for example,
this one is about a certain type of tuberculosis virus,
but it shows completely inconclusive.
No evidence in the experiment.
Oh, great. Do you want to go back and read the whole chapter?
Because what you just got the final point that doesn't exist. Right.
You don't have to read the whole chapter to find out
how the tuberculosis virus doesn't exist. Do you? Right.
You see. And you go through each chapter.
Right. Another chapter is, you know, setting up a standard protocol,
let's say, for testing for disease.
And you go to the end of that. That's the title.
You go to the end of the chapter. You read a few sentences.
It doesn't seem like we'll be able to set set up a standard
protocol for disease for a very long time.
All right. And what was it written?
It was written in the 70s. Well, it's a very long time.
All right. So now you got that.
You go to the next chapter.
You see, now we cover two chapters in what, 30 seconds? Yep.
And you go on. So guess what?
If you use this method within about 45 minutes,
you'll be able to have a discussion with the author,
an intelligent discussion with the author.
But most people, how do they do it?
Let's say this is a 500 page book.
Three days later. Oh, I'm still on the first chapter.
I just got the book three days ago. It's a heavy read.
How many times you hear that?
I haven't gotten to that part yet.
Right. A month later. Oh, I'm halfway through.
I don't know what you're talking about in Chapter 37.
Right. Oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh.
You see, you just you just gave the methodology I used to use
when I would go to a bookstore and I'd see a JFK book
I never saw before and I'd go, OK, and I do exactly what you just said.
Just get through and figure out whether it was worth me
putting down some money to buy the thing.
Right. It's not just skipping through.
You can actually intelligently communicate how you do it
and get a lot of value out of it.
Oh, no. I already knew what was in the book
by the time I was done with the process.
This technique is not discussed much.
Well, no, it's not.
But but that's how I used to decide whether I was going to spend the money.
Oh, yeah. Well, and then if you if it's a text, a college book,
look if there are any quizzes or tests at the end of the chapter.
Mm hmm. They usually do that. Right.
Yeah. And guess what?
You don't try to take the quiz because you don't you're not informed.
But when you're reading the chapter, go reference back to the go start.
If you were to read the whole chapter, go back and look at what the quiz
questions on and focus on those because they're basically giving you,
you know, the whole outline. Right. Oh, Jack.
So this way you could succeed a little more so you could go out to the bar
and drink and whatever you do at college, you know.
So and some of those things are very easy to do, because all you got to do
is like some of them, they say, here's a you know, they don't suggest
you use it as a quiz like in class or whatever, but they say you should take
this quiz, this little quiz at the end here to see if you retain
the knowledge from the chapter.
If you go to that first, as opposed to, you know, what you've set yourself up.
Yeah. You know what they're setting you up for,
which will probably brought up again later in some form of instruction,
you know, class or whatever, which is.
Yeah. Yeah. And if you're filling in gaps in your knowledge,
you can go there and say, OK, I know how to answer this, this, this, this.
But I don't know this.
You can go you can go flip through the chapter usually and find it
pretty quickly, fill in the gaps in your knowledge without a problem.
Right. Speed reading.
By the way, for speed reading, I have no direct way of doing it
other than what's out there.
There's classes that were been famous since the 70s.
Remember, there was speed reading classes advertised in the TV guy.
Oh, yes. The 70s. Right.
So quite popular.
And here's the thing.
What I do is, you know, the intelligence
intelligence officers how to do an interrogation.
The four things.
Listen to how they're saying what they're saying
and look at how they're saying what they're saying
and then look at how they're not saying what they're saying. Right.
Those are the two things.
But basically, I'm just just still paraphrased.
You have to look at what how they're saying, what they're saying
and also look at how what they're not saying. Right.
So what I do with that is when I'm when I want to speed read,
I try to filter out all the does, is, was them, us, all the conjugations,
pronouns, you know, not pronouns, but, you know, what are those things called? Right.
All the grammatical devices that are there to, you know, make it.
And what I imagine in the imaginary, all books have margins.
All some smaller than others. Right. Right.
What I try to do is what's really is imagine that all of those
the is is for and that I imagine a dust of dust brush.
And I and I brush all those words often to the margin.
And what's left is the meat.
And I go through that very quickly.
And in the beginning, it's very difficult to do.
But once you learn how to do it, it's almost as if all the unnecessary parts
are highlighted and you avoid them naturally.
And that's how you go through fast.
But for example, again, with the wife, there'll be something page up
to read on a video, you know, on a screen in the living room.
And I'll look at it's a paragraph and I'll look at it.
Five, four, three, two, one. I read it.
She's like, oh, I'm still need more time.
Right. So why?
Because she's reading it the way that they intended.
What I'm saying is not the way it's intended to be read.
You see. Right.
So I'm driving on the white line kind of thing.
Right. In between lanes here. Right.
But what I do, just like the rice song, you know, sing a song.
Right. There's no song.
What I'm doing is but here what I'm doing is imaginary
in an imaginary sense, all the fluff and excess.
I'm moving over to the side of the plate, you know, which is the margin
and trying to target the main point.
Now, is that a good thing to, you know, if it's something important
and if it's a good story?
No, you shouldn't do that, really.
I think there's speed reading classes that can assist you and better.
But that's what I've developed on my own is to share. Right.
And if you're trying to glean information from something, that's one thing.
If you're attempting to just familiarize yourself with the story, that's fine.
But if you actually want to enjoy the story, I wouldn't suggest speed reading.
Well, because it's yeah, it's also the amount of time
that you spend reading also has an effect on the mind. Right.
Well, but that's the thing, you know, if you want to invest that time
and you want to experience the you know, I used to enjoy.
I don't know. You probably find this silly,
but I used to enjoy sometimes going into the story of things
and really, you know, making it up in my own head, drawing those pictures,
you know, imagining the scene as it's laid out, things like that.
You can't really do that as a speed reader.
I don't think maybe maybe you can.
But it seems to me as though it's time to percolate. Am I wrong about that?
No, there's those also.
You got to understand it.
But what's being served up to the collective, to the common people is garbage.
Always. So if it depends, you know what I mean?
Like one man's junk is another man's treasure, vice versa. Right.
So, for example, all the stuff that they told us in school for the past 100 years,
I've noticed what are the Clavie Elmer said, Emerson, Twain,
Melville. I can't read stuff is junk.
I read them like, well, my gosh, this is a classic.
It's so poorly written. Why are they doing this?
Ah, you know, so that's the dumbing down and the screwing
with the mind was done a long time ago by taking these degenerate writers
and telling you these are the classics. Read them. They're great.
They suck. Right.
You notice you ever notice you read some of the classics, even Dickens.
A lot of Dickens works. Oh, my gosh, it's horrible.
And they're putting this crap.
So the crap, the crapola, the stuff that they've been doing
to make a demented population,
keep them busy and keep them dumb and keep them in the livestock division
is you will find that what they call are the classics.
So when you say, then what do you enjoy?
Like, I think one of the best writers that I've ever read is Frank Herbert.
If you read his stuff, that's of course, it's an opinion.
It's like saying, what's your favorite ice cream? Right.
So but there's stuff out there that is way better than the classics,
way better. Philip K. Dick.
Right. I mean, you talk about a story.
Oh, my gosh. You know, you know, it's like taking drugs. Right.
So you could and you could follow along.
But here's the thing.
We've been messed with for so long that unless you're 100 plus years old
and more than that and you have a good memory, no pun intended, you won't see it.
So, well, that's that's fair enough.
And I you probably think I'm nuts.
But again, you know, what's your favorite ice cream?
I like Kurt Vonnegut.
Yeah, there you go. Yeah. Yeah.
Sluton House. Yeah.
Slaughterhouse Five.
Slaughterhouse Five. I mean, Timequake, even though they panned it, I liked it,
you know, and yeah, stuff like that.
So anyway.