Sonic Event 66, and you know what, I think it's time to go around the world because we
got two of the numbers that represent man, I guess, standing next to each other if we're
going according to the numerology.
But then again, maybe not.
Greek, how are you doing tonight?
Hey, I'm doing it, yeah.
We've been looking at palindromes, by the way, so when we did, let's say, 62, we looked
at 26.
I think we started further on.
So we do episode 64, we looked at 46 and see if there's any kind of a rhythm there.
And it's interesting how you could know and want to use that as a tool, which I don't
think we really did.
But yeah, 66, we went around the world on episode 6.
You're making that noise again, by the way.
Oh, OK.
Really?
Because this is a new headset and it's getting used to me.
You shouldn't be making that noise now, though.
No, I just was.
All right, let's just try it.
It's just like one of those, it's an Apple headset with a built-in mic on the stupid
rectangle, which is an Apple or a pair, right?
And yeah, I've gotten away from the laptop for some reason, I just like it.
I could see the convenience, even though the phones are way too big.
You know, I'm used to a flip phone, so you probably hear a lot of resolution on it.
Yeah, I am.
But I was hearing that noise a bit.
What would you do with a pair of apples, though, right?
Yeah, right.
Right.
A pair of something else, too.
That too.
Yeah.
If you got them.
Do you got a pair?
Do you not got a pair?
What kind of pair does she have?
Anyway.
All right.
Now we've got.
Yeah.
Well, it takes a pounding.
I heard, though.
Yeah.
We keep taking and licking and all that.
All right.
So away from it and away from what's going on.
The world is a crazy place, man.
It really is.
You know, we're all being pranked.
We keep going over that.
We've done that.
Oh, I don't know.
Since we started talking, you know, it has.
It's not.
It's not that crazy.
It's not that bad.
You know, it's getting better.
It's actually much better than it was.
All right.
In short.
What do I mean by that?
In short, there's YouTube videos or videos on replicating life in the eighteen hundreds
or seventeen hundreds.
Go watch it.
All right.
Now, I'm presuming you might see the one that I saw a decade ago.
So, you know, people get up in the morning.
Right.
And it's really cold because no one was tending the fire at night.
Let's say if it's in the cold season and someone's got to go get wood.
Other people got to get ready to make something to eat or drink.
You got laundry to do by hand.
Right.
Good.
You see.
Right.
No machines to help.
No grid.
And by the way, what I mean by no grid in back in the 19th century, in most places in
the world, even in a big city, you didn't have running water, running water.
There was one spigot in a building or two.
And you had bowls that you moved around if you had access pictures of water, you know,
if you had access to, you know, to for washing, bathing was a big deal.
Laundry was a big deal.
Usually people didn't do laundry on their own.
Very often they were laundering was very popular, you know, going to a launderer.
But again, economically and all that.
So we're way better off.
The part that's not better off is there's an aspect to get away with what we should be
doing.
And one thing that I would say maybe the past three Sonics we've covered is how banking and
money works and covered how the attorneys are scumbags and this and that and the other
and the doctors and all that.
Right.
They're not actually all those systems work really well.
See, the system is not.
But there's a set of rules that have been hammered out literally for these professions
to follow based on keeping standards, you know, and no one is following them and no one cares.
No one's holding their feet to the fire, so to speak.
And it's just chugging along and it's still doing OK.
Pretty much.
The only thing I wanted to include in this that that people that were doing OK is this
concept of war.
That is a sport.
So if you like watching like contact sports especially and you complain about war, you
got no business because it's the same exact thing.
As a matter of fact, where wars take place, the battlefields are called theaters, aren't
they?
Yes, they are.
Yeah.
So this is just sport, blood sport, however you want to call it.
It has nothing to do with morality, of course.
And very simply, you could see the reasons why going to war is given.
And there's always a war, you know, when these things pop up like what's going on right now
in the Middle East, you know, it's going on.
Always is just whether you hear about it or not.
Right.
I had a conversation with someone recently and the word terrorism came up.
I said, there is no such thing as terrorism, as you're being told.
It's all state sponsored, not by the elected officials, those that are not elected.
And the money people to create a motivation for that will allow the public to accept things
that they normally would not accept, sort of like the Hegelian dialectic.
Right.
That's all it is.
There is real terrorism, but you never hear about it.
Right.
Only everything that is that you hear about on a large scale of that that's printed or
put through the airwaves, even in alternative media is all scripted.
Right.
So we've got a lot of busy little piggies behind the scenes.
And that's what people focus on.
Is it not being such a good world?
Is the people that are busy dividing everyone and because people get along no matter what.
Right.
It doesn't matter your race, color, religion, social status and all that.
These things are set up by a very small group that wants to keep mankind divided.
And they've been around since time immemorial.
Right.
And there's not enough people talking about that system.
But even if you talk about it, right, it's not going to change anything because it seems
like the majority wants it this way.
Look, look, I'll just shine my own shoes.
Right.
So wait a second.
You know, what do you mean by that?
Well, let's not use that analogy because that requires a story behind it.
But if you how would you put this?
This is a very complex thing to put in a thought and say it.
I know.
OK.
Hmm.
So complex, I can't even speak it.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, you can't look, look, look, take a moment, take a moment, because what you're trying
to get to here is, OK, we have the divide and conquer.
That is very useful.
That is something that is kept constant.
And so are the games one way or another.
Right.
Whether it's at the Circus Maximus or it's on the, you know, the maximum.
Yeah, I see where you go.
But we could hear there is something in the system, you know, like a while back, you know,
archaic brochures.
I don't endorse him, but he puts out some good stuff sometimes.
Right.
If not more than half the time, I should say.
He's big into the simulation, simulacrum, simulacra, whatever.
I've been bringing this up slowly for the past few years because there's no way that
things happen naturally as we're taught, right, because of the repeating on the cycle.
But there is a resistance within the construct, let's just call it, or the setting that we're
in, setting meaning physical and nonphysical.
Because when you do settings in theater or making film, it's the place and the time.
Right.
That's the setting.
So that's what I mean by the setting.
And if, for example, let's just say we did, I would consider past few Sonics on the banking
system to be a major expose.
Major.
Right.
So.
So when there is a secret.
And by the way, anyone can look up anything I said on that and you'll find it.
When there's a secret, how many people does it take to reveal it?
Just one.
And then it should spread like wildfire, right?
And some people should do something about it.
These things, if someone that is not familiar with Greek speak, which I've given a papyri
little smatterings of that past few Sonics over the years, I think I got more intense
in the past couple of Sonics.
Yeah.
If someone that is not familiar with it at all and hears it, they should be really considering
what they're doing when it comes to quote unquote finance or finance or their money, quote unquote,
credit system, whatever.
But no one cares.
So is that care genuinely inherent in the human?
Like there are a bunch of clods that don't care and they're blunt.
Yeah, most of them are.
We said that.
But I mean, another example is like 9-11, right?
Dmitri Kaluzov did a benchmark expose.
This is nuclear.
Aha.
You don't believe it here.
I'll prove it to you.
And his proofs are way beyond what anyone would need to prove it legally and scientifically.
Where is the where's the public outcry?
How many people does it take?
Right.
Well, here's the thing about that.
Look, I'm not trying to defend anybody.
Don't get mad at me here.
OK, but here's the deal.
They hear this.
It concerns them.
They get upset.
They go, wait a minute.
This isn't the way it should be.
I don't want it this way.
They say that to themselves.
Now they are in that mode.
They then go to deal with others who are.
Yes.
But who are those others?
You see, why does it you see there's in other words, resistance is built into the setting.
Right.
But you built in.
It's like it's a wall of resistance.
It's like hitting a wall.
No, because look, I sit there and I go, look, this isn't the way it's supposed to work.
Now, I try and explain this to others.
I could try and do business with somebody else.
I try and make an exchange with somebody else and I try and explain, you know, this is the
way this ought to work.
I try and, you know, exchange a piece of information.
You realize this is actually what happened when you were concerned about this situation.
You hit enough resistance after a while.
It just kind of knocks the wind out of you.
Yeah, but it's it's specific to each person.
But if you average out this, how specific it is to everyone, there is a general resistance
across the board.
Right now.
Now, here's OK.
So let's say to who are going to end this subject.
So what happens is you realize, you know how they say, you know, be able to change the
things you can and accept or be able to do things you can't change, except the things
you cannot change.
The courage to change the things you can and the wisdom to know the difference.
Yeah.
OK, good.
So.
So now.
Yeah, right.
Exactly.
Know the difference.
So in this case, you take it.
So these things cannot change.
And then you must take it with stride, because if you see that it cannot change and you go
back and it's upsetting, well, then you're going to live a very upset life.
Right.
And I know what that's like, by the way, personally.
And but at the same time, you have to take it in stride.
Like Diogenes, he was an interesting philosopher, sage in ancient Greece.
Give you an example of how he took it in stride.
And this goes on the up and down.
He did many things.
But Alexander the Great came to him where he lived out in the forest.
And at the time, Diogenes was like sunning himself under a tree, you know, kind of off
to the side, you know, sunning himself and get some warmth.
And Alexander the Great comes to him and says, I hear you're one of the greatest sages.
That word of mouth has it.
You know, I've been to the academies and they all say that you're the one to talk to.
And since you are the way you are, I'm Alexander.
I can give you anything you want.
What is that?
You said, Alexander.
Oh, if you give me anything I want, can you just move over a little to the left?
You're blocking the sun.
You see, just take it in stride like that, right?
I've seen a lot of stuff, not as much as some people, but more than most, let's say, from
basically the stuff that I've been around and been able to give an opportunity to see.
And I've been I've learned on my own to take it that way.
Been around very wealthy people, powerful people in the oil and gas and other things.
And I watched how they operate and I said, this is kind of like a TV show.
This isn't real.
Right.
So if it's not real, why would you throw your hat in the ring or your nuts in the grinder,
so to speak?
Right.
If it's not real.
So it's kind of funny.
But taking it in stride now, it's it's obviously the nervous reaction of being in a building
where a bomb is dropped on it and having your arm or your head blown off is very different
than what we're doing here, talking wherever we are.
Hopefully we're comfortable.
I know I'm fairly comfortable.
I hope you are.
I'm all right at the moment.
But there's people all any time and, you know, right, that are having a very hard time.
So that's just part of part of this existence.
But I would suggest taking it in stride is the way to go always.
And I know it's been said before, but the thing is, how do you do that?
And I would suggest that when you're not having a quote unquote good time physically or mentally,
pay attention and see how many voices are trying to catch up in your head.
And that would suggest a lot.
Right.
Very rarely does it get you to have that quiet inner peace when that happens.
In other words, like your average NPC mainstreamer that watches Fox News, when he turns off the
TV, he still has it running in his head.
Right.
Those voices are still running in his head.
Sure.
Yeah.
So.
So one thing is to get that silence, which is, by the way, the easiest way to do it is
anticipate it.
So if you understand what we're saying here, which you've covered in previous sonics, is
that voice in your head is not you.
It sounds like you.
It's been going on for so long.
You're used to it.
Kind of like a pebble in your shoe that you don't take out.
And by the end of the day, you don't even know it's there anymore.
Right.
After a while, your foot gets numb, basically.
Yeah.
You become.
And also it's familiar.
So if you are aware that, wow, man, Greek talk about the voice, my head is not beat.
What is talking about?
It's always been there.
Yeah.
So here's proof that it's not you anticipate it.
Go ahead and let it fall.
Let it create a thought.
I've said this many, many times in these sonics.
When you hear it chattering away, whether it's slow chatter, good chatter, bad chatter,
go ahead, let it come to a pause or not.
And just in your mind, say, OK, what else do you have to say?
And watch what happens.
It goes totally silent because at that point, the gig is up.
It's like, oh, he actually he or she knows that it's not them and it's me, meaning another
entity doing it.
And now they're anticipating me.
I better stop.
Right, because I can't continue that way.
The only way these entities continue or this other whatever you want to call it continues
in your head is if you think that it's you.
It's kind of like someone shadowing you, you know, following your every move, which is a
typical thing in the military.
Right. Or when you're following someone, you just follow at a distance.
When they slow down, you slow down.
When they speed up, you speed up.
Right. I don't know what that's called.
I think it's a shadow kind of thing.
But that's how it works.
So if you can, yeah, if you can get it quiet and relaxed, then you'll get better.
At least you'll be in a situation where you can assess what's going on.
And by the way, if your arm gets blown off, you still have to wrap it tight, by the way.
What's left of it? You know, I'm not making fun of it, but that's really what it's called a
tourniquet. Right.
So absolutely true.
OK, well, and the funny thing is, if somebody's shadowing you and you turn in the same
direction that they are coming from and you go toward them, that's when the gig is up.
So, yeah, unless they're fast enough to turn and face away from you at the same time.
Right. Unless they are, which if they didn't anticipate your move, they won't be.
So there you go.
That's how you disrupt that.
And because it's sonic, you know, your survival audio, your survival depends on audio.
A lot of people want to argue this point, but it's very simple.
When you're you rely on your vision, it's straight ahead and about 30 degrees to the
left, 30 degrees to the right from viable peripheral vision.
Some people more, some people a little less.
If you're in a dark place like in a forest, even see this memorialized in film or a dark
room or what do people say?
Oh, did you hear that? We might be in trouble.
What is that? Right. It's your your sound basically is what is basically 360.
It's more direct.
Higher frequencies are more directional.
Lower frequencies are not directional.
So you do really rely on survival for audio and sound.
And by the way, poor sound quality reproduction will damage you as much as chemicals and
food do, by the way.
This is there's been studies on that.
They're not published, you know, so.
OK, well, fair enough.
But I find this interesting because, like I said, if you were to turn to somebody who's
shadowing you like that, though, and you turn exactly in their direction against the
direction that they were shadowing you, that's what it sounds like you're saying to do.
But would you just anticipate that?
Well, yeah. But should someone do that out loud with the whole OK, what else do you have
to say? You could, but it's not necessary.
I think it would be in a thought, see, because when you anticipate them, by the way, pay
attention to what's going on.
You don't hear your voice.
You don't hear any voices when you anticipate them.
You just tag that along at the end of the voices that you do hear.
No, you know, your own voice is totally emo.
It's totally silent.
Well, that's why you're reading emotion.
But that's why you end up speaking out loud when you're actually speaking, because you
don't have that sound in your head.
You actually have to make it right.
One of the some of the personal writings of Walter Russell, he would do it out loud when
he had thoughts that he didn't want to entertain or was in a tizzy or whatever.
He would go up to the get up from where he was sitting or in the room, go to the doorway
and say, get out and slam the door as a purely in gesture.
And he said that would change the feeling in him, in the room, whatever the environment.
Yeah. But but the emo, you're the interpersonal is silent and it's it's still a
language, just like, for example, Braille is by touch.
Right. Versus by sight, the inner voice that sound that sounds like you is foreign.
The inner voice that is you is completely silent.
There's no language attached to it.
Just Braille does not have a font.
Right. There's no font for Braille.
It's either a bump or it's not.
Right. Right.
So, yeah, so it's very much a simple way to deduce it.
It is an interesting way to think about it once you start reading the email, because
there's very small emotion, just like a flavor, a taste can take something that you
can taste just for a few seconds can can almost not even be described.
Like you could write a book, someone who's got a good sense of smell and taste on what
an apple tastes like.
Just one apple, not all the apples you can try.
Right. Because emo is the same way.
So a feeling cannot be right.
So it conveyed as easily as words and words are just condensed versions of emos and
thoughts and whatever you could put in a word.
Right. But the email part, once you start learning how to work that, then you start
seeing how the environment around you is more fluid than you normally would think it
is. Well, that that is definitely different, you know, than what I was thinking.
I want to go back to something, though, because you jumped off it a little quick for
me. You know, we were on the divide and conquer thing and the way that works and, you
know, how that's a useful tool for others.
You sort of suggested a solution, but I didn't quite get it.
Yeah, I don't.
Well, OK, there what is the solution is very simple.
It's just take it in stride because there's a built in resistance in the system.
In other words, if if what you know how they're dividing, right, what they're doing is
they're providing problems for the solutions.
Of course. Right. Right.
They create it's all problems, problems, problems.
And I wait a second. We were all just fine.
And here are all these problems and we already have the solutions.
But then it's like, no, that's not a solution.
Just look at the problem.
So, yeah, it's very simple.
Just take it in stride. People are the interesting thing about people is that make up the
collective. They're still individuals.
But are they really, if they all act very similarly within a general framework of
resisting what they're concerned about or what solution is not being presented, you
present the solution. No, it can't be that.
Right. I've brought up many things that you hear in Greek speak over the years, even two
decades ago to people that were actually fairly educated or whatever as well.
They say, oh, no, Greek.
I don't believe that's true because they would they would be public outrage.
Oh, my gosh. You know, so they're right away.
They already have the plausibility because they're taking it in stride.
They're fine with it. Right.
You see, but that's the net you slam into is that a whole lot of people who don't even
question it. So they're taking it just fine in stride.
Whatever is put in place.
Exactly. So the most mainstream guy, even if he said a family sends all their children to
die in a war, that's OK.
We fought for our country.
They're still taking it in stride.
You'll have a few sad days or whatever, but they're so happy to get, you know, the flag
and the medal. Oh, we fought.
Oh, we're so proud. But I'm proud.
Yeah, that's it. I'm like, that's your OK.
That's your replacement for your flesh and blood.
It's gone that you spent years raising.
I don't. Yeah.
But here's the thing. I just view everyone as backdrop.
Once you have an idea and you focus on it, everyone around you and everything, even the
thoughts are backdrop.
Right. That's how people focus on goals and get them done.
But on the other hand, I tell people don't set any goals because if you don't meet them,
there's no failure. Right.
If you don't have a goal, you're not going to be concerned about meeting it or failing to
meet it. Right. So keep the goal out of the way.
Keep the give and should factor really low, but keep the focus high.
You see, there's a difference like when you have a goal and you see yourself moving
towards it, whatever it is, whether it's physical or whatever, it could be anything.
The goal is to get something achieved.
Right. You have a paramount point in that goal.
You see yourself moving and then it doesn't work.
You get upset. If you're moving, you get really happy.
Why are you so happy? Because I'm moving towards my goal.
Oh, why are you so upset? Because it's not going towards.
Forget about that. Right.
If you stay focused and leave the emotional part out completely, in other words, whether
you're achieving the goal or going away from it, there's no ups and downs emotionally.
You're just learning from it because actually, you know, you'll learn more from not
achieving your goal than achieving your goal.
Right. This has been shown as a hell scenario in Twilight Zones, where the bank
robber, you know, he thinks he's in heaven and he says, I want to go rob a bank.
And they say, OK, well, tell us how you want it to end.
Do you want to get away? Do you want to get caught?
He says, I don't want to.
I don't want to know that.
He says, just that's why I rob banks.
It's just, you know, the thrill is, no, you have to tell us.
Do you want to get caught? Or is this noise?
If this is heaven, I don't want to be here.
And he's like, what makes you think you're in heaven?
Yes. So that's the funny thing.
I remember that. That was the guy was gambling, too.
And he was and he couldn't move or something.
You know, he couldn't. He couldn't lose.
Yeah. And because he couldn't lose.
This sucks. What do you mean?
Well, how is this happening? This is no fun.
Right. And now is it really about winning or losing?
Is it about what you learn from losing?
There you go. The thrill is a different.
There's a thrill for winning and there's a thrill from not a thrill up, maybe a
thrill down, which is still look like drugs.
There's uppers and downers.
Right. They're both. Some people look at it as risk taking.
Right. Risk taking is the thing.
Right. If there is no failure, if there's no pain, if there's no possibility of
getting harmed, if there's no possibility of falling off of the beam, if there's
no possibility of hitting the floor off of the off of the high wire, then it's
not that interesting. Right.
Because there is there's no consequence.
So who cares? Right.
Well, here's the way like my what am I doing?
Like, what am I doing here? I said, OK, when it comes to other people.
Yeah. Consider me like a pet.
I need some water and some food and some shelter.
I can do a lot of different things.
OK. But that's all I require.
Right. Right.
OK. Yeah.
If you if anyone wants a pet Greek, I'm available.
Pet Greek. OK.
Well, I just need food and some water.
I could cook. I could do a lot.
I could fix pretty much anything mechanical and non-mechanical,
creative, inventive.
Yeah. And think about it.
Instead of saying, hey, I want to bank millions and billions like Jeff Bozo and
I want a fancy car and I want to own an island and I want my own lab and I want
to. Yeah, I'd like I'd like a lab with 150 feet of workspace, a counter space
and 200 feet of whiteboard.
That's usually blackboard, you know, right.
You know, and all this other stuff and all the machines and toys to make things
and a couple of associates that could, you know, you have someone in the
grinding department, actually the grinding department.
She better look. Anyway, the the other department, the machining department,
you know, all these other things, you need something made.
Right. By the way, there's a big a lot of hoopla about all these automation
stuff, 3D printing that is so slow and sucky.
Yeah, I could most of the time I could make stuff way faster and better than a
3D printer. But anyway, yeah, keep it simple.
So if your lot in life was to be a pet.
There was a song back in the days that we make great pets.
Right. Yeah. Yeah.
So you're not going to be upset.
Yeah. And by the way, I'm serious.
So if anyone's looking for a pet Greek, I'm pretty much available.
That is the strangest thing.
I would have never expected that to come out of your mouth.
No, it just did.
Yeah, it did, though. It actually did.
So, all right.
All of this aside, I mean, we've been through the banking thing, but I see it
this way and still have this question, OK, which is, you know, if you learn this
and you say, OK, this is the way it actually runs and then you try and implement
that stuff. Yeah, it works well.
But here's the thing, does it?
Because. Yeah, yeah, it does.
Hold on. Hold on. They had to give you the remedy.
Doesn't mean you have to. They have to flaunt it before they went ahead and did
the system because they knew they were going to crash everything and make you
this is like make you part of the system, meaning literally you are the collateral.
Right. But you cannot really get out of that.
But you can get out of a lot of the stuff like when you do a conditional endorsement,
like a demand for lawful money, if you just sign something that requires signature.
Technically, they can't fractionalize that ten to one.
They just have to run it through as that amount.
There's someone that did a payroll check, received a payroll check
and the boss says, don't deposit the checks.
So whatever, because the money's not in there.
So he ran back to the bank after he deposited
and he asked for the check back because it was bouncing.
They did give it back to him and they had already cut off his endorsement.
So it wouldn't show.
So when they gave him back the check, they taped it back on.
So the thing is, it's out of your hands.
Right. At that point, you it also takes two for the endorsement to work.
Right. And here's the thing.
It all goes back to the who is running the information.
It's the Bar Association, which are which is a private association,
just like the banks that have been tasked.
Go look up history of the Department of Justice.
U.S. Even there'll be a whole bunch of articles.
It'll say, oh, it's around 18 something.
But, you know, it's a historical anomaly.
Grant signed it in like no one knows where it came from.
Duh. Right.
So, yeah, they are the problem for the gatekeeping aspect.
You know, there is codes, by the way.
I'm not going on a tangent here. This is direct.
There are codes that tell you that there's nothing you can write.
Like if you have an exemption, right.
So there's nothing you can write that could be held against you
when it comes to banking.
So that means that you could take a napkin to write a hundred dollars,
sign it, and it's good as a check.
Just like that. No count. Nothing. Right.
But yet you go to a stove and it says the attorney general says
that check writers will be prosecuted.
Bullshit.
Because he says so. Yeah.
Because you actually give them the power to do that.
They don't know any law at all, by the way, at all.
They sound like they know.
There's like people all over the you know, I'm not going to mention names
like Cliff High or anyone like that.
But oh, OK.
But there's a lot of people that have followings
and they think they're learning from someone who sounds smart.
Big difference. Yes.
From someone who actually is smart.
Now, here's the thing.
That's one thing about a New York accent.
I always tell you, if you have a New York accent, take elocution,
because in most circles, English speaking,
if you show up with a New York accent, you talk like 30, 30, 30 like this.
You sound stupid.
It doesn't matter how smart you are.
Certain things are impedances.
Yes. Yes. Right.
Like very bad stuttering.
Right. Would be an impedance to communication.
A New York accent. Right.
A very heavy New York accent is an impedance to communication.
But then you have other impedances to communication,
like people who sound smart that draw in a certain attention.
But actually what they're saying is pretty much worthless.
Yeah. Right.
So you have to is all this stuff to be considered back to the banking system.
You can only do your part when a remedy is offered.
You do what you you do your part.
But usually these remedies require them to do their part also.
Right. It's a pairing.
Right. You show that's why the whole thing works.
If you have good record keeping.
So, you know, it takes a little extra work.
But the problem is they set up everyone with programming and conditioning.
I hope anyone who's interested in the subject goes and listens
to the 1913 Federal Reserve Act by David Merrill YouTube.
Right. Yeah. You got to listen to that.
And it's very dry.
But he's correct on everything there, which I endorse that video, by the way.
In other words, everything he's he says on that video is rock solid.
And every every way.
OK, that's why it's it's a really good 30 minute or whatever
is 20, whatever minute education.
And this works in every country, except for certain countries
where they don't consider that they have a citizenship, that they have subjects.
Right. OK. Yeah. Right.
But it's still different.
But it still works because you will find
even in the UK and I know any of the UK or Great Britain,
Canada, Australia, all that, you know, they say they're independent, whatever.
They do have a statute saying that you cannot restrict someone
from doing a restricted endorsement.
Right. So. Oh, fair enough.