Well, here we are again.
And what is this 47 right?
47?
Yeah, I think so.
Can be.
I've lost count.
I lost count after three.
After three?
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm not even counting.
I don't think these things are getting titled.
They're just getting numbers.
So each one is its own individual packaged, whatever.
Oh, before we get started, I just want to say, we do still have newcomers, and I don't
know where to direct newcomers for the background stuff other than starting back at number one,
because it is cumulative to a certain degree, right?
Well, if you look for the others, and I think there's going to be a solution in the next
month or so where they'll be able to get all of the background stuff in one place.
And that's going to occur.
I don't want to talk about it yet, but we are going to organize it so you can get all
the background stuff.
Not just these conversations between you and I, but other things that you've done.
I think we're going to come up with a way to streamline that.
So to be easier.
From ab initio, from the beginning.
Yes, exactly.
That way, well, from the beginning of what it is we have recorded that we have access
to because, you know, you talk about talking in the 90s.
I've never heard any of that stuff.
Oh, early 2000s, really?
Oh, I've been talking since the 80s.
More listening during the 80s, because all the stuff you see, people talking about flat
Earth and the simulation, all that, I was subjected to that very heavily in the 80s.
You know, consciousness and all that stuff.
You know, I wonder if that is a product of the area of the country that you and I were
both in, because I hear from a lot of other people, they never heard those discussions.
But I know that we had those discussions in that area, face to face, directly.
Yeah, it is geographic, which has some pertinence to what I want to talk about tonight, which
is ennoblement and safety.
And neither one has anything to do with what people think when you hear those words.
Yeah, so.
Yeah, well, noble is an interesting word.
OK, so we're at 47, good enough.
And by the way, somebody did ask me to start dating them.
And I asked them, yeah, according to what, though?
You want the Pope's work schedule or you want, you know, just keep the numbers.
It's fine.
It's kind of like, what is it?
Playing cards are like that, aren't they?
What do we do when we get to 52?
Who's the joker anyway?
Well, that's 53 and 54, right?
Because that's how you get to anyway, 52 pick up.
Of course, we were all subjected to that at some point.
Right.
You want to play 52 pick up, Greg?
I'm sure somebody.
Yeah.
Well, anyway.
So go ahead.
Well, maybe or no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'll leave that.
Yeah.
Because the word noble is interesting.
I got you on that earlier.
It's just what it means.
You could do it with material in society.
You have the nobles.
Then you have the base.
Right.
Base are the masses.
And the same with value added to things.
Precious metals, gases that are inert, things like that are noble and base are not, you know,
noble.
See, what's funny is, though, is I would say that some of the people that are described
as nobles are not often people who act with noble character because there is such a thing
as noble character, is there not?
So is there is there a difference between something that is simply named it by by virtue
of its creation, by virtue of its innate characteristics or its its given characteristics upon creation?
And how about actions?
What you can do with it?
Sure.
But let's rewind the tape.
OK.
If there is such a thing anymore.
You actually there might be.
Rewind.
I didn't say people.
I said society.
Well, yeah.
In other words, it's a demarcation in society.
Like, for example, when you speak of noble metals, you know, you look at the precious
metals.
And but at one point when aluminum was considered to be, let's say, put into society again,
it was it was it cost more than gold at the time in the late eighteen hundreds.
Right.
Because it was it was very you need electric purification.
In other words, it's very you cannot really make aluminum as we know it today without electric
refinement.
Right.
So it was not until that process of electricity got to the point where it was available.
So if you had an aluminum piece of anything from the 1890s, you could trade it for a piece
of gold that weighed a lot more than it than it did.
Right.
So that was based on rarity, though.
It wasn't that based more on.
But so is the rest.
Yeah.
There's a twilight zone where some astronauts go to a planet and there's diamonds.
The Street Sweepers sweeping up diamonds.
Right.
It's garbage.
Yes.
As well on Earth.
These are valuable.
And they laughed at it.
Right.
Yeah.
So it's a matter of that also.
But ennobling is that's why I said we're talking about ennobling and safety in a way
that other people wouldn't hear this, say what they attach to it will not work.
What I meant by ennoblement is of materials.
Years ago, it was very well known that if you had gold of a certain quality, you can even
increase its quality by burying it in the ground.
And the ground offered certain to Larrick, etheric to earth, right, energies that would
keep the the metal not only in its high quality, but actually slowly increase its quality.
Right.
Well, same with wines and if you plant anything in the earth, how it reacts with the earth
creates a different characteristic, very much like planting a seed.
Then it becomes a plant.
Then it sprouts fruit and makes more seeds.
Right.
I'm going in a different direction with this, OK, because this has nothing to do really
with the earth per se.
It's a process that one can consider.
In other words, when you go out and select items, material things and for most people,
by the way, knowledge is a material thing.
You know, they don't see it.
This is a slight tangent when we communicate.
Right now, this is probably digital.
So supposedly, it's being broken down to binary and then put back together finally into
some acoustic analog way where we make sense of it.
Right.
But but the information knowledge itself, once it reaches its terminus in the mind of
the individual, it's no longer digital.
It has a flavor.
In other words, it's not zeros and ones.
So remember, remember that.
In other words, there is an analog string, you know, it's kind of like.
I think of it much like the energetic, the energetic transfer that we talked about with
the tapes.
Right.
And tape.
Yes, it might be an antiquated thing at this point.
But this concept that you literally do put different tones, different representations,
words, knowledge, indeed, transferred onto a tape and it's an energetic transfer as
opposed to a physical one.
But it does create a physical result when it's turned back around and played out through
a speaker, which, you know, creates that analog and is analog.
Yeah.
OK.
Now, what I'm going to be discussing, take a minute, sit back.
And this is going to be with the effects of subtle energies.
Now, there's subtle energies that have subtle results.
Most things, by the way, that you see on the stupid rectangle that they call so energies
have no results because it's put out by the, you know, the community to keep people busy.
But in subtle energies, you have weak results and strong results.
This is somewhere between weak and strong.
And this is what this might sound very base and rudimentary.
No pun intended about it being noble and base.
But the effects of location within an environment, like we said earlier, burying it in the ground
on the surface of the ground or up high off the ground, how high that can be, you determine
what you normally would have access to, let's say temperature effects of other living and
nonliving things in the area can change things.
Oh, yeah.
We know that Greek.
OK.
What I mean is by this, for example, I posted some pics, by the way, of the water devices
that I'm trafficking in lately, just in case people are interested or curious, they can't
say, what are you doing?
I just did.
I'm not trying to offer them to anyone.
They're all custom made or whatever.
But I put some information if anyone is interested.
You never know.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
You put that in the chat.
What, today?
A few days ago.
Sorry.
More than a few days.
But maybe.
Yeah.
So.
So what I've discovered is when I'm working with these materials, let's just go to let's
go forward.
Let's go.
The last time we spoke actually going backwards, I said the next project in the near future
will be not a dissectable capacitor, but a dissectable inductor and how it pertains to
the body, creating and manifesting things by induction, not the way we're told by absorption
in these chemical things.
Right.
But fast forward, for example, the ennoblement of metal, you know, like something like aluminum
that I brought up earlier.
When you work with aluminum, you can basically work with it with basic woodworking tools.
It's in the twelve hundred to fifteen hundred PSI, which is like the hardness of a hardwood
like white oak or something.
Right.
But don't hold me in the PSI numbers.
It depends on the aluminum.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
Different.
There's there's different qualities of aluminum.
It's fairly malleable.
Alloys.
Yeah.
You can do a matrix aluminum, which is harder than steel.
But this is not whatever.
This is sort of the thing I wanted to bring up.
If you have a piece of aluminum and you keep it at a certain temperature at a certain pressure
and the pressure is air pressure.
When I say bar, that's one bar is one atmosphere.
Right.
And let's say two and a half bar at the temperature of a fever, which is about one hundred eight
degrees for a certain amount of time.
You'll notice that the tools that cut it prior to that treatment will have a very difficult
time, almost not be able to cut it or drill it.
Right.
So you're changing its quality.
But chemically and analytically, it's still pure aluminum.
But they can achieve something like that, let's say, by adding what's called metal matrix
with ceramic beads in it makes it really hard.
So what I've noticed also working with certain high quality, high grade plastics, I work with
Schedule 80 PVC.
I don't like the PVC, but Schedule 80 is NSF industrial standard.
If you show up anywhere with that in any industry, they respect it.
Right.
And it's also you can get NSF certification, blah, blah, blah.
What I've noticed is what I've been doing to make the pipe malleable to form as it does
is a mixture that an ad hoc mixture that I had here of certain quartz sands and magnetite
and things like that, things like that.
And the magnetite was of a certain quality that I used in a hot form to hot bend the
pipe and form it and have it relax and stay stable in that form.
And I noticed that if I didn't use that ad hoc mixture that I was using, I had a different
quality in the plastic so much so that if I don't use the mixture that I'm using, the
normal plastic bench acts like normal plastic.
In other words, it's not impervious to solvents.
Right. If you put a strong solvent like acetone, it will melt it or damage it.
It was susceptible to heat changes.
But I noticed when I used the ad hoc mixture that I used to bend the material, it was no
longer susceptible to solvents as it was before, and it was much more stable, thermally
stable. You know, that sounds very similar to what they used to do to plastic glasses
frames when they used to use the hot sand in order to reshape it.
And indeed, it became a lot less problematic for, like, say, you sweating into it and all
that, too. That was like this is different.
Well, both in other words, I've tried both hot sand bending.
The one that uses the ad hoc mixture changes the plastics quality where the regular hot
sand did not. Yeah, that was the only reason why I brought it up is that it actually used
to change the quality of the plastic and plastic glasses frames, which actually made it a
little longer. Yeah, which was weird.
I'm not saying it's anywhere similar.
It just had this added effect that I found interesting that it actually by heating it up,
dipping it in sand, hot sand, basically, which was mixed with some old practice.
But the ad hoc mixture that I'm using, I've done I've gone back and forth.
I've cut up sections and subjected them to various solvents and with timers.
And, you know, the best science is the stuff you have.
By the way, if you ever watch a YouTube video or something like that with a scientist as
well, we discovered this using some very expensive equipment.
They're bullshitting. They're trying to get you away from being inquisitive and handing
over all your cognitive beliefs to them.
Like I've always said, if you can't do it in your kitchen or living room table or in
your backyard, it's bullshit.
Right. Even nuclear stuff.
And I don't want to get into that because I have had conversations with people that
worked with chemists like their parent was a chemist, old school.
And Fourth of July, he'd make sub nuclear reactive fireworks.
Like instead of the regular chemical fireworks, he would make small nukes.
Imagine. Right. So and in his in his basement.
So this all this stuff that you hear about it, there's a video, the nuclear scare
scam. I forgot the guy's name, talked about why nuclear material is so expensive.
It's part of the security apparatus.
The reason they did that. Well, they tell you nuclear material is dangerous.
It's part of a security apparatus.
So when people walk near, they say, oh, it's radioactive.
Leave it alone because it's a million dollars an ounce.
Right. Well, look, it's also it's also a solid strategy by people that corner markets
and control things. If you make something super expensive, it becomes difficult for the
common person to acquire it.
Just in general, it doesn't even matter if it's actually dangerous.
It actually matters that it's difficult for most people to acquire it.
I mean, if I tell anybody listening, they ended up being an expensive process, which
it became cheaper, by the way, but it was still around a million dollars an ounce.
Yeah. And they and they figured the it would get even more expensive to build a security
apparatus. So one guy had the idea or maybe a group had a think tank.
Why don't we tell people it's extremely radioactive and hazardous and they will stay
away from it? Well, in fact, it's not expensive and difficult to work.
That my point is, if it's expensive and difficult to work with altogether, whether by
legend or by truth, and it is just difficult to acquire monetarily, the majority of
people that you and I would encounter are not going to ever be able to touch it or
get near it because they want to steal it.
The access, of course, they would want to steal it.
But the access is denied.
And if they try to steal it, well, you better know how to steal it safely.
Otherwise you're going to say that's the whole scam.
Hold on. Hold on. Slow down.
Rewind. What I'm saying is there is no danger with these materials.
Yes, there is. They get hot when you get over critical mass.
No, my point was that you make you make this the common idea and you make this a
common danger with acquiring it, because that way it reduces the amount of people
that will even attempt to acquire it.
And there you go.
And even if you wanted to steal it, you don't want to steal it because.
Hold on. Slow down, slow down, Chuck.
Too much coffee, maybe.
I don't know, because my case is always too much coffee.
If I don't have coffee and cigarettes, I can't do anything.
But anyway, the case ended up being the first amount that they ever
produced, the Americans at least, was a billion an ounce in today's money.
But then they got a little smarter at it and it ended up being in the million an
ounce. And then, of course, it's how do we keep it secure?
Because obviously people would want to try to steal it.
Let's just tell them that it's dangerous.
And now it doesn't end up being on the list of thieves, right, that want it.
And that's a scam. Right.
But it's OK, because you're not going to do much with it anyway.
You can make your own. Oh, my gosh.
What's he talking about? All right.
So let's get off of that.
What I want to say is that the ennoblement of material is something that is way out
of the people's nomenclature in their language.
In other words, when they talk about things, the most they're going to actually
say is, oh, keep it in the fridge.
So it's fresher. Right.
When you get some food or something, right.
Keep it. And you have like certain things of paints and glues.
They have what's called a pot life.
You know, once you open it, it's only good for a certain amount of time.
You have a you buy a tube of glue and you open it and use a little bit.
And a few years later, you're like, oh, I remember I need that glue.
Yeah. I remember that glue you got for this.
Yeah. Yeah. Let's go. I have some.
You go in the cabinet, pull it out.
What? Oh, it's dry. It's no good anymore.
Right. So pot life is over.
OK, so you have these common things that people interact with all the time.
And the most that they ever see in their vernacular is, oh, if you don't put it in
the fridge, it's going to spoil.
There's very little emphasis on ennobling something, keeping it, you know, to a
certain degree, even woodworkers.
OK, for example, if you buy, let's say, hardwood flooring, you cannot install it
until the wood or should not reach a certain moisture content.
If you install it when the moisture content is above five percent or so.
Now, what a nice floor. Two weeks later, you got quarter inch gaps everywhere
because the wood shrunk. Right.
If you go to a good construction site, they usually stack the wood in there for a
couple of weeks or they have a moisture test before they install it.
Not anymore with the synthetic material so much.
So that is that's still not what I'm discussing.
There is there's anyone who plays an instrument knows that you shouldn't record
acoustic guitar on a rainy day.
You can never really tune it properly.
Right. So that's true.
And this is what I actually believe it or not.
A lot of guitars don't think that way.
But I'm telling them they notice it sounds like, yeah, why don't you start applying
it? I always I always check the humidity level because that's what's important.
If the humidity is too high, don't bother because you're not going to consistently
maintain the guitar.
But try to measure try to measure humidity when it's raining.
Yeah. Nearly impossible.
Right. Yeah. Right. Right.
Well, it's it's possible you get you'll get really wide readings and it changes
drastically depending on what floor of the building you're on.
Right. The higher up you go, the more humid it is.
Right. Oh, wait a second.
You know. OK. Anyway, it's another discussion.
So to get off the tangent, there's an ennoblement concept.
The only time you actually see it being used most frequently.
But what I mean by ennobling concept is the combination of certain things in the
environment and other materials to make something of better quality is maybe you'll
see it in the wine industry.
It has really been dumbed down.
Also, I remember speaking to people who were in a legacy of winemaking and
one of the more, let's say, prized wine bottles.
Women were never allowed into the room where the barrels were, because
when a woman a woman is menstruating, she's giving off a certain pheromone
and that pheromone would penetrate and permeate the wood and affect the taste of
the wine. So instead of asking, is
the woman in her cycle, they just prevented any woman from going into the building,
you see. And this is like a level of of, let's
say, critical, you know, let's say not just thinking, but critical level of
operating that you don't you don't see anymore.
It just doesn't exist. Almost, you know, in common.
And it's also dismissed as old fashioned, because, look, you're Greek and I
clearly say to you, I'm Italian.
And we both know that we probably had ancestors who had this idea that you don't
let the women into those rooms at all, because we've known at some point some
ancestor that probably made their own wine and you let them work in
the vats. But that's in open air.
And that way they're not exposed.
And also. Right. But it's a certain level.
But the thing is, it's just a concept.
It really has nothing to do with.
Yeah. But some people think it's just, you know, old fashioned because it's
antiquated based on old ideas.
Specific is that they're trying to get certain analogs here so people can get a
sense of how fine things really do work.
And the reason what inspired me to bring up the ennoblement is because I am just
completely fascinated by the things that I'm working on now and will be working
on on how subtle the effects of certain things can be.
But the result is not a subtle result.
It's a very strong result.
Right. Another thing I'm going to add, then I want to talk about safety.
Well, subtle is not equivalent to inconsequential.
That's really the case here that you have subtle and weak and subtle and strong
results. You have two different things.
Yes, that's that's the point there.
It's not always a matter of well, subtle just means it's not very important.
It's just a small thing.
Yeah. A small burning ember is very subtle.
Right. But if it's attached to a fuse that lights a powder keg, it's still subtle,
subtle, subtle, subtle, subtle, subtle, subtle until it gets to the powder keg.
And then it's very strong.
You see the same exact ember.
Right. So this is somewhere in between just an ember and a powder keg.
What I'm discussing. Another thing when you're dealing with ethereal devices, what
I'm doing with the water and the weather and other things, this just struck me
recently. That's why it's I find it critical to bring it up to see if it's a wave
coming through where other people might have gotten this download, let's say, or
inspiration of thinking when I work with what I'm working with.
And I consider it to be an ethereal device because I use magnets, but I don't use
magnetism. In other words, the device has magnets, but it does not use magnetism.
Right. It's kind of, oh, well, then why would you use them if they don't understand?
Right. So it's kind of like the way we society uses fire.
You use fire, but you're not using the fire on your you say you're staying away
from it. You're having to do its thing in a way that it's very isolated.
OK. What I want to bring up is when you're working with ethereal objects, in
other words, when you're accessing the resultant factor of what we know about the
ether, mass matters.
In other words, the when I'm working with the water, the mass of the actual
center of the piece makes a difference in the end result.
When I'm working with, let's say, the weather, the actual mass of water and the
size of the weather gun actually makes a difference as well.
So it's but it's not either way.
You only see the difference that the increased mass makes in the result, not in
not like having a small cap gun versus, you know, a 50 caliber gun, the kick, you
know, if you shoot a larger caliber pistol, it has much more of a kickback or
flyback. Right.
Not like that at all.
It's there's no direct correlation, but the direct correlation comes in the end
result. That's why it's very difficult for people to
understand working with these ethereal devices, because they're used to immediate
results. Like if you have a small hedge trimmer, right, and then someone there has
a three foot still chainsaw, right, and you go about cutting the same things, there's
a huge difference. But, you know, the reaction you're going to get from anyone
watching the big chainsaw go versus a little hedge trimmer.
Right. So this is the way we've been trained.
But I'm I'm saying that whether it's a hedge trimmer or a chainsaw in the
ethereal, they're both going to be absolutely silent and it'll look like neither
of them is doing anything until the job is done.
So this is this is how the ennoblement works.
Just to maybe slightly finish this off, if anyone's ever gone into what's called
hard rock mines where you find gold, most gold is found by creeks, rivers and
placer, you know, nuggets that are worn out.
But if you go into a hard rock situation where there's like a mile hole, a mile
long, deep hole in a mountain where you're you go in to see the gold inside the
mountain rock. Right.
It's called hard rock mining.
Let's say you will see quartz formations and the usually the gold is forming through
the quartz as if it flew ahead.
Like it was a fluid at one point and help and grew with the crystal.
Right. So that could be a rather quick process.
In other words, that process could just take a few decades where the scientists will
tell you, well, that takes millions and millions of years.
It doesn't. So that's what I mean by, again, it's very, very subtle.
You can look at a mountain. It doesn't look like anything's going on.
But if you've been in a hard rock mine and you've seen a virgin gold vein, you'll
see the quartz, you'll see the gold.
Depending on the gold vein, there are many types, but I have seen that.
And it's interesting when you see it, it's all organic, all of it.
Even the minerals have organic outlays or, you know, the the archetype of or of how
things grow. So with that said, I want to get into safety.
What I mean by safety, not the way that you might think that word means safety
pertaining to Greek speak and other utterings of similar reprisal.
What did he just say? OK, meaning going against right to a degree.
When you hear Greek speak, it's very different than normal speak.
And many people, this is a safety now, many people will take to it on a list on a
hearing basis. They'll hear it.
And very rarely have I ever been, let's say, challenged or negated or whatever.
Or, you know, other people have for some reason in public or speaking with a
stranger or whatever.
I've heard some academics say, well, I don't know what you're talking about.
I have I only like conversations that are linear, you know, like one thing at a
time. Right. So I've heard that and various other stupid remarks.
It seems like the more education they have, the dumber they their remarks are.
So what I mean by safety is what happens is when you bring up Greek speak
utterings, people very rarely see any reason to divert or negate or disagree
with very rarely.
You might have some disagreement here, but it's very superficial because, you
know, if the cognitive dissonance thing.
Right. We're talking about basic, basic things.
Right. Now, what happens?
This is what I mean by safety and why the Greek speak does not work on the mass
collective and why it is a unique factor, like a very, very unique factor in one's
thinking and one's ability to even think about or discuss it.
There's this thing I call safety.
What happens is you approach an individual and you bring up something that's in
Greek speak, or let's say I'll speak from the first person, right, or a third
person like I like to.
So you discuss certain things, whether it's about the character of the person or
society or religious beliefs.
Or did you know, you know, very basic stuff, you know, we're not talking about
like, I read a book and I found this out.
You should never notice like, you know, the days of the week, you know, how to
keep time, anything, anything, even superficial approach.
For example, you can absolutely destroy any religion with a superficial approach
of what's in the text that they're supposed to subscribe to very easily.
So all these very simple things.
I recently took a shot at induction just trying to introduce that idea to somebody.
You know, yeah, go ahead.
Yeah, you have to do it in a way, though, that is personable to the person's what
they expect to hear on such a conversation.
Maybe I'll talk about that.
So even what I do is when you bring up anything outside of the, quote, unquote,
normal collective vernacular, it should be done in a way where the conversation has
the the cadence and the and the intensity that they normally would hear as if they
were watching it on television, right?
Or something benign, you know, even though they try to if you watch the history
channel, such garbage, all of it, not some of it on how they try to dramatize things.
I'm like, why are they putting dramatic music behind something that this that
they're saying is a blatant lie or totally stupid?
It's because it's the music, the background music that affects the mind more than what
they're saying. You see?
So that's what I mean.
It's the casualness.
Sometimes it doesn't have to be casual.
That's why rather subtle soundtracks, not just with music, but with sound effects as
well, are often piped in there.
And you're not really hearing it.
You know, it's not the first thing that comes to mind.
You're listening to the words, you're watching the image and you think that's what
you're focusing on.
Well, yeah, the early TV research, they found that after 20 minutes of watching TV,
almost everyone goes into alpha wave status and that alpha wave, you're very the brain,
right? It's very suggestive, suggestive.
And by the way, early studies on the brain in the early 20th century, what they came up
with was that most of the brain, except for the front of the brain, is is set up to to
believe and accept everything that it sees or hears.
It's only the front part of the brain and not the left or right, but the very front that
has the ability to discern.
So they know how to deal with that because it's on the front.
They could pulse it with low frequencies and like we're talking about.
And now pretty much everybody believes everything they hear and see.
Right. So but anyway, to go back to it.
So once you have a certain relaxed way, you know, not getting up into someone's face,
people are very agreeable, I find.
Right. But the reason why it's never for the general public or 99 percent of people you'll
ever mention anything about Greek speak to is because of safety.
What do I mean about that?
OK, bring me talking about safety.
It doesn't say anything about safety yet.
Yep. Still waiting on that real definition there.
Yeah. Yeah. Very simple.
This is specific to Greek speak, because no matter how much they like or don't like what
you say, how jarred they are by it or let's say unaffected or whatever.
One of the things that they do understand, and I do bring this up is you've probably
never heard this before. And now I finished up and say you'll probably never hear it
again from anyone else.
And they usually agree.
The safety part is this.
They know that because they never heard it from anyone else and probably won't hear it
from anyone else again when they go out into the world, into the collective, whether
it's people on the street where they live, their family, their workers, where no one
will ever go down such a path and bring up anything like that ever again, most likely
so they can listen to what you're saying, you know, the Greek speak to a point.
But they know that once they depart from your presence, even earshot, they are
completely safe because everything around them goes back to how it was before.
Right. And there's no reason.
So there's no they. In other words, they kind of know consciously that even if
something they hear in Greek speak really jars them down to the core, it makes them
uneasy. There is an intuitive part that they know that once they leave the presence
of whoever speaking the Greek speak, they will be safe again because no one else ever
brings anything like this up.
That's what I mean by safety.
And that's why the normies, the collective, whatever the people that are spiritually
lazy or whatever, listen to the Greek speak and, quote unquote, put up with it if it
makes them uneasy, because they know the moment they leave that the presence of
whoever is uttering these things, they are going to be completely safe.
So in plain speak, it would be that they're just simply not worried about getting
confronted with it again anytime soon.
So therefore, it's OK.
Well, yeah. And that is why they will never accept it in other or do anything with it.
So because of its rarity, basically, because they're not going to have to hear it
again because they won't hear it from somebody else.
That's that safety.
I don't think there's anything rare about it because ninety nine percent of the Greek
speak stuff is bringing forward what's already in front of everyone.
Well, yeah, but it's rare that somebody actually does that.
Yeah, right. So I don't think it's rarity.
I think what it is is, again, safety.
There's they can be uncomfortable with while they're listening as much as they feel
uncomfortable because they know the moment they depart, they will be safe again forever.
Well, OK, I I'm trying to wrap my mind around this because to me, it seems
it seems odd, but it's it's almost like since I since I won't ever see this again,
that actually explains a few other things.
I see where, you know, people talk about how could you possibly ignore this thing over
here? It is because they know they're not going to have to deal with that again.
I think that does change the reaction.
I think when they when they this is deep, deep psychological overview here.
Yeah, because it doesn't have to be Greek speak, by the way.
Most of the things that disturb another person when they're confronted with something
that is disturbing is because what is it always boiled down to?
You can hear it in their own language.
They'll tell you, well, I never want to have to go through that, even if they just
heard about something terrible.
Let's just say take anything.
You read a terrible headline in the news.
You know, the old jokes. There's some people that just come up to you and begin a
conversation with. Did you see that there were five murders yesterday?
You know, and you go, well, that's still part of the collective.
The whole thing is, OK, with this is one thing that I try to discern with people.
Well, yeah, especially with Greek speak before.
So tell me something that you've heard on TV, church radio that was not a lie.
In other words, and that kind of thing, what you know, because I know what they're
thinking. Right. So and I'll tell you what they're thinking, but something that's not
a lie. In other words, and then I say, well, in other words, give me tell me a media
story or a religious story or some story you've heard that is not a lie
from any of those groups that I met.
And then one person will say, oh, yeah, there was an accident on I-10.
A truck overturned yesterday.
Was that a lie to Greek?
And I'm like, no, I said story.
That's a report they can.
I'm telling you, CNN could come here right now or your priest and tell you this is a
stop sign, which we're standing in front of right now.
He's not lying because he's just reporting what you see and anybody can see.
But I'm talking about when they start giving you stories, they're all lies, all of
them. Right.
So now they start to discern the difference between a report and a story.
They say it all the time. They discern it on their own.
They tell you this is a story and this is a report.
They listen carefully.
Right. So and the other thing is people are getting wound up because they're being
distracted because the cataclysms that are coming are cataclysms that have not
happened in over 6000 years.
Right. So so you have to distract the people because when when you have something
that is so monumental, let's say even one percent of the population getting a
handle on it is way too much.
You have to keep it like below a thousandth of a percent right to guarantee some
kind of a way you can have a clean escape.
Right. Because they're not they have no duty, no authority.
Whether it's religious, governmental or whatever, has any authority to protect any
duty to protect anyone.
Right. As a matter of fact, they do the opposite.
Well, this is how I explain the JFK thing when people go, well, how come you guys
haven't made this kind of progress or that kind of progress with this or that?
And I go, because there's only about a thousand of us that actually do any of the
work. And you don't understand that a thousand people is inconsequential.
Right. As long as the numbers are very, very small.
They see. OK, if the numbers are not small, yes, there could be obstacles.
Right. They're just they don't view you as resistance at all because they have enough
ordinance to kill everyone five times over.
They don't care about that. And there's enough dumb people to do that.
Right. So for them.
So what I mean by it is the distractions are going to be increasing more.
So even if someone like me who completely ignores everything in the media, it's like I
don't even want to know who the president is because it's all a joke anyway.
Right. But I do find out eventually like the Maui fires.
I didn't know anything about the Maui fires.
I still don't know anything. But I could tell you exactly what went down based on the
previous playbook. Right.
All the conspiracies. And it was for knowledge.
And I don't even know. I mean, am I used to tell me, you know, it was for knowledge.
The government's in on it for as a land grab.
A whole bunch of people died. No one knows why.
Why did metal burn and plastic didn't.
Why did certain houses burn and others didn't.
Right. But that's what.
Right. And I haven't looked at a damn thing about the Maui fires, except maybe two
titles and you bringing it up and someone else bringing.
No, I know you haven't.
And yet you're you're calling exactly what the discussion is.
And yeah. Yeah, exactly.
So the same with politics.
You half of it is blame the people that came before you.
The other half is blame that you're not getting cooperation.
And the other half is you're a victim.
So anyway, what I'm saying is, as we get closer to time that's coming,
there's going to be more and more and more distraction about, you know, look at each
other and starting fights.
So what I'm trying to say, I brought this up in terms of safety, because part of the
safety mechanism that people enjoy when, in other words, if you confront anyone with
Greek speak, they will depends on who it is.
Some people, I suggest, don't do it if you're not a good communicator.
Don't even bother because you're going to jumble it and it's going to sound offensive.
So what I would suggest is if you if you start bringing up certain things that have
nothing to do with left or right or any other paradigms, people put up with it because
they know that once they leave your presence, there's going to be a safe haven with their
family, their co-workers at the bus stop, whatever, because everyone else is in the
collective. So that is the thing that will start falling apart because those people are
going to be pit against each other.
Right. And that doesn't mean that they're going to come back and listen to the higher
order of things. Yes.
Greek speak is definitely higher order of things because it's not like higher order.
You got to go to the top of the mountain.
It's because it's stuff that's right in front of you that you should know.
By the way, there's an old Chinese saying about there are many paths to the top of the
mountain. But once you get there, the view is always the same.
Right. Yeah.
So look, as we draw to the end of the time, you allotted for me for today, I have just
a quick question. Are we trying to say that instead of their safety in numbers, there
seems to be safety in ignorance?
Because. Absolutely.
Yeah. Like, for example, if I'm around a bunch of people that think like the collective,
I don't feel safe at all.
To me, that's dangerous, right?
Because they could be set off in any minute.
You know, it comes on television.
Anyone with a blue cap should be killed.
They'll do it. There'll be a certain amount of them that will do it.
Yeah. But again, instead of years ago, I used to knock people more than I do now.
And now I just study them like animals, just like you would go on a wildlife excursion.