85 is the number of the sonic and here we are, how are you doing, Greg?
Oh, we're doing okay, so are we still unculting humanity?
Yeah, you know, that is the graphic and if you go to the SoundCloud you'll see that it's used as the graphic for the playlist, the Rated Y playlist,
but it's something that you passed along to me, I don't know exactly how you constructed that,
but it was an interesting little, you know, stylish kind of looking graphic to me anyway.
Quick and cheap and dirty, I don't like sitting in front of a computer for stuff like that,
and I usually don't like what graphic artists do.
I'll give you a quick example.
Well, I was peddling, I was trafficking high-end spring water that I was transmuting tap water from LA,
selling it for $10 a bottle, Spring 2.0, and we had some really high-end clients, it was going well,
but the minute I come back to Tucson it falls apart because whatever, it's all stuff I do is kind of like that, walk away.
Other people can't carry it, it's fine, and I deliberately, with a very fancy bottle labeling system,
insulated bag, no light, keeps it cool, really high-end.
Anyway, the design on the logo of Spring 2.0 I did myself,
basically it was Spring 2.0 Synthesized Spring Water Elite Reserve,
and I deliberately picked a late 19th century French font, the one that was typically used like,
if you go back to the late 19th century, late 1800s for those,
and you look at even a pack of cigarettes in France or soap,
they use this really elaborate, almost baroque style font, it's called French Gothic or something.
Ornate lettering implies certain things.
Yeah, but not calligraphy though, it's not calligraphy.
Not calligraphy, I got you, but ornate lettering, what I'm saying is that intricate lettering often implies certain things.
Right, so a lot of graphic designers would come to me and say,
oh, I like your water, you've got great water, let's do a barter, I'm a graphic designer, and I'll design your label.
Okay, so you are a graphic designer up to what everything's going on in the graphic design world,
so you're basically going to take the label and redesign it so it's real trendy,
so I have to redesign it for a few more years, and no thanks, you can keep your services.
Fine.
That's why I went deliberately and used an 1800s font, because it's been out of style for 150 years,
it ain't going out of style any more than it is, and guess what, it's so out of style, it looks good, right?
Right.
So if you're out of style, you're out of style, but if you're so far out of style, you're almost ahead of the game again, right?
Well, much like people that use gold lettering to put on a label for anything that they want to represent as higher end,
it automatically projects…
Yeah, gold standard.
It automatically projects a whole bunch of ideas just in that, and it could be just shiny gold colored foil.
It's not gold.
It's all like that.
I'll give you an example.
You know, with sommeliers, wine tasters, on a double blind test, every time, every one,
every sommelier wine taster prefers a $20 bottle of wine over a $100 bottle of wine,
but when you take the blindfolds off, and they know they're drinking the $100 bottle of wine and the $20 bottle of wine,
they're always going to give you reasons why they like the $100 bottle of wine better.
The moment you do blindfolds, every time they pick the $20 bottle of wine.
What does that tell you?
It tells me that there's a lot of psychology built into what they think is their taste.
Yeah.
Exactly.
And that's funny.
You know what it reminds me of is the old commercial.
Hey, hey, dummy, did you know that in this high end restaurant you were drinking Folgers?
You know, like that was Folgers coffee big thing, right?
We replaced their super expensive high end coffee with Folgers dry roasted, you know, the stuff you can buy in your kitchen.
This has come up a lot, Liz, in big up restaurants,
and I think by now people that are sensitive about food are not eating out as much because it's getting really crappy universally.
Well, it's crappy and way the hell overpriced for what you get.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm reminiscing.
$18 for a hamburger now, right?
Right.
I mean, I'm reminiscing about food, right?
And thinking back to the days when I could, you know, take a girl out to sit down at a cheap diner in Jersey.
And, yeah, I had $20, $25 in my pocket.
I was likely to cover everything, maybe even the tip, you know, without a problem.
Yeah, yeah, for sure.
$20 for two people at a diner was reasonable.
Yeah, you better walk there with $100 now.
But anyway, this has been coming up a lot about status, and I've been – I could go hang out in the ghetto, any ghetto, and people think I'm from the ghetto.
I could go hang out with very, very high social – I'm saying this humbly – the high social elite, which most people have never had the privilege of doing because it's considered a privilege, and they would think I'm part of them.
So what I'm saying is if you go to these restaurants – OK, in New York, you have a lot of waiters with attitude because they're like bitter actors.
They can't get an acting job, so they're waiting on tables, and they're really sad about it or pissed off about it.
They take it out on the customers, like it or not.
It just comes through.
In Tucson, it's different or in smaller places where there isn't a big acting community.
If you go to a restaurant that's known to be prestigious, they kind of act real snooty because they're like, oh, you're here because we're prestigious.
Now you've got to put up with my attitude, right?
So whenever I sense that, like I'd be with my wife or other people.
I'd say, you know, I'm going to break this waiter.
Look at this guy.
He's got an attitude because he thinks he's better than other restaurants, so he can afford – all right, so watch this.
I'm going to break him, and this works every time.
Very few people know this.
I'm very surprised about this.
Well, like I said, it's a privilege to be in the upper tiers of society and going to the private clubs and all that other stuff.
I swear I picked up what language they used.
By the way, no one I've ever said this to – well, anyway.
So basically I'm going to break him.
So OK, so this is how you get these snooty waiters.
What happens when you get to the – they come at the end of the meal.
Anything else, you say no.
I would like to have what?
The check.
Right.
That's what everybody says.
But when you're in the higher elite circles and the host arrives to the guest of honor or the guest of the party, he asks, I am ready for the service debt.
So in the higher elite circles, they don't call it give me the check.
They call it I'm ready for the service debt, right?
So when the waiter comes, they go, I'm ready for the service debt.
And they're kind of like, what?
So he has to put the words together.
Service.
OK, got it.
And debt.
Oh, I guess he means the check.
Like where the fuck did this guy come from?
And suddenly he feels like a hamster running around to go get the check.
He's like, oh my gosh.
Because no one's ever – it's funny.
So anyway, things are said differently and different.
And they keep it to themselves.
You know how I know they keep it to themselves?
There are no films that show what I just said.
Not a one.
How many films have high snooty dinners going on and not a one ever uses that lamp?
Because it's reserved.
You either know it or you don't.
And it's not broadcasted.
It's not displayed.
It's not advertised.
The elite do that kind of stuff.
They have a certain language.
You know what?
I don't think I've been around the super, super elite people before.
But I've been around a different layer of society where there's nothing said.
And it's just an exchange where they know who to direct it at pretty much and it's just that's it.
There's nothing said in certain circles where it's just a matter of who.
And there's like a back and forth where there's –
But this is – what I'm saying though, the part about asking for the service that is quite common, by the way,
in the finer establishments with the finer customers.
Because there is such a thing as a finer customer.
I've been delving into a little bit of Seth Godin lately.
He's – the total collective stuff.
He's like a marketing guy.
Some other marketing guys.
Everyone thinks they don't really – I mean they're playing along, right?
Like climate change and COVID.
They play along with all that stuff.
See what kind of game – what they're trafficking in, right?
And basically the whole thing – these idiots like – all right.
Seth Godin, he sounds really good.
But is he an idiot?
Yeah, he's definitely in the idiot category or he's playing along like all the other ones.
I'm talking about the high – what's the other one not to mention?
Names is another one.
I think Gordon something.
It's very popular.
He wears like crazy outrageous looking ties, marketing guys, self-help guru type for marketing.
They're morons.
No, they're not morons.
They're idiots.
Meaning an idiot means you're self-centered and they get whispered in their ear the agenda and they go for it and they fool the public.
And they're useful.
That's the other thing about idiots.
Idiots are useful.
Morons are just morons.
They're just morons.
Yeah, they're not very useful.
They're cannon fodder.
Yeah, you use them for plugging up holes and stuff.
So the – or shooting them out of a cannon.
That's what cannon fodder is.
So I'm listening to these guys and it's like I see what they're doing, whatever.
But they do have some tips because remember they're – when the collective likes what they're saying and buys their books and takes their seminars and their master class and all that other stuff,
that's what the collective is reflecting on and I'm not part of it.
I don't know what the collective is doing.
So if you're going to see what the collective is interested in – and I'm not interested in dealing with the collective.
But it's interesting to see this is the higher tier reflection of what they're putting on.
It's so loaded with agenda or whatever and he doesn't see.
These marketing guys don't see.
What they're telling you by the way is the old advertising system of TV, like for example, Tide detergent.
Their whole business was built on TV ads.
But they spend $100 million a year on internet ads and no one clicks on it.
No one clicks on Tide ads on the internet.
No one.
They're wondering why because it's a TV culture thing.
So what these guys are telling you now, these newer guru idiots, that you have to focus on small.
By the way, there is no giant market on the internet.
It's accumulation of millions of little markets.
Which by the way, if you apply the yin and yang, if the internet is so yin because it's so wide, you can only have yang sustain it, which is little tiny thorns.
Or if you look closely at your skin, you have the little peach fuzz growing, pointy objects off of a large, wide canvas.
So if you understand yin and yang, you see what's coming.
But get to the point, Greek.
What these idiots don't understand, the questioning, like the old marketing doesn't work anymore.
The hustle and the hard sell doesn't work.
People don't go for it.
On the internet, people are not clicking.
The lower end, they call it race to the bottom.
The people who try to offer better prices, you're racing to the bottom for coupons and stuff, not those.
But he's trying to explain to people the way that marketing is done doesn't work.
But they do not know that we're entering an era of techno feudalism, that these guys are talking rich and no one's going to get rich.
What's going to be happening is the internet is dividing people more and more, and it makes it even easier to divide them.
The TV divided people Republican, Democrat.
But the internet can divide people.
It's not going to divide Republican, Democrat.
It's going to divide all the little splinter groups that are calling the Republicans and Democrats bullshit.
It's going to divide all those other groups, which TV can't do.
Right, which has done quite well because all those splinter groups in the past would have simply walked away.
Okay, so we're not TV watchers.
It would have more effect, yeah.
Like how many people did you encounter media-wise, whether it was Revolution Radio or whatever?
They always made it a badge of honor.
In fact, I don't even have a TV.
Okay, great.
But it doesn't matter if you did.
It doesn't matter.
Actually, you want to watch it because you want to watch how it's going to become irrelevant.
It is.
Look at Netflix.
People think Netflix is an alternative.
It's not.
It's created by Hollywood.
It's a formula.
They understand that you're going into techno-feudalism.
Okay, take the techno part out.
What is feudalism?
I'm not going to get into it on the Sonic.
That's what you're going into, but it's going to be a techno-assist, the techno-feudalism.
Yanis Varoufakis talks a lot about this.
He's the former finance minister of Greece.
I might be doing something with him, by the way, informally.
I didn't really say that, did I?
No.
In the future.
So yeah, look him up.
Yanis Varoufakis.
So anyway, the techno-feudalism is coming.
The Middle East posture is coming as they're going to be the bad guys again.
And speaking of the bad guys, there was a couple of requests as you – as I've gotten
and on the chat as you've gotten about getting into the biblical stuff again.
I will.
Probably not today or tomorrow, but very soon.
I'm rehashing it based on a lot of the stuff that Jason Breshears has brought up
with the chronology, based on other things that I'm looking at in terms of source document
and basically on the chronology because the whole thing is around the chronology of the
Christ, right?
So you got to understand that as a center point.
Now I'm trying to see maybe it's not a center point, but it has procession.
And I have talked about processions before, which is like, for example, time ended in
1998 and then you have a five-year buffer zone, right?
A procession is like a swing off center, right?
So we're looking at that stuff.
But the thing is, here's the thing that I'm proud of about the biblical stuff is
you may not get spot on like month, day, year until it gets further down the line.
But I have been pretty close over the two decades talking about it.
Very, very close, right?
You ever hear the, again, saying Revolution Radio or whatever.
If I put Revolution Radio on right now, I'd have to take a shower, by the way, clean myself
off.
But anyway, I don't even think it's around anymore.
But that's how I feel about any of these patriot pro-America stuff.
Not because pro-America.
I'm a patriot too.
I was born here.
I like the trees, the rivers, the landscape.
It's about it.
But anyway, what you look at, I almost derailed my own thought there.
I think I did.
But the whole landscape of what was coming, remember like on radio like that, they'd say,
oh, the world's going to end on September 23rd, 2017, right?
Yeah, all different doomsday things were coming up.
I mean, at one point it was 2012.
That was a big, you know, time calendar.
Oh, yeah, which was off because it was on a 360 day, not 365.
It was 713 B.C.
Right.
And this is very well recorded and known by, you know, by many.
The Day the Earth Stood Still is a famous way to think of it.
Not the movie, but, you know, the way it was described.
Sure.
And Mars came into view, by the way, and people were able to see the moons of Mars, which,
right, anyway.
What I've always said is there's a period that's going to go on like this and you're
for two decades and it's been spot on, just like, I think, about less than a year ago.
I said there's going to be a war for the end of the year.
Well, I think near the end of the year is, you know, in springtime, but in the fall,
usually, and a breakdown period to break down Israel.
Israel is going to be like the gang that couldn't shoot straight.
It's going to be very unfavorable.
Right.
But the thing where I wasn't as accurate was it appeared that it would be more an attack
on the West Bank North, but it ended up being a big attack on what they call Gaza.
Right.
Yeah.
But it's certainly spreading around and world sentiment.
I know you don't pay attention to the news, but world sentiment is beginning to turn weirdly
against it, which is interesting because that's never happened before.
Everything's going to be good.
And the Palestinians are going to prevail in this politically and all the support is going
to go to Palestine, even American support to a degree.
But there's still be American support because of the Zionist movement.
But here here's the other thing.
One thing to watch out for.
It's going to cost the next prime minister, maybe even this one, his life, this whole
conflict.
Right.
So I'm able to come up with specifics that work well.
But throw in the chronology of Jason Breshears, which I've been looking at it to look at
a little closer and his description of the seals and stuff.
I got to integrate with that what I'm doing, because it's not like I'm wrong and he's
right or she's wrong and he's right.
It's we're all here to learn.
We're all here to compile what's going on, because like it or not, we're all on the
same cruise ship.
Right.
So but you stay in your cabin away from my cabin.
But we're still on the same ship.
Right.
Sure.
So.
Yeah.
So that's that's where I'm at with the biblical stuff.
And I might even go into some older notes that I've had for decades and look at it and
see if I could purvey like how my thinking has changed over the decades.
Right.
Because I started this in around 2003, the biblical look before before 2003.
If you brought up the Bible, I said, come on, what are you joking?
That was written by Shakespeare.
See, I'd never read it.
I just heard references.
I knew it wasn't valid document, but I knew that everyone used it as a basis.
But when I started and I wanted to read it because I wanted to find out what's in it.
And when I started reading it, no one was talking about anything that was in there
making stuff up.
And I'm saying, OK, my crazy is the world crazy.
Right.
Well, it's odd because not not because people aren't following the book.
I mean, that's normal in anything, but they don't even know what's in it.
But yeah, the odd thing is, though, that it's supposed to be the centerpiece.
Right.
It is the guide.
If you ask the devoted Christian out there, the publicly, you know, pronouncing I'm an
absolute whatever they go, all I need to know is in the Bible.
Great.
OK, cool.
Yeah.
But if you show them what they're saying is not in the Bible, then they say they don't
need it.
Yeah.
Especially if, you know, they've got the Bible belt.
Right.
You're talking like the Bible belt is the easiest place to find those.
And then you've got the buckle of the Bible belt, which is even worse.
Yes.
So they'll kill you.
They don't even know what what they're saying is not in it.
Maybe some off, you know, off.
I would say out of context quotes is the best you're going to get.
Yeah.
The guys who play with snakes actually know more of what's in the book than most of the
other ones.
I'd say.
Yeah.
Well, the ones who will have the best chance of knowing what's in the Bible are Satanists
and atheists.
Yeah.
Because they have the only ones right now that have a rational approach because they've already
rejected the the programming of the religions.
Right.
So the Satanists and the atheists, they have a better chance, believe it or not, folks,
of finding out cognitively, like reading the Bible and actually getting it than any religious
person.
Easy by far.
It's easy to say that.
So, yeah, it's like someone who learns how to cook the wrong way or terrible food.
You're not going to get them to make delicious food where someone who doesn't know how to
cook at all and doesn't like to cook.
If they once decide that they want to now get into cooking, they will have a much better
chance of making delicious food than those who learned not to make delicious food.
Right.
Because they already got the bad habits set.
All true.
But let's let's rope it in and tighten the rope.
OK, because here's the thing.
When we when we talked about this previously and we talked about uncultivated, we started
on maybe describing what the cult is.
And also we talked about why we were going to call this rated Y.
And these things are important now, not because, you know, it's not an ego thing here.
It's a matter of what is the point of uncultivated?
Why is you know, don't the cults serve a purpose, too?
I mean, everything you are.
Well, the cult.
OK, it's very simple.
It's very simple.
You know, this is like people say that spiritual everything.
I mean, if you're asleep or knocked out or in a coma or dead, then you're non-spiritual.
But anyone who has is awake and conscious, even whatever level of intelligence or cognition
that's everything that you do and think about has a spiritual connotation to it.
Right.
Spirit is consciousness.
So the cult is short for culture.
I had someone once tell me, don't use that word called because it's it's it means
CUNT.
And I'm like, no, it doesn't.
What's wrong with you?
Where the hell did you get that from?
Yeah.
Just moronic.
You'll hear everything except for what it is.
I believe it's short for culture.
Yeah.
That's why it's that's why it's called a cult.
Sure.
Right.
Cult.
So.
So basically you have everyone is in a cult as you know, as the as it's becoming more
world based now, the culture is evening out.
Right.
Unless the people that are out of touch, you know, are not being affected.
But you have microculture, macroculture than the world culture.
And now they'll point a finger at a group that is outside of that culture as a cult.
You see.
Right.
You know how they always blow, whatever, call others what they're doing themselves.
You know.
So, you know, any government will do a false flag and they'll blame it on someone, even
though they're the ones that orchestrated the whole thing.
It's a typical thing.
So uncultivating means abandoning the culture.
For what?
You know, here's the thing.
A lot of health and status, health and stability of a society was based on their traditions.
And as the generations pass, if you convince the more nation part of the society, the
more naive that these traditions are no good.
You just do something different for the sake of being different.
Now you're destroying stability in the culture.
Oh, wow.
Sounds like the 60s and 70s.
Right.
Well, yes.
Yes.
No.
Because here's the thing.
Right.
To simply be in opposition to the culture is not sufficient enough to affect any sort of
change.
To be.
And that's the other thing.
It becomes a culture in and of itself.
Right.
The the anti-culture, the, you know, the anti-establishment they used to say during those 60s and 70s
times.
Right.
OK.
Great.
Fine.
You're anti-establishment.
Well, what does that mean?
But hold on.
But uncultivating is more this definition would mean to go back to traditions that benefit
social stability.
I'm not I don't mean like in communism, which is never the works.
Anything that Marx and Engel wrote was never been put into practice, by the way.
Right.
Yeah.
But it's not merely traditional.
You see, culture is not merely tradition because culture is about.
Well, actually, it's based on.
No, I disagree.
In a way.
Yes.
But in a way.
No.
Because here's the thing.
Right.
You know, culture is also based on your actions.
What language you speak is not necessarily based on tradition.
It's based on what is functional.
Is that right?
But what I mean by tradition is stuff that promotes well-being overall.
Right.
In other words, here's a very simple way.
And this is what I think about it all the time.
Living in harmony with nature, a very simple thing that I've always brought up is eating
seasonally what's local.
Right.
You're not going to get sick if you do that.
It's impossible to get sick.
If you have good hygiene and I've always got I've always have you uncalled stress, good
hygiene.
Right.
And believe it or not, most people think, you know, good hygiene is so they they you
know, they don't.
Yes.
It's part of it, like part of a complete breakfast.
Right.
But good hygiene.
Keep your underarms and your groin clean.
Keep your hands clean under your fingernails clean and then eat what's local.
And in season, if you have running water and running sewage where the sewage is away from
where you eat, sleep and live, there is no way you'll get sick.
There's no way.
Very rare.
And you will thrive.
You won't have dental problems, skin problems.
Right.
People will, you know, you will thrive.
So that is the simple culture tradition to keep.
And by the way, what I just mentioned was true because people didn't have transcontinental
railways to move things around.
They ate and used what they had.
It's just that people develop from poverty mindset, poor hygiene, and that led to other
things and poor water management.
Another thing that goes along with the hygiene, by the way, is keeping your hair in order.
Believe it or not, your your body hair, your hair on your head or you.
Yeah.
Of course.
And by the way, if if you're if someone I did this recently because I got the circus
look that people don't ask me what the circus flew.
It's a story that I gave a few episodes ago.
Look up Wendy Blades.
That's my sister's daughter.
My niece.
She visited me here.
She lived in a tent with four porta potties and 40 people from Mexico and some from Italy.
And they were breeding some kind of thing.
You just can't help it.
Yes.
Right.
Or they're in a traveling circus.
And I met her.
Give her a big hug and a kiss.
And here I go for three weeks.
I feel like a dog that's ready to be put down.
By the way, if you have something that you can't kick like that's frequency to you call
it bugs.
It's fine.
But if you have like an ailment, whatever it might be that you can't kick, go ahead
and start cutting your nails to the quick shave your head, cut your fur, cut off the
fur, cut the fur off your body, keep your paws clean.
Right.
And you'll heal up much faster.
Yeah.
By the way, that was typical practice in old nursing handbooks when someone would come
in very specific about trimming their fingernails and cutting their hair off, you know, and
cleaning them up because it harbors, like you said, hair and other things can harbor
the frequency of what is making you ill.
So this is the first time I've been this ill in my entire life.
Other than the standard flu stuff that you get when you're a child, you know, right.
Because your body, again, is changing in the frequency, right?
It's all frequency based frequency, not like frequency radio, but the biological vacuum
associations.
It's transitional stress, really, because when when the body is changing, when the environment
is changing, these things put stress.
Right here.
Let me say something I've said before.
This is not a tangent with illness.
The reason you get ill or anyone gets ill from you want to believe in microbes or whatever
when you're affected and you and you induced some kind of illness, you know, if you have
something that really puts you down, makes you really feel what they call sick.
The reason why you feel that way, you're ready for this.
I've never gotten into this before, and I've been pondering this for a long time.
I just haven't found anything definitive to back it up.
So this is like the Greeks opinion is because the illness itself on a frequency level is
trying to change your DNA.
Oh, wow.
Now, if I said this a long time ago, it would sound really esoteric.
But what happened in twenty twenty or twenty twenty two when they were rejecting everyone
with what?
And then RNA injections.
Right.
And when I saw that, I was like, OK, I better start talking about this because that's what
makes you really, really sick is when something goes after the code in your body or it starts
changing it.
Right.
It's attempting to change that.
It's not microbes in your bloodstream.
There's a lot of stuff about that where you could have certain pathogens show up in your
blood, but they show up in your blood.
They didn't come from the outside.
They've done many experiments, especially in war camps where people would have these
horrific diseases.
Certain microbes did show up in their blood and they would inject healthy people with
it and they wouldn't come down with the disease.
So they were wondering it can't be the microbe.
Right.
So but anyway, I just wanted to put that out and I can get into it more because there's
no basis for for this that I found other than thought experiments.
Right.
Why would you feel so ill if it's just something your body can eliminate?
Because that something is trying to change you into something else.
Right.
It's kind of like remember like the old horror thriller movies when the wolf turns into the
wolf man.
It's pretty painful.
Yeah.
Right.
Or when Dr. Jekyll goes to Mr. Hyde, it's pretty painful.
So it's actually a form.
So anyway, it was not a tangent.
We're talking about the culture and changing it.
All you have to do is go and find out how people lived at one point, where you're living
now.
Right.
And you will see that the invaders, whoever came over and changed it, would not have been
able to stick around unless they adopted what the indigenous people were doing to some degree.
And they integrated that.
Right.
So when you look at, for example, those South American and Latin countries, rice and beans
are a popular dish.
Well, in America, it is a popular.
You know, if you go to Mexico, I mean, Texas, New Mexico, Arizona, rice and beans is a popular
dish still here, just like because it was indigenous agriculture.
Right.
And so on and so forth.
So, yeah, going back.
So the uncultivating is very simple.
You know, your body when when you were conceived in the womb, if the moms did not input earth
elements, you would not be here right now.
You would have been starved out of her body.
And while you're born and growing and alive, even her mother's milk, you rely on earth
elements to ingest.
And when you die, guess what happens to your body?
It goes back to what earth elements, doesn't it?
So everything that you have here belongs to the earth.
That's why it's interesting in scripture.
You know, the wealthiest or the poorest die the same.
Right.
I like a line I saw in a film called Fury recently.
It's like when I die, make sure to bury me face down.
It's like, why?
So you go to hell faster?
No.
So the whole world kiss my ass.
Right.
So anyway.
Yeah.
It's one of those things that doesn't really matter.
That's why, you know, we get more into the mental part.
And by the way, let's just end this part right here on the call on the cult.
I just want to bring up a little recap on what we did last week on air, because I have gotten
some feedback that it's an LP.
It's not an LP at all.
And let me just give a little bit of a recap.
a little more support why it's not an LP and some of it might be from something that
may set also.
And I preface before we got into the session that I did, I think I would consider that
a live session that we did on on the episode 84.
Wouldn't you consider it a live session?
Yeah, sure.
Sure.
Yeah.
Walking.
OK.
Anybody that listens to that, even though I was addressing you, Chuck, can go through
it the same way.
Right.
And there's something about it.
You can't really do it to yourself because we have internal survival mechanism mechanisms
that only allow us to go so deep.
But let me just preface why it's not an LP at all at all, is because the premise of this
working and being beneficial is very simply that we only record still images, not neuro
linguistic programming.
Right.
It has absolutely nothing to do with neuro linguistic probing at all.
Zero.
If you've gone the wrong way, basically the needle jumped off the record and the record
fell on the floor and the needles broken.
And if if if anyone thinks it's going that route, that'll be at all.
This has this has to do strictly with even if you let's say let's say it again, that
the mind records everything and still images.
Now, anyone that's been in a projector room and looks at film motion picture, what do
you see when you hold the reel in your hand and you open it?
Still picture, still picture, still picture, still picture, still picture or like a picture
book.
The moment you flip that picture book or start quickly moving that film over a lens, it looks
like it's moving.
Just like when you think of a past event and you think you're actually remembering it like
a movie and you're not, you're actually getting screenshots.
The motion is an illusion.
It is.
That's right.
It is all an illusion.
And even memory of an event in motion.
You're actually viewing fast screenshots with big, big parts missing in between Zapruder
film.
Anyone.
So.
Right.
So it's the same thing.
But it still looks cohesive, but it's not.
So the whole idea, then, is what happens is when the when the body decides that this
is trauma, because, by the way, someone who's into S&M might welcome a certain degree of
trauma and not record it as such memorialize it as someone who is not into S&M.
Right.
You know what I mean?
So force feeding someone Brussels sprouts could be very traumatic where a Brussels sprouts
lover would be.
That was not traumatic at all.
So it's very subjective.
That's why it doesn't matter.
Real simple.
You put a dominatrix in your head with a whip in her hand.
Now, some people might take that as a threatening image and others might take that as something
to get happy about.
Yeah.
By the way, I once dated a psychiatrist.
Right.
And after dinner, she goes, let's go here.
And we went down by the meat district in Manhattan.
It was a black steel door, really dirty place.
Walked in.
It was an S&M club.
I mean, you go in each room, you could see what's going on.
I mean, anything you could imagine, like, you know, the two liter Coke bottles going
in the big end first.
Anyway, crazy stuff.
I don't know how people would survive.
She was into that.
I'm like, my gosh.
And you're a psychiatrist that orders medicine.
I left the cabin.
Never.
She left.
Called me back a few times.
Never called her back because it was just like, this is really.
If she wasn't a psychiatrist, I might have called her back, said, you're a sick bitch.
But because she was a psychiatrist, I didn't know what to.
I mean, like this woman needs to be reported to the authorities.
Right.
But then you find out the authorities are the ones that go there, too.
Anyway.
Yeah.
So, man, I go into that.
But the still images.
So what happens is when you record memorialize one of these still images or a series of stills
that you consider is an event, what happens is it gets buried back there.
But your body deals with it by modifying your ego, modifying your character to just like
you develop pus or blister to protect the body.
The body protects you by modifying your character and creating a little sub ego around that.
So you always have an excuse or reason to deny it or a reason why you always want to
talk about it, wear it like a badge.
Everyone's got a different thing to how to deal with that image is because now you have
this thing that you consider an evader invader in your psyche and your psyche keeps
compensating for it.
So the purpose of this method, it's all emo based, by the way.
If you do catch up with any of the writings or whatever you get on John Mase, he says
it's all emo based, emotionally based.
So basically you're using the emo to get rid of it where that's why we get into
look how big it gets.
Let it keep growing and growing, growing.
Remember, it's all emotional.
And then when it stops, you acknowledge that it stopped getting bigger.
OK, it's static now.
Now let's order it to go the other way into infinitely small till it disappears.
And you're done with it and you are done.
N, D, O, N, E with a capital N done.
It's so simple.
And if it doesn't work once, you do it again.
So this is the whole thing.
It has nothing to do with neurology, has nothing to do with words or linguistics,
has nothing to do with programming, is a simple application of the emotional body
dealing with a stored image or series of images.
Very simple.
And it doesn't have to be trauma either.
I mean, I'll tell you this.
It could be an addiction.
It could be anything.
It could be absolutely anything.
If you come up with a feeling or something that is a general,
you will draw a picture that goes along with it.
Well, actually, this is different again.
No, hold on.
But you'll create a but you're not actually remembering the event
as a form of a still picture.
That's what's in your memory.
You're not actually drawing it.
You're actually drawing from the you're not drawing anything.
What you're doing is you're recording it as a still image.
There's no different than you would take a shot with a camera.
And of course, it would be what you perceive.
Right.
OK, just like a dream.
You know, some people, you know, like in dreams,
if you see if there's a conference next time you have a dream,
the typical things about dreams that they're black and white or whatever.
But the next time you think you're in a conversation,
a dream, try to focus on the mouths.
You'll notice the mouths never move.
And also, you'll never read anything in a dream.
You'll never read a sign.
You'll never read.
There's no reading in dreams because that's linguistic.
Right.
You see.
So these interesting things.
But if you're ever in a dream and there's a conversation
and you see mouths moving and you command yourself to see your hands
and you can move your hands and do something with your hands.
Guess what?
You're not you're not in a dream.
You're an alternate reality because dreams have been looked at
for thousands of years and very well defined.
And it's not shared with the public openly
because the last thing you want them to do
is take control of their dreams
and then find out when they're not in a dream
and take control of that.
My gosh, then you have people with too much control.
How are you going to control them?
I guess I was imprecise with the way I described it.
Here's the thing, though.
Any event, any emotion,
any general category or specific thing,
a book cover arrives for it,
basically in your mind.
You could say that.
Keep the emotions out of it.
The emotions are completely simple,
completely different artifact.
But if you do turn around
and you focus on an emotion,
and I say this all the time,
a particular emotion,
depending on what part of it I'm talking about,
like, you know,
you could use the word love.
OK, so I love certain things.
But hold on, hold on.
I'm going to stop you right here
because it's very critical.
OK, so the image that you store
and the mental story that you give
is not the emotion.
Just very simply,
you can have people that like horror flicks
and other people that throw up if they see it.
Right.
It has nothing to do with the emo at all.
Really, that's the thing I've been trying to do
about the emo work
is that we're never told
what the purpose of emotion is.
It's a faculty.
It's not a perception.
Just a faculty would be like,
you know, using your hands
or using your mouth to speak
or something to create something.
The emo is very simple.
You actually do not store emotions.
You don't.
Emotion is like saying
I'm storing my ability
to write with my right hand.
You're not.
You have the ability
and you use it when you need to.
The images that are stored
are independent on how,
not emotionally,
but how you were affected then
and if it was considered trauma
or not based on your culture,
personal preference and all that.
Your emotion is what you use
to then categorize it as trauma.
It doesn't come together.
It comes after.
That's why very often
you'll see someone experience
something very traumatic
and they seem OK until like
five seconds later
and then they start breaking down
and crying because they have to
attach the emotion to it.
But emotion is a faculty.
That's why I keep getting
into the emo work.
We're never told
what the purpose of emotion
is because it's so powerful
once you learn it.
I find that that faculty
attached to something though
becomes exactly how
that image is retained.
If you're not aware of it.
If you're not aware that they're
distinct and separate.
Yes, absolutely.
It's confusion.
Just like you're not aware
of the soul and the spirit.
One is the physical metabolism.
The other one is the mind.
It's very important.
These fine details are important.
Look, if you're going to do
really good, delicious food,
fine detail.