The Sonic entity known as S.T.E
.A.L. is here to take the lead.
The whole thing with academia is if you
study it, you know, like a lot of
the stuff we talk about, you know, history
of this, you know what this really means,
like the word nice or birthdays, cannibals and
dolls, all that stuff.
When you look at how academia is set
up, it's just, what do you call it,
atrocious, which someone looked up the word recently
for me and it says it's criminal, this,
that.
It's a pretty harsh word when you say
atrocious.
That's where atrocity, I think, comes from.
Atrocity, right.
Exactly.
Yeah, it's horrible.
Yeah, it's nothing like it used to be.
And it's programming, just like what they do
with television, by the way.
If you look at TV programs, right, when
they tell you it's season one, it's 1
-0 and then it's the number, right, for
the season and then the episode.
So when you go to the second season,
they begin with a 2 again.
That's like the same thing they do with
classes.
So it's programming.
Yeah, but you brought up the academia part.
Oh, man, that needs to be just, it's
kind of like the doctors.
When the medical doctors go away, people will
be more fit.
They'll get their fitness back.
Notice I didn't say the H word.
The H word was...
Oh, you disappeared on me, Greek.
Yeah, I'm back.
Whenever the phones, we're using Jitsi, by the
way, folks, and when the phone that's on
the stupid rectangle decides to turn the screen
off, you can't.
So I have to keep my finger on
it, you know, that and other things.
But yeah, we have a couple of things
in the chat, diversified stuff.
Maybe I'll start off with that.
Ed asked, it was mentioned years ago.
I'm just going to paraphrase here about the
Christ being a biblical Christ, which no one
really knows because no one reads the Bible.
Right.
And not being facetious, we will be like
a model human in a way.
Yes.
And then there's judgment and all that.
But those words need to be looked at
closely again, how it's placed.
And there's a lot of biblical talk, by
the way.
This is not answering what he is asking
here, but none of it is accurate.
Very little snippets will be accurate.
But the general overview is not correct because
all we have is biblical and history.
And it seems like you got to pick
or choose because when you pick history, you
don't find much and at all really some.
And when you pick biblical, it sort of
lines up with history.
So you got to know the entire scope,
but you got to know it from a
non urban legend point of view.
It's one of these first hand things you
have to experience.
You experience the second hand information first hand
maybe.
But here he says, basically, do you think
that reincarnation can only be specific to certain
individuals?
No, it's granted to everyone.
Biblically, all men will come back.
Right.
But then there's like different levels.
It seems like if you understand what's being
conveyed in mostly in the New Testament or
even the Old Testament, doesn't get much into
it.
But we're sort of like in a boot
camp right now where we're being monitored and
graded to use not such a specific term.
Let's not be specific with the word.
Remember years ago I said when you grade
someone, that's very degrading, right?
So it's an open subject.
But there's not much of a contrast.
I mean, it's limited information and it's still
an open subject because the information that we
get about what happens later, the next society
is like Swiss cheese.
You know, you got a block of cheese,
but it's got a lot of big holes
in it.
You know, take it back.
Take this cheese back.
It's missing parts.
Right.
Until you find out that's how it's made.
You say, well, no, no, honey, that's how
Swiss cheese is.
Oh, OK.
Yeah.
I never saw cheese with big holes in
it like that.
You're supposed to take it back at one
that doesn't have the holes in it.
Right.
Yeah, no.
That's the way it comes, which is interesting
because it kind of ties together with one
of the questions I have, which is a
Greek said the next thing coming is to
be a cleansing of which you can't compare
to any other times.
Biblically speaking, this era began with the Assyrians
wiping out all of the neighboring tribes.
So if the cycle continues, that's what should
happen at the end.
Severe wiping out of humanity.
But wouldn't that have happened anyways with the
Earth shift and the cataclysms?
Yes.
Both.
Both are true.
Yeah.
But I believe there's a control behind it.
You know, there's a deliberate control, which segues
to the next one.
I think person here, individual, whatever you want
to call, just Brian 44 posted about his
sessions of ayahuasca and basically reduces it to
down there's malevolent and benevolent and somewhere there
to help.
Right.
Guess which ones are those?
Actually, sometimes the malevolent ones can help you
more because the benevolent ones, if you survive,
the benevolent ones are not giving you a
formula to free energy or perfect fitness.
And longevity, are they?
Right.
Anybody say I ran into a benevolent being
and here's the schematic for free energy and
whatever, whatever, whatever.
Cure cancer.
We know some stuff like that.
You can't cure cancer.
Actually, having cancer means that if you didn't
have cancer, you would have died.
Right.
But anyway, yeah, it's kind of tricky.
But the thing is the help or malice,
whether you're dealing with good ones or bad
ones, there's not much of a crossover because
being in a physical state or being animated
because you have a physical body is a
very, very, very tricky thing.
And usually we're left alone, believe it or
not, with all the screwing around that's been
happening to us.
We're left alone because we're really physically based.
You know all the airy fairies always talking
about the spirit and the physical body.
Actually, we're more physical than spiritual when we're
in the physical body because 99% of
your consciousness is, if not more than that,
actually 100% of your consciousness is based
on your physical body working.
In other words, when you're unconscious, unless you
speak to the NDE people, there's no consciousness.
So it's a very, very tricky thing.
They use the reference of snowflakes to people,
the ones that fall apart real fast.
We're kind of like snowflakes, all of us,
to these spiritual beings.
Now, it doesn't mean they can't be around
us.
It just means the indirect interaction and affecting
us directly is really like touching a snowflake
because of the physical body.
Well, and everybody that has these experiences, it's
always, did they ask for the cure to
cancer?
Did they ask for it?
No, they didn't.
They never asked those questions anyway.
That's true.
They can say you didn't ask, right?
That's a very typical meme you see when
you shake the genie out of the bottle,
let's say.
You didn't ask.
Well, right.
I mean, at the end of the day,
you didn't ask for it.
You know, it's like the old, well, the
meme is usually funny.
It's like, I really want to win the
lottery.
I really want to win the lottery.
And finally, you get a note that says,
buy a ticket, idiot.
You know, and so, you know what I'm
saying?
Yeah.
Well, it's like thing is I consider myself
a dream master, be able to navigate.
But recently I had this honest to goodness
nightmare that I was being killed.
And it didn't, I didn't say to myself,
well, this is just a dream.
I'll wake up at all.
I woke up in a terrible panic.
I couldn't go back to sleep.
Kind of like Donald Marshall stuff.
Right.
And I was like, Ooh, that was unusually
realistic.
Right.
But I didn't die.
I was just being killed by some really
odd creatures.
They look like dust mops.
Right.
They were like blue and there were some
individuals and people involved.
And it's kind of thing where you're in
the matrix where you go pull back the
curtains to go out the window and there's
a brick wall.
You open the door and there's a brick
wall kind of thing.
Right.
Very, very interesting.
So at the time I was, I wasn't
even thinking at all while I was experiencing
this, whether I could see my hands move
or mouths move while there was speech or
anything like that.
I kind of like forgot about it.
So what I'm saying is when you're in
the presence of something like this, it's kind
of hard to even remember you had a
list.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
A list of things to ask.
You know, you say, where's that list that
I had for these guys?
But you won't even forget that.
Oh, yeah.
So that's like total chaos, disorganization.
40 years ago, literally 40 years ago, I
had a dream about being wiped out in
a nuclear bombing.
And these creatures that you're describing, very similar
to those kind of like slashing mop sort
of things, they started beating the hell out
of me.
And I woke up thinking, you know, like
it took me a while to talk myself
out of.
That's not what actually just happened to me.
You know.
Not during, but after.
After.
Right.
Yeah.
Because during, I was fully engaged with what
was happening.
I was in a familiar place.
I thought what was going on was going
on.
I thought the bombs were dropping.
Everything was lighting up.
You know, the typical sort of.
Yeah, because we don't have a very strong
connection to keeping the lights on, your consciousness,
in order.
You know, again, just imagine having a list
of questions because you're going to be in
a situation where you could deal with.
You won't even remember that.
So you're very fragile, conscious.
You know, it's.
Yeah.
If I knew I was in the presence
of demons or gods or whatever, I would
have no idea about.
Maybe I should ask him this question.
No, I wouldn't because I was so engrossed
in the experience that there was like.
Yeah.
And even if you prep yourself and meditate
on the next time this happens, you'll probably
still forget.
Yeah.
It's kind of a messed up thing.
But, you know, there's some advantage point.
We only still have the vantage point of
surface to earth inhabitants.
Right.
So I keep talking about vantage point.
Also, someone plugged in YouTube short to Middle
Nation.
Oh, yeah.
That guy does some really good commentary.
Here's the thing.
He knows enough about the monetary system to
discuss that it's not fair, but he doesn't
know how it really works.
At least he seems like he's not using
the proper banking verbiage.
But he's pretty good generally overview.
He doesn't know about what's coming.
He thinks like he'll say by 2070, there
won't be much of Europe left, you know,
as an EU.
No, no, no.
You don't have that kind of time left.
So, yeah, but his commentary is pretty forthright,
meaning he puts forward stuff that if you
repeat it in concept, you'd be pretty close
to being correct on what's going on.
All right.
But by 2070, I don't expect to be
here.
No, no, no.
It's not good.
We're not even going to be in this.
Archaics is pretty close.
The sky won't even be the same.
The atmosphere won't be the same.
Longevity will not be the same.
Most of the people will not be here,
even the ones that could have lived that
long.
There'll still be probably population growth and all
that, but on a different level.
Okay, what else?
You got anything else?
There's always a remnant.
Yeah, well, the last thing, I was going
to ask if you wanted me to play
that clip, actually, from that guy.
It was pretty interesting.
Yeah, go ahead and play it.
Yeah, okay.
You want me to play that?
I'll pull it up right now.
Yeah, the last one.
Yeah, and then I got one more question
after that.
But let's just take a listen to what
that guy pulled up, because it was really,
really dark and direct, what he had to
say, and I think it's worth it, so
let's listen to it.
Sure is.
They have never operated in the world, in
fact, like they're even a part of the
human family, let's be frank.
They have operated in this world like some
sort of alien predator that has just come
down to drain the sweat, blood, and tears
of the human race and to ransack the
planet's resources.
That's how they've acted.
Like they have somewhere else to go where
it's all been depleted.
I mean, we have to be honest about
this.
We have to confront the fact that the
West has operated with absolute malice, with absolute
contempt for the whole world, not today, not
yesterday, but literally for centuries.
And there is no remorse.
There is no repentance.
There is no rehabilitation.
Literally the only thing that has changed now,
today, is that now their malice and their
contempt has made them turn on their own
nations.
They haven't reformed.
They're just repositioning.
This is the only difference.
There's no change in their character.
The A-National OCGFC are not our friends
just because they're no longer constrained by nationalism.
They're just as predatory and just as vicious
as they ever were.
See, now, the OGFC, what is that?
Yeah, it's an acronym that he came up
with, just like we have PWS for Pope's
Work Schedule.
That's his own personal thing.
I looked it up once.
It's the Overall Control, Global Control Group.
I think it stands for something like that.
Overall Global Control Group.
So his version of Illuminati, basically.
Yeah, well, not his version, but he's just
describing it.
Yeah, pretty much.
The Illuminati are supposedly just a section of
a class of people.
He's speaking of someone that you've never heard
of.
We've heard of enough of the Illuminati, at
least the founder and all that of the
group, but you'll really never know.
And they're not even really called the Illuminati.
They have a secret name.
It's someone's name they use, right?
Right.
So just like, you know, if I say,
we got any Mary Jane, right?
Kind of thing like that.
So yeah, I think he's talking about the
power structure.
I've spoken of them that way.
I know they're not human, and they're not
on the surface.
They obviously have agents and proxies on the
surface.
Right.
But it's not so.
What else you got?
Okay, so last thing I got is, this
is about the financial thing.
Also, if there is a new financial system
coming out, and if this is the seventh
cycle, do you think new lawful money is
being introduced to replace the old lawful money?
That's part one of the question.
No, I think so.
You're not going to get anything lawful unless
you do injunctions.
And also, if you study most laws, you
can turn anything into lawful money by putting
a restrictive endorsement.
Not gold and silver coin, which is real
money, but it will put you in the
category as if you were using lawful money.
One day when I brought up the term
injunction, that's the private remedy to what's going
on in the public.
For example, this ties in with an injunction
for driving is when the cops pull you
over and you don't have a driver's license,
he goes to you, looks up your name,
and on the screen it says, do not
arrest, do not detain, release immediately.
He's like, oh, you're one of those.
Right.
You can do that for taxes.
You can do it for anything.
And it's a private remedy.
It's basically a private lawsuit, and they always
accept it.
I've never heard of anyone had it rebutted
or whatever.
But because in public, you always have to
lose.
In private is where you really win.
And when there's a public win, there's still
a loser because in order for you to
win, someone loses.
So in private, you have win-win.
In public, you have winner-loser.
In private, you have good guy, good guy,
bad guy, bad guy.
But in public, it always has to be
good guy, bad guy.
Right.
You have to have that duality in public.
So like in public, magnets are North Pole,
South Pole.
In private, there's the block wall.
There always has to be someone is in
the right, someone is in the wrong.
A good guy, up and down.
Yeah, no, never in the middle, never.
So these things that a lot of these
law gurus that are talking about, it's all
bullshit, unless they delineate public and private, which
some of them do, but they don't know
how to operate in it.
Private is what you make it, right?
So that's why a lot of times with
the homosexuals, most of the commentary was what?
I don't care about what you do in
private.
In private, behind closed doors, all that.
But once you make it public, that's how
you divide everyone because, oh, part of the
public says, oh, those are the good guys.
And the other part of the public says,
oh, those are the bad guys.
Yeah.
Like it or dislike, right?
But the general consensus is it's private.
Whether it's good or bad, it doesn't matter.
It's private.
Private doesn't matter so long as people are
there of their own free will.
Yeah, but the maxims of law are still
withheld in private, the maxim of law.
So if you don't answer, if you acquiesce
to something, you lost the upper hand.
So we'll get into injunctions one of these
days a little bit just to see.
There's plenty of stuff online.
I don't know if I would use anything
there because you have to know how to
do a proper affidavit.
But sure as hell, I'm doing injunctions.
I mean, I already have one for travel,
which I've used successfully.
But it's.
Oh, he went away again.
Yeah.
The screen just cut off.
So, yeah.
So that was what was the second part
of the question?
Oh, the second part of the question has
come up with a lot of people, though.
And they've all asked the same thing, basically,
which is the current financial system in the
process of being destroyed.
Is that going on?
And is it being replaced with something else?
Which is what he says here.
Just another way to clean up the lawful
money by giving people something.
No, no, it's not being you can't destroy
something that's based purely on credit.
So it's already destroyed.
Right.
It's already it's kind of like imagine a
ship sinks and everyone's got these life preservers.
And someone comes up and says, do you
think we're going to get any life preservers?
You're going to say, dude, we're in life
preservers.
What are you talking about?
Right.
Now, what's going on is just like you've
heard, police have a license to kill.
Lawyers have a license to steal.
Right.
Yeah.
So they're just changing the way they're stealing
from you.
It's a little more obvious.
Kind of like when someone's cheating on you,
they hide it.
But then when you don't care, it's not
so they don't have to be so hiding.
They're just not hiding.
They're not doing anything that they haven't done
in the past 90 years anymore or any
less.
They're just making it the actions are more
public, I should say.
Like, for example, if you use a short
example, I remember about four or five years
ago, the FBI went in and took safety
deposit boxes out of California.
Yeah.
Right.
Well, that's because when you got the they
didn't do everyone, only the ones that were
standard agreement.
Whoever modified the agreement, because when you didn't
get a safety deposit, you didn't get their
box raided and stolen.
When you get a safety deposit box or
any agreement with the bank, it says that
you're basically transferring all of your security interest,
meaning any value that you have to them.
All of it, not some of it.
It's not it's unconditional.
So you need to change that.
Yeah, we'll get we'll get into that.
We talked a lot about that in the
financial class.
When Tomiko was around, she's she's very heavily
on modifying and rescinding aspects of a contract
and all that.
So all they're going to do is use
more of the what they've been doing and
just letting you know.
So in other words, when they say, oh,
people are losing their homes, the same amount
of people are losing their homes whenever it's
just it's more popular in the news.
Yeah.
There might be a slight change, like a
deviation, maybe five percent more or whatever.
But it's not like suddenly everyone's getting a
home foreclosed.
There's nothing like that's going to happen because
you're you're living on credit as it is.
Well, in 2008, there was a big shift,
though, because they turned around and they dropped
a whole bunch of, you know, supposed guarantees
were all gone.
So that's.
Yeah, well, that's all one sided, though.
It's all one sided.
You see, those guarantees are whenever there has
guarantees, they were just conditions that could be
modified.
But because no one reads, it doesn't matter.
Right.
For example, do you know that if you
have enough time, let's say you paid off
a car loan, you can go back and
say, you know, that's fraud and factum fraud
and factum.
That's fraud.
And in fact, I am.
F.A.C.T.U.M. Yeah.
Which basically means that they didn't have the
thing to lend you the money.
Yeah.
They asked you to do something because it
was this.
And it turns out what what this was
is not it at all.
Right.
You can go back with several ways.
The main way is with an affidavit and
recoup everything, everything you've paid them, plus the
original.
So then you can go for damages three
times the amount.
So it's a ten thousand dollar car.
You should get the car and thirty thousand
dollars.
Right.
Actually, forty thousand.
The ten thousand plus that, whatever.
But it takes a long time and there's
no court that'll that'll take that as a
legitimate case.
In other words, they don't want that in
the public.
So they're going to settle with you or
drag it on for a long time.
Right.
We notice something is being dragged.
There are ways to speed it up also,
but that will be more later on the
road or more private, let's say, discussion.
But I was going to ask you something
about the safety deposit boxes just real fast,
because it has something to do with something
legitimate that I've been trying to track down
for a few years.
You know, there was a case where something
of historical value was put into a safety
deposit box by somebody who was the alleged
head of a company.
Right.
And then that person died.
So nobody in the world seemed to know
where this person put it in the safety
deposit box, but that it was placed in
the safety deposit box and nobody could find
it again.
Now, that doesn't mean this thing doesn't exist
anymore.
But who can even access that now?
Well, it's a lost property, but it's it's
still if it's in a safety, we're presuming
it's still the safety deposit box, then you
have to find the bank who has the
safety deposit box.
Right.
OK.
Now, it's actually it's not that difficult to
do, by the way, because they're all listed.
And this person, you know, a good investigator
should be able to hunt that down in
a week.
Yeah.
Well, if somebody tried for about 10 years
and couldn't find it because what happened is
it was a good investigator.
Yeah.
But I've seen it done by people that
I thought were good investigators and they couldn't
find it.
But anyway, exactly.
So you don't have to be smart.
You just have to look smart or sound
smart.
Yeah.
Well, yeah.
There you go.
I get it.
It's not a put down, but I'm just
saying, you know.
I hear you.
Look, you don't know until you get the
results most times.
You know what I mean?
Quite frankly, you can try and judge character
all you want, but sometimes you get surprised.
No, I agree.
It's all perform.
I'm performing like my old mentor, Trevor James
Constable said, it's all the results count.
Well, right.
So I don't care what your title is.
I don't care what your history is.
You know, how about what results you're going
to get me?
And if you get the right results, that's
what counts.
Yeah.
Well, you might care a little bit, but
it doesn't factor in if you're not performing.
There you go.
No performance.
No.
Doesn't matter.
Yeah.
So.
Okay.
Well, anyway, did you have any other stuff
from chat or anything else you want to
go over?
Because I'm out of questions over here.
No, so am I.
I think we'll keep this one short and
we'll compensate for a longer one on the
next one.
Fair enough.
Anyway, we'll keep we'll keep playing with Jitsi
and see how that goes.
Yeah.
I'll figure out how to keep the keep
it going when the screen blacks out.
By the way, if anyone hears this, if
you have a slab or a stupid rectangle
and you're on a Jitsi call, when the
screen goes black, how do you keep the
call going?
Just put it in the chatango.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Please do that.
Or, you know, send it to me on
on if you send it on the Patreon,
I'll pick it up and I'll bring it
to the Greek as well.
Either way, let us know if you know
how to do that, because I'm not using
a stupid rectangle.
I'm using a big old bulky computer.
So.
All right.
Thank you.