And why, cuz, uh, whatever, we're not doing the Mickey Mouse Club thing.
Greek...
It is worse than the Mickey Mouse Club out there, but...
You know, the Mickey Mouse Club wasn't so bad.
Nickelodeon seems to be scarier when it comes to grooming and being more pedophile friendly.
Well, at least they're putting pornography books and all that, and doing, you know, sex
changes at four years old and all that.
They're telling you what they're really about, finally.
You know, I've been looking at stuff from the 40s and 50s, music from the 30s, and they
were pretty sick people back then.
Yeah, there's a song called Butcher Pete.
Listen to that.
You know, I mean, really crazy stuff that would be up to par with what's going on right
now.
So it's just an exposé.
That's what the word apocalypse means, to expose.
Yeah, you listen carefully, actually, to music from the 30s and the 40s, and the lyrics
and stuff.
You'll hear cannibalism, you'll hear, you know, I'm going to bang a 12-year-old girl,
you'll hear, you know, you're too young, you'll hear, you know, I mean, crazy stuff.
All throughout that, you know, really clean music, Greek, right?
No.
I mean, really weird.
And I'm not just talking like blues musicians, because, you know, the whole, oh, the blues
musicians sold their souls to the devil, or...
I always wondered what you thought about that kind of stuff, like the Robert Johnson story.
It's just a saying.
I mean, you can sell your soul to the devil by just joining the underworld, literally
the black market, you know.
And if you're really knowledgeable in chemistry, there's a lot of stuff that goes around in
the black market that gets stepped on.
Stepped on means when it gets passed from one dealer to the next, they dilute it, right?
So they increase the product.
That's the way I always understood the term.
I was involved in that as a kid, and what it meant to me is you take it and you whack it
up.
You mix it up with something else so that you can split it out and make it bigger.
You know, we used to call it bulking, too, where you bulk it up.
So if you have a pretty good knowledge of, let's say, food and chemistry, chemicals and
substances, and you're working on the surface world, you can go join the underworld.
They will welcome you as putting out stuff that was, you know, the best quality stuff,
right?
Well, I got to be useful as a young kid mixing things together, because I knew what could
be mixed and what could be properly ground and things like that.
I mean, just knowing how to grind things was a useful skill.
Yeah.
The people in the Latin community called porqueria, it's the white powder, and there's various
of them, and they're really ignorant in terms of, you know, they want to step on stuff and
increase it.
And I'm telling them, like, why don't you study the food industry?
There's like dozens of things that are not harmful, right, that you can add to it that
will actually enhance it, complement it, especially if you know yin and yang, right?
Well, a lot of neutral stuff.
But I mean, we got the easy chemical things.
That's why I tell people all the time, this old fentanyl is a brand new.
That's not new.
We had that in 81.
I think it was worked on in World War II by the Germans, and then they evolved it and
recently again.
I wasn't alive then, but I know we had it in Jersey in like 80, 1980, easily, you know,
it's not new.
So anyway.
Yeah, so these synthesized things, that's what World War I was about, stop the Germans
from synthesizing everything natural.
They had a pretty good key on synthesizing everything, because remember, around the turn
of the century, everything was paper-based, and you needed good quality ink, and the
India ink was the best quality ink, and it was a hold on the market by the British.
So the Germans started synthesizing even better quality ink, and then they started synthesizing
petroleum from plant, and all the drugs that are still most commonly used today.
India ink, as a matter of fact, if you see a tattoo that somebody's had for 30, 40 years,
and it's not stretched out, or it's not green, guess what, if it's still black after 30 years,
that's probably India ink.
Just saying.
Yeah, the synthetic, so anyway, it goes on and on and on, but you wanted to talk about
protesting, supposedly, someone lit himself on fire at another trial, you said, right?
The Trump trial, which is just, Trump, he's Trump, the Trump trial, yeah.
The Trump change, if you will, right?
Okay, so just a recap for the listeners.
So what was his reason for lighting himself on fire, he doesn't like Trump?
I would love to figure it out, you know, he wrote a manifesto, all right, let me just
lay it all out.
Just a short of that, don't lay it all out, please, please, that's like torture.
If it's in the mainstream, just give me the super abridged, the abridged version.
How about 20 seconds, I'll give you the whole story.
Yes, that's fine, 20, 19 seconds.
19 seconds, done, here we go, start.
So this guy decided to write a manifesto explaining that he was gonna light himself on fire outside
of the trial, which is being held in Manhattan for Donald Trump and fraud, a case of fraud
against him.
Anyway, the guy lit himself on fire, did it, but he wrote a substack beforehand explaining
it, and in his explanation, quite frankly, I can't decipher exactly why he decided to
do it outside of the fact that he wanted attention, and he says, you know, the system is rigged
and everything is rigged and that's the way it is, and I want attention.
So he lit himself on fire, and the end of the story is this, about a day ago from when we're
talking now, he died, and about a day before that is when he lit himself on fire.
So he lit himself on fire, he even apologized to the first responders, sorry, that's it,
there you go.
Yeah, okay, so he said the system's rigged.
So, I don't know, it's very realistic, but protest doesn't work, and I'll get into why.
Usually the protest is what they want you to do, you know, again, because it satisfies
an impulse, it's impulsive, right, other than the people planning the protests, those who
join it do it by impulse, and it's based on ignorance.
Anything that's going to change anything else, other than extreme violence, a power move,
right, like a coup, a military coup, is a lack of participation, there used to be strikes
years ago for that, you know, like boycotts.
The reason why protests don't work, and withdrawal does, is when someone is going to withdraw
from doing something as a boycott, they are usually much more schooled and educated in
the subject matter.
Like, for example, when you do the protest, the money system, the best way to do it is
to withdraw from it.
In other words, just for three days, don't use it.
That's enough because of their speed trading to really cripple the speed trading aspect
of it.
And the protests don't work for the simple reason is, in order to do an effective boycott
on the money system, you have to understand the bankruptcy, you have to understand the
codes, you have to understand the inner workings of how the system currently works, and that's
not going to happen with just a protest.
In other words, if you have a protest with anything, especially the money system, walking
down the street, and you're going to grab more protesters, they're so stupid, they're
so ignorant, they need at least three months of research to figure out why they're protesting.
So it doesn't work.
Well, does it help as an introduction, though, to some of the ideas that maybe people need?
No, it's the wrong direction.
So you don't think that even introducing somebody to the real ideas, if you held a public demonstration
to get people's attention, that would not be the way to go?
No, no.
Okay.
You hold a demonstration that they need to against ignorance.
That's what the demonstration should be about.
Absolutely.
Against ignorance.
And then start, and then you break it down in various, it's funny, I was at an academics
house, a doctor last week, and I told him, you know, basically, the way the world works
is you have the business world, which is a smart system with dumb people.
And then you have the academic system, which is usually intelligent people in a dumb system.
So let's go back to the business world.
It's a smart system with dumb people.
But if you're in that system long enough, you'll be smart.
Now the academic system is a dumb system with intelligent people.
But if you're in there long enough, you're going to be dumb also.
So typically, it depends on the duration.
And that's the same thing with protests.
The duration of how long you've been involved in a system, the system will eat you up.
So we all know that the majority of protests have been proven to be planned by, you know,
planned opposition.
Right.
Okay.
So what will happen is if you keep protesting or get involved in that, you will become part
of the system that does the planned opposition.
This is very well known.
If you go look, for example, on a mild perspective, oh, there was more than one group, this whatever
underground and the Black Panthers and so on and so forth, right.
And over a period of about 10 years, they exposed that, you know, the leaders were all
FBI informants.
Right.
One by one.
They didn't say all the leader.
But if you followed what they put out in the public, this leader of this movement was
an FBI.
Then this leader and this guy, and then you piece it all together, or 10 years, they pretty
much exposed like the top 20 people as being working for the feds.
Right.
And in the meantime, what that accomplishes, though, is to put everybody at everybody else's
throat so that there can be no cooperation and no collaboration to get anything done.
Because it goes back to the analogy I gave about business world being a smart system
with dumb people, academia being a dumb system with smart people, let's say.
If you stay in one of those systems, you will be the overarching element of that system
will take over.
Like, for example, when you're new in business, you're not that good.
Right.
How many times you hear people?
Oh, yeah.
I got into selling insurance and I didn't do my first sale until two years after being
in that.
Right.
And now they've been working in it for 40 years and they're kind of smart, you know,
about it.
Right.
If you look at academics, when they get in, they try to do things by the book.
You know, they actually.
Oh, how would you say have reverence and venerate the base of knowledge?
But as they stay longer and becomes peer review.
Oh, don't say that.
You can't say that.
No, you can't say that.
That's what you hear from them.
You can't say that.
Right.
So they become dumb if they stay in it long.
And if you don't believe it, if you have any family members or friends that are professors
with tenure that are over 60 or in their 50s, they're dumb.
They're not smart people.
The system has turned them into that.
But if you look at how they were when they first started, they would you would say they
were seeking knowledge and all that.
Now, the same thing with business.
Again, it's a very smart system with dumb people.
But if you're a businessman for many, many years, you end up being a pretty smart person
because you study protesting.
Protesting is controlled opposition.
And no matter how good you you want to, let's say, participate and change, you stay in that
system.
And and let's say there's people that are career protesters, right?
They protested as teenagers.
Some of the old people that you see out at protests have been if you interview them like,
oh, yeah, I protested against this in 1979.
Right.
Yeah.
Now they become part of the controlled opposition.
You see, they become.
If you any system.
So the thing is, diagnose the system.
What is it based on?
Right.
So, for example, look at the food and nutrition system right now.
They're making fun of the food pyramid, the actual establishment is right and stuff they
put out on their own.
It's like the food system is based on chemical compounds and not how they relate to the body,
but how they relate in the laboratory.
Right.
The medical system is based on cadaver study.
Yeah.
So you see.
So anyone involved in these systems will ultimately.
So if you were, let's say, a doctor for a long enough time, you will have a long number
of cadavers behind you.
What wouldn't you?
A lot of you've killed a lot of people to guarantee knowingly, knowingly after a certain time.
For example, I had a client who worked in a hospital and it was a doctor who became an
admin and we needed room in the garage.
It was a three car garage and he had these banker boxes and they were floor to ceiling
about 10 deep.
I know it took up an entire one and a half parking spots.
It was like you think he was moving.
All of that was his own personal lawsuits over a period of 30 years.
A million pages.
It was at least a million pages of lawsuits there.
These are all malpractice lawsuits?
Yep.
Wow.
On him.
Yeah.
Him and his group and whatever he works with.
So there's actually, I'd say it's about halfway down the middle.
In other words, about 50% of whatever, whoever a doctor does is malpractice.
So if he has 100 patients, 50 of them got malpracticed on and out of those 50, maybe five or two
will sue.
We do arbitration.
And what you're saying is when they're new to the field, it's out of ignorance, but after
a while.
Yeah.
After a while.
In other words, they might do better after a while.
Yeah.
It's like anyone that tries to prove anything in the medical industry, they get stepped
on and they tell them, no, you're supposed to do it the standard way, not the better
way.
Right.
In this case, they either get the pay off or the kiss off because they're either gotten
rid of or paid off.
Right.
I mean, yeah.
And if you go study medical patents, they're all really frivolous.
It's like the one I just recently saw was just like the labeling on some medical, he patented
a thing or someone where it was slightly holographic, easier to read with a warning
label.
OK.
I mean, ridiculous stuff.
They still haven't even.
I mean, yeah, it's just totally ridiculous.
So you're going to end up defining a system, in other words, how the system works in this
reality, this world.
And then anyone involved in that eventually will evolve to being what the how that system
is defined is what I'm saying.
So if people in university will end up being stupid or dumb, if you spend enough time in
it, because it's a dumb system.
People in business who end up being smart, if you end up spending enough time in it,
because it has to be sort of like an oven.
I mean, once you're once you're in there cooked under those conditions, I mean, that's
right. You're going to take on, you know, eventually you're going to dry out the dry
oven. I mean, it's just that simple.
Yeah. I was trying to explain the money system to someone who's pretty high up in the
business world. They didn't know about it.
Honest. I was like, come on, you can tell me if you've been told not to talk about it.
And they weren't so basically told them, OK, you understand that the money supply is
expanded through lending.
And they're like, I know what that I know what those words mean, but I don't understand
how. Right.
In other words, the banks have no way you set up a bank is you get an office with a
phone and you tell people you give loans and you have a ledger.
And what you get from the Federal Reserve is a list of transaction numbers that's in
your inventory transaction numbers.
And then someone wants a loan, you know, you run them through a dog and pony show.
You got demographic and all they're going to be doing psychographics pretty soon, by
the way. That's what social credit system is.
It's psychographics. Right.
And behavioral graphics.
But anyway, when someone wants a loan, basically you write down the amount and
next to a transaction number and whatever that amount is, the Federal Reserve OKs it.
It's called the window goes through the window.
And in the back, the back of the store of the Federal Reserve, whatever that amount
is, gets multiple. It's ten to one gets multiplied times nine.
They give the person who supposedly got that loan from their signature, drawn from
their signature, that amount, whatever is left over the 80 percent, let's say, a split
between various groups or whatever.
So and then you go on to how things are collateralized and it was very difficult for
me to understand, even though it was rather intelligent, because it's so new, no
matter how simple you make the information.
Now, by the way, when money is expanded by lending.
So when someone gets a loan, that money didn't exist prior to that loan.
That means that the money to pay it back does not exist.
That has to be created somehow again by another loan.
Right. So that's why the system gets inflation very fast.
And it's a terrible, terrible it's there's no moral or morality ethics, by the way.
That's why the American law.
Actually, most countries have laws.
12 USC for 11 tells you about Federal Reserve notes are to be issued by Federal
Reserve banks and through Federal Reserve agents and no other use is authorized.
So you're not authorized to use something when you found using it.
It's contraband. You have to pay a fee, an excise tax.
Right. So that's that's normal.
It's just like if you rent a tool from a shop, you bring it back and you wave
goodbye. No, they're expecting a fee.
So if you're using. So, in other words, the public money is owned by private hands.
And this is very normal, by the way.
If you were in the military and you're abroad, what do they call it?
The mess, you know, at the at the base where they they serve food
mess. It could be a mess hall.
It could be a cafeteria. It could be.
Yeah. You'll see a pizza hut in there.
Yeah. And various other fast foods.
That is not a government entity.
It's a private entity.
Right. So so what I mean by this is the same thing.
You have a private entity that is demanding based on its privateering
system. OK, so medical system works the same way.
It's all you know, it's it's for privateering.
You know, it's a private system, no matter how much they say it's government.
By the way, when they say fraud, fraud is one of anyone,
any seasoned attorney or lawyer or anyone that well versed in the law
will tell you fraud cases very rarely pan out.
It's very difficult to prove.
So when someone is charged with fraud, if you go study the case,
if they, let's say, are found guilty or have to write,
you'll see if you read the document, the conviction is not fraud.
It's actually false information
to a government agent or false information
to an official or false record keeping, not fraud.
It's like when all the other charges fall away
and a lot of criminal whatever is the last charge to fall
is usually lying to the FBI. Right.
I mean, it's that's right.
False information.
Stewart did not do insider trading at all because it's all insider trading.
If you go look at her case, it was she was when she was interviewed.
She lied by the FBI.
She lied to this.
So she got time for false information to a government agent.
And that could also be hard because they're not government agents,
which is another.
Yeah, yeah.
So the thing is, if you see that coming, it's like you're not.
How are you a government agent?
You're a subcontractor.
Right. Right.
They're all contractors. Yeah.
That's why if you work in an agency, anyone, please get in touch with me.
If you do, you have like a sheet.
If you work at the FBI and you're going to go investigate,
let's say, a medical thing, some medical place, federal investigation. Right.
Your in-house paperwork.
When you start the paperwork, the play,
who let's say the DOJ orders you to do that. Right.
Or the FDA orders you to do that.
You put the field for filling out his client.
So when you work at the FBI, you're going to do an investigation for the FDA.
The FDA is a client of yours.
Yeah, you're all subcontractors, which makes no sense,
because if you were part of the same government,
then you'd be acting on behalf of the same thing with the.
Yeah, same thing with the IRS has it as taxpayer.
Right. I don't even know what that is.
So but it's all subcontractor, all of it.
As a matter of fact, this the police are also subcontractors of the city manager.
So when you run into anyone's in the police,
roll down your window, whatever it's a how's the city manager doing?
You should know the city manager's name because that's who they work for.
Right. And they're also subcontractors.
This couple of cases were lost by the police on this.
And the attorney general in Virginia and another state
put out a public announcement to police to take if they have anything in their name
to take it out like cars, homes or whatever bank accounts,
because they can be held liable because of this last case that went through
that they're all subcontractors.
They don't work for the government.
No one works for the government because the government's bankrupt.
How can you work for an entity that's bankrupt in law?
There's no legal standing even.
Well, if they can't pay you, then you can't be,
you know, what do they call it?
You don't get compensation for your work.
So therefore, because they don't have money to pay you with.
That's right. Well, then they'll.
So there's the corporate structure and all that is the way that it is.
So we don't have a government.
It's just people saying that they're part of the government.
That's that's the crazy part about it, you know.
And it's a it's a big it's it's a serious inaccuracy.
It's so inaccurate.
It's actually a big fat lie.
And meanwhile, they charge other people with,
you know, falsely claiming to be an agent of the government or whatever.
Right. But they go, OK, any attorney general that you know that I got,
let's say there's a case, someone, you know, or heard of that got railroaded
and was all bullshit.
They railroaded them, false accusations and all that.
You go talk to the attorney general in person, say, hey, this is all false.
Yeah, but he agreed to everything or she agreed to everything.
And the Constitution upholds that, by the way.
It doesn't. It says if you're convicted of a crime,
it doesn't say lawfully convicted or properly convicted, just convicted.
Right. That's why that scumbag, Judge Salia, whatever the guy, they choked.
The earth is a better place without him.
What does the Scalia that Scalia?
Yeah, Scalia, that scumbag. Yeah.
Scalia, the scumbag.
He did a case where someone said that they were in prison falsely.
And he he stayed with the Constitution.
He says the Constitution just says convicted.
So that means if you're falsely convicted, the Constitution still holds.
You can. The Constitution basically does not make an allowment
for a lawful conviction.
And he appealed. I didn't have to.
They could have all did a summary that if it's in the Constitution,
it should be a lawful conviction and kept that as their opinion,
that it means lawful.
But he says, no, it doesn't say lawful.
So it's it's OK to be falsely convicted.
And he turned it right.
So this is the world that you live in now.
OK, just in the past 15 minutes, stuff that name one protest
or anywhere that knows anything that I just mentioned or would be,
let's say, adherent to that.
None. Think about how the protesting mind works.
Right. Yeah, I think.
All right. Burn the whole thing down.
Don't white protest. Right.
Burn the whole thing down and start all over the whole thing.
Not one side.
You see, that's where you're at.
So, in other words, protesting is I don't understand.
Well, that's always been my argument about, you know, people that say
we should run it like a business.
And I say, well, you know, when somebody comes in and takes over a business
and says, all right, this place is not running right and we need to change it.
They don't turn around and make new rules and change a little thing.
You get rid of everybody to start with.
Everybody's fired. Right.
And then you go, look, because everybody's doing everything wrong.
Get them all out of here.
Bring in new people and start to do this again.
The right way is the same place.
The breed and the crop. That's you can't.
You can't do it with the stock that's here.
The stock is too diluted.
Yeah, but what I'm saying makes sense, though, right?
I mean, isn't that what you should do?
Yeah, but it doesn't work that way.
We are so close to.
We're so close to the whole thing is being burned down,
which it's a good thing, by the way.
I mean, literally burned down.
It will happen with forces that are much higher than we can contend with.
So what I'm trying to say,
you ever notice how when we do these sonics,
I constantly try to put little improvements, like put soap in a spray
bottle with water.
It's much better than pouring out, pouring soap down the drain, right?
Yes, of course. Or, you know, I've gotten so many.
Well, you try to make little things make your life better here
because the shithole and
because of the society is a shithole, every society.
And they have certain perks, you know, like if you live in Japan,
you'll notice a much higher quality of life
once you get used to the things that are traditional.
Other places, it's lower, you know, whatever.
Also, I've been getting a lot of messages,
a lot is like four or five messages in the past since I've brought up
the recipe for the cabbage pot roast, right?
Or pot roast cabbage.
It has nothing to do with any cabbage that you've ever had before.
Once you prepare it, what when people.
Message me, I message back, did you
use the recipe or the directions that I gave in the sonic?
Because this is not cabbage the way grandma cooks or the way you cook
or where your mom cooks or the way you ate out.
This is completely different animal. Absolutely.
No pun intended.
If you do that and they're like, yes, that's why I'm messaging you,
because I never had cabbage.
I'm not a fan of cabbage.
I did that because, you know, they've heard me say things
that turn their ideas around and they tried it
and it was most delicious thing they've ever eaten.
So things like that, I need to keep bringing up because.
And the rice, the features and benefits.
Yeah, the features and benefits are being here are very simple.
It's in all the old texts.
Also, we have good conversation, good food, good drink, good company.
You know, you're going to have to slave away and go to work. Right.
Stuff you don't like.
And you're going to have people say and do things that you don't like.
So food and drink and some time, casual time
that's of quality is really is really what it's about.
So what I just said about that, how does that factor into protesting?
I think everyone should just when they're ready for protests,
just go have a party. Forget about the protest.
That's not going to change anything.
Wouldn't you rather have a party or a rave or whatever, or a dance or,
you know, a concert to do that instead?
It's a waste of time. Enjoy what you can.
While you can is what it sounds like to me.
You know? Yep.
So, I mean, that's that's the way to go with that.
But so ultimately.
Well, no, it's not. It's not the way you know.
There is there's many ways. There's many ways.
But I've settled on that because it's the simplest thing to communicate.
There's many ways to do it.
OK, give another example.
Another way to do is bury yourself in your work.
And when I say your work, it's like if you really like what you do
and it brings you joy.
You've never worked a day in your life.
Right. If you're there, 12, 13 hours a day, every day.
That sounds like a 1970s grandpa thing right there.
You know, you've never worked a day in your life.
If you really enjoy what you do, if it brings you joy and excitement.
Make an example.
When I build scalerators, it's like
I'm in total bliss.
So you enjoy doing that?
Oh, I'm in total bliss doing it.
Yeah, because I know what it does.
And so far, I'm the only one who can make them that way.
Right. And I did the seminar and all that.
And a couple of people rose to the occasion.
But still, I mean, everyone's trying.
But no one can come near to the precision and the function
that the way that I'm doing it.
So it's one of these things that it's a I'm speaking to a guy, Harry,
who wants to promote it.
He's become a good friend.
And he I'm trying to explain to him it's not promoting the scalerator.
It's promoting me as an artist.
It's my craft.
It's what what I do.
Right. It's not it's not the product because, you know,
and I've had someone, Jonathan Butts, who has an engineering back
where he passed away from natural action technologies.
There's a couple of videos.
He got interviewed by a few people.
He looked at it and he had his engineer, a retired engineer.
He looked at it says, whoever built this is really meticulous attention to detail.
And he looked at his engineer and he says, well, he gave us the OK to build these.
Um, what do you think?
And he says it's going to take about 200 hours of engineering
just to figure out how to make it right now, 200 hours of engineering.
OK, if you have a 40 hour work week, that sums up to about a month and a half.
Right. Yeah. OK.
So five, five weeks for an engineer to figure out something.
I just came up with just by, you know, into intuitively.
So, you know, to copy it and improve, improve it, let's say.
So this is the level
of of work that I when I say work.
Right. It's it's fun.
It's enjoyment. And it also, you know, does things.
And by the way, the scalarator is a dumbed down, minimalistic device.
There's other stuff that will be put together.
But it's very elaborate.
It will give people a headache.
I know so far I really like the people that have come forward.
But I know so far, if we do the Turbidurator, no one will be able to do that.
There's there's no sense in even putting it out
unless you you're you've got some serious
gone us, which is spent.
As for desire, you need to make it.
And yeah, right.
But that will I will be doing this.
You're breaking it.
You're breaking up a little bit, Greek.
I don't know why you started breaking up.
Oh, it shouldn't be. Yeah.
You started breaking up.
Turbidurator is what is a Turbidurator, by the way?
It's a it's a three function unit.
It's like the scalarator.
And you run dirty water through it.
It comes out clean. Turbid water would be like coffee or tea.
Oh, OK. OK.
And then it comes out clear and it comes out just as good as clear.
But you get through the scalarator now, basically.
No, the scalarator is just for descaling and enhancing water quality.
But clean water, like coffee on one side, clean water comes out the other.
Clean water. Yeah, that's right.
Yeah. Well, that's right.
And yeah, I'm not bothering with the seminars or whatever on that
because it's just too it's too much, too much for the people that I've seen
try to make whatever they're going to make.
Then there's no way there's no way it's an entire that's something
you go to Halliburton and you go to a big engineering firm
that has very well, very well endowed.
You know, unless you've got a machine shop
and a whole bunch of other stuff, you're not going to be able to make it.
So, oh, by the way, I challenge anybody to explain to me
why that guy lit himself on fire, really.
Outside of he wanted to know.
Well, here's there's no challenge there because it's on TV.
Remember we talked about there's real terrorism, but you never see it on TV.
Oh, yeah. But here's the funny part about this, which which I didn't tell you
to begin with. They're not showing this on TV.
This isn't part of the TV news.
The broadcast news hasn't even picked it up.
It's only been in print so far that I've seen.
I know there's a video out there, but none of the like broadcast media
carrying it, which is weird.
They're showing they're showing.
Well, OK, so the idiots, the zombie, which is typical American
that might pick up on it in print or whatever or on the Internet
and not see it on their mainstream TV is being jostled a little bit,
like poked a little like, hey, wake up.
You're you're watching very finely filtered bullshit on one end
and then you're getting raw bullshit.
The guy burning himself, this guy was a moron to do that.
You know, if he wasn't a moron, he'd say, hey, man, I'm just passing through here.
Fuck him. You know, burn the place down.
You know what I mean? Protest. What the hell?
Do you get it? You notice I keep saying burn the place down, right?
Oh, yeah. OK, because he burned himself, you know.
Well, it made me think of that monk, which we talked about
just before we started recording.
And that monk can say he's an idiot.
Yeah, he's he's not.
He's a fake monk because a real monk would would be more like one of the Jedi.
Imagine one of the Jedi.
Would one of the Jedi light themselves on fire?
No. Yeah. So he's a real idiot.
You know, it's just a bag of meat.
The monk and most monks are. They're very.
By the way, this is from someone that I knew that had gone to Tibet
when they bring them a computer, the Tibetan monks,
and they leave them with a computer that's online for more than 20 minutes.
The they all of them without this happened over a period of two years.
They all immediately go to porn.
All of them, every single one get porn immediately.
All of them. Yeah.
So these monks are a bunch of jerkoffs.
It's just a community. Think about
it's like a bunch of Americans and turn them into monks and go visit them.
You say this is a cult, right?
Yeah, that's exactly if you're in Tibet or wherever you go, China
and the people that live there view them as a cult and they're a bunch of idiots.
You wouldn't do anything like that.
Again, it's like with Jason Breshears.
It's dungeon programming.
You're going to let yourself get into that kind of a thing.
You just fucked yourself.
That's not a family term, but it's a medical term.
This is just hilarious to me.
The jerk offs who fucked themselves.
OK, fair enough.
Oh, yeah. They are just.
Yeah. No, the monks did useless, completely go.
That's for the weak brain people.
Oh, they're monks.
Got from. Oh, yeah.
Or you ever hear this alternative podcast?
They they're so happy they have a guest in who has a doctor degree.
You know, it's like, oh, my gosh, that means the guy is a total idiot.
He didn't realize by the eighth grade the whole thing is a fraud.
He kept going.
Well, if you're going to look, if you're going to strive to have idiots
to talk to, you might as well get the best idiot you can.
Oh, my gosh. Right.
Oh, my gosh. You realize by the eighth grade.
Oh, kind of. What's wrong with you?
It's all backwards.
You know, hey, look, I like making things simple,
but it's already really simple, you know, it's already very simple.