Sonic event number four of Ocelli in the Greek rated Y and you know here's a
good why question I guess or maybe it's a why question maybe it's a why not
question. Greek, are things just fine the way they are anyway? I mean a lot of
people want to ascend, separate themselves, improve the quality of things
but maybe things are just fine the way they are. I'd say they are the way they
are because they're fine. How about that way? Okay. It's kind of it's kind of like
wash your brain instead of brainwashing. Mm-hmm. So you know all these things
turned around a little bit. I would say give a little cosmic history. What if
there is an overarching being in a society of beings whether it's social or
familial that control everything that we consider to be the universe, right? And
remember what we consider to be the universe you know scientists if you
follow them they they've told us the earth is aging at two and a half million
years per year which sounds bizarre you know and hundred years ago they said the
universe was a half a million years old and then in the 20s it was a million by
the 50s it was 500 million by the 80s it's billion now it's 15 billion so if
you divide it it's about two we're aging at about two and a half million years
per year it sounds kind of ridiculous but that's what they're telling us right?
Well and again does it really matter? Does it really matter? Because right you
know after all look you're only going to be here for this short period of time no
matter how you reckon it no matter how you lawfully count it or not there is a
finite amount of time that you're going to be in this experience seems like so
what is the point of even knowing the context of that experience I mean is it a
literal nanosecond are we talking about you know I mean look I guess that's
relevant because somebody might want to know what their contribution is their
context is in this experience but are things okay the way they are I mean as
strange as that might sound like I said yeah somebody wishes to seek a little
bit better quality I mean you and I've talked about it many times why not
improve the quality of the food the water the shelter the clothing while
you're here sure for yourself yes but what about the status quo I mean is it
not there for a reason so I don't know I leave it to you yeah well here's the
thing let's say it's an absolute that there are overarching beings more
powerful than us that have full control of everything we perceive as being the
universe and if you hearken back to religion aspects they say well the good
will be rewarded in the poor and the bad will be punished right well why would you
set it up that way unless you're a real sadist right to deliberately set people
up so you could torture them which is which actually happens by the way in this
society even though it's not well publicized it is known so what I'm
suggesting here is that there is a mechanism in place that no matter how
evil corrupt or bad the status quo is it's just fine and the reason why it's
just fine is because anything that is inefficient or quote-unquote bad or
contrary to any law whether it's natural law overall cosmic law or man's law or
the laws of any law contrary will not necessarily be punished directly but
it'll just wear out like an engine that doesn't have enough oil and it's
overheating you're on your way to wherever you want to go it's been
reliable for five years but guess what right now it's going to give it up and
it's going to break down you see mm-hmm so the entropy will catch up yeah well
is that more of the natural order of things anyway or is that something that
is just look everything is meant to be finite see I brought up that idea
already where look everything has a lifespan so to speak everything has a
time period before its obsolescence becomes obvious and inevitable so the
system the construct the organizational principles all of these things are meant
to what fail at some point are they not both in other words there are two
natural systems the the real natural system and the one we called to be the
natural system that we lean on that's where the the issue of your perception
and your confidence comes in and I want to I want to wrestle with that for a
minute sure we did a let's say a little bit of an introduction to it on the last
one right we perceive certain things as knowledge or things we should know and
then once we grasp them or receive them as such we become confident in it
and then any information contrary you know cognitive dissonance or
argumentedness all this other stuff before we get into that I want to pull
up this I think this is like old philosophical stuff I'm just kind of
distilled it I want to read something real quick this is like in the vein of
the old philosophers of the 20th century the guys from the Carpathian Mountains
like Kripke and those guys so think about this for a moment because we I
mentioned you mentioned the status quo and I said it's basically corrupt and
evil it always has been if you go back to the times of ancient times as well
let's say within the five to six thousand year history that we're aware
of and it's not going to be punished directly as we see in the religiosity
and in the biblical mistranslations but it's just going to wear out and if you
understand in context for example it's just for a second talk about the
biblical context it's not punished directly because a lot of the concepts
of hell and all that don't exist right it might just be one word but we attach
it to what we see from the Vatican and from Hollywood what happens is it says
it's no more the same as your car that you've been relying on breaks down
because it didn't have any oil in it you didn't check you didn't maintain it
right so this is what's going to happen it's just a matter of being patient
watching it happen you know basically this universe will be or this society
will be left on the side of the road kind of thing so I want to go back to what
the philosophy this is a distilled philosophical thing about truth so if we
look at truth there are truths that are absolute independent of any individual
mind and therefore universal meaning if even if no one's heard of it it's still
true it's still the truth does it matter if you know about it or not let's say
purely objective then you have the concept of where you go into the way
that we have our human dynamic the way our minds work and I'm saying this very
strictly in a sense that if we really found out how our minds work you ready
for this we would know everything about the past the present and everything
about the future because they all exist at the same time just like the parade
exists and the person up in the helicopter can see the whole parade where
you're on the street right that analogy right okay so these next three concepts
are from what we consider to be the way our mind works now because again if we
knew everything let's just say about the future what would we think about our
knowledge base it would be infinite right so we don't have that so again when
I'm going to mention these other aspects this is from as we stand right
now and when I say as we stand right now even an NPC one of these hollow husks of
a human is able to do this but there but their programming doesn't allow them to
okay okay so the first part about the conventional minds that we exercise now
let's say the concept of knowledge right orgnosis right it's possible with the
mindset that we have now is to gain objective knowledge of some of the truth
that we just mentioned earlier that is universal okay let's say not all of it
but some of it and I've gone over how we have infinite memory capability but I'm
keeping it in the sum so it is possible to gain objective knowledge of these
objective truths in the next one would be the reasoning behind it the reason is
the best way for reasoning is the best way to achieve and justify this
knowledge which is logic and reason again from the religious part you hear
the logos and they translate that as the word right and it's actually the word
logical or reasoning so by logic and reason you have to include the aspect of
time if you hear a new concept you might want to ask when you're initiated to
this concept how long has it been that way when did we first discover it you
see when you know when was this notion you know how did I miss out on it right
so the concept of time and history so one of the ways to bring up reason and
logic is to find out the history of the thing I think I've said this on vintage
Greek speak to know the history of the thing you know the thing I once was
around some very young twins very intelligent and they're always in front
of the TV and the parents didn't want me around anymore because I told them
don't let the TV raise your children and they took it as an affront but the
children asked me I basically said you know the TV is a recent invention they
didn't know that right so when they had the dinosaur book they thought the TV
might have been just after the dinosaurs right they have no idea until I let them
know about the history so this is part of logic and reason in other words you
can infer is a process that you could bring forward when you're bringing
forward an idea especially to the status quo as you said that you know might be
rejected but don't hold that don't be confident that it'll be rejected but you
the possibility is there like ninety percent in your statement include some
history historicity of it okay okay okay the next thing is the concept of
progress I don't like to use the word evolution but moving forward what would
be another word for progress evolving right or going to the next level yeah to
evolve makes sense but you know there is a difference between discovery and
existence right because that's something that just stuck with me when
you're talking about this just because it has not been discovered doesn't mean
it wasn't true but at the same time if it hasn't been communicated then it's
not part of the again it's not part of the status quo's base of knowledge it's
not part of anybody's base of knowledge even having been discovered so yeah but
even the discovery okay again we'll get into a little more the concept of the
atom is total bullshit right it's not a they say it's atomic I say it's a
compound because it's a combination of elements known as electrons protons and
neutrons in different orders so that we're still being lied to about
electrons and all that and what things we couldn't see let's say or we still
can't see but they well the virus thing it's all it's all artist animation right
right and people take it as hard so that's this is part of this car that
doesn't have enough oil is gonna burn up on the side of the road right you
just don't want to be a passenger in it spiritually well when it happens right
because you're gonna end up walking so when you are in a situation like that
make sure you got good walking shoes and some bus fare okay so the progress and
the evolution part is as you let's say the human mind as we consider it now can
improve progress evolve right move forward by using rational reasoning to
this objective knowledge but only to the objective knowledge in other words
the rational reasoning like let's say you're from again confronted with
something new get a little history in there either explain it or ask for it and
that will start to set up that reason and logic right okay in time but what we
see here in other words for humans to to better their position is to act
rationally in response of being confronted or made aware of this
objective knowledge that's the real scientific method let's say right and
all this but what's going on right now is it the knowledge is not objective
it's social right it's social acceptance confidence so I just want to bring up
those philosophical points because what I mean by philosophical meaning that if
you are really looking you know for the word what it means also philosophy you
have to distill things down where you take yourself out of it but can still use
it you know so taking your subjectiveness out now when we when I
brought up the concepts of the confidence you know the you ever heard of you fell
for a con man you know the con man is a negative thing right of course well the
con man is short for confidence right that's where it comes from so the so
somehow someone approached you with some information but their their deal was not
to give objective information their right their deal was to project a sense of
confidence and you latch on to that feeling and you take on some of what
they said because remember Gustav Le Bon the essence of the crowd is you cannot
give them direct information you simplify it and most of the time the
information because becomes so simplified that it no longer represents
the initial idea okay so that's where you have all these theories around
there's no conclusion people say what about this theory that there is it look
there's millions of theories out there when you start garnering conclusions for
these I'd like to know what the conclusions are and you never get that
right because it's all presumptive so back to the con man and I'm mentioning
the the the confidence and their perception the way that everything is
being steered here apparently is by con men in other words you become confident
in the method of their delivery and the contents are ignored right and when the
contents the actual objectifying of the content contents are brought up and are
at the point of being revealed the person becomes it becomes a personal
battle for them like for example they want to debate you and it's not what to
debate to bring forward anything of merit but it's so they can win the
debate so the whole thing goes away from the subject again just like when you're
dealing with the state and the legal stuff it'll you'll see like most people
in federal prison are in there with very obscure charges right like false
information or conspiracy right you know it's just like really obscure stuff you
see because the the definitions of the things that they did being applied in
their law is not being done so you have this concept of the confidence being
instilled in the being now we're not going to get into the different types of
humans here but just say overall society and accepted because of the
confidence now very often I'm not going to mention any names like cliff high or
other people like that but people say you gotta listen to this guy and I said
he's really smart Greek and I'm like okay well there's a big difference
between people who are smart and people who sound smart yes big difference
difference in fact yes right so he's a guy that sounds smart and he's a pure
materialist he's always talking about absorbing nutrients I'm like okay right
there right well you can be a little forgiving he just doesn't know but when
he hammers on this stuff like whatever you know schizophrenia is genetic right
and all this other stuff I'm like okay I've these like five people have
recommended him to me in a year and I might I give the same answer because I
go back and check maybe the guy has turned around and evolved and he hasn't
and there's many people like that the Jason Breshears guy is another example
of someone who is extremely confident and when he brings up stuff not
everything most a lot of the stuff he brings up is valid not all of it he's so
confident that the people just grab onto it because he's
confident right okay and you could prove this by looking at the cliff high in the
in the archaic comments you'll see all these comments and what are the comments
oh I love you Jason great work oh this is so great oh he's a burning hunk of
love oh but it's like wow wow talk about like disposable mindset right so so this
confidence thing has not necessarily ruined society because it's always been
around since ancient times it is a factor so what's going to happen is if
you have listened to Greek speak or anything like that
haha saying that sarcastically if you've listened to Greek speak let's say
which I believe stands alone and you start approaching people in your
proximity regardless of relation you will meet 90% of the time you will meet
friction some some sort of disbelief there's a variety of responses right
right now I have a question about this okay because here is the difficulty for
me personally I'm gonna go personal because I can I can explain this pretty
well and maybe you can help me because I guarantee I'm not alone what I find the
problem to be is that establishing a communication with somebody where you
have look we can accept this both you and I accept a particular concept an
idea a truth if you will let us begin there right I had a problem recently
with this whole thing why are you against you know the vaccination wrote
it up okay well I said look let's establish that this is what is written
by the drug company who made it right couldn't even get somebody to agree to
that even though I can demonstrate it I can give him a copy of it I can show him
they can go get their own I couldn't even get him to do that because there is
this refusal to share right to objectively observe this is something
that's written in that document I'm not saying it's true or not I'm simply
saying this is what we can both observe let's begin from that point there is
difficulty lately it seems to me in getting anybody to do that whether it's
about politics or it's about a situation whatever where it's like look
go outside look up at the sky tell me that what you see is it not the same
thing I see and you can't get an agreement there even to begin with right
so everything skews off from that and becomes a problem with communication
because you can't objectively establish things like this so problems with trying
to explain you know like like you're talking about very much in these
previous sonics this concept of look if you take a look at a tire you know you
dissect it you do a cross-section you look at it you have this you know
enclosed thing now you take a look at the human body it does that too where we
have an enclosure okay there's no absorption again you try and do that
they absolutely refuse to even do the objective look to say oh but it would
be it would be this yeah it would be the same as the VAX or the body or this or
the chemtrail or this or that or that because it's not the subject matter well
but there it is but you can't even establish the objective right because
yes okay let's get into a more and we'll see how we can well my experiences but
you know we're gonna view each thing from our own our own container yeah fine
of course but I just wanted to get into this because I think this is a common
issue where oh yeah you can't we will we will as we started in other words we've
already gotten into it I think you jump forward which is fine because this is
the you know in other words don't give me the history like it's like if I ask
you what time it is don't tell me how to build a watch right right I'm just asking
you what time it is basically the whole thing is it's all personal okay so you
know like for example the VAX is an easy one and depending on who you're
speaking to you have to be able to switch really quickly right you know so
like an old person who can't hear a guy works on Wall Street or four-year-old
baby if you're gonna address them at the same time your message is about 20%
clear but if you address each one of them you're gonna have to speak real loud
to the guy who can't hear the Wall Street guy and the four-year-old a
little different okay so you have to be able to do that quickly make these
adjustments but that's a personal thing but what I'm saying is it's all personal
in other words the reason I read that philosophical stuff there is because
that is something that you could write in stone as a marker and a reference on
how someone with a mind any mind can operate but what I'm saying is the
concept of the con man and the confidence has nothing to do with the
information that they're caught they're supposedly confident that they're
confident that if they say this that are accepted in whatever group or even
personally if you'll personally stable so let's do the Vax very very simple
like for example someone who was logical and I said I you understand there's
something called logic or whatever you know they'll be like yeah I said you
know because they called me a Vax denier right and I said well in logic you
cannot deny something that doesn't exist you can only deny something that
exists so because vaccines don't exist as they're advertised I'm not denying
Vax vaccines because they don't exist there's no such thing as a vaccine if
you call it inoculation right if you call it an injection well the injection
exists but an injection as a vaccine does not exist you see right that's why
I often call it a medication because I think it is a medication it is an
injection in a strictest term it is yeah but but you shouldn't have to what
okay we just established they are actually telling you that you have to
put it under the skin subdermal intravenously somehow because nothing
gets through the body is that interesting right okay maybe by the time
we're in with the sonic I'm going to throw out some more stuff about what what
the body is doing but this is all personal for example if you speak to
someone about chemtrails and they say that's conspiracy theory stuff you type
in chemtrails in a browser on a search the first thing that comes up is it's
conspiracy theory stuff right but if you type in a search stratospheric aerosol
injection what do you get all these patents and methods and companies
offering it for a fee same stuff because when you go to images for the chemtrails
that are all marked as conspiracy stuff you see the images and you go to
stratospheric aerosol injection you have the same images how is that possible or
similar right that's not conspiracy theory so the legal aspect of the words
changing makes a big difference so when you're approaching someone with this
information I would suggest trying that the methodology of pure reason and even
a dopey child has pure reason we would be like you can't watch any TV unless
you do your homework well that's reason and logic in other words in logic well I
have to do homework first and then TV comes second because if homework becomes
zero TV becomes zero you see the logic even a little child right so that basic
childlike essence works in the logic you know nothing that includes more than one
or two concepts at a time so when you provide this knowledge base whether it's
the thing you brought up the vaccine maybe the sky stuff I think when you
said sky you didn't say chemtrails I'm saying chemtrails right right okay but
I've done this before people look up and they just don't know if they if here's
one of the things that is interesting you know how I've always said the opposite
of love is not hate it's apathy right because it's the same amount of passion
to love and to hate apathy removal of any passion removal of energy okay when
you when I was out in the parking lot years ago and I point up what are those
clouds right half the people didn't even bother looking they were completely
apathetic they didn't even want to look up or acknowledge even the kind of glance
that I was pointing up and they didn't even engage me at all zero right and the
ones that did engage me said well there's no way that the government would
allow that right there's no way that you know how come you're the only person
that's ever told me this right or all this plausible tonight it's very
personal right and one person so yeah I know they're chemtrails go online and I
said yeah I know if they're online thanks man right okay so there is the
best thing you can experience with this by the way is apathy so when you bring
up the vaccine to someone or they do and they don't want to engage you at all on
it I know the opposite of love is not what we're here for right we're here for
love it's it's apathy and when you get that apathy it's the op you feel that
sinking feeling I've just been ignored right but I'm telling you would you
rather invest a whole bunch of you know energy and you know when it's not going
to go anywhere as people do most of the time personally I have much success with
all types and the reason why is because I understand that they know jack shit
about anything right and I'm not talking about that you know how it
pretty much say it's a society of morons and most people think yes of course
because I go out in the street and I see how the population is I'm not when I say
that I'm not talking about the general population I'm talking about the
professionals the people the specialists I don't even consider the general
population at all in my in my dialogue very very rarely so when I say society of
morons means your doctors your lawyers your judges your rabbis your imams your
engineers that's who the more you right the rest don't count at all so when I
say that people don't know jack shit in other words I'm talking to about like
you mentioned the human body right just now that the look at the car tire in
this time what I have a car when I bring up an example of a conversation on that
it's never with someone in the population and I stated it's with a
medical person someone who's trained with a doctorate degree in medicine or
whatever biology right so when I bring up energy systems and I talked to
someone it's because I'm spoken speaking to a physicist or an engineer not
because some common person on the street now I do have some examples where yes
you know but being out in the parking lot of Home Depot and pointing up right
most people ignore but when I bring up a specific topic especially with the legal
when I say they don't know the law it's I'm specifically talking about attorneys
does this make it worse yes it makes the situation that humans are in much worse
because most people would say well if he's talking about everyone's a moron is
talking about the population not my uncle who or my dad who was an attorney
and my mom who was a doctor no way right I'm talking about them though okay so
what that does it does two things one thing I've stated before is all fields
are wide open because the professionals and those that are leading you the
educators and authorities or whatever are idiotic and moronic what does that
mean you're not going to get anything logical and reasonable reasonable or even
true from them so what does that mean okay well it means you're in piss poor
shape right you're looking up and you're giving them lots of quote-unquote
credits to get basically very little or next to nothing or false stuff okay
that's the negative part the positive part is this and I've always said this
and I've never really gotten much feedback on it this is the positive side
of these professionals being morons what that what it does is these professionals
are supposedly masters of individual fields okay specific fields if they're
all moronic as a general whole a few exception the positive side is that it
leaves all those fields of study wide open leaves them wide open for you to
progress with it you see so for example when we do the medical thing you look at
the car tire the structure is designed to be completely enclosed and sealed from
the outer environment all right same with the human body when you develop a
science on that let's say we were the first humans and we just became
conscious we build our science on that right we'll be very advanced in a very
short period of time not just alone but you need a collective of people to be
working on it right and what will happen is the choice of this matter versus the
choice of the matter of going with the established medicine you don't have to
go you don't have to see them as competition at all like the horse race
you just run it like a horse race you ever see the Hort people racing on a
horse track are they looking at the guy next to him say hey how did you get
ahead of me or right never they're always looking straight ahead even the
guy in last place is whipping his horse just as much as the guy in first place
you ever noticed that yes okay in a horse race you don't care what the guy
you're not really it's you and the horse to get to the line regardless of what
position you're in the same with let's say the field of medical study if
enough people come together and we start developing a knowledge base and a
practice meaning practice as in practical application don't even consider
the existing medical community what will happen the word will get out and you'll
start and then it'll the choice will be obvious right it'll be obvious you don't
have to say we're going against these guys or bad-mouthing these guys right
because again you go on the alternative media whatever you'll find all these
people and videos or whatever bad-mouthing the current establishment
but do they know really how the body works no no right so that's not
necessary everything is like that completely even history and studying of
ancient texts okay so when you're getting into a relationship regarding
exchange of information it is not that at all I don't know how else I could
drive that home it is personal how many times do you hear people have a
conversation don't take this personal I can only take it personal what's
important is in my person in my mind do I have the subdivision that when we're
speaking about knowledge truth logic and reason to come to an objective truth
a real truth I need to keep myself down you know I can't be angry I can't be
jealous I can't be too excited right I can't be defensive you see we talked
about the lack of emotion right with the Vulcans not necessarily to that point
but setting all of the things outside all the negative attributes that we hear
con men instilling in people see because the con man is totally cool he's like a
con man or like mr. Magoo remember the cartoon he walks through all these
things where he should be killed hit by a car you know something piano dropping
but he always evades it right yeah seemingly oblivious but continues yeah
of course and that's right so yeah a good con man would be oblivious to the
con right well oblivious to the con and oblivious to anything that contradicts it
or impedes it and just simply navigates mm-hmm without it out yeah mm-hmm so
here's the the thing because this has been coming up often well for more than
about two decades now I've been doing Greek speak I started doing public
speaking here in Tucson around 2004 it comes up often oh my wife doesn't want
to hear my husband's want to hear my children think I'm crazy the I'd lost my
job is it well you're not doing it right obviously in other words if that's the
outcome you want you're doing it right right well here's one way that that I
project it for example I know that the they're already going to be they it when
you're dealing with the masses or even the professionals most likely the
professionals that is I have I approach on these subjects at length for example
at length could be 30 seconds to three minutes okay what I do is I bring in some
historicity first you know I remind them of the the medical society that they're
in how old it is right I remind them that we're somehow don't have any money
to pay for anything there's many ways to do that right so people say why is the
medical you know how can when you're using fiat currency how are you going to
get real education with fiat currency it has to be fiat education you know right
just make it so all right the other thing I remind them is that we are in a
temporal local temporal geographic zone known as the earth however whether you
think it's round and a ball or flat and round or whatever it doesn't matter so
what I do is I inject enough sarcasm in a British humor kind of way which it's
accepted if you I think most people have been exposed to it right where I inject
a level of sarcasm where you're not sure if it's supposed to be funny and make
them laugh but it usually does right and one of those things is anybody who's
just came who's been on earth for more than 15 minutes has figured this out now
they that gets into their mind like what do you mean you've only need to be on
this planet for 15 minutes to figure out what he's saying what what what I'm I
missed out on something right this for a third of a second that's what goes
through their mind but then the other two-thirds of the second it's like oh is
he trying to be funny and sarcastic oh okay so he's not really challenging me
because we tell someone a joke by the way you're including them into a social
event whether you're on stage speaking to a hundred people are telling your one
person a joke you're not the joke is not really there's a difference in laughing
with them or at them but either way a joke is a friendly kind of amicable way
to relate you must bring humor you into the situation right right how many times
have you heard it was really bad but we all left smiling okay so I've noticed
very often a quote-unquote truthers in person or online when they go out in the
street or even interviews or whatever they have their demeanor changes and they
become very stoic and very almost affrontive with before they even start
speaking so I would suggest that bringing in satire humor even some
sarcasm is the way to do it the way I do it is not the way that others would do
it and by the way I always tell people don't do what I would do right and it's
not because you shouldn't do what I'm doing it's just that if you're gonna do
anything or say anything that I'm saying make sure that you have your own you
know I've give everyone license right if people go out and speak and say things
verbatim but they don't have to say they got it from the Greek I'm just glad
it's getting out there now but when it softens it softens things to with a joke
you sort of you relax people right when you're doing a presentation it's a very
common thing to do it doesn't matter what the presentation is about actually
if you bring them in on a joke kind of relaxes the audience a bit whether it's
an audience of one or a hundred like you said so yeah commonly yes yeah so all
this communication believe it or not okay the the crux of this the subject
matter on the sonic so far has been what happens when you talk you know do
greek-speak with other people they you know right 90% of time they okay so it's
not just greek-speak when you're having any cop any communication or interaction
with people it's about them from their point of view as they see themselves as
they think you see them also right and then there's the way that everyone sees
them you know what social group are you Democrat Republican are you black white
right all that other stuff so they're very very concerned on a personal level
of what's going on again if all of this information let's go back to the Vax
thing you know it's all calm right okay it's actually by the way let's just
just scratch the last five seconds of what I said if you keep watching the
media whether it's mainstream or alternative you're going to see from now
actually it started already so the next year it'll be parallel to the weapons of
mass destruction thing there's no weapons of mass destruction here right
right so right they told everyone that was the reason for and they themselves
admitted it was not okay so why go through all of that when it's already
very well established that there's no such thing as a vaccine by the way if you
go and look at newspapers from the 1800s they were very much against vaccines
they were killing people by the droves then also so there you know it's one of
these medical fictions okay so if you look at something like the even the Vax
or whatever the humor that you can bring on that is there's a multitude of humor
that you could bring into that the other thing is if you know for example and
here's the thing that I that I charge people with you must learn a lot you
must know a lot you must have a good memory and also good communication
skills otherwise just go be like everyone else okay right it's not much
hard it's not difficult to do but if you can't communicate it and it seems like a
personal front it's it's not going to work when you communicate with people so
you must know so for example I'll give an example again with the Vax at the
height of this someone there I went into a shop and I wasn't wearing a face
diaper and he offered me one and I said I don't know if this is isn't going to
work if this is going to work for me because I don't have an immune system
am I lying no one has an immune system right they call you know this this this
biological function of the body's ability to wipe up the quote-unquote bad
cells or dead cells and get rid of them right and protect the body from them
that lingering they call that an immune system but it's not an immune system
what's the organ for the immune system there is none what that is it's the
elimination system the eliminative system right right right so if you
understand that it's a medical fiction it's just a term right if I say there's
no such I don't have an immune system am I it's a hundred percent true based on
the knowledge base that I have but to them they've heard of the boy in the
plastic bubble remember that oh yeah yeah yeah you didn't have well you didn't
have an immune system so they have to be shielded they live their whole life
in a in a sterile chamber right and why is he in a sterile chamber because he
doesn't have an immune system as if it really existed so they they pick up
somewhere that it is possible for someone not to have an immune system
right right so this corrupt world in these common are actually telling you
the truth but they're not saying it applies to everyone just John Travolta in
the set right okay so now this guy thinks without me saying it that I'm
John the guy at the boy in the plastic bubble it happens to be walking into
Sprouts market holy shit I'm privileged you know I'm a special needs person
suddenly right here's somebody who's so damaged that you're lacking this thing
which is commonly supposed to be with everybody right and he doesn't know that
he doesn't have one either but he's been conned into thinking that he does right
correct think about that for a minute okay so now what are you doing you know
he this guy's serious as a heart attack the store assistant manager he's
walking me through play I don't have the mascot right right okay so he clears the
aisle because I'm coming down people messes get out I want to come you want
to go down this aisle make sure he clears the whole aisle for me shit man
I'm like Ivanka Trump right I mean think of a celebrity going to supermarket
clear the aisle for him and I'm walking around and now here's the thing what he's
picking up on from my intuitively just like a you know if you have somewhat two
people approach a dog and one was a dog lover and the other ones afraid of dogs
neither of them say anything which one is the dog in a bite the one that's
afraid yeah he didn't say anything to do anything to the dog no the dog picks up
on it right exactly what's happening here I don't
have an immune system this guy is overly sympathetic he didn't have to do
that I am full of internally I am full of humor and honesty right now I'm not
assessing well this guy's poor SAP doesn't know it no you know you put me on
a lie detector test or whatever telepath you know scanned my brain right I'd be
telling the truth I have no immune system so he's picked up on that from
that I have a good good energy emanating from me and he got overly
sympathetic on his cause on his end based on he's confident that he heard
that people that are immune without an immune system are so special they
actually got John Travolta to play one okay right so what happened now is I
became privileged okay instead of what I'm not wearing that master's fire
whatever whatever what do you think would happen to that guy that guy gets
argued with we got you got to leave I'm gonna call the cops blah blah yeah yeah
okay so the when you put out this it just like the dog right the person
afraid of dog gets bit even though he hasn't done anything the dog picks up on
it I mean we're more evolved supposedly higher order than a dog let's say not to
put down dogs how much more do we do that so there's this essence of it also
so in essence if you start learning and this is the thing I charge people I
charge means you should do this you have to do it it's not a matter of choice so
you have to integrate it in your life is to study right and learn about things
using logic and reason anything that's new that you come about any information
that is new regardless when did it come into existence when did people find out
about what's the history you must know the history of it and guess what how
many people out there that are Provax know the history of vaccines next to
none next to not I know anything about anything right and and we're talking
about the medical community now okay so once you attach okay an easy way to do
it is if you're learning how to ride a bike the easiest way to learn how to
ride a bike pretty much if you don't have training wheels is to have both of
your feet not on the ground and you're not pedaling but you're coasting okay so
way of learning how to coast and I'm talking about this is all about
interacting with others on let's say Greek speak is stick to the history of a
thing and believe it or not those that have made the world so corrupt and evil
and bad and put out the con men and the cons that the population follows which
is false guess what those are publishing companies information societies you know
digital or whatever University libraries those are the same people that put out
the truth of the matter aren't they mm-hmm true mm-hmm right like for
example you do your JFK research how much valuable information can you get if
you looked at CIA files a lot right a lot yes even though people resist it and
say well you know look they're only gonna put out lies there I'm like no you
don't understand this then right because it's not that that's not the case at all
especially when you find something that's a report and it's actually dated
before the event happened right that's even better when you look at it and
that's the other thing is the timing of the thing is just as important as the
information in it because you can see when it came into existence versus when
a real-world event was supposed to be occurring and this is very important
yes well the FAA report on the flight path of the planes that supposedly hit
the World Trade Center that took off around 8 ish in the morning well that
entire flight plan was constructed and compiled at 530 in the morning of that
day three hours before they took off yeah wait a second okay I mean right but
it doesn't matter because from on a personal that information now becomes
personal I chose to believe that so if you want to challenge their information
which I know nothing about or care to you're challenging me and I will
challenge you to debate and I'm gonna make sure I win the debate information
doesn't mean anything okay so this is okay let's go back to the dog if you're
thinking like the person who is afraid of dogs the dogs gonna bite right and if
you're a dog lover dogs not gonna bite okay so the same way when you start
people start engaging with you or anyone that is bringing information forward and
you see it's going to go south it's believe it or not you what is it there
is no second chance to a first impression is there right so if they're
going south with the argument or it's going south and emotional and the
information doesn't matter it's just going into ad hominem stuff now like
you're a nutcase or whatever you were your shoes are dirty or whatever or okay
if it goes into that it's because of that first impression and you usually
don't have a second chance at that you can't recover on that so this is why
maybe I was I said let's do this sonic because I've got to get this out there
because I feel it you know in the ether that there's this is something that's
been coming up for a long time so what I've mixed here isn't is I did not get
in earlier in the first impression how important it is but this is a mixed bag
nothing that we're saying in the sonic should be done in any order you just
take it how you want but it's really that first impression again the dog
meeting someone who's afraid of dogs first impression if that person says in
their mind I love you doggy that's not gonna work okay if someone says don't be
afraid of dogs he's fine it's too late dog already got it okay so this is a
part of preparation of going out into the world I mean even if you're you smoke
a joint before when you wake up in the morning before your feet even touch the
ground out of bed you can still do what I'm saying it your state of mind is
your personal state of mind your personal habits are not as important as
the way that you organize the things that I'm saying that makes any sense well
I'm thinking that what's really important is what you project as opposed
to what the actual argument is because by projecting honesty and humor even
though you're not articulating that you change the circumstances
automatically you change the way the whole interaction goes that's what I'm
picking up on but I mean maybe I'm yeah well if you meditate think about the
higher order of things you ever see people that are go to war like in the
crusades right and it's because of their religion no matter what they do and no
matter how good the situation goes for them or how bad and they become let's say
martyred it doesn't diminish the cause you know how they feel about their
religion so they're asking God to protect them and they get slaughtered by
all the Muslims even when they're dying breath are still giving God thanks right
it's not dependent on if the situation goes well or poorly they are so deeply
entrenched in their quote-unquote faith so that's why I brought up is there
anything higher than an absolute truth even if independent of the individual
mind nothing there is nothing cannot be anything higher than that right so and
and the the highest individuals will try to get that knowledge you probably won't
get all of it but at least start by bit by bit bite by bite or chunks it right
and the way you get that knowledge is by reason and logic and the easiest way to
start reasoning it is how long has this been going on when did this come into
existence right and and by the way it's forever is not an acceptable answer
always is not an acceptable answer it should be accepted you know even in
mathematics when you're doing calculus square root of negative to know that you
do have the infinity you do use infinity right to send things to that end of the
line but it's not really fully acceptable but it's it's good enough so
within this and then also how are we going to get better and progress if we
don't have this objective knowledge that we've gotten through logic and
reason not from a con man right because a con man if he's giving you objective
truth and knowledge is he really a con man no no not at all confidence is not a
requisite for something to be true even if you don't believe it it does not mean
that it's necessarily untrue right but on the other side if you're giving
objective knowledge and also imbuing it with a confident tone of confidence now
you're more like the the dog lover that approaches the dog the dog will will be
great in your company right okay so are you confident in the knowledge
information that you're giving or yourself actually more in the information
take yourself out of it and this is what you learn from the religious zealots by
the way like the guys at the crusades you see it in the movies they all get
slaughtered but they're still thanking God right right so excellent well what
is it that we could do from here with this well okay I guess I guess I'm going
to ask you to repeat something here because all right we've talked about the
objective truth the highest truth the absolute truth and how this is relevant
and how it is presented but presentation is very important because even if you
have the absolute truth in hand if you cannot adequately communicate it it it's
not it's not really relevant it doesn't get communicated so it doesn't do
anything other than exist right so where are we at with this when you're
presenting easy good yeah easy easy on that so you figure out that something
works here the real scientific method it works for you it works over there
works in China works in Antarctica works for everywhere okay that's the real
scientific method it's repeatable right okay so no pun intended but if something
is repeatable it means that there was some form of communication even if the
people are local but typically you would communicate it in the letter on Skype or
you know somehow you know write a book and the person buys it on the other side
of the world it's all communication okay once that communication is successful
and the people report back by communication that there's consistency
now you have a group you have more than one person that could work and when you
have more than one person that could work on something you get what's called
development by the way in the business world when you hear development it means
raising money okay yeah so or wherewithal okay so once you get to that
point where you have people working on something let's not even call it a new
way of doing things because for example back to the medical once you get enough
people that figure out that nothing that the body works by induction nothing
passes through directly you have enough people working on that and you start
putting out you know your own version of bandage your own tonics your own
whatever you know devices and methods you don't have to accept you don't have
to accept the other system at all it doesn't even exist you you don't go
after it with hate and animosity the existing system you use apathy you don't
exist like look who's talking right now I in the real world you're gonna they're
gonna get the the attorneys after you right and I'll give you an example
recently I messaged someone about but someone wanted to buy a product I said
oh that's Illuminati stuff and I say I can't just say that's Illuminati stuff I
have to explain right so you have these products that come out like Bose
speakers right right everybody gets it right that's that's not an organic system
in other words that's not real free marketing the other one would be Dyson
vacuum cleaners you know if the vacuum cleaner was a dead market for I don't
know my whole life and then Dyson comes along suddenly Dyson vacuum cleaners are
exciting again right what he's like the only one right so you got all these
products and he got the Couric the little little coffee grinder cup that
the shirts shoot shoot steam through right right by these little things ends
up being like three dollars right for a little thing right anyway okay so what I
want to say about that people got the point when I brought up these companies
or organizations I have first-hand it well second-hand experience first-hand
experience knowing someone he wanted to start a particular business that was
part of a very large market and it looked like he went and got a patent all
this other thing and he had some you know he got his family money together
almost a million bucks and they started working right on this right and
advertising and that really good stuff all right what happens the bankers send
their middlemen the IRS after him audit after audit after audit after audit they
send the EPA because he had a gum wrapper on the floor that had some toxic
soy ink on it okay okay so you got the IRS you got the EPA then he gets the
building department the outlets should be at 42 at the switches should be 42
inches from the floor yours are 41 and 3 quarters inch it's out of code I'm
shutting down the place you get the point here mm-hmm you see where I'm
going with this okay so these guys Bose Dyson Keurig all these other things you
know you think they tell you look at the story with these wealthy people right
don't know bill pick pick your lot right you hear of them Soros Bill Gates
both bozos of Amazon right whatever yeah yeah okay so they give you their story
at least you always started off blah blah blah they're selling lemonade and
then move to this number if you follow the story doesn't make any sense it
doesn't do you think these people are set up and put forward you know I
personally have been around very wealthy people and I asked in their history and
they just shrug their shoulders they say honestly you know I know I know what
I've done I got I went to art school got into commodities and now you know I
control 70% of the helium in America which is actually 80% of the helium in
the world billionaire so I really don't know how it happened
Elon Musk to you know his story is weird oh my gosh yeah so all of this is
predetermined and pre put out and the easiest one to see that is glaringly out
there that most people miss is the vacuum cleaner guy I mean come on right
you got more play on vacuum cleaners than like new movie trailers that were
coming out so it's not natural guys it's not you know so this aspect yes you do
live in a controlled environment and that mechanism that apparatus that
structure that puts these guys with that makes vacuum cleaners more exciting than
whatever these guys will come after you so you have to be prepared but here's
the thing if the timing is right it won't it won't be as bad it'll still be
pretty bad how many times have you heard of people being you know things that are
accepted in society today but the inventors were like pretty much hung
from a lamppost for doing it right but now it's accepted so this is the part so
let's say you develop a medical system around that the body is a sealed
biological vacuum it's slightly minus pressure than the exterior environment
regardless of the creature whether it's a plant bird animal insect or whatever
human once you start moving forward there's going to be a lot of casualties
right so but maybe the purpose of saying this at least you don't you don't want to
be a casualty you know a lot of people say you got to stand up for your rights
right you hear that all the time I say that's great but if you know they're
fixing on smashing heads maybe you should take a seat for that day