Rated Y 134 gotta tell you, Greg, it's been a weird week.
You know, have you noticed electronic disturbances because I'm getting reports from all over
the place.
People are having trouble with their Internet trouble with their electricity.
Is there is there something in the ether at the moment?
Yeah.
Well, I thought it was what I was doing here.
Oh, maybe.
No, but not for everyone.
I thought maybe that's a reprieve.
I've been doing a lot of weather work here and you could have some people that are following
and they say, yeah, man, I'm looking at the satellite and storms when you say you're gonna
do something for them right over where you are at the center.
I'm like, yeah, well, and here's another here's another question I have for you, actually.
And I didn't broach this off air or anywhere.
And I'm just going to surprise you with it.
Do you have anything to do with the weird changing of direction of Debbie?
Because no, I didn't do anything.
But I'm sure from their meteorological stuff, they have what's called wind shear, where
one storm can, you know, like billiards, you know, one can bump the next, right?
As also a void area, high pressure could also bump it.
So no, I didn't pay any attention to that.
I don't really do hurricanes anymore or major storm mitigation unless I'm getting compensated.
The last one I did, which was Lee, which was phenomenal, largest storm to form an eight
hour and they never saw a category five form in eight hours.
Right.
And I stopped it from moving, shut it down.
And then the next day came back category five and shut it down again without compensation.
Someone sent me a bunch of Federal Reserve notes demanding lawful money for me to do
it.
So I said, all right, fuck, yeah, I'll do it.
So, yeah.
Hey, why not?
But a weird thing happened because where I am, we were being warned that there was going
to be all this flooding and get ready for it.
And it did nothing.
Yeah.
Nothing.
It's hitting New York is what I see now.
It was hitting New York.
Right.
It steered away from here.
It hit Florida a bit and then decided to skip Georgia.
You know, which was like really weird.
Yeah.
Good.
I've only been doing local ops for a year.
We have there's a there's an op.
There's a map that I sent out for rainfall for the last month here locally.
And I live right in the middle of town.
And you could see we're right where I was last month.
It rained four and a half inches, like a few about a mile out.
It's three inches.
And then another mile out.
It's two inches.
All these inches that I mentioned go out in a radius pattern out from the center.
Now, usually you don't get that kind of rain in the center of town because that's the least
there's no rain magnets.
There's no trees.
There's no mountains.
Right.
So where the rain was supposed to be going was the least amount of rain and where it's
not supposed to be going was the most.
I'll post that map up in chat.
Let's see.
I think it's an image right now.
I'll find it somewhere.
I'll send it to you and then you could post it or someone will.
But what.
So, OK, this is what I did.
I'm just coaching a couple of people about this.
This is basically weather work one on one.
I put up I don't think I sent you any of the videos of the device, the recent device.
It's a remaking of an old device and someone else has reproduced it and someone else is
going to reproduce it with success.
But it's the kind of device that you have a clear blue sky.
You put it out in 15 minutes, you get clouds and within an hour or two, you have rain.
That's pretty potent device.
Right.
It's a pretty, pretty interesting device at a rate of 75 to 80 percent.
Now, I was told by a colonel at Fort Huachuca Army Intelligence.
They had me do demonstrations back in 2013, 15 demonstrations.
And the back word was that after I was done, if this guy can do forget gets three out of
the 15, he's the real deal.
I got 11 out of the 15 and it was so abrupt that they were telling me, all right, tomorrow
put rain down over here.
OK, shit.
That's that's a really short call.
So I would put rain down.
I could see it on the satellite.
But then I go to the forecast and it shows sunny.
No chance of rain.
Right.
Like I can't be because you could see the satellite, you know.
So what I had to do to get boots on the ground confirmation is give you a place with Sarah
Vista in the dry season.
So what I did was, all right, how do I find I don't know anyone there.
Yeah.
So I went to the Yellow Pages online and I found a 7-Eleven on Fry Road, Fry Boulevard,
the main road.
And I called them and I said, hey, I'm driving into Sarah Vista.
Is it raining there?
They're like, fuck, it's raining.
Just came out of nowhere.
Thanks.
Bye.
Right.
That's how you do it.
So if you want to throw rain down on the city, it shows no chance of rain and it's not raining,
but you could see it on the satellite.
You just call a convenience store because they're open all the time.
Right.
And they could tell people, it's not like an office building where you haven't been
out.
We only go out for lunch.
You know, I don't know, man.
You know, so people are walking in and out, right?
Yeah.
No, you're guaranteed.
You're guaranteed front windows, at least at a convenience store.
Right.
Yeah.
Windows and people coming in and out.
And that too.
Right.
So people are going to come in and out with umbrellas, be wet, whatever.
So you're going to know.
Or they'll pull up with wet cars, even though it's not raining there yet.
Yep.
So.
Exactly.
So that's what I do to get boots on the ground confirmation.
But OK, the advice I give people when they get started with me on certain things is it
when you wherever wherever you are doing this on the northern hemisphere above the equator,
it's going to take 10 to 14 days to come back to you, meaning around the conveyor.
No one is the norm.
It doesn't matter if it's flat or round.
If you think it's round, it will go around the northern hemisphere.
If you think it's flat, it just forms that circle.
The inner circle.
Right.
OK, so and I told I said this about a month ago, what you'll see happening is if you're
trying to make rain here in the US, especially on the West Coast, Southwest, you're going
to get really hot weather a few days to a week later.
What you'll see in Europe is very hot weather, no rain, unusually hot, like, you know, Spain,
France, Greece, Turkey.
And then what you'll see about another four or five days later is torrential rains in
northern Asia, Korea, especially in Japan.
Well, this is exactly what happened in the past three weeks.
Very hot in Europe.
And the other I think last week, North Korea has got flooded.
I mean, all of North Korea got flooded.
Right. So it's very you got rugged territory there, mountains and stuff.
But all lowlands were flooded.
Right. This is typical.
And also when you look at what's called the jet streams, they don't go across in this
fractal, random, wavy pattern.
What you start to see is the omega, the Greek letter omega forming over major areas, just
like the omega, you know, with the two kind of flat spots and then upside down.
Right. You. Yeah.
Like an upside, like a horseshoe upside, like a horseshoe with the two little flanges on
the bottom. So that's what you'll see forming.
And that was forming everywhere, too.
So now it's OK. So when you do weather work, what is it, drink responding, do it
responsibly, right, because it goes around the entire conveyor and that's how it
works. But you know what I have to say, look, if you don't like the bad weather you're
getting because I'm making good weather here, call me and we'll set you up with a
device so you can bounce it off.
Right. You lay it off.
It's hot potato. It's what it is.
So, yeah, I'm getting a I turned on another computer that I had and I was starting to
do a media portfolio, you know, from back then, you know, from back in 2010 till like
2015 or 17 when I was the most active.
OK. So, yeah, OK, I got it.
Well, what's what's interesting there is, is it possible that somebody else did this that
I'm asking you about?
We're just. Yeah, there is.
But generally there's not that many people that can engineer.
OK. Anybody could go out and by accident, you can accidentally build one of these
devices with junk and not know what it does and it'll do it.
But it'll be very random when you're constantly hitting the stream from an
engineer. OK, so when you're doing the weather engineering perspective, what is
engineering? These are the current conditions, right?
Let's say there's no rain in a particular geographic location and there's no rain in
the forecast for 10 days, 20 days.
It's not foreseeable. And also it's not the rainy season.
So what we're going to do is we're going to engineer rain by doing this blocking
here, blocking the flow from here and allowing this other flow to speed up.
And then when the two come together, what?
Right. OK, right.
All right. So but when you do that and it happens, that's really a that's a plus.
You know, that's a success. Right.
But when it happens, the you have to follow, like I said, the streams as they go
around the globe or the flat earth or whatever, what you want to believe in.
Right. And you will see what I just stated earlier.
Right. So what you're saying about Debbie and all that?
No, I didn't do it. But OK, so let's just recap on Debbie, which was something the
storm or hurricane didn't really form, came up the middle.
Right. And then it started supposed to go to you.
And then it went up. Now it's up in New York area or something.
So what that is, that's that's what I call sheer, probably.
But but here's the thing.
This has been reported several times, whether you want to believe it or not, about
ninety nine percent of the weather can be controlled.
So if I'm loosely speaking on it here and showing other people, by the way, the other
people that I'm showing how to do weather work or skeptics, they're not like, oh, I
wish I could do the weather. Finally, I found someone.
No, no, no, no. It's nothing like that.
So I heard you could do the weather.
What a crock of shit.
Right. That's the majority, I bet, of anybody who's actually going to get into this.
OK, let me just see this not work for myself is what I'm going to do.
But even with that high level of skepticism, it works because it's I'm not into the
woos. So look, this is this is like if I I've said this many times, I won't discuss
anything that that's too personally based on anyone.
I only discuss things that are technically accessible, meaning anyone, once you know
how to do it, you can do it.
Right. It's like, you know, imagine driving a car was a natural talent.
There'd be hardly any cars, people in cars, let's say, conveying and motorized wagons,
right? Engine driven wagons.
But because it's something that you can technically access, you know, even on a small
ritualistic level, if you turn this wheel left and right, the thing goes left and right.
If you push one pedal, it goes the other pedal.
It stops. That's all you need to know.
You're what you're off to the races, let's say.
Right. OK, that's because you technically access it.
In other words, how do I do that?
You tell them and it works.
OK, there are other things that are naturally you heard about, like psychics, right?
Like the police use them, right?
Naturally, someone.
Yeah. OK.
You know, and I've gone into where why they're psychic before.
We don't need to get into that again.
But it's not them.
Everyone, if one everyone has the same ability, it's just with them.
It's accentuated because of the reasons that I've stated in the past for one of the
reasons. Now, another thing is like Yo-Yo Ma, the cellist at four years old, he's
playing concert cello and fuck out of here.
That's a natural talent, right?
Because there's people that go.
Yeah, there's people that go maybe not at four, but like nine.
But but, you know, yeah.
So I don't discuss those things because it's it's no matter how much you discuss
it, you still can't you won't be able to do it.
Why not discuss things that anyone could pick up and do?
That's that's my hallmark.
Right.
No, it makes perfect sense.
And look, speaking of things that anybody can access.
Right. We've talked a lot about the medical stuff, and I know that's always a
curiosity as well.
And I did know a couple of questions a little ways back, and I wasn't just from my
own head. I was going to ask you about something because I've been having troubles
lately and I've been trying to use compression to change up
different problems I'm having with, say, sensations.
Right. I got a numbness in my hand and I'm trying to bring it back around because it
sort of fell asleep weeks ago and I got this hand that feels like it's asleep.
For how long? Fell asleep, like stayed asleep or fell asleep for a few minutes like
normally?
No, no, no. What happened is I went to sleep, like sleep, sleep and woke up.
And, you know, you wake up and you've been laying on your arm or something and you
go, oh, crap. And you got to shake it a minute and then it gets better.
You know what I mean? And the sensation comes back.
Well, it didn't come back about six weeks ago.
Yeah. Six weeks later.
OK, yeah, that's a yin.
Because if it happened, it started off when you were asleep, which is the most yin
state you could be. Right.
Right. And still have some yang to protect you.
You still you woke up. So that means there's yang there, too.
It's not just yin. That's a yin state.
So the thing to fire that thing back up is it's stuck in a yin state because yin
is spread out. It's not focused or anything.
So if it's you don't have feeling in it, it's it's you know, it's more yin than
yang. Right. So you have a very yin.
It's it's probably the left hand.
Right. No, it's actually the right hand, which is a big problem for me.
Yeah. Well, OK. So because the left is the left is where it goes down.
So the yin goes up on the right.
So it's it's yin going up, but it's it's bypassing
the hand and it's manifesting a stuck zone of yin on the right.
I have to think about it, because that's where the energy on the right hand is,
where the energy goes up. Right.
From so if you're standing with your hands, your fingers pointed, the tips of your
fingers pointed towards the floor or the ground.
Right. What's literally happening is the energy around your body is going up
through your right arm and then going down out through your left.
Right. Right. So so there's a block.
So that's going to affect other things as well, unless it's coming in at the wrist
or elbow, which would be much more difficult.
Right. Because you can look at the surface area.
It's very small. Right. More young.
And what I did, what I attempted was compression, you know, around the forearm,
thinking that that's where the forearm I would do compression on the hand itself.
Wrap each individual digit starting from the tips towards the heart.
And you go to the next figure finger for starting at the tip towards the heart.
Right. Never wrap away from the heart.
Right. So you know what I mean? Right. Right. Right.
Now, what would you suggest I wrap it with anything?
Banana peels, anything. Doesn't matter. Doesn't matter.
OK, doesn't matter. I keep old sheets for that reason.
You know, when sheets get threadbare and they start getting holes or they rip easy.
Yeah, I got it. I cut up t-shirts for the same reason.
Good. Yeah. Don't throw them away.
Yeah. What if you really want long term storage on fabrics that are natural?
Get a pot of boiling water, throw the sheet in there and boil it for 10 minutes
and then dry it. That'll sanitize it. Right.
So you don't take it out like years later and it's sour. Right. Right.
So, you know, years ago, they're really good launderers, by the way.
That's what they did every day.
If you ever watch an old film
about old cultures, when they go to the laundry part of town,
it's all these boiling vats. Right. Mm hmm.
So that's that's autoclaving.
You know, they still do it, you know, in medical or whatever, supposedly.
Yeah. And keep sheets around.
So now you have a sheet you can tear into custom little bands.
You know, bands as bands, you know, several long bands. Right.
What I what I would do is cut one two feet long, wrap your finger, let it hang
or wrap it around the palm and then go to the end.
Also, when I say go towards the heart.
So you start with the pinky finger first. Right. OK.
And then the ring finger and then the thumb,
then the forefinger and your middle finger last.
All right. And sometimes you want to give the middle finger first,
but not this time. Right. Gotcha.
So, OK. And middle finger last and across the palm.
And then just do it to the wrist.
But don't focus on tying it on the wrist.
And that's your compression for the hand.
So what that will do, that will decrease the vacuum
in the hand because you've compressed it.
So the body will say we have too much vacuum in the hand.
So let's release the vacuum
because you've made the volume smaller. Right. OK.
Right. Actually, when you make the volume smaller,
with the same vacuum, the vacuum. Right.
The vacuum goes down.
Right. And it'll balance it out.
But then when you remove the bandages, the hand will expand.
And whatever that low state of it,
you'll have an immediate boost of vacuum. Right. Right.
And that's how you play with with the vacuum, the yin and yang,
because yin and yang is also vacuum.
But that's that's what I would do for the compression.
Definitely on the hand and that should fix it.
But remember, the longer it takes, the longer you have it,
whatever it is, the harder, the longer it's going to take to. Right.
Right. Of course. Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, like with a wound,
you treat a wound like we've been saying it heals in two days.
If you decide to do that a week later, it's not going to it's going to,
you know, it's not going to help. Yeah. Right.
The longer it sits, the longer it sits unattended, the longer it takes to heal.
I have a term for that. It's facilitating the injury.
OK. Yeah. So time facilitates the injury if it's untreated.
That's right. Yeah. And so it's like that would make like you say,
it's people's character. You're dealing with someone.
You're like, why is this person like, let's say, always making excuses.
Right. What do they say? They're set in their ways.
Which means, yeah, exactly.
You try to remedy it and they still they don't want to do it.
You know, it's like, oh, I've always done this.
Well, who's this guy now telling me? Right. Same thing with the body.
Even if you know, the reason why people build up an infection,
it's the body making balance.
And we try to treat the infection.
It's like another injury that you're causing now, believe it or not.
But, you know, sometimes the body makes balance.
It could even kill you to make balance.
What do you think of people dying in car accidents?
Is those people were so out of whack
that the only way that the universe could put them in balance
is by having them whacked in a car accident?
I'm serious. This is when you start looking at things in a big perspective.
Well, same way with the social perspective.
Well, let me let me ask you if something that I've observed is is correct.
And maybe this will make sense since you bring this up,
because I was thinking about this recently and I didn't mention it to you.
But, you know, it seems to me that those that die rather suddenly,
those that have their lives interrupted, you know, pretty abruptly
are only two classes of people, the really, really way
too good people or really bad people, like people that are destructive
to others or people that are just so out of balance that.
Yeah, that act, that quick end actually put the rest of the whole
entire existence in balance.
It's almost like if you're too good or too bad, you got to go, you know?
Well, yeah, the society, you know, a lot of people
complaining about the government, the bad food, their talk poisoning us.
And they're telling us it's good for us.
It's that, you know, that is actually from an overarching perspective.
These social things that are happening that are negative for the population
from an overarching, large cosmic perspective.
That's the cosmos making balance.
It's like this is a really wackadoo society.
Let's get them, inspire them to start toxifying.
You know, the people that they look up to will start poisoning them
and telling them it's good for them.
That's how we go.
It'll take, you know, 30, 40, 50, 100 years to eliminate them.
But let's just set them off in that direction to balance the overall.
You see? Right.
That's why I keep saying that you never say you want to make the world
a better place because it's fine. It's supposed to be this way.
What are you going to do for yourself once you know better?
If you don't know better, it's fine, right?
I guess it's good, you know, with ignorance is bliss.
Yeah, it's been said many times, many times, many ways.
All right. Anyways, it's yeah, it's one of those things.
So balance, it seems to me as though nature and maybe this is wrong
because it's not just nature and maybe I'm just oversimplifying it.
But nature does seek to balance itself one way or another.
You know, life recycles itself
and then finds a way when it's necessary and finds a way to end when it's not.
It's the also, you know, the term piss, you know, getting pissed on and pissed
or whatever is the popular term.
It's there's an art called Doween.
I think it's spelled deal hyphen.
I am. It's like a self stimulation.
Then, OK, ladies, we're talking about just Asian stuff here.
But maybe their batteries are done.
OK, so so what you what is is
imagine standing and take your right hand to make a light fist.
And with that light fist, start tapping your left arm
all the way from your hand up to your shoulders and neck
and then reverse and do that.
And then you do like your back and you're outside of your legs all the way down.
OK, what that's doing is stimulating the bladder meridian.
And this is the athletes that were prone to injury.
I would show to do that.
They would no longer have injuries or crashes or falls or whatever
because the body's trying to make best.
And that's the bladder meridian.
It's the largest meridian, the most around the entire outside
of the entire body is the bladder meridian.
And that requires the most stimulation.
So let's say you're riding your bike and you keep crashing
or you're one of the people that are known to crash often.
If you start doing Doween, right, you will crash less.
And this is also more important for people who are like boxers or wrestlers
or any sport, any sport, right?
Yeah. Or physical.
Let's say you work in construction.
Very important, right?
Anything physical to do doing the stimulation of the outer
peripheral of the body.
There was also there's also other forms of doing that were taught to warriors,
fighters, people that were going into battle
and lessened your chance of getting a hit or getting hit.
And it's the bladder meridian.
So I just want to bring that up, you know, making best.
In other words, if you know the body requires a certain amount of stimulation
and if you don't offer it or it doesn't encounter that,
it will happen anyway in a way that you maybe don't like.
Why don't you do it?
You know, right.
Why don't you do it preemptively?
So that's called going deal.
I am going is in Japanese and doing or doing
or going, going in Chinese.
You know, it's kind of like Jane.
So a lady named Jane from China, the name tag.
I said, oh, what was your name in China?
She was saying, I said, that's close enough.
That's how it works.
So doing.
Yeah, that happens a lot with with with people that come from other places.
They adopt a name. It's funny.
A lot of completely different.
Yeah, but it's good when it's.
Well, names are names are exempt from.
Translation, so whatever your name sounds like
is what it should be in any language spelled phonetically.
That's why when I ask people, is it so what sound do you answer to?
And I'm like, what? I said, what's your name?
Well, what's your name? It's something you answer to, right?
It's a sound that you answer to. True.
Meaning if you're totally unfamiliar with the language,
people are having a conversation.
Go to someone who's unfamiliar with the language.
So how many times did you mention his name?
I don't know what the hell they're talking about. Right.
So they're all sounds to you. Right.
Yeah. So how can we react to this sound?
And look, he's reacting to this sound right now, but punching the guy in the face.
Oh, wow. Look at that.
And you know that if you're in a crowded restaurant
and you hear your own name, you know, being said, right.
You like I'm sitting somewhere and I hear, you know, Chuck over there.
I go, I turn my head because I'm thinking it must be me.
That's the sound that you respond to.
That is the sound I respond to.
That's right. You know, names. That's all names.
Yeah, absolutely.
When you put a number on it, it becomes a beneficiary trust.
So we got into that a little bit.
We did get into that recently. Yes.
And there's more. There's a lot more to get into it.
It's fun when you do it.
I could tell you a story about a drug dealer
that was in there for a little while and Tennessee. OK.
And he shot TBI officer, a detective. OK.
And he was the detective was posing as a buyer
and he shot him in the head, killed him.
So he was in prison in Tennessee. Right.
And he runs into Chris.
Chris, like you said, what do I do?
And give me a death penalty.
Well, maybe we could do something.
I'll give you a death penalty.
By the way, he got out of jail doing this.
Oh, I'm going to tell you.
This is all right. Let me think about it.
I'll give you an answer tomorrow.
So they got together
and he says, all right, back in the 80s,
Ronald Reagan declared a war on drugs and it was written up as a war.
Congressionally and all that.
So because you're being charged with drug felony
and the homicide and all this and it's a war, you're an enemy combatant.
You can't be treated as a civilian.
So what they're doing to you by trying to give you the death penalty
is against the U.N. and Geneva Convention.
Right. You can't execute prisoners, right?
You can't go pick up every and you can't go pick up every soldier
that battled you in a war afterwards.
You know, yeah, in a lawful.
Yeah. So anyway, he says, go in there.
He says, just tell your lawyer that tells the lawyers.
Oh, if I tell him that, I'll pull my license away. Right.
So it's OK. So he goes up there.
He says, yelling in the court, all this stuff out.
Yeah. And there's more to it.
But he's basically because of the war on drugs.
I am an enemy combatant.
I'm a combatant.
And what you're doing to me here is against the Geneva Convention,
the United Nations.
I'm going to I'm filing.
I'm actively filing a report and a complaint to the Hague.
They were like, holy shit.
Is that cool?
That is really because that is really I mean, think about that.
That is fucking cool.
So that's what this law they call it lawfare.
Now it's fine.
It's actually my cup of tea.
I love because you have to think outside the box. Right.
But how far outside?
That's not really that far outside the box to say that I'm in jail
because I'm a drug dealer and I shot an undercover cop and killed him.
How far of a leap is it to say, well, it's war?
I'm a combatant. How far?
Because everybody everybody's been told about the war on drugs.
Everyone for years. Absolutely.
So where is where? How far outside the box is that?
It's not really. It's just right.
Right in the box, isn't it?
Not at all. It's right. Right.
And right up their alley, because if they have a legal declaration, right,
they're supposed to adhere to their legal.
So now we're talking about combatants.
Since when do like county jails handle warfare combatants?
You know, they don't. Yeah, they don't.
It's international law. It's Geneva Convention, dude.
So they yeah, it goes on and on.
He he went to the transfer him to a more minimal thing.
He's out. They gave him parole, like 15 years paroling.
A month later, they called him in.
This is not just three months parole.
And two weeks later, they called him. You're off parole. You're done.
Wow. They went from 15 years to three months to two.
So two weeks he was finished.
They're in and out. Yeah. Yeah.
That's the truth. Right.
It's what he what he was saying was actually the truth.
Well, they wanted him the hell out of there.
So he didn't tell somebody.
Well, they wanted him dead to get that bond.
He was on death row, ready to be put
on death row.
Because yeah, right before you go to death row, they have another trial. Right.
Yeah. No, it's just really cool.
I like that legal thinking.
You see, it's it's all legal, but it's always it's a shame and the pathetic
how we're told about the human body.
You have to go to a doctor and for law, you go to a lawyer.
Everyone should be thinking about medical practices.
The word practice, by the way, is that corporate thing to
in medical has usually to do with administering pharmaceuticals,
but should think about their biology and should think about the rule and order
and law constantly.
You should always be thinking about those things constantly and developing them.
So law and medicine, they both they call them both practices.
You know, that's the corporate side.
That's a term used by the United States.
So it used to be shell shock years ago.
Now it's PTSD because shell shock was an actual condition,
you know, whatever.
But PTSD is something that the bankers have trademarked.
So they can monetize that.
They can't monetize a bond when someone gets bonded,
medically bonded with a condition.
They monetize that shell shock.
You see, it's just like when you look at your states, they're spelled out.
But with those little two letter abbreviations,
those are trademarked by the Federal Reserve. Right.
Right. So the things you use in your mailing codes like Georgia's
mailing codes, language codes, you know, all over the now
the Internet is another government itself.
They're doing another thing with the Internet.
It's another.
So someone recently messaged me about a confused about Arizona or this or that.
I said, no, no.
What you're confused about is everything you hear about on television
that's political.
And they mention a political geographic area.
They're not talking about the geography. Right. Right.
There is no United States.
There is no state of Georgia, state of Arizona.
There is no such thing.
It's a corporation, right?
It has no geographic could be anywhere.
Title 28, section 3002, subsection 15A.
Right. You could be is no geographic.
And that's why it's conferring nationality.
That's when a cop pulls you over.
Let's say if you're going to Tennessee, you run a red light.
So the first thing says, you know, in the state of Tennessee, it's illegal.
They always say, or if you're in Georgia, they before they tell you
why they're arresting you or giving you a ticket on the state of Georgia,
what they're doing there when they say state of the United States,
they're conferring nationality.
You say, oh, I disagree about that national nationality statement there.
But you move a little too fast right now for the purposes of this arrest.
I'm in Antarctica or for the purpose.
And no one can tell you you're not because when you say Antarctica,
it's not talking about the geography.
It's where you're conferring your nationality.
It gets complicated because you've never heard this before.
But if you were raised
knowing this, you'd say, Greek, why are you talking to me?
I should have any better thing better to say. We know that. Right.
I don't know too many people that know that.
That's for sure. Yeah. You see.
So, yeah. So it's interesting.
And we have so much doubt.
If you have the, quote unquote, the law on your side
and everyone, including the judges, lawyers, your family,
it's like that's not how it is. What are you going to do?
Stick with the law. Stick with it.
Because they'll just they'll capitulate.
They'll capitulate.
I mean, just like these guys that call them sovereign citizens or whatever.
They go into court. They start.
It's all, Judge, I have not before.
I'm here in form of proper, a jury jurist in form of proper.
This is not pro se, pro se.
You really get no jurisdiction.
And I'm telling this goddamn court, you judge up there, you start cursing.
And they're like, they can't do anything to you
because you haven't they haven't gotten jurisdiction yet.
I don't recommend doing that.
But just be yourself and be angry.
Be really upset, because they even if you're sitting in jail for a long time,
you start getting upset about the jurisdiction.
They're going to figure out a way to get you out, dump you into another prison,
because remember, they when they transfer bonds, they get a commission. Right.
Oh, yeah. Right.
So and then that that that I've heard that says, oh,
they want me to be somebody else's problem.
Well, you don't have to stay.
Right. So that's your question.
The jurisdiction was so many jurisdictional issues.
So many because all the law says it has to be a competent authority
in government.
These are all listed on Dun & Bradstreet.
How are they a competent authority?
That says a corporation cannot be a government.
And the government cannot be a corporation.
So you stick with all that.
I always tell people, stick with it.
You do the right thing.
It's a lot of people are afraid of the IRS. Same thing.
IRS, every time you do something right, you get a response from the IRS says,
yes, we got your letter about this as Congress has ratified
or has Congress has approved always.
And if they send you a nasty letter saying you sound like a tax protester
and we are taxing you because Congress has.
So whenever you deal with the IRS, everything has to do with Congress,
not when you look for law, stick with stuff that's in Congress has done.
That's because they're working with right.
Congress that Mark Twain said the most dangerous thing to America
is when Congress goes to session. Right.
Yeah. So I just give up the little tidbit.
People like trying to go away.
So the IRS, they go try to pull things here.
They're no, no, no.
Stick with what Congress actions of Congress.
And they'll they'll recognize that right away.
That's what they're trained to do.
It's interesting to find out
how when you're dealing with an agency or a group, even a group,
let's say you want to become a Freemason.
You don't know anything about Freemason, but you want to be one.
Isn't it good to find out
what their inner workings and inner rules are first?
Not what you think they are, what they say they are.
Right. Right.
Well, whatever. Boy Scouts, anything.
I don't recommend any of those associations.
But what I'm saying is find out how they work internally
when you work in the IRS internally.
They're always saying there are people where you see Congress,
you know, blah, blah, blah.
That's why we do this in Congress.
When they send you a letter, Congress, you need a pro or con.
It's Congress.
So guess what? You're going to look for
stuff that Congress has in Europe that will work for you. Right. Right.
Yeah. Demand for lawful money for twelve, four, eleven.
They look like, yeah, OK, cool.
Congress says that's right.
Anything else start hitting you with fines and arguing when
I'm not a citizen?
You know, there's so many other these is a whole bunch of auto workers
that knew about the W-8 Ben filed, and they people working on auto factories,
you know, in America haven't get no withdrawal taken out of their check for decades
because they filed W-8 Ben.
All right. Anyway, so
and then the IRS says you can't file W-8 Ben.
As you say, I'm not a U.S. citizen, even though they're born here.
Right. U.S. citizen means you're a citizen of the United States,
which is somewhere in the District of Columbia.
Right. Everyone has the mistake that the United States is in
is the District of Columbia.
No, it's in the District of Columbia.
So you go to the District of Columbia and you start driving around.
Look for the United States.
You'll never find it.
There's no specific location.
Same with state of Arizona.
Where is state of Arizona or state of Georgia?
Go down to the ability.
Where is the state of this is the address.
OK, I'm at this address.
Where is the state of Arizona?
Where is the show?
Never going to find it.
That's all what you pledge to.
Right. But by the way, I'm a citizen of slow Jamestown.
Slow. Yeah, you know, like at night, the DJs play slow jams.
I got you. I got you.
I took you a second there.
I'm like, slow jam is what?
But I got it. Yeah, it's it's a real place, by the way.
It's also they do have they could make conferred your geographic location.
Look it up to put in the kingdom of slow jam.
There's a king, too. He's pretty cool.
He is a DJ to put in.
I'm doing it right now. Kingdom.
OK, of slow jam and stand.
Well, you got to sign up to be a citizen, too.
And you could you got to pay if you want a passport.
Here you go. What does it say?
You do it slow. Jamestown just says it's J.A.M.A.
Founded on December 1st, 2021 by slow jam DJ Randy Williams.
So Jamestown is located in an empty part of desert state Route 78.
Micronation political entity that claims independence.
Well, if you go to images.
Yeah, he is actually he was accepted by the embassy of Cuba.
He went to Cuba.
Because right now, you know, if you're a U.S. citizen, you don't go to Cuba.
But if you're in slow Jamestown, you can't. Right.
Yeah, he has a border patrol.
He does. He's only right there.
So one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, eight people
and seven people in his cabinet in him. You see it.
Anyway. Wow.
Are you able to pull it up?
I'm trying to pull it up, but my browser is giving me trouble.
Oh, that's why slow and then Jamestown.
Yeah. All A's.
Yeah, it's a real place.
And you go to their site and you sign up your citizen.
If you want a passport, they have passports and all that, too.
Yeah. Now, it says it's not recognized by the United States,
but the all the codes and the statutes and the law says that
how to confer national, how to create a nation.
Basically, you have to do is be at peace.
And Brandon, Joe Williams goes over this.
And you don't have to be recognized by any other nation to be a nation.
So a lot of times when they when they bring them up in the media,
it is not recognized by the United States.
It doesn't have to be.
I got the Republic of Slow Jamestown website here.
Yeah, there you go. Yeah.
I wrote Kingdom, but it's the Republic.
OK, so like, for example, Cuba doesn't exist
because the United States doesn't recognize it.
Ho, ho, ho, ho.
What a crock of shit, right?
OK, I see.
Randy R. Dubb Williams is the soldier.
Yeah, I want to go sign up.
The sultan of Slow Jamestown, the sultan of Slow Jamestown.
There's another micronation in Nevada is a few micronations.
Yeah. And you do have some certain amenities.
Yeah, he's going to you.
I think he went to a California court on a traffic ticket.
I think he beat it because of that beat.
You know, so I'm going to go look up and see what how he did with it.