Another Sonic event, Ocelli in the Greek Rated Y, and Greek, but let's just start this way.
What day is it?
Let's begin with time.
Well, it's whatever day you want it to be, right?
Fun day, whatever day, right?
I'm reckoning around the 19th of the 7th month.
19th of the 7th month.
Yeah, around there.
So we, so in other words, this, this was pretty close to the Pope's work schedule, but it's
drifting again.
Like last month was a day off.
Now it's two or three days off.
Yeah.
Cause as I see it right now on the Pope's work schedule, yeah, it's the 19th day of
the 12th.
Yeah.
Well, it's the 16th day of the 12th, excuse me, 16th day of the 12th month.
So we're at about three days.
Cause it was about three, it was like the 28th or something, 29th, 16th day, 12th, 9th
month, according to that.
But of course, September makes no sense because Sept is seven.
So why are we doing it?
No, no.
September makes sense, but calling it the ninth month doesn't.
That's what I was saying is that I said ninth month, so I'm, I'm all screwing it up.
But the point is, and that's, that is the point, isn't it?
September.
September makes sense.
October makes sense.
But calling October the 10th month doesn't make sense.
Right.
Calling, right?
December the 12th month doesn't make sense at all.
No.
Sept should be seven.
Right.
Oct should be eight.
Eight, right.
I mean, octo, octagon, et cetera.
I mean, we know this, but yeah, the shape of my head tonight.
Yeah.
Octagon.
Sure.
Anyway, I was joking.
Yeah.
Why not?
Look, it could be because you're not from this planet.
That was a question from a while ago.
I don't remember if we answered it.
That's if you think it's a planet, but either way, what planet is the Greek from was the
question.
Oh man.
That's the thing.
I think that does it.
That part doesn't matter.
It doesn't affect anything.
What planet is any of us from?
You know, look, just because we say it's something called Earth doesn't mean that that's not
what somebody looking at it, you know, in their sky.
Well, it's not.
There's an old saying.
It's not where you're from.
It's where you're at, where you're going.
Right.
But yeah.
Well, bring up.
Timekeeping came up in a tangential way in the past few days, and I was thinking of doing
that more pedantically, you know, meaning doing detail, a lot of detail that almost
hurts.
Oh boy.
On the solo sonics.
And I haven't abandoned that project is a lot.
There's a 200 hours of stuff there.
What's happening is I'm in an all consuming rage and developing water stuff right now.
And we've gotten to the point where if in all seriousness, if I go public with what
can be done with almost very little, your life would probably be threatened back in
the days.
Right.
Like what I mean by that?
You know, Bill Cooper and all these guys, right, if they did what they did now, I think
they'd be OK.
Right.
They just had a different approach.
Oh, yeah.
Back then.
You know what I mean?
Well, look, so you can get away.
You can get away with quite a bit more now because it's a lot easier to get lost, too,
because you could just now be one.
That's just one not screaming that on the Internet.
Who cares?
You can say a great many things that are a little dangerous and not necessarily have
somebody break down your door the next day.
Well, that's presuming, I think, that, see, they know they they they in quotes, air quotes
or whatever, quote those people.
Yeah.
They know that it's not who's saying it's who's listening.
Exactly.
Right.
So that's why you'll never get any airtime on on mainstream because it's not them.
I mean, if you get, let's say, Greek speak on mainstream, that would up the quality,
you know, met a magnitude of ways.
But it's not that you're upping their quality.
It's that's who's listening.
You see, it's always who's listening on the other.
And so.
Right.
So it doesn't say much.
It could go either way.
But yeah, I just want to recap on the weather also that, let's say, from certain channels
I had gotten word before it even went down.
This was designed to really hurt the physical country.
And I did spend quite a bit of time and I got a little signaling back or how do you signal
back?
Remember, I talked about spy versus spy.
Yeah.
Right.
How do I get to bookmark certain things?
And I came back when I decided to slid on the up and those bookmarks had disappeared
and a few other things were rearranged on the screen on the laptop that I'm using.
That's a very subtle way.
Right.
Very, very subtle.
And I noticed the subtle things.
I enjoy it.
Yeah.
And look, you know, and there used to be this thing.
Now, look, I read up when I was very young.
I read up the legend of Charles Manson.
I call it the legend because the truth of that matter, what actually happened, a whole
other thing aside from, you know, the the ghost written book that had Vince Bugliosi's
name on it, you know, and and but I did read that.
And I remember one of the big stories was that for a little bit.
It's strange.
It's a methodology for a little bit, though.
He was having his so-called family members, you know, the girls that he had control over
that were all living at Spawn Ranch.
He would send them into people's houses, not to steal, not to kill.
Nothing like that, but just go in there and move some stuff around and leave.
Do something witchy became the phrase.
But they would go in there and just move things around and spook people a bit.
Now, it's funny to me because I've heard that methodology having been employed by guess
who?
People that are involved in that agency to give a subtle warning to somebody, you're
getting a little close.
So maybe somebody, you know, you come home after you haven't been there for two days.
You live alone and maybe there's a cat in the house.
You know that that hot brewed cup of coffee sitting on your kitchen counter wasn't made
by the cat.
And nobody appears to have been in your house, from what you can tell.
And you haven't been.
I wouldn't mind.
I've got a colony of nine cats, not in the house outside.
But so if the cats were gone, let's say, and the coffee was always hot, I wouldn't be.
I'd be happy with that, actually.
Well, you might be.
But would you trust the coffee you didn't make yourself?
You see.
Anyway.
But my point.
I gotcha.
Sometimes I don't trust the coffee I do make myself.
I'm not.
I'm not paying attention.
Coffee is a very, very meticulous and fine thing to make.
It's actually people talk about wine tasting and such sommeliers.
They taste for about 70 different qualities in the wine, but coffee tasters taste for
over 120.
Anyway, well, there's a lot to it.
I mean, I went and got some of the, you know, more, you know, surface level barista training
and all that.
And a whole lot of things.
Funny.
A whole lot of stuff that you've discussed with food preparation on occasion.
Sounds a lot like what they tell us to do when it comes to barista training, like a
bunch of the things that you're supposed to do to clean things.
You know, the very like, oh, well, I should use a heavy detergent and all this.
Are you crazy?
Don't do that.
You know, like this is the way you're supposed to, you know, make sure everything is wiped
down and all that kind of stuff because transference of oil, et cetera, et cetera.
Very easy thing to do.
So, yeah, they really, you know, yeah, well, how many baristas are a part of the intelligence
agencies, too?
Right.
I think that's where they go.
You know, tack cab drivers, bartenders.
Right.
You know.
Fair enough.
But they do need to be able to do those jobs adequately enough to participate occasionally
as a cover.
But the thing is, like I said, switching paintings from one side of a room to another weird stuff
like that.
Yeah.
You know, that kind of stuff.
It's funny because it's like Manson's family was doing it and they were supposedly just
crazy kids on LSD.
They were not.
They were part of a group out of that canyon in California.
Right.
Affected.
You know what it's like.
You know what I'm talking about.
Yeah.
Laurel Canyon and all that.
But the deal is that it's just funny to me that the methodology is the same and nobody
points that out where, you know, the thing that they were supposedly doing is a prank,
which is funny.
It's not a prank.
It's actually communicating a very sophisticated symbol.
There might even be meaning behind the fact that they decided to shuffle your papers,
you know.
Yeah.
Sure.
But either way.
And before we started, I think I showed you a diagram of a wind map that's that that's
kind of like off the wind map I showed you during the op is just as strange as a UFO landing
on your front lawn and parking there.
Right.
Yeah.
Takes you a minute.
And no one notices.
You know, I mean, I mean, this is very noticeable.
It's like, you know, life is kind of surreal, I'd say, always, always is, always was.
But it depends on what you're paying attention to.
You know, is it surreal or is it just boring as hell because you're only looking down at
three feet of space around your feet?
You know, I just it is what it is.
If you look up, you know, it's just another thing, too.
Before we continue, let me just do a quick shotgun how the day starts at noon.
OK, go ahead.
Really simple.
If you want to just use biblical references before I get into that, if you look up any
of the astronomical references, it's mentioned solar noon is when the day starts for for
scientific and astronomical purposes.
Right. Right.
But the civil changes.
Right. So if you live in a religious whatever they do there, they consider that to be civil.
Right. If you live in a what is it called when you when the country is run by a religion,
theocracy, theocracy.
Yeah. Like Saudi Arabia or parts of Jerusalem, for example, is theocracy, theocratic.
You know, the mayor, you know, they tell you, you know, but if you live in Jerusalem, don't
you can't. There's no there's no public services on the Sabbath, but other parts of Israel
there is. So so but OK, so before I think that's enough to look at, you could look at
also the timekeeping authorities, which is the Greenwich Meantime and the Naval Observatory
in Colorado. They both have websites.
You say the same thing.
Biblical is very easy.
You want to go you want to go the latest in time or there it's all Old Testament, by the
way. New Testament is not a study document.
It's good to read.
OK. And OK. Why?
Well, before I get into this, anything the Catholics put out, the Catholic Church is a
lie, period, anything and everything.
So you want to avoid anything that's endorsed by them.
Now, let's take it a little further.
Don't they tell you the Old Testament has been done away with?
It's all the New Testament anyway, makes it even worse.
So you don't want to read. You want to be familiar with it, of course.
Read it. But I pay it no mind.
It's completely adulterated.
There's there's not much there in terms of study material.
The reason I read the New Testament, obviously, is because it is the only record we
have of what the Christ had said, allegedly.
And it shows what prophecies have been fulfilled, allegedly.
Right. And but if you know how to read the New Testament, then read it.
Boy, did I just confuse people?
If you know how to read it, then you should definitely read it.
But in terms of a general consensus, you're not going to get anything from it.
Because it's been you have to know.
Well, give me an example.
Chuck, you do the research that you do.
If you if you get let's say the CIA puts out a publication, you know how to read it.
Right. Yes. You can tell what part they put in.
That's B.S. and what they're actually leaving in.
Right. Yes, of course.
That's the average people take the whole thing at face value.
Prima facie, you know.
Right. I see this all the time.
Look, you see a document and it says, OK, we're recording this and this is the
memorandum. And people focus on, oh, they said this happened.
And I go, no, that's not the point of the document.
Yeah, it's not the report.
That's a report.
It is your the only thing that's really if you want the book of Matthew, like the
first chapter, if you can really solve that, you know, the genealogy, then you
should continue. I'll leave that.
OK, I'll leave that, because most people say there's an anomaly that says 42
generations. They only count 41.
If you solve it, how there are 42 and not 41 that you count, then you should
continue. But otherwise, you're just playing along the Muppet tree of the of
the current Christian.
By the way, if you're a Christian, you're under you're considered one of the pope's
army. Doesn't matter if you think you're Protestant or Mormon or whatever.
OK, so just on that measure alone, just you got homework to do.
Well, they do. And they do tell you that if you ever read any of the hymns or any
of the other stuff like not. And I don't mean read the whole of it.
I mean, just read the book ends of it, so to speak.
You find it says, look, even the Methodist.
Right. Oh, that's a breakaway from the church.
And I'm like, and no, it's not read their stuff.
It literally says we're under the Catholic Church.
Yeah, all of it. You know.
So but they tell you in their documentation right there, you're going to go sing our
songs. Guess what? You know, you're under the Catholic Church, right?
Yeah, it always is. So it's kind of disgusting.
But that's more than an opinion, by the way.
It's just an unspoken truth.
When you speak bad about something, they'll say, well, you could.
That's his opinion, right?
Mm hmm. My opinion is based on unspoken things, right?
That should be spoken.
By the way. OK, so let's go.
So maybe we'll go backwards in time.
So in other words, the latest one, if you look at the book of Nehemiah, OK, he gave
the crowd a hard time because they were conducting business and the Sabbath had
already started. And before I get into that, he was at the city walls.
Now, the city walls are about 15 or 16, 20 feet thick.
And the way you go through those walls is through a gate.
And those gates are large archways.
Now, if anyone's been in, if you want a good example of what it looks like, look it
up. The gates in Jerusalem, the old city.
Another another example would be in Central Park in certain Central Park in New
York. They have these bridges, these small ornamental stone bridges.
Right. Right.
And they're about 15, 16 feet wide.
Right. So let's go back to Nehemiah.
These gates. So you got it's like an archway that in a wall that's 15 to 20 feet
wide. So he's anyway, go back to Nehemiah.
He's complaining about the Sabbath has begun and he's yelling at people.
Why are you still conducting business?
And what was his what? How did he prompt in the text that the Sabbath had begun?
He says it's dark under the gates.
Mm hmm. Right now, if the gates are up and down on up and down vertical archway in
early morning, the light goes straight in the late.
Right. The sun is low.
The sun is low. So the underside is lit.
I have a low porch in the back in the morning.
It's all completely lit.
Now, at sundown, I have a porch in the front.
It's completely lit because the sun is horizontal.
Light goes right under the arch.
Right. Right. So the only the only way.
The only way it could be dark under the archway is if the sun is directly above it.
You think shadow?
Yeah, if it is daylight around, but it's dark under that archway, then that means,
yeah, it's absolutely noontime.
OK, so that may not be that might be ambiguous.
There's actually a couple of idiots that do YouTube's that bring that up.
I see it's dark, so it must be sundown.
I'm like, oh, my gosh, no, completely moronic.
Yeah, that but that's perfect that they do that because it shows you once you bring up
the subject of religion, whoever is up at the dais or the pulpit, you know, is correct.
Right. They don't know that the person that's up there is there to mislead you.
But because people who know these things don't listen to people like that.
And I'm not really this is not religious.
By the way, I don't believe anything in the Bible.
I use it as a rule book.
Right. It's you're not supposed to believe you're supposed to know.
And I use it as a directive for knowledge.
So I'm not religious. I'm actually anti-religious in the way the
it's set up. OK, back to Nehemiah.
So he prompted that people that it was dark under the archway.
So the Sabbath had begun.
Right. Now, if you're not sure about that, he gives a second example.
The second example is that he says it's the Sabbath and he says, this time, I don't want
you to start doing your business until it gets hot.
Until it begins to get hot at the gate, I want the gates to get hot.
All right. So it's so it's not hot yet.
Not warm, but hot. Right.
So when is that?
When does it begin? Things begin to get hot at noontime as it approaches noon.
The morning is always cool.
Yeah. Take a look at your peeker to your higher temperatures are always in the midst of the
day when the sun is between noon and afterwards.
Yeah. Between noon and three.
Now, it's not sundown because it's starting to cool down.
Right. So he's saying, wait until they heat up.
Right. Okay. So so we know that it has to be dark underneath and it has to be hot.
They have to be heated. So that brings you to noon.
Okay. There's a couple of ambiguous ones in the Book of Kings when things start.
The couple of ambiguous ones that can go either way in the Book of Exodus.
Book of Kings, by the way, when the day starts, it's noontime because they have a new
moon festival. So you go research that.
Notice I'm not giving chapter and verse.
Right. The reason I don't give chapter and verse is these Christian idiots.
Matthew 15, 21, 36, 5, 5.
Right. It's like, oh, my gosh, it's kind of like a Marine sergeant or, let's say, Luke
46, 31 or John 3, 17.
I'm like, oh, my gosh, it sounds like two old beef patty sauce.
Right. Hold the lettuce.
It sounds like a jingle. Right.
They're ridiculous when they do that.
It's kind of like the reason you shouldn't give verse chapter like that, because you
only be on this level, be talking to people who already know it.
Just like, for example, hey, you want to hear chapter and verse.
You see the movie Matrix at four minutes and 32 seconds that what's any better than
that? What? Who?
Who talks about theater and movies and previous events that way?
Hey, only remember in Star Wars at 12 minutes, 31 seconds.
Luke Skywalker busted a nut.
And what? What?
What? What did you say?
Yeah. There used to be a guy.
There used to be what you remind him of is there used to be a guy called Mr.
Skin. And what he did is he would tell you where people were nude in movies.
And that's exactly how he did it at three minutes, 32 seconds of he would do that all
the time. And that's exactly who you find, you know, because, yeah, but it's
ridiculous. That means you don't know what's going on and you're conditioned just
like, you know, people are conditioned.
You talk to people in the corporate world.
Oh, my gosh. Talk about conditioning.
I feel so sorry for them.
But anyway, but only as sorry as like for five seconds.
Right. Because, you know, they don't know.
And when someone doesn't know, you just don't know.
And I'm not here to educate anyone.
I'm just here to share. And if you're willing to pick up the pieces and put them
together, that's great. So you notice I don't give verses.
So Booker Nehemiah, when he talks about the Sabbath and the gates, by the way, it's
around chapter seven and chapter 13 around there, like the middle of the book.
Right. OK.
OK, so the one in David, the one with Kings is regarding like when he meets all
about the New Moon Festival starting and he could tell it's daytime.
Also, when he meets Jonathan in the field, you can tell it's noontime the next day
if you understand the setting.
But let's go to the beginning.
There was evening and there was morning the first day.
OK, so when does evening end?
Right. And when does morning end?
Right. Where does evening begin?
It seems like evening begins when morning ends.
Right. So you could look at it that way.
OK, so now if you look at it, Edeb.
You know how they say I've seen this with people, you know, be like twelve or one
and they'll say good morning and like it's twelve or one.
Oh, I'm sorry. Good afternoon.
Right. Notice that. Yeah.
Or or it'll be eleven fifty nine by the wind up tour and they go good afternoon.
Oh no, it's eleven fifty nine.
You have to say good morning. Right.
You notice that? Yes.
Yeah. Because people are very rigid.
They don't know the conditioning is very, very strong.
OK. The same thing is with Edeb.
Even in modern culture, Edeb means good afternoon is noon and all the way
till you go to sleep.
And right before that, the last thing you say to someone would be Laila.
By the way.
Laila, if you don't say like if you're having an evening call six, seven o'clock,
you don't say Laila, you still say Edeb, even if it's eight, nine o'clock.
Right. Only the last thing you say to someone till the next day would be Laila.
And when you're speaking to someone who's Hebrew, when you say Laila, the longer
you say Laila, the more that you like them.
Right. So so very serious.
You'd say Laila and they say Laila, right.
But if you really like them, you go Laila.
And if they go Laila, go back.
They love you, too. It's kind of a funny cultural thing.
I just thought I'd bring it up.
A little sing songy thing that's kind of actually seems to be
pronounced that way in a lot of languages.
People will do that. Stretch it out.
Yeah. But especially in Hebrew.
So anyway, just to keep moving on.
So the Hebrew bracket, I mean, the Edeb also means to be it's the
if you look at the letters, it means to be emanating from the head of the house.
OK, that's what the word literally means to to come out of the head, the top of the house.
So in this case, the house would be the sky.
Right. So where's the top anyway?
Right. The very top.
The apex would be new.
OK, so. Right.
And if it's evening and morning the first day.
So basically it goes from evening to morning.
And when morning ends, your day count ends.
So when does morning end?
And evening begin at noon and noon.
Yeah, it's in your face.
But these things are subtle and they're not discussed.
And don't ever ask me for a chapter in verse.
I think people know that. Right.
So in that way, evening is the beginning of the day because that's afternoon.
And that's exactly the way that evening starts.
Yeah. And when morning ends.
Now, here's the other thing about timekeeping.
You know, time is a form of distance, right?
Now, when you look at a digital thing, it's different.
That that's actually let me just say this.
I'm not going to expand on this.
But if you understand digital time, a digital clock,
that becomes a highly advanced form of thinking,
which which is why I say, you know, most people are idiots,
but they are capable of extremely high.
Right. It's just the conditioning prevents them. Right. OK.
Yeah. In other words, it's kind of like you're driving a Ferrari
to haul garbage your whole life.
The Ferrari can be on the you know, it's a prestigious car.
Why are you hauling garbage your whole life with it? Right. Right.
I mean, it wasn't even made.
You could you could use it to haul garbage.
But, you know, those who know will look at you and say that's a waste of a Ferrari.
So when you look at most people, you're like, what a waste of a human.
You know, you can drive a nail into a wall with a gold bar if you like.
But it's a it's not. Yeah, you can do better.
So but anyway, I'm not going to expand on that in the future.
But when I say time is a form of distance, you know, when you look at the windup toy,
the hands as they move, right, you can determine the distance
of between the numbers. Right. Right.
Now, here's the thing.
We used to call them punks, but they're incense sticks.
You ever see when you buy incense sticks, sometimes they sell them
a wooden base that goes over. Yeah, of course.
The horizontal base. Yeah. Well, that's a timekeeping thing.
If you look at that base, it has marks on it.
Not like we know they have geometric forms.
But the reason the stick, the sticks were standardized and the base was standardized.
And that's how you kept time.
That was like an hourglass.
But in the Hindu culture, are you ever heard this before?
Yeah, I actually have about the incense. Yes.
Yeah. It's a form of time.
OK. Lamps, quantity of oil.
If you have a standard wick size,
a quantity of oil you can keep time with. Right.
So it's a matter of distance and measurement.
So so time is always kept with distance and measurement of some form.
If you can't record that accurately.
You're going to have to find a way that you can.
Right. So if you have people talking about
timekeeping in a way that it can't be recorded,
it's it's just cultural thing.
It's like, hey, I'll meet you in the afternoon. Right.
Well, I'll meet you tonight.
But that's not what timekeeping is about.
Timekeeping, as a matter of fact, solar timekeeping, you can go down to,
you know, a thousandth of a second if you want. Right.
They have clocks in India for that.
You know, the longer the wire or the monument, the more accurate. Right.
You can get, you know, a short stick in the ground.
You might get within a few seconds.
But, you know, if you have something that's precisely built,
that's 40 feet tall, you get down to a few thousandths of a second. Right.
So the purpose of timekeeping
is to have a clear, concise measurement.
Now, how are you going to measure something at dawn or at sundown?
You can't. Actually, all the measurement functions are done.
All measurement functions are always done at the apex or zenith of the sky.
Right. So this is a practical thing that's been going on.
And, you know, forever, forever.
By the way, when I tell I say this often, you're never going to do that.
You're never going to figure it out or you're never going to get this.
People say, Greek, how do you know?
Because they think when you say never, it's attached to forever and infinity.
And when I ever say never, it means in the ever that you have left
before you get thrown back into the Stone Age or, you know,
or what's called a reset, right, where you start all over.
So when I when I I'm pretty accurate, I tell someone,
you're never going to figure that out.
Most people will say, well, how do you know?
Because they attach it again to infinity.
I'm seeing within the time frame that you've got the way you're going.
See, that's why very often when I say that, well, you will never get this
in form of technology or whatever it might be.
Conversation about means in the ever that you have left. Right.
So so these things in terms of timekeeping are
it's another way of timekeeping, right?
It's it's just duration.
But timekeeping in itself has has to be accurate.
And the only way to do it is by reckoning at the apex
of the of the sky.
And this has been known
forever. And that's pretty much it.
And there's a lot of other references you could find in culture.
For example, the simplest one is if you were growing up
before the electronic convention of banks, when you deposited a check afternoon,
they counted it as the next day. Remember?
Yeah. So because they're those bankers, they kept.
The thing about bankers is there.
It's from the part of the legal system, by the way.
It's, you know, anyway, it's about record keeping.
Well, I was going to say, that's what a lot of this is about anyway.
It's about keeping a record.
And it's about, you know, the court record, what it is they're supposed to be doing.
Don't mix the court with the banks.
The courts is OK.
Well, the courts are kangaroo courts now.
Yeah, but it's adapted from that because the idea is it's
supposed to be for record keeping, you know.
And there is such a thing as a lawful situation where records,
you know, you go in for an account.
Yeah. But if the only the only lawful stuff you'll find is inside the bank,
not what they do to you or what they like, for example,
when you look at the Federal Reserve
sheet, you know, their balance sheet, it's only one page long.
And on the bottom, they have asterisks and says, we get to do all this
because of special drawing rights means that you don't have that.
You know, they create money off of a signature.
You can't do that. Right.
Right. So that so that's all unlawful.
But on the inside of what they're doing,
they make sure that they have everything in line.
So that's why they also kept the noon time, because they didn't.
There was. OK.
In other words, in the 70s and up to the 80s, when I first saw
Citibank putting portable ATMs
in parking lots in like 1982, I don't know if you remember that.
Yeah, I actually do.
Yeah. Yeah. I knew that the solar noon thing was gone.
It was out the window because now it's electronic.
And right. So. Right.
So anyway, and at the time, I didn't I didn't know about the day
starting a solar noon, but now, you know, in retrospect, right, retro causation,
I see how the you know, when everything gets connected,
you don't need to rely on that.
Right. Well, yeah, you don't catch you detached
the necessity for people to operate in the daylight hours
to do certain things.
Once you do that, it's all out there.
Yeah. In other words, the lawful timekeeping went out for them also
because also what happened around then, actually, it happened earlier
with the advent of the telex machine, which was before the fax.
And it worked over the phone, by the way.
It's just basically a fancy fax that corporations used and shipping companies.
You know, a good way to describe it is a phone line communicates
and a typewriter on the other end bangs out exactly what it's supposed to.
And boom, there it is.
Yeah, that was the telex.
And then the but you know, all that was invented almost 200 years before.
You could look up the dot matrix and all that.
That was in the 1700s.
They already had that.
But anyway, but it wasn't commercial.
But but the whole thing about
that is also with the telex machine, the stock markets got all connected. Right.
You see, but the stock markets didn't open a certain time.
So the one in Tokyo and New York, you know, had a 10 hour difference,
12 hour difference. Right.
But they were able to still communicate after.
So anyway. Yeah.
So that was a quick insert on that.
But, you know, that's the thing.
You know, I like doing a lot of subjects.
And some people said, if you go on a tangent, come back.
And I try to do it.
But you know what it has to do with is a lot of these things that we talk about.
It's it's what you're interested in.
And you find that
with children, like, what do you want to be when you grow up?
Should I have to grow up?
You know, I'm you know, I'm still in my sixth decade.
I don't know what growing up means.
Yeah. But but this is what I especially young people that haven't been corrupted.
It's like, you know, what should I be interested in?
The answer is everything.
All right. Now, this is this is why it's how you parcel out your consciousness.
And what I mean by that is very simple.
Let's go to a common oaf, common pedestrian person.
You bring up a subject out of the blue.
Let's say it's technical or non-technical.
Let's say I'm not interested in that.
But they're very interested in sitting in front of the tube
for three hours with beer and chips. Right.
OK. You see what I mean?
Yeah. So they've decided that they don't want to be right.
And I think I've given many, many examples in Greek speak
on how people develop interest and shy away and develop this laziness. Right.
Yeah. Now, I do understand why, let's say a typical, you know,
whatever would not be interested in talking about whatever
and rather sit in front of a TV and watch CNN for two hours.
I understand that.
Why? Because it's been measurements done since the 60s
that when someone watches the tube, even the flat screen
after about 20 minutes or so, the brain starts to go more and more into alpha.
Right. It's like a very it's a relaxed state.
Actually, I found a lot of Americans, by the way.
How do I know this?
If I go out to get cigarettes late at night, I look, you know,
look around the neighborhood and I know where the bedrooms are.
I know the floor plan on the houses in the neighborhood and they sleep
with the TV on. Yeah.
A lot of people can't sleep on this, especially the older ones,
unless the television is on. Right. Right.
So I understand. Yeah.
I understand they'd rather be in the sedated state. Right.
But do I is that someone I want to be associated with?
Absolutely not.
And not not would not in any way ever, because they might be useful somehow.
But is it someone that I would want to, you know, on
the associate with anything beyond the base level?
Absolutely not. Right.
Because you've already know they've already structured themselves.
So there's a certain structure.
So the thing is, when people what should I be interested in everything?
It's just how much time do you want to spend on it? Right.
They do this thing.
I don't like it because it's mainstream, but I do appreciate it.
This thing called fun facts that's been going on for about 20 years now.
Right. Fun fact. Right.
It's trying to get people to get a little more broadener,
you know, learn something about something.
Usually most of it's urban myth anyway. Right.
The best the best fun fact is that, you know, you're just a piece of livestock
legally, legally, you're livestock, you know.
And then but how do you give that as a fun fact that 20 hours of support? Right.
Here's the thing.
There's many levels to all this,
but ultimately a larger consciousness can contain a lesser one.
You know what I mean?
So someone.
That's a rhetorical question.
I don't know. That's the East Coast.
That's the you know what I mean?
Well, do you know what I mean?
All right. OK. You hear me?
Do you hear me now? Yeah. Yeah. OK. Yeah. Like that. Right.
So what I mean by that is
a larger consciousness can always contain a lesser one.
And I didn't say person or human or whatever, but consciousness of character.
So someone who tends to be interested in everything
and can easily comprehend someone who isn't right.
Right. Right.
So let's have a neighbor, you know, used to ride motorcycle with him
and he watches football and drinks beer, eats Subway sandwiches. Right.
Yes. Yeah. I completely can.
I mean, I know I know him better than he knows himself.
What I mean by that is super predictable.
I tell him what he's going to be doing next week before he even does it.
Right. And and to myself, you know, I mean, it's just like, you know,
they already have an obvious, established pattern that they've chosen.
Yeah. And they don't even know they're not even conscious of what they're doing
and how they're like, you know, in a particular way.
But with if he spends three minutes with me, he's like, oh, no, you're going to say
talk about things I can't understand again.
Right. You see.
So I'm not saying it's a larger conscious who will always contain the lesser one.
All right. Let's ramp that up in scale.
OK, the elite, whatever they have access to, that's pretty much anything they want.
Oh, Doc, you know, I think I've always mentioned whenever you see an old document.
Right. You have to ask yourself, why did they let they didn't censor this?
Why? Why are they leaving it up on the surface?
What message do they want to give us?
Right. Right. Give me an example.
If you go into the underground or the secret places,
they'll produce, let's say they'll say, give me an old book and they'll give you
something, a scroll or a piece of something that's memorialized paper or whatever.
And they'll look kind of old, you know, like maybe a hundred or whatever years old.
And you look at it and it's a thousand years old.
You're like, my gosh, this is in really good condition, because on the surface,
something that's a thousand years old.
I mean, if you just lean, if you look at it the wrong way, it starts to crumble.
Right. Yeah.
They've got things three, four or five thousand years old that look almost, you know,
like an antique, but perfect shape.
Right. You see.
So if you dumb down the people to the point where they have a lesser conscious,
you can contain them because you have a higher conscious.
You understand what's going on.
You understand that you have a continuous, you have continuity of thought.
You know, for example, the technology that you give on the surface is all of it.
Nothing has been invented.
The cell phones and all have always been around.
You go back as far back as you want to go.
They're just trickling right up to the surface. Right.
So they know all this.
So in other words, when you have access to information and you're interested in it
and you come up to the surface or whatever, you don't have to be underground.
I'm saying, you know, surface, meaning the regular people,
you can look at like someone like let me just this is not because they're like
clerks like the Rothschilds or clerks or whatever.
But let's say someone like that, an Illuminati. Right.
I like the aluminum Ducati. That's right.
That's from what's his name?
Someone sent me a video to look at quantum of consciousness, a YouTuber.
And I like his style, Matt.
I think he'd do well with Greek speak if he got some of it.
But anyway, instead of using that word Illuminati, right?
Aluminum Ducati. I like that.
But anyway, those people, if they come out,
if they have access to all this stuff and they see a commoner,
they can completely contain the consciousness of the commoner
to the point where they can control them using emo, basic emo.
Look, everybody cover yours.
I can control the basic commoner using emo right now.
You know, I mean, look, I think three hundred dollars
for a five gallon bucket of paint is too much. Yeah.
All right. So how much is that? Right.
Or even. Yeah.
We get to the we get to the register.
He brings it up for ten dollars.
And I ask him, is it ten dollars for that paint?
And he says, yes, it is. All right. Thank you. Bye.
It's like, we'll hurry up and get the car right away
before he gets out of his trance. Right. Right.
Yeah. And some people say, well, Greek is stealing.
No, I didn't. I didn't.
I just had him bring it up for heat.
And I asked, I always make sure.
Yeah. Are you sure it's ten dollars?
He's like, yeah.
In other words, these are not the droids you seek.
Remember in Star Wars. Right.
And it's not a mistake.
You know, it's not. Oh, I just wasn't thinking.
Yeah. So I experiment with the commoners frequently.
And I'm like, oh, my gosh.
Did we?
Higher consciousness can contain a lower consciousness.
Yeah, absolutely.
Did we record that?
I think we recorded that conversation about the paint.
You told that story.
Yeah. Oh, this happens often.
This happens with food.
This happens with all kinds of stuff.
Yeah. No, I was just saying in detail.
I think if you go back and it's an experiment, I don't do it often.
But I do. I do.
When I feel the right time to do it,
I will work on it and see if it works.
But and it has about a 70 to 80 percent success rate,
which is not bad considering a whole lot of other things that have much.
Oh, my gosh. Yeah, it's really cool.
And then, of course, you know, affecting machines and physical things
is interesting as well.
But again.
And I've given all the pieces on how this is done, the email work, right?
You know, some people like it, some people don't.
Some people use it, some people don't.
I haven't gotten any enough feedback on it.
Well, that's something you shied away from, actually, a little bit ago
when I asked you about it.
And then we we said we wouldn't get into it then was about the you know, OK,
so what happens when you apply this to something
that doesn't typically have a consciousness, right?
What about a machine?
What about a mechanism?
What about you have to have technical knowledge on the fine point?
Also, what do you want to move?
What kind of a mover do you want to create?
Like, for example, the street lamps are not that hard and cars are not that hard.
You can prevent the car from starting with your mind,
but you have to know the critical component in a car.
For example, if it's a modern car, which most of them are,
I think they had the junk for Jesus, not junk for Jesus.
What was it? The junk clunker cash for clunkers with Obama? Yeah, yeah.
Yeah. They got rid of all the cars that didn't have electronics.
So it was very important that they did that for many reasons.
But, you know, the five volt standard that you have on computers
and cell phones and all that that came from the car industry, right?
The five volt domain rail for a computer inside the circuit board.
It has an ECU, the automobile.
There's a couple of fine points in that circuit board that run on five volts,
and they're very, very fine, especially inside the semiconductor.
If you understand how fine the metal is there and where to detach it,
you can prevent the car from starting with your mind.
The same thing with if you have a street lamp, there used to be silver
sodium bulbs, those real intense bulbs used to use them in gymnasiums.
But people would go to the high school
to watch the basketball game and everybody left with a suntan at night.
You know, silver sodium.
They're very a lot of UV.
It's a very heavy filament.
But inside the glass tube with the base of the filament is that filament is tiny.
It's like 20 microns thick, 20 microns, a little less than a human hair.
If you know where the stress point is that on your mind, create a stress point.
Break that wire right there.
You can make a street lamp go off.
The LEDs street lamp, you'd make that go off again with a five volt controller.
That depends on the design of the LED.
But they do have a five volt controller in there.
Probably some kind of a chip.
You just have to learn about IC chips and then find out the finest point.
And then just at that point is where you affect it.
Right. In other words, if you wave your hand and say, Streetlight, go off.
I'll tell you a thousand years later, you'll still be doing that.
Nothing will happen.
So it does require technical knowledge of the thing.
And it depends if you know, always.
You notice what everything that I mentioned, what it has in common
is you're going after the finest physical point.
So, you know, the chain is as good as its weakest link. Right. Right.
So if you've got a heavy chain and on the end it's connected by a silk thread,
you're going to try to break the big link, the steel link,
or you're going to break the silk thread, you see.
So you find out where it is.
You know, the legal system is the same way, by the way. OK.
Everything. The medical system is the same way, which I saw a comment.
Medical stuff. You know,
I just want to bring this up.
I don't like to address particular direct.
I did in the beginning regarding allergies, a couple of things.
I don't want to.
I found that there's more beneficial if I'm sharing experiences.
You know, give an example.
You know how most people do things in their life and say things in their life
based on what they saw on TV.
Right. Some people are actually a lot more than you think.
And I find that the TV just broadcasts, you know, doesn't go into specifics.
Sometimes you have a call in show or whatever.
I find that if I just discuss the things that I practically do
without thinking about them, they're so simple and so practical.
Because if I get into addressing an issue,
I have to go through all the cobwebs and mothballs and dust bunnies in my brain
and bring up everything I know about that subject
and somehow make a caution, you know, statement about it. Right.
OK. And it's like 10 things want to come out at once and hard to make sense.
Right. But if I start getting into like things I practically do, like,
hey, you want to save money on dish soap,
why don't you dilute it in a spray bottle with some water and borax or whatever?
And you'll be buying just soap twice a year instead of once a month. Right.
I've been right.
Instead of using household cleaners that are toxic,
put some hydrogen peroxide in a spray bottle, clean up baby vomit, wipe it.
You know, by the way, if you have something nasty in the house,
like vomit or poop or whatever from a pet or a child,
don't put the paper towel with your hand.
Grab a plastic bag and not a glove, not a glove. I'll tell you why.
You put your hand in a plastic bag and then and then wipe it with the plastic
bag and then the bag is right there.
Just turn it inside out and retract it. It's gone.
If you have a glove, you know, it's on the glove, right?
Yeah, it's much cleaner to use a plastic bag.
That's what I do all the time, actually.
I got to go pick up something.
I'm going to pick up a piece of paper. And I do have little dogs.
If I got to, you know, they poop on the floor once in a while.
I got to go pick that up.
Sure. I grab a plastic bag and put it down my my wrist,
you know, down my arm a little bit.
And then I go take care of it.
And then I grab from where it is on my forearm,
pull it up and just wrap the bag up. Boom.
Ready to go. Right. Yeah.
So if you put on gloves, you know.
Now, I don't want to shake your hand out with this glove.
Anyway, use hydrogen peroxide and alcohol is a lot better
than these other chemical things with dyes and colors and whatever.
Right. And it's a lot cheaper.
Yeah. You know, much cheaper.
I mean, a bottle of Fantastic's like five, six bucks.
You look at the amount of volume for a dollar.
You know, you get the same amount of hydrogen peroxide.
It's actually it's fine. Right.
So the other thing I want to mention, if you have food garbage
and it's summertime, put it in the freezer instead of throwing it out
in the can and waiting five, six days for the garbage to pick it up.
Because it's going to rot in the can. Right.
That's for sure.
And then even though it's not in your house, it's still attracting flies.
It's bad. Yeah.
It's it's called tomain radiation.
Tomain is the medical term or Greek term for dead.
It radiates this decay. Right.
But because, for example, of a colony of nine, I call it colony nine.
But there are 10 cats.
So it's called a group of a group of cats is called a colony.
Folks, by the way, some of you know it.
Some of you don't. Right.
Right. Like a murder of crows. Right.
Yeah. And all these other various things.
But anyway, I think people are still in herds, aren't they? Anyway,
I would suggest that, like, for example, when you cook for the animals,
like, you know, you buy a 10 pound bag of chicken parts and you cook right.
Whatever the bones, they go into a bone bag in the freezer
and the garbage day, whatever you take them out.
So all these practical things, I rehashed a whole bunch of stuff.
OK, regarding health, the last week I got into the or the week before
I call it rice number brown rice number seven.
And I gave all the ingredients.
And this has nothing to do with anything that most people
I've gotten some feedback from it.
I think some of it was more appropriate than others.
It was all good. I see more appropriate was the point of giving
that was not to make a delicious meal or something you like or don't like.
It was an example to show that a combination of vegetable things,
you know, from the plant world. Yeah.
They were chosen very specifically for their qualities and their energies
that they emanate from the time they were baby, you know,
till the time they were harvested. Right. Right.
And when you combine them with other the combination, this vegetable
with this vegetable, with that vegetable, with this in rice, brown rice,
but it has to be an organic Bloomberg brown rice.
You will get an effect, right?
It's like a superfood, right?
It's not a matter of saying, like, I like brown rice with onions and peas.
It has nothing to do with that at all.
What you like it.
I hope I gave enough of example why I chose the lotus root, right?
Why I chose the ginger. Why the burdock? Right.
Why? Why the carrot? Why the onion?
Why you say and how?
So once you learn this and understand this, by the way,
most of the feedback that I did get for whoever made it,
thought it was very delicious. I find it to be extremely delicious.
I try to make it often.
OK, so when you understand the energies in the body, like, for example,
I look at various alternative like rents, bookmark
and to see what kind of junk they put out. Right.
It's still stupid.
I say, well, certain things in coffee prevent cancer in the liver.
Oh, my gosh. There's nothing.
The only thing that could prevent cancer or cause cancer is you.
You're how your body handles the energy, right?
Because what it is, basically anything, especially I mentioned cancer.
There's no such thing as cancer. It's just a roadblock, right?
The energy moves through the body.
It's funny. Recently, I was speaking to a medical person.
I said, the body's energetic.
And they're like, yes, that's right.
Very, very like dominantly. You know what?
Yeah, I know that.
You know, as soon as I brought up a certain point, so I don't know.
But then because they're entertaining two dichotomy, two things that don't.
They're entertaining two thoughts.
They're diametrically opposed. Yeah.
Yeah. And they maintain those things.
They need to start putting these thoughts together.
And so they cancel out and empty their head. Right.
But anyway, the cancer, all it is, is the body saying, look,
the energy is all screwed up in your body.
And I'm going to put this roadblock here.
They even say it
when they remove something from your body.
Don't they say we remove what the blockage blockage?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's in the language.
You got to look.
That's why you contract the disease.
Which disease do you want to contract with?
I have all these medical books.
Which one do you want to contract with? Right.
It's a legal term.
By the way, there is no medical research that's beneficial
and there is no medical treatment that's being offered
unless it's cleared by legally first.
OK, get it.
So now forget about what the doctors are doing,
their intention or whatever, but they're just as moronic as the rest
of society that you're in.
You have to think about it first.
As if the doctor is saying something,
it means it's been cleared by the attorneys.
Now, what the hell do the attorneys know or care?
Nothing. I back in the days of bike racing,
I was doing some mechanicing and I met a bunch of people, big bike race.
So what do you do?
She's, oh, I'm a book editor.
I thought you're an attorney.
He says, yeah, I am.
This is what kind of books do you edit?
This is medical books.
OK, don't say anything else.
That's all I need to know.
Right. That's all I need to know.
So, yeah, yeah, you're you're you're concerned with the legal part of it.
And that's that.
Yeah. So you can omit a whole bunch of things in the study
that he considers illegal that actually makes it more complete
and actually which will eventually lead to development.
Right. Right. Treatment.
Yeah. So I'm telling you, the people that.
OK, let me give another example.
Maybe I should repeat that.
Attorneys edit medical books, not doctors, not attorneys.
And the only medical experience the attorney has is after he edited books
for like 10 or 15 years.
They don't know anything about the medical. OK.
So when you go to a doctor, I've actually had her doctors tell me
and dentists tell me legally, I can't tell you to do this.
What legal?
So I'm going to the wrong guy.
She's going to an attorney.
You know, attorneys, I don't know anything about medicine.
Right. So you're going to a doctor.
What makes you think he knows anything?
It's the same thing.
It's just like how I explained what you learn about electricity in college.
Right. Positive one and minus one is zero. Right. Right.
So it's all legal.
It's all the whole thing of the banking is still the same way.
Right. Special drawing rights just means we can do it.
You can't. Right.
You heard a special drawing rights.
SDR is right.
That's the whole the whole system is based on.
There's putting it more in your face now.
Actually, if you read the financial stuff, I don't know if you.
Well, anyway, there's OK.
You know what a news bulletin is, right?
Was it what do they do when you go to certain sites?
Sign up for a newsletter.
Newsletters and newsletters.
Yeah. If you want to learn about what an organization is doing
and you're interested, they say, here's a sign up for our newsletter.
Here's actually you go to the newsletter. Why not? Right. Right.
If you want to know what the federal government is doing,
they have what's called a federal registry. It's a newsletter.
Why don't you go read that and then watch what they're saying on TV?
Right. And tell me if one has anything to do with the other. It doesn't.
You know, it doesn't at all. Yeah.
So so, you know, these things I mean, this is insanity.
So the level of insanity has gotten to the point now that I think just
basically preaching and teaching to the choir doesn't doesn't work.
Just sharing a little bit of what you do that you find harmony in
and whether it's in pieces or makes sense or not.
People can pick up on it if they could piece it together,
if they find it to be whole enough and use it would be great.