The Sonic Event 143 Rated Y, Ocelli in the Greek, yeah, here we are, Greek, it's been
an interesting week, I gotta tell you I feel like crap today though, I really do, I've
been reading a lot of messages from people, I guess they're emailing you and checking
in with you and all that good stuff, what do you got?
Yeah, making new friends, I haven't had this much of an influx of people that seem interesting
since the Freeman interviews, so yeah, I've got new friends in Czech Republic, Russia,
Brazil, Israel, yeah, yeah, and you know, when I say friends, I mean, you know, people
that you'd want to meet, right?
Right, it seems though Archaic's had a lot of people like worldwide, you know, there's
definitely a diverse, you know, it's not just all in America or anything.
Yeah, exactly, and I want to get into that a little bit because I want to preface, I
want to preface something, there might be questions or so, and there's some emails I
might answer publicly, anonymously, of course.
The point where we've been for the past so and so years, you can either take it within
your lifetime recently, or if you study enough history, you'll notice that it's always been
this way.
Like, for example, you know, I love doing tangents, drug use is on the rise, right?
When?
Okay, starting in the 70s, 60s, whatever, okay, sure, go study the 19th century, they
had a big problem with drug use.
How about the early part of the 20th century, like World War One time, there was a lot of
heroin around.
That's when it came, yeah, the new stuff, yeah, before that it was morphine, and before
that it was just opium.
You got it.
Go back to the 18th century, a lot of drug use.
Go back to the 16th century, go 9th century, a lot of drug use, 1st century AD, 3rd century
BC.
What are you talking about?
It's always been this way.
But within your own lifetime, you have your lifetime is like your own little universe.
You can only see things from yourself, usually.
That's why it's important to read what other people write, or listen to other people, because
then you see their point of view.
But what I want to be emphatic about is, from this point on, like years now, all the stuff
that you've been taught will not help you, if that makes any sense.
So everything that you've been taught, oh, go to the doctor, oh, that looks real bad,
go to the emergency room, that will not help you.
That is the bottom, bottom, bottom, bottom of the barrel scraping, right?
In other words, financial stuff, go talk to a financial advisor, that will not help you.
You will be in the same boat as everyone else, and they will take your money, the chances
of making money.
And if you do make money, by the way, it'll be very small to what you could have done,
right?
On and on, on health stuff, go see this alternate practitioner, bottom of the barrel.
So what I'm saying is, if you have information that you've been living with, and you're relying
on that still, it's all bottom of the barrel, scraping bottom of the barrel.
The only thing that you will be able to work with that will create new things for you is
new information, completely new points of looking at it.
But the problem with that is, you have to understand that your mind is a human mind,
and just like all human minds, whenever they hear something that is too different, and
it's not in accord with what they heard before, it automatically, the mind automatically rejects
that new information, automatically, before you even think about it, right?
So that's the problem.
Well, we kind of collect, well, humans kind of collect things together in patterns, right?
So if we see patterns emerging, we trust that as reliable.
So if you hear it over and over again, it seems like, well, that must be true, right?
So repetition.
So whenever you hear something like a pattern, you always say, that's bullshit, right away,
you'll be safe, or at least you're guarding yourself.
Right.
If you turn it the other way, but, because that's why we're not making progress, but-
No, you're not here to make progress.
You're not here to make progress.
It's kind of like when you're a paratrooper and you jump out of the airplane, you're
not there to make progress, you're there to safely engage, you know, get the shoot going
and land.
That's what this place is not, for the new people, it takes about 50 years to master
something.
So if you start at 20, you'll be 70, and then it doesn't matter what it is, even making
the best blue jeans in the world, chefing, anything, any craft by hand or study, one
of these big corporate guys, the richest guy from the stock market, Buffett, his partner
said that a real company that does investing, they have an office off to the side where
an 80 year old sits by himself and does all the decision making, right?
So you don't have that kind of time.
Like in a society where you live two, three, four, 500 years, it's way different.
Let's say you were to go to an open air market, like a flea market or what it's called, bazaars,
you know, people bring their wares to sell.
Yeah.
Okay.
Swap flea market.
Yeah.
So you're looking at a rug and it'll be nothing, a small area rug, and it won't be anything
like, or let's say handcrafted chair or handcrafted knife.
It won't be anything like you see now.
So for example, when people live multiple centuries, you go to one of these markets
and you see this rug and you like it.
And it does, if you were from this world, it would, wouldn't resemble any quality from
here and you'll see why.
Right.
So you want to knock the price down on the guy and the guy says, come on, it took me
30 years to weed that, right?
It took me 50 years to weave them because remember they live two, three, four, 500 years,
right?
Okay.
You cannot imagine that kind of workmanship or quality of craftsmanship.
You see what I mean?
This is the, the, the, the, the, the whole thing takes on a different meaning when you
live that long.
There's no reason why you cannot enjoy that with a short life that we have now.
And that's why, you know, we're blocked from education and all that.
So anybody listening to, so what I've, what I've been doing, uh, listening now has also
no and is new has what gets the flavor of what Greek speak is.
But I'd say the past 10 episodes, we've got into a lot of the legal stuff, the bankruptcy,
the bonding process, how money works, right?
So I was on an archaic interview recently, and you could send this audio to Jason, anyone
that's listening that can contact, or I can send it to big John.
But today he, I got up, I was doing gardening and I put it on and it says archaics was live.
So cool.
Put it on.
Let's see what he's saying.
Right.
He ain't no dummy.
So it's worth listening to.
Anyway.
Uh, he's talking about a guy in part was crying the blues about his arrest to get to pay all
this money to these attorneys.
And right away in my mind, I said, Oh, what a move, Jason, you pay you hiring attorneys.
That's a move.
It doesn't mean you're a, it just means it's a move.
So you don't know what's going on.
I mean, that's like bottom of the barrel dungeon programming way down there, you know, with
everybody else.
And uh, uh, based on his character and his demeanor, he won't understand what I'm saying
fully to implement it.
And it's so easy to implement.
It's amazing.
Uh, but it's scary because you're, you know, it's kind of like, uh, let's say you see a
new dungeons and dragons video game.
You've never played it before, even though you're just a video game player, it's kind
of easy.
Scary things jump in front of you.
You get scared, right?
But you got to remind yourself, it's just a video game, right?
Uh, to make a long story short, I want to just cover what's going on because it's in
every country, Czech Republic, China, Russia, all this, and the brainwashing that's going
on with the legal system.
I just want to recover that because I've been recently explaining it to someone in a way
that is very short in Greek speak style.
So what I want to just, the attorneys, by the way, don't know anything like, just like
doctors don't know anything at all.
They doctors a little bit better because it's physical.
So the attorneys don't know anything and it's all paperwork, right?
So for doctor, let's say has to do a C-section, he has to do something more than an attorney
will ever do.
Oh, he's got to get some results here and there.
Yeah.
It's messy.
The attorneys get results.
All right.
Uh, they get results.
Yeah.
But it's physical, meaning it's not just dealing with paperwork and, and, uh, wearing a three
piece suit.
Right.
Uh, but you know, it's funny.
People think they're so advanced.
I had a conversation with a medical person recently and they started bringing up these
procedures and everything that they brought up was either, uh, from the 19th century or
before, like, you know, like doing a C-section, right?
Why do they call it a C-section?
Oh, cesarean, Caesar.
Right.
Because, right.
And how long ago was that?
Like one 30 BC.
Yeah.
Right.
Okay.
So you're really primitive.
Uh, actually you're going the other way.
So all these people at the, the whole society is scrubbing the bottom of the barrel, uh,
and everything that they're doing.
So in order to jump to the next level, by the way, these types of things that I discuss,
we have, uh, people have heard me say this, but it's not for this society.
It's for the next society.
But if you start operating like it now, it could make your life here a little better.
Not only not easier, uh, simplify it, make it better.
You'll definitely be more advanced than all the other quote unquote, hairless monkeys.
Not that they evolved from monkeys, but that's just exactly what they look and act like when
they follow the norm.
But going back to Jason's situation, he put this out publicly, so I'll put it out publicly.
What's going on in reality is all the countries now, I can only mention specifics on the,
on the U S which by the way, the U S is sort of a capital of the financial world.
People talked about, you know, Reagan bankrupted the U S S R with the arms race.
Um, well that's crock of bullshit.
You know why?
Because the U S S R is money.
The Rupal at the time was coming out of the world economic forum, which was also the world
economic Federation and all these other things, the world economic fund or whatever.
And guess where that's based Washington, DC.
Yeah.
So it doesn't make any sense.
So all the world is the same.
So what's been going on with all the world and specifically the U S is the government's
got coaxed into playing a card game with the banking cartel and they lost their country
in that card game.
Some places like what happened in the U S between 1913, 1933 happened in Canada in the
1870s to 1890s.
They experimented on Canada, just like now they experiment on New Zealand and Australia.
Right.
Okay.
All right.
So when they lost the government, lost the, the, uh, country and everything in the country,
the people, the labor, all the patents, the deeds to the banks by contract, they said,
well, if we need to put something in place, a remedy.
So if people find out there's no revolution, by the way, no one ever finds out what I'm
saying.
That's why there's no revolution.
There'll still be a revolution.
It's a dead man's switch.
Once people find this out, regardless of what remedies put in place, that's it.
It's over, you know?
Um, so basically a coroner's report is written for every, all the 196 countries in the world
right now, they just haven't been buried yet.
And for example, when someone dies, like I know someone who had a, uh, was a cop and
he had someone die in their back seat while they were taking them to the jail house and
they put them in the morgue, city morgue.
And they were on ice for like five years.
No, you know, unclaimed, you know, because if they're, it depends on who's running the
morgue too, you know, might say, let's just put them in Potter's field.
Right.
Yeah.
But this guy was on ice for five years.
So yeah, they'll put you on ice.
So right now the whole, all the whole world's on ice.
But so what's going on?
So what the remedy was for every country is we're going to create a, uh, put everything
in a trust and, uh, everybody's a trustee except for the people or the beneficiaries.
And you get a number, uh, social security, social insurance number, whatever.
Everyone has it.
And that is really like your credit card.
In other words, every government, uh, all debt belongs to the government.
Let's say the U S for example, in other countries, you'll find it to the United
States, for example, in the uniform commercial code, there's only one debtor
and it's the United States government or the Czech Republic or the Russian
Federation or the ministry of Iraq or the ministry of Australia.
Each country has one debtor only.
And that one debtor is the government.
And like, for example, for the U S it's, I think UCC nine three Oh seven
section eight section H or Y I there's a few sections and it tells you the
location of the debtor, right?
District of Columbia.
So anyway, all the countries have similar codes in some countries.
They put these codes inside of another obscure treaty.
So you can't find it on basic research, but generally with the AI searches,
you'll find it, AI will lie to you by the way.
So, but it'll get you in the general direction.
All right.
So what's been going on is, uh, all the professional classes, the banking
people, credit card, people, doctors, lawyers, people who run them are, they
make it seem like everything's normal and you have to pay for things.
Uh, and what they do is they make you a trustee instead of a beneficiary
beneficiary when there's a trust, let's say, and you're the beneficiary
and you're going to use that trust.
You don't need to know how much is in the trust.
Actually, it's better that you don't know.
And when you need to buy something, you don't even need to know how much it costs.
That's the trustees job.
So when you're the beneficiary, you're like, Oh, I need a new car.
You call the trustee.
I need a new car.
Okay.
Which car.
And that's it.
That's all you.
And the next thing, you know, you get the car, but if there's, let's say
the, you don't have enough money in the trust, the trustee says, we don't
have that kind of funds to get that.
Pick another one.
You see, but the moment you start saying I'm the beneficiary and I want
to know how much is in the trust and I'm going to spend this and that.
Now you're acting like a trustee.
And in trust law, the trustee always takes the hit when there's a problem
with the trust, the trustees that go to jail, right?
Not the beneficiary.
So what they try to do is they always make you the one of the
trustees, like what they're doing.
So you take the hit.
All right.
So what's going on, let's say you've been in jail 26 years, let's
say, or 10 years or whatever.
That court is not part of the judicial part of government in any
country, especially the U S how do you know?
Well, everything on the functioning court side, whether it's the police,
the prosecutor, the judge, the bailiff, the bill, all of that is
under the attorney general office.
The attorney general office is executive branch of government.
They do what they want to do.
They say based because they were conferred and confirmed by the
legislative, right?
Legislative.
Right.
So where's the judicial?
There is nothing judicial.
It's all general order 100, basically military court.
That's why they have the army flag, according to title four, title five
with the French flag and the Phoenix on top.
Yeah.
It's not an Eagle.
It's a Phoenix.
And they, yeah.
Yeah.
So anyway it's a military court.
So what they're doing is the negotiating.
They, they will, you will not have a case until a penal bond is drawn up.
Three of them gotten into this before I'll do it again.
This is short.
So the whole interaction proceedings is getting you to agree to every, all
the requirements to have the requirements of the penal bond completed.
And once it's completed, they have your social security number.
Uh, you are a beneficiary, but they're making you act like a trustee.
So if they were making you act like the beneficiary in court, all the, all
you would know is come in and we just need you to sign something.
That's all.
No, you wouldn't know that you don't need to know the charges.
Right.
Remember like the car, buying the car, right?
Well, the moment you start looking at how much is in there and what they want to
do and what you're now, you're one of the trustees and you're reliable.
So what they're doing is they're taking you out of your position as being a
beneficiary by law, because remember the government set up that number for you to
take care of, to pay all of your debt because you can't pay for anything anymore.
So the moment you go into that court and you start pleading and talking
about that, now you're one of them.
And right.
But the penal bond that they've drawn up, there's three of them.
He's got your name on it and only your name on it.
And you're promising to pay whatever authority, usually the executive.
And they're not telling you that.
So once they satisfy, they check all the boxes.
The clerk is doing that basically.
Now it's a military tribunal because you need three, the judge, the prosecutor
and the clerk all work together.
Neither one of them has any higher or lower position than the other.
One guy plays the judge who is a failed attorney.
I think I've gotten to all judges are failed attorneys quickly because no one
goes to law school, says, I want to be a judge.
You want to go to law school to become a partner in a wealthy law firm.
If you suck at that, then you become a judge.
Sorry.
You know, it's the truth.
Um, then you have, um, the prosecutor who's a stage player, doesn't know any
law, the less state that he represents the district attorney's office.
And then you have the clerk.
Now the clerk is just as important because they're the ones that in real
time is checking off all the boxes on what's required for that bond to be issued.
Now, once all the requirements are there, all you need to do is go and sign it,
all three of them, and you're, you're done.
They're paid.
Whatever it is now under the CFR code of federal regulations, you'll find tucked
in there, all crimes are commercial crimes.
All right.
So let me just finish up with Jason's case.
So the first thing you should do is ask you, you know, well, you did another
thing you can do is use religious oppression, but this is later.
I'm talking about the beginning, but what you can do now that you're out
that bond that's been run 26 years would be about minimum of 30 to 40 million.
Now remember there's no money.
So it's just a credit value that later on gets given to the judges
and attorneys and all that.
Right.
When you're after retirement, you know, it's just a piled up there.
Cause you don't want all the money.
You just want the interest on it, right?
The interest on 40 million times a million times a million.
Cause that's how many people have gone through there anyway.
So the thing now to do is you call up the court and you say, I need
the bond, I need the court case number.
And the bond, the bond bond is long, just like anything, a surety bond
actually is a performance bond, surety bond.
And the, is it before a bid bond, which is what the charges are put on the
surety bond is you and the performance is the number of years, right?
That's how you're going to perform on it.
So you just want that bond number.
Now they're not going to give it to you.
Cause you asked that much.
They like they're busted.
Right.
And they're all, they'll everything I'm telling you is illegal as hell, what
they're doing, it's illegal and unlawful.
So if they don't give you the bond number, well, where do all the bonds
get registered in order to go through the federal reserve and let they go
through the DTC or the DTC DTTC, which is the, it for sure, just look up what's
called a deposit trust corporation.
Look up the deposit trust corporation and they will tell you they do.
24 quadrillion in business a year, which is a thousand trillion.
It's it's, it just doesn't make, you know, or 2.4 quadrillion, right?
Cause it, what you have billion and then trillion and then quadrillion, right?
Which is a thousand trillion.
That's what they do.
So those guys are really slow.
They don't care about anything.
You just put the request, you will get the bond number from them.
Or if you want to speed up the process, instead of being 180 days down to like 60
days, you go to Charles Schwab, you pay them.
They have a computer that networks right in there.
Right.
But I don't know what I heard like years ago when I first started looking into
this stuff, it was 70 or $80.
Now it's like 1200 to pay, you know, because it's catching on.
Right.
Wow.
Okay.
I'm talking about a private brokerage house, Charles Schwab, Fidelity,
you know, one of these guys.
Right.
But anyway, the DTCC has a request forms and all that, you can look all that up
and you get, once you get the bond number, that's all you need.
Then you go to the treasury, find the bond.
And what you're going to be asking for is the royalties on that.
And who are you to ask for the royalties?
Well, it doesn't, it doesn't every, whoever is on the bond, if it hasn't
been fully cashed out, which they don't, it should, they have it in their
collateral, just like you used to have stocks and bonds.
Well, who are you to ask for royalties on that?
Well, whose name is on it?
Well, they'll say Jason Breshears and, and only your name is on it.
Only your name.
It's your bond.
Right.
So all you're asking for is 5% of the 40 million or whatever.
It's, it could be more, it could be less.
Let's say conservatively, conservatively, 26 years would be no less than 26 million.
No less than that.
That's like heavily discounted.
It could be as high as a hundred million.
So once you start putting all the paperwork for this, Oh, you might go back
to the courthouse and find that everything has been scrubbed off the record.
You were never there.
You were never in jail.
You were never right.
Do you know what I mean?
This cause they're very corrupt.
Right.
Okay.
So if you tell this, what I just told to any attorney, other than like a
senior DA or whatever, they don't know what you're talking about.
If the attorney is younger than 65 or 70, they have no idea.
And the reason why is in the past 20 years, since nine 11, they made sure who's
they, uh, that anyone dealing with the public doesn't know what's going on,
whether it's medical, political scientific, because there were too many, too many
people involved in nine 11 with the public.
And they're all like having these Freudian slips constantly.
Right.
And it had no more of this.
So the, the, the level of separation now, well, let's say you have all these other
situations now where, you know, you've got to go to these parole officers or
you've got to do all this other stuff.
Okay.
That's where I've been talking about the Brandon, Joe Williams,
and maybe Christopher Hauser.
When you define what's been going on since the bankruptcy, since the civil
war state of Arizona state of California state of Texas state of New York state
of Georgia, those are all corporations out of the district of Columbia.
You could look all that up.
Right.
People have even attorneys think it's geographic.
Like they, I was talking to attorney once says, Oh, that's not true.
Cause the guy that was a warrant for a guy is flying from Texas to Arizona.
And when the plane crossed the border of Arizona, the marshals arrested him.
So they had no right to do that, but he agreed with it.
Right.
He agreed with it.
So like when you go pick up a ham sandwich for lunch and why I picked up
the ham sandwich and I ate it, it's because the ham sandwich agreed to it.
Right.
If the ham sandwich jumped out of your hand and protested the chances of you
eating it would be zero, right?
I would say so.
Yeah.
So that's, what's going on, but the brainwashing, but the, what, the way
you get around that properly without falling into their trustee is to
give you an example, like with me.
So riding a bike or something and actually let's tell it and cops from
me over, uh, you ran that red light.
Yeah.
Yep.
That's right.
You know, I'm not gonna, I knew I did it.
I said, who's the red light?
I'm going to run it.
So I was like, well, the first thing they do is they confer nationality on you.
Title eight, you know, in the state of Arizona, it's illegal to run a red light.
Blah, blah, blah, blah.
I'm like, oh yeah, that red light.
I just ran.
I did it without the state of Arizona.
Oh shit.
Now they don't know what the hell you're talking about.
Cause they think it's geographic, right?
So let's say you're California.
You get a tax letter from them.
Cause that's what they're doing now.
They're just sending anybody tax letters.
You know, California reputation.
Oh yeah.
I have this business and I do all this, but all the money I made was
without the state of California.
Or if you have anything with the quote unquote federal, oh yeah.
Yeah.
All that stuff.
All that, uh, uh, yeah.
All that, all the boxes of drugs and stuff that I brought in.
Yeah.
I did that without the United States.
What they require is for you to do it within their jurisdiction,
which is a fictional jurisdiction.
Actually, Chuck, if you're in front of the computer, type this in on a browser.
Uh, what is legal fiction?
Question mark, put the question there because the queries now are
getting more sensitive to grammar.
And I noticed if you put in what is legal fiction and what is legal fiction
question mark, you get different results.
Okay.
And read that.
It should have a caption.
It should tell you something like all legal, anything legal is a fiction.
All of it's a fiction.
You can't distinguish legal fiction from it's all, all
legal, anything legal is a fiction.
Well, I got a AI overview.
A legal fiction is a statement that is accepted as true for legal purposes,
even though it may be untrue.
Legal fictions are used to apply a rule in a way that is different
from its original purpose.
While leaving the letter of the law unchanged, the purpose of legal
fictions is to achieve fairness, consistency, or justice.
Right.
So let's say, say, well, you know, you went outside of your parole.
First of all, they're going to look at all your contracts.
I spoke to someone who worked for the district attorney in Texas.
So we're kind of talking about administrators.
Oh yeah.
He's like, yeah, when we charge someone with everything, we go pull up all
their personal records, see how much they have in bank accounts and property
they own, and the more they have, the more aggressive we are to admit that.
Right.
I also knew someone who worked in the district attorney's office in Hawaii.
Oh my gosh, that stuff.
I don't even know if I want to say on the Sonic, but I will.
So, okay.
So what's going on there is it's all fiction and they, you can make
people believe that the state, like right there, what you just read in
definition, you can have people believe state of Texas, state of Arizona, state
of California is geographic for that case, but you really can't be proven
that it is at all, right?
You see what I mean?
Although I'll tell you, Oh, the state of Arizona is the geography.
You're on it just for you, but they can't, it's not in the law at all.
Right.
You know what I mean?
They'll, they'll insist on that.
So you're doing stuff like I'm doing it without the Czech Republic or whatever,
you know, the Federation of Russia.
I did that.
Oh yeah, I did that.
Just ran the red light.
I just killed that guy, you know, who asked my sister, but I did it without.
The Federation of Russia, Russian Federation or whatever.
Okay.
Yeah.
There's no reason to argue because the music denying is right.
Okay.
So at that point, then they're going to look at your contracts.
Now, if you, most people go ahead, they get contracts, credit cards, bank
accounts, driver's license, all that stuff.
Right.
But at that point, if you're going to get into all these contracts, remember
these contracts and things are usually some kind of remuneration exchange of
money or something, right?
When you sign your name.
Now, personally, what I haven't signed my name in 20 years or so, because
every time I asked, they asked me to sign, I signed void and it looks like
a doctor's signature, a VO ID.
When I put a dot over the eye, but it looks like a signature.
I spread it out, you know,
and some people say, what kind of signature is that?
I said, I used to be a doctor, you know, whatever.
It's like, I said, Oh Lord, it looks like a doctor's signature.
Right.
Yeah.
But if I tell you, it says void, you look at it and you see the dot.
You're like, Oh yeah, I could see that.
Right.
Why would you sign it void?
Because everything on that, the paperwork that you're signing is
completely fictional and illegal.
Right.
But if you are going to sign the name, I, by the way, I had a lot of people
doing that and people going into courts and stuff and they said, Oh, I need
to see your signature because some people are signing that, but they shouldn't be
signing.
It's very powerful, by the way.
Right.
Yeah.
But you can sign your name and then put B E N E dot after that, which makes
you beneficiary.
Hmm.
Right.
So that means that if you're dealing with anyone who has your social security
number, by the way, in America, if you get a ticket of any kind of put social
security number right on top, that means they're the trustees, right?
I don't know if you've seen tickets, they do that.
Uh, and you're the beneficiary.
So let's say you run a red light and, uh, whatever, and they give you a ticket
for that.
You don't even need to know what the tickets for.
If they, in other words, if they have your social security number, you don't
have no right as a beneficiary or even care.
You shouldn't care what it's for at all.
Cause they already have your social security.
All you just need.
You said you need for me to approve this so you could get paid basically.
But you say it like that.
And they don't know what you're talking about.
Right.
So everything they do has to be for your benefit.
And I've seen this.
There was a guy a while back.
I was talking to legal stuff and, uh, driving without a license DUI, uh, back
on child support, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Finally, they got him.
He was in jail.
He's talking to me for years.
I was like, no, it's almost a year, six months out at the mining projects.
And, uh, judge reads out.
Well, I'm going to sentence you to this for this and this, for that, you know?
And he says, no, he said something like no or no.
I disagree.
And he goes, why?
He says, because I don't see how any of that will benefit me.
And the judge says, okay, let's dismiss it.
Then crazy, crazy.
Right.
So I'm not saying that'll work every time, but there's many other things.
So if you're the beneficiary and they're coming after your harm to harm you, and
you want it, you want to be, if you're sadomasochist, go ahead, take it, take
it, you know, some people like it.
So it was like Brendan, Joe Williams getting a giant cucumber up their ass.
Right.
So, uh, he's Mr.
Pickle or whatever, Mr.
Cucumber.
That's who's always saying, if you want a big cucumber jammed up your ass and
you're asking for it, who am I to tell you?
No, you shouldn't do that.
Right.
It's a free world, right?
Free country.
You're free human to do that.
Believe it or not.
Some people want to do that.
I've spoken to people with legals and no, I have to do what they say.
Okay.
All right.
Now it gets a little scary because if you read the Bible and one of the things in
Jeremiah, it says, when you look at their faces, you know, and they have these
horrible faces when you're talking to them, don't be afraid of them, you know?
Right.
So, um, just like the lady that was put in, she used to work for the IRS, the
black lady forgot her name, very famous case.
And before the jury went in, the bailiff stuck his door for deliberation.
Final says, well, I have to pay.
She has to pay.
So that's slave mentality, right?
It's over the IRS stuff, but she, again, hence she started becoming the moment
you are brought, if there's a social security number involved, it's your
number, let's say the number you were given to use and they, uh, they have it.
And they're asking you to make decisions.
Now you become like them, a trustee and that all caps name is, uh, is abandoned.
So let's say, for example, you've get dragged into court for anything.
And, um, they have a social security number.
How do you know?
Cause it's a ticket.
You see your name, they put it right on top hospitals, whatever.
They could just punch your name and address and they get it right.
It's access.
It's, it's not the NC, uh, uh, there's, this is another computer.
It's tied in with the NCIS or something.
Um, that the, what's the national criminal investigation
database or something?
Uh, everything's criminal too.
I mean, there's no criminal, everything's commercial, but they consider you to be a
criminal, uh, presumed presumably.
Um, but okay.
Where was I?
Oh, so they have the social security number when you're dealing with anyone
who has that, and you're asked to make a decision or abort fourth, any material
subject matter, and you start acting on that.
Now you become the trustee.
So where's the beneficiary?
Well, you're the only one who could be the beneficiary and they know that.
So now the funds and the bonds and all the stuff they draw drop
is registered as abandoned.
Because let's say, for example, you got Chuck Coachelli, you go into court and
you start, you have signed a B E N E.
So your benefits, you say you're a beneficiary, but then you start, but
how do you plead?
And you stop, you say, oh, I don't plead or plead or I did this.
I wasn't here.
Now you're acting like a trustee and they're going to treat you like a
trustee and that Chuck Coachelli with their social security number, the
beneficiary, when is he going to come in?
Never.
Because you, you already forfeited your position as a beneficiary, didn't
you, by arguing or defending or discussing any material matter.
Now you're your trustee.
Cause trustees supposed to the member of the car.
If you're a beneficiary, just get great me a car.
You don't need to know how much is in the trust or how much it costs.
Trustee does all that, right?
Of course you see.
So now you're acting like a trustee.
Where's the beneficiary, the Chuck Coachelli beneficiary.
What are the chances of the, another Chuck Coachelli showing
up as a beneficiary now?
Zero.
So all those bonds that were created, they put a 10 99 a on it, which is
abandonment acquisition of property.
And those are researchable too.
So the whole thing, what I would say is all this stuff that's put out all the
state of Texas, state of Arizona, state of Georgia, anything you do.
Okay.
So you violated this parole agreement.
So that's a different agreement.
You can go back, you can go back on that and say that you didn't know.
Now, you know, here's the law.
Um, you know what I mean?
That's a whole other discussion, how to undo those things, but you don't even
have to, now you're acting as a trustee if you do that, right?
Right.
So all you have to do is go find out the bond number.
It's going to take 180 days.
Now, 180 days to tell people they're like, Ooh, some people
don't know what that means.
What is 180 days, Chuck?
What does that mean?
Well, it's six months on the calendar.
Yeah.
Half a year.
It's a long time for some things, right?
Right.
But it comes quick.
So once you have that bond number and you say, uh, I need, now I need the
clerk's signature to release the royalties because you know, you have a hold on it.
Holy crap.
Have you heard of cases disappearing?
By the way, I, you know, I haven't seen it myself.
I I've heard you talk about it, but I haven't.
Yeah.
Well, someone says, well, I want to look it up.
I said, it's disappeared.
How are you going to look it up?
You go look it up.
And there's other people that brought this up too.
And he says, I remember that case and look it up and it's gone.
Nothing at all.
I mean, it gets wiped like men in black, you know, and they said, we're going to
wipe your, remember the movie and he's on a computer and you're deleting the.
Right.
Oh yeah.
Well, that's up.
They do that.
Rodney Dale class, a guy that I studied with years ago on this stuff.
He took it all the way to Supreme court and one, but the Supreme, when he was in
the federal court, the Supreme court sealed the case.
This is back in 2016, 2017.
It was over a gun carry.
Um, and you can look up Rodney Dale class Supreme court.
He won actually, uh, because in the attorneys, it's funny because the
attorneys didn't know any law.
They said, well, it's contract.
It's contract.
You got, you can vitiate the contract because it was thrown in jail to sign.
Right.
So when you show them that they're not following those things, we have a
contract, we have a contract, we have a contract.
If you say, uh, there's no contract to say, well, you have to follow the law.
You have to follow the law, follow the law.
They're really scumbags.
They're all of them.
Right.
So it's kind of like, well, they don't know.
Like, I know some of my sister's an attorney.
I told her she doesn't know any of this.
I said, it's perfect.
She's a perfect attorney.
Right.
It doesn't, you know, especially now.
Uh, also if you don't understand what I'm talking about, uh, there was a, uh,
okay, when you become a federal district judge, you kind of get spirited away and
they show you video, you know, like Starbucks, you or McDonald's, you, when
you're going to go work at McDonald's or Starbucks, they pay you and you sit for
a couple of days or one or two days.
I think, you know, when you watch videos on how to flip burgers or be a barista,
same with the federal judges.
They tell you when a case comes in, this is how you direct the case.
And if you, there was a video put on YouTube, uh, it's supposed to be private
for training federal judges, but someone put it up on YouTube quite a while ago
now, and I guess there's enough benefactors or white hats around the
state, leave it up there.
So people know what's going on, but most people won't understand
what they're talking about.
Um, when you're watching the video, the judge says, when you have a case like
this, this is how you use part of the law, right?
Cause you use part of the law.
Then you have to redefine the law to work for you.
Right.
Or it's Erie bound.
And then they'll say, well, this circumstances Erie bound.
And it's like, what the hell is Erie bound?
Well, in 1938, there was a famous case, this set of precedent
for what's called case law.
It was a famous case in 1938, and it was Tompkins versus Erie railroad.
And what happened was Mr.
Tompkins, when he was working as a supplier, he went on the
Erie railroad grounds and he got injured on the train grounds.
So he sued the company for being injured, but he lost the case because, uh, he
didn't have a contract to be there.
The attorneys for the Erie railroad said, well, we had no contract with him.
So, right.
We have no liability.
So everything that's when everything became, that's the
precedent for contract law.
So when you watch the, the, uh, tutoring for the federal judges and he says
that case is Erie bound, that means purely contract law and Erie bound means
referred to Tompkins versus Erie railroad.
I can give more, uh, other, but that's the most famous one that's cited.
So it makes sense.
If you find that video and you hear this old fart, uh, from Alabama
talking about Erie bound Tompkins versus Erie railroad, 1938.
So, so anyway, that's basically just to sum it up, cause it sounded like,
you know, in Greek speak fashion, I've went all over the place.
You're the beneficiary.
Anyone who has the source security number as a trustee and you're the
beneficiary, meaning no matter who they are, you have to agree that
anything they do is for your benefit.
Right.
Uh, the other thing is you're doing whatever you're doing without the
state of, or United States, whenever you see that, right.
State of Alaska, state of New York, all 50 of them or 55 of them.
Right.
Cause you got territories, right?
Uh, you're yeah.
I ran that red light, but I did it without the state of Texas.
Oh, he did.
The cop doesn't know the reason he's a cop is because he's dumb.
Right.
To these things.
Uh, there's a lot of cops, by the way, waking up to this stuff
and they're in a quandary, you know, they're like, Oh shit, what do I do?
Right.
So they're not so dumb, but they are dumb as a general group.
And I'm not saying this, uh, this comes from their own people.
They're their own, the heads of police say they're dumb.
You know, you know that.
I hope you know that.
Yeah.
They call them dumb.
The attorney generals call them dumb.
So this is not my opinion.
This is based on knowledge of what I've been observing within
their own internal structure fraternity.
He doesn't know, but eventually you get bumped around.
And also when you do this kind of stuff, you ever go to court or whatever, you
notice you, they always call you last, but I've gone in a couple of times
with people and myself that last actually they'll have the judge leave
the court and then come back in.
And so he signs when every time they leave, they have to come back in like a
ship, you sign in again, right?
Okay.
Uh, as if the court is not an order and stuff like that, really funky stuff.
And they never look at me or anyone I'm with.
They always look down at the bench.
They, and they start reading things off before you even approach the bar.
They start reading things up and they look down the whole time.
Like, like, uh, uh, eight year old, uh, for cookies, uh, it's got the cookies,
right?
He ate the cookies where the wizard, the cat that ate the bird.
Right.
Always an area.
So just mind that stuff.
But the whole thing about the court thing, you shouldn't even have to be there.
Um, but everything you're doing is without the state of it's all corporate
contract government, and they got the whole world believing that it's
geographic and it's not, you could find that out basically by looking at, uh,
UCC uniform commercial code, start searching their searches.
You can do, um, state of whatever, all of the revised constitutions of the
states, uh, are, they are revised and separate from the original
constitutions of the states.
Now, some of the original constitutions of the state, they do give
meets and bounds geographic.
Right.
But when you get to the revised section, you'll notice, then they talk about,
you know, it's, it's on top of that, right?
So you can use both.
So for example, in Arizona, it's Arizona territory or Arizona state.
And I think it was 1928 or 32.
They put in state of Arizona, which is the corporation, right?
Same with Georgia, same California.
Uh, I said, uh, you know, what's on the flag of California, the state of
California is the corporation, but what's on the flag, what does it say?
California Republic.
There is a, there is right.
If you pull up the flag of California, it's the bear.
It says California Republic, right?
They say, no, you're a 14th amendment citizen, which is another thing, but the
whole thing is to know who you are and who you are is this, you're a peaceful
inhabitant that just so happens to be stuck in a country and a world where
nothing can be paid for.
The only debtor in the whole country is the United States, meaning it's a
corporation, federal corporation in the district of Columbia.
So you can go to the district Columbia and walk around all day and ask people,
where's the United States?
Cause the code says it's in here.
No one knows.
There is one code that the only rights that United States citizen has is to
visit the district of Columbia by permission or from, by, by and from
permission of the boards of the board of directors, not Congress or the
president.
Or so I never heard of a board of directors.
The United States, have you?
I don't know where they are.
Yeah.
Nobody.
Right.
Okay.
It's like the mobsters, right?
The only reason we know where the mobsters are is from watching the
godfather, right?
Yeah.
So, uh, oh, you know what I mean?
It's the same racket, but this is really horrible.
So that every country has one debtor.
It's your federal government.
So, right.
So all, everything going on outside is all based on misunderstanding.
Uh, and the part, by the way, again, you're in Georgia, you J walking and
the cop wants to give you a ticket.
He will tell you in the state of Georgia, he will confer nationality of
the state of Georgia on you right there.
He'll tell you state of Georgia.
You notice that when they read the chart, they read, they have to say
state of Georgia, state of Alaska, state of New York, always do that.
Right.
And at that point, I said, yeah, I ran over that woman with the
stroller and I J walked, but I did it without the state of Georgia when I did
that and they don't know, but when you get into the higher part, they're
gonna say, oh shit, we're busted.
Just ignore him, but you're also the beneficiary.
So right.
Anything they do has to be to your benefit.
Now, if they say we're going to stick 14 cucumbers up your ass and say, yeah,
I like that, well, go for it then.
I can't tell you, you shouldn't do that.
Right.
But that's really like, well, I was just saying to Jason, basically, that's what
he said, they gave me a big cut.
Told me how to stick cucumber up my ass.
I did it.
Right.
And I said, fine, I'm not going to say, you know, uh, but he doesn't know what I
said, and I don't think he he's in a different direction, but this stuff that
I just talked about tonight is very important because if it just from a
matter of principle, there's over 6 million people in jail or in parole in
the United States.
And, um, there's fewer than 10 million people in prison and jail in the whole
world.
So that means that if you took whoever's in prison in the whole world, added it
up, it's about just what's in the United States.
We have, in other words, 50% of the prisoners and people in the quote unquote
justice system in the world are in the U.S.
Right.
That's disproportionate because there were not even 5% of the world's
population.
Yeah.
Right.
So you have 10 times more, 10 to 15 times more chances if you're in the U.S.
So that's why it's important.
It's no longer personal preference because.
Right.
So that's how I see it.
But there's so many ways to go around it.
Uh, you're not going around it.
You're dealing with it head on and you're dealing with a level of ignorance that
is so high, but that it's just, it's cosmic.
You can't imagine that no one knows this.
It's so simple.
The other thing that you can do that works, which is interesting is they, you
go into court.
I'm just as sure.
There's 10 ways to do this, but the easiest way, if you go into a court or
deal with them, you ask the prosecutor, do you serve justice?
Oh yeah.
You know, I try to, um, the judge, do you serve justice?
Yes.
We're here to serve justice, son.
Ask the clerk, do you serve justice?
Yeah, I think so.
How dare you bring me into a pagan temple?
I'm Jewish or I'm Muslim or I'm Christian.
How dare you bring me into a, you know what I mean?
Into a pagan temple.
Because when you serve, you know, that's a, that's a religious term, by the way.
Right.
This is, you know, you know, I think title 42 has got a whole bunch of stuff about
religious oppression, right?
I think it's title 42.
That has that, you know, it's like, uh, uh, uh, obfuscation of rights under the
color of law, you know, is it, uh, 1940 title it's title 42 stuff.
You know, in other words, there's a whole slew of codes that, um, if you are
forced to practice a religion, it's a, it's a quote unquote against their law.
Right.
You could find them.
The title 42 is most likely where you'll find that.
Um, so that is the, that is another thing, right?
There's so many ways, but the whole, the only thing you're not going to escape is
that it's all legal fiction.
It's all bullshit done by people of poor character, attorneys, doctors, accountants.
These are people of poor character, you know, because anyone of good character
will have a, uh, itching feeling inside of them that something is wrong with what
I'm doing.
Right.
And they start to re-examine it.
So, uh, yeah, the attorney doctors, you only need 10% of the population that are
doctors to do emergency stuff.
And even that they don't know what they're doing.
They just do it.
Right.
Uh, it's so funny how the people sit in the emergency room for three, four hours
where you could have done compression and a few other things.
And actually within that time, have it 60% healed.
Right.
It doesn't matter what it is.
Um, uh, but if you need parts, like, you know, if you have a, you know, like blood
transfusion or an organ or something, it's a little more difficult to do on
yourself, but with attorneys, you don't need any attorneys at all.
Just some for some corporate stuff.
If everybody knew what's going on.
Right.
So there's so many, this is the level of redundancy that is horrific.
Horrific.
Um, yeah, I don't know.
I don't know how else to put it, but, uh, that was the, that was a pretty long
explanation, but then that's the simple part because you see, everyone is, is
wondering, um, whatever happened to the, you know, the sitcom, what a sitcom is
usually 30 minutes or the star Trek situational dramas, or let's say one hour.
Uh, they go through a whole situation.
It's the show's going to be over in five minutes.
And then in the last five minutes, they fix everything.
Right.
And then it's over.
That they got that sitcom mentality.
And, uh, that doesn't work that way.
You're going to have to spend to learn more about what I'm saying.
You're gonna have to spend anywhere between 15 minutes to an hour a day
for a good part of a year.
You have that time.
It's just a matter of making it.