This is SonicEvent198 and it's Rated Y.
Hey Greek, you know, it's a little later,
I don't know, the season seems to be
changing on me at the moment, even though
nobody would tell me the season's changing, but
something in the general atmosphere out here in
the Southeast seems to be changing, but would
that matter to you over there?
I'm not sure.
No, it's fine.
See, I eat seasonally and I go with
temperature and I know what happens in the
spring.
You get bursts of cold, there's blooms and
all that sort of things you do to
adjust for it, just like when it gets
cold, you do things to adjust, but everything's
on time.
The oleander always blooms on the middle of
the second month, so it's blooming now, everything's
on time.
You know, lawful second month, you tell an
idiot second month, they think it's February, right?
February, yes.
Yeah, and when I say idiot, it just
means ignorant.
You know, these words that I use, moron,
idiot, whatever, affectionately known, because they're illegitimate words.
They're real words.
They're not slang.
No, there's a quantifiable, hey listen, there's a
quantifiable explanation for exactly who it is, is
technically an idiot.
There is.
Unless you define what is, is, yeah.
Yeah, you got to know what the meaning,
anyway, speaking of that, just wanted to let
you know that we did get a comment
here, which I found interesting.
Keep water from light, which is something you've
been saying for, I don't know, a decade,
at least with me, and it actually makes
sense, this person says.
Light is programming, and if water has memory,
keeping it separate from it makes sense.
Now, that's a fascinating thing, because light in
and of itself is an energy transfer, so
it would affect a lot of things that
it transfers energy to, one way or another.
It's a perturbation in the ether, believe it
or not.
Everything's healthy, that's, I've had someone that wants
to do, I don't know if she'd talk
about it, but let's just say gravity research,
right?
When you say gravity research, you know, meaning
going the other way, and I'm like, oh
yeah, we could do that.
I haven't, but I understand what it is.
It's not, you know, it's not a pull
force, it's a push, and it's all pressure,
and yeah, we can do that.
But the reason I said the light and
the water is because I've been running tests
now for about two years on the Scalarator,
on what affects water, and you know, various
tests on water, and I found that the
water quality reverts back to closer to how
it was before it ran through the device
when it's subject to light.
And I started noticing that, of course, in
the bathroom, you know, I was shaving and
I got an idea kind of thing.
Now, we have an east window, a large
window in the bathroom, and it comes in
in the morning, which is good light, because
you could say it's just light, because it's
not heat and light from the end of
the day.
The western light is hot, warm, and different
color, right?
Well, it hasn't had a chance to cumulatively
build up, right?
To accumulate.
So it's very objective.
It's a good, it's a clean light, and
the drains in the shadow of both the
tub and the sink and the toilet develop
a little bit more mineral on the side
where the light hits it, but never on
the shadow side.
So it's, right, but it wipes off.
It's nothing like it was before it was
hard water, knows what I'm talking about.
You know, like the shower doors, there's clear
glass doors and they're totally squeaky clean without
any work.
And if you've never experienced this in your
own home, typically around the drains, you'll start
to see in some other places like a
yellowish, almost like a nicotine stain on the
tub.
Sure, sir, but what I'm saying, that was
the, like a pun on basically guy was
shaving or taking a shower and he got
an idea.
It was blatant because after I was doing
experiments, but then I noticed like a half
moon, a half ring only on the side
that gets the light, the mineral developing, right?
And now you'll get mineral development, not scale
is a difference, a scale.
You need like a chisel or a hammer
to get it off.
Mineral is just a mineral deposit.
You could wipe off with even mild scrubbing
is the worst you're going to have with
the scale orator.
But my point here was that it was
so objective because the side that always remained
in shadow because the Eastern light's going to
come in only until about 10, 10, 30,
right?
Up until summer.
And then it starts coming in earlier, but,
and it was a perfect half moon mineral
side only where the light hit it.
And then I furthered on light with chilled
water, you know, keeping the water at 39,
one would light one without radical difference again,
more so than if you didn't bring the
water to 39 back and forth, back and
forth.
But pretty soon we're going to have access
to more, I shouldn't say the tools that
exist for testing water are totally, wholly inadequate
because it's just chemical analysis.
So we're gonna have to develop quality analysis,
which is going to have to go with
subtle electrical qualities and ability to carry mineral
and deposit it and all that.
And that's what we're going to do only
because there's nothing really written about it.
Everything is just, you know, when you look
at water tests, it's a strict chemical analysis,
right?
Right.
It's all about how much of the, but
I won't have time to focus too much
on that because right now it's about setting
up the lab and doing some more larger
units, meaning larger pipes and also getting a
crew together that understands it.
And a new website that will be focusing
on the luxury market only, right?
Like a Timex will never be a Rolex.
So if Timex came out with a $30
,000 watch, uh, it, it won't because you
see what I mean?
Because they already are established.
You would be a joke, but eventually if
one day Rolex wanted to come out with
a $20 watch, people would buy it.
Yeah.
They actually did a little more than that.
But during World War II, you know how
all the companies pitched in on, you know,
the war effort, they did make a serviceman's
watch.
And one of them was called the Aviator,
the one that was for field people.
And it wasn't, it's highly collectible by the
way, because it was a limited run and
it was very cheap.
It was affordable to military people and script,
right?
And they only did that during the war
kind of, you know, like Harley Davidson, you
know, made, you know, all this stuff.
There's a whole history to time pieces and
what they did for the U S military
because some of these things became inherited, by
the way, preserves the European military.
But yeah.
But my point here is, but they did
it in the U S too, just saying,
yeah, we want to establish in the luxury
market first and then go over to the
regular people in quotes, you can't do the
reverse.
Uh, like, you know, Volkswagen, uh, made a
V 12 sedan that actually was on par
with Bentley and Rolls Royce.
And it got very little or no attention.
You could buy a used one now for
like six grand and it's really a ride
like a Bentley and it's the quality level
of that.
But no one ever thought to put it
up against the Bentley or Rolls Royce because
it's a Volkswagen, right?
It's the people's cart after all.
I mean, so the thing is, uh, if
I had 20 regular people that wanted a
scale, right, I would turn them down.
They would have to be a high net
worth person that has, uh, or individual, whatever
you want to call it.
But one of the people that has connections
like an agents that are in the art
industry, the high end real estate, uh, you
know, the private jet, the high end cars.
One of those people that never buys a
car off the lot for themselves.
They actually have, I'll just say this with
the heirs of the original Lamborghini motor company
there, because here's the thing, anyone who looks
at the, uh, the, the device on the
website, even though we don't have the luxury
website is like, wow, what the hell is
it?
It's very impressive looking.
You really don't know what it is or
what it does.
There's quite nothing quite like it.
It's quite the piece, you know, to look
at.
It's like eye candy for people that have
been spending all day looking at water treatment
devices like natural action tech.
They have a bunch of PVC pipes with
end caps and a sticker on it and
it's $3,000, right?
And uh, yeah, it's just a, you know,
it's nothing like that.
So anyway, I just wanted to put that
out because the, uh, it's too, this is
the kind of stuff you do when you're
half my age.
Now, I mean, you could start a business
at 80.
It doesn't matter.
Like, um, you know, the guy Bricklin, the
guy who brought Subaru to the U S
in the seventies, they told him he'll never
work.
Right.
Yeah.
And he made the sports car that was
safe and they beat him up.
Uh, every, everyone that had a contract with
them, reneged on the, did not perform and
they forced him to build it with prison
labor in Canada using Bondo.
Anyway, he's wants to do a three wheel
car electric for 30 grand and it looks
like a Lambo or a Ferrari and he
still can't get it going.
And he's 80.
He just started with 82 and I started
the company at 80, the new company.
But anyway, we'll cut, you got any questions
or anything?
Yeah.
I got a few things.
Uh, but just real quickly on the cars
thing, what was that other super safe car
that was around?
Everybody touted it for its safety.
Uh, That was back in the fifties.
The one you taught Tucker.
Well, there was that one, but there was
one that was more recent, like, and it
was very popular in the eighties and it
was like the indestructible kind of car when
people were worried about it.
Of course, it's gotta be the Yugo, right?
No, not the Yugo.
I know.
Yugo is funny though, because Yugo is the
Yugoslavian car and now the country doesn't exist.
Yeah.
It's just horrible.
But yeah, worse than AMC Pacer.
But no, I'm not sure.
The safety Volvo was always Volvo.
That's it.
Yes.
The Volvo.
And that thing faced a similar kind of
weird thing where it popped up in trends.
And then has anybody even seen Volvo in
a while?
I mean, are they, They saw the company
went under because it got, uh, looking for
funding, just like Saab.
I really liked Saabs.
I think they were good.
Well, you have a Saab story.
Oh yeah.
They're excellent cars for driving.
Speaking of shifting culture, actually, somebody sent in
a pseudo question comment, which I'm going to
condense here, because they want to hear your
ideas about something here, considering where you were
born.
In other words, you have a poor view
of culture and how it's pretty much, you
know, nothing and everything is kind of junk.
And what it boils down to is perhaps
that's because you were born in America where
there isn't a cultural history.
There isn't a, what's the word they use
a lineage.
And if perhaps you were born in an
ancient place that had a longer timeline and
ancient culture behind it, uh, and if you
spent time there and not the majority of
your time here in the West or America,
whatever you want to call it, you would
have a completely different view of the world.
Is it possible that you're simply that, let
me give an analogy, analogous answer to that.
You heard me say like people with a
New York accent, you sound dumb no matter,
no matter how smart you are.
Yeah.
I'm going to sound like Boston, but no
matter how smart you are, if you talk
like turdy turd and turd and you look
for you from New York or you sound
dumb, or if you sound like Archie Bunker,
you automatically, it's like, oh, okay, you're, you're,
you're what your chordal cue to cue is.
So I was always curious about that.
But then I found, uh, that a lot
of them were not smart.
And I said, you know, it's probably because
they sound dumb and they are dumb.
Let me get out of New York.
This is a young age now, early teens.
Right.
Let me go out.
Let me get out of New York.
So up and down the East coast.
I met, and here's the thing in New
York, you're going to meet a lot of,
uh, internationals.
I call them Euro trash, but anyway, internationals.
And um, uh, then I went to the
West coast.
I met a lot of internationals.
I went to Europe.
I said, oh no, it's not a New
York problem.
It's a human problem.
People are generally dumb no matter where you're
from.
Now the thing I noticed about most parts
of Europe, if not even if you go
to like Rome, you know, you still have
to pay for water.
You have to, there's a coin for taking
a shower, right?
They meter everything.
Not still, but yeah, yeah.
You could find, if the hotel hasn't been
remodeled since the nineties, if you go to
Rome, to a hotel, they ask you for
a coin, you know, like the vibrating bed
kind of coin, but everything, everything had coins
or what they call tokens in a lot
of places.
Yeah.
You could pick them up from the desk.
Very primitive.
Yeah.
Okay.
Like if you go to Athens or whatever,
it's like downtown Brooklyn is a hundred times
more interesting.
You know, the Parthenon is always falling apart.
There's not, the ruins are not worth it.
If you really want to see the Greek
ruins, you go to the museum of London.
Sorry.
You know about that.
The statues and all that were taken.
They took everything.
Yeah.
So the Elgin marbles and all that.
So, and if you really want to see
Egyptian stuff, you go to the Metropolitan Museum.
They're so flaunting there that they actually erected
some of the Cleopatra's needles in Central Park.
The actual ones they took out of Egypt,
they're in Central Park with the acid rain.
So it very, very, very primitive.
I found, I think the whole thing is
the consciousness element.
Like for example, I spent most of the
day working on the cars we have because
the, the quality of the, the service of
mechanics has gone down so low, something like
building an automatic transmission.
I don't want to do, but engine mounts
and valve covers and valve jobs and all
that.
I'll do most of it because you bring
it to someone.
Yeah.
So what they, it's $150 an hour.
You'll get a bill, you know, you know,
you buy the engine, not put it in
an hour and the engine mounts 40 bucks
and you know, you're going to, they're going
to charge you 400 for that.
Right.
You know?
All right.
So what?
Okay.
But when you get it, you come back,
there's a bolt missing.
They didn't connect this, this or that, whatever.
It's like, what the hell?
You know, this is real basic stuff.
The same thing in 2019 when we would
go out to eat, we had some really
good meals and I would tell the wife
and say, you better enjoy this because you
know, in a few years you won't be
able to go out.
The food will be terrible.
Even the same place.
And I'm right.
Yeah.
Okay.
But here's the thing.
Everything's going down.
Okay.
But, but, but let me, let me just
stop you because I'm hearing all this stuff
about over here in this part of the
world and literally you're being in places where
you're steeped in a culture that could have
only possibly existed a couple hundred years.
Yeah.
Unless I'm like, I have to be gradually
impressed.
I'm not like a, what is it called?
A nitpicker or whatever.
I just have a certain standard and like
I, like I, okay.
Same thing with people.
When you meet someone, make a judgment call
in the first minute and uh, and just
set it aside as a reference and see
if the person moves away from that judgment
call or is really that because if you
get to know the person after a month
and the, your initial 32nd judgment call still
holds true.
Now what you're doing is you're fine tuning
your, your skills, right?
Right.
Don't abandon, don't abandon what you write.
So practice these things.
So what I use is basically references is,
is how people view the place they live,
right?
And from at one point I would say
Americans are pretty high up on the list.
Like for example, uh, on that end, uh,
for example, uh, you know, there's a, if
you even look now, documentaries on most of
the cities and urban areas in India, you
see litter everywhere.
And that started when they were protesting the
government in the fifties, they did it by
throwing the garbage out of their windows on
the street and, and, and not having it
picked up.
And it's somehow they did, they protested for
so long, it became part of the landscape.
It was a cultural thing.
Just like in Spain, they don't say, they
say, they speak with a list because King
Philip had a list and to normalize him,
everyone started speaking with a list, right?
A list.
So there's the normalization part, there's your own
personal references.
Uh, I, I like to make personal references
as objective as possible that have to do
with what's called, uh, you know, health and
fitness, wellbeing, both mental and non-mental.
But here, here's the thing.
This is one of the things I wanted
to get into and not maybe too much
is if you go to a place where
everyone is insane, uh, it doesn't really prove
that well to call one of them insane
because they're all insane and they won't know
what you're talking about.
Right?
So in order to have that, let's say
a malady or an illness, it has to
be narrowed out from the collective group.
So this is very specific because right now
the quick references that I use, I find
that pretty much everyone I run into without
any, very few exceptions or have a slight
insanity, like not, they're not well, right?
Uh, and you can't call them out on
it because everyone else is in the same
boat.
So what do you do?
Right?
Do you keep, you keep it to yourself
and you start building reference points and that's
why you're like, oh yeah, I could be
in solitary confinement just fine.
But anyway, when you go to somebody's house
and you walk in the door and the
place stinks, the people that live there and
the people that are constantly there don't even
smell it anymore.
It's the same thing.
It's like, what do you mean it stinks?
You can't smell it anymore.
Everyone's house stinks.
And if everyone's house stinks.
Here's the thing, if you go to most
Mexican households, it smells like fabuloso.
Every one of them pretty much.
Right?
And they think it smells good.
Okay.
And it goes beyond that.
Uh, you know, I'm, I'm seeing things that
I really never wanted to see, uh, as
a collective and it goes down to the
individual and it really makes me feel like
this is a hundred, uh, you know, a
hundred percent, uh, wrong, um, anybody from India
or Pakistan or from any of the surrounding
areas, uh, you know, geographically there, if they
came from there for about 30 years, if
I stepped into their house, all their houses
smelled the same and it all smelled right.
But, but it's, it goes beyond that.
It's a communication culture.
Um, you know, what they view as being
wellbeing, you know, there's a, well, there's a
way of, uh, there's a wellness or wellbeing
this, if you could say that, that all
humans can share and it has to do
with good hygiene, cleanliness to a degree and,
um, and, uh, a good diet, you know,
based on the seasons and that's what I
was going to point out is they all
had common foods.
They all had common, uh, toiletries and toiletries
they use.
They all use similar cleaning products and it
just seemed to be a shared sort of
a action where obviously, but here's the thing.
In that case, the Americans rule are the
low, the one of the worst when it
comes to food and a bunch of other
stuff.
Uh, so it, it varies so much that
I can't really say, but there is something
that genetic memory may be, uh, for example,
when I was out at the mines, they
were setting up a 48 inch sand screw.
Now, 48 inches sounds pretty small.
No, it was about 50 feet long and
it's 48 inches in diameter.
It's like an Archimedes spiral and it goes
against gravity and water flows one way and
the gold goes up the other way.
The heavies, right?
Okay.
And they, they set it up and they
couldn't get it level.
So I went, there's my first day on
the mind and I started directing how the
steel should be cut and welded.
And the old timers were very upset because
who's this guy, right?
Especially, you know, with a New York accent,
let's say, you know, he's a Yankee.
Well, I don't sound like an Arizona, right?
Or Nevada or whatever, or a Texan or
an Okie or a Colorado, you know, you
have, you have more of a bland East
coast accent.
It's not really specific to New York, but
yeah, sort of a Yankee, but they're very
upset.
So the boss of the operation shows up
and he says, listen to what the Greek
says, because when his ancestors were building the
Parthenon, your ancestors were living in caves.
So and I was like, Ooh, okay, well
thanks.
But I, that's not, that's going to piss
them off even more.
But they chilled out.
But that actually, that actually, this is the
level of truthfulness to that.
But the thing is when I heard, you
know, maybe because of the culture or whatever,
but anyway, I have no direct answer.
What's the other question?
Okay.
Well, there's a couple of things.
Anyway, let's see.
We went through that.
Oh, okay.
Here's another one.
The Greeks, I would like to hear the
Greeks thoughts on Ayahuasca.
And then they go into a whole thing.
I don't know if you want this description
about their experience.
No, no, I've had, I've heard, I have
never done it.
I don't feel like I have a need
for it.
The, I would do, what's the other one
that's popular where you start seeing the matrix
now?
The, well, there's, there's psilocybin, there's psilocybin, which
is natural, there's DMT.
DMT.
I would do the DMT before I did
the Ayahuasca, the synthetic one, believe it or
not, in some cases, synthetics are actually better
to do than natural hallucinations because I've done
the LSD verse and the, not the Ayahuasca,
but the mushrooms.
And actually I would prefer the speed, the
speed high from the synthetic.
See that's weird.
I have exactly the natural, exactly the opposite
experience.
I either got nothing or a very bad
time out of the, uh, uh, the synthetic
and the psilocybin to me was extremely, uh,
helpful, therapeutic.
I, it allowed me to do things psychologically,
emotionally, and even physically, and it never leaves
you.
In other words, you, you could think about
it and he puts you right back in
that state, right?
When you remember what you got from it,
you are literally, you have a permanent alteration
with the psilocybin.
Uh, I've gotten, okay, I've gotten people from
all walks of life.
It was very popular about a decade ago
for people to make pilgrimages, like, you know,
the yuppie type, you know, the guy, you
know, he's taking a month off from working
on wall street.
He's going to spend a 5,000 bucks,
find a shaman down and wherever, and, uh,
do some ayahuasca and they're going to guide
him and all that.
Right.
And they're going to put them in a
teepee or a tent for, uh, they all
had very different reactions.
So one can't say, uh, it does this
or it does that.
Most of them were negative, meaning, uh, in
terms of the way they felt through the
whole thing, uh, in terms of terror and
feeling like they're going to die.
So with that said, why don't, why don't
we give his experience?
Do it.
Instead of just dismissing it, how, what's paraphrase
like what this person's experience was like.
Yeah, I'll do that.
But just a quick commentary here.
You know what, to me, all of this
stuff is legitimate medicine and why?
Because it does have a, there is no
one size fits all anything about it, which
is the way medicine truly works.
There are general guidelines here, but the truth
is some things will be more effective for
you or less effective for you than they
are for me, et cetera.
And it's based on the fact that we
are all constructed just slightly differently.
There are rules that apply, but when it
comes to true medicine, there isn't a standardized
everybody.
There is.
And that's why I believe in medical racism,
whether it's synthetic stuff or natural stuff, people
are, we're very different.
And we've talked about it from a medical
standpoint, ask any anesthesiologist, if he doesn't practice
medical racism, you'll have a lot of dead
black people or melanated people.
Right.
And, and the whole thing with Asians and
there's a, you know, different tropics, they'll kill,
you know?
Yeah.
So anyway.
Okay.
So give us a little bit of a
paraphrase on this person's right.
I'll read part of it.
Let's see.
Okay.
Let's see when.
I was good.
Okay.
So his experience goes like this, you know,
and he talks about how some people talk
about, you know, being able to actually speak
with the gods and all that.
Okay.
He says, I can easily buy into that
concept because I had an experience where I
visually experienced visualizing the hierarchies of various individuals
that seem to play influential roles.
Now they had human form and, but they
look, you know, different because of the experience
itself.
They were amazing, beautiful, all that.
And he doesn't quite know how to describe
it.
And there was not much going on because
I felt too dumb to communicate with them.
So I just sat and observed mostly.
Do you think substances like ayahuasca, another sub
questionnaire, do you think substances like ayahuasca and
psilocybin mushrooms give us direct access to the
realm of the gods?
Indirect access because direct access would be on
command, right?
And it would be a lot cleaner.
And how, how careful should we be about
these experiences?
You know, how seriously should we take them
or is it just kind of another, you
know, form of entertainment?
I think it's personal.
Like, you know, ask someone like Ken Kesey,
Timothy Leary that, you know, and you have
a different answer.
But I don't even know if people know
who Ken Kesey is at Magic Bus Days.
I used to hang out with Michael Graden
who did the trip with him, but he
went by the name of Moses.
And I said, why Moses?
He says, guys, Moses was known for guiding
people.
That's what I do.
And it was a trip when I was
hanging out with, with for a week or
so with Larry, Larry Fishburne.
He's always looking at people in situations and
he says, I want to do a short
movie with Moses and Mike Graden and I
want to have Mickey Rourke cast as him.
And I was like, OK, to give people
an idea.
But the variations of how it should be
used and how often depends on the culture,
believe it or not, and personal preference.
I would suggest and I don't get much
into, you know, after death, what happens.
But if there is any consciousness after you
die, you're going to feel like you're high
and doped out seriously.
It's not going to be anything like a
sober body.
And I would almost want to say when
I told you so later on.
But yeah, when you die and you have
any consciousness, it's like you're high and doped
up.
So if you get high and doped up
now and some serious hallucinogenics, I can almost
say speculatively that's what it's like if you
have consciousness after death.
So to live it up is another way
to think of it.
Another thing, though, just to say here is
I object to the idea of describing the
psilocybin experience as high.
It was not like a high.
It wasn't like smoking weed.
It's almost like, you know, when you're in
movies, they have these multiplexes.
You could walk out of one movie and
go into another.
Yeah.
OK.
It's more like that.
Yeah, it's definitely like that.
And then you're immersed in, you know, like
when you actually get lost in a movie,
in that experience and you're kind of, you
know, sort of suspended.
But here's the thing with the psilocybin, LSD
also, I heard before I first did it,
advice, make sure you're around a good crowd.
Don't be in the city.
You know, it's advice because if someone gives
you a bad head, you know, a bad
vibe, it lasts for the whole time.
It's really hard to get out of it.
And fortunately, that's never happened to me.
But I've seen how people did not have
a good quote unquote trip.
Yeah.
And then people tell you, be around people
you trust because, you know, some people just
decide to be, you know, tricksters of sorts
and, you know, mess with you and, you
know, because they they use themselves.
But psilocybin was just a generally really good
emotional well-being feeling.
Yeah.
Right.
But but they did.
There was a whole other stuff.
Housewives were popping in the 60s.
What was it?
A whole bunch of stuff.
Oh, yeah.
Right.
And yeah, they had a bunch of different
things to make him feel good.
And that's why when you say, hey, dear,
you know, you watch a movie from the
50s, hey, dear, she's so.
I said, I bet she's she's high on
something right now.
Well, there were a lot of 70s that
the actress actually, you know, would be high
as well as.
Well, there were a lot of there were
a lot of what they would call mama's
little helpers right out there.
There you go.
Yeah.
All right.
What else you got?
OK.
Please ask the Greek how we can further
heal old scars on the skin that seem
sensitive after years.
Also with tattoo removal to help with the
skin heal.
Can I compress the skin and wrap it
tight right after a laser treatment?
Yeah, absolutely.
Vacuum wouldn't be lost as much than if
you had a cut on the skin.
But what will happen is the actual burn,
let's say, from the laser treatment will be
your body will interpret it as an injury
and start sending the emergency services there to
swell it.
And right.
So you don't have to wrap it as
tight because it's not an inclusion on the
skin.
It's not anything cut or open like you
would want to seal a tire that has
a cut in it.
Right.
Literally think of it as a pressure differential.
You wouldn't have to have that much.
I would do blue light if and blue
lights.
Very simple.
Go get some blue glass at a thrift
store, stick a light bulb in it and
give yourself an hour of that.
You know, like, for example, when didn't didn't
show God, he is the name chroma therapy
or chroma light therapy thing with the blue
lights and all the different colored lights for
different things.
Yeah, that works like you get a sunburn,
you know, you're going to get a sunburn.
So when you come inside, you know, it's
always worst at night.
You know, if you got some you come
in at night, you're going to sleep anyway.
Put a blue light, which is at least
a hundred watt light bulb.
Now we just have LEDs, very bright light
bulb inside, like a blue mason jar or
something.
We'll get that blue film and sleep with
that on and you'll wake up and there'll
be no sunburn.
It does work.
Really?
Because, you know, I get that if I
get a bad sunburn, I get that physical
feeling almost as if my skin is smoldering.
You know what I mean?
It's a tingling and it's a pain.
It's painful, actually.
And if you take a warm shower, it
feels like you're being scalded.
But the blue light does work.
I mean, I've had I've had doctors look
at it and call it, you know, sun
poisoning many times when I've had, you know,
a lot of damage.
You could justify that several ways.
You got to get melanated, dude.
You need anyway.
No, I have a little bit of that.
So yeah, but no, I would say don't
treat it like an open wound, but definitely
not doesn't have to be that tight.
I would say firm.
You could even do cold water, not ice,
unless you have an ice pack with a
barrier, like, you know, a couple of layers
of cotton or something to keep it from
freezing.
But the blue light would definitely be a
big help.
And yeah, and I don't have much experience
with that because tattoo removal is a laser
treatment and lasers are really funky.
A bunch of people I've been in touch
with actually one is really big on the
laser thing.
And but they don't understand the vacuum and
all the other stuff.
So it'd be interesting to give people that
are practitioners a real understanding of how the
human body works and then go reapply what
they think is a cure all for a
lot of things.
But anyway, anything else?
Not really.
There was there's a question in progress the
next time we get together.
It's about colors.
And I'm going to wait until he responds
to me because I asked him to clarify
to make more sense of it.
But also somebody, you know, was there was
a couple of comments that standing out this
week about, you know, everything is a waste
of time.
And I say that, yeah, a great T
-shirt could come out of that, except instead
of quoting the Greek on it.
What you do is you give people the
idea that since they're the ones reading it,
you and everything around you is a waste
of time.
Make that like a thought of the day
T-shirt and just print that on both
sides and big, big white text on a
black background.
And boom.
I wonder, though, the market that would actually
buy that T-shirt, would they think it's
so much of a waste of time that
they wouldn't bother buying the T-shirt and
it wouldn't work as a product?
Yeah, that's right.
It's self-defeating.
I would think of it.
Yeah.
The wordage is very important, like brainwashing and
washing your brain.
Right.
Very different syntax.
Well, you should say syntax, but very different
impression.
Like I was very sad to see the
people that came up and actually started using
the moniker mental floss because I thought that
was a great concept.
Mental floss.
That's actually you cleaning out the little bits
of crap that are stuck around your mind.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
The stuff that you chewed and never really
got to where it was supposed to go.
It just hangs around.
But I would say that there's probably a
better way to say it.
I've been thinking that everything is about wasting
your time for a very long time.
I just didn't know how to say it.
So I said, just call it how you
see it.
Yeah.
It is.
What is it?
Occam's razor, the simplest solution is often the
correct one.
There you go.
I mean, I paraphrase.
Some people resist that.
They say, it's not a waste of time.
I have memory.
I'm like, oh my gosh, triggered.
Occam's razor.
In real life.
So look, I know you had a couple
of ideas, etc.
But anything, this will be our final get
together on the the platform they call Skype.
So I do need to ask you, and
somebody did ask it because I guess they
missed the last couple.
Are you going to continue the financial discussion
you were having as a group discussion on
teams or.
Yeah.
I'm taking.
Here's I'll do a public thing.
If I'm not going around that much.
I'm not.
I wanted to get a bunch of people.
This is not for anyone.
Whatever.
Don't take it personally.
But I need.
I don't know.
It just didn't it didn't work out for
me.
Let's just say it that way.
So I haven't been revisiting it or anything.
It's still.
OK.
Yeah.
It just didn't work out.
But that's fine.
I mean, I have no expectations.
And but no, but I am still continuing
the financial work with another group, believe it
or not.
And we'll see how that goes.
I have no expectations there either.
The reason I did it is like from
the old parlance that you hear and what
they call Buddhism and the old philosophy, philosophical
reasons.
If you do something for selfish reasons, but
it's still good.
It's still a good thing.
Right.
Because if you didn't do it, no good
would have come out of it.
I'm doing the financial thing strictly for selfish
reasons, because I want to stay with the
inventing and the creative stuff.
I have so much to do that I
do not want to spend time on the
financial end.
So I figured if I can get some
people up to speed with it, they will
benefit clearly in their personal lives.
And I could work with them and they
would also handle my stuff.
So I don't have to spend time with
it.
So they get the benefit of knowing how
to do it and they can take it
off your hands.
And there you go.
So, you know, yeah.
And then I could start a trust and
then they could be a trustee of my
trust and I would reciprocate trustee of their
trust.
And to have an organization, all that now,
I'm not condemning anyone or anything, but right
now, as it is for me, it's on
hold.
And give an example like today at 10
a.m., I was contacted out of the
blue the other day from someone that I've
known for 15 years, haven't met their they
do real estate and all this other stuff.
And this is, hey, I'd like you to
bring you into a conference that we have
every Saturday morning.
And these guys are into the financial system
and they are and they're actually working in
it.
But they don't know much and they were
quite impressed with what I brought.
And I was not so impressed, but it's
very workable.
My big thing with people is communication.
I think everyone needs to work on their
communication skills, including myself.
But when I see the communication is lacking,
I just have to step away.
I'm not there to correct that.
People have to work that on their own.
And I say, hey, if you if if
you ever get a criticism that you're not
a good communicator, just emulate someone who is.
That's how physical therapy works.
Right.
Or mental therapy.
Just copy.
Like if you know someone who is an
artist, for example, they you know, they have
like writer's block.
Yeah, it's almost like the concept of act
as if.
Right.
I think, yeah, I've known some artists, professional
artists, portrait painters and stuff.
And when they go through like a block,
a creative block, they get these big coffee
table books.
They pay like 200 bucks from these large
Picasso books or Rembrandt.
And they start just copying that painting to
see how well they can copy it, to
go through that other person's motions.
Right.
And then that breaks them out of their
funk.
Right.
So I've told people, if you have a
problem, hey, listen, I may not be the
best to ever just just, you know, emulate
the way I speak.
Well, a lot of musicians, when they get
down creatively, kind of what do they do?
They get together with a couple of friends
and they start playing the songs that they
enjoyed to try to emulate the creations that
they were inspired to do their own.
Enjoying, I'm saying is just do a cover.
Do somebody plays with somebody else's play?
What I'm saying is the thing that inspired
them to be a musician.
Now they go through the motions of doing
it.
And it's sort of a way of accomplishing
the same goal, right?
Yeah, sort of.
It's just a matter of the thing is
to still have a discipline, even though it's
not your personal way, but you go through
the motions just like a physical therapy.
If someone has trouble walking, there is a
standard way of walking.
Everyone has a different gate and a different
step and all that.
But if there's a standard way, go ahead
and do that just to get yourself moving
and then go ahead and freestyle.
It's called freestyling, right?
Everybody's freestyling.
So, yeah, it's fine.
But everyone has their own pace at learning
and being proactive.
But I need it like front loaded and
fast.
This is kind of like we're going to
war in 30 days.
This is not a 90 day boot camp.
It's a 30 day boot camp, you know,
kind of thing.
So I would hate to have to do
what I'm doing and the financial stuff and
the administrative stuff.
Oh, my gosh, that would be that would
really like stuff that I would say I
get done in six months now will take
me a year or two years.
So it kills, by the way, doing the
financially administrative stuff, the stuff the bankers like
to do, you know, being like that, because
you have to be just like them for
them to, you know, to work with them
destroys creativity for me.
I can't go back from in the middle
of doing some R&D or developing something.
And I spend an hour doing bulls of
exchange or studying something that I want to
get into.
I go back to what I was working
on.
And it's like, what the hell am I
doing?
I forgot or this doesn't you know, even
if I took notes, I can't go.
So I know I have to separate that.
Right.
And that's why I'm doing it.
I just want to find people.