Hey, SonicEvent194, and hey, Greek, what is that?
I heard something tapping there just as I
was...
Oh yeah, I just turned...
I have an automatic ignition gas stove, I'm
making seasoned rice, but it's brown rice.
And it's funny, you know, people invited me
for dinner over the years, I got a
reputation of showing up about an hour, hour
and a half before the dinner starts, so
I could go to the kitchen and do
the cooking.
With your tools, with your tool bag, so
to speak, right?
And I got my tool bag and some
ingredients, which, you know, good salt, you know,
whatever.
And I got this, Sondra Means is her
name, she knew about that from the grapevine,
and I showed up and she goes, I
know what you're doing, you're here to cook,
no, I'm cooking.
She gave me a hard time about it,
and my wife was there at the time,
she was laughing because she thought I would
always get away with it.
But the point here is, she made a
dinner...
Wait, you mean you didn't get away with
it that time?
No, she wouldn't let me in the kitchen
because she knew that was my MO.
I'm surprised, I'm surprised, because dealing with you,
I have this hard time thinking that people
resist you in person, I don't know why.
Well, no, but anyway, she prepared like a
broiled salmon with veg and brown rice, and
my first comment was, this is an unwritten,
unspoken rule, when you have an animal protein
like fish or meat or whatever, fowl, and
you always serve that with white rice, never
brown rice.
Brown rice is when you go veg across
the board.
Why?
Because brown rice has got more than enough
energy than you're going to need.
Here's something, we eat food to get energy,
and energy is different qualities.
Most people don't think it that way, they
think, oh, well, yeah, I know I get
energy because when I'm hungry, I go along,
and energy, there's even like a Snickers commercial
about that, right?
Well, they're still on the burning concept, and
they go, oh, it's my fuel, it's the
fuel, we're burning fuel.
Yeah, well, not at all, yeah.
We could get into it with the car,
by the way, you're not burning gasoline in
a car, you're actually, you're adding vapors and
things that are ignitable to the air, you're
actually burning the air.
Right.
That's why a gasoline, you could substitute gasoline
for propane, like in warehouse forklifts, you could
substitute it for alcohol, you could substitute it
for hydrogen.
So yeah, it's just a very juvenile way,
but the people, you know, they're minors, right?
Remember, I've read the statute that even though
you will still be considered a minor even
though you are of legal age, what does
that tell you?
You're a minor for the rest of your
life.
And if you remember from early Sonics, I
always say, you might, people that call yourself
minority, shame on you, it has nothing to
do with your skin complexion.
It's purely that you're incompetent, right, legally.
So anyway, you've heard that, but anyway, back
to the dinner stuff.
Oh yeah, and by the way, back in
the 50s on the Sonics, like somewhere around
Sonic 50 something or other, somebody was catching
up and they just, you know, started not
too long ago and they were saying how
great the cabbage was.
I just, oh yeah, well, I've gotten a
lot of, yeah, the cabbage roast, it's cabbage
roast and broccoli steak and right.
I just got, I just got that feedback
like two days ago.
So I'm just telling you that that was
like a couple of new people that are
coming through and searching through and they're actually,
the reason we're really doing this is because
when I occasionally get an email, I've changed
my entire life, you know, and I'm like,
oh, great.
Because if you know that my adage, if
half the people in the world helped one
person, right, the whole world is taken care
of.
So I've done that with hundreds of people,
if not more.
And it's objective.
It's objective information.
It's not like, well, that's how he likes
it.
So I do it.
So, you know, it's very objectifying.
But anyway, back to the food, when you're
doing a whole grain, people don't really eat
whole oats, you know, they're very difficult to
eat.
Right.
I've had whole oats.
It's quite interesting.
They usually roll them because the shell on
the outside doesn't soften with with cooking.
But whole grains usually is veg all the
way.
And when you're going to do an animal,
when I say, you know, people are used
to calling an animal, right?
Fish, poultry, bird, fowl, you know, whatever, four
legged, whatever, anything that's animal protein, go with
white rice, a very basic starch.
Here's another thing, way to look at it.
You know, the concept of potato skins and
potato with the skin on and all that,
you can do that with an all veg.
But when you're going to prepare a potato
dish, start with animal, make sure all the
peel is off because that peel carries all
this energy.
But by the way, potato peels produce soil.
They produce what's called by by two minute
by humus, lignites and all these other things.
So when people when you buy potatoes, you're
like, oh, there's dirt on there.
That's actually the dirt that was produced by
the potato.
Is that wonderful?
But anyway, just to give you an idea
of the perspective, but I have some tuna,
some tuna that I've been curing out slowly
and I'm going to have that with the
brown rice.
So I was a Greek.
You're just contradicting yourself.
Yes, I know.
But I'm going to have like a very
tiny amount of brown rice on the side,
mostly with some veg after we finish the
sonic because I didn't feel like making anything
else.
I felt like an extra protein.
But if you ever wanted to, like, do
a super load, do like beef or lamb
with burdock stir fry and brown rice.
If you just ate brown rice, you'd be
fine.
If you just ate the beef, you'd be
If you just ate the burdock, you'd be
fine.
Could you imagine all three together?
It's like rocket fuel, jet fuel and racing
fuel put together.
Right.
And TNT.
I was just thinking all three things are
like highly potent.
Oh, my gosh.
The burdock will give you more energy than
the beef.
The brown rice is in between.
And, you know, what beef does, you know,
it's very energetic.
Cows like to kick.
You want to you don't want to eat.
The reason you get energy from beef is
cows are kickers.
People don't know that.
Right.
They kick a lot.
A cow doesn't like you.
It'll turn around, just get out of the
way.
But anyway, but I think the cows that
most people are familiar with are totally subdued
and drugged out.
Right.
They're so doped up and messed up from
the hormone treatments and whatever the hell else
is.
Yeah.
Their horns are cut.
You know, all the cows have horns as
part of their character and they cut the
horns and all that.
So, yeah.
So that's the spiel on the food.
Very, very important.
No date on the food seminar yet.
And I have to blame.
It's not an excuse, but I'm going to
put the blame on the financial seminar.
It's taking a lot of energy to get
it set up so it can run.
People can run on their own.
We've got some new people coming in.
It's really good.
All right.
Probably the only thing I have is a
stupid Skype link to something.
So I've gotten some people interested.
But the thing is, if you're not active,
you get booted.
And there's a bunch of people that are
not active.
And I still haven't booted them.
And I may not.
I don't know.
But the food seminar, when things slow down,
I keep saying that we'll do that.
That's very, very important.
Right now, that link to the financial seminar
is still in the Patreon chat.
Yeah.
If you go there, the link for the
other one is there because I keep just
changing groups.
If you're a guest, no guests.
If you're a guest, we'll boot you.
You got to have a name if you
want.
Just pick a stupid name just so we
know not who you are, but how to
refer to you and call you, you know,
whatever.
You know, when you say someone's name, you
know what name you use for your avatar.
But if you say guest 348, you're like,
I don't know, that may not be me.
I mean, you know, maybe I'm a guest.
I hear you.
So you're going to carry that over to
teams after the fifth, though.
Right.
You have no choice.
I just tell everybody, leave it alone and
they'll automatically switch for you.
That's what it says.
Yeah.
But but teams is like they're they're copying
Zoom.
They're giving only one hour on calls.
And then there's a premium for 30 hours,
which Skype was unlimited.
We ran around the days 10, 15 years
ago.
Brain food.
Yeah.
They ran a group.
Ran for about a year.
Went for like a year.
It was like a year.
As long as two computers were on all
the time.
Right.
And that was run by a guy, a
Brit expat that lived in, oh, Jamaica or
something, or Belize.
One man outfit should salute to you if
you're still out there.
So, yeah, that was back in the day.
I met a lot of people there.
I wonder if that guy.
Not much.
Yeah.
Much brain food.
But I got you.
I wonder if anybody ever recorded any of
that, though, because some of those I mean,
some things were just stupid and some things
were very enlightening.
And there were interesting people.
I didn't find anything, but that's OK.
It's a matter of taste, right?
Well, it depends.
I mean, I went in there at certain
times a day and, you know, it would
just be like a personal conversation almost because
they just, you know.
Yeah, that's what it was.
And most personal conversations to me are absolutely
worthless.
Well, like I said, OK.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, I know.
It's you got to be.
Look, I don't have that much time left
here.
I don't think anybody really does.
I just tell it like it is.
If you want to know what I'm thinking,
listen to what I'm saying.
I have no inner monologue.
And I've stressed that to that.
No one should have that.
But all right.
What do you got?
Got questions tonight?
Well, I got a couple.
Just a few, though.
Let's see.
Please ask the Greek to elaborate more on
why he mentioned that sex is for procreation
only.
That's from the last Sonic, by the way.
Well, that's right.
You were given.
It's kind of like a pinky.
You have a pinky so you can pick
your nose, right?
Think of it.
So, you know, you have a thumb.
So you have an opposing member.
There's a purpose for everything, like your appendix
is.
Yeah.
Your appendix is not there because of evolution
that shrunk away.
It was another thing.
No, your appendix is a sourdough starter.
So when you're lacking positive intestinal flora required
for positive intestinal flora and fauna for having
efficient digestion, it's it's produced in the appendix
and then pumped out.
These medical morons will never.
They can never just like the legal morons.
The attorneys never learn any law.
Right.
So you you have a component that is
psychological and it's good for the beneficial for
energy flow in the body, you can say.
But there are exercises.
There's an extra.
There's an old video.
Wilhelm Reich developed an exercise for men who
had too much pent up sexual energy to
do.
So it's basically just laying on your back
and arching your back up and then doing
rapid breathing motion, rapid contraction, extraction of your
diaphragm, you know, like you suck your stomach
way in and then push it way out
while your back is arched up a little
bit.
I've tried it.
It works.
That's to give off sexual energy.
Give me an example with the sex, the
way it's done.
It's used.
The social engineering part is interesting because that
is purely for population control.
When they want to increase the population.
Yes, you have herders, masters, groups that control
you.
And it's good if you don't know it.
It's working right.
If you don't know that you've been socially
engineered, that means that the social engineering is
working very well.
Right.
Yeah.
OK, so when they want to increase the
population, they restrict.
Sexual activity, you can't talk about it.
There's no condoms behind the counter at the
store.
Nothing above the knee on TV and media.
Right.
Very like you'd see in Muslim countries, very
much.
You'd see in whatever restrictive Mormon, whatever.
OK, so when they want to decrease the
population, they promote sexuality.
Now, suddenly, you have condoms behind the convenience
store counter visible.
A lot of sex insinuation, a lot of
sex showing all the way to the point
to where the rating would not be for
below 18 on regular media.
But like right now, they oversex you.
So you're popular.
So you have no children.
Right.
Even the publicly shown numbers right now are
demonstrating that in the United States, we are
not even, you know, keeping up with replacement.
Oh, we passed that like five years ago.
It's like one point one point two children
now or something.
I'm being born.
Might be lower.
And it might be lower than that.
One, two, you're seeing that the fertility rate
is lower.
Sperm counts are lower.
All these things are lower.
That's right.
Now, let me just give this because most
people never heard these.
Most people have never heard the stuff I
talk about and never will.
Unless they get it from here.
That's the sad part for me.
Right.
Because I'd like to shut up and sit
back and listen to somebody else.
But anyway, give me an example, if you
didn't quite get my point.
When you go to one of these Mormon
community, a Muslim community, I don't pick some
other sexual what they call sexual repression, which
it's not, by the way.
But that's a form.
That's how the label would be put on
it.
Puritanical in general thought.
Yeah.
The thought process of a puritanical kind of
mindset regarding sex.
Pick any society.
Go knock on their door.
How many children are here?
Oh, we got five children and one more
on the way.
How many should not go to the next
house randomly knock on the door?
How many children?
You have nine children.
How many children do you have?
We have three.
And how old is your wife?
She's 18.
You know, no, those are a third baby.
I used to meet guys from Muslim countries
all the time.
And from the 90s, the early 2000s and
stuff.
And they were always parts of families where
it's like, you know, 70 kids.
Right.
OK, now let's let's change it over.
Just to illustrate, let's go to a place
like New York City, Tokyo, L.A., do
a random knock on door.
How many children?
We don't have any children.
Oh, you've been married 23 years.
OK.
Now go to the next.
How many children you have?
We have one child next door.
How many do not next door?
One, two.
We have two children.
Wow.
So where the sex is being promoted, the
population has been going down and where it's
not promoted or actually slightly held back or
held back.
Now, when I say the pop, the sexuality
is held back.
They still have a lot of romantic songs,
courting, courting, you know, those Muslim countries.
I was just telling you about every single
one of their songs.
If you translate it, everything is about love,
their love, who they're loving, who they're being
with, who they want to be with.
That's everything.
So so this is a phenomenon that is
actually one on one social engineering that no
one is talking about, by the way.
No one is realizing it because the social
engineering works.
So when you tell people, you know, it's
a conspiracy theory, that means that the the
the mind control is working.
Well, some people have talked about this, but
they've never connected what you just connected there,
which is that in a place where you
have like what people think of as repression
is where the population is growing, you know,
where it's like, keep the you know, the
women in turtlenecks and make sure that their
skirts are long or maybe no.
But there's no reason for it.
I still fervently tell people, hey, you, you
know that everyone around you and your family
at work on the street is a moron.
So if that's true, no one has ever
said Greek.
My parents are not morons.
My family's are not morons.
No one's ever come back today.
Greek, I feel so.
Everyone's like, yeah, I guess so.
In this sense, the people I don't even
know.
And they're like, yeah, you know, I specifically
say the people you live with, the people
you work with, the people you see on
a recreation are all idiots.
Yeah.
So OK, so if we take that as
a given with few exceptions, right, how easy
it is to put on a social control
mechanism.
And why would you tell them, quote unquote,
the truth of the matter?
We're idiots.
See, that's the thing.
A lot of the social engineering is completely
misunderstood because they have a logical sort of
through line for these things.
And they think, oh, it must work this
way.
So in a place where they're promoting sex,
that must be a place where they're wanting
you to breathe.
Like when they put terrorism on a country,
that's because they're they they're telling the people
we're not afraid of you.
Now we're coming after you.
Middle Nation talked about that in one of
his videos.
I had it in the background when the
government is afraid of its people.
It tries to maintain peace and order when
a government is not afraid of its people.
It just goes out and just kills anyone
randomly like the drone strike.
Just does what they do, you know, whatever
they want.
That's why the CIA does these experiments, because
they, you know, they're American based, supposedly, and
they want to know.
But, you know, we might want to try
this here.
Let's go take over a country and just
have that that government, a puppet government, put
and start just killing people publicly and see
what the reaction is now.
You know, every decade they do that.
Right.
Speaking of that, speaking of that, a funny
thing is going on right now.
Right.
Everybody's talking about, you know, Trump and the
politics and blah, blah, blah.
And everybody's having their moments of outrage.
But these people are not understanding certain things.
Like they're trying to get rid of USAID.
And they go, well, that's us doing good
around the world.
And it's like, no, what's happening there is
they're reorganizing the intelligence community because all of
that.
Yeah, but let's go back to the theme
here that I brought up.
The U.S. government is afraid of the
U.S. population, and it's not because of
the guns, because they could slowly, just like
they restricted population control, they could restrict the
guns are no good without bullets.
You don't go after the guns and bullets
and the best guns you're going to get.
You're outgunned by.
So, you know, you're not.
There's more people with guns in the U
.S. and then people with guns in the
whole world combined.
And it's like ten to one.
The military in the U.S. military that
we know about is very small.
That's great.
The U.S. population has at least ten
times more.
If you got 80,000 BB guns, though,
you're no more than a nuisance.
OK, what I'm saying is that the small
arms and everybody thinks is there, you know,
their big defense against the gun.
If they want to, they'll hit you with
a drone from the sky.
You won't even hear it coming.
Well, it's not even that.
Yeah, that's true.
But that's singling out.
But I'm talking about mass population, but they're
moronic.
You see, the Americans are too moronic.
They cannot work in order to have a
revolution or a civil war.
We never had a civil war, by the
way.
They'd call it a civil war.
It was the war of northern aggression, the
war of the states.
It was to give the federal government taxation
power.
And that's I've seen documents written at the
time about it.
But here's the thing.
The people in order to this is from
Middle Nation.
So he he made a good point in
order to be revolutionary or whatever to go
against any power structure.
You have to have good art.
You have to have good knowledge.
You have to have a knowledge of the
classics.
You have to have rationale.
And Americans don't have that.
Of course.
Right.
It's been because of the social engineering.
I'm not saying people are not capable of
that.
I don't see many that are.
But it's they're victims of this social engineering
program.
All right.
What else you got?
Well, you know, I have an odd question
for you, because I think I picked up
on something from you in our many conversations
here.
And I want to check.
I don't think you've ever been around.
Like, I know you've been around black people
and you talked about it being in New
York and melanated individuals, you know, what most
people call black people.
But I don't think you've actually spent time
around black people that grew up in the
South, have you?
Oh, yeah, I have.
Really?
Yeah.
I've been to Buford, South Carolina.
I've been around in my early in the
70s.
I have.
They are very much still social engineered the
way of the slave days.
But it's terrified of dogs.
Yeah.
Terrified of dogs.
Even a little chihuahua.
They're terrified.
They look down when they speak to white
people.
They look down at the ground.
Very if you want to know what it
was like to be black in the 1800s
in the South, it hasn't changed very much
in many ways.
But at the same time, what I did
see that people don't know that it's never
really talked about is the affluent communities that
are like Georgia.
You know, there was a joke.
Why don't we send all the black people
where they came from?
Atlanta, Georgia.
Right.
There's some guy comedian made a joke about
that.
Right.
But no one talks about the affluent communities
you'll find in and around near Georgia, in
and around New Jersey.
Well, there are even places.
When you say black people, they're so stigmatized.
There are even places in Mississippi, quite honestly,
which you would think of as one of
the harshest, most, you know, like definitely throwback
kind of to slave day states possible.
Right.
But they even had whole communities where they
separated and created an affluent situation where they
put in the.
Yeah, that's why they were against civil rights,
because they knew with civil rights, the white
man's going to butt in and and bring
their police and create slavery again.
It's like 20 percent of the people that
produce crimes that go to prison are black.
But 80 percent of the people in prison,
I mean, are indicted for crimes.
Let's say, yes, 20 percent of the population
is black.
But the 80 percent of the population is
black in prison.
So what they're doing is bring back the
slave system for black people with civil rights.
People don't know this.
Civil rights was the worst thing that ever
happened.
It's a 14th Amendment thing.
And I think I believe in meritocracy and
believe it or not, the world really runs
a meritocracy.
That's why people in general, any country in
the world have a dislike for government workers,
because they know if you work for the
government, you could go punch in and go
to the movies all day, not do nothing
and you won't get fired.
It's not a meritocracy working, you know, in
a public municipal job.
Right.
I find it strange that you think the
world works on meritocracy.
Because it does work on meritocracy.
Well, quite honestly, when I mean, do you
do you think a guy like Elon Musk
is there at a merit?
Oh, no, that's well, no, I'm talking about
the world, except for the power structure.
You know what?
Elon Musk is 200 billion.
He's just a slave.
Then no one talks about the two and
a half trillion.
The Rothschilds are worse.
Why not?
And the Rothschilds are just clerks.
They're not even part of the power structure.
I mean, they are.
They're the closest you can get publicly about
the power structure.
You know, the Rockefellers, the industrialists and the
bankers.
Right.
Habsburgs, they've lost their power a long time.
It's all under the main power is underground,
subsurface, literally subsurface.
Now, the let's go back to the people
of darker complexion.
There there's no separation in terms of behavior,
conditioning or anything like that that anyone else
would be subject to.
Right.
There's no.
How would you say it?
And I'm not trying to be political correct
at all.
I mean, I don't care about like member
Jimmy the Greek.
He said, you know, the black people are
better at why there's so many black people
in sports is because they were used to
running around in the jungle and all that.
And they got something like that.
Right.
Well, he said what happened is, is that
when they were breeding people slave days, they
decided to breed the biggest, strongest women with
the biggest, strongest men.
And they got the biggest, strongest.
Yes, we made a point like that.
So there's stupid stuff like that.
But it's a very in other words, it
doesn't matter what your complexion is or race,
quote unquote, because you have the Asian race
or whatever.
It's it's the society and the mind control
that you've been subject to.
And it starts in your culture, in your
family, how you've literally how your parents were,
unless you abandon what your parents, even the
Bible tells you, abandon the ways of your
parents.
Right.
But but here's the interesting thing.
There was a study done a long time
ago about Chinese people speak Chinese because they're
Chinese.
So they did an experiment where they put
in Caucasians from Europe in America, born in
China, and they spoke Chinese just as well
as Chinese.
Right.
And behaved their mannerisms and all that just
as equal.
So all that racist stuff doesn't work.
Now, there is medical racism.
We've talked about that.
Right.
Yeah, there's certain that's why you won't find
certain psychotropic Prozac in Asia kills people.
If you're Korean, take Prozac, you die.
We've talked about this.
There are biological differences that have come up
among groups of people that are connected to
particular by biographical areas.
Right.
I mean, it's just not biographical.
You know what I'm trying to say?
The discussion, by the way, with people of
darker complexion always ends up being a class
struggle discussion.
It's a class.
Yeah, it's a class thing, not a racist
thing.
Well, we do have in America a caste
system and they wave it in your face
all the time.
Middle class.
They're getting rid of the middle class.
Why is there any class system at all?
So they're developed a class system that they
pigeonhole people in and they cloak it with
racism and all that.
You know, the most racist people towards black
people are black people is what I've noticed,
you know, in the mixed environment, not just
in one specific deep south thing, but being
around different parts of the country.
Well, I don't know.
The deep south thing is different to me
because the the linguistic base is different here
than it was up north.
You know, I mean, I'm familiar with it.
I remember being in Buford, South Carolina.
Guy literally had a pickup truck with a
dog in the back and a rifle rack.
Yeah.
And he says that's common, by the way.
He says, listen, Greek, we pulled up from
someone's house.
You got to stay in here because I
got to go talk southern to these folks.
Somebody say in the car.
So, I mean, that's how critical it can
be.
Right.
The culture.
Yeah.
But I mean, it is it is strange
because I mean, it does not even remotely
resemble.
I mean, up north, it would resemble the
language.
I was the reason why it was settled
by Scots and certain people from Europe that
maintained a closed structure.
They were merchant class.
And you don't want to corrupt your your
status.
You want to corrupt your bloodline.
So they kept to themselves.
Language formed a certain way.
And it just stuck that way.
Look, just like why do people from New
York sound like they're from New York, dirty,
dirty, dirty?
You know, I learned at a very young
age if you had a New York accent
and you spoke like this, no matter how
smart you are, you sound dumb.
Yeah.
Right.
And there are.
And fortunately, you don't see a lot of
that on YouTube.
And but whenever you heard someone that is
showing New York accent, it was like, oh,
that's a really there's not there's no.
So I learned that, you know, you better
not, you know, because I saw it coming
and I ducked.
Well, yes, I got you.
Look, even the Jersey accent, which I have.
They they they often already.
Yeah, it's not thick, though.
It's not.
They could it could come through if I'm
around for people from Brooklyn or Jersey, wherever
I get way worse.
Yeah, it gets way worse if you're around.
But Jersey, Jersey is more like this, you
know?
Yeah, right.
Exactly.
Jersey is, you know, you got a thing.
It goes like that.
New York is a little softer on the
top.
You know, it's more flowing.
It sounds more like Italian.
Right.
Jersey.
You know, Jersey is like, yeah, yeah.
From Jersey, you know.
Right.
But either way, let's listen to Nicholson.
And what's the little his little friend?
Oh, David.
Danny DeVito.
And who else is from New Jersey?
I almost got in one of his movies
once.
But anyway, you know what I'm talking about?
I think that was a fairly correct assumption.
The Jersey New York accent.
I got you.
You know, you're right.
But the thing is, it's either either one
of them, though.
It creates an assumption in the listener that
you're not as intelligent.
Just not like the Boston.
When you Boston cock the calf, that's a
little bit.
It's almost as bad.
But not you don't sound like if you
have a New York accent, right?
You sound dumb.
Yeah.
You're not automatically stupid if you're from Boston.
I mean, you could be your suspect, you
know, but but you're automatically stupid if you're
from.
Well, it's kind of like when I got
on the Internet, like people from Australia sounded
dumb to me and people from New Zealand
sounded like arrogant assholes.
Right.
And initially and I used to joke around
about that and they didn't find it funny.
So I stopped joking around about that.
You know, they meaning the New Zealand, the
Kiwis and the Aussies.
Yeah.
What was what was even worse is when
you mix them up and I go, well,
what's the difference?
Well, what?
Oh, there's a big.
I know.
And then there's South African, which is the
mixture of Dutch and English and all that
stuff.
Yeah.
You got to be good with accents.
Also, believe it or not, I could tell
a person's race and nationality but just by
their voice.
Right.
If it's a black guy, Asian guy, even
if they're completely whitewashed, you can tell there's
a vocal cord thing.
There is biological differences or whatever.
Right.
When it comes to voice and major.
Well, to me, I can hear it.
Like when I was speaking with Sam, people
thought he was a white guy.
I said, oh, he's black.
How do you know he's black?
And I said, no, it's obvious he's black.
I said, I can't tell.
Right.
So I can hear when I spoke to
him, that's for sure.
But yeah, there's subtle differences.
This is all part of being on planet
Earth.
But what is social engineering?
It's just got everybody at arms, even within
the groups, you know, even within the groups
that's been going on for a long time.
And it's going to go on as as
long as you don't have rocket packs and
hotel on the moon, it's going to be
going on.
Because when you have rocket packs and hotel
and when things will change again, you're never
going to get those things.
So these things are never going to change
in this society, not in this lifetime.
Anyways, I got one more question and then,
you know, we can just run from there.
Can the Greek offer advice for the best
ways to eliminate parasites in our body?
Now, that seems to me to be a
wide.
Yeah, because the parasites are changing constantly.
Like dog breeds from 100 years ago are
not the same.
No matter how you like German shepherds were
really, you know, great dogs.
And now you got a German shepherd who
hip dysplasia.
He's going to have hip problems.
Right.
So you have certain parasites that are not
even acknowledged.
Like I remember the fleshy bacteria or whatever
showed up at one point.
And I went, whoa, where the hell did
that come from?
Because that wasn't here before.
A lot of the parasites that were dangerous
100 years ago are harmless.
And a lot of there's new parasites that
they don't acknowledge, because when you work in
the medical industry and if you see something
on the slide that you are told you're
not supposed to see, they just negate it.
They do exclusions, right?
Complete exclusions.
There are there are parasites that live on
put on plutonium rods in nuclear power plants.
Well, also, as some things have thawed out,
OK, it appears to me as though we've
lost some we have lost some ice cap
here and there.
If we've thawed out stuff that's been frozen
for a thousand years, it's very possible there's.
Yeah, but I'm talking about emergence.
I don't go for that.
That stuff has to come from somewhere.
Stuff comes from nowhere.
You know, you can have pure, sterile conditions
and put it in in a certain way
where it's absent of certain light and you
introduce some gases and you'll see things forming
in their biologicals where there was no way
that we live in a world where things
emerge from inorganic life, yet organic life, believe
it or not.
And they have the conditions just right.
Let's go back to the thing.
There's a walnut, whole clove.
Right.
And one other thing, walnut, whole black walnut,
whole clove and one other mixture.
There are capsules you could buy.
It's a powder.
Start off with that.
Those are the basic there.
If you if you if you did a
search on this online, that's the basic I
think they still exist.
There were parasite cleansing was really big 15,
20 years ago, especially with Hilda Clark and
all that.
OK, so the basic capsules that are available,
it's got walnut, whole clove and one other
thing, I forgot what it was.
Wormwood.
Yeah.
And that's it.
Thank you, Wormwood.
That's the basic.
It's like 30 bucks for 100 capsules or
whatever.
Do that.
Start off with that.
Go very mild.
Start off.
OK, start off mild.
If you work a job or a job
that you have to go to work from
nine to five or be somewhere because you
might get the shits.
Right.
And in a way that you don't expect.
Yeah.
Be careful with the Wormwood, though, because I
used to be able to get that in
whole and I could grind it myself.
And it was a lot cheaper than buying
a powder.
And, you know, get it from a trusted
source.
This is very much when it's a powder.
It takes in three days.
It's oxidized just like coffee.
Coffee connoisseurs ground the beans right before.
Because if it's pre ground, it's oxidized.
It just tastes flat.
Well, that would be the reason why I
wanted to grind it myself.
The reason I'm suggesting what I'm doing is
this is very, very mild.
The next step up would require research and
some self diagnosis.
Right.
The main thing about parasites is, believe it
or not, most people now have them in
their liver and they thread through your liver.
Those don't come out very easy.
Right.
And if you if they try to, you
can have a liver damage, which you can
recover from.
And by the way, anything that's not in
your intestine your body created.
That's a pretty scary thought.
But for an example, OK, let's get off
on this.
You ever see surface dust mites on skin
mites?
Like when you show they show a picture
of it.
Oh, yeah.
And it looks like some sci fi creature
from another planet.
And so that lives on your skin.
Yeah.
They show you the weird things that live
on your eyebrows even.
Right.
The.
Yeah.
And you cannot get rid of those because
they they form.
They emerge from all the conditions on your
on your body.
And that freaks people out, especially if you're
if you know about this.
You just found out about this.
All the pictures are tripped on LSD.
You'd probably get like 80 grit sandpaper and
sand all your skin off.
Right.
So, yeah, it's some crazy stuff.
But anyway, these things are emergent.
So the thing is, are you in harmony
and are you in symbiosis with it?
Is it causing harm and damage to you?
Uh, everyone has them to a degree.
Like I said, if they're not just in
your intestines or stomach, your body created them.
Now what?
These things emerge from different conditions.
Right.
So the people in cold climates will have
a different set of parasites than people in
the tropics.
Right.
And vice versa.
I mean, people in temperate areas and different
ones in the northern hemisphere.
If you think the earth is around different
ones on the southern hemisphere or the southern
plain, northern plain, these things are emergent.
So most of the toxins that are things
that are found in the blood, if not,
well, all anything found in your blood, by
the way, your body created.
Right.
It's a completely closed system.
And when it's done, it's usefulness disintegrates and
becomes energy.
And it goes out through the appropriate organs,
bladder, intestine, liver, kidney, you know, the urinary
tract, which is the entire, they call the
urinary tract, the entire system of kidneys and
bladder and all that.
But yeah, so don't, don't, uh, you have
to self diagnosis is the key.
You have to diagnose that.
Right.
But I'll tell you that most, the majority
of the stuff that is disabling to people
are parasites and a metal in their bodies,
thallium from old, uh, the amalgam fillings, they
put some nasty chemicals in there, uh, and
also not having proper dentistry.
Uh, so yeah, this is a big topic.
Um, I would study, if I were to
get into this for whatever reason, the first
thing I would do is research diagnosing, uh,
parasites, not the parasites themselves with diagnosing a
man or a woman's health condition, and then
which parasite would be responsible for that.
Right.
And then how to test for that.
But remember, I'm saying it again for the
fifth time, if you find anything like in
the liver or any of the organs or
whatever, or suggest even in the brain that
was created by your body because of what
you eat, what you've been exposed to.
Right.