Sonic Event 14, Oteli in the Greek, welcome to it.
You know, this is, this is going to be yet another diverse discussion, I think.
But I don't know, I don't know how much input I'm going to have on this one, Greg, how you
doing today?
Doing all right.
It's about what the second week, I think.
We're just starting the second week of the second month, 2.2.
You know, it's funny, I was listening to somebody that, they got these YouTube channels called,
actually, if I say what they do, it's in their title, but they call themselves decoders.
And they're supposedly so smart.
And it's funny, because they recently put up a two and a half hour video, had it on
in the background while I was working on a class D amplifier, just redoing the terminals
and stuff, running silver wire, taking the copper out and stuff like that.
But anyway, I was listening to that.
And it was funny, like the first half hour, they're talking about calendars, and oh, my
goodness, the presumptions and the, what, you know, which, oh, this one's, this Hebrew
calendar is really, yeah, because it's 13 lunar months.
You're always like, oh, my goodness, oh, my goodness, and hey, I'm not going to contact
them.
No, if you guys want to contact them, you know, whoever's, thinks they got hot pants
on for timekeeping, I would suggest you go and contact them and lay it out for them if
you can.
Because let me tell you, man, YouTube, I call it you, you know, when people want to change
a water pump or something, or want to learn how to do dovetail joints, they go to YouTube
University.
And one guy, one time on a call, Greek man, I can't find this YouTube University online.
I said, Oh, no, no, no, that's what I call it.
In other words, when you want to learn how to do something, like physical or whatever,
you know, in terms of like real basic rudimentary based stuff, I call it go to YouTube, watch
YouTube video, call it YouTube University.
Right?
Like I saw a guy the other day, which I thought was perfectly acceptable, teaching you how
to play a keyboard.
He says, Listen, if you can learn four chords, I can teach you to play about 500 songs.
Sure.
Yeah, pop music.
Yeah.
And I said, Okay, fair enough.
And then I took a little look, you look at his demonstration.
I said, Yeah, that's about right.
Because there's common elements to commonly known songs.
Again, you know, if you want to learn how to change a pipe in your sink, if you want
to learn how to change the oil in your car, if you want to learn a little bit about maybe
how to work with some wood or whatever, you may find different qualities of individuals
on there, but plenty of how to's.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
I'll tell you the only thing like being completely forthright.
I'm kind of glad archaics came around Jason Breshears.
Because I don't subscribe to him.
I mean, literally, I've never I don't subscribe.
I haven't subscribed to his channel, or I endorse what he says.
But he's a breath of fresh air, because he's reasonably intelligent.
And he actually cites, let me just put it this way, for years, like when I was started
on Revolution Radio speaking publicly in Santos Bonacci back in 2010, 2011, and all that my
whole thing was, look, if you want a new idea, read an old book, you got to go back to stuff
from before 1920 and 1800s is fine.
You don't have to go back before, because they did in the 1800s, they did so many anthologies
and all the ancient writs.
If you're reading something about, let's say, the book of the Egyptian Book of the Dead
that was written in the 1800s, it's good, trust me, it's fine, it's trustworthy, right?
But if you read something about the Egyptian Book of the Dead, published 1920s and later,
no good, no good, right?
So he's always hearkening back to the old stuff.
But the rest, I don't know, and I got to tip my hat, because he gave me something I didn't
have, which was the 138-year cycle, which is contemplative.
I don't see diehard proof of the 138-year period.
I think he's reading into it more than he's reading out of it, you know what I mean?
And that was Santos on that, huh?
Because I used to speak with him a bit.
This was Jason of Archaic, that's my critique, and I'm glad he came around.
Santos is too airy-fairy for me.
Yeah, that's why I was surprised.
Yeah, he was intrigued, you know, because we were on American Freedom Radio, I used to
call in American Freedom Radio all the time, and Danny says, you need to get a show here.
This was back in 2010, and I was calling Vinnie Eastwood all the time.
And I said, no, no, no, stuff I have to say, it's not time yet.
People are too excited, you know, it's too free, they're not, they have no, I don't see
enough evidence of people looking back far enough to understand what the hell I'm going
to say.
Everything is too new.
I want other people to crack the ice, you know, about going back to old books and stuff.
I don't want to be the one to break the ice on stuff.
But not until we did the ONG, I said, okay, it's time to start breaking the ice.
Or trailblazing.
Because it ain't happening, you know?
It was, we started 2015-16 on the Pope's work schedule, something like that, 2015.
Yeah, I think it was 2015, the first ones.
You know what's interesting is that a bunch of people that I'm not sure ever heard you,
I hear little bits and pieces of things that were lifted from some of those on occasion.
Just in passing, you know, and it just, it catches my attention because I realize how
different that was at the time.
But over the years, I've noticed a couple of people, it's like, wait a minute, that sounds
really familiar.
And yeah.
You mean like Greek speak?
Yeah, like Greek speak.
Oh, like, this thing about the books.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It started, because at the time when I was yelling about it, and timekeeping and how
the human body works and stuff, people were like, huh, what?
And so I said, no, no, no, I need, I'm not the type of person to break the ice on this
or be the first one, you know?
I'm not going to pop anyone's intellectual cherry, so to speak.
I'm not into that.
Virgins are boring, by the way.
So anyway, yeah, yeah.
So anyway, I just wanted to put that out.
And you know, I've been saying, look, I've run into people.
Yeah, well, fair enough.
I want to bring up something from the chat, because you just mentioned this 138 year time
period.
And I noticed in the chat that somebody had asked about these time periods, which you
mentioned in a previous Sonic.
I think it was the 30, 40, and, wait a minute, no, no, no, 120.
Yeah, 70.
But the big ones are 20, 40, 70, and 120.
And they're close enough.
Like, if you look at, for example, the biblical chronology of 70 years in Babylon, it was
really 71.
And if you count the entire thing with the getting to Babylon and getting out, it was
closer to 73, 74.
So that's how the chronologies work, you know?
But it's not like the moon landings.
Remember, Bush says we're going to be going to the moon in 2014.
He said that in 2000.
And then in 2014, so we'll be going by 2022.
And now they're saying they're going to go by 20.
You see what I mean?
It's not like that.
We're talking about stuff that is mentioned to happen and then when it actually happens.
Well, it's interesting to me because, look, 40 years is like a full generation having
come and gone.
You know, 70 years, you have that cleansing, that time for perspective.
Psychologically, I look at this.
And 120 years, you're completely removed from what came before, right?
Well, I think you could do it today.
You can do it in two weeks.
No.
Well, see now.
It's not 120.
I mean, not two weeks, but two years.
Well, things disappear.
11, 20 years.
Yeah.
I mean, see, that's the thing is that I've noted an acceleration, but the natural flow
of things seems to be more like this, where over the course of a lifetime, you have people's
memories that shift.
Now, like you said, nowadays, yeah, it happens faster.
You kind of stole my punchline because I was going to say that, you know, that requires
people to have an attention span and to retain knowledge, which is almost unheard of anymore.
Yeah.
If we, okay, this is how I look at it.
This is my kind of from the Victor Schauberger point of view, trees and rocks.
You know, people call rocks inanimate or whatever, but, you know, it's not fair because I'm suggesting
that rocks have one thought for a few seconds every few thousand years or a thousand years.
So the rock has a five-second thought.
I'd like to be closer to that rock right there.
She's real pretty.
And a thousand years later, he has another thought, oh, what happened to that rock?
Right?
So, okay.
So that's one way of time.
And then trees are the other.
If you want to know really how the generations in terms of the earth is concerned, look at
how long it takes for forests to grow.
I'm not talking just trees, but a forest, which is a community of trees, let's say.
And then you have these aspens, which they look like a forest, but it's really one organism.
They're all connected, right?
So just like society becomes all connected.
So in the sense of 120 years for a tree, well, it's not very long, is it?
You know, no, not very long.
And again, you have various things that interact.
And by the way, I don't think it's just the one kind of forest that's like that.
I think all forests sort of interact in that way, but some of them are more cohesive than
others because they're all interdependent.
Even the animals.
They need shade.
Some trees, trees that need shade have to grow near trees that are taller.
Well, even their death, the death of the animal, when the animal dies, decays, and some of
it sinks into the earth, that literally does put a nutrient in the soil that allows other
things to grow.
So, you know, sort of sinks into the soil.
You haven't been around dead animals.
They get eaten up or picked up by others before it sinks into the soil.
But I got you, though.
That's a good point.
But eventually some part of it does.
Yeah.
It's more processed.
It's not as direct.
But yeah.
No, I mean, well, even soaking the soil with blood, which typically happens if something
is attacked and actually taken down, right?
If it's being...
It's a symbol.
It's definitely a symbol.
Well, more than a symbol, though, because doesn't it literally feed the ground a bit?
Not really.
No?
No.
Okay.
Misconception on my part.
But back to this 40-70-120, what does that, you know, some people start going into it
and you get the, like you said, airy-fairy with Santos there.
And I like Santos.
He's not a bad guy.
Oh, no.
He's not.
He's actually...
It'd be a lot of fun to tell him to bring his guitar, hang out.
Absolutely.
So you have a blast.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
But some people might go, well, those are frequencies.
And I'm like, no, they're not frequencies, but...
They're vibrations.
Yeah.
You know, but here's the thing with Santos and Jason.
He's taking advantage of ignorant people.
In other words, from two points of view, if you read the comments section, oh, my gosh.
Oh, my gosh.
These people are...
Anyway.
What I mean taking advantage of ignorant people is he makes a lot of mistakes.
So do everyone that makes mistakes.
But some of them are big.
And I'm not being light and fair here because, sorry, you're going to have to know Greek
speak to see the mistakes.
Because no one really looks there where I've looked, you know, and usually in most cases.
So I look at the comments.
So let's say, for example, you know, you'll have a thing with 400 comments and I go through
most of them, if not all of them.
We'll get into speed reading one day.
You know, you actually look at something and then look away and see if you could read it
while you're looking away, like you're taking a picture of it.
You know, that's another form of speed reading.
So anyway, I look at all these comments and I'm like, wow, okay, no one here brought up
timekeeping.
No one here brought up this part of this.
No one brought up that.
There's 400 people commenting and no one picked it up.
Wow.
You know?
So, you know, what was one of my mottos for a while has been, why bother?
I mean, but they mean well.
Here's the, you know, intent.
If you pick up on someone's intent, right, like people don't like attorneys even though
they don't understand the legal system because it's not because of anything other that they
know the intent of the attorney is to cheat and lie.
Even the attorney doesn't even know that.
He's just in that culture.
It's part of his culture.
He doesn't even know, most of them don't know that they're doing it.
So, people don't like attorneys and now doctors specifically because they don't know anything
about what they're doing, but they know that they're going to cheat and lie.
So, these guys that we mentioned are not like that.
Their intent is good.
But at the same time, if the people don't know, it grows and grows, you know, and it
becomes a certain cult, as I should say, kind of thing, cult of personality.
So, and this is not to mention any more names like Cliff High or someone like that.
You wouldn't believe like every few months, oh, Greek, you got to go listen to Cliff High.
I said, okay, Cliff High, all right, he means well.
Actually, he means very well.
He doesn't have to be doing what he's doing.
A lot of people might have heard of him.
He's a perfect example of someone who sounds smart and is not, right?
And someone, if you're making hardcore predictions with dates and they don't come true, you only
get one or two chances.
This guy who's making predictions every six months with dates and everything for like
the past five years and nothing ever comes through, ever, and he still has a growing
following.
So, is he doing anything wrong?
No.
Actually, it's kind of like when Fox, some businessmen try to sue Fox News back in the
day and went to court and they dismissed the case because they said you can't sue Fox News
for libel because they're entertainment.
Yeah, right.
You know.
Right.
Which, yeah, they're currently going through a lawsuit, too, and I'm waiting for that to
come out again.
Yeah.
It's all entertainment.
So, this is all entertainment at the end of the day.
At the end of the day, if you're listening to these guys and it's more fun than being
with whoever you're usually with or your job or job, you know the difference between a job
and a job?
Okay.
Go ahead.
So, a job is usually, you know, you do an application, which is you do a pledging, begging
form.
To apply means to beg, by the way, to plead.
And they pay you a usually prevailing wage of some kind with some kind of ancillary compensation
they call benefits.
And by the way, if you know anyone that works in the military for a career military or airman
job, like I said, how's your job?
Oh, I love it.
It's got a lot of bennies.
They call it the bennies.
Yeah, right.
Yeah.
So, I'm like, oh my gosh.
When I hear that, that's like, you know, borderline, this person's an NPC.
But anyway, that's a job.
You know, they file, you have to file a return to the revenue department.
You notice I didn't say pay taxes?
Right.
Right?
Because I don't know anyone who's ever paid any taxes.
I've never met anyone or really heard.
People say they do.
So, when people say they do something and they're really not, what do you call them?
Crazy.
Crazy?
Anyway.
So, okay.
So, you file with the revenue department, you know, return, right, because you're using
private credit.
You can't just go and rent a chainsaw and bring it back and wave goodbye and say there's
no law that I have to pay you.
That's going to cause a lot of trouble.
You're using private credit.
So, you have to tell them how much of the private credit you use and you have to give them a
cutback, a kickback.
That's all it is.
And if you don't do it, you get in big trouble.
This happens with the mob also, by the way, guys.
It happens with any organization, legal or not.
I had a hard time trying to explain that to somebody recently where I was like, look, what
it's really about is you can do whatever you want as long as you operate and you pay the
person who...
Or return.
Yeah.
You pay, the term I use, but what you're doing is you're giving them a cut.
Right.
Of what you're doing.
They do this all the time when you go to a cherry or apple picking thing, co-op, you
pick apples, you have to give so much back and you keep a certain amount.
You know?
So, okay.
That's...
Okay.
So, anyway, that's a job.
You know, the basic stuff.
You get retirement pension.
Okay.
A yob, like I got a yob, man.
A yob is there's no application.
There's no return.
Usually, you get paid with bank notes, Federal Reserve notes or some kind of barter.
There's no retirement.
Anyway.
Anyway, it's a bad joke.
I got you.
It's not racist or ethnic, but it's a yob, man.
I got a yob.
Okay?
I totally understand.
That's the difference between a yob and a job.
I've had both.
Okay.
By the way.
But, yeah, go ahead.
I've had both.
Yeah.
All right.
So, that's basically...
We drifted away from this and that.
And I just wanted to say that, yeah, the internet is funny.
I do like YouTube University.
We also spoke just briefly before you hit the red button or record about debating.
Yes.
And I wanted to bring this up because I've always been challenged, not recently because
I try to keep to myself now as much as possible.
The academics used to want to debate me and I used to tell the academics and say, okay,
you just got professorship and you want to debate me on the medical stuff.
Okay.
You're going to need to go and find your professor and his professor, if he's still
alive, all the whole department, the physics department, hydrology department and chemistry
department, the entire department, all of the authors, if they're still alive, of all
the books you've ever read on all of these subjects and you're still going to lose.
And that was like, I didn't mean that to be an intimidation tactic to them, but they got
intimidated.
They said, oh, no, I won't debate you then.
They actually believed what I said and I wasn't joking, by the way.
Another time I went and someone wanted to debate me, a similar subject was on physics.
I said, okay, someone was there with their daughter, with me, had their 12-year-old daughter.
I said, I'm not going to debate you on physics.
I need 20 minutes because I'm going to coach her.
She knows nothing on the subject for 20 minutes.
She's going to debate you and you're still going to lose.
And this was like a master's degree, whatever, physics person.
So, this is the problem with debating and why am I so confident about that confidence?
And I can prove it.
I can do it.
This is what happens in debates that's a big flaw and no one notices.
There's a saying that says, never correct your opponent when they're making mistakes.
Actually, it's more like, never correct your enemy when they're making mistakes.
See, I don't see anyone as an enemy, but your opponent, your adversary.
Never correct your adversary when they're making mistakes.
What do you hear, Chuck?
You've seen debates on various subjects, probably the one that you research.
Yeah.
What do they do?
Always.
One guy finishes and the other guy starts to correct the other guy.
Right.
That's not how you gain any ground on the battlefield at all.
And typically, by the way, before you even discussed this with me, before I pressed record,
I recognize that.
That's why people say, you should debate this.
I don't debate these people.
It is so pointless.
Well, you can.
Oh, I can.
But you've got to show up.
You don't show up to a knife fight with a knife, because then you're going to try to
prove that you're a better knife fighter and you might get cut in the process.
And you don't show up with a gun, you show up with a nuke.
So everyone within a five-mile radius is done.
See, because the debates are not between the two debaters.
It's to educate the audience.
It's an excellent Socratic education tool.
Even though the debates in a Socrates-type setting only last ten seconds, you see, they
don't go on and on and on.
Oh, no, I agree with you.
It's an excellent tool, but the execution...
That it's just exactly as you described, by the way, where it's just, oh, well, let me
tell you what you just said wrong.
That doesn't help you, and it doesn't help...
No, it gives me a headache.
It actually helps them.
It gives me a headache, because, yeah, I'm watching this, and yeah, I could maybe learn
something from it, possibly, but it's not effective.
I mean, you know, please read Sun Tzu, at least, before you do this.
You know, we were talking about maybe there should be a video start here for Greek-speak.
Anyone who's listened to what I call primary or fundamental Greek-speak, the basic, basic
rants that I go on, I cover timekeeping, the human body, water, a bunch of other stuff.
Okay, those simple analogies that I give on fundamental Greek-speak, like if I had
just 15 minutes to say what Greek-speak is about, that is what I use in the debates.
Strictly that.
And that's it.
Never address what they're saying, because how can you address what they're saying?
Why would you address what the opponent is saying if it's false?
You would just be... if you're looking not to correct him, because that would be a disadvantage
to you, right?
Remember, never correct your enemy when they're making mistakes.
So you cannot address what they're saying to correct it, and you cannot...
you shouldn't really repeat what they said, because then it's redundancy.
So you have to rise above it and give an overall perspective that a five-year-old...
I like to keep the perspective within eight-year-old comprehension, eight to twelve-year-old,
which is Victorian grammar school.
People don't know.
I think I've mentioned this before.
If you go study like the, quote-unquote, intellectual giants of the 19th century,
there was something called Victorian grammar school.
It was more of a formalized type of education.
Later on, the formal education that exists now came from Prussia.
But in Victorian grammar school, you went to school, basically.
You had the primer, basic, and then your schooling, which would be, let's say,
considered high school and college, would be between the years of seven and thirteen years old.
And your bachelor degree would be between, let's say, twelve and fifteen years old.
That's why when you look up people from the 19th century,
like this one guy was at Cambridge, right, or Oxford, and he was in this year.
Well, you go back and see when he was born and what year he's at Oxford,
and he's 20 years old as a professor.
He's like, wait a second, because 20 years old, I'm basically not even...
I have another two years to get a bachelor's degree.
Well, how could I... you see?
So you'll see evidence of people having all their education done by 15 or 16,
completely college... you see what I mean?
Right.
Back then, that's basically how it was.
I got off the subject.
Let's reel this back into what we wanted to talk about.
Well, I started with the time periods, and then we kind of went into debating and all that,
which I think you should...
Oh, the chat.
The essence of the chat is good, usually.
In this Rated Y chat, I've noticed that it's hopping enough and pertinent enough to address,
and we will.
I asked about what subjects to get deep and solo, or solo and deep,
and there are quite a few, and I think you brought up orally earlier
about the farming and the ether and all that, that Vandy brought up in the chat,
and that's a really big subject because we want to keep the little guys happy,
which are the plants, and some of them are big, too.
And the easiest thing, just like people...
Okay, we'll get into that on another sonic, but this is how I approach plants.
They're organisms, living organisms.
Of course.
Eating just plants is vegetarian and plant-based, but they're still a living organism.
Okay, I've gone over this loosely, but plants are always in a dream state.
So imagine you're in a dream, and your arm gets cut off, and you're like,
oh, I'm in a dream.
My arm got cut off.
Big deal, right?
Right.
Well, that's why you can go up to a plant and break off a leaf and eat it or whatever,
or get chewed up.
By the way, other than frogs, all hallucinogenics are gotten from what source?
Plants.
You see?
It's very simple.
Well, plants are the decaying plants because the mushrooms are different.
Yeah, well, mushrooms are not plants, and they're not animals.
They're something else.
Well, that's what I said.
It's different.
Yeah, just like spiders are not insects.
The other thing about spiders, we'll get back to plants real quick,
is spiders are incredible.
They can turn off their psyche.
In other words, there is no psychic perception of spiders.
You know you have a psychic perception if there's a bug around,
if you're tuned into it?
But a spider could crawl on your shoulder, and you won't even know it's there
until you see it, if it wants to hide itself psychically.
So anyway, I think David Bowie sung about the spiders on Mars at one point, didn't he?
Yeah, he did.
But I've taken notice of that before, that spiders are one of those things.
The way I've always put it is spiders are one of the creatures
that can really, truly sneak up on you.
Right, because of their psychic ability.
In other words, within the ether.
So back to plants.
I gave the person an analogy, and the human body is like an upside-down plant.
You have the limbs, which are the arms.
You have the seed, which is the ovum and the sperm.
And you have the flower, which is the genitalia.
And you have the root ball, which is the brain.
So if you turn a human upside down, stick him in the ground,
he basically resembles a plant.
Okay, so we have an ethereal flip.
But basically, I said you want to keep the little guys happy.
I have a primrose bush here.
It makes these little roses, and just because they're little,
the plant is large, the shrub is large,
and it's full of maybe 2,000 roses right now, maybe more.
It's a beautiful primrose.
They're not really roses, but they kind of resemble a rose bush.
I guess it is.
So anyway, these guys, the plants, you want to keep them happy.
So let's go back to the people analogy.
I've been giving people analogies here with the dream state
and the upside-down nature and this and that.
Okay, Chuck, we've got a group of people.
We can make them happy by internally making them feel,
and also giving them good food and drink, let's say.
A good party, so they're gratified, right?
Let's say you make people happy.
Or you could break out a whole bunch of drugs, get them high.
That's another way to make people happy, isn't it?
It'll work, yeah.
But usually when you have good food and drink and gratification from that,
it lasts a long time, and you come off of it good.
What happens when you get people happy when you give them drugs?
Some of them come off of it not so well,
but everybody's going to say,
it was better when I was high, right?
I'm not high now, and I've got to go on with the rest of it.
Whatever.
Well, it's either that or you get them caught in a cycle of,
they continuously go back to getting high, in which case, you know.
Sure, and that's what's going on with plants.
So you live in a society,
and by the way, this is Greek-speak.
You're not going to probably have anyone else hear this.
I'll say this this way, very simply.
All these fertilizers, chemical or whatever,
you know what they're doing?
They're getting the plants high,
and when you get them high, they do what they do.
Just like if you got a crowd, and you got them high,
and you put on some music, they're all going to want to jump up and dance,
take their clothes off, whatever, right?
So you give plants these drugs, what do they do?
They spurt out leaves and buds and bloom
and put out veg and fruit and whatever, right?
But they're high.
So it's not going to be that great.
A musician knows that if you do a session,
and you get really high,
you think you're playing the best stuff ever,
and you go the next day, and when you sober up,
listen to the recording,
oh, that sounds like shit.
I have tried so many times to explain that,
and I'll tell you it takes so many times.
I was a musician for a while,
and I can't tell you how many times I've had to have that conversation
where it's like, I realize you're enjoying playing
when you're high.
And you think that you're doing a great set,
or it came out really, you played it really well this time.
Yeah, because you think it's great,
because it sounds great to you.
Make sure you're recording it, though.
Yeah, right, because when I listen back,
I go, ooh.
That was really bad.
This is exactly what's going on.
So when you get a fruit or a veg from plants
that grew that while they were high,
it might look good, but it has no flavor,
no taste, and no nutrition.
I'm giving this analogy
because what I'm trying to do is pair up our existence
with everything that exists around us, right?
And this pairing, what it does is
it allows one to understand the flow
of when to give, when not to give,
what to do, what not to do,
instead of, oh, I read it somewhere,
and I think this might work.
So we'll get into that.
But essentially, I did give an answer there
that most of the vegetative layer
is slightly below the earth and slightly above the earth.
That's where you want to make ethereal adjustments.
And I'll have to think about that a little more
because on the solo sonics,
I think I'm going to go really, really deep
and give a lot of information.
So I'm going to need an outline for that.
So all that stuff's being worked on.
Fair enough.
But also that brings us to water
and the subject that we neglected
in the last sonic, which is hygiene.
But no one knows we neglected it
because we never even brought it up on the sonics.
I thought we brought it up for a moment
and then just spun away.
I think in the end, yeah, cutting it off.
So the water, which one should do first?
They both go together because
to have something spiritually clean,
it has to be cleaned with water.
Are you familiar with that, even from pagan rituals?
Yes, practical.
I was just going to say, in a very practical way,
there is nothing that gets cleaned either.
And again, think about the practices.
All right, I'm going to bring up something really bad here,
but even the idea where they do the baptisms, right?
There is water involved.
Anytime you're cleaning, resetting,
anytime you're transferring energy,
all of these processes involve water.
Now, somebody might say, well, obviously,
because you're on planet Earth, dummy,
and the majority of what happens on this planet
is dictated to by water.
Water is a part of everything that occurs, right?
Right, but from a spiritual point of view,
it's not chemical.
Like, give an example.
You can have something that's deemed unclean
and then have it cleaned just by washing it, right?
Right.
But if you were to scan it with all the men's materialistic stuff,
you won't find anything unclean.
It's just a spiritual, it's part of a process
because the memory of the thing,
I think it's like synesthesia or being synesthetic,
like certain people, I don't think it's the correct term.
This is where you can have sex.
If you give an axe to someone that was very psychic
and that axe was used to kill someone,
they'll pick up on that, where an average person won't.
Yeah, I have experienced that with metallic objects myself,
but only metallic objects.
Sure.
So I want to get into the more important part
because, you know, I always say if you're giving,
got something important to say and your battery's low,
just get the important part out
so when the battery dies, at least you got, right?
You see?
Yeah.
So, water, okay.
I think on the page you have the water thing
that we did a few years ago, quite a few years ago now,
more than a few.
I added that to the playlist, yeah, I did.
Okay, so I think I remember what we spoke about there.
So all that holds true.
But what I've been working on lately,
and if anyone is familiar with Ken Wheeler's talk on magnetism,
and if you're familiar, not just glossed by,
when I say the inertial plane or the block wall of a magnet,
okay, what is that?
Okay, so if you look up in standard, you know,
the guys who are major league bullshitters,
you know, the academics.
Right.
Even if you go to their diagrams, everything's incorrect,
but they do, if you put in block wall in a search,
B-L-O-C-H, it's with an H instead of a K for block,
you're going to see a line going through between the poles
along the body of the magnet.
When I mean the body of the magnet, typically,
now a lot of refrigerator magnets and magnetic tape
are not magnetized this way, but your basic,
except for horseshoe magnets on the left and right,
but your basic magnet, you'll notice one side,
it can be marked north pole, right,
counterclockwise, and the other side is south pole,
if you look at it.
It's still counterclockwise, but because you flipped it over,
it looks clockwise, right?
Okay.
There's no pole, just a vortex going through,
just like if you work at a hardware store,
you know that all your screws or most of them
are right-hand threaded, but you have a drawer somewhere
for what?
Left-handed.
L-H, left-hand threaded, so, you know,
you try to screw it in, it goes the other way, right?
Okay, so it's kind of, that's what happens when you put
like poles with like poles, okay.
So let's say you take a ring magnet or a bar magnet
or something, so let's say the north pole,
which is going towards the south, right,
attracted really, if you use a compass,
we're not going to get into how to determine
north and south pole, it doesn't matter,
but I'm just saying you paint, usually you paint
the north pole red on a magnet and white on the south pole,
that's the typical nomenclature.
Okay, so when you paint those two faces,
or you determine the two faces where the poles are,
what are called poles, that block wall is equidistant
between the two poles along the body of the magnet, okay.
All right, so I want to jump over to another notion.
You could look up fuel magnetizers or water magnetizers
and you're going to see thousands if not millions
of images of people selling you magnets
to strap onto your fuel line for better gas mileage
or strap onto your water pipes to reduce scale
and other things like that, right.
They're all wrong.
What they're doing is they're taking the two magnets,
two separate magnets, and sandwiching them pole to pole
over a tube or a pipe for fuel or water, okay.
And to add insult to injury, there are websites
that have had debates, oh, should we put two like poles,
you know, the poles that push away,
give the appearance of pushing away,
or the ones that attract.
There's a big debate on that.
They're both wrong because you shouldn't be doing that anyway
for this treatment of water because we're still speaking
on water even though this is a magnetic treatment of water.
So what you would like to have done is have the water flow
because this is not for static water.
Most of it, 99% of it is for flowing water,
is when you have a conduit of water, a tube,
a pipe or something, in this case it would be better
if it were flexible.
You want, yes, you do want this,
and you need to have the water pipe or the conduit wrap
around the block wall of the magnet
and avoid the poles as much as possible.
Now this is very unintuitive because if you show someone
a magnet, it sticks to the refrigerator really, you know,
let's say it's a good strong magnet, ring magnet,
square magnet, bar magnet, boom, it sticks on the fridge,
oh, it's a really strong magnet, flip it around, boom,
it sticks to the fridge, okay, it's a really strong magnet.
But now try the block wall against the fridge,
eh, it doesn't stick at all.
So if we're going to magnetize water, we've got to put it,
put the part of the magnet that's really strong
against the water, right?
This is the mentality.
This is typical human thinking, you see?
Well, obviously you've got to apply force to make a change.
So you're thinking to yourself,
this is what gives the appearance of force.
Yeah, exactly.
So, yeah, that's why, you know, your starter toolkit
is just three hammers, large, medium, and small,
for everything, right?
Anyway, yeah, so, okay, so this is the human,
everyone's stuck on this, everyone's stuck on this.
So you want the water, and you need to have the water
running along the block wall.
Okay, and you want to increase the area to that block wall,
so it's good to have two like magnets stacked on each other
as they normally would stick, and it gives you a little more
area along that block wall, and it also sets the poles apart.
A little more talk about magnets.
Another thing people are distracted about,
if anyone says, oh, these hard drive magnets,
these neomagnets, you know, number 52, 48, whatever,
oh, they've got these really strong neomagnets, right?
Wrong, you don't want to use a neomagnet.
You want to use an iron ferrite or strontium, you know,
the basic barium strontium, iron ferrite,
cheap speaker magnets or whatever, you know,
the black colored ones, not the shiny neos.
Why? Well, it's Greek.
The neomagnets are really strong.
The other ones are junk.
I'm like, well, okay.
When you make a magnet really strong like that,
it has a very high magnetic density,
and that field wraps around into the block wall,
and it's much smaller of a field.
Yes, it's a stronger field.
Yes, I'm not going to say that it's not good because it's weak.
It's not good because it's too strong.
As you increase the magnetism of the object,
the field gets denser and denser and denser.
That's what you're really measuring, more density,
and it ends up wrapping around the block wall,
the area where you want to affect your fluids,
and it doesn't give you a lot of room,
where the magnet that doesn't appear to have such a high density,
and it's like the regular magnet, let's say,
that works much better because there's more room for the block wall
to adjust and affect whatever liquid that's going to be passing by it.
So the neomagnets don't work. I've tried them.
So the vortex itself has a greater amount of space,
even though it's less intense.
Is that about the way to put it?
Yes, like on a neomagnet, the vortex is more upright and skinny,
like a skinny tornado,
and the vortex on a regular magnet, a ferrite magnet,
is really wide, almost like an upside-down pyramid.
Okay, so you need that clearance.
Well, thinking of a tornado, you're talking about the difference
between the type of tornado that wrecks a whole town,
but does it pretty slowly and does a lot of damage?
No, in terms of shape, because the neomagnets will wreck a whole town.
If you have a four-inch by four-inch by one-inch-thick neomagnet,
and you walk by something in your hand,
and something, iron or steel, about a foot away,
it will tear your hand off.
It will crush your hand, and you might have to have it removed.
Even doing pressure and wrapping,
biological vacuum goes out the window at this point,
because it will shatter everything.
Right?
Wow.
Yeah, no, it's pretty strong, yeah.
But the thing is, we're not looking for the strength.
Right.
We're looking for the block wall.
So there are ways to accentuate the block wall.
Okay, so I've been experimenting this for a while and developing it.
I started this a few years ago, and recently, the past few months,
I've developed it to the point where I can now talk about it with confidence
that it will work for anyone and everyone, anywhere.
And I'll give you an example.
I'm in Tucson, near Tucson, Arizona, or in the middle of Tucson, Arizona,
on Tucson, not in Tucson.
I'm not dead yet.
Right, okay.
And we have scaled water here.
In other words, you take a shower with clear glass doors, and it leaves a fog.
When it dries, if you wash the car, it ends up leaving this white scale on the car.
If you have a top-loading or a washing machine,
have one of these newer very deep drum washing machines
with a highly polished stainless steel drum,
the clothesline usually where the clothes are usually agitated is really highly polished,
but everything above that has like a powdery white finish that's stuck on there
that you really have to use acid to get it off.
Okay, the toilet bowl will develop a very strong calcium ring where the water level is.
Okay, I don't have any of that.
I used to, to a certain point.
What I did was I used these large 3- and 4-inch magnets, and I stacked them.
Two of them, they're half-inch thick, so I stacked them so they're an inch thick.
And I got a flexible tube, a flexible connector.
If you go to a hardware store or whatever, it looks like a hose,
but it has a stainless steel braid over it usually to prevent mechanical damage.
The thing is if you use the one with the stainless steel braid,
you must make sure the magnets don't stick to the stainless steel,
that it's a non-magnetic.
It's a martensistic stainless steel, which is a fancy way.
He's the guy that came up with stainless steel that was non-magnetic.
So martensistic, anyway, one of those words.
So what I did was I did it around, the easiest thing is a garden hose,
but you need to put a spring or a wire around it because you shouldn't have it kinking.
What I do is I wind a piece of stainless steel that fits inside the hose.
It looks like a spring, and I slide it in there,
and when you bend the coil or coil the hose around the magnet, it won't kink.
It'll be even.
Usually you see this.
It's called a tension relief on hoses, something that looks like a spring
where you connect the hose.
But I do this on the inside with stainless, which, again, is non-magnetic.
All right, so I've been experimenting with this,
and recently I discovered that you put a center magnet and three magnets total,
one on the outside, one on the inside, stacked, just a stack of magnets.
They're slightly smaller as they get further away, kind of stretch out that block wall.
And remember, if you go to it with a piece of iron, when this is set up,
it won't go anywhere near where the water is running.
The iron won't stick where the hose is.
It'll only stick away from the hose.
It'll stick to one of the ends, which are away from the hose.
Yeah, so you're like, hey, man, I've got a nail here,
and where your hose is on the magnet, there's no magnetism there at all.
I'm like, yeah, exactly, that's why it works so well.
So recently, well, anyway, I've been running this for a while,
and I've noticed that there is absolutely no toilet ring at all, calcium at all.
There is no  the stainless steel tub is completely polished all the way up running.
We use it every day.
Washing the cars here is hard because you want to  as soon as you're done washing,
you want to dry it right away, otherwise you get these spots, you know,
like if you don't live in a place where there's hard water.
If you have a dishwasher, one of the big things about marketing soap is it doesn't leave spots, right,
on the glasses, right?
Okay, well, you get these spots on everything, and when they dry,
they just look like very benign water spots, but they don't rub off, you know,
because it's a hard mineral, not an argonite.
An argonite is when the mineral hardens, and it's a large molecule,
and it breaks off easily, very, very fine.
Okay, so also the water heater would start making noise with scale buildup.
Well, it comes on a gas water heater.
Now it doesn't.
So what I found out was where is all this scale going?
It's not being deposited on any surface.
By the way, you use a tiny amount of soap.
The clothing is coming out much cleaner, right?
I do water processing to drink.
The water is much better.
It's like if I give anyone a sample of the water that I process here for drinking,
one of the comments is, it tastes like melted snow, right?
I thought that was really cute.
But I do remember melted snow being delicious.
At one time, yeah.
Yeah, this is before chemtrails.
All right, so what is the takeaway on this?
Why am I saying this?
If anyone, I think we mentioned last time, I like to see people develop more skill.
Many of the people I discuss about this, they kind of look at you cross-eyed
when you bring up building or making something.
And now I just ask people, I said, you might be interested in building this.
But by the way, before I get into it, do you know how to operate a screwdriver?
Depending on that answer is whether I continue or not.
So here's the thing.
This also works.
I haven't done it with the fuel treatment.
But I'll give you an example of what I do with that.
I don't talk about this much.
It's a 1998 Dodge Caravan with a Mitsubishi 3.0 six-cylinder engine.
It's supposed to get 17 miles per gallon in the city and like 21, 22, 23 on the highway,
if you're fortunate.
Well, I drive around in the city here, and I have a computer that gives me the mileage.
And I think the last route I went, I got 33.5 miles per gallon in the city.
Nice.
Is that with a fair amount of, like, stopping and starting?
Yeah, a fair amount of stopping.
So, in other words, if I put in 16 gallons of gas, I get 484 miles out of that on a gas tank.
So I've done it both ways.
It's a scan gauge.
It tells you your actual MPG, your average MPG, engine temperature, all this.
It's called a scan gauge.
You plug it into where the USB computer goes.
So it's very unusual what's going on here because it's not just  I'm doing a bunch of other things, right?
And there's actually, I think, some people that are subbed here that are familiar with what I'm talking about
because I've helped them out with their own cars on things.
I've made things and sent them back and forth.
Wes, you know who you are.
So I just wanted to bring up the thing about the magnets because something
when I started seeing this working before I got to the triple one, it worked really well with the single magnet.
I was like, oh, how cute, how cute.
I've got a real efficient way to prevent scale from building up, right, on things,
which is annoyance in a place that has hard water.
Yeah, but you said before, where does it go?
That is a big question.
This is the history of where does it go because that's what I said, how cute.
I figured out a really efficient way by just approaching the block wall with the fluid instead of the poles
like everyone else, and it's really cute that the scale has gone away or going away.
When I did the triple magnet, it went away away, but this is the part where it got really serious.
I'm going to go back to the car part.
Well, here it's very dusty.
If you drive into Tucson, Arizona or from any other part of the world other than New Mexico,
it feels like you're driving into Mars.
It's like, you know when they show photographs of supposedly Mars,
everything's got a red or brownish, tannish tinge to it, right?
Oh, yeah.
Well, that's what you start noticing when you're driving into Tucson.
Everything's got a tannish tinge to it.
It's not ugly.
It just has a tannish tinge, right?
Okay, so when you have a car washed or polished and you park it out for four hours, eight hours or overnight,
you come back and you can almost write your name on the hood from the fine dust, very fine dust.
You don't really see it.
It's so fine, but if you, let's say, lean on the car or move it, you know what I mean?
Like a car may not look that dirty, but you run your finger across and then you kind of see where your finger was.
Oh, it is dusty or dirty, right?
Right.
You don't know.
It's fine enough so that it's not noticeable until you actually like make a clear mark away.
Yeah, until you clear it away.
In other words, when you look at it, oh, the car's dirty.
It's not dirty.
It's just you don't, because also because you're used to it.
But if you run your finger along the hood or any part, now if the car is out and about
and then you rush it into a garage and close the door and you've got a good seal on the door, yeah, probably not.
But this is typically here.
Okay, so this is the part that got me, got really serious and noticed that something more than just treating the scale,
turning it into argonite crystals, which is their academic way of saying fine minerals make scale,
but when you magnetize it or treat it with ions, the fine minerals clump together, become larger,
and it's called argonite, and it won't bond.
It breaks off very easy.
Okay, I thought that was going on.
How cute, you know?
Okay.
But this got serious when I washed the car, okay, or cars, and at the end of the next day, I told my wife,
hey, you notice something weird here?
I pointed at the car, really shiny.
I washed these cars yesterday.
There's no dust on them, no dust at all.
And the next day, hey, it's been two days.
Look, there's no dust on the car.
How is that possible?
So what's going on here is the water became so negatively charged that anything that it touched became positively charged,
which became an anode.
So it repels it.
Things will not, yeah, well, sort of repels it, yeah.
It's not going to feel at home.
Well, much like what happens when you try and put, like you said, you put the North and the South Pole together,
it appears as though they're pushing away from each other.
It won't merge, yeah.
It won't merge.
It's something dissimilar, yeah.
Let's just say it puts a positive charge on it, right?
Okay.
The other thing is when you boil down the water, the amount of scale that you have in there is almost nonexistent also.
So it's going somewhere else.
It's going somewhere else.
Now, here's the interesting part.
You know when you walk in front of a shop like Macy's and there's a piece of glass and you see the furniture or the mannequins,
you know, and you have this piece of glass between you?
Okay, I've always discussed that everything comes from water.
By the way, one of the tasks that I have, it's kind of a secret in terms of outcome, but it's not secret to talk about.
I'm tasked with taking hydrogen and helium and turning it into lithium.
Okay.
Right?
It's actually very simple.
You just have to find the right way to do it.
Hydrogen is very abundant.
Well, there's 20 different types of hydrogen, but also helium is not that abundant.
It's a byproduct of the petrol gas and oil industry.
But anyway, they could be combined to produce lithium, which is something that supposedly they're fighting wars for,
or it's a metal that, you know, to get into it.
It's all about the batteries right now.
Yeah, yeah, exactly, yeah, and whatever.
So we can make it from hydrogen and helium.
We're in a different  at least when I succeed at this, it'll be real fun to talk about it.
It's going to get some people mad.
But you guys will know first.
Once it's done, I'm going to try to monetize it.
That's why I'm not going to talk about it.
If it's done, we'll see.
And if it's monetized and done, I may not  I might say, hey, it got monetized.
Part of the agreement is I can't talk about it.
I'm assuming that that might happen, to be honest with you, because I cannot foresee anybody discovering that,
having that in their hands, and wishing to allow anybody to really know for a long time.
Yeah.
Well, look, the Germans, the Germans, World War I got in trouble for synthesizing oil from carbon dioxide and water.
That's all you need.
Well, you need a catalyst.
You need the right set grouping of catalysts because hydrocarbons, hydrocarbon literally means water carbon, right?
And if you look at a hydrocarbon petroleum molecule, with CO2 gas, which is abundant and it's a byproduct, it's cheap,
and water, you have to get the right kind of water and the right kind of catalyst, just like, you know,
vegetable shortening, Crisco, right?
They use it for baking, whatever.
I'm not going to get lascivious on this one, but it's oil and water.
Well, you have to  you can't mix oil and water, but you can if you run it through  the process goes through nickel beads over nickel.
Now, the nickel is a catalyst, and it will change both of them.
There's no nickel content at all in it.
It's just a catalyst.
By the way, when you  I could say this much.
Yeah, well, if you synthesize oil from water and CO2 gas and the right catalyst, the oil ends up looking more like a transmission fluid.
It's a dark pink color, almost  yeah, and it has a wonderful smell.
I don't know if you ever have a pleasant smell from petroleum.
It's possible.
I've never experienced that.
I worked with gas, and I never
Well, that's refined.
That's got  okay, the gasolines, what they do, just like with the food industry with fluoride, right,
is when they have toxic chemicals that they can't get rid of, they just put them in gasoline.
Yeah, or the diesel.
To burn them off.
Or the diesel.
Right.
Someone says, oh, I'm a believer in fluoride and toothpaste.
That's sodium fluoride, dummy.
Calcium fluoride is what the teeth have, and they say, oh, does it make a difference?
Okay, so you're drinking a cola right now.
That's  you like it because it's  you don't like it when it's flat.
You like it when it's bubbly, right?
That's CO2 gas, carbon dioxide.
What if I replaced that carbon dioxide in your soda with carbon monoxide and you drank that often?
Would you like that?
What's the difference?
Well, I'm pretty sure the carbon monoxide will kill you.
Well, what's the  well, the sodium fluoride will do, too.
This is  by the way, I've never heard this analogy.
Feel free to use it.
If you're one of these fluoride whatever people, just tell them calcium fluoride, not sodium fluoride that they put out, right?
Because carbon monoxide and carbon dioxide, big difference.
And if they don't see that, just keep walking because they're just  they're just repeating a thing.
Okay, so here's the important part of it.
When you see the water, like the glass and the things behind it, you know, like maybe it's not a great analogy,
but in a showcase, you know, the glass is between you and the object, right?
What's happening is it's creating the water between  whatever the water is carrying stays in the flow of the water.
It stays in the water body.
The water body, after it's been treated with the block wall of the magnet, stays within the water body,
and it changes it enough that it wants to become water.
So it won't stick to the washing machine tub.
It won't stick to the car, meaning what's in the water, okay?
Okay.
And it stays in the water, and it wants to be  so the minerals and the stuff in the water want to become water once it goes over the magnetic part.
Now, I've been  what I'm experimenting with now is degassing the water.
Well, not now, but the next step  not now as we're recording this,
but the next step is to treat the water with some implosion, which is water under a vacuum, right, to degas the water.
By the way, most water has at least 5% to 10%, depending on your altitude, dissolved gases in it.
Have you ever go to your tap or whatever and pour a glass of water and leave it on the counter?
You come back five minutes.
What do you see all over the glass?
Little tiny bubbles all over the glass, on the bottom, top, sides, right?
What that is is the gases that are in the water coming out.
So part of the implosion process of water is to degas the water, which is very simple.
You just need to build some apparatus to do that for a given volume, let's say, or you could do it while it's moving, and then affect it with that field.
Now, if you're going to set up these magnets, do me a favor and what's called the north side of the magnet goes towards the north and south towards the south.
You orientate.
Okay.
And if you can't  if it's not vertical like that, if it's horizontal, so the magnet is either going to the ceiling or the floor,
make sure that the south side of the magnet is pointing towards the floor.
Then you're safe there as well, north towards the sky.
Okay.
Because that gives you a counterclockwise spin, just like, for example, when water goes down a drain, most likely it's counterclockwise.
So that's the orientation.
I wanted to bring this up because this is going to lead into transmutation aspects that are  they call it low-energy transmutation or something like that, right?
We're taught that you need high-energy bombarding.
What they say in a nuclear power plant, the lead turns to gold and all this stuff,
but you don't have a nuclear power plant, so you can't make lead into gold.
Anyway, that kind of stuff.
But the way you make lead into gold, by the way, is by removing a hydrogen atom, right?
So out of the lead.
But what are you talking about, Greg?
Lead is lead.
There's no hydrogen.
Okay.
That's another discussion.
So if you get something to look like a duck and smell like a duck and act like a duck, it must be a duck.
But not always because you can make a robotic duck that looks just like a duck.
I think they even had  in some recent films, they were going to do a real lion, a CG lion, or a robotic lion.
That's how good the robots are getting, right?
Right.
I think they did the Lion King and they were merging these things, trying to figure out which one was the best.
Wasn't that the one you were doing?
Yeah, something like that.
Yeah.
So what I'm saying is you get some of the lead to act like hydrogen, smell like hydrogen, look like hydrogen.
It's hydrogen, right?
And then in that process is where you have the rest of it turning.
By the way, when you start doing transmuting metals in ingot form like that,
let's say you have a hunk of copper and you want to start turning it to gold, it looks  it's very strange when you see the appearance.
And whenever the gold starts to appear on a piece of metal that you're transmuting and something that's not in solution,
something that's on a piece of metal, an ingot or a bar or something, always  as the gold starts to make its appearance,
it always looks like it's growing organically or it looks like raindrops.
You ever see when raindrops initially fall and they spatter?
So you'll have the drop section where it made contact and then a spatter marks all around.
It's as if the gold is falling or the elements that you're changing it to are falling in here from somewhere else.
It looks identical to raindrops on a sidewalk when they start forming.
So it's very  it's like it's  yeah.
You know there's a ratio, by the way, of how a rock falls, right, from a certain height and it reaches terminal velocity,
I think 140 miles per hour, and how it accelerates.
There's a proportion of the acceleration of a rock as it's falling.
Someone did a study on the growth of a human embryo in the human body.
As the embryo or the egg that's been conceived, the zygote and all that, goes to an embryo fetus,
the proportion of its growth over nine months is exactly the proportion of a rock falling.
It's as if the body has the same proportions of something falling.
So you know the fall of man, get it?
I get it.
Anyway, yeah, yeah.
So you could find  and what I'm trying to say is you could find similarities in many, many things,
but you have to read out of it.
Don't read into it what you want, like the sun of God doesn't mean the sun in the sky.
You ever hear people say that all the time?
Yes.
Because in Hebrew it would be ben, not sun, right?
And in Greek it would be yos, right?
Or iko in Spanish.
It wouldn't be sun.
See, so you know what I mean, the difference between reading out sort of reading in, right?
So you've got to always read out of these things.
All right, the magnet, very, very, very crucial, very simple, very easy to do.
The main point, the main takeaway here, this is part of a water discussion,
because when we do get into a more concerted, deep discussion on water,
we'll be talking more about the effects and not the setup, but referring to the setup.
I think we gave enough about the setup.
What do you think?
I think so.
I think it's very important to remember, though, that lining things up with its natural orientation,
because that's the way I take it when you're telling me to either, you know,
look, if it happens to be vertical, put the south pole to the floor,
and if not, try to put north to north and south to south if it is vertical, right?
But here's the thing, if you could only turn the magnet east-west,
I would rather have the floor go to the south than crisscrossing, right?
So, like, for example, in the bathroom under the toilet tank,
the way the tube only allows for it to go east-west,
so I'd rather turn it horizontal and have the south go towards the floor.
So sometimes you do have to make, what do you call it, a compensation,
or you have to make the call yourself, right?
And then there's magnetic north and true north, which will give you 10 or 15 degrees.
That's fine.
If you could be within 30 degrees of north, do it.
Otherwise, just turn the south towards the floor.
You'll be safe in almost all cases, especially if it's something that's movable.
Now, this is very, very important to me because I'm noticing that there is a change in mass
of the things that are dissolved in the water,
and there's also a change in properties of the things that are being affected by the water.
Now, the next thing is to affect this in other ways, like I said, and also in other places,
but it's so drastic here where I'm doing it, where I dwell, where I inhabit.
It's such a big difference. It's not like a slight difference.
It's so, like, in-your-face noticeable and, like, what the hell is going on kind of noticeable
that I wanted to bring that up, and it's ironclad at this point.
It's like an iron law kind of thing.
The magnetic treatment of fluids must be along the block wall, case closed.
There's no debate or no option to that.
So if you go to magnetic treatment of fluids online,
it's all they're sandwiching the lines in between the poles of the magnets.
So anyway.
Yeah, well, they're creating a different effect, and it's not the one that you're creating with this.
They're creating the effect that they were impressed with when they stuck the magnet
to a bag of nails or the refrigerator,
but whatever fluid is going through there is not impressed at all.
As a matter of fact, it ignores it.
Okay, so this is a really, really big deal,
because if you don't have hard water and you have other things in the water,
it will affect those as well, right?
So, yeah.
So I just wanted to bring that up on the water.
It's very, very, very important to me,
and many people here might care about what I consider to be important,
want to know what does the Greek think is important,
and this is one of the most important discoveries
and workings that I've done in the past year.