Rated Y Sonic Event 2.11. Oh look,
I think I'm a little low this time,
Greek.
There we go.
Now I think I'm at my regular volume.
How are you today?
Okay.
Yeah, just doing it, man.
Got any questions?
I got questions.
I got comments.
You want to start weird or you want
to go with reactive?
No, it's up to you, it doesn't matter
to me.
Ah, dealer's choice, eh?
Okay, so let's start with this one.
This is somebody who's talking about dreams, okay?
And they've listened to everything you have to
say, and yet they have a question that
I think you've already kind of answered, but
let's try it anyway.
They're dreaming of dead people, okay?
And in the dreams, they're usually seeing them
in mundane situations.
However, in a recent string of them, lately,
this is women that they've been with in
the past, and now they're seeking to like
move in with them.
And these are the circumstances they keep having
dreams of until they realize that they're, you
know, obviously it's like, wait a minute, you're
dead, this and that.
So anyway, the overall- I get it
because I've lately been having the same stuff.
Really?
So the question is, do you think that
there are messages in patterns like this in
dreaming?
Yeah.
If so, what should someone do to change
or stop?
It always goes by the same rule.
If you can manipulate it, you're not in
a dream.
In other words, if you can remember when
you're in the dream, the thing is we
get so caught up in the dream, we
forget to look at our hands.
Oh, and that's what he says.
You see, he says he's so caught up
in it, and then the moment he goes,
wait a minute, you're dead, you know, then
it ends.
Yeah, that's right.
Okay, so you're being messed with.
If you can remember, it takes a lot
of work.
It could take years just to be able
to get yourself to remember.
So look for your hands, or look for
mouths when there's speech, because usually the mouths
don't move.
If you can move your hands, you're like
in a membrane, a threshold into another reality.
Still in this reality, it's just a very
fine, you know, just like anyone who does
radio, you could tune into a whole bunch
of terrestrial radio right now, right?
So it's just tuning into it when you're
asleep because your senses don't allow you to
tune into it with too much sensory input.
Looking back over his explanation and his comment,
though, two things I realized.
One, he doesn't realize about the mouths moving
because he mentioned that, that he references it.
Like I said, he listened to you talk
about this before.
Yeah, but he didn't bring it up.
He didn't know.
So it's probably he's being messed with.
Well, he did see his hands, though, in
the last one.
Oh, did he?
Was he able to manipulate them, move his
fingers?
Yeah, he grabbed- Oh, so he's in
another, he's picking up a finer reality.
Here's something from years of study and listening
to people.
As you get closer to death, the individuals
having the dreams, the dreams will become more
vivid and you'll be seeing more people that
have died and the dreams become more vivid
and they also interact with recent events.
As you, so in other words, when you're
60 or 70 or 80, you're closer to
being dead than when you're 20 or 30.
So I reckon this person is probably older
than 40.
I don't know.
I'm just guessing.
Yeah, I'm guessing too also, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
So, yeah, that's an entirely, but just remember
that there are beings that hang out and
they're like, hey, what are we going to
play on these humans?
And what, you know, what, you know, if
we want to scare them, what scare, what
have they been taught to be scared of,
right?
If we want to get them aroused, what
have they been taught to be aroused by?
And they present those things and they rarely
present them flawlessly, but they present them enough
that enough of it is there that you
go for it, right?
Right.
But if you feel like you're in another
reality and you can move your, and there's
mouths moving when they're speech, especially.
And they've captured this in film, by the
way, where there's someone's in a dream and
there's speech, but the mouths don't move.
I forget which film.
It might've even been a twilight zone.
I think it was a twilight zone.
But yeah, believe it or not, it's taboo.
Just like the financial system, medical, whatever law,
it's not talked about the dream stuff because
it's not really dream.
It's a very big subject, right?
It's a very big subject because you can
easily mix it in with the world that
you perceive that when your senses are tuned,
you know, the regular senses are off, you
know, when you perceive another world is very
different than being messed with, but they kind
of mess with you in that world anyway.
So big subject.
All right, let's move on.
Big subject, but just on a personal note,
you know what?
I've noted that I've seen dead people a
lot lately too.
And you mentioned it yourself.
That's a weird crossover right there.
Now I'm not afraid of it, but I
wonder if that means I'm on my way
out soon.
I mean, if so, whatever, so be it.
Well, it's on different levels.
You know, there's the worldwide, there's the national,
then there's the familial, you know, the associations
that you have personally.
Okay.
On the worldwide level, we're all, the majority
of the big part of the planet is
pretty close to being dead and very soon,
like, you know, in terms of Earth time,
you know, a decade, decade and a half,
right?
According to the archaics timeline.
Not all the whole world, but a big
portion and starting even earlier than that.
So on a worldwide level, there is a
lot of death coming because when you look
at 10 or 15 years on a world
timeline, that's like a few seconds, right?
So indeed, we all could be having a
common sort of just- On a worldwide
level, yeah, it is.
Everyone is getting a sense of death coming
because, you know, it's like the two seconds
to midnight, right, over 6,000 years, right?
So then there's the national one where whenever
a big war breaks out, people prior to
the war breaking out have death dreams in
that nation.
And then there's familial dreams where there's a
lot of the symbolism, like, you know, if
you're having a dream where your teeth fall
out, someone's gonna die, someone close to you
is gonna die.
Remember the old wives' tale and stuff, right?
I thought that was sexualization if the teeth
fell out.
I thought it was.
Okay, well, there's different interpretations and they change
every two decades.
So yeah, it's a big subject.
How about we make a footnote somewhere or
a note or a market somewhere that we'll
get into the dream world and the parallel
worlds soon?
We'll do an entire thing on it.
Dedicated Sonic to the dream world and parallel
worlds.
You got it.
Yeah.
Okay, when you realize, this is another one,
when you realize this entire planet is run
like a family business, it all starts to
make sense.
When you realize we live in a biological
program, you understand why they keep the prophecy.
Obfuscation is how you maintain power over the
masses and power is just getting people to
take action on your behalf.
Right, like a horse or a beast of
burden does work for you, yeah.
So let's see, this is, nope, nope.
The next one I wanted to get to.
That's the Rolling Stones song, A Beast of
Burden.
Yeah, of course.
Most people are beasts of burden.
That's why I'm like, I'm totally happy just
being like either in the lab or at
home, you know, like that house arrest thing.
I couldn't care less.
That's what I want.
I hate going out.
And I'm not agoraphobic.
It's just, I look forward to going out
and I'm like, what the?
I come back and I'm like, what the
hell is that?
Is that what humans are like?
And I'm talking about running into like, you
know, not trashy people either.
I'm talking about running into people that are
quote unquote professionals.
I said, oh my gosh, that's, I felt
like these are, this is the best society
has to offer.
I felt like I was scraping the bottom.
I need to just avoid it, you know,
just so, yeah, anyway.
Sounds like a cross between a George Carlin
and a Jerry Seinfeld riff because, you know,
Jerry Seinfeld does the whole, when you go
out, you want to get home, when you
go home, you want to go out.
But George Carlin goes, you know, I hate
going out because all I got to deal
with are morons and a-holes.
Anyway, Greek has made a good point saying
that this is not an actual war.
Now, the reason why I go to this
comment, Greek, is because there's a bunch of
them about the conflict.
You know, I'm calling it the two eyes
war at this point.
The two eyes war, Israel and Iran.
All right, hold on, let me stop here
for a moment.
We know what Trump is doing.
He's replaying what Obama was doing.
Word for word, play for play, except it's
going more hot.
Do you remember during the Obama thing, Iran
was really bad?
Yeah, I thought it was more of a
Syria thing.
I could play Syria in the same place.
Yeah, but Syria is still going on, so
that's already started.
But if you look at what was put
on Iran, when was Obama, 2008 to 2016?
Yeah.
Something like that, yeah.
Look at Iran, mentioned Obama, and it's a
replay of it all.
It's all weak, stupid shit, but go ahead.
I just wanted to say that he's carrying
on Obama's policies so that, you know, don't,
yeah.
I noticed that they were releasing many images
of missiles being dropped on both sides, but
they never mentioned dead people, civilians actually being
injured.
Well, I see mentions of dead people, but
the numbers are pretty low.
I even saw a video of an outside
party where a bunch of people are actually
having fun and filming missiles in the sky
as if it was some kind of New
Year's Eve firework, this guy says, so.
But it's weird, because they're asking questions like,
is this now something that's being lit off?
Is this a sign?
This is what people want to know about
it.
Yeah, there was an article a few days
ago about 10 countries like Qatar, UAE, Saudi
Arabia, Kuwait, and whatever are joining into a
union.
Did you pick up on that?
Yeah, they have a, there's actually a name
for it, but yeah, there is.
Yeah, but they decided to form this alliance
of six countries, and they're gonna recruit more.
I just think it's funny, because they said
around 2025, you're gonna see a Middle East
Union coming around, so.
Yep, oh, I was just grabbing my keyboard
so it didn't fall off the table, so.
Oh, that's fine, yeah.
So what else you got on that, yeah,
so he's got some interesting, or she's got
some interesting comments about the war is not
a war, yeah.
Yeah, it's not a war.
It does seem kind of fake, because they're
not really showing you massive casualties, but they're
talking about it and whipping you into a
frenzy, and of course, Trump is threatening stuff.
This is all a combined group of comments,
by the way.
You know, Trump is threatening stuff, but is
he really the guy in charge?
You know.
No, no, Trump is a TV person.
Of course, you know, he didn't learn.
It's cumulative, so before he got into politics,
he did the TV shows, right?
Right, he's the boss on the TV show,
but he doesn't run the TV show.
You know, it might be a prejudice.
Yeah, it's an unlawful, the United States is
an unlawful, some say it's not a corporation,
it's a scam.
It's a total scam.
It's kind of like when you work with
the mob, or you play a card game
with the mob, and you own a sporting
goods store, big store, just 10, 15 million
a year in sporting goods, right?
And you play, you get addicted to gambling,
and you're in the whole quarter of a
million dollars with them, and you can't pay
them because you don't have any cash flow.
So the mob comes into your sporting goods
store, starts taking this stuff and selling it
on their own, and they order more stuff
so they can sell it on your end,
close down your shop.
This is like a thing from the Sopranos,
right?
Yeah, it's called a bust out.
Yeah, yeah.
A bust out, yeah.
That's what they're doing, a bust out.
All these idiots, they're all idiots.
And whether you're working in the DMV as
a clerk, you know, reinstating people's driver's license
all the way up to the president, they're
morons.
There's not one person that makes any sense.
Now, there are people behind the scenes that,
for example, going back to the Obama thing,
whether it be Obamacare, there was one guy
that popped out, and it was kind of
hard to get someone to comment on it,
and he came out and says, the reason
we're doing this is because the American people
are stupid.
They don't read, right?
Do you remember that guy?
I do remember that guy.
Yeah, yeah, so you have people like that
that know what's going, but the people that
you, he was never supposed to be on
camera.
No.
He was never supposed to, because all the
people that know what's going on just think
everyone around them is stupid.
Right, and that guy said it.
So if you think everyone around you is
stupid, you're doing great.
That guy said it on TV, though.
That was the big deal.
It was like, I can't believe this guy
said this on, like, for weeks and replayed
it.
Because he's one of the people that are
actually doing something.
The rest of them are morons, pretty much.
So if you got, like, the three million
government employees, there's probably less than 1,000
that are worth anything.
And that union, by the way, which they've
now dragged China, Russia, and North Korea into
is what they refer to as the axis
of resistance, by the way.
But, okay, it's true.
This is another one.
It's true what the Greek always said, that
we must have done something wrong to be
here on this planet.
Yahshua said, my kingdom is not of this
world.
Satan is the god of this world.
We have no business being here.
Okay, I checked, does the Greek, oh, does
the Greek believe that the descendants of Cain
are ruling the earth?
That's the follow-up on that.
It's more than that, because remember, scripture is
very specific of a certain area.
Like, if you read the genealogies, they didn't
know that the Zulu people existed or the
Moors existed, right?
Right, so it's limited to a certain area.
There's always something going on in parallel somewhere
else, right?
Yeah, like they didn't know about ancient China,
let's say.
Yeah, there's nothing mentioned about, you know, supposedly,
yeah.
So, no, there's always something going on somewhere.
And my favorite is the, where else was
that?
The Japanese government officially put out a map
a long time ago in the 60s that
showed the seven continents and then, like, Antarctica
spread out and then a whole bunch of
continents beyond that that we've never even seen.
Have you ever seen that map?
Yeah, it's weird.
It's like the world plus, yeah.
Yeah, so it goes on like that.
So, you know, our world, you know, like
the sea, you know, our world is really
small and we've been tricked in believing we're
shown all of it, you see?
So even scripture runs that, you know, idea.
So the descriptions might be places that we've
never heard of otherwise.
Yeah, there's a lot more to everything.
There's a lot more than that came from,
we should say.
There you go.
But the God of this world and all
that other stuff, this is an evil place.
And when you get it down to the
nuts and bolts of it, it's not run
by humans at all.
And that's pretty obvious when you look at
the level of deceit.
There's no species that deceives its own species
to the degree that humans deceive other humans.
Yeah, but that's the thing.
Even when you observe the animal kingdom, right,
they're not really stealing from each other like
we do.
And the level of deception, like for example,
the bankers will kick you out on the
street and take your stuff and they know
you've already paid for everything more than twice.
That's not a human thing, right?
But that's the same thing you do with
cows.
You know, you feed them until they get
big and plump and ready and then you
slaughter them for their meat.
But here you're being slaughtered for your credit.
So yeah, okay, what else?
Well, let's see, this is totally a death
camp place.
I'm in Canada and the local public health
is now calling us and saying we have
to get measles vaccines.
Obviously this is- Yeah, tell them it
has to be, they have to follow an
affidavit.
If it's not an official order by the
government, they have to have a sworn affidavit
that you have to have that done.
It's in the laws there.
In other words, they can't make you do
anything unless there's an order that's accompanied by
a sworn affidavit and they can't do that.
So I just wanted to let you know
- And also you have privacy laws that
they're evading.
So if someone asks you a question, you
don't have to answer it because answering it
you feel is an evasion of privacy laws.
You can, right?
I got you.
People have done that with the census takers
here in this country where- Yeah, you
could say, well, you're asking me or telling
me to get the measles vaccine.
What if I already have one and what
if I don't have one?
That's my own private business.
Or if I gotten it already, I'm not
gonna tell you.
And if I haven't gotten it, I'm not
Go look at the laws.
A sworn, anything that's compelling someone to do
something by judicial order or whatever has to
be accompanied either an order or a warrant
for arrest has to be accompanied by a
sworn affidavit.
A sworn affidavit, no one's gonna swear.
So, yeah.
And you have the privacy laws that protect
you.
That's the only way- And they started
back in 1974.
Yeah, that's the only way you're supposed to
legitimately get probable cause is through a sworn
affidavit where a witness actually swears to account
that you did some damage or caused some
harm.
Yeah, and if they're arresting you or detaining
you for it, then there's due process.
They have to produce all of that again,
so.
That's, what do they call it?
All the countries have that, by the way.
You just have to find it and know
about it.
Nobody knows about any of this because it's
a planet of morons.
That's why I don't argue with those guys
who talk about the use of the Magna
Carta from 1215 or whatever, because it basically
states everything is under this.
Yeah, yes and no.
But look, when it comes to vaccines, I
think so far most of everyone that I've
ever met should get vaccinated often and early.
No, that's if you don't care about surviving.
Anyway- Yeah, yeah, it's a good way
to get rid of a lot of people,
I think, but anyway.
So, outside of a bunch of feedback that
said they really enjoyed the Arkham's Razor podcast
there, which we posted on Patreon as a
bonus.
Oh, good, okay.
That's about it for the questions and comments.
I covered everything pretty quickly there.
So, where else do we need to go?
What else do I need to learn?
Yeah, we'll just plan some theme-based sonics
that we've been having, well, more questions about
dreaming and stuff like that.
I'll just have to think about it.
That's one.
You also wanted to go more into the
body.
Now, I don't know if you want to
continue on with that.
Do we need to cover more, or should
we go more into the biological vacuum?
We're going to wait a little bit because
I have some, myself and other people, maybe
one or two others, looking into some ways
to demonstrate the biological vacuum.
Ah, okay.
And it's not just like years ago when
I talked about biological vacuums, everybody's a vacuum
cleaner, ha, ha, ha.
The typical room temperature IQ people, right?
They don't understand what causes a biological vacuum.
So, it's very easy to demonstrate the heart
is not a pump.
And there's no pumping action that it's all
suction, because the capillaries, how they terminate, how
is the pump going to send something forward
and then pull it back, right?
So, it has to be done autonomously within
each capillary at the cellular level.
That's very difficult to prove when you want
to scale it up, right?
Because a cell is, compared to, let's say,
a vein, you're talking a magnitude of 100
or 1,000 times, right?
So, how do you do a scale experiment
and still have it visible?
You'd have to have the smallest capillary tube
and then something like the size of a
four-inch pipe.
It gets really spooky when you look at
the scale of the human body.
Wasn't there a film with Raquel Welch called
The Incredible Journey where they miniaturized people and
injected them in to kill cancer, supposedly, or
something in some way?
Well, they did a few different takes on
that sort of thing with the miniaturization and
injection.
Yeah, it's kind of fascinating.
And then they put them in a little
vehicle and they're fighting blood cells and things.
Yeah, it was just totally ridiculous.
But yeah, the idea of scale, though, is
massive.
So, it has to be done philosophically, almost
Rudolf Steiner, but he's too airy-fairy.
Like, Rudolf Steiner had a lot of correct
ideas, but to get to the meat of
what he was talking about was so airy
-fairy, I just wanted, like, I felt like
I was going to float away.
I had to tether myself down, right?
So, that's how airy-fairy he is.
But it doesn't mean that he's not correct.
Fair enough.
Look, I saw in the chat, there was
some discussion about the shape of the kidney
and foods and relating it to it.
Yeah, look, that fruit that was put up,
I suggested it would be more for the
kidney than the lung.
And there's reasons for it.
Look at how the fruit grows, also.
See, the lotus root is the lung because
the way it grows in clusters and it's
in water, right?
Where the other fruit grows more like a
regular fruit, like an apple.
So, that would be more like the kidney
and it actually matches the kidney better.
So, yeah, there's a lot of that.
There's a term, someone will find it and
probably put it in the Chitango later, about
getting how certain foods and things appear to
be, like, parts of the human body, right?
Like, the cabbage is the brain and the
lotus root is the lungs and the beans
are the kidneys and the cucumber is, you
know.
So, whatever.
Yeah, I would say that there's a term
for that.
I forgot what it is, but that's not
the be-all, end-all.
It's the energy that, and energy is also
how these things move when they grow.
Like, the simplest thing to imagine to illustrate
this is fruit.
When the blossom is pointing up like a
flower, but once the fruit forms, the fruit
is pointing down towards the ground.
It gets heavier and it's trying to reach,
it's trying to get to the ground because
ultimately that's what happens, right?
It falls off.
Yeah.
I think generally that might have been called
the doctrine of signatures or something because there's
like a signature shape to different, especially fruit,
like you were saying.
It's a- Yeah, but it's the energetic,
not just the way it looks, the way
it grows, right?
Yeah, but it's- So, that's why when
you take fruit, you feel good for a
moment or a little bit and then you
want to crash, right?
It brings you down, believe it or not.
Fruitarian diets always do that.
You want to sleep a lot.
What they call a sugar crash.
Yeah, they call it, but it's not, it
has nothing to do with sugar.
Yeah, but that's- It has to do
with the energy of, yeah.
I'm just saying that's what they call it,
but the anatomical shapes that match something is
also an indicator, but it's not the only
thing.
Like you said- Because of the energy,
and it's, in other words, an archetype.
Yeah, okay, an archetype.
There you go.
Well, there's some words and phrases for you.
I'm not sure if they're exactly correct.
Because we live in such a limited archetypical
kind of structure here.
This existence that we have, 3D, it seems
complex.
We're amazed that it's complex, but it's actually
very simple once you understand universal principles.
It's all made of the same stuff.
It's hydrogen-based, by the way.
The other thing you have to get your
mind around if you're going to assemble a
biological vacuum, we're not carbon-based.
We're hydrogen-based.
Hydrogen-based, okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So that's a, yeah, it seems like I'm
just contraire on everything, right?
It does seem that way, but then again,
like I said, there's a bit of a
logic to it with observe.
I mean, you can observe stuff like, what
is it, broccoli and cauliflower very much look
like the brain, you know, to me.
I mean, just simple examples like that.
The lobes, yeah.
The lobes of the brain, fine.
But the cabbage more so.
Okay.
And cross-section.
So neither one is fully like the brain,
right?
In other words, your point on the broccoli
and cauliflower and the point on the, they
do look like the lobes, or let's say,
or the lobing, but the cauliflower overall is
more, but neither one is, but they're close.
Yeah.
Right, the lotus root is really close to
the bronchi.
It's not for the entire lungs, by the
way.
The lotus root is for the bronchi.
Okay.
So when the bronchi either are too expansive,
pneumonia, or too contractive, asthma, right?
Now, the lotus root, you don't wanna do
if you have asthma, because if you ever
handled lotus root, it's very dense, very difficult
to cut, right?
It's like sugarcane.
You ever cut sugarcane?
It's really dense.
I can imagine something like that, or ginger
root.
Okay, ginger.
It's harder than ginger root.
Wow.
Yeah, so you don't wanna, if you have
a contractive issue, you don't want it.
You want it when you have a loose
issue with the lungs.
And most people misinterpret expelling a phlegm and
mucus as a loose condition.
No, no, loose, expelling mucus and phlegm through
the mouth and orally and the nose is
loss of body vacuum on the young part
of the body.
A loose condition in the lungs is something
different.
It's more like a pneumonia where it stays
in the lungs.
It doesn't come up, doesn't expel.
Right.
So you know what'd be interesting?
I don't have the time.
I probably will never do it, but discussing
more of like the basics, and this is
gonna help, quote unquote, God forbid, heaven forbid,
young parents, right?
Oh boy.
With children, right?
You know how young parents are major targets
for the medical industry, you know?
Well, because they can't talk to the baby,
so they bring them to them.
Yeah, and all the time for the slightest
things, yeah.
And the thing is, I can't stand it
when people are having babies and all that.
I'm like, how dare you have a child?
Unless you know you're raising the next messiah.
And when I say that, I'm not talking
about the J-E-S-U-S, I'm
talking about a messiah that's gonna come out
with a thing and really bring hell on
earth to end all the shit going on,
right?
That kind of a messiah, right?
So- When I was young, I definitely
thought my children would be very impactful and
would definitely shake things up.
That's what I thought.
Yeah, everyone does.
Everyone thinks they have, you know.
We need, like, Genghis Khan, Adolf Hitler, Joseph
Stalin, Andrew Jackson all wrapped up in one.
Yikes.
It'll probably be blue-eyed, red-haired, and
seven-foot tall.
Male or female, doesn't matter.
They kind of did that in a G
.I. Joe cartoon years ago.
They called him Serpentor, where they went around
and they got, like, Hitler and some Egyptian,
you know.
Well, by the way, Hitler has a really
bad rep.
He was very mild-mannered, you know?
He was an artist.
He was kind of a terrible artist.
He was a flunky.
He tried a whole bunch of stuff.
He was thrown in jail for, you know,
protesting whatever, the woke movement.
What was going on with the gray shirts,
and they became the brown shirts, the Democrats.
What they call the beer hall, pushed, and
pushed, or whatever, yeah.
Yeah, they were against the woke movement.
They were against transsexual stuff, and prostitution, and
all that stuff that's been going on with
the Biden administration was what was going on.
Pre-1933 Germany was going on for more
than a decade, since after World War I,
and it was put on by, basically, Jewish
intellectuals from Brooklyn and Germany.
That's why they went after the Jews.
They didn't go after the Jews, per se,
because you could look this up.
I think it's University of Kansas has written
a paper trying to examine the fact why
there were 100,000 practicing Jews in the
German National Socialist Wehrmacht, in the army.
There are 100,000 practicing Jews in the
German army under Hitler.
So how could they be going after Jews?
You see, we've been given a bill of
goods that is, yeah, just bullshit.
But yeah, Stalin, he was just ruthless.
He didn't want intelligent people around him.
He wanted stupid people around him, because he
couldn't sleep if he had intelligent people around
him.
So it sounds like the current state of
the United States.
But actually, like I said earlier, there probably
are some intelligent people, and I'm sure they
don't last very long.
If you want to know what the current
United States is, it's BlackRock and Vanguard, by
the way.
It's not, anyway.
Oh, they own a piece of everything.
You can see that publicly.
Yeah, they're like combined 20 trillion on books
or 10 trillion on the books.
That's what they're showing, right?
And that's their controlling.
And actually, the guy from BlackRock came out
and said, with the Biden, you're going to
take on this new movement, the BLM and
the woke stuff, or you're going to suffer
consequences.
Remember that?
He did a speech.
This is the new way of stuff, with
the trannies and all that and the Black
Liberation Movement or whatever, Black Lives Matter.
Black Liberation Movement and Black Lives Matter, right?
BLM, right?
You're going to have to put up with
all that, or you're going to suffer consequences.
So they're trying to tell you, they're just
trying to push.
So what happened after the woke movement, after
World War I in Germany, you had the
Reichstag, supposedly, which was the 9-11 here.
It doesn't quite parallel, and then the National
Socialist Party.
So now you have Trump, who's going to
do the...
So when people say Trump is like a
dictator or like a Hitler, they're not far
off, but it's the Disney, Elon Musk version.
It's the Disney of it, right?
That's the one thing.
Look, there's two things missing, is that he
needs a war that needs to go on,
like an actual war where we're involved directly.
That's not going to happen.
And the other thing he needs is a
Reichstag fire, an inciting event, right?
A 9-11, which will get everybody saying,
well, we need to stay behind the leader.
That's not going to happen either, because of
cell phones.
Well, there you go.
So you have to have something happen that's
going to be with AI, an AI war.
Where AI starts, they blame it on AI,
starts taking down infrastructure and killing people.
And then that way, since nobody understands it,
it'll work out fine.
Yeah, but you'll have to wait a few
years for that.
So Trump won't be alive, probably, by the
time that really comes in.
So who's the next figure in?
No, it's only just a few years, like
2027 or so.
Well, he's what, almost 80.
I mean, he don't look healthy.
Well, which Trump are you talking about?
Oh, I don't know.
You know, when they brought the...
Yeah, you know what I mean?
When they brought the...
I doubt these people are real.
When they brought the Department of Homeland Security
lady into the hospital earlier for an allergic
reaction, I was wondering about that too.
Did you read about that?
No, no, I don't.
No, no.
No, you don't really read.
I try not to, yeah.
Because you missed a whole lot.
I do a lot of reading, but not
that kind of stuff.
But I get where you, yeah.
I think that we're in a, what is
it?
Star Wars, the Clone Wars, right?
Clone Wars.
We are in the Clone Wars.
I think there are more...
Remember, we were being warned in the 70s
and 80s about human robotoids replacing politicians.
That's true.
They call them robotoids, which has nothing to
do with robots, you know, like an Erector
set.
Androids, no, it has to do with cloning,
yeah, so.
Exactly.
So, yeah, I definitely noted that.
So anyway, we got the dreams thing and
you...
Yeah, more on the human body.
We'll see what transpires in the next couple
of weeks.