Rated Y Sonic event 99 here and here we are what's a few days away from 99
Sonic's on the wall 99 Sonic's on the wall yep and what are we a week and
geez I don't know a week in five days or a week in four days depending on how
you're counting it an eclipse coming up yeah but also it's the first I think
rating it as the first month is good too I think everything was squared away the
other day was first day of the first month and the number of the year doesn't
change until the at the year is over it's kind of different so I think
there's a bunch of people in the chat we're looking at it we've been under
solid cloud cover big storms here so you didn't see the you didn't see the
fullness of the moon about three four days ago okay no not at all not at all
even coming to it it's just been very very stormy here I did some weather
stuff about three months ago very low and slow let's say and it's yielded a
day of rain a full day of nice slow penetrating rain every week for the past
three months the place is blooming so very unusual very much against the
forecasts but they do show it because it's unmistakable so yeah redeeming the
desert is is totally doable one day someone asked me by the way but speaking
more in Trevor James Constable we'll do that and we'll talk about the pitfalls
and benefits of weather work in the future but yeah the eclipse yeah let's
just tie that into some questions in the chat regarding the Archaic's videos I'll
bring up the videos let's see let's see get the laptop going here once again I
mean you you appreciate the chronology not necessarily signed on yeah well it's
Texas country meets the internet he's pretty rough around the edges but I'm
very grateful for the information is put out look if we're here about learning
you know look if you're here doing okay you do sonic events or podcasts or
whatever for performance you're doing it for performance entertainment but if
you're doing it to share what can be learned you notice how I that's beyond
third party right what can be learned then you have to stick to it right so
that's what I'm about that's what I've been doing and because the major major
thing that I've noticed about surface-dwelling earth inhabitants it
tense other than their apathy is they don't learn they just don't learn and
it's very easy to do almost like a fait accompli you're always gonna have
history repeat itself I mean I try and combine it does the cycles of
catastrophism do I once while back with the Archon I was saying you know the
earth could have been completely destroyed or you know up until the year
800 and I kind of gave loose interpretation of what I found in
history but when you look at the archaic stuff he nails it down to the
years okay the the it's our kicks it's the first one he did on this subject
matter signs of the artificer archaic's interpretation of 2024 eclipse the other
one what would be harbinger of the second seal for a sorry more 820 24 yeah
what would be an artificer there's a word I don't recognize immediately
what's an artifies there's an artist oh okay all right let's look it up let's
look it up okay yeah it's that's art you know that yeah well you know
artifies or could be artifact you know I mean I don't know one who makes art of
skill or or one who makes by art or skill agent of an artifice inventor of
devious artifies is military sense a soldier mechanic so it tends to be more
on the malevolent side okay my craft or skill but artifies artifies or yeah it
would be something like someone who makes let's say the tools of the trade
for magicians press the digitation ledger domain would be an artificer
right you know I have a niece she goes by Wendy blades she's like one of the
top five sword swallowers in the world and she said for a while she worked with
magicians and I said oh cut lady in half and she goes oh yeah I said were you in
the box or out of the box I was in the box and she was so surprised that you
know I was able to talk about them the artifices of the magic trade because it's
about perception right okay without going too much of a tangent so by the
way I think I've gone over this you know when a woman's cut in half on stage and
put back together the box is always big enough to have another woman who's very
let's just say we someone's very flexible what do they call them people
that say what I call it contortionist what are they contortionist that's right
so you have a contortionist on the lower half of the box and as the woman is
stepping as she's placing her body in the box the person the woman inside the
box has to carefully time it to stick her legs out and she's all right and now
you know it's completely separate the whole time it runs the saw two separate
legs I put it in that right and when the woman's getting out of the box the one
that's contorted on the bottom half of the box has to pull her legs in and very
good time it's all about timing yeah so that's how that trick is done but you
see the magicians lies everyone if you don't know the trick you swear that you
just saw a woman being cut in half and put back together so that's what this
reality is going and has been going for it it shows lies and people swear to it
so I lie and you swear to it how's that for a deal hmm that's what attorneys are
doing that's what doctors are doing magically using a saw on somebody should
result in some blood being spattered but you know forget about that that doesn't
happen so well there's other things that go on I mean that do result in that with
the animals yeah so true yeah animals are flattened out right birds
especially when they're put put away you know when they're pulled out and
then put away and disappear they're actually flattened out so okay so the
you got the two videos first one was signs of the artifice or a second was
harbinger of the second seal I read them the back I listened to both of them I
didn't sit and watch if you put up anything he had some charts very
plausible very rational but we live in a world that's more plausible than
rational I like it I like it very much what I do like more than the information
that he gave out is by the end of the very convincing quote-unquote as the
academics say argument he said this doesn't mean that any of this is set in
stone so what he's doing is laying out what he would breadcrumbs he found right
yeah so you know I I like it I like it I would agree with everything that he put
up is pretty fundamental so yeah I give it a thumbs up yep on that so that
would be my review on it without getting into specifics because the specifics are
laid out in those two videos I don't think do I need to give the dates let's
just click on one here what the date on the first one which is sign of the
artificer would have been on March 20th 2024 and the other one was following
that you'll see it's part two okay so that's my comment on that but we don't
live in a rational world see the rationalists I've been in really really
enjoying an audiobook by Rory Sutherland it's called alchemy and why rational
ideas don't always make sense and sometimes the opposite of a good idea is
another good idea right so he it's very interesting this psychology I've always
been inclined to that but I always speak on being logic and rational because we
don't have enough of that without it being a specialty right you have
statisticians economists mathematicians and that's a specialty and their whole
job is about being logical and rational but the entire population is not so when
you're doing marketing you're just unless you're marketing to economics even
to them they would be fault economists mathematicians scientists or whatever
who tend to be rational you're marketing to the masses who are not and I really
enjoyed I'm still listening to the audio book in the back room basically where I
live and work I have speakers indoors and outdoors in a control center I could
put on a video or an audio or music and anywhere I go it's playing I could turn
some areas of the downer so it's high fidelity very high fidelity stuff it
sounds like you know someone's here you know so when I'm listening to the
audio book it actually sounds like someone's in the room speaking it
doesn't sound you know so I get I get them I get the full effect of it really
enjoying it if you he's done with quite a few YouTube videos Rory Sutherland he's
advice this is senior vice president of Ogilvy and Mather I think I did mention
if you ever watched the AMC series Mad Men it's modeled around the story of
ogle of Mather and Ogilvy Ogilvy is the British side matters in New York side
okay so the rationality of what he put out going back to archaics is pretty
good again it has a feathered touch to it because you know what you're doing is
taking information from here and seeing how applies through coincidence and
rationale right and it's very good very good by the way you see that boat hit
the bridge it's a ship hit the bridge yeah yeah that was that was really cool
because what's cool about it well first of all it's a shit bridge the towers
were made of the same expanded or you know channeled steel you shouldn't do
that by the way the tower should be very robust right but the second thing it's
the deliberate crash I mean it's a deliberate ramming right until you know
it looked like something that the Assyrians would have done 700 BC
breaching the walls of Damascus right with siege works you know they have this
ram right he's got hundred people on each side and the rams like this tree
you know it's two foot in diameter right with a bronze plating on the front and
they ram the wall right yeah sometimes I refer to that stuff as siege machines
and things like siege works yeah they sometimes fashion them as large penises
yeah that's what they did with this thing and what they did was you know the
commentary if you know anything about mechanics you could see the black smoke
billowing out and gray smoke that means something blue in the motor or the
boiler actually that was probably a diesel direct they were flooding with
fuel I don't know if that was just a signal a ship was in trouble but there
are redundants redundant safety controls on these ships by the way and they
they could be you know how you have the self-driving cars yeah it's an unwritten
rule but all ships of any measure are self piloting now by satellite in other
words pick up a line like mask right a big crew of shipping line all of their
ships are tagged and seen by satellite all of the instrumentation the status
engineering is uploaded to satellite back to the home office wherever the
home office is anywhere in the world and the ship can be piloted automatically
anywhere in the world so does that make any sense yeah it does because there's
tremendous backup systems for a tanker fuel tankers have this in it where every
single fuel tanker on the planet has a tracking device in it they know exactly
that's why it's always BS when they just track you the image show whatever the
plane that disappeared yeah the engines you know the plane that disappeared those
engines have 24-hour seven-day-a-week tracking from the it has to be done
from an engineering perspective Rolls-Royce and GE who make most of the
engines yeah but I was they have yeah I was gonna explain that look I don't
necessarily know about airplanes but I do know about the fuel ships because I
work for Exxon and the thing is that they had tracking stuff in there that
also allows them to be able to send other signals in order to take control
in case there's any sorts of that's right it's it's not I'm not talking about
tracking I'm talking about piloting yeah but which is the actual driving of
the ship yeah but I'm saying that all of those systems in a tanker including the
the the cargo ship yeah well but but I'm just saying about Exxon's tankers I know
this specifically that they have a cargo ship yeah and they are very different by
the way tankers and cargo ships oh I know very very different yeah you can't
yeah so I'm just backing you up I know but I'm just backing you up that there
are systems like this where they can absolutely track and exert influence
from a satellite on ships that are constantly running this is not some you
know rarefied thing that maybe wasn't there but it's interesting how it's
Francis Scott Key Bridge you know which is a patriotic name yeah the guy in
history yeah the guy wrote the yeah so it's like let's hit the one leg of the
bridge what does a bridge do right it connects so connectivity you know how
you had all this stuff talking about the connectivity was going to be taken down
what am I talking about how do you get connectivity connectivity connectivity
through the internet right right it didn't happen right so they unmanifested
it this way but yeah anyway I think you're on top of these current events
you saw that thing going in there I mean there that was a trajectory I mean yes
they're they don't they take they're very cumbersome but before you even got
into those I would call them narrows mm-hmm right the the water body you
would have set the ship in the center they deliberately in those kinds of water
ways they do dredging in the center for large ships to come through and he was
there off to the side and that didn't seem kosher to me at all see again with
these large things on water here's the thing you have to be very intentional you
can't you know the old expression you can't turn on a dime so clearly long
ahead of any turn you'd have to make or any obstacle you make sure to line oh
no you're you're not fighting where you're going to be an hour from now and
you're setting it up now right that's what I was yeah that's what I mean yeah
just just like yeah just like anything big like that which is the very fact
that it was lined up with the tower away from the deepest part of the narrows
well the only counter to that okay the only counter to that and it's a
question I have for you is that you know of course they in the news stories
immediately and I do mean universally they were stating that there was a
power failure just before and of course this happened that you know in one
o'clock in the morning or two o'clock in the morning at 130 a power failure on
the ship you mean or a power failure on land they were saying that there was a
power failure on the ship and by the way according to the last thing I saw
there's six people that were working on the bridge at the time and of course
that's always interesting to you ever notice how there's always workers on
whatever's your yeah but the numbers it's like in Russia the initial numbers
it was 11 terrorists and 133 right 11 and 33 make 44 144 you know yeah these
these are all this is what I call signaling this is six workers missing so
that's what I was gonna ask you about yeah six it's sick cuz six is a number
of men they're signaling stuff here and there and what's funny is the okay the
signal is what you know they ran a cargo ship rammed into a bridge which
doesn't happen even even sailboats are better than that so so what they're
signaling is what you saw objectively a ship a large ship rams into the Francis
Scott Key patriotic bridge right bridges bring people together right where they
normally couldn't come together easily and without getting wet right so you
have dry crossing you know represents all these things but I don't like to go
down that path but it's interesting and the people that they hire to explain it
away are really really dumb and the excuses are really really dumb why
because if they were intelligent no one would believe them but if you make them
really dumb and farcical everyone believes them same stuff going on do I
really care I think that bridge should have never been built the way it was you
know so maybe they'll build something better I doubt it I doubt it but you
know you can build something like that very fast now but those towers were out
inadequate right hmm so but that's okay I just think it's funny as hell I mean
yeah people lose their lives but you listen if we if anyone ever hears us
making fun of people getting killed in these events I want you to remember this
I'm not making fun of it I'm just making light of it that more people are killed
by your medical doctors than any other reason you core an incident ever every
day so you're gonna have to have an incident where you get more than 3,000
people to 5,000 people a day for them to top what the medical doctors are doing
of course you know one weird thing I wanted to ask you about actually is the
fact that they claim that this this vessel is precisely the same vessel that
was involved in a collision when leaving the port of Antwerp in Belgium in 2016
fine which is fine interesting so the vessel is a bully
apparently it's a you know it's other collisions as history of bullying and at
the schoolyard yeah I guess of course lost to the bridge you know yeah that's
often that's to soften the surprise so this is what literally literally some
people say what you just said about happening in Antwerp they'll say oh that
makes more sense makes more sense because oh that but it does it that boat
had trouble so yeah but all they're doing is oversimplifying and saying yeah
you know oh that thing had trouble before so trouble again you know so yeah
just to me and it's all bullshit 100% right yeah I love it because you know what
I say I love it I'm not that I like bullshit but just another day and still
running the same program so that's what that's what rated Y is about just we
just talk about this let's see the program it's very simple and another
day stupid stupid games you went through stupid prizes fair enough and
you know and look the one thing you're guaranteed is is a fair amount of
consistency you know much like we said earlier you know does history repeat
itself of course it does but it's again it's it's consistency really more than
rhyming or you know but what I do like what the archaic stuff again is the
cycle and I've gotten into that sort of I was never again my stuff was just let's
look at what we have what's being put out like archaics did brochures but he
did it in a very very narrow and deep way and there's other people that
probably know this but he's the only one speaking out on these matters what I
always said is let's just go look at things that are significant in our lives
and what's written about them or memorialized or shown about them and
just use that as our baseline and no one's doing that well not no one but you
know very few and let's just talk about them because it's very surprising when
you find out that the truth of the matter which by the way is not a fact you know
facts and truths are two different things in many times especially legally
so I guess people have surmised that if you're if you've been listening to Greek
speak for a while well they might have surmised it but I mean I wouldn't mind if
you elaborated about that it's maybe we should do do one on that oh it's a
subjective truth is not but it's very again we live in a reality that likes to
impress us with perception so give an example it's a fact that if I wear a
pink baseball cap on what they call Monday keeps the elephants out of Tucson
that's a fact because there's no elephants how is it a fact because
there's no elephants in Tucson that's where you win that means that that is a
fact it's what I just said is a fact it's a fact there are no elephants in
Tucson because I wear a pink hat every Monday right that's the state well it's
can we prove that yeah well not the part that the hat is keeping them away but the
whole statement that there are no elephants in Tucson right well on the
whole but you did that there's therefore no elephants in Tucson I mean I could
tell you I ate a cheese sandwich and you slept four hours you know and two things
they could both be true but it's not because causality is not attached you
know yeah that's why this is tied back to if you ever been set in federal cases
you bring up any law the judge gets very upset so you can't bring law into
this courtroom but when they have the media and the press they say well the law
says this look so you live in a very distorted devious situation so that's
why when you're dealing with anyone or anything you hold them accountable to not
what's what the situation is the subject matter but are they doing what they're
supposed to be doing right you know just like with anything if someone go if
the medical parts kind of difficult well the police and the police have kept
you alive for 50 years Greg you've been alive for 50 years and there have been
it's because there you go yeah the banker they're basically clerks for the
central banks well they're the police what they are I think we've gotten to
this police are when when the central bank the private bank takes over your
town they protect their they own the property on paper so they need to create
policing to protect their property so every police force that you see whether
it's Interpol or local or city or whatever is there to protect the
interests of the bankers period that's the history go look at it well and
that's why this small towns don't happily they have sheriff's which put
which sheriff is the interest of the king again so yeah yeah it's pretty it's
pretty yeah I mean but you know it's better no I got you again it's it's just
two facts put together don't necessarily make a truth again I mean you could say
look there's 15 prostitutes in my town therefore I get good vegetables it
they're not connected but you know I say they're connected and both things hey
look there are this many prostitutes you do the JFK thing so you see what it's
kind of ludicrous but again based on the stuff that I just enjoyed listening to
Rory Sutherland on his alchemy audiobook that it's all percent look
most of the stuff that works well with people in general isn't doesn't make any
sense at all and you know you tie that in with what I've been saying that if
you you know like if you had a real education system that was viable no one
would understand anything they they wouldn't understand it so you have to
have right because they've been indoctrinated and almost bred it's a
grooming is you have breeding and grooming breeding is when you put the
male-female pair together based on certain criteria to procreate and then
grooming is when they procreate from a young age you guide that offspring into
living a certain way so what people don't realize even with all the
subjectivity that they have in their lives is that they've been part of a
breeding and grooming program that's been going on very strictly since the
early 1700s right so that's that's that also has to be taken consideration and
that's where the psychology is the psychology is very simple when you
understand the breeding and grooming programs that have been put in place and
they drop it in front of you in a very oversimplified manner like grooming at
this point the common vernacular is to use it for preparing a child to be
exploited yet no no to be exploited as sexually is generally what grooming is
about at this all that as well yeah it's all set well it has to be it has to
be because the sexual aspect of it has to be always in the mix because that
leads eventually back to the breeding right the cycle it's part of the
parameters that need to be set by the culture anyway I mean in yeah that's why
there's Huxley where the test everyone's is grown in a test tube right and the
sexual part is completely separated you know right and people and then they
become more pneumatic inside jokes anyone read this stuff you know a comment
was if you enjoyed sex with someone you said oh they were very pneumatic anyway
it's an inside kind of if you haven't read the Brave New World stuff like if
someone as well how how was that date oh she was very pneumatic you know
anyway yeah you have to you have to read it by the way the BBC BBC does a three
hour I think it's on YouTube still free I got to get a film I got the CDs also
I got the CDs yeah there you go it's a word it's worth a watch it's it's if
you're fond of the rated Y stuff you'll really dig it yeah do you like do you
like the black-and-white the old one or do you like the newer one the newer
BBC one the one done in the 80s because there was one I should say that without
criticizing with not much of a criticism because I'm not familiar with the black
and white one yeah there's a very old black and white one that I think was made
like at the end of the 50s I want to say maybe I should Wow I think then I would
go with the one made in the 80s of which might have been a little more risque
yeah definitely definitely but I mean they definitely had a different view of
the like I think it's a view screens oh no maybe it's not the view screens it's
yeah but either way check it out to be yeah it's probably still on YouTube okay
I'd say watch them all really