Rated Y, Sonic Event 147. And here we go, a little skip there at the beginning on the
intro. A little glitch, a little glitch. There's glitches in the Matrix now and then. I saw
something in the chat, by the way, where people were talking about this article, I guess,
in the Guardian or one of, you know, one of the two British news online paper things,
right? Where they were saying there's certain traits in the face that show people scientifically
when you're gay. Well, it made me think of faces and traits.
I didn't look at that, but yeah, you've heard it before with the genetics, there's a gene
and all that. Remember, anything, anytime you hear scientific, it's bullshit now. It's
been proven already, right? Is that funny? Because they use the same term. Scientifically
proven means absolutely nothing. You're supposed to trust the science all the time, right? Trust
the science. It's part of the religion. Well, the whole thing here, let's go harken back
when one of the things about ancient Greece is there were a lot of homosexuals. What people
don't realize is when you read the classics, there is no homosexuality. You might have this
guy having an intimate relationship with this guy, but they're never called gay. Right?
So that the whole thing about the homosexuality and whatever, I think that emerged recently,
like past century or two, maybe three. Well, there's even the concept of, say, Achilles
and Patroclus, right? Or Patrick, please, whatever you want to call them. And, you know,
they were they were intimate and they were cousins or something, too, which is another
whole thing. But but it doesn't say, you know, Achilles is gay. It just says that he
has this very close relationship with Patrick. There is no stuff in the Bible to Jonathan
and David, but there's no classification. So when you start seeing these classification
now scripture, the Bible tells you man lay with a man or woman lay with a woman. That's
a death offense. Right. Right. Because it's kind of strict. It's very that's another discussion.
But why is it like that? It doesn't matter why. It's just that, you know, it's a set
of rules, like Simon says, let's say. Right. OK. But the there is this classifications
that create that are created are done as part of the social engineering outline. Right.
So then it could be used against you both when they create homosexuality as a category,
the LGBTQ, RST, UV, whatever. Yeah. As to you, P.I.D., whatever. Yeah. As to you, P.I.D.
Of course. Most that's what there may not be LGBTQ, but they're definitely as to you,
P.I.D. So it seems that way. I would say that when I say that it's to be used against you,
meaning both sides, both pro and con. Right. That's right. Like the. Yeah, it's so it's
all these are weaponized word magic. I recently put in the chat one of the since we had Dimitri,
I found this very rare and asked Bruce to make a copy of this. The first minute it was a member
of Bush was in the book on the goat and he was in a classroom with the black children. It's funny.
I was only black children. Yeah. Remember that? Not 11. Yeah. In Florida. He's down in Florida
and he's reading my pet goat or whatever the book to the class, supposedly. Something like
that. We never saw what we never saw a video. Did you catch the video what the children were
told to to read out loud? No, I don't think I ever put it in the chat. Yeah. Check it out.
Well, anyway, it's the teachers recite these words quickly. Steel. Children are like steel. Hit. Hit.
Plane. Plane. Must. Must. And the children recite play must hit steel. Wow. Yeah. Pretty trippy,
right? That is trippy. I never heard that. Yeah. Well, no, that's what I said. Let's make a copy
of the first. It's only in the first minute. Yeah, definitely. Because that's going to be
that's not going to last. And it's funny how it emerged 20 years later. It seems pretty legit.
Even if it wasn't, let's say someone put that together with AI. It looks legit.
This is how the world is based. And people don't understand. It's it's so subtle.
Let me put it this way. I'll settle. Okay. Tangent. We don't live in a real reality. In other words,
it's it's malleable. And I've had I experienced a Mandela effect every three or four months,
a big one. Give an example. Very stark. It's it's irrefutable. I have a table saw with a fence,
and it's a small, portable construction is called the construction site saw. It's not that big.
And I have some pieces of board that I cut at 10 and a quarter. Okay. You work a table size,
you set the fence and you measure the distance of the word between the fence and the blade,
right? Okay. So this is literally a saw a saw that's set in a table that you actually use
things to it's called a table saw tool, right? So yeah, there were like four or 500 bucks,
you get cheap ones for 150. So anyway, right, okay, I made a cut bunch of cuts at 10 and a
quarter. Well, today, I went to to make some at 11. And I bring the fence all the way to the edge,
and the fence doesn't go past nine and a half. So in other words, that saw was made
to only cut up to nine and a half inches. Now, how long ago did you do the 10 and a quarter?
A month ago, a month ago, I did I cut, I cut stuff just fine, it was setting the fence at 10
and a quarter with some room to spare, because you don't want to run the fence to the end of
the saw table, because then it's got nothing in the clamp on. Right. So you can't possibly
have run it to 10 and a quarter if it only goes to nine. What did you say? Nine and a half? Yeah,
nine and a half, it wouldn't go past. If I lined it, I said, Wait a second, because I moved the
have the tape measure open between the blade and the left side of the fence. And I have the tape
measure up a new 11, right, like 10 and three quarter. And the fence falls off the table.
I'm like, Wait a second, why is that possible and put it back on? And let me let's push the fence
over to where it doesn't fall off the extreme edge. And it was only nine and a half. So how
the hell did I cut 10 and a quarter the other day? Yeah, right. And I ran it's not it because
I see it in front of me when I cut and I ran a bunch of it. So how can it only be and it's
on the left hand side, the right hand side is the same the blades in the middle. So
whether you go right or left, it doesn't matter. So how was I making these 10 and a quarter cuts
where now the maximum cut you can do is not enough on a tool that's been sitting outside in
the rain. It's been 20 years, it still works. And it's not a new tool where maybe I you know,
maybe somebody swapped it. It's the same tool. And I was like, You know what, fuck you, whoever's
doing a skull, fuck yourself. I'm going to deal with it. I'm going to build an extension. So I
had some blocks of aluminum. I've been working with cryo, cryo sacro late CA glue, which is
crazy glue. Many things you can do with it. So actually crazy glued some large aluminum section
to the table saw it's actually holding I'm going to put I put not in a ball do I remember the crazy
glue commercials in 70 they had the guy picking up whatever actually does that can't take a shock
load. No, they had the guy actually puts it on the thing on his hand on his hard hat. He hooks
the hard hat to the girder and he hangs from it. Yeah, yeah, right. Now you could take off,
but it can't take a shock. You know, shock load is when you tap something right, right, like an egg,
you can drive a truck over an egg if you have it in the right, but it can't take a shock load. So
yeah, buildings are very sensitive. By the way, that way when I was doing engineering,
shock loads on buildings are very sensitive. In other words, you have a lot you can imagine a
floor of a skyscraper loaded with people, right? It's designed to take that, right? Like, let's say
having a big party, you don't want the thing to collapse, right? Right. So it's designed for that.
But the shock load is minimal. Once you start putting a shock load on that you literally can
collapse a floor with only 40 P at 40 pounds per square inch. Only 40 pounds per square is not a lot
and at shock load value, right? But no, you know, you're not going to get that kind of shock load.
But anyway, that's why we used to break up sidewalks, right? Jackhammer, what's jackhammer?
It's a shock load. It's a shock load focused in a particular area. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. So anyway, I throw a little tidbit, just see how the mind works. That's what I you
know, when I think about something that's like my process. But anyway, weird stuff. And yeah,
the whole thing, the class, watch how more back to the gay face thing or whatever you thought you
bring up because I talked about an old book from the Third Reich era on phrenology. Right? It's
similar to for Yeah, what they're doing is phrenology. I didn't look at it. I'm just, you
know, very rarely do I click on stuff that people send me. That's why I say if you drop a link, give
me a short description of what it is. So I have the option not to click on it. Keep moving, right?
Right. So and that's good. There was a message on that. But it's all bullshit. And it's going to
get thicker and thicker. It's so ridiculous. What was it? Just like ridiculous. I saw it was a
governor Newsom, California announced they're missing 24 billion or something like that. I love
it. That's a new one. Yeah. Yeah, I love it. Like what do people do? You know, it's like, what do we
do about this? Yeah, where's the outrage? You know, how many times you heard these people that
are popular, famous? I'm not suicidal. And then they're found like a month later hanging in the
garage, right? Where's the outrage? Right? Why don't the people get together? Yeah, it's a bunch
of stupid, like Dimitri says, they're stupid cowards. You know, so who cares if you know, you
know, they're stupid cowards are not going to do well. And you know, if you're not good, here's
the thing. People say let's change the world, make it better, right? For who? A bunch of stupid
cowards? The majority? No, they don't need to have it better. They need to have it go away real fast.
They need to go away real fast, whatever it takes, whatever it takes. And that's what's happening. So
fair enough. Fair enough. Yeah. But I mean, you know, phonology is interesting, though,
because I think there are things you can see you can actually judge, you know, instead of judging
a book by its cover, you can judge somebody by their face a bit. I mean, I think people do wear
things on their face. Yeah, loony Dick Tracy. Look, this is if you want to know what phonology is.
Look at who shows up on Looney Tunes and Dick Tracy type stuff. They exaggerated the phonology
on that. Right. You ever notice how the regular people look fairly regular and the criminals
always had an exaggerated feature of some kind? Yes, always. And Dick Tracy himself with the
strong. OK, yeah. Look at the comic cartoonists are experts on phonology and body type.
I had a roommate who was a cartoonist and he basically like every artist, you struggle to
create your own style. Right. And he was trying to create his own style. And we would go we would
trip. We take some psilocybin, mescaline, which is, again, a synthetic. We hang out by the fountain
in Prospect Park and Central Park, depending when. And he would start sketching people walking by and
he would point out this lady here. She's got the fat lady gene. And I look at the ladies pointing
out she's not fat. So I didn't say she was fat. I say she has the fat lady gene. What's the fat
lady gene? Slightly knockneed, small feet, cutesy face, kind of roundish around the hip area, kind
of like a pear shape. The shoulders go in narrow when the arms are laying down on their sides.
They're kind of short and they have like a double bend by the elbow. That's the fat lady gene.
And then like another person to walk by, that guy's got the skinny man gene and he's not skinny.
But look, yeah, he's kind of slender, big feet up on his crotch, middle point area. There's a gap.
You ever notice some people, you know, their thighs don't come. The thigh meat doesn't touch.
It's a big gap in that area. Right. Right. Kind of a long neck with an Adam's apple that's prominent.
Right. OK. OK. That's the skinny man gene. And it has nothing to do with them being skinny
or the fat lady gene. Her being fat has to do with the how they're growing, right? How they fit
the model. Then you can exaggerate that. You know, when you're going to draw a skinny man,
you make the exaggerated Adam's apple and the gap, you know, by the groin area,
wide skinny slender legs. And you start exaggerating how how bad is he a badass skinny
man or is a badass. Right. And you have to have those features to communicate that.
And that's what phrenology is. That's all. It's just what's being communicated. Yeah.
But all the science is BS. Here's the thing. Any branch of science that you study, even engineering,
if you include all the things they took out in their studies, you'll find that you're not
learning anything. It's all experiential observation. There is no laws. There is no
they have no firm body on anything at all. You know, it's pretty interesting.
So that's what do I say here all the time? I'm rated wide. I've been saying for a long time is
all fields are wide open. Every field of study you can imagine is completely wide open. Like there's
the Thomas catalog, which is for industry. I think it has like 10,000 different categories or 3,000
categories of things that are in industry. All of them are completely open, completely open.
And I'm proving this with the water stuff, with the scalarator. I'm proving it now with the acoustic
modules, counter space modules. And the world is there's stupid cowards and they're idiots.
So, you know, how well can you do in a society like that? Well, put it this way.
On one hand, you can say you'll do great because they're idiots. Right. And if you're not doing
it, you don't even have to be smart. You just don't have to be an idiot. Right. That puts you
ahead. Right. Sure. But then it should. But then who are you doing it for? Who are you doing it
with? A bunch of idiots again. And are they going to hold you back? Bet your ass they are.
Now, you notice how he said, on the other hand, if you're someone who's busy and you have the
wherewithal to have people around you, like, for example, a consulary, right? And you need people
around you like a right hand man. You know, they always use a right hand man. Never say left hand
man. Or they say, on the other hand. Anyway, when they did the Federal Reserve thing,
they brought over a German guy. It didn't speak any English. Nobody in the banking system spoke
any English when they brought the Federal Reserve over. Nobody cared. But one of FDR's requests was,
with this new economic system, I want a one armed man. And they were like,
why do you want a one armed man? Because he could never come back to me and say,
on the other hand. But anyway. OK. Fair. Was the decision was there's only one way to go all the
way to go. That's right. Yeah. And he was making that point because that's where we are right now
with that. Now, I've been getting some emails from the newer people that have joined from
the Archaic's interview. Right. Oh, I watched in our recent Archaic's interview with the Hawaii
family. Let me just say. Close your ears. No comment. No comment. I'm done with that stuff.
I'm glad he I'm glad he put forward what he did with the Phoenix and all that stuff.
It's just anybody. Well, if you've been if you know what's going on, go listen to that last.
Don't listen to it. Actually, the Hawaii video and the one before that. OK. We're being dummy
loaded with slave talk now. And that's it. I just took him off my bookmarks for now. But anyway,
nothing against him. It's just shit, you know. And I thought I had something really interesting
to fight to look forward to eventually, you know, because on the Internet is here where I work and
live. I have speakers in every room just about and, you know, and outside and have a control
center. So if I have a YouTube video on or an audio book, I can decide where I want it to play.
If I'm going to be working on the shop area or whatever, I have it playing there so I can
actually put on like a book that's six hours long and in two days not read the book, but hear the
book. Right. And I could be doing other stuff. And I used to do it for a lot of his videos and
enjoy them. But the last whole bunch of them, I was like, OK, no more. This is over. Sorry.
And this this happens. It's not like, you know, you get enticed. In other words, what I'm trying
to say, I'm objective enough to know when things are going down. Right. It's kind of like when you
when your restaurant opens and I don't mean where they honeymoon you with,
you know, when you get in honeymoon means they're treating you better than
you know, will it be acceptable? Right.
Honeymooning is a thing that's used in a lot of terms used in a lot of places. Right. Right.
Yeah. It's like what I told you when you get a new job, don't do your best work in the beginning
because then they're going to think that's normal. And it's the standard
to do the minimum amount, minimal amount when you get hired. Don't try to impress them and then
do slightly better. And then that you're right. That's more impressive. Right. Right.
But people are used to it's called honeymooning. But anyway,
I've noticed with certain very rarely, very rarely,
most of the audio books, the stuff that I put on YouTube and Jason was on the list
for a go. He's got a new video. Great. It's two hours. Great. I'll be outside in the shop. Put it
on. You'll hear something. Right. Cool. Not anymore. In other words, like a restaurant that was good
and it's not good anymore. Right. You know what I mean? OK. And it's kind of disappointing.
And I'm saying it from an amici point of view, from a friendly point of view, criticism
in a good way. I'd like to see the quality stay the same or get better, not get worse.
And if you understand the point that I'm coming from, you listen to it.
Most people will say, great, there's nothing wrong with it. Boy, let me point like a 15,
25 things up. You know, it's like I just I had. In other words, I can't
lately with our kicks. I can't watch more than 15, 20 minutes. I turn it off.
You know, so it's it's because his stuff is some of the I would say Jason has put out some of the
best stuff that's been on the Internet in the past decade, a year ago or two years or even
six months ago. And I was very impressed. So, you know, I hope he I hope he gets he brings it back.
Now, I'm not speaking for anyone other than myself. And it's from a positive criticism.
But the reason I'm sharing this is more private area to share it. I'm not trolling him or being
a shill or anything like that. I always wish everybody the best. But if anyone hears what
I'm I'm not saying what I heard, but it's just the basic slave talk that's really hard to listen to.
Anyone else hearing that? I'm with you. Right. So but I'd like to see him do well. And he has
doing well because he's doing it for material reasons anyway. And he brags about it in a good
way. You know, he's not greedy and let him do what he's got to do, you know. But I've been kind of
disappointed lately. And in other words, anybody got any any anything else substitute anything else
to listen to? Because I have several projects I have to be machining and building things. I'm
making my own loudspeaker drivers. I'm actually buying a loudspeaker drivers, taking them apart.
It's kind of like remember the Johnny Cash. I brought it all one piece at a time. The song
built a car. Right. OK, so I'm building my own speaker drivers, not from scratch, but I'm buying
drivers that I passed muster, taking them apart and recombining them like Frankenstein in order
for them to perform, because I don't feel like spending five hundred dollars on one speaker
driver. Right. Because scan speak makes some good. And even then I would have to take them apart.
They're flawed. They don't know what they're doing at all. The industry at all. If you don't believe
that, go look at a car commercial. Aside from them touting that it's electric, it has Wi-Fi
or Bluetooth. Oh, my gosh. Nothing about the tolerances of the engine or the mileage anymore.
Right. You know, yeah, we were supposed to be. There was enough engineers, if you remember,
in the 80s that got fired or quit because they already had technology that would have big cars
going at 100 miles per gallon with a computerized fuel injection. And what I want to say is they
have this thing in a car called an oxygen sensor. Right. Right. And it's part of the emissions
pollution control. If you were really against pollution, they wouldn't call it an oxygen
sensor. They would call it a pollution sensor. Think about it. It's all backwards. It's all
backwards. So what I'm trying to say, it's all fucked. I mean, you're fucked, but you're in a
fucked up spot, fucked up place. If you're hearing my voice and you got, you know, perceiving what's
around you, make the best of it. It's more than just making lemonade, because the last thing you
want to do is take a bath in lemonade. Right. You're not always making lemonade. Right. True.
So, yeah, that's pretty much the idea. It's not a good spot. Can you be happy when you're
not in a good. Yeah, absolutely. You can you can make. OK. You know how people say I don't have any
time. Right. You hear that a lot. Right. They're not thinking all you have is time. You're born
and you die. What do you have in between time? That's that's what you have in between.
All you have is time. Right. Right. So what you do is you make happiness. No one. Right.
Everyone's level of what they consider to be, you know, with, you know, that bullshit they
said 300 years ago now, almost a pursuit of life, liberty and happiness and all that stuff. There
was they changed that. It was some other stuff because it was basically for themselves and they
had to take out the personification, make it sound like anyone reading it. Right. Right. But
and then there's other letters to prove many letters that they've things they wrote to each
other to prove what I said. But anyway, by the way, just to distract, you know, that Jefferson
wrote, I'm paraphrasing here that one day the governments will be able to put something into
the bodies of their citizens to be able to track their moves and everything that they do. You know,
Jefferson wrote that. You remember, I think I read that quote. I've heard about it. I've heard
about I don't remember you reading it, but I have heard about it. Yeah. Yeah. It was a while
back. We did it maybe on the previous iteration of our sonics or something to look it up.
And when was Jefferson around like late 1700s, early 1800s? He was an old fart by the
early 1800s. I don't know. Did he live past the 1812? I don't know. But anyway,
200 and something years ago, they were already basking in the idea, which was more than an idea
because remember, all technology exists all the time. When you get it, it's new to you.
Right. An example, I was at the CES show in Chicago in 1985. And the CD players,
Phillips and Sony was just barely hitting him. But Phillips came up with a CD player. Wow,
you know, no more scratchy albums. And I was talking to one of the engineers says,
yeah, that's good. But you know what? It's really about uncorruptible memory chips,
which is, you know, you don't have it on it. You don't need to play anything or spin anything and
just put it all on a chip. Right. And I was like, yeah, I know what you're talking about,
because I had an answering machine. Remember, answering machines, they had tapes and all.
Right. But I had bought an AT&T answering machine that didn't have any tapes that had that chip in
it. You just record everything on a solid state back then. Right. You'll just come out. It would
be like 100 bucks for today's money before 100 bucks for an answering machine. But anyway,
probably didn't have it. Yeah. It's like four times from the 80s. So they bypassed, you know,
so they put out. Right. You see what I'm saying? But when did you have all the music on a chip?
So what they call an iPod or what? The Apple made it popular. Yeah. The iPod through Apple
and the Zune through. Yeah. Which is it was a little better. I had a couple of them.
So you know that people don't know you could find someone wants to find it's not important.
But I remember there's a company called Logitech. That's right. They came up with it before Apple
and Apple stole it outright. They had it patented and all that. And Apple stole it.
And Logitech went after. I think it was not called Logitech went after Apple and they won.
They settled for 300 million or something out of court. Well, they just settled. Apple settled it.
And that gave them, you know, to to get into the periphery. They're a big peripheral
company. They make peripherals. Right. So you don't hear about these successes and all that
stuff. So from the supposedly little guys. But any company that does more than 10 million is
or it used to be 150 million to be in the big boys. What happens is let's say your company
doing 150 million in business. You're going to have someone planted mid-level management
or one of these positions in there that's hard to fire. That's that's part of the insider group.
You want to call them Illuminati's. You want to call them military intelligence.
You want to call them, I don't know, the secret college, you know, whatever. You know,
there's many names for these. The Deep State. What other what else are the Freemasons like
Dimitri likes the secret. So it is the secret societies of all the side. You're going to have
a secret. And they're connected with, you know, the in the bankers, the IRS and the military and
all that. And they have they're in a position where they could steer and influence your company
constantly. Right. And then they are also in a position where they know everything. You can't
hide anything from them because they already in a position where they can access things. Right.
Your finances, people, goings on your personal life. Right. So that's the reality. And I've
heard this from two different people at two different times, about 10 years apart,
separate people. And that's how it works. And from speaking with Jonathan Butts,
who died a sudden death, he started working when he died a sudden death at 49. He says,
oh, it's a lot less than that now. It's more like 10 million. It's more like 10 million now.
So they're really putting a hold on the control of what they call finances. And I think for my
last sonic financial is not money. Right. I need to stress that. Yeah. Finances is not money.
Economy is something the economy. No most means laws. It goes. It goes means house.
So equals equals. But it means like the house in a symbolic sense. That's where you get eco
ecology from. Ecology means knowledge of your house. Yeah. Knowledge of all the things that
are. But that's all the things in it. That's not just monetary. That's everything in it,
though. The ecology. Right. I mean, that's you're supposed to manage economy and economy is what
rules you use, like the Bible, biblical economy. When you say that, that has nothing to do with
gold and silver, even though it does. And when you say biblical economy, it's the way you transact
and the way you set things up when you live that way. Right. So when you say economy,
it's the whole setup. Like, for example, the communists have a slightly different economy
than the capitalists. Right. But neither one has anything to do with money. So when people say,
what about economy? I'm like, that is the economy, the financial part or the money part,
because you can have an economy with no money and have finances. You can have money and finances,
by the way, because this current credit system where you sign an unconditional order to pay.
Yeah. Right. That's what a bill is. And when you give it back, that whatever they when you return
it to them, it's good. It credits their account wherever they have it. That's been going on
since the law days way, way back, way, way back. Minimal like the John Locke days and
law. What's the other guy's name that started pushing this? It was a refined,
redone system from that the Medici's try to put it in. One day we'll do the history of banking.
I have to collect my thoughts because there's really two or three different styles of banking
financial systems that were running parallel. And it didn't get finalized until the UCC in the
1940s with what we have now and Bretton Woods. So none of that really matters.
Yeah. You go into like Friedman and all that, right?
You can. You can. Well, in the 80s, they have all the big economists that also suggested,
just like you have Jung and Freud. You know, you had I forgot their guys names, but there's like
two or three different major economists in the 20th century. Right. And they still use their
philosophies and none of that matters because all that matters is the way you perceive scarcity.
Well, that's why I mentioned Milton Friedman, because he's the one of the guys who's they
say is the major one of the major economists right from the 20th century.
There's a whole bunch of them. Who's the other one? The one that was more than Friedman said
right now, I'm not I'm not accessing those files, but there's several of them.
No, we'll get it together on another meeting. Put it all together. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But if
you look at their stuff, it's interesting if none of it is. There's nothing really to buy.
They're not addressing bankruptcies, receiverships and the fall of nations. None of them are.