Hey, Sonic Event 89 on Rated Y, no, not 89, whoops, 98, other way around, either way it'll
be similar.
It will be similar.
It could be similar.
Often things are similar like that.
So Greek, you know, I would ask you how you're doing, but instead I'm going to go at you
with a question that I got on Facebook, of all places.
That's how I'm doing.
Just hit me up with the questions.
Even if you ask me how I'm doing, it's not a question.
It is.
Anyway, go ahead.
Sure.
But this one came from a sub on Facebook, a subscriber on Rated Y, but they sent me
in the message via Facebook for some reason.
Anyway, they wanted to know about what is actually in the biblical text regarding the process
of death.
And I know we've discussed this before, but I think...
But I have to preface, because I haven't been doing this a lot.
Biblical text that we have that people read, we in any country, is a version.
What's memorialized in the scriptures you'll find very different.
But the reason I got into this, big but, is because I had no desire, you know, if anyone
said they had a Bible, I was like, ah, it's, you know, written by Shakespeare or whatever.
So I was like, wait, how can I knock it if I've never really read it or even studied
it, right?
It's kind of like watching a trailer of a movie and saying it's a bad movie, right?
You can usually.
But anyway, I started studying scripture and I found out what was in the Bible was not talked
about in religious circles, in churches, whatever, synagogues, or even in public or in memes
or cliches.
And what they're talking about is not in the Bible.
So it's like, ooh, wait a second, it seems like everybody missed this.
So that's the reason why I got into it.
But it is the order of things that anybody who, you know, basically clings to a text
and says that this is their Bible, and by the way, they use the word their Bible, their
book to mean a lot of things.
Yeah, but they don't know anything in it.
They never know anything that's in it.
It doesn't matter.
Even when somebody says, you know, look, I'm in whatever, name an industry, and they say,
this is my Bible, you know, and it's some instructional manual or it's something else.
Yeah, the federal people, they see the U.S. codes, and they don't, they never even read
the definitions.
And they don't know what it means.
Anyway, even if they know the codes, they have no idea what they mean.
Yeah, but the definitions undoes most of the codes when it comes to the general population.
There you go.
It only applies to those that work for the executive.
All right, give me an example.
The last general order, I think, was 1871, you know, executive general order.
It was Order 100, General Order 100, and that was the last time there was an order put out.
But all of the other ones are called executive orders, and those are for people that are
employees of the executive branch.
And they could apply to other branches, meaning the judicial and legislative also.
So when, right now, if you watch television, the President of the United States says, putting
out an executive order, everyone thinks it applies to them.
Well, it only applies to whoever's working for the executive branch as an employee of
the executive branch.
It doesn't apply to the general population.
But general orders do, like General Order 100, which is the Lieber Code.
It's the orders for the army in the field, because they pretty much decided that they're
going to use the army to control the population from then on.
But anyway, anyway, so anyway, if you go out telling this to people, they'll think you're
crazy.
You know, executive order applies to me.
Yeah, you're crazy.
Everybody knows that, you see?
No, the executive order came...
Biblical stuff is exactly the same way.
Yeah, it came down from the President, and therefore he said, and here's the funny part
about that, is that even the people that tout that and say that and say that it applies
to them, they never read that either.
I find that they never read the executive order, even if they know of an executive order.
They know the number of it and everything else.
They never read that either, which is really funny.
But even if you read it, do you comprehend its application?
Give me an example.
All of the codes, even the local ones, apply to persons, corporations, trusts, et cetera.
Now, if you look up a person, a person is either a corporation or a trust.
Right?
It doesn't say people anywhere.
So none of that really applies to you, unless...
That's why when people complain to the Attorney General, you know, why did you railroad this
guy in a mistrial or whatever, you know, whatever, you didn't get a fair trial.
He says, well, he agreed to everything we said.
It's a contract, right?
So yeah, but if you go out and start...
You can only do this, by the way, if you're dealing with a judiciary or any administrative
office.
You cannot do this publicly.
It's best to do it privately, because there is someone there that knows.
Give me an example.
Most of the people that work for the executive branch don't know what I just said.
They don't know it.
But there's someone in there that does, high up on the ladder, right?
So making it public to the people that work, even work for the executive branch, isn't going
to get you anywhere.
In other words, if you understand something that's been codified, because the Bible's
codified also, I'm using that in a literal sense, and if you bring this up to someone
who supposedly subscribes to it, whether it's the Bible or the codes or the laws, and they
don't understand what you're saying or don't see it immediately or agree with it, you're
too low on the totem pole, right?
So that's why a lot of these patriots, whatever, we'll get back to the question.
You know, they try to talk to the police officers about the law.
Oh, my God, those guys are handing out contracts, right?
They don't know anything.
As a matter of fact, it's very well established that if you score too high, right, on aptitude
tests for becoming an officer, what do they say?
No, we won't hire you.
And the reason they gave, the semi-official reason they gave is because, oh, you won't
be interested.
You'll be bored by the job, right?
That was the reason.
I don't know if you remember that.
So the same thing goes with the biblical text.
Now, the biblical text, the other reason I got into it is because it seems to be what
is the anchor for law, culture, morality, and ethics for the Western world.
And of the Islam also, because the Koran does say, you look at the laws of Moses, right?
Well, and they have an arranged, digest, or systematic collection, which is the definition
of codified, right?
So they do have these things arranged in a...
It not only is no one really discussing what's in the Bible and what they discuss is not in
the Bible, even in the versions, even if you aren't as strict, let's say pedantic and conservative
as I am to go and look at the original, what was preserved in Hebrew or Greek before it
was turned into a version.
Even if you don't do that, reading the versions will clearly show you very much a mirror of
what's in the original.
You make a lot of mistakes, but you still end up with a very similar product.
The product being how you should think about it.
And again, just to repeat myself, basic world ethics, commerce, you know, a lot of commercial
stuff, ethical stuff, moral stuff, it comes out of the Bible.
So it's an important thing to know.
And let's go back to the question.
The process of death we've gotten, which we will get into the container again, is when
the soul dies, then the body, the container starts to go into decay and then the spirit
leaves that situation because the body is made up of the soul, which is the metabolism
that runs the body, like the gas in the car, the oil in the car, right?
No gas or no oil in the car, it doesn't run.
And then the car decays because it doesn't run.
And the spirit is the computer in the car, right?
So there's nothing much in that process, actually.
I don't know if it's been redacted.
Yeah, I was going to say it's also the breath, though, when you say spirit, right?
I mean, yeah, well, no, the spirit would be the mind and the breath is part of the soul,
which is the metabolism, because it's one way to know if a person has a metabolism is
that they're breathing.
They check for breathing first, even, you know, in medical community, where they check
for breathing and then heart rate, right?
If there's no breathing and there's no heart rate or heart beat, that means the metabolism
is gone, but it's not too far gone.
We try to revive the heartbeat and the breath.
Now, you can have no breath and no heartbeat.
Like someone, you hear about people with the NDEs that fall in Frozen Lake and they
pull them out a half hour later.
They're not breathing.
There's no heartbeat.
But they're resuscitated.
Right.
OK, so the metabolism was able to be brought back.
So that's and that's the soul is part of that.
Right.
You need the breathing.
OK, so there's like a car.
If you put your hand over the carburetor or put a potato in the muffler, it doesn't work.
Right.
But it doesn't mean the car is wasted.
But if you are breathing is prevented, the car is wasted, right?
The body is wasted.
You run out of gas.
Everything stops running.
But you could pour some more gas to breathe.
Well, see, a car also has breathing.
It has to be there.
But it needs fuel.
Right.
So the body, when the body dies and there's no metabolism to keep these processes going
and exchanging elimination and nutritive functions, it goes into chemical decay, strictly
chemical decay, because all the ethereal energetic part is gone.
Now, the spirit is just the mind.
So the process is not there, which always kind of made me feel uneasy about the document.
Not getting into that because it's a major personal eschatology, you know, the end of
all things.
But for each person, all the scripture, the Bible ever gets into is that death equals
sleep.
Right.
There's no consciousness.
And then, of course, there's the decay and all that physical decay.
That's all there is.
And there is no consciousness at all.
So these NDEs where people see things, you know, whatever, take your pick and they come
back.
They didn't really die.
How do I know they didn't die?
Because they came back to tell the story.
So the scripture is very, the Bible is very strict about that, that when you're dead,
you're dead.
Right.
And then you have to wait for something called the resurrection in most aspects.
So so there's not much.
Now, if you look at, for example, other cultures where the Bardo, let's say, in the Tibetan
culture, it was before Buddhism, it was called Bo, I think.
What they do is they they sit around.
Well, they have several processes and they have someone, if you can afford it, speak
to the body for quite a few days to make sure that the person continues on their path once
they left.
Right.
OK.
Because it seems they talk about that even though you've left your body, you still can
see everything that's going on.
And you're wondering why you're, you know, you know, ceiling height or bird's eye view
of yourself and other people.
And you'll have someone there in the room, let's say a monk reading the Bardo or whatever
for days and days to tell you, you know, you're dead now.
So keep going.
Right.
Or there's several paths that they discuss and write a more a more modern presentation
of that is, you know, the people that see themselves laying on the end, you know, whatever
this goes in line with the modern NDE.
So the Bardo, what is what it's doing is it's pretty much taking into account that it's
possible for the person to, you know, jump back in their body and be revived.
All right.
So what they're doing is like, well, if you left, there's you know, it's like, you know,
it's one strike, you're out if you, you know, so they keep talking your way.
So these people have come back with NDEs, saw myself over the operating table or whatever.
Then I came back and I woke up.
Well, in this case, there'll be someone talking at you that you left to buy and you're dead.
Now, continue on.
Go to this place.
Go to that.
You know what you see, what colors you see, what level of light you see, and it would
be directed away from the body not to come back.
Interesting.
So and these things have kind of been.
I don't know if you would call stories of NDE people coming at confirmation because
there's a little bit of a mindfuck going on with those, because if you're a staunch Christian,
you see Jesus, right?
If you're a staunch Muslim, you see Mohammed, right?
Or if you're in from the Hindu culture, you'll see, right, another character.
Well, and a lot of people thought it was like, wait a second, wait a second.
So it's culturally based.
Now, something's got something more to this.
Definitely because some people don't describe any other character there.
They talk about, you know, a tunnel and then maybe aliens.
They'll see voices.
They'll see disembodied figures.
Or they think they're ancestors.
The most popular one is they see whatever religious figure is prominent in the culture
that it came from.
So to me, that doesn't seem.
Or they're ancestors, which is another thing, because a lot of cultures teach you that your
ancestors are still watching over you.
Yeah.
It could be anything, actually.
Sometimes it gets quite bizarre.
So there's no uniformity to this.
So the answer to that is no, there is nothing much about that.
Which actually makes, let's just say it this way, what they call, what's called the Bible,
even Preservation, highly suspect of being the be-all end-all of knowledge, because it
doesn't give anything about death.
It's very self-directed towards this world.
So to me, that's like, I'd want to give some more information on that.
So that's what made, that's one of the things, it's a good question, because it made me very
suspect about the preeminent nature of the Bible.
Because if it was a preeminent text and such, it would include more on that.
So that's actually a good question, because it did, it's like, ah, you know, people ask
me that, it's like, yeah, that's like a weak spot in the Bible, a major weak spot.
You know, when I say a major weak spot, because death is a major issue.
No, it's universal, right?
I mean, the one thing that we're pretty much guaranteed the moment that we're born onto
this world, right?
And we become, you know, part of the...
Yeah, at this point, at this point that we, in the cycle that we are, yeah.
I think that at one point, yeah, another point won't be a consideration.
Well, maybe not.
But at this point, you can't really direct me to anybody who has, you know, not succumbed
to death, right?
At some point or other.
Or will.
Or will, yeah.
Everyone either does or will.
Yeah.
But for me, the big point is that we're not getting information from the Bible, which kinds
of brings it down in priority quite a bit in that subject.
And you know, if you have, there are other things in there as well that make it seem
like, eh, if this is like such a high level, let's say communique or memo, why does it
not have this stuff in it that seems to be preemptively important to anyone personally
or socially or whatever?
So yeah, it's a little kink and chink in the armor.
And I've always viewed it as such, but that's okay.
This is where we are.
Like Woody Allen said, if death was so bad, how come no one's come back to complain, right?
So, yeah, so all right, what it was, I looked in the chat, there's some talk, some people
coming back and forth, something recently put up by Archaics about the second seal and
things going on in the US and with the eclipse and all that.
And one of the questions was on one of the Freeman, I think 2020 podcasts I did with
him, I brought up the vaccine is that the vaccine is all based on astrological, they're getting
away from some astrological alignment to put it out, which is pretty much what the
Archaics Breshears has been talking about recently.
So I think I brought that to light four years ago with Freeman, and there's not much more
I can expand on that, which astronomical alignment or astrological feature they're looking for,
I'm not so sure, but I'll tell you what.
Even these elite, let's say you want to call them whatever, Illuminati's, whatever, they're
not that smart.
In other words, if you have heard of them, seen their name or their face or know about
them even historically, they're just a front man.
They're always been the powers and never revealed themselves ever, ever at all.
No one has.
Now, that doesn't mean they're not on the surface.
They work as the janitor, right?
Like the real, like, okay, give you an example.
The Bilderbergers, right?
They have these meetings and Alex Jones is out there with his megaphone, let's just say,
you know, harking back, you know, a decade or so.
And they get these paparazzi shots of the limos coming in with Rockefeller and the Secretary
of State Kissinger, right?
You see that all the time, right?
There was a who, yeah, you know, well, you know who the real important guys are?
They put on the chauffeur outfit and the hat, they're the limo drivers.
That's how they get it.
Because they don't want to be have their picture taken when they're sitting in the back of
someone prominent being chauffeured.
They actually dress up as the chauffeur.
They actually dress up as the janitor.
Right.
Or the waiting staff, you know, or the waiting staff, you know, yeah, or a prostitute or
whatever, you know, 15, the service industry people, right?
15 is service industry, by the way.
15 buses wearing the same jacket, nobody's going to pay attention to a single one of
them.
You know what I mean?
Well, it's no, you just dress up like either a homeless person, security guard, service.
Take your pick on service.
It could be food, sex, driving.
It could be all kinds.
So that's how you get in and out of these places and never be focused on.
Never have your picture ever looked at or examined.
But I'll tell you this, if you took this, what I just said, I assure you, as a let's
just say as a baseline research project, and he started looking at all these places where
these quote unquote elitists go.
And he just focused on who was the security or who was the chauffeur, the driver.
You'll see it's the same driver, different people in the back for different events all
over the world.
You're like, wait a second.
How?
Why is this guy the driver here in Belgium?
He's also the driver in Australia.
He's also the driver in Dubai.
Wait a second.
Who is this guy?
No one's looking at all.
The same DoorDash guy brings pizza to him in Germany and also in Canada.
You know, well, they're going to show up at the event somehow.
Also, they have secret.
A lot of these places I've stayed at the main Bilderberg Hotel here in Washington, D.C.,
in the US.
And you go and they have elevators, like three or four stories.
They have you go in that elevator and you know that's not an elevator for three or four
stories. You look, they have a presidential suite.
I went up to the you could see they could tell that elevator goes down and down and
down and down.
Right. It's not.
Yeah. I don't know how to kind of explain it.
There are elevators and then there are elevators, you know, when you go to the basement
floor, you the basement, you put in a code and it opens another control panel and you
can go to another lobby or in the old days you might switch elevators to another
elevator. Right. Yeah. Or you might see, you know, in the old days, you know, OK, it's
five stories. So you see six buttons because one is for the basement and then you see a
bunch of key holes, right?
A bunch of places. Well, you hear from I'm very familiar with elevator engineering.
Let me put it this way. And also, I've been in elevators thousands of times because I
was a bicycle messenger in the early 80s in New York City, which means you're going to
be going through at least 20, 30, 50, 40, 100 elevator rides a day.
Right. I noticed elevator construction and the fewer stories, the
less robust the elevator, the more stories, the more robust the elevator was and more
technologically advanced.
So you go into that Marriott in Washington, D.C.
So it's right by the George Bush CIA headquarters, by the way.
It's about three blocks away. Right.
You get in that elevator, it's only four stories to go up the presidential suite and you are in an
elevator, the type of elevator that would be in a 50 story building.
Elevator, elevator cab style.
You're like, wait a second.
This is like this is this is not an elevator for a three or four story building.
So if you once you get a sense of this engineering involved, you can you can tell.
Right. Some hospitals are like that as well.
We'll go into some small building and you get into an elevator.
That's you know, these you've seen these elevators only in skyscrapers before.
Why would they put this elevator in a three story building?
Well, because it has to go a lot of floors down also.
Very interesting. I always it's always been in the back of my mind.
I don't know how to bring up any real salient points to really show this, but I assure you
that's what's going on in some capacity.
But in terms of we've diverted from the that was a long
tangent from elevators to whatever.
By the way, stay on the elevator thing.
It's I've been listening to stuff in the background here.
Rory Sutherland, he's my age.
Actually, I'm three months older than him.
Big guy at Ogilvy Mather.
If you've anybody's watched Mad Men.
OK, it was an advertising developed.
It was a series AMC developed to the point where it's an advertising agency merged
with in New York with one from England, an old fashioned one from England.
That's Ogilvy and Mather.
And when I was a bicycle messenger, I did deliver to Ogilvy Mather as well.
I remember those advertising accounts were very kept this very busy.
He wrote a book called Alchemy and there's some it's it's kind of a neat little thing.
I don't think I'd ever want to read it, though.
But the in marketing, it's not about objectivity.
It's about perception.
So for giving an example with Uber, well, it gives good stick with the elevators.
So there's an apartment, medium sized apartment building in New York City.
And everyone's been complaining on how slow the elevator is, meaning not just to arrive,
but once you're riding the elevator and it was not cost feasible to upgrade the elevator.
So what they did was they installed mirrors floor to ceiling all around the inside of the
elevator cab. And then they did a survey.
Does do you still think, you know, the residents, do you still feel that the elevator is too
slow? And everyone said no.
And the reason being, they didn't explain this.
They suppose the reason being is now because there are full body mirrors in the elevator.
People are actually looking at themselves, their hair, their clothing during the elevator
ride. And they're not so focused on the time anymore.
So nothing objective change, but the perception changed.
That's what made Uber so popular, because when you called a cab.
Whether they said it, they were two minutes away or 40 minutes away, no matter what they
told you, the wait was, you're always wondering, are they going to be late?
Are they going to miss me? Right.
But with Uber, they have an app where they show you where the cab is at all times.
So if you say, well, the cab is supposed to be here at five minutes.
Let's see where he is on the map.
Suppose that you could read a map.
It's amazing how as I'm getting older, I'm realizing how few people can actually read
maps, by the way, which is shameful.
But anyway, one of his points that he made was, you know, he said he'd be here in 15
minutes. But look, let's see where he is.
He's obviously stuck in traffic.
Let's go have another beer.
Right. So it's the same.
The waiting time hasn't changed.
Let's say they told you to be there in 15 minutes and they arrive in 15 minutes.
That's 15 minutes. It could be hell on who's waiting.
It's like, what if, what if, what if?
But if you know where they are at all times, you can manage your time better.
So objectively, the waiting time hasn't changed at all.
But your perception of it has.
Right. So this goes back to who's driving the elites.
Right. The perception that the that the elites are the ones sitting in the limousine, not
the driver being the one that you know about.
Right. Right. So it goes on and on and on.
So I really like that little bit.
It's been coming up, I play, you know, play stuff in the background while I'm building
things and I'll usually put a YouTube on and a long one.
And it also lets me know how, you know, time goes, you know, for videos, two hours
long and the video is over.
I said, wow, I spent two hours on that.
So I use it as a clock.
But Rory Sutherland has come up lately and he's just make some points that it's are
what were well worth considering.
It's not objective change or objective realities, perceived reality.
And you change the percept things are perceived.
See, another one he gives is like with branding, like you can go anywhere in the world
to a food spot, like let's say a street food vendor in Bangkok, Thailand, or a three
star Michelin restaurant or a five star American restaurant and ask for a Coke.
And if they don't have one, they it's something wrong.
But if you ask for a Dr.
Pepper, something wrong with you.
Right. You see, so it's all about perception and branding.
So what people are used to hearing the Bible is something like that.
All you have to do is tell someone it's from the Bible and they'll agree with it.
You know why? Because they don't know what's in the Bible.
Nobody does because nobody reads it.
Well, it sounds kind of right.
In other words, as long as it sounds like it would be in there.
Right. And the perception, the perception, which, again, like you said, the waiting
time didn't change, just like in the old days when they used to promise you, you know,
your pizza in 30 minutes, which, by the way, they do that with food now, too.
You can watch where your pizza is.
Right. Well, yeah, it's it's yeah, it's not the actual.
Yeah, it's not the object of waiting time.
It's how you perceive the waiting time.
Right. Right.
So if you know where the if they told you they're 30 minutes away and it looks like
they just left, you're not going to be so upset.
You might less upset when they show up in 50 minutes because you know where they are
the whole time. Yeah. You know, the guy's still over at the whatever pizza joint.
And it's like, OK, I know that that's 15 minutes away.
So I know that he's at least 15 minutes away.
He hasn't left there yet. So they didn't prepare the food for him yet.
He's waiting. Yeah. So he's going to be in other words, they're not going to arrive at
the time that they told me to expect.
They will. But I'm less upset now.
And the person doesn't think because I know what's going on, what's going on.
Right. OK. Right. So this is the perceived aspect.
And this is what's being used against people.
Look what the VAX thing recently, because that also came up with the archaics video.
I haven't gone after you did a part two today.
I have to go back and look at both of them before I can comment.
Right. Wouldn't be sure to comment on it without listening to them.
With the VAX thing, it was all about trust the science is to show me the science that
what's wrong with you. Right.
So you see, they don't have to.
They just tell you to trust the science, even though there is no science behind it at
all, ever.
But because they use the word science and they state that it is scientifically
back, then people will just.
Well, because it's venerated and science is more venerated than religion.
That's why it's at the level of a religion.
Well, and it's more venerated than your best guess.
And it's more venerated than.
So that's the thing, though.
No, this is scientifically proven.
And if you don't if you don't go for just the comment means you're a Luddite or
something, you know, you're a cave or, you know, you're a caveman.
Or a troglodyte like you're a caveman or you're not worth talking to you anyway.
Well, I've got exactly that problem.
Literally, I lost the whole thing.
I was supposed to get some funding and stuff for radio and all this.
And literally it stumbled over.
Wait a minute. You don't do vaccinations.
I'm like, no, I don't. This is before the big vacs, you know, the most recent big
vacs. And I said, no, I actually don't.
You know, this is one of those things.
And this is a person who's about freedom, supposedly, who's about all these things.
And well, they were using these phrases even before it became popularized.
Don't let me give you this point.
This is where this is where it works.
They have been convinced of a science and be the vaccine.
Anything that disturbs that A and B position is disturbing.
Right. Right. So instead of just disagreeing, this is what you do in honor,
honorable trials and things like that.
You don't disagree directly.
You just conditionally accept that with these conditions being met.
So when people I've seen this where I think I've gone over the story several times,
I wouldn't say I'm anti-vaccine, but I would say if they're considering my body
weight, gender and blood type, I'll consider the vaccine.
And then that opens up a whole thing.
Now, it's not yes or no or you versus pro versus con.
Now it's like, oh, wait a second, because when you bring up blood type, body weight
and gender, that sounds something
that could be part of a scientific study and experiment.
That's those are things that are considered, especially in the medical field.
Right. Especially blood type.
Right. You've watched enough mash.
Yeah. Like we can't give him a trick.
We can't. He might die because why?
We don't have his what blood type. Right.
Oh, wow. People have seen that on TV even.
So now when they instead of saying, no, I'm not anti that I'm not.
I'm anti-vax or no, I'm not.
You know, Novak's say, well, are they considering your body weight?
Blood type and gender.
Wait a second.
What you're saying is too reasonable to just say you're a nut job now.
Well, and body weight is a reasonable assumption
because any kind of medication of any sort, right?
Anything you have to consider.
But anything injected that has particulars, it's not just saline.
Should have blood type as well.
Well, OK, but because there are blood cells in there are cell.
There is mitochondrial stuff in there.
So they're not mesh. Right.
So but the whole thing is there is the premise of the vaccine.
Any theory that's based on a falsehood, anything that comes from that theory
must be false. Right.
OK, so the theory that there's an immune system is false.
There is no everything that they describe the immune system is doing is not immune.
It's an eliminative system.
So there's no such thing.
So what's it when they talk about the immune system,
what they're really should be saying is that it's the elimination system.
But they don't because that sounds boring and untechnical and very unscientific.
And if you say immune system, right.
Oh, that's too complicated for a commoner.
Instead, we should do what they say.
Well, elimination.
People generally think of, you know, urination.
And, you know, right. It's too. Yeah, it's too dirty.
In other words, yeah, it's it's kind of like the thing about toilet paper.
You know, you want toilet paper to be dry.
Not the moist kind.
Why would you want moist toilet paper?
Because you're using toilet paper to anyway.
You see, it's the same.
This is perception again.
It's all perception.
We've seen nurses.
I don't know which shop it was back when the vaccines were being done.
This is before this bout of vaccines.
This is when they were doing them under Obama.
Probably some nurses were lined up.
And someone I was with was saying, no, these vaccines are bad.
And all the nurses and everyone was were laughing at him like,
well, we got a real loose nut here.
And I said, well, are you considering body weight?
But and then they heard that they packed up, they packed up and left.
Well, you're mentioning body weight first.
And that's why I wanted to focus on that, because even, you know, a fool,
you might not necessarily understand blood type or there's an issue with that.
And that's kind of complex.
So what I'm saying is, you don't have to know you do,
but you do understand there is something I do.
I do. But I'm saying if you're having this conversation, it's a little different.
Look, like I said, when it comes to any sort of medication,
somebody would realize that.
Let's just say you wanted to apply an aspirin.
But a vaccine is not medication.
OK, but it is not under the medication category.
OK, then what is it?
It's under inoculation. Inoculation.
OK, but. Yeah, yeah.
It's vaccine actually means VACA, which means it was done for animals and cows,
again, which was a business with people.
Yes, sir. This is it came.
The vaccines came before the Industrial Revolution or at the beginning,
at the at the beginning of it, where the tail end of the agricultural
so they were maximizing, you know, to get after the agriculturists,
you know, the medical. Yeah.
OK, but introducing any chemical into the body in any way whatsoever.
In proportion, in proportion, a weight must be considered.
And that's why, you know, the ones for animals are frauds
because they'll give the same CC or volume vaccine to a grown
Great Dane as they will to a puppy Chihuahua.
Well, but that's the madness of it, right, is that, look, if you're telling me
that a puppy gets the same, you know, the same injection that the that the full
grown, full grown, they do that's what the vets do.
And by the way, if you want to learn about hoaxers,
they're hoaxers to the vets.
But I'm talking from the medical point of view.
What was the last time someone took any animal to the vet
and they checked it for blood pressure, you know, hypertension?
Never. It's something that they only pull out the wool or diabetes.
Now they're doing diabetes for animals, too.
Yes, because that hoax worked.
It worked really well for there's no such thing.
Anyway, you know, I've been studying the medical stuff,
not from what's on TV or in college, but in their own manuals
that they put out since the 1980s.
And I it's just like the I am so like livid on how little even doctors know.
And they're like, oh, my gosh, you know.
No, the point of the point I was going to try to get to, though,
I thought was relevant because it's it's the easiest, most observable and accessible.
But it's not it's it's not as long as you don't do body.
And but you don't think the perception about body weight is is a very.
No, it's not. No, it has to be.
It has to be that the vaccine is not a medication.
It's an inoculation, which is something completely different.
Just like if you go for a treatment for.
OK, but forget about calling it a medication.
Then what I'm saying is introducing a chemical into the body in any way, shape
or form. No, no.
But you don't want to class about weight because that's too it's too OK.
You want to do a three strikes.
You're out with these people because if you just body weighs
generally, most people have the same weight and they do have a children's dose.
Right. Which they do. But they don't get.
So the thing is to hit them off with enough stuff
that sounds the perception is that, you know, more, you know,
how come that was left out?
Because the three are very important together.
One. Right.
Each one is not important.
Not that it can easily be, but if you hit all three,
it creates the perception that you're looking at a holistic,
the whole well-being of the person, not just one attribute. Right.
I just everyone's been trained to just look at one attribute.
It's a fast car. I got it.
It doesn't have brakes. Right. I just thought it was. I got you.
I just thought it was more accessible if you're looking at body weight,
because like, you know, if I'm sitting here with a guy who's five foot nine
and weighs one hundred and forty pounds. Right.
And I'm you know, I'm six foot and I weigh two hundred and thirty pounds.
You know what? Him and I have a shot of whiskey apiece.
He's got that more than me. You know what I mean?
That's different. I think I've gone over the anesthesia.
If if a 300 pound black man and a 90 pound white woman with red hair
and freckles go, both go for the same appendicitis.
Yeah, the white women out of anesthesia that the little 90 pound white girl
is required to take to put out would kill the 300 pound black man.
So the weight doesn't add up there.
But you have to consider race, gender.
And I didn't get into the race part, but it's race, gender, body weight
and blood type. You didn't mention race. No, you didn't.
But once you hit them with because race is too hard of an issue.
Remember, this is all perception.
If you hit them with those three things and say, wait a second,
how did you come up with these three things? That makes too much sense.
I know those things are important. Wait a second.
As this has nothing to do with discussing the efficacy of vaccines
because the whole premise is false.
No, absolutely. All right.
Yeah. I see Tuesday. Yep. There we are. Ciao. Ciao.