Ah, Rated Y, Sonic Advent 2-3-3,
anyway, what it be, Greek, how are you?
Hey, that was quiet, I usually hear the
bumper or whatever they call it, I'm doing
alright.
Let's go for it.
You gave me a link by the way,
Alive Water in Canada, those guys have been
around for a long time, I remember seeing
them even before the Spring 2.0 days,
and vortexing water in a copper pipe doesn't
really do that much.
It does, it's better than not, otherwise I
would have gone that route, I've tried it.
It's marginally small improvement, yeah, but yeah, there's
a lot of stuff, I'm even with potential
clients now, they ask me, so what's the
best water structuring or water whatever device?
I'm like, the best?
I don't know, but this is what I
can do, and this is, you know, and
no exaggeration, and if you feel like, you
know, you really want to know, you have
to try it.
It's like, you know, you ever ask someone
what they thought of that movie, you know,
and then you go see the movie yourself,
and it's like, it wasn't like that at
all, right?
So, I tell people, go buy them all,
buy everything, just do it all, I mean,
but yeah, we have no competition.
What I want us to throw out is,
you guys, I put enough, you go to
waterhelix.com and see what the scalerator looks
like, you know, it doesn't, you don't need
a, if you go shopping, you don't need
a $30,000 Hermes bag to put your
groceries in, as a matter of fact, they
give you cheap ones for free, and now
you got to pay 11 cents or whatever
for some places, and bring your own bag,
so the way you bring your own scalerator
is just go to thewaterhelix.com, and of
course, you're not going to be able to
bend pipe like that, I know it sounds
sarcastic, but no, you're not, you can try.
Well, you didn't say lay in pipe, you
said bending pipe, so, you know, I guess,
maybe it's the same thing?
Yeah, well, here's the thing, they're not going
to be able to make the device, but
what you can do is imitate everything that's
going on, you just use a bunch of
45s, you just go to the hardware store,
and you spend, you're going to need at
least 8 to 10 45s, maybe 12, and
for one inch, they're going to cost you
like 10 bucks each, and figure another, so
200 bucks with the magnet, and you could
just start bending them around on a Sunday,
get a heat gun in case you got
to move things a little bit, because when
you're working with plastic, it's going to be
able to warm it up, and you could
actually mimic that, you can even mimic it
with just putting the 45s at 10 o
'clock, 1 o'clock, 8 o'clock, and
4 o'clock, and using T's on the
end with two magnets, I mean, there's so
many ways to mimic the scalarator geometrically, pretty
close, it won't be on, you'll get 90
% if you lay everything flat and centered,
and try it, so yeah, you just got
a bunch of squirrel noise back there, you
wire or something?
Yeah, yeah, I just moved something, because it
seemed to be wrong, so I just moved
it, sorry about that, didn't mean to make
noise.
Oh, that's fine, that's fine, but people ask
me all the time, like, what should I
read, right?
What do I say?
Read everything, try everything, you got to read
the shitty books too, because you got to
know what a shitty book is, if you
only read the good books, you wouldn't know
what a bad book was, right, so what
is it, I can't read everything, yes you
can, just read what comes across you, whatever
the echo puts in front of you, right,
ECCO, Earth Coincidence Control Office, it's God's field
office, right, you want to be simple, they
control the long term, you control the short
term, when they say, when you figure out
how they do the long term, then you
never have to come back here anymore, so,
but you can play with these guys, in
other words, it's, what's that movie, guys used
to wear fedora hats and they controlled this
guy playing the senator, running for the senator,
Matt Damon, the Adjustment Bureau, the Adjustment Bureau
was totally on the ECCO, not as overt,
because it wouldn't, if you really, I guess,
you can't interact with the ECCO, maybe they
do, I don't know, whatever.
Well most people did in that movie either,
right, it was just because that was what
was special about the main character, is that
he knew what was going on, he tried
to fight it.
Yeah, and they went interviewing him, remember they
had another case back when, and yeah, but
you got to do everything, but you got
to do it in the way that it's
put in front of you, remember it's the
journey, not getting there, right, I never understood.
Some people do search for stuff though, like
we do have somebody asking again about, you
know, do you have a suggested, because I
can't find the literature, I can't find a
book, this person says, so you know, but
go ahead, yeah, go ahead.
Well everything works on, the entire ethereal, anything
alive, anything in weather, anything that was so
-called ether, right, the primary force, it's not
even a force, it's a substrate, is all
by induction, there's no material exchange other than
what we see directly called material exchange, but
most of the things that we think are
material exchanges, they even got everyone, well not
everyone, but yeah, I'd say statistically everyone, 90
% of the people convinced that they're actually
electrons moving down a wire, most idiotic thing,
you know, I've told you about my experiment
with cutting the wire with a dustpan and
a microscope and I cut the live wire
waiting for the electrons to fall on the
floor so I could scoop them up and
look under a microscope, yeah, that sounds ridiculous,
right, but that's how ridiculous they are and
they got these websites like Veritasium and some
other moron with physics, whatever, like 10 million
subscribers, millions, I mean it's like just hopeless,
that's why I'm like, you know, you got
more than a few thousand people listening to
you, you're tickling them, because people are idiots,
this is just the way that it is,
sorry, I mean I might be the only
one speaking, using these words, not strictly in
medical terms, but when I say idiot, I
mean in the medical, it's a medical term,
they don't like to use it anymore, and
look, I was having a discussion, someone says
a businessman, I said really, what do you
do when you get a bill of exchange
or like a bill, oh, I write a
check and pay it, I said you're not
much of a businessman, are you, you mean
pay for it twice, you ever go to
Starbucks, you know how they order, you order
the coffee, they put your name on the
cup, you pay for it then, and what
would you do if your coffee's ready, you
gotta pay for it again, and then you
gotta pay for it again when you walk
out the door, and plus they send you
a bill at home, would you do that,
no, pay for it four times, no, and
why are you doing the electric company and
the gas company and the car, no, and
the house, it's paid for three, four times
over, and I never heard of that, maybe
I should look into it, I said yeah,
you've been on this planet for more than
a month, you know, anyone that, well, anyone
that's known me since 2002, I'm saying, you
know, you sign your name on a piece
of paper, I get fully monetized, remember, I
used to be on Revolution Radio, and I
said, you know, when you guys fill out
applications and all that, you know, that's the
full monetization plus everything, and I've been telling
people this for 20 years, and it wasn't
until recently Brandon Joe Williams, you know, made
Fun and Simple and Discovering Mansa, and through
Brandon Joe and a couple of us said,
oh, look at these young guys, finally, because
when I got into it, it was, oh,
you stand up, my left leg again, I
gotta take a hot bath after this, Herb
Crawford and Roger Elvick, Rice McLeod, these people
were doing since the 80s and 90s, they
were buying in the Midwest with a draft,
just, you know, it looks like a check,
it's just a draft, you know, you just
go buy something that looks like a check,
they were buying tire companies and stuff in
the Midwest and all these big things, and
the FBI would come back and say, oh,
that's a fraudulent instrument, oh, it's all right,
you say it's fraudulent, give it back to
me, and they get a copy, and it
says received by the bank, so just writing
a few things on a piece of paper,
the bank uses it, man, there's no such
thing as a bad check unless you agree
to it, if you, you go into shops
and it says bad check, attorney general's message,
attorney general, whatever, says bad check writers will
be prosecuted, yeah, they're gonna also prosecute you
for stealing rocks from the moon, you'll probably,
they'll probably be able to get more evidence
on you for stealing rocks from the moon,
evidentiary, let's say stuff, case, than writing a
bad check, you cannot, it's impossible to write
a bad check, now, you don't know what's
going on and they tell you their funds
weren't there to cover it, and you agree
to it, you wouldn't know better, by the
way, if you write a check for someone
and you come back later on and you
see, let's say, $100 check, right, and they
took $100 out of your checking account, that's
100% banking fees you paid, there's no
reason for that, the person who you sent
the check to when they endorsed the back
of it, that bank that he did that
with produced $100 from that signature, the two
signatures, they see if there's signature front and
back, and then they told the other person's
bank, hey, we did that thing, you better
take $100 out of it because we're keeping
this show, this game going, and when they
do that, when you pay 100% banking
fees, anyone who's ever written a check or
done a debit thing, that's 100% banking
fees, so I was proposing with a bank,
listen, I'd be happy with 10% banking
fees, and when I explained to them what
they were doing, they thought I was crazy,
because how long have you been working in
a bank, 22 years, never heard of this,
and I showed them, this is how it
works, that's like going to a car mechanic
for 22 years and he doesn't know what
a steering wheel is, right, I said, look,
I write a check to someone for $100,
take $10 out of my account, 10%, if
I write $1,000, take $100, not the
full amount, that's all banking fees, because the
amount is created on the other end, wholly,
and completely, right, so one proposal is when
people figure this out, why are you doing
any kind of checking with 100% banking
fees, everyone needs to just possibly stop for
a few days, write a letter, just call
the bank, why are you charging me, there's
100 million, I don't know, 50 million people,
for three days, just say, hey, bank, I
have a checking account with you, why are
you charging me 100% banking, explain it,
it's a negotiable instrument, if it says pay
or order to pay or promise to pay,
the funds are generated from the instrument itself,
it's just bookkeeping, the other thing I suggest
to people is if you get a bill
and you don't know how to handle it,
right, you don't owe the money, it's all,
you know what it says, it says the
account is due, does it ever say you
owe, occasionally you'll see that, because they're dumbing
it down, because you know, your average, I
was going to say, sometimes you might see
a you owe this amount, yeah, just saying,
go ahead, right, because that's like going to
the coloring book section, I got a four
-year-old, what, you know, I got a
five or I got a seven-year-old,
what should I, what kind of book should
I get them, oh, and by the way,
I'm doing some financial business, it's in the
same category, seven-year-old, right, your average
college professor is operating on six to seven,
what is that, third, fourth grade, your average
college professor, doctor, lawyer, they're third or fourth
grade, they're wordsmiths and all that, but it's
all about accounting, so they don't know what
to do with this, like for example, let's
say you get a bill of exchange and
you don't know how to properly negotiate it
or perform on it, just write up a
bill for the same amount and send it
to whoever sent you the bill and watch
what happens, it's all about accounting, really, because
it's, right, because now your accounting, you see
what I mean, balances their accounting, well, yeah,
right, if you each owe each other, let's
say a hundred dollars, I owe you a
hundred dollars, you owe me a hundred dollars,
there's no reason to change anything, yeah, right,
and the easiest thing to say, so let's
say you get a bill for $1,750
or whatever, this is just from your typical
scumbag utility company or whatever, you just send
them a bill, you acknowledge that you got
their bill for $1,750 and you're sending
them a bill for $1,751 or you
can make it a dollar more, because it
doesn't matter, it has to be more than
a dollar more to matter a difference, right,
to create a debt, right, so $1,751
is still even and you say the reason
for sending you the bill is for, it's
a processing fee for processing the $1,750
bill they sent you, it's called a processing
fee, you've seen that before, of course, it's
all accounting, there's nothing being exchanged here, guys,
the banks are the borrowers, 12 USC, 1431,
very clear there, they're the borrowers and everything's
backwards, right, it's like satan is your god,
right, and everything's backwards, you know, so yeah,
the devil is actually the one that you
think, right, so it's all bad, that's what
these religious things are telling you, the whole
world is backwards, if you read, I think
it's Isaiah 28 somewhere, it tells you they
inverted everything, everything's inverted, but the easiest logic
for sending a bill is telling, please, this
is for accounting purposes only, I'm sending you
a bill for $1,750 as you requested,
after receiving your bill for $1,750 and
the $1,750 is for processing that $1
,750 processing fee, please apply this to your
records and when you do, we'll consider this
to be a zero balance, if you have
any questions, please contact me no later than
seven days, that's it and it's like, holy
crap, man, this is so simple, it's all
accounting, now, of course, it's not going to
go very smoothly, but you've satisfied everything legally,
right, completely according to the banking rules, which
nobody knows, just like, show me a medical
doctor that knows, knows functionally that the heart
is not a pump, it's actually a breaking
mechanism or what cancer really is or here's
a good one, if you know one of
these medical morons, ask him, what's the organ
for the immune system you guys are always
touting, I think that story might be worth
repeating, with the one day, you know, where
everyone was supposed to mask up and I
would, I wouldn't wear a mask and then
they'd say, hold on, hold on, you got
to come in with a message, I don't
have an immune system, so I can't wear
a mask and they'd be like, oh, oh,
you don't, okay, well, hold on, then, then
the manager would come out, okay, where did
you want to buy today, he walked, he
says, wait till this aisle clears, are you
done here, sir, please move out, okay, go
ahead, what did you want to get, and
carried my stuff, brought me to the register,
opened up the register, you know, brought me
to an empty closed register, opened it up,
right, yeah, yeah, chauffeur, I said, man, this
is great, this is like private shopping, yeah,
right, and I could have, yeah, I could
have taken a thousand lie detector tests and
the most sophisticated lie detector test equipment and
I would pass every single one, you know
why, because I know for sure there is
no such thing as an immune system, so
no mask plus concierge service, huh, yeah, and
for people are hearing this for the first
time, ask the medical morons, what's the organ
for the immune system, very good, there isn't
one, thank you, I knew you'd know that
right away, all right, what's the function of
the immune system, what's the function, well, you
see, there are antibodies and nodes, I was
talking, they're taken away and took it out
of the body, oh, so it's removed from
the body, so it's the elimination system, yes,
I have an elimination system, as a matter
of fact, a lot of people ask you,
you know, did you eliminate today, that's a
very polite way to say, did you take
a shit, right, yes, I do have that,
I do take a shit, yes, so, yes,
yeah, even with their strange explanation about these
antibodies, which come out of nowhere, you know,
because induction, they're not immune, it's eliminative, eventually
it gets to, this stuff has to be
eliminated out of the body anyway, even their
long, stupid, crazy explanation, eventually you're eliminating something,
right, it's all about the elimination system, and
I will swear on a stack of Bibles,
like they say that, yes, I do have
an elimination system, I do, and it's fully
functional, right, but I do not have an
immune system, I'll take the most sophisticated lie
detector test, retina scans, whatever, and you will
see that I am telling the truth, and
this is a fucked up, ridiculously stupid place,
this planet, so have fun, have fun while
you're at it, really try to have fun,
speaking of this, but you're not, but here's
the thing, if you're operating like they are,
sorry, if you're operating like they are, you're
not going to have fun, no, so you
got to be smart about it, but anyway,
go ahead, I'm having trouble adapting to doing
the things, I'm getting the concept now, it's
taken me a while on what you just
discussed, I'm getting the concept, but executing is
yet another step, and I'm trying to, I'm
working on it, I tell you I'm working
on it, because that's why we do this,
well, yeah, anyway, depends on what it is,
with a capital T, it could be a
hard one, but we talk about, if you
notice, like sometimes, like I'll have an argument
with someone about something really trivial, like how
to open a jar when it's too tight,
for example, and I show them a method,
and they're like, you know, this has nothing
to do, I'm being aggressive, because it has
nothing to do with opening a jar, it
has to do with the approach, it could
be a jar, it could be something else,
it's what approach do you have, most people
do what they do, I'd say most women
that I've seen through my life, 90%
of them, 90% of what they do,
they learn, guess where, on television, from watching
television, so yeah.
And yeah, the amazing thing about the jar,
again, it's like Sun Tzu was not an
idiot, you know, the whole thing about you
win the war before you ever go into
the battle, it's kind of right there, it's
just metaphoric, anyway, and we could get into
Sun Tzu at some point, but not today.
Greek said the next thing coming is going
to be cleansing, of which you can't compare
to any other times, okay, biblically speaking, this
era began with the Assyrians wiping out all
of the neighboring tribes, so if the circle
continues, well, I'm just reading what it says,
if the circle continues, that's what should happen
at the end, severe wiping out of humanity,
but wouldn't that have happened anyways, with the
earth shift and cataclysms?
Yeah, yeah, I think so, I'm leaning, see,
I'm evidence-based, right, evidence-based, if that,
whatever that means, right, to you, or what
the term means, which is forensics, forensics means
evidence, I think, if you look up that
word, right, so the chronology that Jason Breshears
puts out on archaics, I think, is Trump's,
a lot of the stuff that I've talked
about prophetically, on the minutiae and movements, on
the, most people think I'd never say this,
right, but I'm just, you know, we're here
to learn, on when things will happen, and
even how they're going to happen cosmically, because
the Bible is like Swiss cheese, and I'm
the kind of person that, when I see
Swiss cheese, I'm like, I don't want to
buy it, because unless they could give me
all the stuff to fill in the holes,
right, where's the, if you can get the,
I'll buy the Swiss cheese, if you can
give me the rest of the cheese, fill
in those holes for me, right, then I'll
take it, right, so the biblical text has
been severely messed with, I predominantly go to
it for law, because guess what, right, pretty
much all laws are based on it, like
it or not, know it or not, right,
and like regulation Z, the three-day right
of refusal, by the way, where does that
come from, right, all these things that you'll
find in business, and there's business, and there's
busyness, there's two different things, but I would
say prophetically, I'd say, I think the phoenix
is right on, I think still the, and
the other two things to be seen, and
it looks like the chronology does line up,
I would say that a Middle East union
is still in favor, actually, believe it or
not, I did see something about a week
ago that Egypt is now collectively trying to
create a Middle East NATO to unite nations
as a protective front against Israeli aggression, yes,
isn't that interesting, it is, so let's see
how that, man, I said 2025 would be
the point for that, so I'm more relaxed
about all that stuff, but, and all the
stuff that I've put forward is pretty accurate,
excuse me, pretty accurate based on what's in
the text itself, it's very clear, it only
has to say it once, like Assyria will
rise up in the end, right, it's only,
it's only listed once in the Psalms, and
that's enough, you don't have to, you know,
people, what is the mind-control thing, Chuck,
they keep repeating it, like TV, right, and
all, repeating, repeating, Osama bin Laden, Osama bin
Laden, COVID, COVID, COVID, repetition causes people to
believe that a statement is more true even
without any supporting evidence, there's a theorem to
that, but yes.
Yeah, yeah, there is, but then you have,
so that would be something that is not
true, meaning non-existent, not important, then you
have someone falling off of a cruise ship,
and they're saying, help, I'm drowning, what did
he say, that's too short, can you repeat
that please, right, you know, so you just
got to say some things once, right, so,
and that's what I've been picking up on
it, and have picked up on it, but
yeah, I would say human carnage is definitely
on the front, financial ups and downs on
the front, like you've never seen before, because
remember, there's no more money, guys, it's all
credit, so all they can do is make
stuff hyperinflation, or prevent you from getting credit,
by the way, whenever you're denied for anything,
they've gotten the full amount paid already, so
Henry Ford was right, if the people found
out how the money system worked, he was
talking about applications also, yeah, there would be
a revolution, I don't think there should be
a revolution, because the people are too dumb
to even go read the constitution, which supports
everything, you don't need anything more, you know,
it's like someone walking around with a Swiss
army knife in their pocket, or one of
the deluxe models, and like they say, do
you have a knife, do you have a
toothpick, do you have a scissor, do you
have a file, you got it all in
there, have you ever looked?
Well, that's what I find most frustrating about
all this, is that it does seem as
though we're going to come to a point
where, yeah, war is inevitable, and sure, civil
war is coming, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
we're hearing that a lot lately, but here's
the thing, not over anything that actually counts,
it's going to be all over BS, and
that's what the problem is.
Well, it's a sport, nobody really wants to
go to war, nobody ever, ever wanted to
go to war, it's a sport, how many
people get excited about what are the NBA
playoffs, and the stupid bowl, and the World
Series, that's how you get people excited about
war.
It's people who chose to go on the
field of battle, who chose to have an
opponent, who selected one, and then put on
a uniform voluntarily, this is literally what's happening,
and, and, yeah, so this is not a
metaphor, no, of course not, that's why sports,
that's, that's why there was always sports, and
that's why, remember, whenever there was guerrilla warfare
through history, it was frowned upon, because all
the soldiers, the infantry had to line up,
you know, a certain way on both sides,
and then start the fight, right, so like
the Parthians, and you know, the American, the
Revolutionary War was all taking pop shots, guerrilla
warfare, right, hiding, and yeah, they weren't used
to that, there was no training for that,
so that's bad sportsmanship, that's like, imagine the
Super Bowls going on, and somebody, let's say,
with a couple of drones, drops 50 footballs
on the field while the Super Bowl's going
on, right, and play, all of a sudden,
all these footballs fall everywhere, and they're like,
whoa, whoa, which one, what, right, so that's
guerrilla warfare, just mess them up like that.
Anyway, yeah, not much of an answer for
that one, but I'm glad, glad for the
comments, always glad to hear that people are
thinking about stuff.
What else you got?
They are, well, this one almost sounds redundant
with what you just said, but let's try
it anyway.
Also, if there's a new financial system coming
out, and if this is the seventh cycle,
do you think new lawful money is being
introduced to replace the old?
Okay, that's what I thought you would say,
but no, it's not a new financial system
at all, it's still going to be based
on the Federal Reserve Act, and if you
read the 16th Amendment, by the way, it
prefaces that it's not introducing anything new, so
that's why there's people that don't study, cry
about the 16th Amendment, and you know, with
the IRS and the Federal Reserve and all
that, but if you read it, it basically
says this doesn't bring anything new, in other
words, whatever's in this amendment's already been going
on, it's like an acknowledgement, so it's a
moot point, no, it's all credit, and the
main thing is that you never find out
that it's all based on securities, just forget
about credit, forget about money, forget about currency,
look up securities, what are securities?
It'll tell you it's checks, drafts, promissory notes,
orders to pay, bills, coupons, blah, blah, blah,
anything that you could possibly, stamps are securities,
everything that you call money, currency, or whatever,
anything that has a bill notation on it,
anything that says pay, or a number with
a cent, was it a cent stamp, or
a dollar sign on it, is a security,
it's all about securities, and the main thing
is that you never find out how they
work, that's what the new system is, it's
just another distraction, there's no such thing as
a new system.
So that tackles, just to let everybody know,
that tackles all your CBDC questions, that tackles
the other new system questions, I'm just clearing
them out of the way here, because you
already answered it.
You can do an injunction on all that
stuff, learn what injunctions are, you know, I
was going to look up, let's, you know,
since I have the laptop, go ahead and,
let's see how well I can multitask, how
well I can answer the next one, or
discuss the next one, while I'm looking up
driver's license injunction.
There's a guy who did the first one
that hit the media, right?
Right.
Let's see, so go, yeah.
Yeah, no, absolutely, I'll move on, but I'm
just clearing away first all of this stuff
that needs to be cleared away, because it
was already just answered.
There is a weird short question here, Greek
in the spirit of the best food, clothing,
and shelter, yes, okay, I got that right.
Is renting a place to call home lawful?
I feel like having my name on a
deed won't necessarily make life better, but open
to hearing info on this, like, what are
your thoughts of renting versus owning?
I like, well, right now I'm in an
owning situation, but renting, it could go either
way, depending, see, if you rent and something
breaks, you're not compelled to fix it.
You're not compelled to fix it if you
own either, but you have to suffer the
costs, let's say, right, and time and all
that.
I know stuff, people that rent and something
breaks, and they never get it fixed, right?
You've heard, you know, slumlords or whatever, they
never get to it or whatever.
I'm renting, and I'm having mixed results with
that myself, personally, because some things have been
fixed right away, and other things, eh, not
so, you know, maybe not, depends.
Anyway, it's a mixed bag situation for me,
but the lawful, I think what they're looking
for is, they're personally, are they lawfully okay,
like, is that acceptable to be a renter,
is the idea, I guess, yeah.
Depends if you're competent, yeah, of course, I
think it's lawful.
I think the Rechabites in Jeremiah, they never
lived in houses and never drank wine.
They lived in tents, food, clothing, shelter.
Yeah, well, the thing about having a deed,
you can develop equity as long as you
buy low, sell high.
Remember, if you go apply for, go apply
for a house, expect to be denied, and
then say, that's fine if you deny me
because you don't like my shoe size or
whatever, my breath stinks or whatever.
Just that application, which has the full price
of the house plus all the interest and
everything, just apply that towards the account, because
when you apply for a house, you're actually
opening an account with that company.
It's an account number on it, right?
Just say you want to maintain the account,
and you already have a collateral in there,
and just start building up your case.
And yeah, or you can find a banker,
like the kind that have a little office
hole in the wall, a couple of guys
started a bank, right, and it's possible to
find that and say, listen, I'm going to
come and apply, and I expect to be
rejected, denied, and then I'm going to come
back and apply again in a month, but
this time, I want 76% of that
application to go towards the account, right, because
you do a 24-76 split, and then
I'm going to sign a purchase order agreement,
and I want 76% of that to
go towards the account.
You guys keep 24%, and then I'll sign
a promissory note.
So now you've just created four times the
value of the house, and you're getting 76
% of each one, so four times 76
% is way over 100, so you're good.
Any extra money to tell them, yeah, I
want to invest it in your company, and
let's settle the account and transfer all the
necessary titles and deeds.
See what they say.
Try it.
You don't have to go.
Everyone online is fighting everyone.
You got to sue them.
Well, just go and find a banker.
Hey, look, you know, you don't, you know,
it's just, you want to play?
This is, you're the borrower.
The banker is the borrower.
12 USC, 1431.
Not you.
And the same amount at 76% by
four means that you've got 304%, right, of
the original price if you consistently negotiated for
76% of it each time, right?
And they got 96%.
Yeah.
There you go.
Okay.
Because remember, you're going to do a split
on each one.
So yeah, yeah, I can, now I just
gave you the short, the short form, the
outline on how to work with banks properly.
Now that's funny.
I will say, I did, I went, I
did this, like I said, that's what you're
saying is illegal.
Greek, a banker told me, right?
So I'm like, would you be able to
put that writing that it's illegal?
I'll be glad to consider it.
If you put it in writing, show me
how it's illegal when you're the borrower.
I've never heard of you're the borrower.
I don't care about the law.
He caught himself, caught himself.
You know what it's like to imagine?
Could you imagine you have a guy in
a suit with a, that's a banker and
you have the, the nightly news there.
And he says, I don't care about the
law.
Do you, how good would that be for
his business?
Not so good.
Yeah.
On the topic of cheese, so you didn't
bring up cheese earlier.
On the topic of cheese, I have heard
that the majority of rent it used today
as GMO from Pfizer.
Is that true?
Does the Greek have a recommendation?
Sorry.
Yeah.
Rent list would be the best cheese, but
the rent is just a cow.
It's, it's not really proper cheese.
It's forced cheese.
And they've done that for a long time.
Rent list cheese, or, you know, cheese with
a natural, a non rent culture.
It's taken from the cow's stomach.
I don't think that's really a good cultured
cheese, but yeah.
Good.
Continue with that.
Yeah.
So is that true about Pfizer?
They ask, I'm not certain about that myself,
but it wouldn't surprise me.
Yeah.
The thing about GMO is very simple.
These people are idiots.
So how are they going to do GMO?
Right.
Everything comes from cabbage, all your green vegetables,
whether it's lettuce, broccoli, kale, whatever.
It all came from cabbage because of seed
manipulation.
Chihuahuas are GMO because there's no such thing
as a Chihuahua.
It was bred down certain dogs.
But there's a distinction.
Of course.
Yeah.
But there's a distinction.
The apple head.
Between.
Oh yeah.
The apple head versus the deer head or
whatever they call it.
But the thing is there, there's a distinction,
I think though, between breeding something and manipulating
the gene, the genome that way.
And literally.
That's the thing.
I think how are they, how are they
going to manipulate?
Okay.
Here's the thing people let's, let's liven up,
listen up and liven up and sit up
when these morons are playing around with cells
and all that stuff.
Do they know how to keep it alive?
And you know, when you break a cell
wall, how damaging that is, do you think
the cell is going to have virility to
continue?
It has to be regrown and regrown.
Yeah.
Over and over and over their success rate
with what they got you thinking that they
could manipulate all this stuff is so low
that it almost doesn't exist.
What they're doing is mixing some crazy horrific,
like Frankenstein stuff using 200 year old technology,
right?
The technology hasn't changed.
Well, yeah, they have led lighting and cell
phones.
Okay.
But the concept even of cloning is very
simple.
There's you don't need any fancy technology.
You just have to accommodate what it takes
to grow a clone of a human, right?
So like, for example, they got away from
glass, stiff glass containers, because as the clone
is growing, and it gets it flinches a
leg, it could break the leg.
So then you put grow them in plastic,
soft plastic bags.
But the, the genetic engineering, like, for example,
they're finding stuff in nature, like, that that
meat substitute stuff, there's certain algae that produces
something very close to hemoglobin.
So they're making like a vegetarian blood to
put in stuff.
So you think you're eating beef, and you
shouldn't be eating that anyway.
You can do selective breeding, and gene manipulation,
but these morons doing getting down and doing
what they're saying.
Oh, for some reason, you disappeared there.
Let me see what's going on.
Because I don't know if you dropped off
or muted yourself.
Let's see.
Well, you're still there.
But you you're not making noise.
So after an interruption there, where we're quite
frankly, look, I lost internet first, then power
went out.
So you know, what can you say for
where I live?
But anyway, little weird confusion there.
I've been hearing tales of odd behaving electronics
lately.
But that's not what we were talking about.
We were talking about cheese when we were
interrupted.
And yeah, that's right.
I remember.
Yeah.
So that's where we were.
And I had only given you a part
of the question.
So anyway, just as a refresher, just just
just to fill in, Chuck, hold on.
When was this today?
That was four or five days ago.
So we're going to basically catch up from
a few.
Yeah, yes.
I know.
I just gave it away.
But yeah, no problem.
I didn't know if you wanted to.
So I didn't do it, but you did
it.
So cool.
Whatever.
That's fine.
Just however, however, the recording is, however, the
recording is, it ends up that way, right?
Trying to take this with good humor.
Anyways.
All right.
So the question was that when we were
interrupted, does the Greek have a recommendation for
cheese that's easier on the gut?
I get a raw milk cheese from Switzerland
that specifically states it has a non GMO
rennet goes down, you know, while most of
the crap in the U.S. gives me
issues, I believe the non pasteurized goes down
easier with enzymes that benefit digestion that I
would be cooked off that would be cooked
off in the standard process.
There's the whole question, finally.
So, yeah, cheese.
Yeah.
Vandy posted some Michio Kushi stuff.
I put it on and peruse Filo Kushi
or just put in Michio Kushi.
His son has a channel.
And it was interesting.
He was speaking like eggs, cheese, chicken.
Um, why chicken?
Because it's usually poultry.
Turkey will probably do the same.
So eggs, bird, poultry, meat and cheese generally
contract.
The center part of the body is very
contracting, compacting, and you're going to feel a
tightness and all that.
Now, you know, all American food has been
poisoned since the 70s.
I remember back in the early 70s, having
a McDonald's burger and it was actually delicious.
Right.
And it's it's I don't think it's edible
now.
But all American food, unless you have good
sources and vetted sources, vetted, meaning it's not
just a label.
You know, it says it's good.
You know, it's good as a reputation for
being good.
And it is good.
Right.
You have to really work hard.
That's why food, clothing, shelter, right, are the
three main things.
If you could figure that out, that's a
whole life.
Life's worth of work.
But cheese, in essence, if you're sensitive to
it, you're sensitive to those types of foods.
So I wonder, let's just leave it at
that.
You know, let's say a retort or a
question back would be, are you also sensitive
to eating poultry, which would be chicken, turkey,
which is the most common.
We don't have to get into exotic birds.
And eggs.
Right.
If you're sensitive to that, then it lines
up with the concept of it contracting, which,
by the way, Michio got into when you
eat that kind of food, cheese, poultry and
eggs, it leads to, quote unquote, diagnosis for
diabetes, which is he didn't know that diabetes
and AIDS were fake diseases.
Right.
But it harms the liver.
So my question back would be, it's not
the food so much as it is the
quality of the food and not just the
quality of preparation and handling and, you know,
top tier quality as we consider it.
But what does the food actually do in
the body?
Right.
A simple one would be like sugars, typically
very highly refined sugars make people whimsy.
Right.
Like lightheaded sugar rush kind of you've heard
of the great Milky Way Snickers bar or
whatever.
Oh, yeah.
And that's the quality of that.
They got a whole thing with the Snickers
where it's like, look, you want to change
your day, actually eat a Snickers.
Right.
Yeah, no doubt.
Yeah, you definitely will.
That's for sure.
It will change it.
Now, will it make it better?
There's another question.
That's a different question.
Well, well, also in the 70s, candy bars
were delicious.
Yes.
Now, candy bars are just sweet.
You don't taste anything else but the sweet.
Right.
So now an objective observer, though, might ask,
is this something that is just attached to
your changes or has the food actually changed
or is it a bit of both?
Because someone might say that as you.
OK, because as you mature, right, it would
be more extreme.
Yeah.
So it's just a more extreme because of
your age.
You've now gone to a different place where
you're a bit different from where you were
in the 70s.
Right.
So therefore, you've got to factor both of
these things into that equation.
It's not just the candy changing, but you've
changed as well.
Yes.
Well, yeah, I'm also experimenting with myself because
I do a lot of crowd.
I'm like 20 or 30 grams a day,
which is not a lot.
There's people who do five times that amount,
but it slows down digestion, but it makes
it stable.
So it won't harm you.
So in other words, if you do too
much of any kind of opioid, you get
constipation.
So I've noticed my digestive has changed, but
I do a lot of coffee, like two
and a half, three liters of coffee and
about a pack of cigarettes every day.
And I could feel the effects of each
one.
And I compensate.
I know how to compensate and balance it.
But just just on a side note, I
mean, these things are, it's real hard to
derive a good answer.
Give me an example.
This is a side note.
I listened to our cakes video lately, and
he was touting that he's got this archaic
underground, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, and he's got
a health and wellness section said, Oh, okay,
let's check it out.
So I went in there, and I signed
in, I forgot what password because you got
to have a very complex password.
I didn't write it down.
One, let me get in again, at least
on the phone, but the computer is still
on it.
And I went to the health and wellness
section, and all these people are posting all
this stuff.
And I'm like, all I said was greetings,
y'all, you know, and a couple of
question marks, you know, are you the Greek,
whatever?
I didn't answer back.
But I went down and saw what people
are consider health and wellness to be and
I'm like, there's no way I'm going to
post here.
There's so much background.
In other words, the stuff that we discuss
here and the stuff that I tell people,
basically, is so radically different.
You can imagine imagine a health and wellness
section on alternative media, what people are going
to be posting, right?
I don't have to get into it.
I don't have to imagine.
Yeah, I've seen it.
So yeah, yeah, you've probably seen it.
Okay, yeah.
So there's no way I can go there.
I'm not gonna I can't.
And it hit me.
It was good that I did that.
Because like, I'll just put a few things,
you know, why don't we just say health
is really fitness.
And believe it or not, there are people
with their fitness is so poor, they're always
in pain and can't walk, right?
Duh, you would call them unhealthy, right?
So let's look at it as fitness.
Let's look at seasonal eating.
Let's look at the energy movement in the
body, Boba, are you kidding?
Are you kidding that will go over like,
I don't know, like a Led Zeppelin, right?
That will not work.
No, you need to smooth.
I don't know.
Here, Chuck, I don't know how to introduce
this stuff, even though it's just dead nuts
simple, right?
I just don't know how to bring it.
I mean, it would have been better.
It needs to be done on a sonic
only it cannot be written.
There's just too many things.
I could definitely speak faster than I can
write.
But I cannot be done.
It has to be done in conversation.
I just maybe it's because I saw what
else was being posted.
I said, there's no way this is this
is going to, you know, so I just
want to bring this up when when questions
about things like specifically about the cheese, it's
not just the cheese, which was there were
right to ask, you know, the quality cheese,
like American cheese versus not American cheese, but
American manufacturer versus European and all that.
That's a big difference.
But then there's also what cheese any cheese
does to the body, you might be sensitive
to that.
So there's always two layers.
And also there's seasonality.
You might do better with cheese in cold
weather, Wisconsin cheddar, right?
You know, it's 40 minus over there in
the winter.
You might do better in cold, higher latitude,
or very low latitude, depending than near the
tropics or moderate latitude in the summer.
Right?
So that has to be taken into consideration
seasonal eating, right?
Right.
You know, but what do you do?
You know, like, years ago, especially when I
was bike racing, and I would order a
pie, right?
Pizza pie.
Yeah, we call them pies, by the way.
When you order, you go to a pizzeria,
I'll take a pie, they know exactly, you
know, you know, you didn't say they know,
you don't mean apple or cherry, right?
So there's a lot, there's a lot of
cheese on a pie like that, right?
So and I would eat a quite a
bit of it.
And I didn't feel like doing as much
baked goods in the summer than I did
in winter.
This is before I contemplated all these things.
Then I have recall.
So I would, I would emphasize seasonality, I
would say that the majority of the people
that I've helped the most are the ones
that took seasonality as a as the strongest
message.
And think of it this way.
Even if you know nothing about the effects
of seasonal eating, or you know, cold food
for cold climates, tropical food for hot climates.
Think about it.
Imagine a hot day back east, you're not
going to eat as many slices as you
would in the wintertime.
No, logically, I mean, you just can't you
just write so you're going to get the
Italian ices and you're going to get whatever,
you know, so it's not the same.
In other words, try to tap into your
intuition, try to recall how you you know
how you found yourself eating anyway, combine that
with seasonality.
And that would be the most arching effect
overarching effect on anything, right?
Even when I was a kid, difficult.
Even when I was a kid dating, the
girls would often say, look, it's too hot
to eat.
You end up with one slice of pizza
piece, maybe on a date where you're out
for, you know, six hours.
And yeah, so that's that.
I mean, it just would come up naturally.
Anyway, it's what you're you know, and that's
the other thing is you got to kind
of pay attention to what your body signals
it needs, I think.
Or do you disagree with right?
And no, no signals.
But recall, recall how you eat when it's
hot out and how you eat when it's
cold out.
And you'll notice it's very different.
Oh, yeah.
You intuitively do that.
But you can even observe it, like I
say, in a date, right, where she would
be like, look, it's too hot to eat.
And like I say, you both end up
getting one slice of pizza piece.
Now, that's not going to work in the
winter.
You're going to want more of that just
naturally.
It's going to come up.
But but one slice and keep walking and
make sure you have a drink.
All these natural things come up because you
seem to desire them.
But your desires actually give you a prescription
in a way.
I mean, I hate to use that word,
but it seems applicable.
What do you think?
No, I agree.
That's fine.
Fair enough.
It's a very broad subject.
Yeah.
So a couple other quick, broad subjects, and
then we'll close this one up.
And by the way, I'm going to address
something that people might have heard that I
should have just addressed, but I'm not going
to.
We're going to do it in a separate
short sonic, which which will be posted after
this.
OK, but anyway, let's talk a bit.
This is another topic.
What is that?
What topic would that be?
Oh, because you brought up forums and you're
going to address.
Yeah, you brought up forums and politics.
So I'm going to do that in the
next short sonic that's concentrated on that.
Anyways, got it.
Let's talk a bit about this is, again,
another comment about the first ever A.I.
prime minister of Albania.
She looks very sexy.
Are they testing first in these banana countries?
I didn't hear of this, but apparently, you
know, there is some talk online, but I
haven't seen it myself yet.
But they're like there's an A.I. prime
minister of Albania.
Sounds like Jack Fresco stuff.
It does.
Jack Fresco talked about replacing the government with
computers.
They do a better job.
I have no I have no comment.
To me, it doesn't matter if it's you
only have the rights that, you know, and
people don't know anything.
So the complaining about the way they're being
treated by governments financially, however they are, you
know, politically, religiously, whatever, as long as everyone's
following what's been what the agreements are.
Right.
And but no one knows what the agreements
are.
So they do it.
Right.
So it to me, it doesn't matter as
long as the agreements are being held.
You know, each party's performing according to how
they're supposed to be performing.
And I find that to be untrue anywhere
I look regarding any subject.
Right.
Fair enough.
So it doesn't matter.
And assuming this is true, look, the A
.I. prime minister or whatever would just be
the interface or the face of what's going
on anyway, which wouldn't be all that much
different from you looking at the president on
Twitter, TV and all these other things.
It's the same.
You're not actually interfacing with a human being
anyway.
You'll interface with the bureaucracy.
But yeah, OK.
You know, so.
But they're telling you.
OK, so they're telling you it's A.I.,
but they're not telling you that we have
clones here.
Right.
So so what's the point?
There you go.
Is they going to.
Yeah.
So no.
Yeah, I think the worst what I pray
when for for for people is that their
government gets so bad that they have to
throw it, overtake it, get rid of it,
and they have to educate themselves like we
haven't had any real revolutions in a long
time.
We almost had a real revolution here.
Actually, it is that we had a pretty
good revolution here in the US.
But, you know, Lafayette said before he left,
he says, well, we'll get you back using
commerce.
You know, don't don't worry about it.
You know, whatever.
And then Franklin, didn't he say something?
Was it Franklin or Jefferson?
You know, it's you have a republic and
a constitution.
If you can keep it, something like that.
Yeah, I believe Franklin.
So.
Right.
Because they asked him, what kind of government
do we have?
Mr. Franklin is the legend.
And he said, well, you know, you've got
a republic or, you know, if you can
keep it.
So, you know, there you go.
And obviously that didn't work out.
It did not work out.
We didn't keep it, so to speak, or,
you know, the proverbial we.
Anyways, I Chuck, can you ask your greatest
thoughts on, quote, ego and quote, specifically the
idea that if you hate a person, you
hate something in him that is part of
yourself.
Is this wisdom or new age distraction?
New age, all of it is like, for
example, the ego is no, that is that
is a Freudian construct.
You're you have one sense of conscious and
then you have a sense of unconscious.
And that unconscious also is capable of dreaming,
meaning asleep.
Right.
When you're not conscious and when you're conscious,
it's it goes back to the John Mace
therapy that we talked about.
Because everything in the brain is held mostly,
I should say mostly by imagery.
It's your ability to bring up those images
and relate those images to your identity.
There is no ego or super ego or
it or whatever.
That is all Freudian constructs.
Um, so no, I believe a lot of
the these quote, unquote niceties that people, you
know, like, for example, when someone isn't doing
well, socially, they say that you're the problem.
Right?
No, they're the problem.
Depending on the individual.
Usually, they're the problem, the society's fucked up.
And you're not adjusted to it.
Like, you know, I'm interviewing people constantly.
And I get resumes.
Fortunately, I have someone filtering it.
And I said, look, I don't want to
see any more resumes.
If they have an interesting name, put their
or put their name in one of those
pieces of paper in a fishbowl and pull
one out, right?
It doesn't matter.
What is that?
Like, you know, random?
Yeah.
Random generator.
And if you get any resumes, the best
resume would read dropped out by the eighth
grade have been on the FBI most wanted
list between 2015 and 2024.
And I couldn't afford art school, or I
didn't want to afford it.
And I have my own art studio, that
would be the prime candidate.
Right?
So that wouldn't make it too far anywhere,
right?
Imagine no corporate job have been in the
FBI most wanted list for the eight years,
right?
Or I dropped out of the eighth grade.
Can you imagine?
That'll still take your application, though?
Yeah, it's it's not the society is messed.
In other words, the models, that's what okay,
dropping out by the eighth grade, being on
the FBI most wanted list, and starting your
own art studio, to me as one, in
air quotes, a model citizen.
You know, so I might be the wrong
person to ask these things.
Because if you go somewhere and say that,
which is true, that the ego is in
super ego, all these are Freudian constructs, and
they're watch what happens to the person you're
telling this to.
Right?
Yeah, they can't they can't see it.
I've kind of done that where I've been
like, Oh, so you've been reading Freud, you
know, that's all that is you're reading Freud.
So that's an influence on you.
But other than that, you know, it is
a construct.
Well, he would do like Darwin got it
from the stuff at the time.
It's like Einstein, right?
And relativity and all that.
So all this stuff.
Yeah, there's gonna be no, no, no.
I say that everyone around you, whoever's listening,
everyone around you is fucked up in a
severe way.
Can't be fixed.
What are you going to do about it?
There's no fine point to it.
And this is sledgehammer, right type approach.
And you might as well watch Dr. House
if you want psychology, you know, beginning with
everybody lies.
You know, I'm just saying the guy making
fun of the medical industry with that show
is that one all the time?
Yeah, all the time.
Everybody's stupid.
And nobody knows what they're doing except him
and kind of well, kind of reminds me
of somebody.
Anyway, there's there's my joke.
I don't know.
There's my attempt at a joke.
But speaking of jokes, and I'm not sure
if this is a serious question or somebody
just trying to, you know, like poke us
poke you with a stick or not.
But here goes anyway.
Question.
Every time somebody starts question with a question,
I got to tell you, it usually means
they're trying to stick a point.
So I don't know why that indicator is
that stick away, stick away.
Here we go.
Question if the Greeks died, if the Greeks
died is so good, why does he have
such bad teeth?
Oh, that's a good point.
Hereditary everyone on the father's side lost their
teeth, like in their 40s.
And I had perfect teeth, and they just
started falling apart.
Why?
Because the teeth are the head is young.
And what makes the teeth so sensitive is
they're not antagonistic to the head.
The teeth are very young, right?
Right.
No matter how you look at it, and
shape and texture and everything, right?
Even in color, young is white, right?
So you have a young attachment to with
two to a young object by another young
object, who is just waiting for something to
flip it over.
So teeth can be very, very sensitive energetically.
So, but what was interesting is I remember
as a young child, and it was like,
you know, so and so uncle, whatever is
getting dentures, I'm like, he's not that old.
And, and then social uncles getting dentures, and
he's not that old, maybe I will, too.
But I still have teeth, some teeth.
But, yeah, and I bring up all these
personal things, because I know there's other people
going through things similar and whatever.
And I try to, you know, speak about
how I've dealt with them.
And here's the thing about teeth.
When I was very young, I broke the
number of eight to throw teeth in the
front.
And I had a bridge put in when
I was 13.
Like I had my adult teeth for two
weeks, and I broke them right, falling off
of one of those monkey bars perform really
high, like, don't go up so high as
I'll be all right.
So I've had a bridge the entire life
until about 10 years ago, I started getting
loose and all that.
And I was like, Oh, man, you know,
I don't want to get a partial I
don't want to.
Anyway, I had it removed, and I had
a partial made, which was a temporary flipper,
which I'm still using a decade later, because
I rebuilt it.
And I make my own, by the way,
temporary teeth and all that no one can
tell that they're temporary.
But what was amazing as the dentist acquaintance
that I have, I got really upset at
him, I said, Why don't you tell me
temporary teeth, and partials are wonderful, I can,
I can buy it into anything I want.
There's no temperature sensitivity, right?
If I want, I could put titanium inserts
in there, right?
Like jaws, remember?
And right, so I'm really big on that.
Moonraker, Moonraker, Moonraker jaws, you mean not, you
know, jaws, the shark?
Yeah, good.
Yeah, the Moonraker jaws.
Yeah.
But the teeth that bites through suck.
I mean, I've joked around, it's like, because
I make spark plugs, I have the ability
to make, you know, very Swiss Army knife
thing.
Now, I don't want a full denture, I
have enough teeth that they're called abutments where
the temporary like fits into no metal.
And I'm really, really, really pleased with it,
versus sensitive teeth that were not doing so
great.
Right?
I'm very impressed with the temporaries, which technically,
according to the UN that makes me a
cyborg.
Because I have artificial, if you have anything
artificial in your body, doing what your body
would normally be doing, like an arm, a
leg, teeth, teeth, whatever.
I think they call it was a transhuman,
whatever you have.
Yeah, technically, you you now are what do
you call when you integrate technology with a
human body?
Well, there's a whole philosophy of what I
call transhumanism.
Yeah.
So technically, I'm partaking in that by having
synthetic teeth.
And I tell people, does it look like
these are not made?
No, those teeth look like they're your teeth
as Oh, ha, gotcha.
And you know what, I made them.
I built these things, you know, so I
feel sorry for people, by the way, that
are getting partials and dentures from dent from
dentists, because they're so large and cumbersome.
There's no reason for them to be the
way that's why you ever hear someone dentures,
you're like, Oh, I could tell he's wearing
dentures.
Yeah, right.
They're not, they're, they're not fit to the
mouth properly.
And they don't do that.
I go back and even recently, I went
to have some dental work done, I had
to add two teeth to the bottom in
the past two years since I've seen him.
And he's so proud.
He, the dentist takes it out, I take
it out, show him and he shows his
assistants, dental assistants, look, he made this.
And they kind of look the other way,
you know, like, Oh, whatever, you know, like,
they're, they're just there for whatever.
But he's so impressed.
And dentists usually are very impressed when their
patients make their own body parts, shall I
say, but Yeah.
But anyway, that was a diatribe about teeth.
But if you have a bum tooth, have
it pulled if it's in an area, like
in the front part of the mouth, like
anything between six and 12.
Or let's say 22 and 30.
Get partials.
I'm really but yeah, but you're gonna have
to get a dremel and you have to
learn.
I get most of my stuff from Amazon,
by the way, dental supply.
Because years ago, if you walked into a
dental supply store, especially you know, wherever they
say you, you know, you have to be
a dentist to buy from here, right?
So Amazon doesn't discriminate.
So I wonder if they have a brain
surgery kit.
But anyway, fair enough.
You know, and lastly, just to just to
recover that question.
Look, like you said, hereditary, hereditary issues are
the problem there.
Frankly, I mean, look, mine are busted and
messed up because men usually don't even live
to be my age.
So therefore, yeah, their teeth fall out and
then they die.
So I'm about to your teeth didn't live
to your teeth didn't live to be that
age.
Look at it that way.
But you remain Yeah, right.
I'm still you know, I'm stretching that side
of the average.
That's all.