Sonic event number 7, Ocelli in the Greek, rated Y.
Not even sure if I need to announce that every time because you're subscribed here so you
got it and you know what you got, or maybe you don't, we'll see.
Meanwhile, we ended off the last event, Sonic event number 6, discussing briefly a bit about
well what is a naturally occurring disease.
The Greek mentioned a few things there really of interest that I don't know, we need to
get into it a bit more but there's quite a bit that has come up in the chat which we
do have toward the bottom of the page if you're on the Sonic event page and this interaction
is interesting so I'm going to try and touch on some of those subjects that were brought
up there as well as other feedback we've gotten but anyway, Greek, how are you doing today?
Hey, what I'm doing, no natural diseases here.
You know what, I got kind of sarcastic on that about being natural about drinking too much
alcohol and your liver rotting off, right?
Or your groin rotting off if you're too promiscuous.
When you hear me make comments like that, it means it's for another time and I just
want to leave off with a strong visual, you know?
Mental image there, definitely strong if you're thinking of, I don't know man, the whole crotch
rotting off thing was a bit much in my head but hey, whatever.
Natural causes, what's natural, suicide, whatever they call these days, the suiciding, two bullets
in the head or he hung himself and then shot himself in the head with a rifle, you know?
Yeah, well you know the guys that shoot themselves in the chest twice with bolt action rifles,
yeah, that's always interesting, I got to say.
You know what they're doing there, they're accommodating the idiocy of the public.
Here's the thing we might have touched on, you don't deal with the, if you see the media
as it is, it's not rational, it's not logical.
So you cannot deal with someone who has abandoned all rationale and logic in that form.
You have to deal with them as a crazy person or the way you would look up protocols for
dealing with the insane and there's a lot of it, I'm not going to get into it, a lot
of the protocols just basically arresting them and confining them, right?
So until what is served to the masses, those purveyors are, you know, let's say confined
and eliminated, it's going to continue.
But it's not their fault, they're simply accommodating the public.
So in essence when you see ridiculous stuff being put out into public, that's what the
public wants.
It's the same reason why you open a service station, a gas station, a convenience store
on the side of the highway, let's say I-10 or 95 in the middle of the desert, right?
Why?
Because you got a quarter of a million cars or 100,000 cars passing every day, right?
So if the people stop traveling, that highway closes, what happens to that convenience store?
It closes too.
So you have this highway of what's called the collective, the mainstream, the normal,
that they're just accommodating.
So I tell people, stop giving any energy to what's being put out to the public unless
it's for you, you know, and the same goes with disease.
You know, that's one of the common themes that I bring up often at every turn, actually,
any presentation I give where I say, you know, the reason why, when you want to complain
about, here we go with the why again, you want to complain about the quality of the
information you're getting, the truth is that it's there to accommodate a waiting audience.
You know, there's a waiting audience that wants this, that wants to be lied to, that
wants to be misdirected, that wants to be told the ludicrous.
It is what they want.
Yeah, so the media, the purveyors are not the problem.
Yeah.
No, you can't sell something without a ready and waiting customer base.
You just can't.
Yeah.
They're fulfilling a demand.
Right.
Fulfilling a demand.
That's a better way to put it.
It's an unspoken demand, because if you ask these normies, and when I say normies, it
could be someone you're living with, it could be your wife, your husband, your children,
your parents, your neighbor, people at work, it could be anyone around you, so don't get
upset at them.
It just happens to be they were just cut from that cloth.
They won't admit it, that that's what they want, but you know, that's what they want.
That is what they want.
Now, it's fascinating, because one of the things that came up in the chat, I think ties
directly to this, because you mentioned fake terrorist attacks, you mentioned fake pandemic,
and I agree with you there, because not as advertised, any of it, of course, just like
the so-called vaccination, not as advertised over and over again, but look, I don't want
to go into that necessarily, because the question was asked in the chat, is it not time for
the Project Bluebeam kind of stuff, right?
Is it time for that?
Now, I often wonder this, and I know a lot of other people do, because we've heard about
the theories of, well, okay, the fake alien invasion, that'll come, right?
Some people have talked about that.
Well, that could possibly unify humanity, because we would all see a common enemy, and maybe
come together and realize, hey, look, we're actually all on one ship together here, this
rock, this planet, this place, right?
We're all in one place together.
Nobody's gone to Mars yet that I know of, at least not in recent times, so, you know,
I mean, we could talk about ancient history, maybe at another point.
If there is a Mars, as advertised.
As advertised, there you go.
But, I mean, the fact is, we're all here, right?
I mean, this we could say, we're on this one particular astral body.
Let's call it world.
Okay, we're on this one world together.
So could this be a unifying thing if there was an alien invasion, whether it was real
or fabricated, a complete Hollywood production?
People have also brought up the 30-story tall Jesus, you know, showing up maybe in a major
city to make a declaration that's being projected out there as a giant hologram.
Again, all the Project Blue Beam type fantasies, which, it's not a fantasy, there were people
working on these things, and the possibility and the concept, and as I've tried to explain
over and over again, think of anything ridiculous, somebody has gamed it out.
Somebody has come up with a contingency plan.
Somebody has come up with strategies for it, but what about that?
Is it time for that kind of thing?
Would that be part of the equation?
I mean, we've already got other productions here with footage and witnesses and victims
and everything else, one way or another, fake pandemic, fake everything else, why not an
alien invasion?
Okay, let's do, okay, let's go to, use 9-11 as a, let's say, an explicit model.
Most people call it a terror event, but the whole thing was hinged on hijacking, right?
Airplanes, right?
Yeah.
Even the missile that hit the Pentagon was called an airplane, okay.
So this was reoccurring since, I remember growing up in the 70s, and there was always
a joke about the Cuban hijackers on an American plane saying, take this plane to Cuba, was
a joke.
I don't know if you remember stuff like that.
Oh, well, that wasn't just a joke.
They were trying to popularize.
Yeah, no, they were trying to popularize that, and also Middle Eastern terrorism, too, because
there were hijackings from what I could see on television, anyway.
Yeah, the real, there were more, actually, there were more real hijackings than ever
been advertised because they used Israeli Mossad forces who were trained to stop it,
and there's a, long story made short, I worked with someone, pretty famous architect now,
back in the 80s, and his girlfriend's mom worked for the CIA in that department.
Anywhere in the world where there was a hijacking, they were able to deploy several teams within
a few hours, and once they got into the airplane, it took about 15 seconds to arrest the situation,
to take control of the plane.
That's never been shown in Hollywood, by the way.
It wouldn't make a good movie, right?
Well, no, because they showed us Dirty Harry going onto a plane, right, and dressing in
the captain's uniform, and of course, people's imaginations was sort of captured by the Dan
or D.B. Cooper narrative in the early 70s, so again, this is the kind of thing that was
already sort of injected in the culture as, well, as you and I were growing up, I think
you're maybe a touch older than me, but either way, still, we were kids at some point in
the 1970s and 80s, so there you have it.
This was part of the cultural memes of the time.
I know there weren't memes yet, because there was no internet, well, not for us yet.
But they were memes, nonetheless.
Right, exactly.
So you know what I'm saying.
It was there, but different.
Go ahead.
Yeah, but the hijacking thing was not mentioned.
It's called terror, right?
So, okay, so it kind of sat latent for a long time, and then 9-11 happened.
If you examine the gaming of that, it was about hijacking, but we don't really view
it as a society as that, right?
It's just this fear concept.
The alien invasion's going to be very similar.
So if it's in the popular mind as a meme, as it has been for the past few years, it's
not going to happen soon.
But just like 9-11, it has to serve multiple functions.
I can give you a very strong, educated speculation.
Once the Middle East, let me just cut to the chase, the important part first, in case we
run out of battery, right?
I always tell people, give the important part first.
When you're having a discussion, you should always preface, inform, and then discuss.
Here's the preface and the information.
When the Middle East Union comes about, and everything's focused there, and it turns into
a jihad-type situation, that's the time to do it.
So you're going to have this, in other words, it won't be to some people, it'll be aliens
to other people, it'll be Mohammed to other people, it'll be the J-E-S-U-S to other people,
it'll be Elijah to, you see what I mean?
Okay?
So it'll be like that.
But I know I could tell you another educated guess, that if you do see on television, flying
saucers shooting a beam to the ground and everything vaporizing and turning to dust,
including people, that's what you'll see on TV.
But if you're in place and you have a cell phone, by the way, now, if you take a film,
especially with an Apple phone, a video of something that you shouldn't have, you'll
go back and replay the video and it won't be there or it'll be different, right?
This technology exists.
So let's say you record it with your iPhone, what you see on TV is a spaceship or a saucer
or something shooting down to the ground, vaporizing everything and everyone on the ground.
When you're there, you won't see a ship at all, you'll just see the ground shaking and
vaporizing everything on the surface, because they'll be using underground nukes, right?
But it's very convincing that if you see it on TV, they're going to insert whatever, something
aerial, the same thing in 9-11.
By the way, just a little tidbit, if an airplane, if you study airplane crashes, by the way,
the moment, the moment, doesn't matter what speed it is, especially in flight, the moment
the nose of a plane up to the pilot's cockpit touches or hits something, a wall, it's a
phenomenon, you could study this if you like, the tail rudder in the tail section falls
off automatically, because the force is longitudinal, it moves to the back and then moves back and
forth like a standing wave.
So you could watch planes crashing into things and the tail falls off right away.
So if 9-11 really was a plane, what you would see, no matter how fast it's going, as the
nose, the front part of the plane fuselage before the wings made contact with the building,
the tail would have fallen off completely, right?
I know it sounds kind of crazy, but that's how physics works in the real world.
Yeah, it kind of makes sense to me in that it might create a pressure pocket, so to speak,
that would push back and might, yeah, actually push.
Well, you could look at, study every legitimate plane crash.
You may not see plane parts, but you'll definitely see the tail and the tail rudder on every
occasion.
I've seen them hit a runway.
The plane could be completely disintegrated.
Yeah, I've seen them hit a runway and they do that, you know, where they burst into flames
and all that.
I actually watched a bunch of those crashes that they, you know how they filmed a bunch
of crashes to study them?
You know, the FAA did this for a while, they filmed a whole bunch, I don't know if they
do it anymore.
You won't find, well, you won't, it'll be hard to find, but yeah.
Used to be, though.
They used to be online.
Yeah.
Go ahead.
Sorry.
No, that's fine.
That's just a phenomenon.
It's basically what happens is it's a longitudinal force.
In other words, the moment the front of the plane gets crushed, it instantly reacts to
the back, right?
Because it's being, you know how sound moves at 700 miles per hour through air and moves
six times faster in the water and 20 times faster on a steel railroad track.
You know, the Native Americans used to put their ear to the railroad tracks and hear
the trains from 30 miles away instantly, right?
So it's a phenomenon like that.
It's, yeah, it's very interesting when, you know, if you get into all of the real physical
aspects.
By the way, the nuclear hypothesis on the World Trade Center can easily be, you could
see the foreshadowing of it by just going into YouTube, put in Project Plowshare and
just study the videos up there.
You know, there's about 10 or 20 videos and it's just like a World Trade Center disaster.
You won't see tall skyscrapers being vaporized, but they're all underground tests.
So that'll be interesting.
By the way, I just want to throw something in.
You know, the cigarette smoke causes cancer.
Cigarettes cause cancer is another bogus thing here since we brought up disease and
all that.
People were getting in the U.S., downwind or east of Nevada, lung cancer in the late
60s and 70s.
Everyone was pretty much that had weak lungs or whatever.
That's because of all the aerial, the nuclear testing, the ionized particles were going
into the air and people were breathing it.
And when the particles got into your ears or your lungs, they were irradiating you day
and night.
It's the same as like getting eight hours worth of x-rays every day.
Of course, you're going to get cancer.
But cigarette, the statistics on cigarette smoking causing cancer is still, lung cancer,
for example, can easily be looked at, but 85% of the people that ever get lung cancer
even today have never smoked.
85% of that 85% are black and Jewish women because what actually causes lung cancer these
days is grief.
Do you think black and Jewish women have a reason to have grief?
I mean, based on their culture, right?
I mean, I'm just saying this, you know, it's just a way to look at it.
So I just wanted to throw that in because when you say nuclear, it's a multi-multi-multifaceted.
It would be, imagine cell phone technology as it is now was not released to the public
and we were still using rotary dial or push button dial with corded phones.
But the technology was up to it, whereas it is now, but hidden from the public.
That's what's going on with the nuclear technology.
It's extremely developed, but if you bring this up to anyone in public, they just still
think of the world, you know, the Hiroshima, Nagasaki bombs with the big flash and the boom
and all that, and they don't think that's evolved from that point.
During the Bosnian War in Serbia, when they had a ceasefire, there were still rogue colonels
and generals out in the field, and they got upset when their cell phone stopped working.
So here's your new cell phone.
The guy powers it up, hits a few buttons, and it leaves a 40-foot diameter by 30-foot
deep crater.
And of course, there's a bright flash that could be seen from 20 miles away, right?
In normal, right?
You get my point?
Yeah, I got you.
Yeah, this was in the mid-90s, they were that small.
So the alien invasion, if it's overplayed, like let's just go back to what you were saying,
being up young in the 70s and 80s, the whole thing about Cubans hijacking planes and saying,
take this plane to Cuba was a little overdone as a meme, you know, it was very much in
the public light, very much so.
But it never turned out that way, you know, ultimately.
So the Project Blue Beam isn't going to happen that way.
All the Project Blue Beam stuff is fine, it's being gamed, but ultimately it's what you
see on TV.
They don't even have to, you know, here, if you go back to 9-11, they still say those
planes were holograms.
There's no one in New York saw any plane.
Now obviously they have, what they do is when you work for an intelligence agency and retire,
you know how they say you never really retire, they call on you while you're in retirement,
and they say you'll get 30 grand if you put on a Con Edison or, you know, New York City
power and water hat and get in the truck and start driving around tomorrow and tell people
you saw a plane.
Sounds very convincing, right?
It's very simple.
By the way, what you never hear about 9-11 also is all the people that were getting hit
over the head and their cameras taken on the street.
You don't hear about that very much, right?
I know of someone who this had happened to.
So, well, it was with someone who this had happened to.
There were people driving around and on foot saying, hey, you got a camera, come here,
come here, come here, and they just take the camera, smash it or hit you on the head if
you don't give it up.
Hundreds.
I'll tell you something.
I think this is a pretty good piece of advice and you could tell me otherwise, but in fact,
I think that some people should go and get the old technology for a camcorder, even if
they go get like a DVD camcorder or a tape camcorder, if they want to actually record
events and be able to preserve them, I think they'd be better off with the DVD one, probably.
Here, there's two problems with that.
One is carrying that thing and you never know when it's going to come.
Maybe it'll be foreshadowed because I remember about a week before 9-11 coming, I was doing
some mural work for someone who comes from a copper mine family and I was saying, be
careful, they're going to pull something with this Osama bin Laden guy and I kind of talked
about it.
Like, you know, hey, look, it's 9-11.
Get it?
9-11, 9-11 is coming.
Emergency, emergency, you know?
I knew something was wrong when CNN, the government was looking for Osama bin Laden, but CNN was
able to hold an interview with him, right?
So this alleged government, I talked about that.
It's in receivership, you know, the ice cream shop that went out of business but still open
in business somehow?
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
So, yeah.
So, there is no Project Blue Beam that will be put into effect because all they have to
do is show it on TV and they don't even have to use really great technology.
Everyone will believe it.
Those that actually witnessed nothing aerial, nothing in the sky, no flying saucer will
second doubt themselves because of the trauma, right?
I mean, if you feel the ground shake and everything turns to dust in front of you, including people
standing there, you're going to be like, yeah, maybe I did miss the saucer, you know?
You see what I mean?
And this is how gullible people are if they still want to be attached to their friends
and family, right?
Well, that's the other thing is that, look, if you show a burning building on TV and you
say a bomb was dropped on the building, people are going to go with the idea that the bomb
was dropped on the building.
All they actually saw was a burning building, right?
I mean, this has been done before.
Well, that was done, you know, the military is for hire.
They shot a missile up near San Francisco area to take out a woman that was Obama's enemy
or whatever.
And they said it was a gas line explosion.
You actually one of the TV crews got there too soon and he could see the gas company
with trailers unloading old gas pipes, throwing them on the street, right?
It's people in the area witnessed a low flying jet and they heard a whiz and a bang.
So, I mean, also there was the guy who the reporter, I don't recall his name, talked
bad about Obama and his car exploded in the Mercedes, right?
That was pretty popular.
There's a few of them like that.
So it's pretty out in the open.
No one really cares.
And I don't think you should care either.
Just protect yourself.
You know, meaning you, whoever's listening, just be this is the type of world you're
living in. But essentially, the alien invasion is going to be very simple.
People are overhyping it and overcomplicating it.
It's just what's shown on TV.
You know, that's it, period.
I mean, but if you're going to leave a footprint or make events happen, yeah, they're
going to have small underground nukes and sewers and buildings and places like that.
And when they go off, yeah, they may look pretty unreal and unnatural.
It would be very plausible that it would be an alien invasion.
But I don't see it happening now.
It has to be it has to serve several reasons.
And the only dynamic that I see coming or something like that will serve multiple
purposes when the Middle East starts becoming the center again.
Well, again, meaning thousands of years, but the center of attention in a conflicting
kind of way. So if you're going to have a
public alien invasion, it's going to be there.
But doesn't mean that they're not going to go to like Washington State or the Midwest
or Florida and say the spaceships flew over here, too.
Right. But it won't be until the Middle East thinks that starts getting hot and
popping. You know what I mean?
Right. And look, in previous Sonics, we talked about the Middle East, Middle Eastern
Union and stuff like that, which I never could quite follow exactly how that was
going to go. We
talked about what was it, Israel, Syria as well.
Well, when you see Iraq separate as a country and a new country is formed in
northern Iraq, which takes parts of Syria and parts of Turkey, which, by the way,
Syria has been softened for the past eight years.
I mean, before the Syria thing happened, the fake revolution there and all this
stuff going on with Turkey, with the Kurds, the Kurdish people, no one really talks
about their their own people, their descendants of the Persians.
You're going to have a new country. Well, if that, let's say, formed in a week or so,
we are on it's hot and popping here in a couple of weeks.
Right. Once that starts.
But that's one of the signs.
But the another sign that you're going to see is conflict in and around Israel.
It'll be a typical of, you know, when the security apparatus is removed before an
assassination assassination takes place.
OK, this is typical.
You're going to see politicians in Europe, in Israel and generals and military key
people be out of the country and there will be an invasion on Israel.
But this time they're going to be subdued.
Right. And if you are in the Israeli military, you will witness insubordination
because you'll be given orders to do things that are clearly suicidal or you'll
be attacked and be told to keep your arms down.
You know, don't fire back.
Really dumb, really dumb, dumb stuff.
So if you're in the in the IDF or in the Israeli military, be prepared for
ridiculous orders like literally, you know, having even infantry or air coming over
you and being told to to not fire back at all.
Right. You know what I mean?
This this is the kind of overt, you know, basically the leadership, meaning the
world leadership and the leadership in Israel is going to give up the country.
Well, you know, what forces?
Yeah. Watching some atypical news feeds recently, actually, I'm seeing some
reports about protests and things in Israel and the military actually starting
to not be as cooperative as they once were.
People not, you know, because you have a compulsory service there.
Right. If you're supposed to claim citizenship, you have to go and serve for a
bit. You know about this.
Well, apparently there are some, you know, for the first time ever.
Refusing to to to comply.
Something is happening there.
And I'm not sure all of what it is.
It's difficult, you know, because there's not a lot of reporting on it.
But that's starting to happen.
Do you think that that's the that that is a beginning signal like right now that
we're going to see the beginning signal started more than let's say quite before
that, with the political system being overtly in shambles.
But yeah, what I meant about the military reaction is they're going to be basically
told to stand down no matter what happens.
And the only defense they will put up, any Israeli military will put up are those
that are not following orders.
I'm just saying as a general thing, they'll be told to stand down, which won't
make any sense at all.
And this will make it out once once this happens, which is actually pretty soon.
I either see it this fall or next year in the spring.
Don't hold me to that because I don't really see much of that happening till 2025.
But I could see more of a signaling.
But essentially, let's just make it simple instead of just watching what's in the
news and like trying to read into it when it starts.
The military of Israel will be told to stand down on the only fighting back or
fighting. Defending will be those that are not taking orders or not following those
orders, which is going to put it into even more confusion.
And so, yeah, I was speaking with someone from Israel recently and I said, basically
the conversation ended up.
So just watch the news when you see like all the Knesset and major figures out of
the country. It could get hot and popping real soon.
So it's pretty, pretty.
Look at the basic stuff.
Don't very often.
I've been looking at the Middle East in detail and you get pretty, pretty wild
about and start reading in things, you know, and I just sit back and just look at
the major stories because the time we're not at that time or near that time yet.
We're close to it. So so that's what I have to say about the alien invasion.
It's going to be centered in and around that part of the world when it gets moving.
So I wouldn't I wouldn't be concerned at all with the holograms and blue beam and
everything. They don't have to do that.
That's that's pretty simple.
Well, it won't be necessary, but like you said, they can broadcast a variety of
things. And like I said, they could also show you the burning building and tell you
why it happened afterwards.
Right. Here's the aftermath of what this occurred that occurred.
Here's some witnesses, whether they're real or not.
And there there you have it.
That's what that's what happened, because that's what the TV show says.
Right. Well, yeah, even when they're real witnesses, they edit out and they put it
together how you want to how they want it to see that there is nothing real about the
TV other than the perception that people that receive it think is real.
And, you know, so it's pretty far gone, but it's always been far gone.
And if you look at periodicals, which are it's getting harder and harder to find.
But in the 19th century, even the 18th century, they're basically saying we have a
problem with the news, you know, basically don't read, don't read them, don't believe
what's in the newspapers. It's trash from the seventeen hundreds, eighteen hundreds,
early nineteen hundreds. But there's always been a movement, but that hasn't
changed. Right. There was a big movement in the eighteen hundreds, you know, what's
going on with the media. It's all they called it yellow journalism at the time.
Right. Did it did it change in the 20th century or now?
It didn't have no effect.
No. Even when they first started making the newsreels, the films and all that, they
were staging that and they kept getting caught, you know, doing that where it's like,
oh, we're showing you a film of the invasion that nobody knew was supposed to happen.
You know, and it turned out it was all choreographed and better than what Hollywood
was putting out. So well, the the War Department was their secret.
It was the Laurel Canyon.
That's right. The famous Laurel Canyon in Hollywood, L.A.
That's where they met and brainstormed a lot of stuff.
So I want to go back to the natural disease.
Yeah, absolutely. Because, you know, and again, I want to integrate something from
the chat room one more time, because, you know, people did ask about
treatment of animals in a way.
Somebody asked about pets.
There was a couple of different discussions.
And I always find this interesting because, again, the the, you know, the pandemic
narrative, right? What was going on?
People were eating animals they shouldn't be eating, right?
The wet market. Remember that whole thing?
The. Oh, is it a penguin?
Or remember there was maybe it's a bat, maybe monkeys, monkey.
Yeah. I mean, squid.
So look, there are real consequences to eating the wrong things.
OK, there just are.
But some of them are practical considerations, but there's more to it than that.
So, you know, what about the stewardship of the animals?
I mean, I'm sorry to go to the very pedestrian biblical text here, but, you know, it
doesn't have to be biblical.
You'll find it everywhere as far as, you know, Vedic means knowledge.
Right. Right. And they basically considered killing anything as murder.
Right. So you can take it again.
What's right is what wrong is what covenant you live by.
If you lived, let's say, in a Polynesia where they still have cannibals, if you're at a
birthday party, you'd be fighting on who's going to eat the eyeball of a human.
Right. Which is I'm taking that from, by the way, when they roast lamb at a wedding in the
Middle East or in Europe, southern Mediterranean rim, the people fight who's going to
eat the eyeball. You know, it's a pun on that.
So so here's the thing.
Right or wrong is right or wrong within the agreement or covenant that you have.
Right. You know, if you get caught with pot, marijuana or weed in Malaysia, it's death
penalty. Right.
But here it's legal.
So supposedly they're called covenants.
Right. We're laws and rules.
So it depends on where you live.
It's geographic to a certain degree here in most of the Western world.
You pretty much pick how you want to live, what rules you live by, you know.
So, you know, the biblical one is easy.
Four legged has to four legged animal, cloven hoof.
Choose the cut. It's clean and clean, meaning it is spirit.
Your spirit. It's spiritually allowable.
Like it would be halal in which means permissible in Arabic or haram is not permissible
in Hebrew.
We call to me, which is not unclean or kosher, which means fit and proper.
Right. So what's fit and proper is the way to look at it.
And but anything you any animal meat, if you cook it to death, if you've known anyone
who's been a world traveler, if you're going to eat meat somewhere, you just have them
cook it to death, meaning cook it till it's really dead and then cook it again.
Right. Char broiled almost to the point where it's totally dry protein, then you'll
pretty much be safe, you know, change most of the energy where it won't harm you, even
human food. By the way, what's what covenant you live by?
I could tell you, I just live by the Old Testament covenant, covenant of what to eat.
You know, like I mean, we were sharing pictures of pizza, Chuck, and you showed me one
where that looked like pork sausage.
I didn't comment. I said it just looked good.
But, you know, you learn a lot about people by what they show you, what they eat, what
covenant they live by. Right.
Because if you were living by an Old Testament covenant, you wouldn't have that.
I'm presuming it was pork sausage.
No, actually wrong.
Sorry. It was beef.
But that's OK. OK, but I'm presuming.
No, I sliced up some meatballs and they were, you know, beef as far as I know.
OK, definitely beef and overcooked, like you said.
OK, there you go. That's fine.
Meatball should be rare anyway.
So here's the point. It's who am I to tell what covenant to live by?
Because, by the way, there is no conversion.
You know how the Christians have missionaries and convert people.
And if you weren't Catholic or Muslim, you paid a tax in the back in the old days or
whatever. Even today, if you're in the registered public media in Europe, you see
something out against the Vatican.
It's a 5000 euro fine.
Right. So either way, there are other covenants are forced on people.
You know, fortunately and unfortunately, here we have a legal system which is all
presumptive, which I do want to touch on again a little bit because I was recently
reading a court doc from someone I know and he lost the case.
But the case he lost because of something that wasn't even part of the case.
So I was like, oh, my gosh.
And so anyway, here's the it's all presumption.
So the thing about animals is this again, if you go back to the Old Testament, any
time you touch the flesh of an animal, you're spiritually unclean until the next
day you wash and then you're spiritually clean again.
Next day starts at noon.
Right. Because it's not sundown like the, quote unquote, Jewish people think.
Because if you're in if you've ever been in the desert, if you wash your clothes
and hang it up to dry at night, you know, the desert, you could have a 40 degree
temperature drop when the sun goes down.
Right. It's very cold.
Yeah. Yeah, it can be.
So but if you're living in a desert climate and you and you wash your clothes at
eleven o'clock, you hang it up at eleven fifteen, you put them back on, they're dry
pretty much. So whatever, you know, you who am I to tell people?
I could just tell people what I found out and what I could hold to be true
mathematically, you know, like two plus two equals four and four minus two equals
two. You know, it runs it runs both ways.
So here's the thing. The biblical text tells you if you touch meat of any animal,
you're unclean. Right.
Spiritually. Well, let me ask you, if you bring up what animal is OK to eat?
I'm saying spiritually. Right.
Because you could get to death even if it's human.
You can eat it. Right. So here's the thing.
What animals is properly or ultimately it indirectly tells you if you touch flesh,
you're unclean. So let me ask you, if your chicken is allowable, let's say beef.
OK. When you're eating a meatball sandwich, it's all beef.
Are you touching the flesh of an animal?
Yes or no. Very simply. Of course you are.
Of course you touch. If you're not, you know, you may not you might be so good.
It doesn't even touch your teeth when you eat it.
You know what I mean? You just. Right.
So, yeah. So what what I'm saying is the biblical covenant indirectly promotes
vegetarianism indirectly without telling you that.
Right. To be a vegetarian.
So there you go. There's a lot of people that I've spoken to that are not doing
well financially. And I talk about clean foods.
I can't afford to eat clean.
What do you mean you can't afford to eat clean?
Actually, the best food you can eat are high quality grains and legumes, which are
all cheaper than meat.
So, you know, so if you run into someone who says I can't afford to eat proper
food, they could win the lottery the next day.
They're going to go to, you know, still eat junk food.
It has nothing to do with what you can afford or not afford, you know.
So it's a state of mind. There's an excuse for everything.
I would suggest that on the other side, if you don't eat clean and know about it
and you still eat pork products, I assure you up to 10 percent of all the pork
you've eaten, if you've been eating pork since the 1980s is human, human flesh
ground up in there for several reasons.
It's a pranking.
You know what I mean? Like they say, let's put some human in there and they're
still going to eat it. Right.
And look at them. You know, it's just another way to, you know, point that the
those that eat it right now, by the way, when you get into Illuminati, high end,
whatever, whatever, whatever, secret society stuff, they that's they use.
They know that the stuff that I'm talking about here with biblical stuff, that's
what they follow, by the way, even when they do a human sacrifice, by the way.
So there is no there is no right or wrong on this.
But I will tell people very often Greek, you know, what about this?
I can't say it's wrong, but I'll definitely tell you it ain't right.
Right. That means it's a moral issue.
It's an ethical issue.
And again, I don't know how to stress this.
If you eat pork products, I assure you, you you've eaten let's say you eat you've
eaten 10 pounds of pork products in the past 10 years.
One pound of that is human flesh.
If you're listening to me or know someone that's still are you OK?
Yeah, most likely you are.
Right. You see, this is the condition you're in right now, by the way, make no
bones about it. It's pretty much out in the open.
Pepsi, Doritos, Frito Lay, they tell you they put aborted fetus tissue in their
food for flavor. It's pretty open.
It's pretty well known. It's actually more than that, more than those two
companies. Yeah, I found that totally bizarre.
Like, what would be the purpose of adding that to a soft drink?
I don't spiritual, spiritual purpose.
The same with the vaccines.
Like I look, I don't talk since if you knew me in the 80s and you asked me to
talk about vaccines now and you took a transcript of what I say now about
vaccines and you took a transcript of what I said in the 1980s about vaccines
and you held the two transcripts up in the light, they would be identical.
I'd be saying exactly the same thing.
So, I mean, don't you get a little tired after a while?
There is no such thing as a vaccine.
You cannot inject because there's you don't have an immune system.
I think I went over that. No one has an immune system.
No one has diabetes.
There's no such thing as blood sugar test.
By the way, people who take blood sugar, by the way, you know, the pancreas,
which is sole cause of diabetes, supposedly do not exist as an organ on their own.
It's like saying you only need one wheel on your car.
The pancreas are part of the liver function, period.
Right. You know, Asian medicine does not consider the pancreas as a separate thing.
It's part of the liver. When you take a blood sugar test, that is purely based on
hydration. Liver takes about three or four.
When you're thirsty, all you need is three ounces to four ounces of water.
You take more than that. Your liver can doesn't do deal much with it, just sits there
for later. So this is very well known, by the way.
You could research it on your own if you're thirsty or dehydrated or you drink water.
It changes the blood sugar.
You know, the little prick, the dot, the blood sugar thing has nothing to do with blood
sugar, has to do with hydration levels and the way your liver is functioning.
They, you know, so we got 50 million people that are diabetic, type one, type two, that's
liver function, purely liver function.
The liver. Yeah.
Oh, you know, when you give chocolate to a dog, it's bad because the liver can't
process it. Right.
It's all liver. Anything you put in your body within three minutes, the liver reacts.
Right. So it's liver function.
So what do you know about liver function?
You know, so, yeah, high blood pressure, the same thing.
And yeah, it's all fiction.
I'd say 90 percent of what the medical community indulges in is pure fiction.
And about 75 percent, I'm not going to say 90 percent of the diagnoses that they give
people are fiction because let's say 20 or 15 percent are emergency medical.
Right. If someone cuts you with a broken bottle, it's hard to misdiagnose that.
Right. So so I'd say 75 percent are misdiagnoses because you got to include some of the
emergency medicine in there.
But it's a it's a big fraud like the money system and the religious system.
And you want to go on the legal systems, complete fraudulent.
So you just happen if you're listening to me, you happen to be on in a world where
they base their stuff around fiction.
You know, I think they have transmissions when they go out from the earth and ETs
pick it up. They don't know what to make or they think we're totally insane.
Some think we should be destroyed.
Other things avoid this place because they think all the I love Lucy shows and CNN
that makes it out there is how we really are.
Right. So they had to put up a secondary beacon satellite to say, if you get any
transmission from earth, don't ignore it because this is all for entertainment.
They have to explain what entertainment means.
Right. So they're not not not much entertainment of that style, I guess, elsewhere
because they don't necessarily understand that that's what it is right away.
Yeah. They don't know what entertainment is because you look when you get down.
Like, for example, I'll say personally, I don't need to be entertained because
anything I do is entertaining.
Yeah. You know what I mean?
When I anything I approach, I approach wholeheartedly with my full mind and desire
to do it. If I see that I can't put my full mind and full desire to engross and
put passion and desire and my skill behind something, I'll just say I'll pass on
that. Why do you it's called.
Otherwise, it's just half fast done.
Right. You got to have your heart into it.
That's why when you and I have a private cause, I don't want to get into making
websites. I don't want to get into doing that.
I mean, I can't do it.
I could do it. It's going to be half fast for me.
I'd rather have someone who could put 100 percent.
Right. You see, I'll tell you right now, if someone if someone says, you want to do
this, I'll look at it. If I can't put 100 percent of my effort in, I don't want to do
it, you know, while I'm doing it.
Right. Right.
OK, so if it doesn't entertain you while you're doing something, then you don't want
to do it. Well, when what I'm trying to say is, is when you put 100 percent of your
effort, skill, love, intuition, desire into what you're doing, the entertainment's built
into that. It's built in.
You know, it's like getting the car with the with all the fancy audio system.
You don't have to put it in later.
I don't have to do something and then entertain myself.
You see, you see.
So when you find yourself in that state where everything is built into what you're
doing, you don't need an extra, you know, entertainment thing.
It's built in. You know, I did not expect you to go in this direction today, but this
is this is very interesting to me, though.
I like this.
OK, so sorry.
I just felt the need to say that.
Natural disease is what I because I wanted to get into that a little bit.
We kind of left I left off sarcastically the last time.
And I just want to finish off a few thoughts.
Well, please do, because look, here's the thing, right, is that we've all been given to
this idea. Look, just naturally occurring.
Certain things are going to happen seasonally.
In fact, they'll tell you that certain things happen during certain seasons.
Right. Because there's greater exposure to pollen and stuff like this.
So via induction.
Right. You're going to breathe some things in.
They're going to get in there.
You're saying a lot, though, there because season and pollen, if pollen was really a
problem, they would build a dome over the city.
So when the pollen came like a bad sandstorm, everybody goes underground.
No, it's not. It's the individual that has that.
I don't have those allergies like my wife does sometimes with certain plants.
And that's because of the energy flow.
I think we got into it in one of the sonics.
Right. Yeah, well, yeah, because but the season has to do with seasonality, not the
season. In other words, eating like if you're eating food, if it's getting cold and
you're eating food that was grown in a warm climate, you're going to your body's going
to lose vacuum because your body is going to be adjusted to the tropical food while
you're living in the cold and vice versa.
If you're in the tropics, you need food that from a cold place, your body's going to
say, hey, what are you doing here?
You know? Yeah, yeah.
But I but I get clogged up with, you know, I mean, not as bad as I used to.
And I got to tell you, if I'm around cats, I can't be around cats.
You lose vacuum. OK, here's the thing.
If you get clogged up, runny nose, weepy eyes, swelling.
Yeah. That means your body.
It's a signal you're losing biological vacuum.
No different. The opposite of that is you got a bicycle or car tire.
You want is kind of low.
It's losing pressure.
Right. It's the same thing.
It's just which direction.
You know, the pressure in the car tires pushing out and the vacuum in the body is
pushing in. Right.
So when you have swelling, you know, if you've ever seen a corpse, human corpse, what
does it look like after a few hours?
It swells up, starts to swell up.
Yeah. Yeah. Because it lost vacuum.
So if you want to know that what a biological vacuum versus no biological vacuum in
this similar body is look at someone laying down in bed that's alive and sleeping and
someone who's been dead for a day.
Big difference. So it's irrefutable.
You know, so that has to do with seasonality.
By the way, the seasonality is vacuum also.
Right. You know, let's go back to car tires.
You know, you want to check your pressure when the tires are warm or hot on a cold day
like you just put, let's say, 75 degrees.
The tires are at 35 degrees, 35 PSI, you know, American metric, American measurement,
let's say, pounds per square inch.
Right. But it's 75 degrees.
But if it goes down to 40 at night, you measure it's 28.
So do you want you don't want to put the right you want to you want to put it let's
say you live in a cold place like Alaska, then it gets a little more tricky.
But still, you don't want to inflate the tires until the temperature is at a higher
mean temperature.
Body is the same.
You know, when you start losing biological vacuum, you go through sleep therapy.
Right. You relax, you stop moving, because if you the body vacuum goes down, you lose
levity, literally levity.
You're not standing up because your feet, you know, you're balancing yourself.
It's because you're actually experiencing slight levitation.
You know, you're if you remove someone's arm, it's about two pounds of bone and meat,
maybe three pounds.
When you're lifting up your arm up and down, do you feel like it weighs like it's
heavy? No. But when people aren't feeling well, they say, oh, my arm feels heavy.
Right. Your whole body feels heavy, you drag it.
Yeah. It's not the muscles that make it feel light.
It's the it's the levitation that you're experiencing.
So so here's a small thing.
If you want to go to advanced aspects of levitation, you know, anti gravity and all, just
study biological vacuum and how you counter that in a direction
where you increase it and increase it mean counter because it does have a limit, you
see. OK, so natural disease, the effects and what causes it, it's it's not
what causes it's the anti cause.
OK, so how did I know this was all fake?
And I've talked about this for a long time, but I'll reiterate, OK, in order to have a
quote unquote pandemic, you have to have a lack of running water.
I don't know how else to say that if you're living in the country, that means if you're
wherever your water source.
Whatever it is, whether it's a well, a stream or a creek or whatever that that goes
away or gets polluted in the city, what would it be either really dirty water
when you open the tap or no water?
OK, once you get into that condition, lack of running water for for hydration
and sanitation for in washing.
Number one. Number two, the waste products, sewage and garbage
is not separated from your main sources and your dwelling.
Right. So if the sewers go down or the garbage,
you know, decay, organic material, mostly animal and other things.
OK, if that's not done properly.
OK, so you have to have the two working together where they had the cholera in London.
Many people died. It's because they started putting new pipes to put taps
in London, but they were running them near the sewer water.
Right. And they would mix sometimes.
So you have to keep them separate.
Right. So if you can't separate the garbage and the sewage from where you live.
And you have no clean and running water, you're going to have, quote unquote, a
pandemic. The other thing is stressing the food supply, low quality food,
which already exists, by the way.
OK, so you have to see the food supply being stressed, stressed.
No lack of running water and and sewage separation and, you know,
presence of waste, human waste, animal waste, whatever, and garbage.
Once you have that, you have all of the not necessarily now, but about you're on your
way to having disease breakout.
OK, it sounds like that causation is a plague, what they used to say.
Sort of. Sort of.
Yeah, they're really bad plagues.
Look, I'll give you a little thing here.
You ever heard a patient zero?
OK, they always play.
OK, this is actually a reality of it.
They very rare to be a patient zero.
You don't even have to show symptoms and you don't have to show that you will
symptoms or be under under the malady or actually suffering the disease.
You know, to be symptomatic, they might say.
Right. C.R.A.
symptomatic and all that.
Now, the way that's done and this I've gotten this also from someone who in East
Germany back when it was it was in East Germany.
I'm going to bring up another East German here because of if we get into a little
more talk. But there was always a really bad stink.
And after East Germany went down, that stink went away in the forest because there
was an underground biolab base and they were doing it properly.
It wasn't like the Wuhan thing with stuff in the freezer with Petri dishes.
What this East German base was doing was the way that pandemics were created all
throughout history. What they did was they would capture humans, prisoners and put
them in cells, either two people or three people or a single with an animal, usually
a bird or rat or other animal.
And no one gets food or water and there's no toilet.
So after a few days or a week, you're so hungry, you kill the animal, whether it's a
rat, a chicken, a bird or a goat, and you eat it.
But remember, you can't wash your hands and you have no toilet.
And they keep this going for about a month or two.
Then you'll notice people start getting really, really sick.
Right. You can't.
Right. So you're in a month's worth of poop with a dead animal.
OK, but then you'll notice most if you have 30 people, you're doing this with
prisoners. It's pretty horrific, by the way.
Yeah. Right.
So you have 30 to 100 people.
You'll notice that most of them die, but there's one or two people who are just
fine. Well, you go up to the guy who's just fine.
Very carefully. You have other people do it.
You give them a toothbrush, a shower and a shirt, some new clothes, some money.
You're free to go.
Maybe some brainwashing, wipe their mind, right?
Some drugs. Free to go.
Go home.
Well, they go home. Everybody's so happy.
Welcome them back.
Suddenly the family starts getting sick.
He's still fine.
And they and their friends and whoever they contact get sick.
They're still fine.
They got patient zero.
I just gave out the whole outline.
There's more to it.
This is how the American army flu started.
You know what they call the Spanish flu, which started in Spain because
they delivered the men to Spain.
It was the only country that would take an American warship back in World War
One, right? Because remember, England was still the enemy back then.
Sort of.
Yeah. And the only reason the American ship was able to land in Spain is
because it said, hey, you remember the Spanish American war?
We'll pay you like two million dollars reparations if you let our ship land.
And it was bad news.
The crew on board, the army knew that it was there was something wrong because
they told everyone on the ship to be unsegregated.
Everybody sleep like what a segregated way.
You know, something's up here. Why are they being why are they doing
unsegregation? Right.
Anyway.
So this is the way the all these the
the Mongols did this in Europe.
They'd go through villages and capture men, women
and children, keep them prisoner.
And they put guinea pigs in cages with them.
And the same scenario.
No food, no water, no toilet.
After about a month or two, everybody's dead except this one little girl or
you know, whatever. A couple of people.
And they dress them up and bring them back to the village where
they came from. You're free to go.
And everybody is so happy that you're back.
Right. Lots of what do they do when they thought you were dead and they
see you? Hugs and kisses.
Hugs and kisses, throw a party, invite neighbors over, right?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. There you go.
Now, this is all by induction.
You could do all the blood tests you want, all the fluid exchange.
Now, if you probably did a fluid exchange with the patient zero, the one who's
transmitting this literally transmitting mean like a radio tower.
This is the mystery of it. But this is not ever taught because it leads to too many
other questions. Like, for example, if you're taking biology class and you
show us, let's say, a slide with the human intestines,
even a microscopic died slide.
If you took a sample of the human intestine and put a dye on it, I don't know if
you guys are familiar with microscopes.
They always everything goes like all fuzzy rainbow colored.
It's kind of hard. So you put a dye in there to blur all that light out.
Right. Even if you did a lung tissue scan or
with your own equipment.
And show that nothing penetrates the intestines or the skin or the lung tissue or
most of the organ tissue or any of the organ tissue, and then showed, you know, a
bicycle tire crossing and see how it's almost the same and say, hey, there's no
absorption going on over here.
Nothing passing through here. It must be through induction of some kind.
Right. This is not difficult to do.
Why? You know, well, once that is taught in school and people start thinking along
those terms and developing the field of study and the science based on induction,
is it really difficult to imagine that disease is
also transmitted that way by induction?
Also, by the way, when you read serious, let's say books, old published stuff,
even new published stuff, reference books on disease, it's not called it's there.
It's called induction anyway.
It's induced.
Yeah. Induced. Right.
Yeah. Yeah. So it's so blatant.
So blatant until, OK, give you an example, there's
Andreas Wecker, W.E.C.K.E.R.
He traffics in essential oils like the best essential oils in the world.
And when I was trafficking water spring to back in the day, we were in the same
place, Rossum, and he's an East German gold medalist gymnast.
OK. And, you know, I went by the Greek or whatever.
And, you know, he's a German.
And we talk a little bit about politics.
How are things there?
He would never want to talk about anything about back home.
And the reason why it was very simple, and neither did other people that were with
him. Anytime you brought up anything, even looking political, he just shut you down.
He said, stop. I said, well, why?
Why don't you want to even talk about it?
Because we don't have a government.
That government that's there is a government that was put in a long time ago, has
nothing to do with us at all.
At all. So he was quite aware and very adamant that he, whatever was being shown,
right. But the Americans are not.
It's just as drastic there as it is here.
The Americans just think that they still have a government.
Like, let's go. Who voted this?
And it doesn't matter. You know, there's nothing to vote for.
There's not. You know what I mean? It's all a big show.
Right. But what I appreciate about Andreas is he was very adamant about zero
discussion until we get something legitimate.
It has nothing to do with who you vote for or what it has to do with after World War
Two, it was replaced with this artificial non-existent entity.
But most people still think they have a government.
But he was very adamant about that.
I've gotten this from a couple of other people.
There is someone also from Russia is very much like that.
Basically, they haven't had a government since before the Bolsheviks.
Very adamant. Doesn't want to talk about anything because it's all like talking
about Mickey Mouse or Disneyland cartoons.
But the Americans are taking it seriously still that they have a government and
this, that and the other. So the interesting thing is what?
From a side note, if you have any political interests or economic or anything
that has to do with quote unquote government and their agencies.
The only way you will see a change is if people completely disregard of what is
existing there as being legitimate in any way.
At all, until that argument or point of view comes up, you're not going to it's
just, you know, fairly fairy tales and fairyland, you know, and the proof I think
I've given in the past, I also gave it on a recent interview.
People were talking about the recent bank failures, the reason being bonds and
Chinese banks and this.
And I'm like, there are no banks to, you know, they're all operating under
emergency. Right now, someone once put put a little thing on me, says we're not
operating under emergency anymore.
I said, yeah, there's been about several acts in the 50s, 60s, 70s and 80s that
were not an emergency anymore.
And the reason why overall is because the people have completely accepted the
system. But in other aspects, they still say we are under emergency indirectly.
Right. You see what I mean?
There's a big there's a big difference.
It still is because, yeah, your evidence, again, that it's all fake is the the US
Treasury says they're twenty three trillion minus.
How are they paying anything?
How can they write?
How could they cut a check for one government employee for a thousand dollars?
How is it possible?
No, we talked about this last time that if you had a bank account of any kind, you
know, the way it was explained to me initially is, look, you can only write a
check if you have the funds in the account to cover the check, to cover it.
That's what you have to do.
So how is it that you can be at a deficit?
If you're at a deficit of ten dollars right now in your bank account, you know,
theoretically, you can't write me a twenty dollar check and have it do anything
other than bounce. Well, no matter what the deficit is, let's say the deficit was
one hundred bucks. If I gave you one hundred bucks, you still can't write a check
because it's not with zero zero.
Right. You have to have.
Yeah. So but but the real thing is there is no debt because there's no way to pay
for it. Number one. Number two, that's just a formality.
And credit card debt is a formality.
Also, you see, it's drunk.
But here's the thing that I haven't I try to bring home to people.
When you get a stimulus check, let's say for a thousand bucks.
Right. It's ten to one fractional.
So really, the bank, when you when you give the check to the bank teller, some
people are going to say, why is he talking about this again?
Because it's important. I want to talk about the third party here, too.
If you get a stimulus check from the U.S.
Treasury for a thousand bucks and you go to the bank, open the envelope and give it
to the teller, she's going to give it back to you, says, I can't do anything with
this. You say why?
Because you have to sign the back once there are two signatures on there.
She has a transaction number and she types in a thousand dollars and the thousand
dollars appears because she can't type anything in until there's two signatures on
there. OK, but behind in the comptroller, the legal department, the bank comptroller,
it's ten to one fractional that thousand dollars becomes nine thousand now because
ten to one, it's not really ten thousand, it's really nine thousand ten.
It's ten to one becomes nine thousand dollars.
So three thousand of that nine.
Well, you get the thousand out of the nine.
So they're left with eight thousand and the eight thousand.
A third of it goes to the Treasury.
Three thousand goes to the Treasury and three thousand goes to the bank.
And the other two thousand just floats around or it's an asset or for whatever on
paper. But it's like an attorney takes a third, the one third in piracy.
Right, right. OK, so that's general.
But the numbers could go back and forth.
All right. So so this is how they're funding stuff.
So this doesn't make any sense to people because they haven't set their mind around
the system. Every country is the same.
All the banks are the same.
All finances are the same.
If you're a government and you want to finance a project that the ledger shows you
don't have the money for, you start giving checks to people and you know that's
whatever amount you give to the people is going to come back nine times and you get
a third of that. You see how it works.
So years ago, I think when Bush was in office, there was somebody saying, go out
and spend and get in debt. We could use the money.
Yeah. Publicly.
They said that. Go shopping.
We can. We need the money.
All right. That was that was a big thing.
And I'll tell you, there's a trend right now of, you know, come and sign up for
these cards.
I don't know if you've seen this online a lot, but they're saying there's all kinds
of programs. You can get money delivered to you every single month if you just sign
up for this card.
Perfect. And there's tons of them like out there now.
Yeah. Remember, the more money is being created, the less money that's in
circulation is going to be worth.
Right. So that's why I tell people, maybe on previous Sonic events, I said, you
know, inflation is kind of low for the amount of credit that's being used.
You're going to get hit with a big inflation boom here soon.
And it didn't happen when I thought it would, like by the 2020, 2019, I said,
ooh, if people if there isn't a big jump in inflation by 2019
or 2020, it's going to get really bad.
And when it gets really bad, you have to at least double your salary.
You know, a lot of things are double the price that they were almost double.
Things that were 15 are now twenty three dollars.
It's not quite or twenty five.
It's not quite double.
So if you're not if your salary and they're doing this deliberately or deliberately to
hurt the population.
Well, this is regional right now.
I've gone over these numbers on other shows of mine where I say, look, they keep
saying that there's this level of inflation and it's B.S.
because depending on where you are, it could be double or two and a half times what
the price was only two years ago.
That is not 40 percent.
That is not 16 percent or whatever percentage you're representing it as.
There is a realistic price increase.
It's eighty one.
Yeah. Someone recently crunched the numbers for me recently, like two months ago.
And he says overall, most goods like from lumber to food to clothing, it's eighty one
percent increase in the past two years.
Price increase. That's that's exactly where I'm coming up to.
That is exactly what I started coming up to as an average of I thought it was about
seventy five percent.
But even even so, I think we're in the same area here.
Yeah. Eighty one percent was what they came up with from lumber to food to clothing
and building materials, cleaners, all that general stuff that gets sold.
Not we're not talking about washing machines and cars and houses.
No, no, no. Commonplace daily items, daily requirements, let's say for your basic
requirements, food, shelter, food, shelter, clothing.
Right. If you take a look at those things.
Well, yeah, I was thinking seventy five.
But then again, I'm not a mathematician.
Yeah, they did the math and it came out to eighty one point six nine whatever percent.
And yeah, yeah, it's about right.
This is just from two years ago, three months ago.
Now, in other words. Absolutely.
I believe that. I absolutely believe that number.
Yeah. OK, so and essentially, so when everything goes up 80 percent, how many people
salary going to go up 80 percent?
The most they're going to get is five percent.
Right. Yeah. Well, that was the so that's right.
So that's how that's how that works.
So and at the same time, I'm working on starting a high end speaker company where a
pair of bookshelf speakers are ten thousand to fifteen thousand.
And these are like the size that if you go to Best Buy, you get a pair for fifty bucks
right now, real small speakers, you know, like tabletop.
And I found out that that market is never going to be hurt.
You know, OK, so it's very interesting to be in that market, by the way, because, for
example, if I build these bookshelf speakers and I have a way to create sound that no
one else can, let's say messing around with the laws of physics, even though they're
small bookshelf speakers, they sound the full output of the floor tower speakers, but
very, very high definition.
The interesting thing is I have these small units that I'm building with the packaging
material. The way you have to the packaging is very expensive.
You know, if you're going to sell a pair of speakers to someone for ten thousand or
fifteen thousand dollars, let's say the you can't just throw them in a cardboard box
with some peanuts, you know, packing peanuts.
Right. So they each have to be in a separate case.
And that goes into another case which goes into a double box.
And then, yeah, it gets very interesting.
And the packaging gets actually almost as expensive as the materials.
Well, not really, but to build these things.
So so what I'm on a side note, I'm suggesting when things go bad, focus on the high end
economy, but not as a servant.
You know, if you're a maid for like Donald Trump or Rockefeller, you still get paid
minimum wage. You know that, right?
No. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah. You don't just because you're made for a billionaire doesn't mean you're going to,
you know. So, yeah, but providing their stuff, you know, I also might want to get into
selling, you know, fifty dollar a liter, a bottle of water to them.
Right. You know, because believe it or not, when it gets because when the inflation goes
up, they're on the front end, they're going to dip, they're going to get wealthier and
wealthier. Sorry to say.
You know, so that's what's happened even in the publicly observed numbers, right, where
they say that what a new billionaire was created like every day for about a year during
this, you know, pandemic, when you see all these small businesses went out of again the
pandemic. I'm using that.
But you know what I'm talking about, the time period where you had all these shutdowns
and lockdowns, et cetera, a whole lot of small businesses went out.
They were gone. But that's the idea.
That's well, that's where the inflation comes in.
Give you an example. When the Walmarts come in on the targets, the Home Depot's, the
small stores go out of business eventually.
Not all of them, but mostly they do.
Now, when I went to an AutoZone or a Walmart or Home Depot, they would raise the prices
exactly what the Federal Reserve Index was overnight.
So I bought like a roll of some damping material.
And let's say at Home Depot was twelve dollars.
The next day it was fifteen dollars.
The week after it's nineteen dollars.
Right. But if I go to the hardware store, initially it was twelve dollars, but it's
still twelve dollars. They haven't raised their prices.
It was expensive before, more expensive than Home Depot.
But they're not adjusting.
So your main your large circuit, what do you call those big chain stores, big box
store, big box stores, all of them, whether it's automotive, house, food or whatever,
even a Walmart is attached to the Federal Reserve.
They change their prices on the fly where the little mom and pops don't.
If they have the inventory, they'll say, hey, we paid 40 cents for this.
Selling it for a dollar is fine.
Well, Walmart paid 40 cents for it.
They sold it for seventy five cents.
But now it's a dollar fifty.
Right. Right. So so what I want to say was what I was saying twenty five years ago or
more, avoid the chain stores if you can support local business.
Doug, that's such a cliche.
Well, here you go.
This is why you do it. Right.
Another example, like spark plugs I was getting for three bucks are now eleven bucks
at AutoZone. How can you go from three dollars to eleven dollars in one year where at
the small mom and pop auto shop there were five dollars, not three dollars.
So I didn't go there. But now there's still five dollars or six dollars, not eleven.
You see. Right.
So there's this interesting thing.
But I tell people, if you don't find a way to double your salary in the next year, I
think we said it on one of the open.
You're going to you're not going to be able to live the way you're living, depending
on how much you're making, of course.
But you see, no one's going to get their salary double, by the way.
So, yeah, I don't I don't see that.
I mean, I know a lot of people talked about the raise in minimum wage and this and
that. But truthfully, that's not panning out.
We know it's got to be minimum wage.
There's got to be just under 30 bucks an hour, like twenty five to thirty bucks an
hour to.
Yeah, because when the minimum wage first came out, it was just a little bit over the
price of silver. So the price of silver now is around twenty dollars an ounce per
hour. So you have to be over twenty three or twenty four dollars an hour to be a
minimum wage comparable to what you could buy in the 70s.
Right. Give you an example.
So, yeah. So, yeah, the fifteen dollars at McDonald's ain't cutting it or whatever.
So, yeah, it's it's a you know.
I used to use the 1968 index, which would give you that approximately a couple of
years ago. Anyway, the exact number was twenty five dollars.
Now it's up. But either way, you're right on target.
If you use the 1968 number and you just adjust for inflation, that's it done.
An easy way I tell people if they if they work by time, by the hour, just a dollar a
minute. That's the easiest thing to remember.
Right. So an hour is 60 bucks an hour.
Right. That seems to be prevailing.
Someone pulling wire in California, the prevailing wages around that a dollar a
minute, you know, to pull wire through a building for an electrical company.
They get a dollar a minute.
Well, I told people a dollar a minute's a fair a fair wage if you're working.
Right. It is. Well, look, it is.
But but where can you get that again?
You know. Well, you find it.
You make it happen. Yeah, somehow.
Yeah. Where? Where?
What? That's the big question at all.
As long as it doesn't lead to your death, as they tell people, most of the stuff, the
information that we're given that doesn't lead directly to your death, but it's always
these big things that you'll probably end up dying happen.
You'll probably end up dying before most of these things happen.
Right. You know, especially if you look at all the spiritual advice and all the health
advice, you'll die before that happens.
Right. So that's why I call like leading to death advice.
You know, most people don't get practical stuff.
That's why I've always been talking about food, clothing, shelter and all this other
stuff. Focus on that.
You know, this has been a very practical discussion so far, but I know you wanted to
get into, you know, the third person aspect of this.
Now, I had a thought about it when you were we discussed this just a little bit before
we started recording, you know, and I was thinking to myself, royalty in the way that
they refer to themselves or the way they used to, you know, we are the queen or we are
the king or whatever.
This third person thing, right.
A lot of people think of that as an egomaniacal weirdness where somebody refers to
themselves in the third person and all that.
But you had something to say.
That's the high. Yeah, good.
Yeah. People of high spiritual standing always do that.
Also, you'll see it in the legal and also you'll see it in formal language use.
Like just real quick, anybody can sense this by looking up or remembering it.
When you read what the Christ said in the New Testament, for example, he always
referred to himself in a third person.
An example would be when you see the son of man coming down from the clouds, he's
referring to himself.
Always speak to the third person.
If you read any of the ancient texts that were either the being or the person
speaking verbatim in their speech, they're referring to themselves in the third
person always.
And this is usually of higher spiritual nature.
People tend to do that.
Why? Because when you are of higher spiritual nature, you know that you're occupying
this body, the container, right?
You are not the body.
Right. This is sounds cliche.
So you happen to be using it like when people say like when I nearly chopped the
thumb off, I said I didn't chop my thumb, nearly chopped my thumb off.
I'm just using this thumb.
So more accurately, the thumb on the left hand, not my left hand.
Right. You see.
So this is something that once you start, it will cultivate a certain level of
spirituality or your mind in you, and it'll make you more objective and you'll be
able to easily see through things that you weren't able to see through before.
If you start to seeing yourself occupying anything that you're doing as a visitor,
as a sojourner, as you're just using it, not not owning it.
Right. Kind of an example.
For example, if you go into certain languages in a highly respectful form, instead
of in Spanish, it would be Ustedes, which is plural for Usted means you.
So when you're asking someone, how are you, you in a very high form, Ustedes is
plural, like how you's doing, like you guys doing, but it's just one.
And in Greek, instead of saying Ustedes, which is or Ustedes is to one, you would
say Ustedes as in plural.
So when you're referring to someone else in the high formal Latin and in Greek,
the you're you're addressing who you're speaking to in a plural form as if there's
more than one person there.
You see, that is another form of third party.
Yeah. I was just going to mention that.
I mean, I have a bit of a grasp of Latin and I know that that's in the more proper
form of Latin. That's how you address.
It's a high form.
Yeah. The singular is proper in Vietnamese.
It would be also like you would say when you're addressing.
In Vietnamese, it would one individual of respect, it would be Cuivi, which would be
the plural form again.
So you'll see this. It's a high like there's high in Spanish, high Latin, high
English. Right.
You'll find it.
So not only referring to yourself as in the third person, but also to others in a
plural form that gets a little sketchy unless it's already part of the culture.
Right. So like in Greek or in Latin or other languages, I'm not familiar with the
cognates in Chinese.
I'm familiar with some of it in Korean, the Jean-Baptiste in the Hangul.
But I think Jean-Baptiste also is almost a third person.
If anyone speaks Korean, let me know.
But I haven't practiced that in a long time.
The other thing, as I suggest people, if it's a sign of respect when you're going to
be interacting with someone where English is or whatever language is their second
language, when you learn their core language, you can also use certain terms not to
play to be placating or flattering, but just to show out of respect.
Like if a foreign dignitary was sending someone to another country, right, you want
to send someone who speaks the language.
Right. Usually.
Of course. Yeah.
Yeah. So this is the same.
It's out of respect. Right.
Americans tend to be the worst.
I've seen this before, even since I was young.
You're an American now. You got to speak English.
Right. You've probably heard that yourself.
Right. Of course.
Yeah. So yeah, there's a term called the ugly American is what they were known
as in Europe, mostly back in when I remember the 70s, 80s and 90s, because they
always demanded everything be their way.
But that's another discussion.
But once you start referring to things in the third party, then you start to see how
presumptuous this world is.
You also learn a lot.
This is the important part from those around you.
When you start hearing people say this is my or my thing or my this or my that or my
leg, my website, my foot, my car, my, my, my, my.
Guess what, from a spiritual level, let's say from one to ten, ten would be like, you
know, a Christ type figure and one would be your dog, you know, halfway a number five
would be someone who starts to discern.
Not everything is mine, but once you once you the more mys you hear my this, my that,
my thumb, my hair, my car, my this, my that, that number goes down and down and down and
down and down. Right.
In terms of rating them spiritually, if you can get half of your discussion instead of
my hair, the hair, I know it gets kind of it's odd.
Right. Instead of my thumb, the thumb.
Right. What do you mean the thumb?
The thumb I'm using.
Right. If you can do 50 50, you'll be halfway spiritually evolved.
You know what I mean? Like half you'll start getting it.
And it's really hard when when you anyone comes across a certain methodology or
perspective or an idea, it's very foreign in the beginning.
And there's always doubt that says, well, I'm not going to do that or I can't do that.
Or how funny is it?
Will it be if I start doing that?
Try it. I highly suggest people to start lending things into the third category.
This is how the legal system works, by the way.
This is how many of the high spiritual, let's say, beings that we can access what
supposedly they said, it'll always be in the third person.
You see, I've always wondered about this myself because, you know, I've always found it
strange that people feel as though they can take ownership of anything because you don't
really actually own much.
No, you know, like in other words, everything is very temporary.
Your entire time where you're occupying the container is very temporary, very temporary.
And you may have control over certain things.
Right. But you don't really own them.
I've always felt out about ownership.
Well, this is that's many levels to ownership, you know.
Uh, OK, well, if you say you own your body, well, all the legal paperwork says you don't.
OK, when you go to court, your name is always in all the name you're using, the sound
that you answer to.
That's all a name is, right, is always in all caps because you're collateral for that
all caps right now.
They'll deny it because, you know, there is supposed to be an adversary.
They're a private group there.
The legal system in every country is there to administer the bankruptcy.
Right. Doesn't matter which country you're in.
My praise goes to like the East Congo, Somalia, Darfur, places like that, you know,
where at least you have local warlords, you know, and they'll behead any missionaries
that come through there, that kind of stuff.
They're pretty hardcore about understanding.
And the reason I have them in praise is this.
You can claim ownership, let's say, with land or anything like that.
That's fine. Anybody can do it.
But you cannot really back that up unless you can defend it.
Right. Right.
Are you going to. So if you want to know who owns the land you're on.
Well, you got the police there to defend for who.
Right. No.
Yeah. You see in the fire department and all that stuff.
They they work for those that supposedly.
But they'll never tell you directly.
They own it. But they are the agency, for example.
So, like, you know, most people don't understand there's no private ownership of
land. Now you can get away from all the taxes and fees if you just use the law with
the law, says, for example, in the US, everybody talks about property taxes.
Right. Well, first of all, all the laws on property tax says that it's for profit.
Right. So let me ask you, if the property is used for profit, it's a residence.
Now, you know what a residence is.
You're a resident in a hotel, a prison hospital.
Right. Somewhere where you live, where you are staying, where you are.
Right. Staying temporarily.
You have no claim, no claim to.
You're not an inhabitant.
The law doesn't have inhabitant anywhere.
It doesn't say people, it says resident.
So and it has to be.
And if it's used for profit.
So let me ask you where you eat, sleep, wash, fuck, do all these other things right in
that building. Are you doing that or any of that for profit?
No. And so that means you're not.
Are you an inhabitant? Yes.
Are you a people? Yeah. Show me in the law where it says people and inhabitants where
they eat, sleep, shit, you know, and all that stuff has to pay.
They don't. It's very simple.
It's for taxation.
I mean, it's for you're making a profit.
And someone I was working with on recently said, what about for what if I'm renting
out the house and I'm subject to the property?
I said, no, because it's a private contract and you have a right to personal.
It's in all the laws you to all your what is it called?
Personal effects and papers.
Yeah. Privacy. Right.
Yeah. Fourth Amendment.
So, yeah.
So you're not this is a private contract.
So buzz off. Right.
You see. So there's no tax on that either, because all of his rental, you have to.
Well, if you report it as a public part of the.
OK. And by the way, well, you know, then how are the municipalities going to function
about the property tax so they could just print all the money they want?
All right. You don't need taxes.
Don't pay for anything. I'm not against tax.
Just like I'm not against if I need a hammer to break a sidewalk.
I have a rotary hammer, a jackhammer.
It's too small. It won't go through four inches.
I got to go rent one. Right.
A big one, like an 80 pounder.
OK. Do I expect to go rent and use the store's jackhammer and get it and bring it back
and wave goodbye and leave and that's it?
Or do I have to pay him a rental fee?
You're saying let's pay a rental fee.
That's what taxes are. You have to report or they assess you.
You know, we assess this property is that much you're using.
You know, and, you know, we claim on and they can never say they claim.
It's just ambiguous.
But while everything is ambiguous, let's see what we can get.
It's very interesting how it works.
It's all presumption, all third party.
You know, if you go to a municipality or city and say, why are you taxing?
He says the state gives us that authority.
So then you go to the state.
Why are you taxing? He says, we're not taxing you.
The city gives you gives you the authority.
And you go back and forth passing the buck.
Right. Because no one can.
So but they can make your life very difficult because that's what they're here for.
You see, it's not here to be easy.
Yeah. Without compliance, you will have difficulty.
That's for sure. Yeah.
No. Well, no, you are compliant.
Even if you say I'm not subject to that, you're still complying.
It depends, you know, you're complying to because you don't fall under that category.
Right. No. OK.
OK. I get you. Yeah.
Like if I don't like I don't work at Dunkin Donuts.
So no, someone can't knock on my door and say, you didn't comply to your work contract.
You didn't show up. I never had a contract to work with you guys.
But the guy who's who's fell asleep late, the Dunkin Donuts manager come to his house.
Hey, you got a work contract with us.
You're not complying. You got to come to work.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, that's right.
So it's all propaganda and brainwashing.
But it's it's pretty rough place, you know.
Look, at least you're not under the Vatican, you know, directly.
Oh, no, not directly.
The horror stories, you know.
Although they did declare at one point that every soul on Earth belonged to them.
Right. Yeah.
But they can't prove it.
All they have to do is put out the presumption and you got a billion people out there that
believe it. Yeah, this is this is the type of places.
But the third party also, it'll all be it'll all be third party.
All your legal stuff is presumption.
And it's a fiction.
Actually, you could look up legal fiction in a browser.
And it'll basically tell you everything and anything legal is a fiction.
Yeah, of course.
Yeah. Well, people say, you know, legal or illegal, who cares?
That's just a sick bird, right?
No, I know that's the concept you were you were you know, when you when you brought up
the name in all caps, I was thinking about the concept of legal fictions and and so on
and so forth, because that's really what they're what they're dealing with with that
administration is the legal fiction.
You show up, you answer for it.
You're agreeing to come, you know, to to deal with that particular element, which is
not you, although it's got the same name, the same sound that you answer to.
Right. And they can't address it.
They just make fun of you.
But here's the thing.
This came this is also a big proponent of what happened in the Nuremberg trials.
So remember, everything is acting under a state of emergency.
Everything's temporary goes day to day to day.
That's why if you go down to the court buildings, all they're not judges.
Interim judges, temporary, all of it is.
OK, that's why even the POTUS, he's the current acting POTUS, right?
The current acting one.
They can never say he is the president, right?
He is the current acting current elected something, right?
Everything is temporary.
So what they got out of the Nuremberg trials is this, that in the future, if everything
is corrected and brought back to being lawful and they pull out all the paperwork and they
said, well, you unlawfully imprisoned these people.
They'll say, no, we didn't.
We just went after this trust name that we had registered, Department of Health and
Human Services, and they just volunteered for the rest.
But but because you have no enforcement authority now, if you try to say that now, they'll
laugh at you and whatever, right?
See, because it all boils down to enforcement.
So, you know, there is no lawful enforcement, right?
In other words, if, you know, 90 percent, if not better, of the people in prison or
a jail or they are illegally and unlawfully, right?
So but the other thing is, do you want them all out back into society, right?
But this is not the point where whether they did something bad that could be harmful to
society.
But once you're in there long enough, what happens to the individuals?
You see, so yeah, once you're conditioned to that, I mean, I know nobody comes out better
after a long stay.
I'll put it that way.
But for sure, the only people right now based on the system and people don't even know
the difference between jail and prison.
A jail is there to protect people.
A prison is there for sentencing, but a lawful society doesn't have prisons.
OK, what is a jail when there's a big bar fight?
Everyone goes to jail because if they don't, they'll be the violence will continue.
Right.
Everyone gets arrested and while you're in jail, they get everybody's story and they
could make a legal determination at that point who they should let go and who they should
hold for a little longer.
Right.
OK.
All right.
So when the accused is found guilty by confession or otherwise, they're sentenced to prison.
But legally, they're bonded.
And that's what funds your streets, by the way.
It doesn't say thank you for your taxes.
You ever see when they put up a new road or something, it's your taxes that pay for
this.
No, it's the bonds, birth certificates and prison bonds.
It's funny, I used to call and say, yeah, you got this sign here.
And in order for them to put it up, it has to have a registration number that they put
the sign up.
I said, this sign number so and so.
What do you mean by bonds?
Can you define them?
It took me three months in a run around, run around, run around, run around.
No.
OK, so.
So in a lawful society, there's no prison.
Why?
Well, very simple.
If you stole, it's three times or twice.
You have to pay back to who you stole from the value.
Right.
But but the reason the person stole is because they had no money.
That's OK.
You work it off.
They become your servant at an agreed price for X amount of time.
You see, or quote, unquote, slave or whatever, you know, you have to pay for it that way.
If you kill deliberately, you're put to death.
If you killed by accident, let's say what they call second or third degree, you can
no longer live in that city.
You have to go to another city.
And if you ever leave that city and you're hunted down by the people that think you should
be killed and you're not in that city, sorry, you can't be you're not protected.
You see, it's called a city of refuge.
And this goes on and on these.
So there's no prison.
There's no allotment for prison in a lawful society.
But a legal society loves it because they're bonding everyone, you know, prison bonds.
So what what I'm saying can easily be validated and verified.
And I think I've gone over the police there.
The police work for the private banks, all of them, whether you like it or not.
Sorry.
The sheriff works for the state or the county.
And the only arresting or fine levying by law power they have is for littering.
The sheriff can only write a ticket for littering.
Sorry.
In law, in their own paperwork.
It's actually was on a Wikipedia page.
When you look up the sheriff's duties, we talked about a little bit of the history.
This is, by the way, they can only arrest or write fines for littering.
It was on a Wikipedia up until recently.
I think I made it kind of a stink about it.
Someone said he got a speeding ticket by the sheriff.
I said, so tear it up, throw it away.
He has no.
But you see, when you get the ticket, it has everything on their federal, state, local,
blah, blah, blah.
Right.
So it's very interesting how the system works.
It's the same system that people think planes went into the World Trade Center like a hot
knife through butter, like what was her name?
The stewardess came out a while back.
She used to say that a lot.
Do you remember her, Rebecca something?
Oh, yeah.
Rebecca Roth.
Yeah, yeah.
She used to.
I like what she said.
Something was wrong here when I saw.
But here, take a subculture.
You know, if you took the people that work in the airlines, the stewardess, the pilots,
the mechanics and all that, how many of them came out and made a stink about what happened?
Very few, not any.
Yeah, so when you say the entire collective is useless, within the collective, there are
other societies, you know, like let's say the people that work in the airline industry
is like a subculture.
How many of them came out and made a stink?
There's like, what, half a million of them?
How many?
Is this her?
So it doesn't show very well for any human.
Small organization.
What was it?
Pilots for 9-11 Truth or whatever.
They came out and had questions and, you know, various.
Yeah, very.
And then you have Dmitry, poor Dmitry Kalozov.
I'll spell it for you.
Dmitry Kalozov, the K-H-A-L-E-Z-O-V, I believe.
He's right on the money.
And when I first heard his testimony on that, it kind of shook me to the bone because I
told people around me, I was told there were nukes in the World Trade Center back in the
80s, but I didn't know what the hell that meant.
I didn't know it was for demolition.
I thought it was that big ball in the middle of the courtyard between the two buildings.
You know, I had no idea.
But it kind of shook me to the bone when, you know, you have a premonition or told something
and then it happens in the future.
So I think just to bring it back to where we started, we started off with the Project
Blue Beam and all that.
And you see how much headway that's made still is being talked about.
But no one's being rational about it.
They don't have to do holograms.
All they have to do is put some CGI on TV and everyone will buy it that way.
Meaning, you know, everyone won't believe.
What is it?
You can fool some of the people some of the time and not all the people all the time.
You got to break it down even better than that.
They're going to fool enough people that it's made.
So, right.
Well, that's the thing is if you've got a strong enough group, you know, not a majority
necessarily, but if you have a significant minority, that's enough to sway everybody.
Pretty much right.
They're convinced.
I mean, that's all there is to it.
Yeah.
And they're not even putting out quality product when they when they do show whether it's the
World Trade Center or the future alien invasion.
It's going to be really cheesy CGI.
I mean, not so cheesy that you can see the pixels and segments, you know, but really
cheesy because everything they do is really cheesy because they usually hire Muppets.
They don't, you know, they don't really.
It's funny.
You know, you'd think they have all the resources in the world, but they put out junk.
The easiest thing is the financial and the legal situation.
You know, go look at the treasury again.
Any treasury is all in the minus.
How could they how could you work for any government and get a check and be good because
you're funding it yourself.
By the way, when you get a paycheck, that's a that's a rain check.
You know, it's a paycheck.
It's not getting paid.
Right.
And when you go and cash that paycheck, that money is the funds that you get, let's say,
is created with your own signature.
But they go back to your boss's account and take it out of his account to make it look
like, you know, right.
And that money is still in your boss's account.
He just doesn't know how to get it.
And if you try to get it, they close your bank account.
Right.
So this is the society that the only way to fix it is to physically remove the people
involved in the system and the system being physically remove them from the world.
You cannot, you know, let them be because they'll just come around and create another
crisis and restart the whole thing again as it's been done over and I'll just keep doing
it.
Well, yeah, we're good, I think for now.
That's what I was just about to say.
I was thinking to myself, you know, you've come full circle in this one and I've got
some interesting ideas for next time.
But but wow, a lot to think about here today.
So you want to you want to close it with anything else or should we just leave it there?
We'll just leave it there.