Sonic Event 28, Ocelli in the Greek, rated Y.
Yeah, I still keep announcing that at the beginning, whatever.
Here we are once again, and I appreciate you guys for tuning in and doing so and all that.
I did get a note about the Chatango, and I will go through your comments and suggestion, I guess, that's included in that note.
Just to let you guys know, I do read the emails when you send them, and you can do that by clicking on the email logo or whatever it is,
the icon on my website if you want, and email me directly, or send to blindjfkresearcher at gmail.com.
That's my personal email, and if there are questions, comments, or concerns, I do read them all.
Anyways, getting to what else is happening.
There's things going on in the chat, and I've got to start where I've got to start.
Greek, how are you doing tonight?
I'm doing all right.
I just want to mention I'm staring at the monitor.
I just got the date up, just the home page, and we're going on the first day of the fourth month, and I see 6-3-23.
So for the Pope's work schedule, it's the third or the fourth or the third, right?
And you can see the time drift.
It's not that much, three, four days?
Yeah, it's still pretty tight.
It's close.
It's still pretty tight.
I mean, at one point, we were kind of close to lawful time.
They did cross over.
They kind of converged, right?
Yeah, well, two months, most three months out of the year, they get really close, and they drift again.
But that's not the point.
The point is, you know, why, you know?
Well, here's the other thing.
The months always tend to lean towards starting around a full moon anyway, so there's your hint, right?
There you go.
So, yeah.
Yeah, you mentioned in the chat not a lot of stuff about other things other than water.
I try to be active in there.
I've been going to the laptop or the computer often lately for reference materials, like looking at just reference stuff, you know,
different schedules in terms of, like, industrial stuff, you know, materials,
and I'll check the chat while I'm sitting down looking at –
I don't know if anybody's familiar with McMaster Car.
It's an industrial supply warehouse, and they sell to anyone.
They have everything there.
So let's say you imagine some kind of material like, you know, foam, you know, like the foam in a mattress or, you know, foam, whatever.
Let's say you wanted to get some foam.
Instead of made out of urethane stuff, you wanted it made out of aluminum.
Take aluminum foam.
You go to McMaster Car, aluminum foam.
Holy shit.
They got four different sizes.
You're like, which one do you want?
I'm like, oh, my gosh, you know.
You know what I mean?
Right.
They've got everything.
So just when I say references, you know, I just put – give you an example of what I mean.
Right.
I mean, unless you're going to forge metal and things for yourself, I mean, you're going to have to go for supplies somewhere.
I mean, you were talking about that place with the wire, what, a couple of weeks ago, I guess it was, where you had to go to get the silver, right?
Oh, yeah.
Well, that's the funny thing.
You'd think it would be something common.
It's hard to find.
I think there's maybe – well, there's a dozen places that talk about it, but you can't get it from them.
Right.
Well, and isn't that the way it goes?
You know, people talk about a lot of things, but you can't actually get the good information from them
or the good whatever material from them.
It's just the way of the world, it seems like.
Even if they're talking about it, they don't have it, right?
Sure, yeah.
But it's back to the – well, yeah, do you know the Sears catalog?
You ever heard of that?
Oh, yeah, of course.
Yeah.
You could even buy a house, right?
You could at one point, yeah.
On the Sears catalog, right, through the Craftsman.
They're quite popular.
Oh, yeah, well, that was the whole tools and everything.
Everything was great with that.
I like the Craftsman tools, actually.
Yeah, but just anything.
If you look at a Sears catalog, you buy anything and everything there, right?
And it was mail order.
Well, we kind of went back to it with the internet, right, buying stuff online.
Because prior to the – well, prior to the Sears catalog, it was walk-in places.
And then the Sears catalog comes along, and you could buy a house from a catalog,
and they'd ship it to you in truckloads.
And then it went to walk-in places again, and as the Sears catalog lost popularity, right?
And the Sears catalog gained popularity through the Midwest and not so much in the cities
or the expanding, the westward expansion that was continuing until the early 1900s.
You know, you hear about the westward expansion in the U.S.
What did L.A. look like in, like, 1902, 1910, 1915?
Like, nothing, right?
What was the movie, Chinatown with Jack Nicholson?
Yeah.
About the water company in the – what was that, 30s or 40s?
Well, there's that, and there's also the famous films.
I mean, look, San Francisco is a well-developed place now,
but if you look at that earthquake from the early part of the 20th century
and you take a look at the development of what is considered to be a fairly major city,
it's still dirt roads and stuff, you know?
Oh, yeah.
It's the beginning of the century.
Yeah, so there was a westward – yeah, I like, again, I don't endorse him,
but Archaics gets to a lot of the stuff.
His narrative starts to fall apart if you try to study a lot of the things that he does,
but he's done a really good service by putting out the repeating disasters.
Also, there's a sense of, you know, when you look at the world's fairs,
this has been going on for a long time,
but even as a child when I was made aware of world fairs
and how elaborate they were, right, in the 1800s,
and it's like what the hell happened, you know?
Why did everything get so plain?
And I guess in Forest Hills, Queens, the last world's fair I think they did,
you know, with the big, huge stainless steel globes and all that.
Right, right.
That was probably the last time they made some kind of elaborate presentation.
But, yeah, I posted some things in the chat,
and mostly it's been about the water stuff.
I'm coming up with a term.
By the way, if you're listening to me, you're a sub most likely,
and you are being made loosely a party or privy to what I'm working on.
And it's very, very – by the way, it's – what would you call it?
It's very rarefied, disruptive, and proprietary, okay,
because this is very, very unique.
But here's the thing.
I have firsthand experience with this.
Let's say you're working on something that is very unique.
Let's say – okay, let's just make it a little more to the point.
Let's say you're working on anti-gravity and you build a small flying saucer, right?
Okay.
And let's say you're in a place where they won't shut you down.
So you call up Raytheon or all these other companies,
and they send someone over.
You tell them you've got anti-gravity or whatever.
And they're going to send someone over that's just not somebody.
It's like in the police they have detectives, right?
And detectives are like the best liars.
If you're in the law enforcement and you're a really good liar,
they make you a detective, right, because you have to show a certain side.
Like what do you want them – what are we going to do?
What are we going to show?
So anyways, let's say you've got this flying saucer and you call Raytheon or whatever,
and they send people over to look at it.
They're going to act like they don't know anything, right, even though they have it.
They have this technology.
Yeah, they know it backwards and forwards, but they're going to act like, oh, gee, that's interesting.
Sure, explain it to me.
How did you come up with that?
I've never seen this before.
So when I say there's disruption and proprietary and really next-level stuff,
all of it already exists.
It's just not for us poor saps, right?
Right.
So, yeah.
By the way, for those interested, I noticed in the chat many people are getting into the magnetic stuff.
It's actually a lot of people are getting a lot of correspondence about magnetic water,
and occasionally I kind of sound like a prick, but I don't mean to,
and say, you know, it's not really magnetic water.
It's actually anti-magnetic because we're running the water where there is no magnetism in common parlance, right?
It's where if you give a magnet to anyone and say, show me where the magnetism is, all right, you sure about that?
Okay, great.
It's not that they're wrong, but we run the water where you sense no magnetism.
That's where it goes, right?
Backwards, right?
I mean, there's a lot of social moral statements about that, right?
If you do what everybody else is not doing, you're probably better off, right?
Of course.
So it's very much like that.
So just a public announcement.
Right now it's getting to the point where I'm starting to name it,
and one thing I'm thinking of is a biased magnetic distillation.
Biasing means to push forward in a certain direction or lay down an undercurrent magnetic,
which it's not biasing, it's not magnetic, and it's not distillation, which is little droplets falling.
But that's how things work.
Kind of like Federal Reserve is not federal and has no reserves,
but biased magnetic distiller or distillation sounds, ooh, wow.
It sounds like you might get invited to a really good party one day, you know?
Absolutely.
But anyway.
So, yeah, you mentioned something about an e-mail about mind, Silva, and all this stuff.
Oh, yeah.
Well, you know, because a few sonic events back you had talked about taking the concept of mind control
and applying it to yourself.
Right.
And this is, of course, common theme, you know, uncommon in general,
but a common theme among people that try to speak about uncommon things.
And, you know, they talk about mind control.
A lot of people do that.
Now, that's way common.
And they talk about, you know, the CIA and your MK ultras and stuff like that.
Negative effects.
Right.
There's also an industry out there, though, where it's sort of like the self-driven mind control,
like, you know, oh, get into the secret, right?
Like the secret was a huge thing for a while.
Oh, just, you know, positive.
What was that positive?
If you envision something in a positive way, you know, then therefore it will happen, this kind of thing.
All right.
Well, somebody sent me a bit of a message about this Silva method, this guy Jose Silva,
who I'm only vaguely familiar with, and I'm not familiar with the particulars on it,
but I know that this is one of those methodologies that, you know, sometimes people end up grabbing
and, you know, turning it into a guru cottage business kind of thing.
And I know that that's got to be what it is, but I've heard about this enough
that I'm thinking there might be something to it.
And I was just wondering if you had any familiarity.
I'll give a few analogies on that.
Mind control, how it's done and by who is just like agriculture.
It differs in different parts of the world, right?
Study agriculture in different parts of the world, and they have certain things in common,
like planting and rows usually and things like that, but it's very different, right?
So, you know, cultivate the mind, no pun intended.
So it's kind of like agriculture.
Who's doing it right?
Who's doing it wrong?
Nobody or everybody.
You know, in other words, it depends on the terrain.
It depends on what you're growing, right?
So if you look at agriculture in Vietnam or China,
it's very different than agriculture in Kentucky or in Ukraine.
Well, much like I've said, when it comes to mind stuff,
I've said this about, like, say, Alcoholics Anonymous, right,
where I find it to be completely stupid.
That's a cult.
And it is a cult.
And it's self-admitted, yeah.
It is a cult, but here's the thing.
If somebody takes that and applies it and it improves their life,
I have no argument.
You know what I'm saying?
Well, okay, this gets into relationships also.
They keep making you admit that you're an alcoholic and you're a piece of shit, right?
So they're telling you, you join us and this is how you're going to do business with your life.
So whenever you get into a situation, like here,
I had some neighbors arguing a while back.
She goes, if you don't like it, leave.
And I'm like, oh, she's telling them how she likes to do business.
So in other words, what I mean by that is, like, if two people are trying to work something out,
well, you meet in the middle, you compromise.
One might have to compromise.
One might have to learn a little more.
And you make adjustments, you know?
But when somebody says, if you don't like it, leave,
what they're telling you is, this is how I do business.
Fuck you, right?
Right.
You get it?
So whenever I hear somebody say, well, if you don't like it, leave or whatever,
it's like, oh, look, she's telling them how she does business, right?
And what I mean, how you do business, that means that you're planning on sticking with that model, right?
You know what I mean?
You're not going to change.
So I like to take common things the way people use them and don't think about how they're using them.
They're usually emotionally based.
And I like to translate them into English to be easier to understand.
You know what I mean?
So it helps.
It helps those that are especially watching.
When you're in the middle of it, it's kind of hard to get it.
So next time someone says, if you don't like it, leave, that means that's how I do business.
Screw you, right?
So it's not a matter that they can't change or won't change.
That's how they do business.
In other words, this is what they're happy with.
Right.
So this goes on and on.
The same with all of this stuff.
Going back to, I don't know if I went off on a tangent, but we're still on the mind control aspect of it.
Silva, okay, here's the thing.
I don't know if I should give the analog or the analogy or talk about Silva first.
I'll do them at the same time.
I'll talk about Silva first.
He discovered that there is a state in between being conscious and unconscious where you're able to do things you normally can't do.
So what he did was he slept on an easy boy, easy chair with a big steel ball bearing in his hand with a metal bucket right under the armrest.
So when he fell asleep, the ball fell out of his hand, hit the bucket, and woke him up abruptly.
And for that first few seconds when that noise startled him, he was able to see things in the room and do things that normally wouldn't be considered being able to do with normal consciousness.
So he was getting into a different state.
The analogy there is there's a family, and the mom always makes a roast a certain way.
They love the way she makes the roast.
She buys a big roast, and she cuts the ends off and tosses them to the side and makes the roast.
And it always comes out well.
And she says she got the recipe for grandma.
So one day they go over to grandma's house, and they ask her, you know, grandma, mom makes the best roast.
And she makes it this way, like you said, you know, cut the ends off.
Why do you cut the ends off?
She goes, oh, when we had the small oven and the small tray, it was too small for the roast.
It wouldn't fit, so I had to cut the ends off.
So there was a practical reason for it, but then it just became, yeah, okay, gotcha.
And then it became something elaborate that was mystified and, you know, a secret recipe.
You see how that applies to this whole thing?
Right.
So something's going on here with these people by getting yourself like these remote viewers.
Oh, I like to listen to theta waves and get in a state or whatever.
I'm like, oh, my gosh.
But here, perfect for the public.
If you plan on having an audience of more than, like, five people, let's just say mass audience.
I say five.
I mean, for rarefied information, it should only go to a handful of people anyway.
When I say when you plan, like, this is all mass stuff, you know, even though it's alternative, it's mass.
I mean, like look at alternative media.
Some people have millions of followers, right, or millions of observers, spectators, whatever you want to call it.
Sure, whatever you want to call it.
Yeah, it's not small.
So if you're an alternative media guy or alternative thinking or alternative whatever and you want to put it out to the world,
you can almost acquire an audience that would be considered, like they say,
there are more people watching alternative media than watching CNN, according to their Gallup polls and things, right?
Right.
So when you get to that point, guess what, folks?
You're still going to the masses.
So what do you give to the masses?
You know, I've been hammering this on Greek speak for years and years.
You don't give them much and you give them stuff that, you know, accommodates them, right?
So it has to have that mystique, you know.
It generally ends up being BS for most people, just like they say, well, it didn't work for me, but I had fun.
It was entertaining, right?
Why?
You know, okay.
So I'm not knocking Silva, but I'll tell you this.
If he does have stuff that's valid, he's not sharing it publicly, I'll tell you that.
Or if he is sharing it publicly, you're going to have to sift through a lot of, you know what, to get some edible corn.
Okay.
For it to work, you know.
Do I need to?
Well, let me just say, I don't know if you guys remember, I used to use a lot, you know,
that's like eating, going through poop to get some edible corn, undigested corn.
Yeah, it is indeed in there, but it doesn't mean that you want to go through all that to get to it, but okay.
Yeah, we don't want to waste.
That's good corn.
Look, it's good.
Yeah, really?
Yeah.
Right?
Instead of fresh corn, you know.
Speaking of which, I wanted to get more into what I was thinking about.
You know, food, clothing, shelter were the three things that I keep telling people if you're a surface dwelling earth inhabitant.
Right.
That's what it's about being here.
By the way, your mic is, you're falling off and sounding a little distorted there.
Oh, sorry about that.
I probably leaned back.
Sorry.
Go ahead.
Oh, is it?
No, it could sound a little crinkly there, crackly too, or maybe the cable's coming off or something.
Okay.
Food, clothing, shelter.
One thing I got a response is, Greg, that sounds so base and simple.
You know, I don't even mean food, clothing, shelter.
I said, but listen, if you're pursuing, this is the qualitative, not the quantitative part.
If you're trying to pursue the highest quality of food, clothing, and shelter that you want to afford or can afford, it's going to be quite a trip.
Right?
And while you're pursuing a higher level of quality in all of those things, you will start learning a lot more about everything else.
So you're basically using that as a focal or an axial pivoting point.
Right?
And basically, if you look at someone who's barely getting by or someone who's a billionaire, when you become a billionaire, what do they always up?
They up their food quality.
They up their clothing quality, don't they?
And their housing.
Don't they do that?
Absolutely.
So you see that.
Okay, so when we continue, food, clothing, shelter, then it'll be water, energy, and silver.
I never got into this, I think, publicly before.
No, I don't think so.
Right?
Okay, so food, clothing, shelter, water, energy, silver.
Let's go backwards.
Silver, yes, the metal silver, but silver also implies currency and common use.
And also, silver implies the master metal, which has properties that actually no other element does second to water.
All right?
Energy would be the ability to handle a workload.
Okay?
It's not what, and I'll get into that.
And water, water would be that substance in either using it for, water substance being cool and clear and clean.
For all purposes, even for sewage, in other words, right?
So cool and clean and clear water access to, and moving water.
So those are the things after food, clothing, and shelter.
So we can go down.
I want to just insert a few things on that.
Which one do you think we should, should I start inserting things?
Water, energy, or silver, Chuck?
You pick.
Well, let's see.
Okay, you picked energy.
Yeah.
I'm just joking.
Go ahead.
That's fine.
No, that's where I was going to go, actually, because look, the other things can be assisted by energy, right?
Especially given the definition that you just laid out.
So why not?
You should get your energy together first.
This will assist you with the other two.
Sort of, yeah, but they all kind of work together in a way.
So energy, basically, give an analogy.
You know, you heard about all the Europeans or a good majority of people from all over the world coming to the U.S., right?
Migration, right?
Right.
It started a long, long time before they even told you.
You were just made aware of the influx of immigrants at the turn of the 20th century and on, right?
But, you know, the colonists and all that.
The reason, the main reason why they came, there's two reasons.
One is because you had cheap energy here.
Okay, and the other one was to escape justice because it was killing them.
Justice meaning the goddess religion.
Right.
And their laws in Europe, okay?
Which has, by the way, people have been quote unquote brainwashed to believe justice is a good thing.
It's just the name of a system.
Right.
Okay?
So, okay, what I mean, they came here, okay, so you're living in, if you look up statistics, you know, you don't have to lean on them, but at least it gives you a broad brush general thing.
Europe was deforested 500 years ago.
In other words, what I mean by that, if you look at country statistics,
like pick a country like Greece and it gives you the minerals, you know, what they have in population and all the stats on a country, right?
Okay.
When you get to forests, it says 95% deforested.
You get to another company, company, I always say company with countries, which is actually more accurate.
Actually more accurate, yeah.
Yeah, even my Freudian slips are accurate.
I hate that.
Okay, so, you know, other, you know, you look at this stuff.
So, what they were using for energy was hydropower and they were using solar, but solar passive, you know, like, hey, you got to dry your clothes, put them in the sun, right?
You might, okay.
Or drying food, right?
These sun-dried tomatoes, hey, right?
Okay, on and on and on.
So, solar and also for passive waste and also wood burning, all the way from, you know, a simple stove to a fireplace to a steam motor, right?
And so then you would use wood burning or coal burning, bitumen of some kind, bituminous lignites and humites, right?
All those things are burnable.
Those are like softer coals, right?
Anthracite coal is the most, it gets the hottest.
Okay, yeah.
Anyway, give examples and you basically dig and try to, well, they used it all up, right?
So, you know, you got to, you know, you're going to be cold in the winter and, you know, when you want to cook food, you all kind of get together and do it cooperatively.
Not always, but energy was, even now, for example, the euro and the dollar are very close together.
So, if I say one euro, one dollar, I'm pretty close, right?
It's like 104, 102 euro to the dollar or something.
So, if I say a dollar, when the euro first came out, it was $1.50 to the, right?
Right.
To the dollar.
And the pound was almost double.
I don't know what it is now.
But, okay, so let's say this.
So, typically in gas here, it's $4 a gallon, which would be four and a half liters or something, right?
Well, if you go to Europe.
Eight dollars, well, eight in the Great British Pound goes to about 11 and change, like 11.20 right now.
I know that is on top of my head.
It's not double.
In the 80s, it was double, pretty much.
If you saw, you know, a pound, it was like $1.85, right?
Yeah, something like that.
Yeah.
Yeah, but it's double.
I don't know.
Yeah, okay.
So, it's one and a third.
All right.
So, anyway, you get gas at four bucks or, let's say, even five bucks, right?
A gallon now, right?
You know how they have the price at the pump, right?
You know, four, whatever, five, whatever.
Yeah.
Well, you go to Europe, you see a similar number.
Three something, four something.
But you know what?
It's a liter.
It's not for a gallon.
It's for a liter.
Yeah.
You get it?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, it looks like the same price, right?
It takes approximately two liters to make a gallon, though.
More than four, yeah.
More than four.
Is it more than four?
I thought it was two.
Yeah, well, a liter is less than a quart.
Oh, wow.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I thought two liters made about a gallon.
My mistake.
Well, you could do it this way.
It's eight pounds for a gallon of water.
Anyway, a pound is 454 grams, right?
A liter is part of a tenth of a kilo.
You know how you could do the conversion pretty quickly?
But four liters, you're still short on a gallon.
But I use that pretty close because a liter is close to a quart.
You've worked with beverage.
Yeah, yeah.
Right?
So you can see the quart and the liter very close.
If you have a quart and a liter next to each other, the quart looks kind of fat compared to the liter.
Sure.
They look very similar.
Anyway, so you see, even today, it's kind of going on.
If you go to, like, remember in England in the wintertime, they have a heater in each room.
So when you leave one room, you turn off the heater in that room,
and you go to the next room, you turn the heater on in that room to conserve.
You know what I mean?
Okay.
They don't do that here yet.
So cheap energy.
That's what I mean by energy availability.
People came over to this part of the world for that because, hey, it was everywhere.
There was coal.
There was surface minerals.
Right?
Right.
Trees everywhere.
Right?
This has gone on for a very long time.
Like a water heater in the Netherlands that you heat with gas or electric to make hot water for the house is super efficient.
I mean, you can almost use a plastic flue pipe to vent it out.
Where in the U.S., when you have a forced air heater gas burning or a water heater gas burning,
90% of the gas you're burning is going out the flue, and only 10% is to heat the water.
That's how wasteful they are.
Wow.
Where in Europe, when they design them, they design them so it's the other way around.
You're only wasting 10%, right?
They actually have some new ones now where, you know,
when you have a flue or a chimney exhaust for a gas burner or whatever,
it's got to be made of pretty good metal.
You don't want to start a fire on your roof or something.
Some of the newer devices are so efficient, you could actually use a plastic pipe.
Wow.
You know, that's how little heat they lose.
And I think those went away.
They came out for a little while, and I said, no, no, we don't want to let people know there's a really good way to do this.
So that's what I mean by energy from the living perspective.
People came, let's say, to the U.S. and the Americas because it was cheap energy, right?
Okay.
So that's – okay.
Now, from the older Greek speak, I talk about how the Western world is going to be brought down,
and the Middle East is going to be up.
And one of the ways that's going to happen is you know how you have these things –
a certain lifestyle in Europe, people come to the U.S. and are like, wow, I love it here.
You've got so much stuff.
Well, they're going to make the U.S. more like Europe, right?
And then once the U.S. gets more like Europe, then they bring the whole thing down even further, right?
Because in order for the U.S. economically, energy-wise, availability, commercial-wise, to be like Europe,
they have to bring it down, tamp it down, create more scarcity, higher price,
even though the value is the same of the item.
You see?
So this is happening.
I've talked about this a lot, what you see going on right now in crazy inflation.
Even when we were talking about the ONG eight years ago or six years ago, seven years ago,
I was saying, look, you guys are going to get hit with some crazy inflation
where stuff is going to, like, double in price in a year and a half and all that
because they're holding it down, right?
Here's fiat currency.
Every time someone uses a credit card, you should have inflation because they're creating new currency.
Every time someone gets a loan, the money to pay back that alleged loan does not exist.
It has to be created.
Right.
You see?
And every time new currency is created, it takes value from the existing currency supply,
so therefore it devalues it and creates inflation automatically.
It means you need more of that currency to get the same thing, which is inflation.
So people say, Greek, you don't pay taxes.
They pay taxes all the time.
It's called inflation.
What I mean by that is, let's say you have a time machine in the 1950s
and you sock $2,000 to get a new car.
You put it away.
I got it.
It's 1953.
All right?
I got a time machine.
So I'm going to go to 2023 with my time machine tomorrow.
But when I get there, I can't get around in my time machine.
I need a new car.
So I'm going to put $2,500 in a box.
So when I show up in 2023, I could walk into a new car dealer with my $2,500 and get a new car.
Right?
What happens when you do that?
You show up in 2023 with $2,500 to get a new car.
What?
Right?
You're lucky you get a moped.
But not even, right?
I mean, they charge you $500 just to leave the dealership.
So you got to have nitrogen in the tires, right?
So anyway, yeah, you're going to be in for a rude awakening
if you don't know how the currency system means.
So that's how you're paying a tax, right?
See, that's where the tax really is.
What people file returns on is not really a tax.
It's you're filing a return just like let's say you want to make a hole in a sidewalk
and the tools you have aren't strong enough to do that or powerful enough.
You go to the tool rental place and you get a jackhammer, right?
And you use it.
You make the hole in the sidewalk and you bring the jackhammer back to the tool rental place
and you wave goodbye and that's it.
You're done, right?
Right.
Nope.
You have to pay a fee for that.
Okay.
When you return, right?
No, I know.
Look, just by renting something, you're paying a fee when you show up to get it.
Yeah, so you go, right.
So in other words, when you get the jackhammer, you can't just say,
hey, I brought it back.
What's wrong?
Why do I have to pay a fee?
You get in trouble, right, for stealing.
So that's what the IRS is.
You're using private currency.
Here's, you know, early on commercial laws, even still, but they don't teach this.
The currency that's being used, whether it's electronic or paper, is called commercial paper,
commercial transactions, NFTs, NFCs, all this other stuff, right?
There's a presumption that anyone using it is an expert in that system.
That's the presumption.
Yeah, well, it's not a very good presumption.
The presumption is, here's another way to look at it.
If you sit down at a poker game, the moment you take the chair and get your hand dealt to you,
there's a presumption of everyone on the table that you know how to play the game.
Right.
Right?
So what if you don't know how to play the game, and you sit down at a poker,
you get dealt a hand, and everyone's presuming you know the rule,
but you don't know what the hell's going on.
What happens?
Well, a lot of things could happen.
Not only do you lose, but it's going to upset everyone else, right?
Of course.
So if you're endorsing credit, private credit, you'd better file for returns with all the authorities
or you will get in trouble, right, if you're unconditionally endorsing it, right?
That's why people say, you know, oh, they're unfair.
No, what's unfair is your education is unfair.
So I keep leaning on this.
They take it very seriously.
It's serious as a heart attack.
They'll even kill presidents over it.
So I know you're not a big proponent of Kennedy being killed over it,
but I'll tell you what, Jackson sure was, and so was Lincoln.
Oh, well, there I won't object.
Sure.
Yeah.
They made several attempts on Jackson over this.
Oh, yeah, and you know what?
It was very open both ways.
It was very open.
He says, you know, you can see here whether the statements are true or not,
they're very open statements against the bankers, right?
Yes.
And the bankers made a lot of the open statements against him, open, you know, so.
Oh, yeah.
And the most open thing that I've seen with Kennedy was the 10001 to make currency again,
but he didn't have to do that because it was already in effect.
It just wasn't being printed, right?
So he didn't abolish the Federal Reserve, and the president cannot abolish the Federal Reserve.
That's an act of Congress, right?
That's true.
It's an act of Congress.
Yeah, an act of Congress.
So people look at presidents.
I love the distraction.
It's the Congress that's screwing you, not the president.
There is nothing any president can do that could screw you one-tenth as bad as anything Congress does.
Absolutely true, yeah.
And that's why you're focusing on the president.
And even though the Congress is illegitimate, it hasn't been legitimately in session,
lawfully in session since the start of what they call the Civil War.
You can look that up.
There's a Latin term for it.
It means a dead day or dark day or a done day.
D.M. something.
Congress went into that state where they cannot reassemble.
Anyway, it's all crap.
So, okay, the energy part.
Energy is the ability to do a load, to work a load.
What does that mean?
Okay, so the floor needs to be cleaned in a house, right?
It's dry.
Dry, clean.
You don't want to sweep, right?
So you can grab a broom and sweep it, dustpan, et cetera.
All right.
That's physical energy.
So you would actually manually do that or have someone manually do it.
Then we go to the next level.
You make machines that would do that, right?
It even gets to the point where they have robots now that sweep the floor, right?
The little disc thing that runs around.
Yeah, the little roombas, yeah.
Yeah, okay.
Right, right.
So those things need some kind of power to run them, right?
Okay.
So that's where the energy is, and it's a load.
But what do you call it, a Roomba?
Yeah, that's the little robot that moves around.
Yeah, okay.
Or let's say an old Hoover or Kirby vacuum.
You plug in the wall, that draws a lot more current or whatever.
Now, let's say that's electric and it has a motor.
When you go over to, let's say, something like an electric car,
that requires a tremendous amount more current, right?
Right.
So here's the electric car thing, by the way.
If I were to be interested in that, there are some adapters,
like if you were living off the grid or if there was a blackout,
the battery bank in an electric car with a proper inverter and converter,
you could plug it into the mains in your house
and power your house with it for a day or two, right?
Right.
Because if you look at the average house using less than 10 kilowatts
and the average electric car being twice that, right, do the math, right?
So kilowatts, 1,000 watts.
So the energy factor here starts to increase.
So if you were to manually sweep with a broom and a dustpan,
and let's leave the Roomba out of this,
and you were to plug in a Hoover 110 volt
or whatever line voltage vacuum cleaner,
if you were to step off to the side,
because of efficiency and the designs we're getting,
you had to manually run on a treadmill
or turn a generator to make electricity to power that vacuum cleaner,
you'd say, oh, it's a lot less work to just sweep with a dustpan, right?
Right.
So if you had a generator to provide for that,
but while someone else is vacuuming,
you're running on a treadmill powering, right?
You'd be like, screw that.
I would have been much better if I had a broom
and you had a broom, it would be less work, okay?
Right.
So that's the, when I say energy, it's quantity and quality.
And I gave the example with you producing energy for the vacuum
or using the vacuum or the broom is a quantitative and qualitative point,
because it comes to the point sometimes when you're using energy,
whether it's while you're performing the load,
in other words, executing whatever load you have,
before, during, and after, you're like, oh, that took too much what?
Too much energy to do.
How many times do you hear that, right?
Right.
That was just too much energy to do that.
So you're always thinking about a more efficient way to do things.
So ultimately, even if you go back to all of the sacred texts, right,
if they give you any direction in life,
it's basically to grow crops, eat meat once in a while,
have a roof over your head, stay cool when it's hot,
stay warm when it's cold, and then you die.
That's it.
Okay.
That's the purpose of life.
And grow crops.
Right.
Right?
I just gave you the whole purpose.
So if you look at all the ancient texts,
it basically says you're agriculturally based,
have a good time while you're doing it, have a few festivals,
have sex when you want to, have children, blah, blah, blah, blah,
and then you die.
That's it.
That's the meaning of life.
You're like, oh, I need more than that.
Well, you've got more than that even if you're not trying.
It's called Netflix.
No, I'm just joking.
Okay.
I'm just joking.
That's a horrible idea.
It's all right.
Scratch that.
That doesn't even have a pun.
It's not even a worthy punchline.
Okay.
You see, you know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
You get it, right?
What's the purpose of life?
All right.
Let's go look at, let's say, the Bible.
Let's go look at it.
What are we doing here?
Well, you know, we're supposed to wipe our bum and have babies
and make some shelters and grow some crops, and then we die.
Oh, my gosh.
It's really easy to be more interesting
than what all of the holy books tell you to do, right?
Oh, sure.
Very easy.
So this is, when I say food, clothing, shelter,
and then water, energy, and silver,
it's along the lines where it's still anchored in the ancient texts,
but it's also anchored in the way that what we can do,
because most of the ancient texts actually, here's a way to say it.
If you subscribe to a set of laws of antiquity and there are prohibitions,
consider the prohibitions as such,
but if something is not prohibited, you're open to do.
It's almost some of them are indirectly encouraged, right?
You see?
So when people look at laws of antiquity, it's so limiting,
but it's such a limited amount of limiting,
and while you study what to do as being the prohibitions or the limits,
it actually makes you aware of more things, you see?
It's like the subject matter.
So we're at the point now where you're still very open.
You know, if you get engrossed in what's going on in the world,
you could see it's been happening all the time.
What's going on right now is a repeat of the 70s.
Gas prices, terrible presidents, let's say, right?
A little bit of war here, a little bit of war there.
You had the Vietnam War ended, and then you had the Turks attack Cyprus.
You had skirmishes in Africa.
In the 70s, the big thing was give money to Ethiopia because they're starving.
Remember that?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, not anymore.
You don't hear that anymore, but it's Ukraine now or whatever.
So anyway, the whole thing kind of repeats, and it pushes through again,
and when it pushes through again, it's like, what's going on?
The world's coming to an end.
What do you mean?
It's almost a replay, right?
It's coming back around again to the same thing it was at before.
So food, clothing, shelter, water, energy, and silver is a replay over and over and over,
and it gets really interesting when you start pursuing these things in your mind
and as a mindful pursuit, let's just say.
So the energy part, maybe not to sum it up, but just to give more of a way that I'd like to see it,
is you have a load, a task, a work that needs to be performed,
and what does it take to get it done, right?
That's why I gave the analogy of sweeping.
You have a dirty floor.
How do we get it done?
Well, we could sweep it, dustpan, or we get a vacuum cleaner,
but which one is the least amount of energy?
By the way, which one is it, Greek?
Well, I shouldn't say, obviously.
The dustpan and the broom is the least amount of energy, right?
Completely.
Now, here's the other thing.
If you can source the Roomba or a DC-powered, or if you're running on solar power all the way,
that would be the most available energy as long as the sun is shining,
but you still have to get the equipment, which is much more elaborate.
As far as I can tell, I can go price any broom and any dustpan,
and it will always be less than any vacuum cleaner.
Oh, of course.
So cost-wise, yeah.
That's the silver part.
But the difference in cost here is your personal use of energy, right?
Because to utilize the Roomba is no energy just about.
You set it up, it goes.
By the way, I didn't know those freaking things were like 300 bucks or 200 bucks for a knockoff.
Yeah, they are.
Right?
Yeah.
I was like, what?
That thing, you know, you could step on it, it's made out of thin plastic.
I saw, what, 50 bucks, get another one.
I said, 50 bucks?
What are you talking about?
No, they're not 50 bucks.
They're kind of expensive.
Yeah, yeah.
But still.
But what's interesting here is that there's a difference because the distribution of the different elements here is different, right?
Because it's more personal energy you have to expend for the broom.
But you're expending less silver.
You're expending less energy in general if you're just objectifying the energy if you just sweep it yourself, right?
But personally, you expend a lot less energy if you put the little robot in charge of it.
And it's a lot less energy to use the vacuum as opposed to manually stroking the broom back and forth and using and picking up and putting down the dustpan, right?
And you've got to know how to sweep, by the way.
It sounds a lot of what they call labor.
Right?
It's not that just because it's called labor, like let's say you're a laborer on a construction site, doesn't mean that anybody can do it.
It requires a lot of skill to be a good laborer, by the way.
Look, I can tell you just very simply how many people I had to teach how to properly mop a floor.
Oh, of course.
Because they don't know.
That's another level of sweeping.
Yeah.
Exactly.
It's not like walking where you put one leg in front of the other.
It's called walking.
Right.
And, you know, I get it, yeah.
But here, okay, so at some point you have to decide what works better.
I personally like vacuuming, but, you know, it has to be the right proper vacuum and all that for many reasons.
But ultimately the bottom line is the least energy consumption now, later, and much later is going to be the dustpan and the broom.
So, like I don't get around much, and we have two cars here.
And the only reason I use the car really is to go get cigarettes and do some minor shopping once in a while, which I could actually just walk.
I don't even have to use that.
So it's being very, very wasteful, right?
You see, so actually I'm exaggerating there.
I do need it.
I do go on trips and things like that, but personally I could get away with just the bicycle most of the time and being on foot.
Your day-to-day needs.
So that's another consideration.
Yeah, your day-to-day needs you could generally address with a bicycle or on foot is what you're saying.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
And it would actually make it more interesting because you're not inside of this human terrarium, right?
Right.
You might meet – the chances of having more conversation and whatever and interaction is much greater walking.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
So there's that aspect also.
So the energy part, again, you notice I keep saying it's a load, right?
It's a load that you put on yourself.
In other words, if you're really, really tired and ready to go to bed and someone gives you a broom and a dustpan to sweep the floor, it's going to be like,
wow, what a task because you're ready to go to sleep.
So you sense how much work it takes to do a job like that when you're not ready to do it.
Right, right.
So when I say energy, it's that aspect.
And then there's also the chemical energy.
We've discussed some of the – chemical energy would be purely when we say we have to heat or cool something.
We don't do it usually naturally unless – like in the cartoons, the grandma makes the pie and she puts it on the windowsill to cool down
and someone always comes and takes the pie, you know, the old meal.
Right, right.
You steal the pie because it's cooling off.
When I say heating and cooling, we do chemical heating and cooling.
And when I was in a discussion with someone regarding ether energy and stuff like that,
I was talking about some inductive processes.
As soon as you feel the chemical heat come on, you have to remove it.
And most people wouldn't know what that means.
If you have an electronics or if you have anything plugged in anywhere or running on anything and you feel it getting warm, that's a chemical heat.
It's not a natural heat, right?
So let's say you walk over to your computer, right, and you say it's running.
How's it running, Chuck?
Put your hand on it.
It feels like it's running hot.
That's a chemical heat.
Right.
That's not a natural heat, right?
Okay.
So that's what I mean by heat.
We usually – energy, you're going to pursue the chemical aspect of energy, heating or cooling and all that.
So all these things should be considered.
If you go camping, which, by the way, this is a modern phenomenon, by the way, camping.
It's more a part of the Western white culture, I call it.
By the way, when I say white people and white, it's not the color of your skin.
Yeah.
In ancient – I remember – I can't remember exactly.
I was reading a translation of an ancient Egyptian text, and if you have no flavor, no culture, no personality, you're like blah,
in ancient Egypt they called you white.
White is not being used as a color.
It's used as a qualitative term, like blah.
Okay.
But anyway, back to camping.
This whole thing about camping is a very modern thing.
People get excited.
I'm going to go camping.
Oh, my gosh.
For thousands of years, people lived in cities, and they pointed as the mountains and countryside as places not to go because it's dangerous.
And you've got stuff coming out of the – why would you suscept yourself – right?
I never understood it.
It's kind of like – I've gone camping, by the way, and from the minute we got there, I was thinking, when are we getting back?
Right?
Yeah.
It's foolish.
It's just part of a cultural training.
It's not quite like an adrenaline junkie, like the bungee cord.
You know, the guys that jump off the bridges, the bungee cord jumping, adrenaline junkies, skydivers and whatever.
Humans are the only animals that pursue dangerous things.
And all the other creatures, when they find out doing a particular activity is dangerous, they avoid it.
But humans don't.
And to show how stupid they are, they keep pursuing these dangerous things that could bring death or injury to them by making devices to protect themselves while they're pursuing those dangerous things.
Right?
Think about it.
Anyway.
Yeah.
So, yeah, let's make an airplane so we could jump out of it.
Whatever.
So the camping thing, when you have a reasonably – a culture that's based on a reasonably ancient mindset, they would never do that, ever.
Well, they did go out into the woods.
You read stories about that when they had to leave the city because someone was going to kill them.
Right?
To hide out in the woods.
Well, but that's choosing a level of danger.
It's more dangerous to remain in the city, so we're going to leave the city.
Yeah, it's more dangerous to stay in the city.
That's why we're going out in the country, not because we're going to REI and buying camping equipment.
Oh, my goodness.
And, look, I'm not – if you enjoy that kind of thing, I'm not knocking it.
All right?
No, and I wouldn't say it's a bad skill set to have to know how to survive out there and stuff like that.
I think it's not a bad thing to know how to do, for sure.
Yeah, but they're not really – they go and buy all their gimmicks and all their gadgets and all the things that the little, you know, one thing does this and it does that.
The camping stove and all that.
You know, all that's depleted.
Most of the stuff that people buy to go camping is depletable.
Right?
Like they open the little packet, the freeze-dried thing, add water, heat it up, and you've got a meal or the little pellets or this and that.
The flashlight, right?
All that shit is going to run out after a few days or weeks, depending on how much crap you buy.
And then what do you do then?
No, I got you.
I'm talking about the kind of guys who like – I had a guy on a show many years ago that won that series on History Channel called Alone
where you just go out into the wild with a knife, basically, and you survive.
And if you need rope, you make it out of the trees.
You know what I mean?
Yep.
Well, I like the knife that has the compass on the back.
You don't really need the compass.
It has the little fire starter inside the handle.
Oh, yeah.
No, I understand all that.
But, no, these guys generally go out there with a knife that, like, you know, they could carve things up with, but they could also chop down a tree with it.
You know what I mean?
A knife knife.
You know, like Crocodile Dundee, that's not a knife.
The thing about knives are really – it's just a slight tangent.
If I had to rely on a knife, like I would have to make it, I'd forge it on my own instead of going out.
You can get a – by the way, a really good knife should be in the several hundreds, not a couple of hundreds, several hundreds.
I'm talking the one you put in your pocket.
There are – it is possible to have a steel good enough where you could chop down a small tree with it and also slice a tomato.
Right.
Right?
It won't dull out, yeah.
So, I know they're out there.
I just don't trust them.
Like, I don't want to go out and spend $300 on a knife and find out it's not the one that I thought it was, you know.
Of course.
So I'd rather take my time and make one.
By the way, making forges now is easy with inductive.
You just get a piece of copper coil and an old whatever transformer, put the metal in the coil, it turns red hot almost instantly.
You forge it that way instead of a fire like in the – they show you in the movies.
So, yeah, I understand.
But the survivalist – the food, clothing, shelter, water, energy, and silver is basically a survivalist mentality, not taking anything for granted, by the way.
Right?
I mean, when do you ever hear – look, go on YouTube right now.
And I'm talking – when I say food, clothing, and shelter and now water, energy, and silver, it's about being in the society.
If you go on YouTube or Internet or whatever and you see about what you should be concerned about living in society, no one is going to say food, clothing, shelter.
They're going to tell you, oh, how to be a millionaire, how to make $50,000 in a month, how to do this, how to be vegan, how to live off the grid, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Nothing about the basic reality.
You know what I mean?
Right.
Tell me more about – tell us more about the survivalist.
What was the takeaway from the survivalist guy that you had?
What was the ultimate takeaway from him?
Well, it was simply that if you are in the woods, if you're in nature, you can find the means by which to create just about anything that is useful.
And you can feed yourself.
You can clothe yourself.
And you can shelter yourself from the things that are just there if you know how.
That's what he did.
I'll give a personal example.
I don't – here's the thing.
Tell me yes or no.
I don't give – I'm not the – if you listen to all the sonics that we do or I've done, very rarely do I give personal accounts, right?
Just tell me, you know, either back me up on this or say no.
I mean, I don't want to – I like to avoid that.
And if I say something personal, it has to be more applicable to everyone than telling people my story, right?
Right.
No, generally you'll give an anecdote, and it's usually not about you at all.
It's about something that you observed.
Right.
Like I – you know, like if a guy goes to a drugstore and he says, what do you got for crabs?
I have a friend who's got crabs, right?
Remember that?
I have a friend who has hemorrhoids.
What do you got for that?
Yeah, sure you do.
You should have a friend.
You know what I mean?
It's kind of like – it's another anecdote, right?
True, true.
But no, generally, though, you'll just tell a story like I was out, I saw this, I heard this.
You don't really tell your story, so to speak.
Yeah.
I like to avoid – again, when you go online and podcast, it's all about me, me, me, me, and this is not about me.
It's about you.
By the way, if you – this is not a joke.
Maybe you could take it as such.
You hear a lot of me, me, me, me in the world, right?
Always, wherever you go.
Mine, right?
Yours, mine, you know, me, me, me.
If you go to a bar in Vietnam and just open the door and yell out, me!
You know, like half the – maybe not half.
If there's 50 guys in there, like 10 will look at you.
Like you called them with their name because me is an actual name in Vietnam.
Right.
Like John or Steve or Tom.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You went into a bar that was busy and you said, Steve or Tom.
You know what I mean?
How many people are going to look up like you're – handful, most likely.
Yeah, yeah.
Very common.
Yeah, me, Ho Chi Minh.
Anyway, stuff like that.
Yeah, right.
Ho Chi Minh.
Survival.
Well, I found myself, okay, years ago, more, about 30 years ago, in cycling, mountain biking
or whatever, Jersey area, right?
Like off of Bear Mountain and more, let's say, west or east that area.
You know, Hudson River Valley, New York, you know?
Okay.
Yeah, you get the metro, you know, you get the train going north, you get off, you know,
this one, and you go riding in the – right?
Okay.
Anyway, when the forest gets deep enough, you get disoriented and suddenly it's dark
and you're like, oh, shit, and we think we got to go this way to get to a road and you
keep going and you're getting deeper into the woods.
It's like, how can you be so disoriented, right?
And it gets to the point where you try to find a shelter and it's starting to rain
and you're not prepared for it.
You just got one layer of clothing on and you start to make a fire and you don't have
any kindling so everybody has to contribute whatever paper money they have so we can start
the fire.
I don't know if that sounds – I don't know if the story is getting interesting here.
I've never heard of people contributing money to a fire in that situation.
Yeah, you couldn't get anything to start and say, oh, let's use a dollar.
Okay.
Let's use two dollars, right?
Okay, I guess so.
Why not?
Yeah, it works, by the way.
Yeah.
Because, you know, they call it paper money.
It's mostly cotton, by the way.
Money is mostly cotton.
Like in other countries now, it's plastic, right?
In Australia, they have plastic money.
It's some kind of like a tie-back, right?
Anyway, so you get to these points here and then you got to find a place to sleep.
And you're like, holy shit, this is some serious survival of shit.
There's a big difference.
Okay, not serious because we got out of there when daybreak came but it wasn't easy.
Unfortunately, it was early spring, late – it was like just after winter but, you know,
in the springtime at night, it gets pretty cold.
I mean, not like winter where you'll threaten your life but you're not going to be comfortable at all.
See, I've known people that have done this in like the Pinelands area which is the south part of Jersey.
It's a little different but similar concept, I assure you.
Yeah, but the whole plan was to go out and get back to the city, right?
Not to get lost, right?
And when we started getting lost, we didn't take it seriously enough.
We'll find our way out.
We actually were doing worse and worse.
So, anyway, this is a common thing.
No, no.
Then it starts to get dark.
Yeah, no, but like I said, in the Pinelands, same thing.
It starts to get dark and you go, wait a minute.
We're going to wind up wandering through these woods in the dark.
Forget it.
No, it's that way.
Yeah, so maybe we should –
The worst is – well, the worst part is when everyone agrees that we should go in that direction
and then the worst part is when you find out you're going in the wrong direction.
Then it gets worse when every one person thinks we should go this way and the other person thinks we should go that way.
Then it starts to get worse and worse and worse, right?
So, that's when you know everything is going south.
But here's the thing.
When I say survival situation, it's more taking you back this way, the way I just mentioned.
You weren't expecting to be in a survival situation.
It's very different from saying I'm going to be put into a survival situation.
Yeah, of course.
Very different.
So, when people say survival situation, I mean intentional or unintentional, right?
It's like the difference between being in a car accident or being a stuntman in a car accident.
Big difference.
Yes, you're right.
They smash up the car in both cases, but guess what?
Very different.
And by the way, just because it's a stuntman and he hit a plane doesn't mean he's not going to get hurt, right?
True.
There's plenty of stuntmen that get, you know, really hurt.
Seriously, yeah.
But you don't hear about that.
I think, by the way, when they make a film and the stuntman has been hurt, they should do a little tribute.
It doesn't mean – I'm not saying killed.
I'm just saying hurt.
The most popular one was when they were shooting The Twilight Zone in the 80s
and they dropped the helicopter and killed a whole bunch of people from that, right?
Oh, yeah, right.
That was Vic Morrow and a Vietnamese kid.
I forget the rest, but yeah.
Yeah, I mean it went down.
I mean it really went down, almost as like a real life battle scene would have.
Right.
So, when we say survival, I always bifurcate.
And I'm like, you're caught in a bad situation and you've got to make do is very different.
So, one thing I've mentioned, I don't know, on the survival.
Real quick, if you need a plant to eat, do you remember the protocols on that?
Chuck, I've gone over it maybe with you at least once or twice on the O and G.
Maybe I'll go over it really quick before we depart from the energy.
Yeah, because I don't remember you going over this actually.
I don't recall it.
Okay.
So, just like we didn't expect to get lost in the pylons or whatever,
you may not expect that you're going to need to find a plant to eat, but you might, right?
So, what do you do?
Well, the way is before you ingest it, you take the plant and you rub it in your fingers and your hand, right?
So, before I get into this, it's not like the method that I'm giving you now,
it's not like you're going to see a plant do a few things and eat it right away.
This takes a few hours, right?
But you'll want to eat a plant.
In other words, it's not life or death because if there's plants around, greenery,
you're going to want to eat it.
You've got plenty of time.
It's not like you're going to die in four hours if you don't, right?
You have days and days.
So, even though it's a several-hour process, at least it gets you started.
If you're not familiar with the botany, rub it in your hands and you let it go and you wait a few minutes.
No reaction, right?
Then you take it and you rub it on the soft parts, the susceptible parts of your body,
which is the inner part of your wrist.
You ever see how women put perfume on the inner part of their wrist?
Believe it or not, the palm is one of the toughest parts of the hands or the upper body,
but just a few inches down at your wrist is one of the most sensitive and receptive parts of the upper body,
which is the wrist, right, the inner part of the wrist.
The other part is the inside of the elbow and the armpit.
The armpit might be even more susceptible.
In other words, sensitive.
In other words, if you're going to have a reaction with something,
if you rub it on the inside part of your wrist or the inside part of your elbow or your armpit,
you'll know if it's going to react with you if you touch those areas.
Very different from the outer forearm or shoulder, right?
Right.
Okay, it's the under-soft parts.
Okay, so what you do is you rub the plant on the wrist, elbow, armpit, and you wait.
No reaction, right?
Okay, great.
So the other thing you do after that no reaction, you smell it, obviously, through all this.
You will get the smell of it, like it or not.
The other thing there is you rub it on your lower lip, upper lip.
Not in your mouth, not on your teeth, just on the upper, lower lip.
Now we're getting more sensitive.
And you wait.
How long?
Five minutes, ten minutes, an hour would be really safe.
No reaction.
Now here's the thing.
You can rub it on your palm, no reaction.
Wrist, elbow, armpit, no reaction.
Rub it on your lips, you get a big reaction, right?
It's possible.
Could be.
Yeah, right?
Well, that's a stopping point, isn't it?
Oh, yeah.
Even though it passed the other two tests.
Third test would be the upper lip load.
No reaction.
Now we take a bite of it.
One, two, three, chew, spit it out.
You may not have had a reaction on your lip and the other two processes, right?
On the wrist, elbow, armpit, no reaction.
No reaction on the lip.
You take a bite, chew, spit it out.
Now you get a reaction.
That's your stopping point.
Right.
Reaction could be several things, right?
You know.
Your body will know.
It will communicate to you without sound, without voice, right?
That's where the inner mind gets really quiet.
You'll know.
And then you'll have to make up words to describe it.
No reaction at this point still, right?
If you have a reaction, well, that's your stopping point.
No reaction, okay.
The next thing is you put it in your mouth and chew it again, but this time a little bit longer,
until the contents of it in your mouth reaches the same temperature as your mouth.
You notice that you could take a bite of a cold sandwich.
When you start chewing it, describe what it is.
It's a cold.
It's still cold, right?
You chew, chew, chew, chew.
Now what happens?
It starts to what?
Warm up in your mouth, doesn't it?
You no longer sense that it's cold.
We're not talking about eating, dousing yourself with ice cream where you get brain freeze.
That stays cold all the time, you know?
Right, right.
But you just chew on it until it reaches temperature.
Throw it out.
Spit it out.
No reaction.
Well, now is the time to take a little bit and swallow it.
Oh, reaction.
Bad reaction.
Well, stop.
You just took a little bit.
Yeah, of course.
Right?
But by the way, if it passes the wrist, elbow, armpit, lower lip, single bite and chew,
the chances of you swallowing it at that point, the body works so well.
We're put together well enough that if it passes all those preliminary tests,
you probably won't get a reaction when you chew it and sweep it.
Now, you might want to wait because it might taste good and not have a reaction,
but it might be what?
A super laxative.
So, right?
So that might take another go.
And that becomes an inconvenience right there.
Yeah, right.
And it may not be good.
For example, a super laxative, if you were on a deserted island and you just had coconuts,
you would be dead to eat.
And coconut, right?
Just coconuts, you'd die in two weeks.
Yeah, because you'll just dehydrate yourself to death.
You'll die.
Right.
Yeah.
You think it's because it's so on.
It's such a gun into the plant's so tall and the coconut wants to go down.
So, it's going to be a very radical trip up and a very radical trip down.
Extreme.
It's an extreme reactions on the body, certain foods that we call benign.
Well, it probably produces a lot of energy and all that stuff.
It's got a lot of fluid in it, but here's the problem.