Sonic event number eight here on this particular day, whatever day it is that you are capturing
this and deciding to listen to it.
Welcome to you wherever you are, whenever you are.
And interesting thing, because I'm going to first, I guess, start with the question that I used to start a bunch of the public Ocelli and the Greeks with, which is a Greek, you know, what, what, what day is it not, not according to the Pope's work schedule.
Well, let's do that one.
It's it's what they call 319 2023 that I see on the on the on the screen here in front of me.
Yeah, I would suggest that it's the 14th day of the first month, a reckoning here near Tucson, Arizona.
OK. And yeah, yeah, that's, you know, it's it's how would we say here's one way to think about it.
You know, the sun rules the day and the moon rules the month, basically the metric.
Right. You know, it's not like a tape measure where, you know, you got the inches and feet and all that on the same thing.
Right. Imagine you had you used you're working in carpentry or whatever and you need to tape measures because one one, you know, one only measures length and the other one measures with.
Think about that for a moment.
It doesn't put your panties in a twist, so no twist at all.
You know, what I was thinking is actually it's, again, important to remember.
And I'm starting to utilize this a bit.
And I don't know if you want to get into this today, but just thinking about the idea that the day beginning at what most people call noon.
Right. Yeah. Solar, solar, solar noon.
When the sun is at that point in the sky, the day begins there.
I got to tell you, it's an it's an odd adjustment, but it makes more sense to me internally than than the the way that, you know, people have presented it.
You know, you wake up, it's still dark outside most of the time, you know, because they tell you the day is supposed to begin at this time and it's still dark or it's just becoming light.
You know, at that time and you say, OK, this is where light begins, but not really.
The day begins with with that highest point in the sky that just feels right.
So anyway, beginning to reckon the day is one thing. Right.
So we got the day and then oddly, though, we're in the first month.
Now, is that sort of because it's spring and spring is the beginning of.
Well, it's the beginning of things. Right. It's it's where things begin.
I don't know. It just feels right when you say it's the first month as opposed to.
Well, now they would call it the third. Third. Right. Yeah.
It just feels more right that this is the first month. It feels more right that the day begins at noon.
Solar noon. It just feels more right.
So I don't know. I'm just throwing that in.
Well, you're you're in what they call the continental U.S. like me.
Let's say Southeast. I'm in Southwest. But there are a bunch of folks living upside down.
Right. Where right now they're going into winter.
You know, South America, South Africa, the Aussies, New Zealand. Right.
Right. So they're going into winter. I don't really address that.
And I've I have there's an overriding aspect where it's I take the season as a precedent.
So I ever suggested to people that if you're living down there and it's going into winter,
you would be at the seventh month instead of the first month because it's seasonally this way, because this is agricultural.
So if you start looking at it as the first month for planting and the winter is just starting, you're kind of like going to have a hard time.
Right. It's not going to work well for you. So I suggest that it's seasonally based being Earth based.
Let's say I mean, when I say Earth based, I don't mean from the astronomical point of view, but meaning that we have to live off of the Earth.
Right. Legitimately. You know, I basically discussed this with a computer programmer once.
I don't really live off the Earth on a computer programmer. I'm like, where are you wearing blue jeans?
Right. It's cotton. And you're wearing those blue jeans, got metal buttons.
Someone was mining to get that metal. Right. And you're going to go for lunch.
You know, something was grown or slaughtered for you to eat. You know, people are that disconnected, by the way, in a trivial way.
But I want to go back to the solar noon. An easy way to discern that is when you're let's say at any part of the world,
you will see that when the shadow when it's morning, the shadow of the sunlight goes towards the West and the opposite in the afternoon.
It goes towards the East. So when your shadow is just do in the center, neither East or West,
it's going to be a little towards the North or towards the South. If you're living on the other end, that's when it's noon time.
And you make marks basically on the ground. You could use a stick. Right.
So that that would be solar noon. It's not just the reckoning is is measurable.
Here's the thing. Time is the recordation, memorialization, record keeping of events.
If there is no record keeping, there is no time. But if you're Earth based, let's say you have to eat plants.
They will tell time for you. Right. Right. You know, if you're growing a garden, you know,
you have a plant that comes from a seed and then it bears vegetables for you to eat.
Then the vegetables come off and the plant dies and the cycle starts again sometime in the future.
Whether you have multiple crops that year or you have to wait till next year, you could use that for keeping time.
When the cucumber comes up, it's this. Right. You see. So you're still measuring events even.
OK, so so everything will everything that anything that changes will measure has a measurable event.
If you record it, you know. OK, so without having extreme precision, let's say for some, even in ancient times,
you're not going to have precise records. So the sundial was very, very precise.
In essence, the longer the armature or the the reference, what would you call it?
The landmark is, you know, the stick. Let's say the more the longer the angle, the more accurate it is.
For example, if even today in India, just to do a search, large sundials or large sun structures in India,
they build these things look like buildings. They look like modern art buildings and they're very old.
Some of them are, you know, three, four stories tall. Right. To measure the time.
And when you get to a shadow that's that long from a structure sundial that large and they don't look like sundials in the Western world,
you can get it down to a tenth of a second, a hundredth of a second. Right.
Just like now. Right. Don't you have stopwatches digital that gets down very, very accurate.
So the reason I said this, it's kind of redundant is because when people you start telling people to stick in the ground and the bigger it is and the straighter it is,
the more they think, you know, measuring shadows is primitive. You know, we're more advanced than that.
No, you can go as far down to the split second as you like with it. You see. OK.
So it depends on what you're using to measure it. It's not a matter of it's, you know, unrefined.
It's not like you're trying to cut things with it with a blunt stone.
You depending on how you sharpen it, that that's that's how sharp it is.
I mean. Well, yeah. And you want it's techno lithic lithic, meaning rock or stone because it's more stable.
But at one point I used a concrete pad with steel cable and all this other stuff and it gets really, really accurate.
I mean, you'll see the shadow move just as much as watching the seconds dial on a clock.
It's that it's that refined. But, you know, you're talking about dedicating a structure.
So in essence, this is just as accurate as any other system.
It's a relative system because if the if the earth stops and the sun stops, time stops. Right.
And this had happened around 2011, by the way, in the spring for a very short time.
And I had a witness to that guy named Jerry Kirk in Arkansas.
I was not in I was in California at the time.
He just desperately wanted to get in touch with me if I had witnessed and I had not.
But he had. I know. I don't think I ever got into that, but that's all I could say about it.
Time did stop for a short time around 2011 in the spring.
OK, so you said you feel you feel it. Well, because you're biological. Right.
All of the systems, I would even say metals and minerals and things that grow on the earth,
because metals and minerals do grow. If you look at naturally found gold in quartz in the ground,
it almost looks like it grew into that shape. You know what I mean?
Well, there are mineral elements in your bloodstream, too. Right.
So which are affected by many things. Native Americans had shown me this in the past.
You know, the the the effect of magnetism on on your blood and this kind of thing.
I'm not saying I fully understand it. I'm just saying I recognize that that's part of the you know,
part of the the mix, so to speak. Right. Right.
And remember the all that all that mineral and metal in your blood is created by the body out of out of.
Well, through induction, I was going to say through by thin air.
But, no, we've kind of covered that.
I probably will do more of an advanced aspect into that because I am every day.
I do think about it, how things are produced in the body.
And there are ways to manipulate that. And terrariums are a good idea, by the way.
Grow a terrarium, you know, where you lock close everything up in a bottle.
You don't add water. Things grow in there and the bottle gets heavier and heavier, even though it's completely sealed.
That's one way to think about it.
But anyway, to go back to time, when you feel the noontime being when the day starts, that's actually quite correct,
because that's pretty much how things work.
And most people tend to venerate those that are intelligent, you know, the geniuses or the wise men of the world.
Right. But when you get into what these people put out, you know, the really, quote, unquote, smart people,
if you were to spend time with them, how are you so smart?
Well, they'll tell you it's all intuitive, right?
It's not book smart, right?
So the intuition that comes along with understanding the day starts at noon.
It's also in the language when you fast for a day, you end your fast by eating, you break your fast, right?
That's before noon.
Okay, so there's many aspects to that.
You know, years ago, anything past noon was considered the next day, on and on.
This is stuff, basic Greek speak stuff.
You could do your own research.
And most college courses still in astronomy do dedicate about five minutes or a half a paragraph that the day starts at solar noon.
Right.
And we talked about that during the banking discussion, too, about how, you know, after a certain time of the day,
it would become the next day, even though, technically speaking, the calendars had not changed.
Well, because there's two systems to separate.
Right.
It's the – I think you always put out – it's like a metric to see where society is.
You give them two choices.
One is obviously wrong and for the dummies, and the other one is sustainable through verification and, you know, actual knowledge and things that work.
And if you notice that most of the population goes for the real dumb shit, well, you've got a real dumb shit population, and this is how you control them.
If you notice that you have a good amount of the population going for the stuff that is based on, you know, accurate knowledge or things that are verifiable,
then you're going to have to control them a different way.
And by the way, those are really difficult to control, right, because they ask too many questions.
Well, yeah.
I mean, I think if you're prepared for the questions, though, maybe it's not so difficult, but we don't know that verifiably because I have not witnessed it.
Well, what do you mean, which side?
Well, a more – okay, a society asking questions, if you know how to direct those questions properly, okay, it's just like any debate, any discussion, it can be handled.
I don't think it would require that much more difficulty.
You know, just intuitively I feel like it wouldn't, actually.
Well, we went through – well, in most people's memory, the second time that you're not supposed to question what they say with the plandemic,
before that it was 9-11 and before that it was most likely JFK, the big ones, you know, that you're not supposed to question.
Right, right.
Because the knowledge put out is, you know, unmoving and that's the way it is.
Yeah, obviously all that stuff is tailored towards the dummies, what they put out, which is the majority.
Okay, so the Sun, again, there's no way to really emphasize it.
It just is, and everybody's going to have their own, quote-unquote, personal relationship on how that works for them, right?
And you could study that, by the way.
Without even studying, unfortunately there's not much in the written you can get these days unless you really make a big effort.
If you're studying the Sun starts – the day starts at solar noon with the Sun, you can't query that very easily.
I mean, if you put that in, let's say, a browser search, you know, Google it, people say, you're not going to get much, very little.
But if you start searching the behavior, certain behaviors and cultures and traditions that are done around noontime or early afternoon,
you're going to start to see, you know, the siestas in Europe, everybody eats lunch and takes a nap, right?
It's the end of the day, right?
They shut down all the stores about 11.30 or so in Spain, right?
And they open the stores back up at 2 or 3 in the afternoon, right?
You see, so it's the end of the day.
So you could look at all the various cultural – you mentioned Native Americans.
They have a very rich – if you can get into it, very rich history about the day starting at noon and things that they've done or did culturally.
So that's pretty much it with the Sun for now.
When you go to the moon, you start speaking on anything with the moon right away.
I've gotten a few comments.
People say, oh, you're on the lunar calendar.
No, no, no.
It's not lunar.
It's not solar.
It's both.
The Sun determines when the day begins and ends and where the days start is determined precisely.
And the moon determines your monthly feature, you know, where you have the four weeks per month, when the month begins.
The way you really date things are typically what day of the month.
People didn't really add numbers.
We still don't add numbers to days.
It's not day 245 or it's not – I think now it would be like day 100 or something.
We don't speak like that.
We say it's March, meaning the moon, whatever, right, or April, whatever.
So the days are not really numbered as much as they are parts of the month.
So when you reckon when the month starts, you actually get a better day count.
So that's the difficult part maybe that I've noticed – well, not the difficult part.
It's less clear, and more people I've noticed that have tried to figure the system out have had more difficulty with the moon than with the sun.
Let's just put it that way.
Right, but I have heard you say in the past fairly simply how to reckon when the moon begins its cycle, right?
So that should be when we have an actual new moon, right?
That should be the beginning of that monthly cycle, unless I'm misunderstanding.
There's two misunderstandings there.
Okay.
The cycle is part of a bigger cycle, meaning whether you have 12 or 13 moons,
and the new moon is the full moon, not the dark sliver, because you can't measure anything with the dark sliver.
In other words, how would you measure the start of the month visually using light of the moon with the dark sliver that they call the new moon?
You can't.
But with the full moon, you use the same sun dial or you make a moon dial, right?
It casts a shadow and you can measure, you can see the progress along the equatorial as well.
So when you say new moon, it's the full moon.
I'm using the word new moon because it adds conflict, and the new moon I think I've given…
Well, yeah, I meant the moon when it is fully observable is what I meant, actually, when I said new moon.
So it's full moon, dark moon, yeah.
Okay, so the full moon versus the dark moon, and the dark moon would be when you have a sliver or maybe not even a discernible sliver, right?
Well, what happens is it goes, it wanes and it becomes absent, and then it's absent for a night, and then it appears again maybe the next night as a very fine crescent, and then it waxes to a larger…
Right.
And also you'll notice that the moon is at a different position during the day.
When you get more into this and the night, like, for example, if you knocked someone out and they woke up from a coma a month later or six months later or a year later and they went outside, it doesn't matter what day or night it is, time of day or night or week or whatever, can you go outside at any time of day or night and look up or look at the sky and figure out what day it is and what month it is?
That's pretty advanced, right?
That's fairly advanced from what I can observe, yeah.
Well, I could do that, by the way.
Okay.
Because I've been looking at it for two decades now, and I can give a brief explanation, a real short way.
But, for example, if you're out in the morning, any time between sunrise and, let's say, 11-ish, a couple of hours before noon even, and you see the moon in the sky going from east to west, it's the first 10 days of the month, right, depending on where it is.
You see?
That's an easy example.
If you're going out in late afternoon and, let's say, 3-ish, 4-ish before sundown and you see the moon is up in the east, you're probably in the late 20s of your day.
You're in the third week.
Okay.
Right?
And then where you are at night, again, so the moon, you could actually keep time with the moon where it is in the sky at any time during the day or night.
When it's absent completely during the day, it's the middle of the month.
Right?
Okay.
And then you use other factors.
So, this is more, believe it or not, there are people even today that can't read an analog clock down to a second or a minute.
You know, usually when someone looks at an analog clock on the wall, let's say it's 3-27, everyone tends to say, well, it's about 3-30, right?
Right.
But if you ask people, let's say it's a large clock and it's graduated down to the minute, what time is it?
They'll look at it, well, it's 3-30 and a couple of lines short.
You know what I mean?
They don't really – so, it's along that function as well.
How well are you at reading instruments?
When the sky becomes an instrument, well, now you're pretty fully engrossed in your environment in terms of timekeeping.
So, let's get into the moon a little bit.
Many people are – again, very easy to figure out solar noon.
It's pretty general, but if you want to be precise, we just said how to do it with shadows.
Now, the moon is a little more complicated, not because it should be or it really is, but it just appears to be initially when you get into this.
And sometimes people miss a day or so.
They'll think it was the full moon a day after or two.
So, instead of it being the 14th day, some people think it's the 13th day or the 15th, right?
You have a day off.
One day off.
Okay.
One way to look at it is very simple.
Well, the first way to look at it is when is the moon full?
That's when it is the most round and the brightest.
It has nothing to do with how big it appears in the sky because after the moon is full, you'll notice it rises much later and it seems much larger, much, much larger.
But if you look at it, it's not as bright given the surface area, luminosity, and it's not very round.
It's kind of like a flat spot, like between 9 o'clock and 11 o'clock, if it were a clock.
Okay.
If it's a little shy, if it's prior, if it's before the full moon, it'll be a little flatter on the lower part of the moon and it won't be as bright, right?
And it'll be smaller, way smaller.
So, the full moon is defined at how round it is and how bright it is for its surface area because you could really get some really big moons.
You could look at moon images and people say, hey, look, it's the full moon.
And they like to photograph it because it's a huge moon, right?
And it's like three days after the full moon, right?
But they just call it a full moon and it's still within the full moon, quote, unquote, festival or time of the beginning of the month.
So, yeah, so generally, if you're going to say the beginning of the month, it's a two or three day spread.
It could be as much as four day spread, right?
Okay.
But do you want to get more accurate than that?
Most likely you do if you're listening to us.
Right.
Because you want to be able to number the days and figure out what portion of the month it is.
So that you know when the next month comes and, yeah, okay.
Yeah, or what day of the week it is, let's say.
So, one, the easiest way to also begin looking at the full moon is you'll notice that before the moon is full,
it kind of rises in the east and there's still a lot of blue sky.
And if you look over to the west, you'll see the sun disk is still visible.
It's just maybe touching the horizon, maybe slightly below, but you can see the sun disk.
Well, in that case, the moon hasn't ruled over the sun.
I don't want to sound like an astrologer or whatever, but there are dominations in the sky.
What dominates is the feature to pay attention to.
So if you see the sun disk in the west and the moon is coming up, it's still a little before the full moon.
If you see the moon rising in the east and it appears to be kind of yellow, that's because of the atmosphere,
the dust through the atmosphere.
And if you look over to the west and the sun is below the horizon, there's a 99% chance that's the full moon.
Okay, so, and it would be coming up in the 12th hour.
So your hours with the sun, by the way, there are 12 hours in the day, daylight.
But it's divided by 10, right?
So it's 18 degrees each, 6 plus 6 plus 6 per hour, right?
What does that mean?
Okay.
There are 12 hours of daylight, but the sky is divided into 10 segments.
So noon is in the middle, you have 5 on the left, 5 on the right.
Well, how does that give us the 12 hours?
Well, the first hour is when light appears in the east and the sun is still below the horizon.
Once the sun comes up above the horizon, you're into your second hour.
So then you have 10 divisions, right?
And when we get down to the horizon in the west, that's the 10th division.
So that's 10 divisions plus the first one that you don't see the sun.
And as you get to the west, if you see the sun going down and it's still above the horizon, you're in the 11th hour.
When the sun goes below the horizon, you notice the sky is still lit, but you don't see the sun.
That's the 12th hour.
So your first hour in the east in the morning is when the sky begins to light up, but the sun has not appeared.
The 12th hour is when the sun has disappeared, but it's still lit.
Well, would a way to explain this be that the sun is coming up, that is, it begins as it's emerging and doesn't quite emerge yet.
That's your first hour.
Your last hour is it's disappearing.
And this is where?
Sunset.
That actually makes perfect sense to me, because you have the two transitional hours, basically, even though there's 10 segments in the sky, and therefore you have 12 hours.
Right, because you have the hour before it appears into one of those segments, and then you have the hour after it disappears from one of those segments.
So the first and 12th are not visible.
Similar with the moon, but in a different way.
I just had to throw that in because they're intermixed.
People again say, oh, it's a lunar calendar.
I'm like, no, it's not.
It's solar and lunar.
Imagine working in construction or whatever, and you need two tape measures, because one is only good for measuring length, and the other one is only good for measuring width.
It's kind of absurd when you first think about it, but if you lived in a world where that was true, it would be normal.
I suppose.
I don't know how you make sense of that, because length is length.
Well, they're both linear measurements would be what I would say, but they become nonlinear when you have to go get another tape measure.
Okay.
All right.
Well, that makes a lot of sense.
For time.
For time, yeah.
But go ahead on the, what would you question on the, because there's more to the moon, by the way.
I'm going to let that settle in.
Yeah, I'm letting this settle in.
That's really, really interesting, though, because the 12-hour span, I never thought of it before that way, where we have one hour where the sun is not fully visible, but it's coming into visibility, and the other one where it's not fully visible again, but going out.
Still, the light is there.
I never thought of that before.
That's totally new to me.
Sure, sure.
But no stain on you, but I've only mentioned it about 20 times on Ocelli and the Greek before.
You see, when the time isn't there to hear it, right, there's hearing and listening.
And this is, I'm going to humbly say this.
No one ever held my hand or told me any of this, right?
So, I've come up with this stuff in the beginning.
I thought I was inventing it, because it just, I couldn't find it or hear from anyone.
Right.
But I just sat down, and just using logic and reason, how would you work this as a clock?
Like, imagine you're drawing.
You're the first person to make the clock with the large hand and the small hand, right?
It existed before, but you didn't know it, and you ended up coming up with one that looked exactly like the one that existed before you knew it even existed.
Right.
Right?
Okay, so I felt like I was reinventing the wheel, but I have two things working.
One is that the system is accurate, and second, the system is, well, it's conveyable.
Anyone can see it, and it's flawless, and it works, and it fits in with pretty much however you want to use it, whether it's scientific or cultural or whatever.
Okay, so I think we kind of interjected.
It went from the moon to the sun to the 12 hours, and it's easier to describe.
So when the full moon makes its appearance at night, it's going to be in the second hour where the sun was in the morning, right, because it's above the horizon.
Okay?
Okay.
All right, so let's say we have a day where we say, I think the full moon is coming tonight, right?
So you all gather around, and you see, or yourself, you see the moon rising.
The sun is already in the 12th hour.
It's below the horizon.
And you see the moon coming up, and it's kind of a slightly dark gray, black background behind the moon, but a slight blue background behind the sun.
There's a 99% chance that's a full moon, right?
And you're going to say, oh, it's the full moon, but so is today the first day of the month?
Yeah.
Yeah, okay, because, yeah, if that's where, yeah, okay.
Yeah, but hold on.
But when did the day start?
It started at noon, didn't it?
Before you saw the moon, because remember, it's evening time now, isn't it?
All right.
Okay, so.
It started at noon.
In other words, so, you know, you're quick to answer.
You're correct, though.
Yes, is it today the first day of the month?
It is.
But when does the day start?
At noon.
So does the day, so is it tomorrow that you mark it, tomorrow noon, or was it today noon?
Yes, today noon, but noon already happened, right?
So it seems like the marking of the first day of the month happens in the evening when the moon rises,
which is already when you mark that day, that noon, you see.
Well, it sounds similar to me to the first hour, right, where you don't have the observation of the sun yet,
but it's coming.
Very much so.
Yeah, maybe, yeah, sort of, but let me just throw this in.
This is, this was a, this you won't find anywhere, by the way.
I have been looking for a long time, and I just chalked it up as being like one of these priestly secrets.
You know how certain classes of people take control of information to use so they can venerate themselves over others, right?
Okay, so I classify it as a priestly secret, and this is the secret.
All of the metrics that we use to determine a full moon, which is how, what makes it full is how round it is,
in terms of being perfectly round, equidistant from the center, and how bright it is, meaning its luminosity per given area.
Photographers would know exactly what I'm talking about with a light meter.
Not the size of the moon, but the intensity of the light for its given area,
and that given area is within a perfectly round circle.
Okay.
All right.
Well, that occurred the previous morning, before the day started, that morning, in the West.
So let's say it's evening time right now, and we're watching, and the moon comes up full right now.
We call it the first day of the month, like you so aptly said earlier.
Yes, it's the first day of the month.
But remember, the day started at noon, which is, let's say, six hours before.
But that morning, we went six hours before the day started at noon.
And that morning, even another six hours before that, at dawn, when the sun was still in the first hour below the horizon,
if you were out really early in the morning, in the summer, not so early in the winter, it could be as late as seven-ish on the clock,
if you get up and go outside and look towards the West, you will see the moon is full in the West.
But it would be in the eleventh hour position, and it would be as full, if you took a photograph of it,
and the photograph of the moon that night, that you declared the first day, they would be identical, which is an anomaly.
Because when the moon moves through the sky, every time it's viewed near the horizon, it looks different.
What I mean by that is, the day before the full moon, the moon will look smaller, not as round.
And the day after the full moon, the moon is much larger, but not as round and not as bright.
But what's interesting about this is that if you cite the moon, if you think, like, well, tomorrow night's the full moon,
and that morning you get up, tomorrow night meaning afternoon, and you look in the West,
and you will see that moon is full in the West, in the morning, pre-dawn.
If you photograph it and measure it, well, you wait until noon, the day starts,
and that night when the moon does appear full in the East, and you photograph it and measure it,
it will be identical to how it was almost 12 hours before, which is an anomaly.
No progress.
That should not be happening.
So there's no progress on the first day of the shadow, like, you know, starting to take a piece out of it, so to speak.
There's no change.
And actually, there's a moondie.net.
They measure the moon, and they pretty much, let's say it's a 99.1% chance it's a full moon tonight.
You'll see it happens in the morning at that marking, and then it stays at 99.1% or 99.2% all day.
But the next day, the percentages start to go up and change.
The percentages change very radically.
So there is no change in the moon for about 12 hours, which is astronomically an impossibility, by the way.
But it does happen.
It's kind of an anomaly.
It shows you that we live in a simulation kind of thing.
Does that always happen, or is that?
Yeah, well, for the past 20 years, yeah, that I've been viewing this.
So here's the interesting thing.
So tonight we look at the full moon, like you said earlier, and we see that the moon is full.
So today, like you said, it is the first day of the month, right?
Right.
But that moon was actually full that morning before you started your day count at noon also.
No one talks about that, by the way.
You won't hear this anywhere.
And they're identical.
So you actually have a full moon that appears in the west before you mark that day as noon,
and you also have it within that day after you marked it as noon at night.
So you have two witnesses, and the full moon, or the moon being full in the west for a very short time,
then you have the noon day count, and then the moon being full at night,
it seems like the moon puts brackets around the day.
Like you have one witness before you measure the day count at noon,
then you have your second witness after you measure the day count at noon.
Right?
Isn't that interesting?
So what I do is if I use the Pope's work schedule calendar, you know how they put each day number in a box?
Right.
Okay.
Well, where the box ends, let's say you're looking at March 5th, you see a box,
and then there's March 6th, and they're separated by a vertical line.
Okay.
Right?
Well, that's where I put my day start point.
Instead of counting the days in the box, I count the lines.
Count the lines.
Okay.
You see, instead of the box, and it works well.
So let's say the moon, let me just go to the monitor here for a second.
I'll give the website.
It's fairly accurate, and I want to talk about it just for a little bit more.
It's called a moon phase.
Oh, it's a D-I-E dot net moon.
If you just put in moon phase, D-I-E, like die, dot net, it's pretty accurate,
and they give you a visual.
Okay.
Like right now, it's the waning crescent, 27.4 day old moon, 5.1% lit.
So where were we?
I just wanted to give that.
Oh, when they tell you, for example, on that website, okay, this is what I wanted to say.
On the bottom left of that image, when you open it, it says full moon last was March 7th at 1242 p.m.
So what I do is I open the calendar, let's say, and when I see the seven, right,
I move over to the left where there's a line, a box, you know, and it's six prior to seven.
In between the six and the seven, yeah.
That vertical line is my day one.
The next, so the line where the two boxes in between the seven and the eight is day two, day three, right,
and you just count those lines in between, then counting the box.
So because those lines where the two numbers meet signifies midnight, but I make it signify noon.
Because, see, when they go from six to seven, they change that at midnight.
We're changing it at noon.
So I use the line instead of the box.
Oh, that makes sense. Okay.
So let's say I just opened up, let's say I wasn't around and I want to reference this.
It says here on the di.net full moon phase, the last full moon was March 7th.
So I open the calendar, the Pope's work schedule, and where I see the box number seven,
the vertical line between the six and the seven is day one.
The vertical line between seven and eight is day two.
The vertical line between eight and nine is day three, four, five, six, seven, right, eight, nine, ten.
I keep going.
Right.
So and that's just a simple shorthand way of doing it.
Because, by the way, when you look at the Pope's works, you know, the calendar that you get,
you hang up on the wall from the hardware store.
We're taught to look at that and each box is the day, right.
So it's a shorthand way.
You don't have to write it that way.
It can be a line.
Right.
So I like to create a shorthand method and I could still use the Pope's work schedule with the citing
and I just count the line between the numbers.
It makes it much simpler for me.
So that does put us on the 13th day then, right now as we're speaking, right?
Yeah, let's just take a look at that.
So if we're to convey that methodology, the shorthand,
so I would go 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, on the 11th, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, and 14 because it's past noon.
Ah, okay, okay, right, because it's noon.
Okay, so right as we speak, we're at the 14th day.
Yes, yes.
Although according to the Pope's work schedule, third month, 19th day.
Yes, so the 13th started on the 18th at noon and was over, the 14th started on the 19th at noon.
Right, okay, because of the time of day.
We're at 4 p.m. where I'm sitting.
Right, right, okay.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, that's right.
You could actually, I'm speaking, you're in the future.
We're speaking, but you're talking to me from the future.
Yeah, yeah.
Very much so.
That's why this is all spiritual.
It's not physical.
See, so when you're speaking to someone in the future, it has to be a spiritual thing, right?
Okay.
It's not physical.
This is the first time this has made as much sense to me, to be honest with you.
So this is really a great explanation.
Well, I'm giving more of the shorthand and the methodology, less philosophy.
Yeah, that helps.
The philosophical part is how screwed up we are because we're on the Pope's work schedule.
Well, one of the thousand reasons we're so screwed up.
Right?
So, okay.
It's kind of like taking a pill.
It's like I feel terrible.
My health is in bad shape.
I'll just take this pill.
The doctor said, or a doctor, remember, the doctor.
Who's the doctor?
A doctor, a medical technician said, I'll get better if I take this pill.
Do you think you'll get better?
Never.
Right?
So that's what the Pope's work schedule on the clock is a pill.
Just take this and you'll be fine.
Actually, you won't.
I've had experiences with people.
By the way, when I say people, I'm not talking about common people.
I'm talking about your professionals, your wealthy, your upper tier people.
People that were, let's say, successful financially in business and whatever.
When you get to have a one-on-one conversation when no one else is around and they're in a tired mode,
when people are ready to go to sleep or they're drunk, it's hard to be dishonest.
They're most honest when you're ready to go to sleep and when they're drunk, right, supposedly.
Well, I've done this with several, quote, unquote, where people use a metric as people being successful.
I approach them with this in mind, the topic we're speaking on.
I said, do you feel like there's something lacking in your life or in general?
Do you feel like you've got a pretty good handle on everything?
How do you feel about life? How do you feel about things?
Yeah, I've always felt there's something lacking, always.
I really don't know. I just go day to day.
One of the reasons why is because they're out of whack.
Their body's out of whack with time.
They're not harmonizing in time.
That's not saying the only reason.
So once you start getting the actual physical and spiritual reality of time,
that's just one less thing that's going to add to that doubt of what the hell am I doing here.
But let me ask you this because this occurs to me.
I mean, you're talking about successful people and all that,
and I'm not saying I have a lot of interactions with those people.
But frankly, I find that if you get somebody into a more relaxed state like that
where they've either been drinking or there's a couple of other instances where that occurs too,
drinking or tired or whatever,
I would say that almost anybody would say that something is lacking, something is off.
I mean, no matter how successful or unsuccessful they are,
almost anybody who's thinking about it.
Now, there are people that give no thought to anything
and just seem to be – a popular term is the NPC thing, right?
But honestly, it's just – there are some people that have no thoughtful direction.
They just seem to go through life and try to give as little thought to it as possible.
They don't have the ability to think, by the way.
So when that subject comes up, they have to skirt the issue.
Well, there you go.
But are they skirting the issue or don't they feel it?
I would just say that anybody who's ever given any sort of consideration to the meaning of life
or the meaning of things or the meaning of themselves,
almost all of them would report, yes, something is lacking, something is missing.
Sure.
The reason I brought up the successful people is because I've noticed most people –
when I say successful, the metric is depending on what society you're in, right?
If you lived in a society of cannibals, it would be how many shrunken heads you had in the bag, right?
Sure.
So in this one, it would be most of the time when I've discussed this with your more common folk,
oh, if I could only get a better job, I'm just thinking about my job.
Oh, if the bills weren't so high.
Oh, if the children weren't so whatever.
What I mean by successful is the people that don't need a job, don't have any money woes,
can have access to any material thing or anyone they want.
See what I mean?
That would be more of a metric in terms of the human condition than someone who –
believe it or not, there are quite a few people, quote-unquote, in the masses
that their quote-unquote job is stressing the hell out of them whether they're at the job or not, right?
I mean they're constantly thinking about it or if they're trying to make ends meet, as they say,
they're constantly thinking about that.
It's like that's – to me, I see that as an artificial imposition on the psyche.
It's all artificial, right?
But there are consequences for them if they don't perform,
but their want and worry on a constant basis I see as unnecessary and uncalled for
because you're never – it's like you're not going to solve it by worrying, right?
Just like you can't solve an algebra equation by chewing gum, right?
Right, right.
So that's why I bring them up and that's why when I bring up a metric regarding knowledge and education,
I'm always speaking about the professors and the professionals, not the common people
because if you – when I say the people don't know what's going on with the human body,
I'm not talking about the everyday person on the street.
I'm talking about the doctors, right?
If I say people don't know law, I'm talking about the attorneys.
You go right to what would be representative.
In other words, if – remember in the 1950s, the flying saucer lands on the –
and what did they have?
The little green men come out and what do they say?
Take me to your leader.
Right, because you know nothing.
Because your leader represents the state of – what state of development your society is in.
You'll be able to represent that.
That's what I usually say or usually mean what is the representation.
Okay, so back to timekeeping.
Do you think – okay, let's just – I'm going to back off for a – what do you think, Chuck?
I mean is it easier now or is it what?
Where are we so far?
How do you feel about it?
Well, that made it a lot more – I understand it a great deal more.
I mean I know you said, okay, I've said it 20 times on here.
But yeah, you have.
But I've got to be honest with you.
It just clicked with me better this time.
I don't know if that's because I'm honestly internalizing the idea about noon being the more comfortable
and right beginning of the day or not.
I don't know if that's something that has just sort of shifted my psychology so I'm hearing this more.
Or if it's – I just finally landed.
I don't know.
I feel like I'm dense here.
You've actually broken something here.
What's broken?
It's kind of like a new pair of shoes is a new pair of shoes, right, until you wear them a little bit.
Okay.
Well, it took me a while, but there it is.
So no, I feel good about this.
This seems to me like people that question it and have had troubles with it will have much less trouble looking at it this way.
And I like the shorthand.
And the idea – I don't ever remember you talking about the calendar and marking it in between like that.
That's very interesting.
Okay.
Yeah, I have.
But that's all right.
It's not a matter of – everything is about timing.
Another way to mark the calendar, for example, is you know how they have the grid pattern, the boxes,
and the number is in the box, right?
Well, if you move the number over the line where it overlaps, then your time span –
because you notice how noontime is in between the 24 hours that they measure now.
It's still 24 hours.
You can make it 30 hours, 20 hours, whatever.
But basically the daytime is measured by a factor of 12, 10 divisions in the sky.
The first division is below the horizon in the east.
The last division, 12th hour, is below the horizon in the west.
By the way, that that I just mentioned, you won't find anywhere again written down as simple as that.
It's just – here's the thing.
Even with my wife and other people, I'm a very passionate, forthright individual.
To some people, they're actually afraid to listen to me speak in person.
Like they'll cower like, why is he so angry?
He's not angry.
That's just the way he speaks, right?
You know what I mean?
And I tell people you have to be more confident.
So what I mean by this is we lack – we are beaten down to the point –
not specifically beaten down but society is set up that way that you're never good enough.
One day you'll grow up to be – right?
Or what do you want to do when you grow up or what –
maybe you can be – one day you'll be president too, right?
All this stuff.
So you're never good enough.
So there's this underlying indirect low self-esteem that's embedded in the culture, western culture.
Well, you actually talk about low self-esteem embedded in the culture.
I don't know if you know Asian culture.
Okay?
A little bit.
That's even more.
Right.
So I mean even now, by the way, if you – Asian, especially from mainland China,
when they come to the U.S. and emigrate, you'll always see the woman in the backseat, right?
In the car.
Never in the passenger side, for example, if the man is driving.
I like that for safety concerns but it's – trust me, they don't do that for safety concerns at all.
So there's this lack of self-esteem and I constantly tell people when I say something
and they're kind of jarred and they're like, you need to be more confident
or if they do something and it doesn't turn out well, don't feel failure.
Just be more confident with yourself.
But that confidence has to be based on something, not cockiness.
However, there's – I don't know how else to say another word for cockiness.
But that's what – so like a chip on your shoulder or anything like that
because the Greek says you should be more confident.
No, if someone asks you not only – it's not only the how.
It's the why.
So once you understand the why, then the how is simple.
Most people say, show me how to do this, right?
But if you ask them why they're doing it, they don't know.
But once you get the why you're doing it, then you can – you also get the how.
But when you're doing the how, you say, I know why I'm doing this.
I think if I do this, it will be a little better, right?
But if you only know the how, it's going to be very difficult to improve on it
because if someone asks you even 20 years later why you're doing it,
this is how I was shown, never why I was shown, right?
An example, another example would be like I go to a sushi place
and the younger guys are – actually not anymore.
I do it all at home.
But when I was patronizing a sushi Japanese restaurant,
the younger guys seemed to be better.
You pick who you want as a sushi chef, and they would point to me this other guy.
He says, why don't you ask him? I'm busy right now.
He has 30 years' experience.
Well, my answer to that was, well, there's 30 years' experience.
In his case, it was one year's of experience 30 times.
You see?
So you can have – so to me, the amount of time that you've been doing something,
someone says I have 20 years' experience.
Yeah, but what kind of experience?
Is it a building up or is it you figured out this is how you're going to do it
the first few months you did it, and you just do the same thing over for 20 years?
Where's the advancement in that?
Yeah.
You see?
You know, it's weird, but I became like a training manager at a certain point,
which is kind of funny considering my visual problems, right?
But it occurs to me that the reason why I was effective at that is because
I always did explain why you had to do things.
I didn't simply say, look, just press this key, press this key.
I did that at a certain point, but I also would say, look, this is why this is done.
And what would happen is when a new situation would come up,
my guys were trained better because they could think about how to address something
even if they hadn't dealt with it before.
Right.
Instead of just the how.
Yeah.
I mean, I know that that was just a matter of functionality.
I just thought that it was best that they understood the logic
so that when something new came along, they might be able to address it
if they knew how to think about it.
I know that sounds weird, but –
No.
It just made the most sense to me.
Well, it is weird in a way that with the collective, the NPCs, for example.
But just to go over, I mean, do you think, okay, there's a lot of talk on AI,
and I'm telling you there is no AI because the AI is all about how, how, how, how.
They program the AI to sound like it's human or have emotion,
but the AI has no why where people have why.
Have you looked at those?
Actually, that's a pretty good, interesting little jump off point
if you wanted to go there.
You know, the chat GPTs and things like that.
Have you looked at those?
That's what happens when you have an elaborate machine.
In other words, it has access.
It's actually doing more what we do in terms of accessing all things
that when we hear, okay, cognition is to know,
and when someone asks you, do you recognize this, is do you recognize this?
In other words, are you comparing it to everything you've ever seen before?
How does it match up, right?
To recognize, to recognize, you know, is you're re-knowledging it.
In other words, where does it match up?
It's kind of like every time you see something or ask something
or someone tells you something, it's the same thing as the wooden blocks,
the square block and the square hole, the round block and the round hole.
You're trying to make things, where do they fit, right?
Right.
Okay, that's how the AI works really fast, and it's fooling everyone.
See, with me, if you gave me the odd-shaped pieces
and I wanted to make it a little easier, it might take a little longer
because I'm going to take out a knife and start whittling them, changing the shape.
You see, that's the why, you know what I mean?
I'm going to start whittling down the square block so it's round,
so it'll go into the round hole and the square hole, you see.
So it's just a matter of speed, really.
It's a matter of a force multiplier
as opposed to something that actually thinks at this moment
because thinking would actually require some of those other things
like the why and where this goes and how this makes sense
and, of course, recognition again because there are many patterns.
It is able to do some recognition because it can observe a pattern and match it up,
but that's all it does.
That's all it's doing.
Earlier we started, if you speak to someone who's, let's say,
advanced spiritually, mentally, what they call the smart, the wise, whatever,
geniuses in your society, when you have a one-on-one with them
or read any of their personal stuff,
they attribute it all to intuition or mostly to intuition.
Well, what's intuition?
To intuit, it's something actually, inspiration, intuition,
it comes from somewhere else.
It's almost like if you're a ham radio or CB radio operator,
you try to get a signal that's even further away than you've ever had before,
you see, kind of thing.
The AI will never have intuition as it is now.
It has to be biological, which will eventually get into our discussions with water.
And by the way, just to throw something in, whoever's listening,
there are quite a few people interested on water.
Before we start speaking on water in the future,
look up a woman named Vida Austin, V-E-D-A, Austin, just like the city in Texas.
And she does stuff with water.
She calls it hydroglyphs, where you take a petri dish of water,
a flat, let's say, dish of water, and put a photograph over it for a minute or two
or next to it, start freezing the water.
Don't freeze it solid, just till it frosts on the top,
and you'll see it reproduces very closely the image that you had near it.
It'll also do that with thoughts.
So if you have a dish of water, and you put it in your hand,
and you think of an octopus, and then put it in the freezer for 15 minutes,
where it frosts up, you take it out, and you'll see something that looks either
like an octopus or part of an octopus.
It's pretty interesting, right?
Especially when you ask it, what does God look like, or who is God,
or what's going to happen tomorrow?
Watch what happens when you look at that kind of stuff.
I just want to, Veda Austin.
Veda Austin, okay.
V-E-D-A Austin.
It's interesting because I have seen spiritualists that use bowls of water, but, you know.
This is specifically her shtick, and she traffics in hydroglyphs.
Hydro meaning water, glyph meaning writing or picture.
So that's her thing, hydroglyphs.
So anyway, look her up.
It's very impressive, and that's just one aspect.
Just to put in your Rolodex of what water can do.
Water is one of the most basic things, and yet complex things, it seems to me.
Well, of course, but go back to the AI.
Your AI doesn't do that.
No.
It can't on that level, and you're not going to get AI.
There's someone, Jason Breshears of Archaics, and I agree with him on this that he said,
and I've contemplated it.
We won't be able to have an AI, a real AI, because we're already under an AI,
and an AI that is overarching and has been here since time immemorial will not allow another AI
to come into its territory, just like a bear, right?
So you're only going to get the marketing or promotion of an AI where it's really not.
Think about this.
Imagine what computers were like in the 60s, 70s, and 80s, even 90s,
and now what you can get on a computer.
Doesn't just that variance in advancement seem like AI in itself?
Oh, yeah.
All they're doing is putting the next advanced variance of technology that, let's say, we could have,
but they're not saying, well, this is how your computers are going to be working in five or ten years,
and let's not tell them that because you know how they say the military is 50 years ahead of us
or whatever, right, technology.
Instead of just telling them this is what they'll be like, oh, this is just AI,
and you really can't have it because it's AI, but you can access it through chat, whatever you see.
What they're doing is parceling out technology.
It's kind of like, you know, there are flying cars, right?
You could look this up.
They're not mass-produced, but they're flying cars, plenty of them around.
Basically, you're in a traffic spot, push a button, it flies, just hovers and takes off,
plenty of those around, right?
But you're not hearing about that, you know, next Toyota is going to be able to do that.
Never, you're never going to get that.
But they do exist.
Yeah, I haven't seen those.
I haven't seen those.
Well, they call them flying cars and whatever.
Yeah, but they're not going to be like, well, this is what Toyota is working on, you know.
So this is how the AI is.
It's another aspect, a variable of technology that's being repackaged.
So instead of being part of the normal technological advancement, which it kind of is,
it's being dubbed AI and thrown over to another category.
Just like, for example, you have super exotic cars like Lamborghinis, Ferraris and all that.
You know, you could, Toyota could make one for really cheap.
It's just the shape, right?
But they don't because they want to keep that category alive, you know, like the Ferrari,
Lamborghini, you know, that supercar look.
Anyone can make a supercar.
You can make a supercar as cheap as, I don't know, as cheap as any other car,
but they don't stamp out that shape so they can keep that category.
You're going to maintain that category of AI, which it's not.