Just do it cold. Let's get started unless you got any news. Well, I have a bunch of talk about it later
Okay, you have a bunch of questions. You want to just put those aside or you want me to just throw them at you?
Yeah for after uh the questions for the for the thing just you know, I do best just throw them at me
I cold. Okay. I came to this world hot. That's why I like it cold. So let's just get started. Okay
All right, and that's what we'll do
So
Another sonic event, I I think we're at 141 greek. Is that correct?
Oh, i'm not keeping count and I think it's less than that
Well, we'll find out it's okay to make a mess of things. It's not so bad. Okay, fair enough. But anyway, yeah, what's going on?
Well speaking of making a mess of things. Haha. Uh, I have someone we this is the first time we have a third person
uh
Uh here and he's going to give some testimony. He can stay anonymous if he wants
But i'll let him uh
I don't know. Um
Okay, fellow should I say what the subject is or would you like to introduce the subject?
No, great. Go ahead and uh introduce it. Oh, okay. All right, if you didn't have any okay
This is regarding uh, you know, you guys have always heard of me about doing weather work and showing other people
And uh, i've done it with many people maybe a dozen or two
And uh, this man was very eager and um
He got into it and he bothered me quite a bit on details
Which I actually like I told my wife I said he's just like me when he gets into something
uh
He doesn't let it go, but he's actually
What made him stand out more than other people who want to know about weather?
There's a few more also that he just was constantly building devices
and trying to improve them and he actually
It i'd say it took about maybe a month or two or thereabouts, uh to get the get
You know some pretty effective work going would you say?
Yeah, I would say that that's pretty accurate. Um, most of that was was uh more of my uh,
my error because uh
Just trying to understand the concepts and the principles and then on top of that trying to actually implement them
Yeah, it took it took some time and then build them yourself by hand as it takes time
So what's you know, what's an instruction now?
What sparked it?
We speak often and what sparked me asking you to come on and give some testimony is because I found what you were saying
To be almost exact with what i've experienced and it's actually quite dramatic
So do you want to maybe it was a few days ago?
We last spoke about what you're going to talk about the fires and changing the wind and doing this that and the other and speaking
To the firemen, I guess that would be something really good to get into because the weather seems um haphazard and random
But when you start applying it engineering wise to attack a forest fire or something
You get you got some feedback back and forth. So maybe take it from the top on that and i'll let you run with it go
yeah, so um
I'll just give them the location because it kind of helps the uh, the listener just understand like the position
So i'm based in southern california
Anyone can go look at a map and you'll see the map of california and it's burning in all kinds in the north and the south
everywhere
And uh the one fire that affected me was uh within 12 miles
Uh, it came over the mountain and the smoke plume was huge
There was no I mean in previous times. I would have just said, you know, I I just have to wait and
You know breathe the current air and just leave the condition as it is because I did not know what to do
In this situation since i've been building devices and and testing them and affecting clouds and things like that
I decided to basically
Take the opportunity to put them into action in a much more proactive way for myself in the in the area that i'm in
um
and so I began to take the
the the water gun specifically
uh and pointed at the clouds and and the plume and it began to create holes in the plume and
Clear the air out and that was basically the step one. Uh, but the fire is a 23 acre fire
Uh 23,000 acre fire forgive me
and that
That is something that was at zero percent containment
And it went like that for about four days at zero percent
Uh, there were already a couple homes burned and uh evacuations were already happening in the local area
Um at this point I reached out. I was like, you know, i'm i'm not proficient enough to the point where I can get rain
You know the the way you can greek, you know like that
But I I wanted to you know, try to do something and so that's kind of the mindset that I came in with
Um the
So I reached out to a friend of mine. Um
And I asked him he's a firefighter. He wasn't working that particular fire, but I asked him I said, you know, like
What what would you want if you had a wish list as a fireman? What would you want?
And greek as you know, the first answer is rain
And I said, okay, I can't can't try to help you with rain
But what about something else and he said the wind if you can stop the wind we can set you know
A control line and then from there begin to work the fire
So I said, okay, let me try let me uh, so
um
As you know, there's different layers of the strata and from there
It's it's kind of like you kind of kind of have to feel and even with the technology that we have in the the satellites
that can tell you
uh an idea of where the
The jet streams are flowing how the wind is moving
It still takes a little bit of effort to find that specific
Spot where the where the wind is coming from and then point the guns at it
And from there once I did that
um
the wind stopped within minutes
And overnight the fire went from zero percent containment to five percent
And the air quality massively improved the moment. I implemented what you call the worldly gig
As well, and it basically created a bubble around my area almost like a force field in a way
and uh
Yeah, i'll just stop there greek. Uh, I kind of threw a lot out there. Oh, yeah
Um good. That's great. I just want to say when you said water gun, you know, it comes to mind
It's not a water gun. It's a water
Powered gun, uh, like an electric motor would be powered. It's just plugged into a water, uh source probably something with misting
preferably a lake you
Discussed you probably doing that but I think it was misting a small chamber that powers a uh,
What looks like a metal tube that's about roughly eight feet long by six inches wide, right?
Yeah, I have two of them I have two I've got 10 10 footer and an eight footer
A lot of people hear water gun and think that water is coming from a tube or from a gun. Yeah
So yeah, we're spraying water out of fire naturally it would change right because you know, you got a really big water gun, right?
Right, but uh, no, no has nothing to do with um, the water itself
What we're looking to do is get the energy out of the water
Just like when you plug in an electric motor, right? You're looking for the energy, right?
Uh, you're not shooting electricity out of the motor. I just want to make that clear. Otherwise, yeah, right
Uh, so you got feedback
And also you were able to change it and you've experienced a lot of things that i've been talking about for years now
Yeah, the feedback I got was from neighbors. I you know, I just you know nonchalantly asked them, you know, like
Did you notice a change last night? How is it that because the air quality in my area was at 140
Uh, which on that scale for the air quality is is
Particles per particles per cubic foot or meter. Yeah, there's a scale. Uh-huh
And it went down to blue that was like brown or purple brown probably or tan and it went down to blue 50 or something
Yeah, it went down to 39 and it was green and if you looked at the sky
You would have never known there was a fire happening 12 miles away. That was 23 000 acres happening
Yeah, it was quite phenomenal and it was quite uh, yeah, it felt good too
So good because i've been speaking about the weather lately and if anyone wanted to get into it like you have recently
I thought it would be great to have you on and just kick it with us on what you experienced and of course other things
When when he says a whirly gig it's rotating cones
Nothing, very special. You just build it and it wrote you rotate them about
Uh
What would you say 30 revolutions per minute something like that? Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, and you actually create a bubble an etheric bubble
Around a given area based on the device
And i've always chased fires. We've had them here. Also. I've had exactly the same experience
so
yeah, um
So I wanted also because i've been speaking about weather
Maybe it's a little bit of encouragement to hear what you have to say give a testimony you have to give
You know anything else you think uh, you want to say I mean regarding the recent weather stuff
I think you did make rain. You did make rain though, didn't you? Yeah, I did two days ago. Yeah contrary to forecast. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah
Showed up in the forecast, but it showed up. Uh
As a result of what I was doing, right? Yeah, it was not in the previous forecast. Yeah. Yes. Can I ask a question here?
How how long did it take? Uh for you to get proficient enough with this to
uh, you know, did you did it take you a few months did it take you a few years did it take you a few days in
order to be able to uh
Have a such a large effect. It sounds to me like you affected a pretty large area
So, I mean were you able to do that right away? Uh with with the principles that you were applying or no
How long you've been working with it basically
From for me. It's been about two months
Yeah, exactly. That's why but but like rick was saying I I built these devices
Um, he's he's provided some guidance on how to build the devices and uh, they're they're basically, uh
I would say an evolution above what uh, some of what trevor james constable was was building as well. Um,
and uh
But I I don't sometimes I really don't know
like, uh
how
It's it's I would say it's almost there's an inspiration that comes when you start doing this type of stuff
I don't know how to explain it
I don't know greek. I don't know
Yeah, if a furniture if someone is making furniture or building guitars will have the same
Yeah, anyone that uh, really well, that's what it's about if you I think you when you were building it
You really wanted it to be to succeed
Right, so you did and most people do and actually it's uh, sometimes better
That when you build these things you don't succeed so, you know what not to do
But in your case that was about maybe 50 50
right
so
Uh, and it's worked out well, so oh i'm just saying a couple of months worth of investment to you know to
Experience this in order to create such a large effect. I mean that's next to nothing compared to
You know, yeah, uh, what what you would think would take? Yeah
Go ahead chuck ask. Are you next to nothing? What was what would you say?
Rough cost would be good for what you used. Yeah, that's right. Not not labor just materials. Let's say
Is
Is that directed to me? Oh, yes
Yeah, what would be the cost of the devices and what you put into it materials because you can't go to you know
Buy them off the shelf
So yeah, some of the things uh, like the like the spiral pipe you get at an hvac store or something like that a supply
Yeah, you over you overpaid for some things but roughly a few hundred bucks, right?
Yeah, I would say around between like three or four hundred but I mean i've built a lot of devices, right?
Right, well here's here's the other thing if you took your time, could you find all that stuff in in a junkyard?
Yeah, for sure. I've actually been looking at garage sales and like, uh, you know, like
uh
Metal recycling spots
Yeah, it's kind of like remember et phone home the movie he built his thing to communicate with this capital
Mothership with junk
It's very similar to that. Yeah
But you can go out to buy you can go out and buy stuff. Uh
Motors and things like that, but basically
When you're around your neighborhood and you see people put out certain things for the trash, you know
Like recycling or whatever you pick them up and use them
And if you're building it from scratch the materials i've scaled it down. My designs are very inexpensive
uh, if you went with like
What trevor if you could even understand what trevor james constant was doing it would cost a lot more
You would probably need a fabrication
shop
Okay
Right. So, uh, would you say you could probably build this in your backyard front porch or kitchen, right?
Oh, yeah backyard backyard and garage. Yeah. Yeah. So would you say if we had uh,
Someone like yourself and someone like myself spread out. Let's say a thousand miles apart around the entire world. We could pretty much control
The climate and weather to a certain degree
Yeah, for sure
And uh, you had if you just had whirly gigs out there
I think you would you would get rid of a lot of smog problems that yeah a lot of rotating cones. Yep
the rotating cones yes, okay
Yeah, cool. They would get into hurricanes
Eventually i've done maybe 50 hurricanes
Abatement and I don't do them anymore because people you know, they love disasters, right?
So when there's when the hurricane goes away, they're like, ah, okay. What else is going on? Right?
So you're taking away their tv greek, you know, if you take away the disasters, what are you doing?
Or if you're feeling really evil, you could wake up and turn a county into a federal disaster zone. It's up to you, you know, so
But you gotta you know be responsible, you know, um and take control
This is this entire realm was given to us to a certain degree if we could find out how to do it, right?
so
Excellent. Cool, man. Thanks. Thanks for sharing that because really I wanted to have you on again in case
I've been bringing up the weather a lot. And what if people want to get get going on it, you know, and here you go
You know two months or so. Thank you very much. Yeah anything else?
You want to I'll just say uh, if you start doing this work try to get
You know nonchalantly just feedback from people in your area so that you know
it's that the changes you're affecting are not just your imagination, you know outside of the
The tools and the apps and the things that you can see from satellite views
But I mean just so that you know that it's not just something you're manifesting in your mind. It's actually happening around you
So when you hear other people notice
some a change
You and you know that you were part you affected that change. It's it just helps
Build confidence in my opinion. I would advise against talking to people about it. They'll think you're crazy
But that's okay. Yeah, do it if you if there are people you're already speaking to. Yeah
Yeah, not about the details I meant more about like
Oh the conditions they notice the change in the conditions. Got it. Okay. Yes sort of survey the conditions
You don't have to bring up why you're asking exactly, you know, well i'm changing it
No, you don't have to say that you can just say have you noticed, you know? Yeah. Yeah. Gotcha
okay, I I almost gotten I set up once on the side of the road years ago and I said, you know where the uh,
Highway has these rest stops and there's 100 cars or so parked and uh the bathrooms sure
Oh i'm echoing here. Uh, anyway
Oh, I do am I do I hear myself doubling you're not echoing here, okay, and it's just me
Uh, and I told some people I was doing weather work and the sheriff one of the deputies came maybe a half hour later
and he was very upset and I
I had to tell him. Oh, come on weather. No, this is a
Daytime, um optical device. So come on the weather. Come on. Don't you know only god can do the weather. He's like, yeah
Yeah, that's right. Right, right. It's just telescope. Don't worry about it
Yeah daylight optical because
You don't see any mirrors in there or anything
But yeah, yeah, but they they don't need to they they won't understand even how to look for that
You know, they see a tube and you say hey, you know what? It's a telescope. They won't even bother
Right, they won't even bother uh, because even if it was a telescope
They don't know how to see most people unless they're familiar with it
But I want to try to say is you have plausible deniability on your side, right?
I want to see if pluto looks any bigger in the daylight, you know
They won't under they won't even know that that's a silly thing. This is plausible. Yeah, right. Yeah
cool, excellent
All right any final words maybe and we'll continue with the rest of the sonic anything else
Well, unless you want me to throw one more question in there if you don't mind. Yeah, please go ahead. Okay. So, um
What do you have an idea of what inspired you?
Uh besides the fact that you know
Obviously there was a bunch of talk about this is affecting the area and you wanted to have a positive
change that you wanted to uh
Initiate I mean is there some reason why you chose to do this particular thing or
Was it just the first thing that came up once you felt good doing this work?
I I this is not the first
fire
So this would be I would say the fourth
But this was the biggest and this fourth in recent in recent days in recent weeks. Okay
and um
Since it was the since it was uh, 23 000 acres, um
the conditions were
Massively impacted. That's why
I put a little more effort behind it because it was it turned the sky black. So
So because of a sense of urgency you decided to try and affect this particular because I mean, you know, california there's a fire
Uh, you know constantly right?
The way I see it it's like california is on fire and also it happens to be a nice day outside here
Uh, you know just could be any given day
But the fact that this was kind of large it was nearby and you that that then you said to yourself
Okay, this would be something I want to affect
And you uh targeted particularly because of that
And rain probably as well because you're looking for me to make rain
Rather than the wind the wind here's the thing it might be difficult to make rain, but uh
But the because it requires certain conditions that have to be met first
But the wind you can change regardless any time and usually what would you say about 30 seconds or to a minute?
You're gonna affect the wind every time
Yeah
I would say a couple minutes
Yeah in greek you would say that this is uh, this is the kind of results almost anyone can achieve if
They put in the effort
and uh, you know, it's in other words, it's not something that uh,
Should be too difficult to achieve if you can wrap your mind around the base concepts, right?
Well, it's just like you want to play guitar, you know what a guitar is and that's it
You go buy a guitar you pluck the strings and sounds terrible then you start learning
Right, right how to play and then you practice and then you play better
right
Okay, well, thank you. I um
I'm satisfied. I don't know, you know, there's probably a hundred questions
Here's some bragging points years ago where american freedom radio danny before we started speaking, right?
He says my brother, you know, he's in washington state. Do you remember that?
Is my brother's coming from florida we got rain all week. Can you do something about that?
I said like do what he says can you make it like sunny and not rain for about a week?
I said, yeah sure
And then the next week we showed up and danny's like thanks. There was no rain at all
It was clear skies sunny, right right even stranger is unprompted by you. Uh, I happen to be you know
Because I do other radio stuff
All that was from the the lake. Yeah, too
So I was talking to a guy about this and uh, he mentioned
Oh, you know you talked to uh, the greek recently and I just started speaking with you
And I said, yeah, and he said, you know, uh, he uh, he came up with this thing that uh
Was able to help me when I was out fishing
I said, what are you talking about?
And usually he talks to me about a lot of technical things and uh, he he does a lot of work
The coil guy. Yeah. Yeah, he does a lot of work with what they call free energy, right?
So, uh, so that's what I was talking to him about and you know magnetism and how it's missing, uh from a lot of equations
And etc. Anyways, uh, so he just added the blue goes. Well, yeah, you know that guy well, you know
maybe don't tell too many people but
he uh gave me some directions about a device and uh, I had great a great time fishing because I was able to
Affect the weather directly around and this and that I said wow
With what actually? Yeah, and then he showed me what it was. Yeah, and he showed me what it was
So yeah, very rigid more specifically. I wasn't myself. It was someone I was working with in australia
uh, and he was uh
On various skype groups with this guy and he says well if you can affect the weather
And this person that I was instructing in australia for a couple of years. He would say
I'm not keen on that. It's a bunch of bollocks, you know bullshit, you know
and he had a reason why he wanted to try it and it worked and he
Then I just told him build this tube this way and when he goes out on his boat
He could stop the wind and go fishing right? Yeah, and he got back to me on that and says yeah
That's what he takes out
So I I don't think i've ever spoken to him
But I think that it came from the greek was relayed. It was because it was relayed to me pretty
Heavily, uh while it was going on and a result and then eventually it came up with you in conversation. Yeah
He just passed it along to me and uh, and I said, well, what are we talking about?
and it's just you know, what i'm saying is it's not like you're building a a giant, uh,
Uh, you know like like peewee's big adventure machine that makes breakfast. Okay, you know with
Your fishing poles. Yeah, it's basically what we call a translator, right?
Uh, it's a tube built a certain way with a double mirror configuration certain materials, but he yeah
And it wasn't that large and I think the one he built was only two feet or something
Very small three inches
Like I said, he showed it to me and it wasn't even like anything that looked like a device of any kind
Like you said it could have been something that he was carrying
To uh hold his fishing pole. Maybe very innocuous looking right?
And uh, so that was something that came, you know completely on
you know on uh
Un-signaled by you or anything. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. There's a lot of people out there. There's a chemtrail harry. He's got
He got real excited. There's a whole bunch of people but the whole thing is to have more of an organization
Where we can communicate in real time be like, you know, very simply put like the ham radio guys, right?
So actually
That would be a good thing to do the weather devices and ham radio
So when if there's an interruption you can still communicate, but right
Yeah, okay
so, you know the reason i'm bringing this up is because I have a feeling it's going to be
in the near future something that uh should be taken in account for meaning doing
more weather control, so
Excellent and you know
look
a lot of people like to talk about chemtrails and all that stuff and they they uh,
You know tell you how to build devices to affect the chemtrails and this is not no
That's not what we're doing at all. I was just going to say this has zero
That's right zero but this is that's a good cover for it because those guys are viewed as uh breakfast cereal variety
You know fruit nuts and flakes. Yeah, and um, and yeah, so you can easily associate or disassociate
Uh, you got plausible deniability on your side, right? Oh, that's right
That's another thing you could do, you know
If somebody doesn't understand or doesn't want to go with the telescope idea you could say well
No, i'm i'm here to affect the chemtrails, you know, and you just and they're not yeah
I'm, just uh, we're not it's just i'm building an optical device. I want to see if the tube can line up and
Yeah, there you go. That's so that's what works too, you know depends on your audience so to speak. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, exactly. So in other words, it's about being empowered, you know
right
Instead of you know, mealy mouth sheep or goats or whatever
Okay
Cool. All right. So
Maybe we should just uh, call it a sonic if the
Weather guy's still here. I think we this was pretty good
Uh, we've never done this before with a third, uh having a third leg on the stand here
Well, not somebody who was going to come on to discuss something that was relevant to us
No one time a long time ago. We had a guest. Uh, we had jack blood come in actually when we did a live broadcast
Yeah
So fundraiser for the show. Yeah for american radio. That was that was funny. Yeah, that was yeah, that was kind of interesting
Yeah, I would say it was a disaster but yeah, it could yeah with jack blood you never know
Oh, no, it's entertaining like a car accident, you know, just just so you know, but it didn't produce anything but it was showtime, right?
All right, so fine
Maybe we'll just call it. Yeah. Well, this is we'll do a wrap. I think this was a good break and something different and
You've been on for a little while you got it a little something different for the people on uh on patreon
And so, uh, don't don't forget you can comment on each sonic if you like and therefore attach it to the sonic event and let
Us know what you think or questions you have for each one as we go along
And the chitango is a good place
You could crack a beer open and go hang out in front of the chitango and see whose shoulder you want to cry on or
Want to write something and I read it
The most I stay away from it is a day. So every 24 hours, I'll take a glance at it
Right, I drop in and on in on it a couple times a week as well, but uh, but that's about it
Yeah, cool. There you go