The Sonic 50 Jubilee and Ocelli in the Greek.
So we forgive anyone who hasn't signed up yet.
Do we?
Anyway, I'm just joking.
Do we forget?
I don't.
Anyway.
Yeah.
You see what I mean?
It's just one of those things, right?
It's 50.
Okay.
Yeah.
I'm just throwing things out here.
Look, I want to have some fun tonight, and we're going to do that, and we're going to
explain some things, or you're going to explain some things, but let's kick it off with something
just to get it out of the way.
I did a drawing for the Aquius Argentum among memberships at the website, and the funny
thing is I drew the same name with two different methodologies, so I'm assuming that that should
be the winner.
Yeah.
Now, hold on.
Didn't I say when you started, I had a vision that the same person came up on two methodologies
and who it was and what time you did it, and you were like, wow, yeah.
That's exactly right.
Isn't that funny?
Yeah.
Here's the messed up part.
I started telling the Greek this after we were done recording.
I said, you know, Greek, listen.
I did a drawing, and he said, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on a second.
You drew it twice.
I said, yeah.
I didn't tell him anything yet.
I just said I did it, because he said, did you get to that yet?
I said, yeah, I did, and then he said, well, okay, so you drew the same name twice.
I said, yes, I did, then he started to tell me what time of day I did it, and he was correct
again.
Now, I didn't communicate any of this to him.
I love when that stuff happens.
This is what I keep telling people.
Time is not linear.
You know what it's like?
It's like when you go to the shops, and something's up on a shelf too high, and you figure out
how you're going to grab it, because you don't want to wait for a clerk to get a ladder.
That's what time is like.
I hear you, and look, sometimes, I mean, look, it's rare for things like that to come to me,
and most people can't pick things off of me like that, so it was really weird.
I was like, wow, how did you know all this?
But it was very strange.
I used two completely different methodologies.
I used a random number generator, just for the record, and then I had Frankie, the boy
here, my offspring, select a number, and both times, we got the same number and the same
person.
Actually, no, it's a funny thing.
There was a difference in numbers.
Different numbers, yeah, but the same person.
But the same person came.
It was a random, random, not a random, yeah, not a random selection, but each selection
was random in itself.
Well, right, because the random number generator, and plus, I have no idea what's in the mind
of a nine-year-old boy.
I just asked him to pick a number off a list.
That was it, and there you go, boom.
Same person came up.
Yeah, yeah.
We got a lot.
I think the person doesn't mind, we'll just use their first name, Joe, I think.
That's correct.
Now, there's more than one Joe who's a subscriber, but he's already been contacted.
He knows who he is, and yes, indeed, Joe is going to get that, and really fascinating,
because I drew him twice somehow.
I'm not sure why that happened, but I figured I'd note that.
Now, let's get to something that was in the chat room, and I think is important, and might
require some more clarity, because, again, this is rarefied information.
This is stuff you're not going to hear anywhere else at all, at all, okay?
You'll hear some version of this, maybe some sort of the same words in a scramble together,
but quite frankly, this idea about your inner voice, you hear about this all the time, right?
The secret, you got to listen to it, you got to listen to your inner voice, that's your
higher self, your blah, blah, blah, all of this nonsense in the woo-woo world.
Not the way the Greek explains it, and you have explained it before, and you have talked
about this inner voice, but there was a question there, so I wonder if you wouldn't mind going
over that some, and maybe providing us with a little bit more information, go ahead.
Now, that must have come up in the chat, or was it an email?
Well, it was both, actually.
Oh, okay, I'm curious, because the reason I asked that is because in the chat, someone
was fastidious enough to go back and hit maybe a month, or two, or three, and do a screenshot
of an answer that I gave, and let me just pull that up, and the inner voice, well, yes, voices,
any voices that you hear distinctly, especially the ones that sound like you, are not you.
You don't need a voice to talk to yourself.
One of the analogies, I don't know if I could find, maybe I'll find it.
Well, you go ahead and look for it for a second, but I mean, the thing is, this came up before
on a previous Sonic, and you started to explain that at a certain age, you do have your own
inner voice, it is there, but then it goes away, it goes silent.
Do you really want to do a whole recap on it?
All right, let's do a quick recap.
I think it would be worth it, yeah, because this is something that might be a little confusing.
Like I said, they're not hearing this from anywhere else, so it's not like they've heard
it before, unless they heard it on one of these Sonics, and I don't remember covering this
on the original Ocelli in the Greek, actually.
Yeah, let's end up with, okay, you know when the cell phone's low, and you got to give important
information, and the phone dies, but you had enough time to get some words in, so why don't
you just put the important stuff out first, even though it might seem out of context,
so the message gets across.
When you have an inner voice, most people don't think of it that way, but if you consider
that, you know, you're aware of it now, if you anticipate it, it stops, it goes silent.
That's proof enough, more than theory, that it's not you, right?
It's kind of like when someone's jabbering, and you tell them, go on, they stop, right?
Go on, go on, they stop, and you think it would encourage them, but you're anticipating
more like, oh, wait a second, you said go on because I'm just rambling, right?
Yeah, exactly, right?
It's like a reverse psychology, right?
If you indicate to, and it's sort of a weird indication where it's like, look, all you're
doing is making noise, but please proceed, that's usually my phrase, and please proceed
quite often stops people from speaking, they just go, oh, never mind.
But what about the same psychology works, spirit, study of the spirit, knowledge of the spirit
works with the inner voice.
If you find yourself on the toilet, on your way to work, in the shower, before you lay
down, or as you're laying down, or having whatever you're doing, and that voice starts
to be prominent, anticipate it, say, okay, I hear you, what else do you have to say?
As if you're a third party and watch what happens, or listen to what happens, it goes
totally silent.
And then you have this refreshing moment of, should I call it clarity, but it is clarity,
but it's not recognized as clarity.
Let's just call it silence, right?
Right.
It is silence.
Well, the analogy that I gave is the voice that we're given, it sounds like us and changes,
I'll get into that.
It's kind of like reading a billboard, reading a newspaper, reading a monitor where you see
a contrast with the black ink on white paper, right?
Or you get to read the font, different sizes, right?
The inner voice is more like Braille, where there is no sight, and you have to read Braille
by touch, and you have to learn that, right?
It's different, right?
It's a different sense completely.
But both communicate, both are communicative, right?
Ask someone who reads Braille, right?
But it has to be learned.
Now what happens is when we come into the world, there's a lot of theories of, I like
the Jack Fresco, when people ask him, what happens after you die, he says, what do you
remember from 500 years ago?
Nothing, usually, right?
Put the airy-fairy hypnosis stuff away.
Nothing.
So that's what happens when you die, it's just nothingness, right?
To a degree.
There's all these theories, but what I suggest, and I was having a conversation with a very
intelligent individual yesterday, engineering type person, whose subject of death came up,
and when we come here, we're kind of given a mind wipe, and it's as if we're raw and
ignorant and have to figure things out based on the environment.
And when I say the environment, I mean the culture as well, what culture you grow up
in, right?
And environment, I mean in total.
Environment meaning the physical, geographical, the family, the village, the city, the town,
the culture, all language, the history, when you were.
We have to figure it out on our own.
We don't know anything.
Now, just to make the point and paraphrase the conversation I had yesterday is this.
If we had the memory of being outside of this realm and what was previous, everyone would
seemingly be far more intelligent, forthright, and a lot more stuff would get done the right
way, but then we'd end up with a really sterile world, because everything would be right, pretty
much, or on a higher level, and it would seem sterile.
Ergo, when you watch someone, some poor sap is like a farmer out in the field, the UFO
comes up, picks him up with a light beam and takes him to another planet of advanced civilization,
and talking about Hollywood now, right?
You see a story like that.
When they take him to the advanced planet, doesn't everything seem a lot more sterile
on that advanced planet than Earth?
Yeah, that's true, always, yeah.
The way advanced society is always so clean that it's scary clean, it's very shiny, everything
looks brand new.
Minimalist.
Yeah, minimalist.
Everything's taken care of.
Yeah, everything is just handled.
That's true.
I think a part of what you're describing, though, about being reborn and forgetting
and all that, it sounds very similar to what Native American spiritualists say about being
born.
The idea that when you come into this world in a state of forgetfulness, something like
that they had said to me, because I tried to listen very carefully to what some of those
guys had to say years ago when I spent time with some of them, and it's very interesting
that it sounds exactly the same as what you said, just slightly different language where
you're saying about getting into the culture and this and that.
They certainly would say that the world around you would begin to teach you what is, and you
will learn from it, and then you'll begin to remember, but not everything.
You're not meant to remember it all.
And that's the kind of things they would say to me, and it sounds like, you know, very cryptic.
It's a common theme amongst many cultures and many theorists, philosophers, spiritualists.
Okay, so let's go on.
The reason we brought up the death and coming in is so you're here as an infant.
Now, one of the reasons you can't remember infantile thoughts, pre-formative years, formative
years, I call like, usually between four and nine or 10.
And before that, you never notice, when the infants are really young, they are very similar
looking and you know, there's some are different, you know, there you have to, you could size
them up, you know, like they size people up from short in size order.
Yeah, sure.
You could do that with infants, too.
But there's something that they have in common, which is extremely infantile.
You don't remember much from there, or from that time in your life.
It's because that is when you're totally in that raw state.
Like you just got zapped, and you're brought here, but there is a connection to who you
are and thought process.
I think on the last Sonic, I mentioned how the babies, one baby was rambling, and the
other ones were looking at him and baby, you know, rambling baby talk, right?
And when he stopped, they all laughed like he was telling a joke.
And it was exactly choreographed looking like it was if you choreographed it for a TV commercial,
they make things, edit things and stage things to look a certain way.
It's exactly what exactly what it looked like a baby telling a joke and the other ones laughing
their asses off.
Like you could have easily like in other words, you could have easily dubbed over like the
guy going, hey, two Jews walk into a bar and then a voiceover comes over and messes up
the joke a little bit.
But then you can tell he tells the punchline and they all laughed all at once.
Exactly.
Edit that together.
And it would look very sensible and orderly for the commercial.
OK, gotcha.
Good.
It almost looked like a TV commercial and it was surreal.
And I said, oh, my gosh, they have their own language and it's cogent and it has a lot
of information and so much that you could actually form a joke in a punchline.
Right.
Because when you have a primitive language, you probably don't have jokes and punchlines
because it's primitive.
You're just struggling to communicate when you develop humor and jokes and punchlines.
It means that you reach an advanced stage of communication with a lot of color and soliloquy
and then themes.
Right.
There's a certain level of sophistication you have to get to to get into, you know, using
metaphor and all these other things.
This is more complex than just pointing at something and going rock.
Yeah.
So I've discovered that exists in baby talk.
Right.
But we forget that.
So go ahead and speak the baby talk.
Right.
You know, so we can only, you know, sound like we're not saying anything, kind of like
when you bark at a dog or meow to a cat, they look at you like, what are you trying to do?
Right.
Just speak.
Just speak your regular language.
You know, you're not doing it.
Right.
Because most of the bark and the meow is inaudible anyway to us.
What I would suggest, though, is if you understand the size parameters in ham radio where antenna
lengths matter, there's something about the body that when it develops to a certain age
and we begin to have that inner thought that we think is ours and our voice is actually
beings that are on this plane, but a very ethereal plane.
In other words, they don't see our physical body just like we don't see invisible gases.
We could walk through them.
It's the inverse.
But they see our intent.
They see our thoughts as physical things because they're not physical.
So the nonphysical aspect of us is physical in their realm.
One theory is that this earth was dropped into their world physically.
This earth bounced off of another solar system into this solar system and it fell into the
line where their world already exists.
Right.
And but the physical part doesn't disturb them because they're energetic, but they see
all our energetic qualities and they're pretty advanced.
And they said, well, wow, this is the way our reality goes now.
So let's have fun with these humans.
Right.
So what they do is they give us a voice and we think the voice is us because it actually
sounds like us also now when they give us a voice, there's a mind behind that voice,
meaning let's just say a simple deduction.
When I say mind, it's like your level of education, your level of awareness, your level of whatever
your tastes.
Right.
OK.
And at this point, let's just keep the juvenile tastes and things like that.
When you develop your body changes again to pre-adulthood adolescence, they usually switch
up and another one takes over.
That is the adolescent voice.
All right.
That's why people in stages of their lives from childhood, adolescent to adult, young
adult, middle age and then older.
They feel like different people sometimes.
And you see this in society, by the way, oh, I'm having a middle age crisis or whatever.
Right.
You've heard of that.
So go out and buy a fancy car at 60 years old or whatever.
Fifty five.
Right.
I think in your 50s is when they had their midlife crisis.
Yeah.
Between the 40s, between 40 and 60.
Usually.
Yes.
Yeah.
This answers a lot of things that the rebelliousness of certain age groups and the yeah, the playfulness
of others.
Right.
This is all trained in these other beings that influence us.
And that sounds crazy.
Some.
But you follow it.
Follow it through.
So you notice that when you go past the formative years, let's say nine, 10, 11, become an adolescent.
What else changes is your physical length, the physical size of the body, different frequencies.
Just like the ham radio.
You change the antenna position and length and you get a different frequency.
Then the thought processes change again and they bring another individual.
You become an adult and they switch out to another individual.
Fortunately for them, let's say for economy of economy of exchange, in some ways exchanging
these beings.
I have gone on many sonic events for over two decades saying that most people stop maturing
at about nine or 12 years old between there.
OK.
Yeah.
That's so it's pretty easy for these guys to leave you to stick you with the nine or
12 year old entity that gives you the voice for the rest of your life.
Right.
And I'm talking about most of the people you'll ever meet, even their 70s or 80s, if you actually
objectively analyze them, you'll see that their mentality is pretty much the same as
it was since high school.
You might interpret it this way.
You'll see that no matter what age people are, they always have the ability to be what
we would call childish about things.
And it's like odd to me.
It's like, isn't this more mature a person than to get involved with this name calling
or nonsense that I'm saying?
Sure.
But that's a little more complicated, believe it or not.
What I'm suggesting here is they never get to.
We look at them as adults because of the age on their driver's license or the way they
appear or whatever or whatever position they hold in society.
But I'm telling you, they're infant and immature young adult high school mentality.
I'm talking about attorney generals, scientists, politicians.
You know, I once met who was it was a it was a former judge slash politician.
And I thought he had this teenager kind of attitude, high school kind of attitude because
he was a public person.
Well, I had conversations with him in person.
He was just like this.
Oh, my gosh, this guy stopped growing at 13 years old.
You see.
And if you have parents or grandparents or people are older, just sit down, listen to
some Greek, speak for a few days and then go talk to them and tell me I'm wrong, right?
I don't think so.
And I'll tell you another weird thing, though, that I'd like you to address here right here,
actually, is that when you're like, say, 20 years old and you're a little older than
me.
So you've already experienced this.
But when you're like, say, 20 years old and you look at, you know, say, 20 year old women,
they appear to be full grown adult women to you, generally speaking.
And then you get to be 30, 40, 50.
To me, I look back at a 20 year old woman now and I say to myself, that looks like a
child, a high school child.
Yeah.
A high school child at best.
Now they look like children to me, and yet they were fully realized adults when I was
in that age group.
Your perspective can change as well about your view of other people just looking at
the surface even.
But that presentation does happen where at a certain point, you know, you're looking at
a matured person physically, but that doesn't always follow that they behave like a mature
person physically.
Right.
I mean, mentally, emotionally, it's not and they don't.
And most societies like that.
OK, so let's carry on.
So let's take an individual that decides to mature beyond whether they take a professional
career or they they're autodidactic, teach themselves and they evolve, let's say their
awareness.
And when I say awareness, OK, the more you learn about the scene, the more you will also
learn about the unseen.
More will come to you.
So what I mean by that is like, you know, most people don't know how the money system
works at all.
And they feel like they have to pay taxes to keep society going.
Right.
They haven't lifted a finger to it doesn't.
And they all know at the same time, they all know at the same time money is created.
It's fiat.
They're told that.
Right.
So but they never put the two together.
So they're so they're one theory or one thing they believe does not match the other.
So people say, oh, you have to pay taxes to keep the buses and trains and schools going.
But yeah, I know the money.
They draw it out of thin air.
So you got to put those two thoughts together, man.
They cancel out.
Right.
You see.
So what's this?
So they're making you they threaten you if you don't pay taxes, nothing to do with running
the municipalities.
It has to do with something else.
What is that?
And they can't they can't put it together because it's not like you have to come up with why
they're doing it.
Just put the two together.
You see, it goes to zero.
You're ground.
This is the same with anything, with the human body, what the doctors tell you, what they
tell you about history.
And none of it adds up.
Right.
So the people are keeping everything bifurcated.
They have two thoughts that are contrary to each other in the same category.
Right.
Whether it's like taxes or the body.
Or whatever.
You know, they have one thought here that they oh, you have to need this to absorb nutrition.
But they already know if you look at it at a diagram of the intestine, there's no way
anything to go through.
So they maintain these these opposite poles, not more than polar opposite.
They're not poles.
They're like canceling opposites, like anti and pro.
If you put them together, they cancel out.
They maintain this in their mind their whole life and they never go forward.
So that's what I mean about the more you learn about what is seen, the more you will learn
about the unseen.
Because, for example, back to the money, you could find out pretty much all the propaganda
they tell you that taxes pay for for services and things and employees of the government
and all that.
But it's the same people that put that out, put out that it's a fiat currency.
But they don't put out what happens when you put the two together and you end up with zero.
Then why are they so stringent about why do they take it as serious as a heart attack for
you to pay taxes when there's nothing to pay with and it doesn't pay?
They don't give you that.
But once you put the two together and they cancel out now, it will what will come to you
is immediately so simple why they're doing it.
Right.
It's a control mechanism.
So and then and it's but it's unspoken.
So all of these unspoken things that exist in the realm will come together when you start
studying everything that has been put in front of you already.
That's what the whole premise of Greek speak is.
Right.
If you want to join a religion or science or a profession or anything like that, go see
what's been written about it and, you know, go ahead and read everything.
But you don't read everything word for word.
You just go through all the material, right, get your conclusions together.
And then you will start to see more and more and more.
OK.
An individual like that, which this is more of a spiritual awareness maturity, the beings
that give that dominate and give the inner voice, they got they got to go to a specialty
one now.
They got to go to another being that handles those people.
Right.
Because that's not normal.
This guy.
So the regular ones that are around that give everyone their regular voices, they got to
go to a professional guy to give this guy his inner voice.
But if you know that this inner voice is still a foreigner and by anticipation and you test
it, now they got to go to an even higher one.
This is where you hear about the demons, right?
You hear about when you exercise a demon, he comes back with a worse one, right?
Comes back later with his buddy.
It's kind of like the schoolyard thing.
You beat up someone in the schoolyard and a few days later you see the same guy you beat
up coming with two other friends and a big guy, you know, his brother now.
Right.
Yeah.
I was going to say a lot of times, a lot of times when I've knocked a bully on his ass
as a kid, what happens is they bring their older brother the next day.
And yeah.
Exactly.
It's the same scenario.
So once you start advancing and they are running out of candidates to substitute for the ones
that gave you the normal voice, then they bring in the big, the senior guys and, um,
they give you the voice too, but you know, it's you've busted them.
You already know it's an artificial voice when you hear something in your head that
sounds like your voice, right?
So then what they do is they mess with you a little bit.
They start giving you anticipatory thoughts, stuff of the future that's going to happen.
Kind of like what we did with the lottery thing.
Right.
So it's, this is a theory now, but so, so it'll be like, uh, you get up in the morning,
you got to go around town and do this and that, and you get this strong vision of a
red car, you know, uh, running over a cactus and, um, an old lady, you know, beating her
dog and you just get these visions in your head and you're like, what the hell, why,
why did I see that?
So you go out around town, you do your things and you see, um, this red Toyota Corolla station
where I can run into the media and knock down a big Swarovski cactus.
You're like, Oh, that was shocking.
You drive around a couple hours later, you're ready to go home and you see this old lady
crossing the street, hitting her dog.
And you're like, Oh my gosh, I saw this stuff.
I saw this on the way out.
These visions are put in my head and then I'm seeing, right.
So this is when, when you get to a certain level, these inner voices don't only give
you a voice.
They start giving you premonition stuff that's going to happen in the future to mess with
you because of this.
I need to ask something because here's another thing that I think messes with people and
it's about this inner voice and the way this works, because as you said, you don't need
a voice to talk to yourself.
But here's the thing when I dream, okay, uh, Greek and here's something that I realized
many years ago.
And when you said it to me on one of the Sonics years ago, I said, wow, you're like the only
person that I know that realizes this, I'm in the dream world, right?
And I realized that although I am receiving information, even from characters in my dreams,
all right, people I know, people who have passed, whatever else I'm receiving information
as if they were speaking to me in reality, based on my observation, their mouths are
not moving.
They're not actually speaking in the dream, but information is being communicated directly
to me in a very concise way so that I'm getting something as if even better, quite frankly,
than if that person, like I have been visited many times by people who have passed on in
my dreams.
And usually when they communicate information to me, whatever it may be regarding the situation
in the dream or life or whatever, I know they're not speaking, but they are communicating to
me.
One of the things that I mentioned is if you ever recall your dreams and there's dialogue,
look at the mouth and it's never moved.
It never moves.
Right.
People never brought that up before.
I knew that automatically.
So what I'm saying is there's a communication there, though, that is not through the standard.
There's somebody talking.
There's an actual voice.
No, there is communication there.
There are specific beings that do dreams also.
And then Native Americans knew about the dream weavers, catchers, whatever they made for
addressing that aspect, which is different than the conscious world.
Indeed.
But there's another level to it.
And I think Castaneda got into it, where if you can see your hands in your dreams and
move things around as simple as a light switch or picking up a mug of beer or doing something.
Now you're not only in a dream, but you're actually transcending to a different.
You're figuring out that you're actually going to a more energetic plane while you're unconscious.
One of the things I brought up is that all of the intelligence agencies and think tanks
that have been doing work on consciousness since the 50s, if you study what they it's
very clandestine.
It's hard to find the information.
Look around the Internet.
There's plenty of it.
The easiest one to find is the Monroe Institute, whatever.
I'm not a big fan of them, but look at that anyway.
Right.
What I'm trying to say is the conclusion that they had is that a lot of it was inconclusive.
But what they did gather is that when we sleep, our consciousness is being used elsewhere.
Like Isak Pantov is a big proponent of that, right?
So P.D. Ospinsky, George Gorjev, all those guys talked about where everybody's asleep
here and you have to do the work, right?
So there's many ways of saying the same thing.
It's kind of like the ancient Chinese.
They say there are many paths to the top of the mountain, but the view is the same, right?
So find out what what is similar amongst various studies, and then that's what you end up with
seeing simply.
But what I'm trying to say, dreams are a whole other category, a completely different category.
But yes, what I what I suggest about dreams are very quick, a way to to move forward in
dreaming.
If you dream, I don't really dream very rarely.
But when I do, it's not like I would say it's a dream.
It's more like a very strong thought when I'm awake, right?
Or prior to waking, it's always prior to waking up or taking and I would be I would get something
while I'm a very short nap, like a cat nap type thing.
But the more I study, let's say things like scripture and ancient, the less I have no
dreams at all.
There was a time when I didn't have dreams for a decade, right?
So also now, because I'm focusing on certain projects that I'm not dreaming at all, right?
So but what I'd like to bring up to people based on the things that I've studied in absolute
from my experience with it is if there's dialogue, look for mouths moving.
If not, this is something that's being implanted by a dream being if you have the ability to
have tactile movement, meaning you can see yourself walking and you can see your hands
like Castaneda said at moving and doing things with your hands.
It's more than a dream.
It's actually you.
You've gone.
You're somewhere else.
It's ethereal.
Right.
I can tell you, I had one recently that was really powerful like that where I saw my hands
and I was conscious.
I was like, oh, I see my hands.
That means this is not a dream.
Then I look up and there's this long wooden table like medieval, right?
Big room, castle like what I was talking about, I made White Castle, Hamburg, Chateau
Blanc.
Right.
Yeah.
And there's a horse sitting on the on the ends of the table.
And they're actually sitting like human style.
And they they have hooves and they put their hooves through us like a beer stein.
That's about two feet tall.
That's designed to be picked up with a hoof.
And they and they took a sip from it.
And they look at me and said, toast to us, Greek toast to us, Greek.
I said, this is this shit is crazy.
And I'm like, yeah, we know.
And I was out of it.
Wait a minute.
Was this before or after you and I had that discussion about the whole Williams offerings?
I think it was off air about Gulliver's Travels and the horse people was a couple of weeks
ago.
I think we brought it up.
I brought it up to you after I said the dream thing is crazy.
It wasn't even a dream.
And then the other thing I also brought up where I'm in a room and it's I see my hands
and I'm like, oh, there's a mirror and I look in the mirror and I'm like a five foot three
Latin guy, you know, like, you know, like your typical guys that you see that they show
on Fox News that cross the border illegally.
Yeah, of course.
Right.
Yeah.
Like that.
And I was like, that's not what I look like.
I look like Johnny Depp.
People tell me.
It's like, oh, my gosh, what am I playing?
You know, this is some crazy stuff.
You know, it's not like a passive dream.
This is where I'm interacting with it.
So I'm just sharing these things because maybe other people have it, too.
I really don't put a lot of credence into it.
I'm just sharing them.
Right.
Well, back to the voice.
Let's go back to the voice.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I offroaded there for a second.
It's just I recognize that the communication felt similar to what it is you're describing
here where you have communication and it's not because you're hearing a voice, but you
are being communicated to.
Yeah.
But let's just finish this part of the change and go back.
Dreams and the inner voice.
I have no there's no interrelation at all.
It's a completely different category.
OK.
Fair enough.
So we got into dreams.
Yeah.
Inner voice that people have when they're conscious through.
They has nothing to do with dreams.
It really doesn't because it's completely different beings, by the way.
OK.
So what I'm trying to say here is the voice, the beings that give you your inner voice
actually change as you change physically and mentally as you advance, they get more advanced
beings.
Right.
Of course.
Could you imagine someone who is more advanced, spiritually developed, let's say even physically
developed is into higher thinking, higher learning or whatever?
You can't give them like, you know, the guy who watches, you know, Monday Night Football
every night, drives the bus and plays the lotto.
And you know what I mean?
And is relying.
So what you do is when I retire, I'll get Social Security.
That's my whole thing in life.
You can't give him the same voice you give someone like that.
Right.
You'll go nuts.
Well, this is what creates crazy people.
And that's the other odd thing I wanted to ask you here is, are any of these inner voices
which you clearly said are not actually our voice, whether it sounds like us or not, is
irrelevant.
No, no, no.
It is relevant.
Oh, it is relevant.
OK.
Yeah.
It is.
OK.
The standard playbook is it's different.
Probably people that are hearing impaired, but the standard actually people that are hearing
impaired are probably at an advantage.
But what I'm trying to say here is that the way they play the trick on you is that you
pretty much audibly know what you sound like.
Typically, most people recognize their own voice and they play that in your head with
the tonality that you would be anticipating and hearing your own voice.
And that's what fools people.
Well, there was a point in my life.
I don't know about you, but there was a point in my life where I heard myself on tape and
I barely recognized my natural speaking voice because it does sound different inside of
my head.
But hang on just a quick second.
I just.
Yes.
Similar, but off.
It was like, wow, do I actually sound like I hate the sound of my voice?
Well, the sound of your voice is different when because, you know, you know, they have
this thing called bone headphones instead of a speaker on the ear that vibrates the bones
in your jaw, jawbone or something.
OK.
Right.
So when you're speaking, whether you hear it or not, you're feeling it.
You're actually not hearing what is terminating from the vocal cords in the end of your mouth,
in the air and to the room.
What you're really hearing mostly is the vibration of the bone structure, which is
kind of which has to sound different because now it's going to a different place.
OK.
There's a different tonality.
What other people are hearing when they hear you speak.
Right.
Actually, there's a way to do that.
You put your head.
You put a just go up to not a wall, but put something in front of you like a plate about
a foot away.
Right.
And speak into the plate.
And what you hear is what other people here typically that's more like what you sound
like.
Right.
OK.
You know, hold an object, your hands in front about a foot away from your face and speak
into it rather loud, not too loud, but enough to project.
And you'll notice it sounds that's what that's what you really sound like.
Right.
The audible part.
And what people also hear is the way you project and the reflections in the room and all that.
Right.
All of those things come into play.
So that's not the point.
They don't have to really duplicate your voice.
Exactly.
Fifty percent. Seventy five percent is all they have to do.
And here's the thing, who's going to question that?
It's not them in their mind anyway.
No one's going to question it. So they could be only 10 percent what you sound like.
It's close enough, you see, because you're not aware.
OK, fair enough. So here's the other thing, though, that I just wanted to ask quickly
and have you throw it in.
Are any of these inner voices, which are not ours, even though we think they're ours
quite often, are any of them actually benevolent or are they all?
They I'd say they're neutral.
They all. Oh, OK.
I was wondering if they provide both sides.
So, you know, the cartoon where you have a guy wants to do something questionable in
the cartoon and he's got an angel on his right hand, on the right shoulder and a devil
on the left shoulder. The angel says, don't do it.
It's immoral. And the devil says, go ahead and do it.
Nobody knows. Right. Right.
Right. They provide they provide the moral argument, the moral stance and the immoral
stance. Also, they do both.
They have there is no right and wrong.
I've been saying this for a while. There is no right and wrong.
That's why it's important to find out what law form you will abide by.
So you have a reference system.
Right. OK. And most people do the state because they're because the state law form,
which is bizarre, but they do that because it's a fear of penalty.
Right. They're motivated by penalty.
They don't do the laws of the state or whatever state you're in because it's the right
thing. They do it because if they don't do it, they'll be punished.
Right. It's the motivation by penalty.
The law, what I'm talking about, law form is something that motivates you because it's
the right thing to do. Right.
Regardless of penalty or fear.
OK, so the voice thing is is one thing.
And I showed the various ways I kind of jumbled it up going off on tangents, but it
changed the beings that give you the voice.
Yeah. I keep saying the voice.
I'm sounding like Frank Herbert and doing because the Bene Gesserit have something
called the voice that you can manipulate other people with.
Right. Make them do things. Right.
Right. So the Frank Herbert doing files would know.
OK, so doing an examination of this, are they benevolent or malevolent?
They're neither and they're both.
So that's again, it depends on you.
They're not here so much.
They can be teachers.
They can help you and they can also be malevolent and they can harm you.
Right. But that depends on you again.
In other words, the element of choice is open.
The decisions are up to you.
There's many choices.
Well, you could get used as a weapon against others, too, couldn't you be?
I mean, you could sort of be weaponized.
Let's encourage this one to go ahead and cause problems.
Let's do an advanced tidbit here.
When we talk about the emo work, yes, that's silent.
And what have I spoken about?
Your true voice, your true method of communication is silent.
When you do the emo work to influence someone,
that is far more powerful than having them hear voices in their head.
Because when you do the emo work on someone good or bad,
what people think, right,
as good or good or bad, that goes right to the core spirit part.
And that's far more powerful than putting a voice in their head.
So let me give you an example.
Right now, most people that are subs and listening,
I consider to be fairly intelligent.
And you and I might be fairly intelligent right now.
If some gray van drove by with a little satellite dish on it
and beamed some kind of energy weapon and you heard a voice in your head right now,
you'd be more startled and humored or scared than saying that's really my voice.
You'd recognize it, right?
Someone beamed a voice into your head, you know, voice to skull technology, right?
Right. All of a sudden you have a disembodied voice.
It's like, wait a minute. Is that a ghost? Is that a technology?
What is that? You're not going to eat that.
You're not going to say, oh, I just have to do this because I just heard it in my head.
You're not going to follow that.
You're not going to answer it directly.
No, you're not going to answer.
You're going to say, I just had this anomalous thing.
I heard myself, you know, tell myself to go, you know, get a
kitchen fork and stab the dog. I'm not going to do that.
My first question is, where the hell did that come from?
I'd be trying to track down where it came from.
It'd be more of a distraction.
But for some people, it's not right for some people that are not aware of this.
So anything audible in your head or in that degree.
Again, the silent you're feeling.
So, OK, see the silent voice that is you is communicated through feelings.
But when I say feeling, it's feeling like a machinist has what's called a feeler gauge.
Right. OK, look up what a feeler gauge is in machining to get ultra
very, very precise spacing.
It's more like that.
It's a non audible, non literal, non.
Well, anything that uses words or language.
It's a non language, but it has a language of its own.
Just like when I speak on the emo work, you know, when you feel
when you give someone a hug, there's a certain feeling you have that has.
That's a word.
Imagine that feeling is a category in itself.
When you're angry, you have a certain feeling when you're hungry, right?
Hungry or desire.
You have a certain feeling when you're jealous.
That's always feelings and emotions have their own language as well.
But they're not in words.
How many times you even heard?
I can't put it in words, but I feel it.
Right. Of course.
Yeah, that's the basis of it.
Right. Again, the poor old sap out in the field gets picked up by a UFO,
taken to an advanced, sterile planet.
One of the things that one of the features is that they're telepathic.
Right. Usually in Hollywood.
Right. They're trying to show you all these different ways that things can exist.
So essentially, it's the evil is really the highest level because that's the silent level.
But it's yet very dynamic.
You see?
Now, I'm not saying that that voice will ever go away,
but I'm saying I gave you the gradations that I've discovered as it moves on and on.
Now, I think I got to the advanced part.
If you're a more advanced person, you know, culturally,
spiritually, intellectually, academically, whatever,
they switch up to a more advanced voice to keep up with you.
But when you keep advancing, it's more rarefied.
And they have some rare beings on their side to give you a voice.
But to stay ahead of you, because they know you're a type of person that's always advancing.
Right.
They start anticipating giving you the future.
So you have some people that this happens to.
And guess what?
They call themselves psychics.
I'm psychic.
No, you're not.
You don't have any more psychic ability than anybody else does.
But yes, the reason why, because you have been anticipated to be given this.
Right.
Trait.
It's another being.
I know this is kind of harsh to say it this way.
Yeah.
So we all have the same abilities to a certain degree.
You know, there are some people that could jump higher, run faster, think faster,
count numbers faster.
Yeah, there's natural degrees and variations in talent.
But generally, everybody, you know, can do almost the same thing.
So when you see someone who's like a real psychic, not the fake ones, let's say, or
the ones that say they're not.
There's a video that I like in French, where a guy sitting on a train and he greets someone.
He says, I was looking for you.
They say, you're a psychic.
Are you a psychic?
He says, yes.
And then he slaps him across the face.
And he says, oh, you're a charlatan, a fake, because if you were really psychic, you knew
I was going to slap you across the face.
Right.
So.
So, OK, so, yeah, there's that aspect as well.
It's kind of harsh.
So when you get to a certain level, they will start giving you anomalous paranormal stuff
to chew on because they're anticipating that you're going to keep growing and they're like
running out.
They don't want to spend so much energy on you.
So they mess with you.
Right.
They're giving you like they show you things of what you're going to see and hear today.
And you're like, you just take that in stride.
Right.
So that's where they can help.
That could be helpful.
It could be hindrance.
A lot of the people that are locked up because they can't manage this, believe it or not,
there's a guy, Jerry, whatever.
Oh, my gosh.
I should know.
He's actually a Tucsonan.
Well, let's get to bed.
Something like that.
He used to work in the psychological field, psychiatry, treating criminals, criminals
in psych wards.
And he said, yeah, there's a voice in my head and it tells me what to do.
So it would get to the point where it tells me when to break into a house, which room
and which drawer and the combination in the safe and open it and I'd get all the stuff
and leave.
And if the police would show up, the voice would tell me, hide right here from count
to five and then run to the next spot, count to 10 and then run.
And he would get away.
So it was like this other entity that was able to see, you know, a nonphysical entity
into other people's homes.
Right, right.
And even like once I was with the wife and we had some valuables in the in the car, let's
say.
And I said, it doesn't matter where you hide it in the car, because if you have one of
these thieves, like the Jerry Walensky guy talks about, that is guided by one of these
other guys that are nonphysical.
No matter where you hide it in the car, the other entity knows where it is.
He's going to tell him when to break the window, how to reach in and where it is hidden
exactly.
Right, right.
So and the reason these guys got caught is because the voices made them crazy.
So it's like, you know, there'll be three in the morning.
They jump in a cold shower and run out in the street naked.
And the neighbors are like, what the hell are you doing?
Call the cops.
That's how it gets caught.
Not because not because he got caught.
You see what I mean?
Right, right.
Well, look, a specific question then.
Look, you had an instance here where you knew something ahead of me telling you about it.
Were you told that by another entity, another voice?
Of course.
I'm not psychic.
OK, I just figured I'd ask because.
With me for a long time, since I was 12, giving me stuff that's going to happen.
So but hey, you know, this is planet Earth.
You know, this is like the whole thing.
You know, when I start Greek speak out in the public, let's say at the shops, at a grocery
store, I start talking about it.
But after five minutes or so, I get a crowd of people.
Someone in there says, hey, you should write a book.
I'm like, oh, my gosh.
You know, and I'm like, listen, all the stuff I'm talking about, you know, if you've been
on this planet for more than 15 minutes, you should know this.
They're like, oh, well, I asked him, have you been on this planet for more than an hour?
And they're like, yeah.
And I'm like, and you don't know this.
And they're like, huh?
You see, it's the same thing.
It's the same thing.
It's no big deal.
You know, just because you hear things you haven't heard before doesn't mean you're special
or whatever.
You're just mixed in here.
So here's the thing.
Have you been on this planet more than an hour?
So you should have figured it out.
And what?
OK, what do you mean, figure out the whole planet in an hour?
Yeah.
OK, so when you walk, you got to go to the bathroom and you're a guy, you walk into the
girl's bathroom.
How long does it take you to figure out you're in a girl's bathroom?
Or OK, here you park the car, you go out, you go into a dive bar.
How long does it take you to figure out you just walked into a dive bar, right?
Like, what, 30 seconds, a minute?
This is a dive bar.
Not long.
You can figure it out.
Yeah, you're pretty quick.
Yeah.
So what I'm saying is you walk into things that you were told or thought you should go
into and they end up being not what you thought they were.
That's what I mean about figuring it out.
Right.
You notice it's like the same with the bathroom.
You know that.
Oh, wait a second.
I think this is the girl's bathroom.
You know, what's what's your first clue?
Because everything in here you have to do sitting down, right?
No urinals.
Yeah, that's what years ago you say.
It's a man's world.
It's a bullshit.
All these houses that are being built.
Forget about the regular homes, ticky tacky houses and all that go up to where the rich
people live.
I want you to get a tour of 10 houses and tell me what you don't see.
I don't know what you mean, Greek.
You got all these expensive houses.
You don't see a urinal.
So how is it a man's world if they're not putting urinals and bathrooms in people's
houses?
How is it a man's world?
How have you ever seen a urinal in a man in a house before?
I've never seen it.
Only the ones that I put in.
I have only ever seen that in places that are meant for public people to keep coming in
and out of where there's masses.
But it's a man's world, but they're not accommodating the man's world.
Not at home.
You see, this is a big deal to me, right?
Because look, I'll get a little personal.
Sure.
I was bike racing for a long time and you sit on the thing sometimes and it goes numb.
And after a while, I started realizing I can't pee straight.
I can't be straight.
I can't.
You know what I mean?
It pees like that.
You know, when you go to the irrigation department in the hardware store, get different
sprinklers that have different fan patterns.
Anyway, I'm not going to get into it.
But you see what I mean, right?
If I need a urinal.
If you pinch off a hose long enough, it stops letting the flow go.
Yeah, I get you.
Okay.
Or when it comes out, the flow is like one of those 15 degree sprinkler heads, right?
Yeah.
So yeah.
So anyway, the reason I'm saying this is because for some, for me, it's exaggerated.
But I've been exaggerating this point for 30 years now.
How is it a man's world?
They don't say that anymore.
But when they said it more, you know, like in the 80s, they used to say that more, right?
I mean, how is it a man's world?
I've never been in even a mansion or a wealthy person's home that has a urinal.
They're making everybody sit down or stand up and make sure that, you know, there's an
imaginary target in the toilet.
You got to, you know, you can't drift, right?
You can't read the newspaper or something, right?
You know, while you're, you know, anyway.
This is the point.
These things are obvious, what I'm saying.
But it's not a matter of knowing about everything.
It's like, what do you know quickly, right?
Like, this is a bar.
Let's go to the bar.
When you walk in, you think it's, you know, a bar, you know, should be a bar, you know,
place you go to enjoy yourself.
But it's a dive bar.
It stinks.
And it's right.
So you're like, wait a second.
Hold on.
The same thing.
When you are given all these premises and things in life, not only do you have the inner
voice, which you think is you, which is not you.
You have all of these things around you, which not are not what they should be or you're told
they are and no one cares.