SonicEvent142, rated Y, and Greek, how are you?
Oh, you got the number right.
Yeah, I did.
I got it right last time, too.
We were wondering about that, but yeah, I got it correct.
So there it is.
Well, even how I am is interesting.
I don't take interest, I mean, well, how can I say it, not take interest in my own baby,
which is lawful timekeeping.
By the way, it's really, I'm really sad to pronounce I'm the only one that does it, right,
other than those have, you know, got it from me, let's say, lawful timekeeping.
Right, they have mentioned it in the Chatango, they were seeming to.
Well, it's an intercalary year, and last night, it's the first day of the seventh month, yesterday
the moon was at least 20 or 30 degrees more southeast.
It was east, south, south, you know, the bearings on the compass.
Right now it's almost due east.
Now, how the hell does it move 30 degrees across the horizon?
It only does that on the seventh month, sometimes on the first month.
So even though it's an intercalary year, and you're not sure, should we really reckon a
13th month?
They're like, yeah, yeah, because the moon just showed you, I don't know if you know
how, people that don't really watch the sky, but these things take a certain position,
and they don't move 30 degrees north in one day, right, in terms of the track of the ecliptic,
and the moon just did that.
And I predicted yesterday, I said, I put it on the chat, just watch how it's going to
go from southeast to due east overnight, and it did that.
That's pretty big.
Oh no, we're not talking about, you know, during the different phases, we're talking about
overnight, same phase, it shouldn't, it doesn't, it doesn't make any sense, you know, you couldn't,
you know.
So from one to the next, it typically doesn't move that much.
Yeah.
I mean, that's across the equatorial, not the ecliptic, which is, it shouldn't, in other
words, it's not math, it doesn't work, there's no math to show that kind of a change, but
it happens every seventh month.
It's kind of exciting, the most exciting month is the first day of the seventh month, which
to show how far off it is now from September 11th, 2001, September 11th, 2001 was the 10th
day of the seventh month day of atonement.
By the way, the, I was on archaics recently, and I tried to talk about lawful timekeeping.
I thought Jason was falling asleep, but some people got it.
And, um, yeah, I didn't think he was falling asleep.
I thought he was getting overwhelmed is what it was.
That's not my problem.
Yeah, true.
But yeah, just don't fall asleep.
The rest is fine.
But here's the thing, the lawful timekeeping, whenever, like 9-11 was on day of atonement.
The COVID announcement was on the Passover.
If you look at other major events like stock market crashes and the Murrow building, all
that in April, they're all on biblical holidays.
So when you read on the biblical day, like on the 10th day of the seventh month, you know,
most people don't know what that means at all, right?
Well, they do.
I mean, a nine-year-old, if you say on the 10th day of the fifth month, they know what
that means, but they can't find it, right?
You know what I mean?
That would be July 10th, seventh month?
No, right?
So that's why I did the lawful timekeeping.
And then later on, I found out lawful timekeeping is that if you look up astronomy 101, they
teach that the full moon is the new moon and denotes the month.
And the day starts at solar noon.
I mean, you could look that up right now.
Any astronomy college course 101, 102, they'll teach that.
But for five minutes, they'll just mention it.
They won't teach it.
So that's exciting.
I've got a bunch of stuff going on.
You got some questions.
I just want to mention, soon I'm going to be talking about the acoustical counter space.
And I think I mentioned to you, I sent some modules to a speaker company that has a YouTube
channel.
They're pretty high end, unusual products.
And they did a YouTube video on it.
And in the YouTube video, they said, we got these incredible things.
He called them quantum, which they're not.
And he says, well, we're not installing them properly as per instruction.
They didn't install them right.
And this is a YouTube video on this.
But they still said, but I did notice it did still do what he said.
And here are the graphs to prove it.
And he actually said he did not install them according to instructions more than once,
when he could have quite easily.
And they did a YouTube video.
Now, that video since has been taken down, not because of my comments.
The comments were fairly favorable.
And it's only a private video.
I did show it to some people.
And the responses that I got from my side was, why did he not install it right?
He actually says he's not installing it right.
Just my luck, as they say.
Could you imagine, Chuck, you come up with something and you send it to, I don't know,
a toothbrush company and a new toothbrush.
And the toothbrush company does a video on your new style of toothbrush.
And they said, we're not going to use it to brush teeth.
We're going to brush.
I don't know.
You pick what, right?
But it still works really well.
We're going to clean shoes with it.
But it works great.
Yeah.
Why would you do that?
That is so.
If you told me that's what was going to happen, I'd say there is no way in a moronic universe
that we even in a moronic universe, anyone would do that.
Right.
So anyway, this is the kind of stuff I've been living with and doing now for over two decades,
three decades coming up, you know.
Whether it's water stuff, energy stuff, whatever, you know, it's like, yeah, we want to test
it out.
I remember going out to Houston, Texas and the Halliburton labs.
Yeah, we ran tests on it and it was great.
And I saw what tests they ran.
I'm like, that's not what I said should be.
What are you guys doing?
Oh, my gosh.
Do I have a right to bitch?
Not really.
I think I have more of a right to observe and report.
Oh, certainly.
I mean, and besides that, it's not as though this should be a shock or surprise to you
anyway, right?
No.
Now, what is interesting, though, is we do have people that are listening to some of
the sonics and giving them some thought and then spitting back questions or, you know,
really interrogatory statements in some cases about stuff that they heard.
Do you want to start with the most recent or you want to go back a ways?
No, it's up to you.
But most recent, as long as we don't lose the ones that are more back.
So you shoot up to you.
I like I like going cold.
OK, no problem.
Let's go with this because of the weather.
Cold, but not dry.
Not dry before penetration.
Always cold, but not dry.
Gotcha.
At least at least a little little spit.
There you go.
Anyway, to the Greek greetings.
Have you experimented with this dissipating clouds and then in parentheses naturally
formed in the sky purely through a focused stare with a small amount of question?
Well, this is a weather question, but they're asking, you know, basically without equipment
in a long sort of way.
Yeah, it's called the IRA.
There's a guy, Peter, or something that during the time of Freud and all that there was, you
know, we hear about Freud during that time in the early part of the 20th century.
But you don't know that Freud was part of a an entire movement.
Like a woke movement in the psychology, there was no psychology industry.
Then anyway, I was sort of, you know, what they called people, you know, the loot.
It was lunatic, lunatic, lunacism.
It was called before that.
And there was the master lunacist in the court.
You know how you go to court and they they have a psychos psych eval.
They call it right.
Well, before the Freud, you know, that's a new system of psychology.
The court brought in what was called a master of lunacy.
Look it up.
And they would judge whether the person should be, you know, his fit.
Right.
Just like today was called master of lunacy.
But anyway, during the time of that, there was a lot of interesting research on the power of
the mind and its extensions, meaning sight, hearing, touch, feeling, telepathy, PK, you
know, psychokinesis and all that stuff.
You know, we don't we get little drips and drabs.
I'm talking about mainstream textbooks.
We're talking about this stuff anymore.
They don't use the word lunatic anymore, either, which was.
Yeah.
If you go to a master of lunacy is in law, the courts had a master of lunacy anyway.
By the way, most 99 percent of my education is not from the Internet.
Of course, you know.
So yeah.
Anyway, so it's old books.
And Jason, OK, it's the same thing.
It's kind of kindred in that way.
Now, during that time, they found this called the visual ray.
And there's some stuff on it online.
I think I haven't seen it in a long time.
Maybe, maybe not what you can do.
And we all feel in certain language.
It's called putting light on you.
You know, when you're in a crowd, suddenly you want to turn around.
It's almost as if someone tapped you on the shoulder, but they didn't.
Someone staring at you from the back.
You could feel it.
Right.
They were able to put make these literal black boxes.
There were black velvet boxes in another room.
And people were able to trigger solenoids by just giving them where to look on the wall.
Right.
OK, they could trigger things.
So that research right away was put down.
So in other words, I'm shown that on a local level with certain amount of research,
you can trigger a magnetic solenoid with your eye.
Right.
By looking at it through a wall, through a box.
Why not make a hole in a cloud?
I gave the long winded version of that because it's not about going around and saying,
well, I made a hole in the cloud with my eye.
Fuck that.
Oh, excuse the medical term.
All you got to say is you got a lot of power coming out of your eye, period.
Mm hmm.
They also ask, does the device discussed in the sonic work on a similar principle?
They're asking.
I don't think so.
But I'll tell you how the device works.
Very simple.
We don't know what the ether is because it's one of these first principle substrates.
You're not allowed.
It's like if you're a cartoon character on the TV, you're not allowed to question the pixels.
That's outside of your right.
It's outside of your reality.
But actually, that's what makes you look real is the pixel on the if you're a video character.
Right.
You know, I don't know how we like fish.
Fish are always arguing, you know, like we put this fish in jail in the psych ward.
Why?
Because he says we're all underwater.
He's crazy.
But I'll tell you.
Yeah.
Right.
Because they're used to it.
So but, you know, could it be that when a fish dies, the last thing he entertains is that
he's underwater.
Right.
So yeah.
And by the way, you know, when a lake is poisoned and the fish die and some don't,
the ones that die first are the ones that drank the water first.
That doesn't sound like it makes sense, but they do actually intake water through their
gills, through osmosis.
OK.
And then it goes to a separate area where it works just like the human body, where there's
no penetration at all.
You know, induction.
So it's the thirsty fish that die first when the water is poisoned.
That does make some sense.
Right.
Gotcha.
Yeah.
So this.
OK.
The ether is what we're in is our water.
We cannot question it, just like fish cannot question water.
So how do you work with it?
Well, we through the works of Wilhelm Reich, which you have to give him the Paramount credit
on this because he simplified it, is that we know that the potential goes from low to
high versus the potentials were taught where everything goes high to low.
We've discussed this before.
Yes.
So we know that and we know that a low potential feeds the high.
So we need to create a low potential somehow.
So what we do is we make a device which is exactly an unbalanced capacitor and it's a
conical device or tubular device.
It has a double mirror on the ends, layers of metal and nonmetal.
So we know that when the ether sees that device, it's going to slow it down a little
bit and theory.
And when it slows down a little bit, it acts like a low potential.
Ah, whammo.
So within the geometric matrix of that device, because it slowed it down a little bit, it
actually represents a slightly lower potential.
Guess what that's going to do to the high potential?
It's going to feed it because it goes from low to high.
Right.
By the way, this is how the phaser weapons work on Star Trek.
Yeah.
There's a book.
I don't know if you could find him on how the Star Trek devices work.
It was written right around that time.
I remember perusing through it.
There's a handful of technical manuals now.
They've actually expanded that.
But yeah, yeah, yeah.
If you could find how it works, not just a blueprint.
Oh, yeah.
So yeah, yeah, right.
So we know that.
The water gun, it's not a water gun.
It's a water-powered gun, just like you have an electric motor.
It's not, right?
So it's plugged into a water source, literally.
Just like you would plug an electric motor with a short cord or a long cord, you could
plug in the big water gun with a long cord or a short cord.
In other words, your water source could be 100 feet away, and you could have a 100-foot,
let's say, tube going to the gun that you're going to be working the atmosphere, right?
There's no water in the gun, right?
I just call it water gun for short.
You could call it, Wilhelm Wright called them cloud busters.
We've evolved them, made them very efficient since then.
That works on both of these principles, because the water with the gun directs out.
Now, for example, the first device I mentioned goes from low to high potential.
This one can create a high potential, which will drain the atmosphere.
That's what makes a hole in the cloud.
So if you can make a hole in a cloud with your eyeball, that means your eyeball has
a higher potential than the ether, right?
So when you subject the ether to a high potential device, it will drain it.
It will go to your gun, which could eventually make the gun dangerous, because if you touch
it with bare hands, it could shut down your nervous system, right?
It's just like touching a...
If it's worked enough and charged enough, it would be touching no different than touching
a power line, but the results would be different, right?
There are many people whose hearts have stopped that did weather work, especially in the desert
at night with a water source in the desert's extreme environment, and they touched the
water gun and got a heart attack, what's considered a heart attack.
The heart attack feeling is numbness in the legs or arms, can't breathe, or you can't
control your breathing.
It feels like an elephant sitting on your chest.
You get dizzy, lightheaded, and you start going into a panic, because you're wondering
what the hell's happening to you, right?
Those are the male symptoms.
Actually, female symptoms differ a bit, but go ahead.
Yeah.
Yeah, they do.
They actually go more into the fainting a little bit quicker, don't they?
Well, they also have other visual cues and a few other things that occur that don't
occur typically in the male, but yeah.
Right, like gray, they can't see through one of the eyes or something.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
Yeah, there's big differences, of course.
But yeah, because male and female is not just two genders.
It's actually a separate species altogether, by the way.
Right.
That's why, yeah.
You know, men are for Mars and women are for Venus.
Remember that?
Oh, yeah.
I remember that whole trend.
Yeah, okay.
So well, anyway, there's a little bit, by the way, I'm outside.
There's a little bit of an eclipse happening.
Oh, I wasn't aware of that.
On the top between, I'm southwest USA looking east.
Moon is about 20 degrees above horizon.
The sun had barely some light left.
The between 9 o'clock and 11 o'clock, it looks like you put a ruler or something flattened
it out on the top.
So it's a partial eclipse.
Interesting.
So look, speaking about potential and low and high, somebody asked on here, is there a place
that I can get more material on the yin and yang, you know, blood, heart, etc.
Uh, that name is Creek, by the way, that that asked that question.
Right.
I think I got some similar questions of that.
Now, here's the thing that's so sad.
You go online, look up yin and yang, you can get this rudimentary stuff that if you think
it's that it's better than if you never looked at all, because I have spoken to people many
times.
Well, not at all.
But it's not just that, right?
It's like saying a Ferrari is a cart.
Yeah.
Okay.
So what I've said to people and when I say, oh, yeah, I know Taoism, you know, I said,
oh, yeah.
So you know that the young projects the yin.
And they're like, huh?
You have a cat that does that, by the way.
But I call them.
They go, huh?
I'm like, oh, I'm going to use that.
So, yeah.
So it's like, oh, my gosh, you know, so they just think like when you say young, right?
You know, the definition is hard, pointy, bright, right?
Yin, soft, dull, spread out, right?
Okay.
That's fine.
Crayons away.
You know, that's fine.
But there's many levels to it.
So until you understand that the young protects the yin, you don't have a working relationship
with those concepts.
So is there a place to go?
No.
The place is called your mind.
And if you don't have it in your mind, you're going to have to get it out of somebody else's
mind.
And that's why we've been trying to do the sonics here.
I think I might.
I was thinking, you know how we did the scalarator seminar, and I'm going to probably do one on
acoustic counter space, right?
So you're doing one on yin and yang, but that would actually be a disservice because
it's one of those things like martial arts where you have to practice for your whole
life, right?
And but you practice in your mind and with predictions, the beautiful thing about understanding
yin and yang, you could pretty much predict anything.
So if someone shows you, let's say you're in a lab and you see one chemical and another
chemical, if you study them and see where they are in the yin and yang scope, you can
actually predict what's going to happen.
You put them together, even though you don't even know what they are.
I've never seen them before, right?
It's about predictability, right?
Like, for example, you know, they say, oh, that kid's eating too much candy, his teeth
are going to rot.
It's kind of like that, right?
Right.
But it doesn't always happen, right?
No, it doesn't always happen, but it's a fairly predictable thing, given that, yeah,
given the circumstances of culture.
But this transcends that.
So we've gotten to some yin and yang on the earlier sonics when we were addressing, quote
unquote, health problems.
And I don't like to call them health problems.
As you know, they're fitness issues.
There's no such thing as health, right?
It's what fitness level you need for whatever you want to keep your teeth.
Right.
That's a fitness level.
Like, I want to eat healthy so I don't get sick.
Well, that's a level of fitness.
In other words, what one person considers sick is another person's healthy, right?
The reason why I'm saying that when I travel cross country and I stayed with Americans
and I ate their food, I felt sick.
I just ate what they normally feel.
So then I questioned, do they feel maybe I'm getting sick because I'm not used to it?
Or is this how they always feel?
And it turned out that's how they always feel.
It's normal for them to feel that way.
You know that, you know, when you eat food with no nutrition or overcooked or whatever,
you feel like low, heavy, no energy.
You don't feel good.
That and you're still hungry, too.
That's the other thing.
And you can be.
You can be more often.
You feel like you need to eat more often.
Right.
So it's kind of like when you start using alcohol, you run out of gas.
I remember a place where the small town of Grants, New Mexico, the gas tanks were all
polluted.
So they just got alcohol.
So I bring alcohol in the car.
You can run a gasoline engine on alcohol, but it has no power.
You could floor it.
You're barely going 30 miles an hour with the alcohol.
Right.
It does it, but it doesn't do it.
Well, yeah, it has to be adjusted.
So this is how.
Anyway, I would say there's if we did, you know, Mr.
Rogers, every time he opened, he changed his shirt.
Beautiful day in the neighborhood.
This neighborhood, the Mandela effect, whatever changes issues every day.
You do food.
I wanted to do maybe every time we do a sonic, not every day, every day.
I do it anyway.
But when we do a sonic, bring up a health thing, a diet, a food thing or something, a
yin and yang thing.
Right.
That's the only way to do it.
A little bit of time.
How do you learn a language?
You got to learn a language.
You sit and do Rosetta Stone.
Think you're going to get it in a week?
Or what if you are immersed in a Spanish speaking neighborhood like it or not?
You're going to learn Spanish, right?
Oh, yeah.
One way or another, you're going to have to communicate.
That's right.
So when you put yourself in a situation where you want to communicate with your environment,
you have to learn yin and yang because it is a superior way.
I'm just saying that in a modified way.
I remember since we started discussing this, I don't want to call it yin and yang because
it sounds like I'm modifying some Asian philosophy.
Right.
It has nothing to do with it just because it was preserved by them.
And you don't have a better descriptor for it.
That'll that'll just, you know, that'll wrap it around and give give people a reference.
I got you.
Not yet.
We have a lot of descriptors for other things, but not we haven't come up with anything for
that yet.
What I suggest, though, is just constantly looking and thinking about it until you make
it normal.
You know, it's kind of like, again, the cliche of tying your shoelaces.
I remember it was so difficult to tie my shoelaces the first maybe 10 times.
Right.
I was like, did I do it right?
You know, but after like 10 times or a month of learning how to tie my shoelaces, I don't
even think about it anymore.
Right.
So that's how I'm functioning with the yin and yang.
Like I'll run it.
Just recently, someone was doing something.
They said, if you do this, that's going to this is this.
And this is going to happen.
They're like, really?
They're like, oh, yeah, because that's yin and this is yang.
And this one is going to do this yin reaction.
Oh, my gosh.
It's yin and yang.
Well, I don't know how else to communicate it.
I don't know how else.
Right.
So there's got to be a better way.
I think if we come up with another way, other than it's calling yin and yang, it'll be more
universal and easier to accept.
But in the meantime, go study on the Internet.
There is no place for any of these things.
I want to get into places also tonight.
But what else have you got?
I'm not sidestepping the yin and yang.
No problem.
I'm just saying this is it's one of these things like, how do I learn French?
Oh, my gosh.
I mean, so many people could tell you so many different ways.
But the only way to learn any language is by immersion.
True, true.
Immersion and make things that are commonly useful right away.
Easily useful.
Like, you know, you're in that Spanish neighborhood.
You're going to want to learn how to ask for food.
Ask where something is.
So asking where directions are or something is going to be something you're going to need
to not only be able to ask, but understand when it's told back to you.
Right.
So she's really cute.
Her phone number.
Yeah, that helps, too.
All right.
So a couple of things that are more modern question wise, and then we'll go back in time
on the on the timeline, if you will.
Let's see.
Have you come across the Matrix?
I guess five Roman numeral five or V quest of the spirit volume of works by Val Valoran
Valerian.
No, no, no.
OK, fair enough.
And I don't read much stuff that's after like 1920, 1929.
Right.
It's suspect.
I just it's fine.
OK, anything past and if it's less than 100 years old, I would rather get the cliff notes
from someone who read it.
Tell me about it.
You know, I'm not familiar with that book.
Otherwise, I would try and give you a cliff notes on it and see what you thought.
But I don't have it.
So anyway, if that person wants to give us a cliff notes, go right ahead and maybe we
can work from there.
The Greeks thoughts on a tech billionaire taking a spacewalk this week.
So that was in the news.
You know, the whole no, no comment.
No comment.
Fair enough.
OK, so now we go to the biblical.
Do you think we will see the return of the Christ in our lifetime?
No, no.
OK, fair enough.
Because for many two points, whether you have the timeline or not.
Correct.
Is it the Christ that comes back or is it his crew that comes back in his name, in his
full power?
But what we see there is crew in our life.
Exactly.
OK, fair enough.
Last thing along those lines is, does the queen of heaven sit on the left side of why
h w h?
I don't have any information on that.
I really don't.
I have never come across anything, but it is.
But that's good that they asked left or right, because that kingdom is a lateral kingdom.
You know, we keep saying for the people that are outside of the knowledge, it's always
higher and lower.
But once you gain the knowledge, you understand how things really work and you're invited
in.
Everything is lateral.
You're either on the front, the back, the left or the right.
Right.
The left hand path, the right hand path, so to speak.
Yeah.
But for the profane, it's always high or low, high or low.
Right.
Fair enough.
So that was the grouping of coherent questions I got so far.
And if you guys drop them over on the Patreon, I will collect them and bring them to each
sonic, as I told you, especially for new people who don't know that.
Also, we bring up things that are going on in the chat over on the Chatango, which over
there has just been about the lawful timekeeping, which is where we started.
Yeah, it's a big deal because it's an intercalary year.
And it's the seventh month, which is the most exciting.
You know, there's like nobody, nobody.
This this is like these are like major events, stellar events happening every year.
And nobody's paying attention.
Right.
And they're major.
You know, it's just what they're told is major is major versus what really can be witnessed.
I'm looking at the moon right now, and it's dead east.
And last night it was more than 30 degrees towards the south.
We're talking about lateral movement, not across the ecliptic, you know, where things can move,
take different paths, which I mean, you know, diagonally across the sky normally.
Right.
We're talking because where we are, this is pretty amazing.
And yesterday I was looking at it with someone.
I said, you see where it is all the way down there?
It's going to be all the way up here overnight.
Amazing.
So yeah, lawful timekeeping.
That's cool.
Yeah.
So last thing, last thing I want to push on that, though, is that we do have some people
that are brand new and are just getting familiarized with Greek speak.
As a matter of fact, I referred them back to some of the original OG stuff where, you know,
we went for two hours and focused on a couple of things on a cat per category versus loose
conversation.
Right.
And, you know, so they're just getting accustomed to this.
What what let's just say I'm brand new and I say, well, what what is the difference?
Why is lawful timekeeping useful, even considering I have this thing called a clock?
And that's well, that's well, it's because it's based knowledge.
It's based knowledge.
And I think I always said you don't have to buy anything.
You're not dependent.
It's like a slave has to do.
OK, when you're a slave, illegals law permits slavery and the legal people tell, you know,
there's no slavery because they can't see it like the fish in the water.
Right.
They do you know that the slave automatically takes on the religion of the master automatically?
I have read that.
Yeah.
It's automatic.
So that's why when you look at the the quote unquote black slavery in America, they all
took on whatever religion.
Right.
Even though they had long traditions prior to that.
Exactly.
That's why the only thing that they were allowed to do was listen to someone read from the Bible.
Right.
Mm hmm.
Because it was the Bible of the master.
Therefore.
Right.
So the lawful.
Yes.
If you ask us, let's just use the term.
Let's be more candid slave.
What day it is, not only what they normally tell you, January through December, Monday
through Friday, whatever, you know, Sunday through Monday or whatever, or the time by
the clock.
That is a system that if everything just went away and they were put in a place, you know,
they couldn't tell time without that subscribing to that commercial calendar or commercial
clock.
Right.
For navigation.
Mm hmm.
So they don't know.
I mean, in other words, they're depending on their what their master gives them.
Right.
Yeah.
So that's what that's all it is.
So the lawful timekeeping, you're going by another master.
You know, the ones have who have wound up the clocks of the sky, the ones who put everything
in place in this physical and nonphysical reality is more who you're subscribing to.
Right.
I mean, if you I've been practicing now for about a month because I'm doing most of my
a lot of projects outdoors and every day I get up and I look no matter what time of day
it is, I can tell you what time of day it is and what day of the month it is just by
looking at the sky.
Right.
A very simple way you'll notice between dawn and noon for the first 10 days of the month,
you can see the moon in the sky during the day during the day.
Right.
Yeah.
And then it changes and there's times where you can't see it during the day.
You know, it has to be those days.
Right.
I could go on and on and on, but there's no reason for that because there's no reason
to elaborate on these fine details.
It's kind of like, you know, how do you make a peanut butter jelly and sandwich or where
do you put the knife and the fork and what you know what I mean?
All this stuff is gets too much into detail.
But you'll notice that if you go outside and observe every day and just mark what you see
and go back and look at your notes after a month, you'll know what month it was, what
day it was just by looking at the sky.
Now, that's priceless.
Now, if you ask a slave that they're going to be looking down and scrambling for a device,
right?
For a device or a calendar or yeah.
Yeah.
Printed or whatever.
So even the free calendars are, you know, the reason they were given away free.
Someone said, well, the calendars were free.
I'm like, well, there were there were promotions.
There were promotions.
Remember?
They were always part of some sort of business.
You had to open a bank account to get a free calendar.
You had to sign up for something.
Yeah, it was a promotion.
But typically calendars are for sale.
Clocks are for sale.
Right, right.
All these things.
So yeah, what it does is it lets you operate.
Also, like I mentioned earlier, if you know the biblical days, you'll see what they're
using.
The globalists are using these days.
So I say globalists.
That's what it's called, you know.
By the way, you know how we had someone talk about the weather.
People like having a third leg on in a good way.
You know how we had someone for the first time.
Right on.
Come on.
And there was someone that I asked a long time ago who was a frequent emailer.
If you would like to come on also, we might.
He does some pretty.
He regularly keeps me up on things that I don't normally keep up on.
He sent me a video.
I mean, an audio about what he sounded like.
It wasn't.
I said, just let me see what you sound like.
And he did.
We might invite him on.
And there's another person.
I'm not going to mention his name.
Dimitri Kalasoff.
But we have him come on, you know.
Right.
So if that's OK with you guys, we'll maybe do that a little more often just to spice
things up.
But the lawful timekeeping, I don't know what else to say.
You know, I mean, here's the thing.
Uh, if you know lawfully, a triangle has three sides.
Do you need to how many once you learn that, how many times you need to reference a geometry
book?
And if you did see a book on geometry and it said a triangle had four sides, well, you
could call that bullshit right away.
Right.
That's true.
Yeah.
So, yeah.
But the biblical, you need some kind of reference.
Doesn't have to be biblical, you know.
But if you understand timekeeping, I remember looking through early American history documents
and it said on this seventh day of the fourth month, June, whatever.
Oh, wait a second.
Wait a second.
June is the sixth month, isn't it?
On the calendar on that.
Yeah, but why did you call it on this fourth month?
Yeah, right.
So they're running.
They were still run 1700.
They were still running two systems, right?
So you both or they're awful.
Yeah.
The other thing about that is anything has a lawful side, like lawful money, right?
You know, no matter how many times you pass a $20 gold piece, that's when you hear I got
a score to settle.
Score is 20.
Someone's owing someone a gold piece.
Right.
It's a 20 gold piece, no matter how many times it gets passed.
True.
Where with other things, it's, you know.
So, yeah, lawfulness is very important.
You know, this is the maybe 10th time in a month.
Someone I ran into said this and I have to say it.
Greek, you're the only one who says the body works by induction.
You know, they brought up all these guys talking about this, this person.
But you're the only one.
There's 10 times this happened in the past month.
I have to mention, you know, I said I have to mention if I get repeat synchronicities like that.
Right.
He said, but you're the only one talking about induction.
I'm like, now I'm trying to get all those comments and say I'm the only one talking about
induction.
What am I supposed to do with that?
Right.
And, you know, it's like, OK, I'm the only one.
Do I need to start, like, you know, yelling about it, doing more research on it or whatever?
What do I need to promote?
What?
I don't get it.
I mean, these are things that are, in other words, when you look at the medical stuff
and they tell you, by the way, if you do a search, I'll show you how what lawful means
and unlawful.
You know, they say if you can't dazzle them with brilliance, baffle them with bullshit.
I'm outside right now.
I've heard that.
I got the stupid rectangle in my pocket.
I'm having a smoke.
I'm going to go in for some coffee.
If you're in front of a terminal, a lot of sci fives, they call them computer terminals,
right?
Sci fi books and movies.
So if you're in front of a terminal, do this.
Type in how.
Let me see what I did the other day.
And I said, I got to do this on a sonic.
How does absorption occur in the small intestine?
Question mark.
And when you put pronunciation like that, the A.I.
kicks in, too.
So we want that.
Now, how does absorption occur in the small intestine?
Question mark.
Now you start reading all that stuff from the A.I.
and from websites all the way down because they give you a capture of the website.
You're going to see what a bullshit story looks like.
Can you do that?
Would you look that up, Chuck?
Oh, I'm doing it.
Yeah, I just I type slow.
Sorry.
No, that's fine.
OK, let me know when you start reading off.
I might ask you to pause.
I want to show you what's going on and how to wreck it, because I've never done this before.
In other words, an analysis of, you know, conventional bullshit.
Small intestine.
OK, how how does absorption work in small intestines?
Right now?
No, no, no.
What I put in was how does absorption occur?
Occur.
OK, OCC, you are in the small intestine.
Question mark.
How does absorption occur in the small intestine?
This is also an experiment to see how different the result you get, but that's
you want to sound more academic when you ask these things, and it will shift the response.
OK, more towards the academic side.
So I get an initial answer sort of put together at the top absorption
through the Vili and across the intestinal wall can occur by several mechanisms,
diffusion, facilitated diffusion, osmosis and active transport.
OK.
Figure 212 it references and then the duodenum
ileum and terminal ileum contribute differently to the function of the small intestine.
OK, so far they haven't answered anything.
But go ahead.
No, they're telling me the different pieces of different types of intestine contribute
differently, which I already know that the ileum is the initial small one.
And then you go into the other part.
Yeah, duodenum is the drain in the stomach.
Yeah, I try to avoid those terms because people shut down.
OK, you know, you know, when the stomach transits through the small intestine,
duodenum, I call it duodenum.
OK, and then you keep reading.
Yeah, the first reference, the first thing they give me to click on is small intestine
absorption and overview on ScienceDirect.com.
All right.
Either one.
When you start going down to some sites, it'll give you those way,
all these different ways, diffusion, osmosis, whatever.
Right.
And then it'll say this.
Well, how does it do it?
You know, it says that these cells do it.
And there's some special cells that do the absorption.
In other words, you start looking.
Well, how does it still hasn't answered how it happens?
And then when you get into the special cells, they don't want to tell you what
those special cells are, because guess what?
Those special cells don't exist.
Phosphorus and homeostasis, magnesium.
Yeah, it's like five different ways, right?
Yeah, all these different things, right.
Yeah.
So but none of them, they can't tell you really.
They're just giving you these distract.
These are all distractive terms.
All of it.
So if you ask a professor, let's say, oh, no, it's by osmosis.
Then if it's not by this, it's by that.
If it's not by this, it's by that.
If it's not by this.
Oh, my goodness.
What you will see eventually when you start going, there are special cells that contribute
to absorption.
OK, show me which cells I once I brought this up.
I bring this up again because I brought it up two decades ago.
And then they go down and you can't see that you need a special equipment.
It's so special.
It doesn't exist.
Yeah.
Then they're trying to bring you down to, OK, then it transports things to the gut.
And here's how gut works.
And here's no, no, no, no.
Go back to the read the original question again.
How does absorption occur in the small intestine?
You can be specific.
That's why I said small intestine.
And if you said the GI tract, it's all over the place.
Yeah, no, it took me all the way from that by going into the here's where it goes next.
And then absorption, salvage, absorption slash salvage.
But how does it occur?
Yeah.
How?
It doesn't say.
OK, if you keep slamming on the how, it'll eventually end up telling you there are special
cells that do that, period.
That's it.
That's all you need to know if you want to pass the test.
Total bullshit.
Now, any reasonable, normal person, space heater, NPC will look at that and be totally
satisfied with that response that you've just pulled up, whether you're clicking on sites
or looking at the top caption that Google provides is overview.
Right.
They're all going to be satisfied.
But I'm telling you, it's bullshit.
All of it, because when you start narrowing it down, they have no explanation or description
at all, at all, at all.
It's such bullshit.
I remember reading from a nurse, someone who's been working for a long time.
They personally examined everything.
And not only does it all absorption, it's hydrophobic.
Just like I said, hydrophobic means it repels, repels water, repels anything that's on it.
So this in other words, they're able to tell you why is the rain yellow?
And they're giving you all these different reasons, except all they have to say is because
you're getting pissed off, right?
Yeah.
Well, it's not yellow rain, you know.
So what I'm trying to say is when you look, this is what I mean by lawful and unlawful.
It's not lawful what they're saying, but it's so not lawful that they can't even, you cannot
glean what lawful is by reading that.
In other words, let's say you had your bullshit detector on and the needle hit the red and
busted because you're reading that.
You still don't know how it works, do you?
No.
Yeah.
So that's what I mean, why am I been getting for the past month, almost 10 people saying,
Greg, you're the only one that talks about the body working by induction.
This has been coming up.
I'm not taking it like it's a bad thing, like I'm the odd man out, I'm crazy.
They're like almost saying like, okay, now tell us more or what am I supposed to do with
that, right?
So I'm been thinking about it as I've been doing my chores and all the things that I'm
trying to get out and finish projects.
I'm trying to finish in several different fields right now and trying to see in my everyday
life, how can I see it expand the knowledge or expand use of it, right?
Because once you understand that it doesn't work the way we're being told and it works
this way, you're better off.
Even if you don't know exactly how it works, at least you know it's not that, right?
And I wanted to bring that up as an example because you'll see the type of explanation
looks fairly academic.
It's all bullshit, by the way.
And you see, you can see again, I'm repeating myself here, how the normies would think that's
adequate, right?
But it's not.
It's all deflection, bullshit, and all of it.
All of it.
So what do you do with it, right?
How do you progress, you know?
And that's where it takes the counsel of multitude, right?
You need more.
You can't just do it alone.
You can, but you have to narrow it down to one thing, you know?