Rated Y 137, so let's jump right in with what you're hearing back from people about what
they've actually, you know, paid attention to, heard on the Sonics and worked with, right
Greek?
How you doing?
Yeah, I'm doing okay.
Um, yeah, just, uh, yes.
What about our acupuncture?
I said, well, I've covered that before, but let's, let's go over that real fast one more
time.
Um, you ask those people that practice it, they don't know what it is.
They just, you know, well, they'll just like an attorney, they'll just read off what they've
been told to say, right?
Um, what, what the original, uh, premise was that there is a field around the body, right?
Um, more, and it actually interacts with the way you look, the way you smell and your
heat, the amount of heat you give with all those are factors, right?
Uh, but this field is, they call the aura, it's the, you know, the, the, um, the typical,
you know, the breakfast cereal types, you know, fruit, nuts and flakes, or, uh, exactly
say they don't know what it is, but it's an energy field around you.
Just like there are contactless, um, electronic, uh, equipment, you know, you can measure and
see if the, you have a hot wire, uh, without, you know, uh, touching the wire, right?
Right.
Okay.
Uh, yeah.
There's all these, uh, like radio sensing and all that.
So it has been proven that we have a field around us now that field is also is perpetuated
or let's say pumped by your musculature.
So let's say you have someone who's a quadriplegic wheelchair bound, the field will measure very,
very small.
And you have someone who is a bodybuilder, their field will be huge because typically
that field like it or not, or no, it or not is perpetuated by the muscles, which by the,
by the way, the word muscle means tiny mouse, by the way.
So I thought that was funny whenever someone says they've got a lot of muscle, but anyway,
um, they got a lot of tiny mice.
Okay.
Yeah.
So it's, yeah.
So it was all right.
Uh, so this field, by the way, in Tai Chi, certain practices, you can amp it up regardless
of your musculature using the emo work.
All right.
So this is the field, what we're talking about, and that's actually more important than the
acupuncture.
Now, the science of acupuncture is based on a movement of energy through the body.
Now, energy is a loose term here.
Uh, it's in other words, I like the word to encompass more than what the standard definition
of energy is.
Okay.
Meaning non-material should say it's all non-material.
So there was a study way back when that, uh, parts of the body, they're in balance, have
the potential, uh, to tap into this energy field and parts of the body that are in balance,
meaning they have too little to tap into that energy field surrounding the body or parts
of the body that have too much energy to discharge into the field.
So where did we first find out about sticking metal into a living thing?
The earth is a living thing to attract an electrical circuit or to make an electrical
circuit, a lightning rod, imagine what a lightning rod looks like.
And that's exactly what acupuncture does.
And basically based on the techniques that are taught and how skilled the person doing
it is, they can either use it to send energy to your field, a drain and energy, uh, you
know, too much energy in one part of the body or bring that energy that's lacking in the
body from the field that's surrounding it.
That's all it is.
Think of it as a lightning rod.
Uh, another idea would be why did they put lightning rods on buildings in place?
So you had a more predictable place of where the lightning would strike, right?
It was just, it's not that the lightning rods prevent lightning from striking.
It's a, you now make that strike predictable location wise, right?
Okay.
And you feel, you feel safer around it.
It's exactly acupuncture works also when you study it now.
So what this sounds like is you're balancing things out by staking it out and, and make,
making things distribute equally in a way.
So remember, there's no steady state, even though we seem to be thinking that way, you're
either discharging into that energy field, the aura, or you're charging the body underneath
the aura.
Right.
So some parts of like most, believe it or not, uh, if you live in a society that's got
the EMF radiation, that we have stimulants and food, uh, toxic ingredients, do you, most
people will be overcharged.
Their organs will be overcharged and you have to discharge them.
Okay.
Right.
Uh, uh, cases of, uh, renal exhaustion, like you've been stressed for a year and you can't
take it anymore, a poor diet, dehydration, uh, poor mental state, your body will be too
low energy.
You need a boost, right?
So stimulants and chemicals and electromagnetic will overcharge the organs where the other
ones I just mentioned, the starving, you know, undercharged.
So a good, uh, when I used to have medical practitioners, I'd speak with them, they'd
bring me a case, these medical practitioners in many different fields, both allopathic neurosurgeon
types, a standard, you know, and, uh, the alternative medicine types or whatever they
call themselves.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, every time they bring me a case, I say, hold on.
What about ABC?
I would ask these questions and they would always go back and say, oh, I don't know.
I never asked those questions.
Right.
So, uh, so what I'm trying to say is it all is based around, do you know about asking the
right questions?
I mean, you've probably heard this before, right?
You know, if you're asking the right questions, you know, that means that you're, you're, you're
going to figure more out than if you didn't.
So the same thing goes with acupuncture.
Um, it doesn't work for everyone, uh, because they're not asking why they should do acupuncture.
In other words, also not every acupuncture practitioner knows what knows is very good
at just like a carpenter or a plumber, but empirically, and it's in a form and it's valid.
It's a valid form, but it's very difficult for many people to grasp because you have to
acknowledge there's a field around the body and that many don't want to acknowledge that.
So that's like a overview of acupuncture and pick and choose, I don't know the question
of whatever acupuncture might be from that.
Uh, never is acupuncture, a local thing.
Uh, okay.
It is sometimes someone says, I have a pain in my ankle pain in the ass, right?
Oh, wait, that's my, well, no.
Okay.
Uh, whatever.
Yeah.
Uh, yeah.
Uh, so, uh, whatever.
Uh, and they'll go treat that.
No, a good practitioner, uh, will not.
Okay.
You have the pain in your, your ankle.
But he has to look at the entire body, right?
Right.
Okay.
Uh, not just the ankle.
Now I've seen, I've seen this before where someone went in, they had a recovery from
an injury and, uh, it was their neck and the practitioner did not, did not, was not inclusive
about the rest of the body.
So that's, it's not going to work that cause they're maybe it's hit or miss 50, 50.
It didn't work.
And then I found someone who knew about asking about the entire body and also per other conditions
and near person's habits and all that.
And it did work for them.
So it's just like anybody, anything else.
Yeah.
Like for instance, if somebody is having chronic pain, you got to look at their, their actions,
the way they walk, uh, what it is they surround themselves with, uh, let me just say it this
way.
Um, when people come to me for pain, I totally ignore that.
It's like a pain is absolutely inconsequential.
Okay.
You're in pain, take a freaking pain inducer or what are they called?
A painkillers.
I mean, there's so many, some of them, especially if you, I'm talking about over the shelf, aren't
there a lot of pain relief things that are over the counter that you don't have to get
prescription, all kinds of stuff.
Sure.
Yeah.
And then they have the prescription ones, right.
And they get really up to the fentanyl, right?
Isn't fentanyl primarily pain relief.
Yeah.
Okay.
And then Oxycontin, all those.
Right.
And, uh, yeah, I'm not against any of that.
Absolutely.
In other words, if someone says Greek, what I do about this pain, I say, okay, take anything
you can.
And if it has an orange, if it's prescription and it has that bright orange warning, it
says, do not take with alcohol.
That's the first thing you want to do.
You want to take it with alcohol.
Absolutely.
Take it with alcohol.
Right.
Yeah.
Um, you're laughing cause you know, it's true.
Right.
Cause it amplifies the effects.
Oh yeah.
And you don't need as much.
The alcohol is always going to end up being cheaper than the pill.
Absolutely true.
Yeah.
It depends on what you're drinking, but it doesn't matter.
Cause anyway, so, so the pain, then the thing is then finding out why the city, it's kind
of like the smoke alarm is going off in my house.
What should I do?
I'm not going to sit there and address, well, what does the smoke alarm alarm sound like?
How long has it been going?
Who cares?
Where's the fire?
Where's the smoke?
Right.
You see big difference to me.
Pain is something I never even consider.
It was like, you know, pain, what were we telling you?
Why are you, why are you in pain?
You should have taken care of that before your next meal.
There's a whole bunch of stuff you could take on them.
Here's the thing.
If especially, okay, here, if you know anyone who has a grandmother, the social security,
Medicare, whatever, they all have pain pills.
So if you know someone who has a graph, Hey, is your grandma have something in her medicine
chest?
You know, does she have anything yet?
You'll go there and you'll find they're easy.
I'm talking about the, the prescription ones are really easy to get.
I threw my back out about 10 years ago.
I couldn't walk for a day.
And I said, I told the wife, go ask around.
This is, you know, I see, you see, there's an old lady that lives with that young guy
across the street, knock on their door, man, they had all the pill.
They gave me like half a pill of, I forgot what it was, a nebutal or something, or I don't
know.
It was, it was a couple of really powerful stuff, man.
I was, I was great.
Pain was no longer an issue.
It was now the issue was, what do I, can I do to get mobility back into the back without
it's sending a trigger?
So don't, don't ever ask me about pain because pain is like an afterthought.
It's like your smoke alarm.
Forget about the smoke alarm.
Who cares what color your smoke alarm is or how loud it is.
Why is it on?
Why is it going on?
Why are you?
So you have to address the cause.
I am all for, if anyone is in pain, I am, it doesn't matter toothache, whatever, you
know, your wife or a dog where there's no reason to be in pain at all.
There are so many things out there to take.
I'm particularly a Kratom head.
Years ago I was having some dental issues and I was just not happy, you know, 21, 27
someone said they've tried Kratom.
I'm like, Oh, what the hell is that?
And I'm just a Kratom head.
I love it.
I buy it by the kilo.
I get the stuff called, it's a train wreck blend.
Usually the kilos about 200 bucks at the smoke shops.
I get it for 69 bucks at a wholesaler, Kratom, wholesaler, whatever.
And I do about 30 grams a day of that stuff.
I love it because years ago I used to like getting high, but then I discovered that
I was better when I wasn't high.
But now I discovered that when I'm taking Kratom, getting older doesn't feel so bad,
right?
It's kind of a euphoric thing.
It's very interesting for some people.
Like if you have a low sex drive, it'll give you a strong sex drive.
If you have a strong sex drive, it'll damp out your sex drive where, you know, it depends.
You have to experiment with it.
Some people find credit.
It's an opioid, by the way, it's, it is classified as an opioid, opioid, and it's used in a lot
of, um, we got off to painkillers from acupuncture, but it's used, uh, you know how they go from
the people that go from a drug addiction, let's say like heroin into a synthetic heroin
that doesn't get you off the addiction.
Well, now you've got to get off, you know, you've got to get off the thing that was supposed
to get you off of that.
Kratom is used for that.
So people that take the Kratom, uh, that were on heavy opioid addictions can taper off and
it's done.
It's really a wonderful, uh, tool for that.
And the FDA was going after it.
There was a lot of kickback.
It's actually legal in Australia, I think, in England and a couple of the States like
Arkansas.
It's treated like, what is it?
Class three, class four.
What is the lower class, uh, drug?
I forgot what it's called.
What did they have?
Different classes.
Class one and two were together.
Yeah.
It's like, it's like a third or a third or four.
I forget.
Yeah.
It's low on the bottom, but you're not supposed to have it.
Right.
Okay.
Still.
Yeah.
Right.
So anyway, so that's the story about acupuncture and pain.
But again, we got into the pain because how many people actually consider acupuncture,
uh, because they're in pain just about everyone, right?
And that should not be the reason you're doing it.
The reason you should be doing it is because for pain, there's so many things you can take
pain.
Pain is a, uh, is a quick and dirty thing.
Well, you know what I, you know, when you tell someone just do it quick and dirty, it
doesn't matter.
Right.
Uh, that's what pain is.
If you have pain, just do a quick and dirty solution.
It doesn't matter.
Just get rid of the pain so you can think more clearly.
That's not what you should be chasing.
You should be chasing what's causing the pain and acupuncture done properly can do that.
But good luck finding a good practitioner that understands it.
Yeah.
Because it becomes like chiropractor.
You know, when chiropractor was being fought in the 60s, 70s, uh, they were fighting the
chiropractors.
Right.
And then they, then they took them on.
They, they, they accepted them.
They embraced them and they became shit.
Right.
You're not as good.
Not to say they became shit, but they're not as good as they were when they were more rogue.
Right.
And that's the weird thing about the acupuncture thing is that there are some people that practice
it or that, you know, actually do it for people.
And they don't even know what, what works or why or anything else they, they just do
it like anything.
Yeah.
It's weird.
I mean, you're thinking, well, somebody is sticking you with a whole bunch of needles.
They got to know what they're doing.
Right.
No.
A bunch of them don't.
You know what?
They're not even really needles.
You know, they're really high end ones.
They're very fine.
You don't even, they're so fine.
You don't feel them.
And they're like tubes.
They, they have found, uh, I'm trying to recall, was it for these, these wires, these micro wires,
and they're actually tubular.
It's like, how the hell did they get that micro hole in there?
Right.
Um, yeah, they are needles, but they're not like sewing needles.
They're not, they're, you know, they're made to, the geometry is made to penetrate the skin.
Yeah.
Right.
So that you basically don't even notice it.
It's, you know, if it's done right.
Yeah.
The twisting.
Also the thing about, uh, acupuncture, it's the, the practitioner, let's, let's not even
getting into it.
Let's do an analogy.
A, uh, I got a lightning rod.
I'm going to go install it.
I'm climbing the long ladder and I got the lightning rod in my hand as I'm going to the
top of the building.
What are the chances of that lightning rod getting hit by lightning and me holding onto
it also getting hit by lightning?
Very high.
Right.
Yeah.
You see like holding a live wire.
So, so guess what?
When the practitioner is working on you, are they grounding themselves and do they understand
that they have to somehow isolate their field from yours?
What is the likeliness when you're getting acupuncture that the field, uh, that's on
the body, on the ground, let's say, right.
Cause the body would be like the ground is being transferred to yours or vice versa.
Are there draining you more?
Right.
What are the chances of that?
150%.
Yeah.
Because they have to know.
It's like holding a wire.
Wait, hold on to this wire, Chuck.
Yeah.
Like what they often call static electricity.
I mean, you're almost guaranteeing a discharge once it's built up or vice versa.
So let's say someone's overcharged.
Is it possible that the practitioner now when they apply it, let's say a quote unquote,
a needle to that area, they're either going to accept that charge.
Of course they are.
Yeah.
So these things are considering their techniques on that, by the way, with the acupuncture,
there's mock subduction.
You ever seen that where they put a cup on your, it pulls the skin up, you know, it increases
the vacuum in the body.
Oh yeah.
I've seen that.
Familiar with that.
Yeah.
The glass, the cupping.
They just put a hot air, the light of match or a burning, uh, whatever.
And then they put it and it sucks your skin up.
Uh, that, what do you think that's doing?
It's increasing vacuum artificially, right?
And that works also.
Yeah.
That's exactly what I was thinking.
It changes.
Cause like you talked about with the, with the vacuum, you know, the body and the, uh,
yeah.
It's like, it's like pulling a play.
When you pull the plunger up, what is it?
It's a vacuum.
When you push the plunger down, it's pressure positive.
It's all, it's all about vacuum and induction.
By the way, with induction, when I say induction, I think I give enough examples that it is a
broad term because if you have an induction cooktop stove, your pots won't work.
They have to have some Ferris in it.
Right?
So if you have an all copper pot and all glass pot, where it won't work on an induction,
so it has to have a, you know, that's why years ago you got pots and pans and when they
were aluminum with Teflon, they said, okay, on induction stoves.
Yeah.
That meant that it had a piece of steel in it, you know, Ferris for it to work.
Right.
So what's the, uh, this is a completely other Sonic.
The induction aspect of the human body is what do you have Ferris?
By the way, the blood is not magnetic.
It's not, the iron in the blood has nothing to do with the iron you'd find anywhere else,
but cause it's organic.
But the, uh, so what is it inducing?
What the induction of the body, what is it required?
You know how you need Ferris and pots and pans to induce for, uh, the soap to work or
what do you need in your body to, for the induction to work?
You want to take guests?
A very good guests.
Water.
Now we're dealing with the water as an inductive element.
Now how much research is being done on that?
Zero.
Nobody's doing research on that.
I don't want anyone understanding that.
Yeah.
And, and what do you have to incorporate to understand, uh, understand it?
Uh, guess what, uh, block wall of the magnet, the part of the magnet that nothing attracts
to.
Okay.
That's enough for that.
Anybody who's been around knows what I'm talking about, but I think that's like part of a seminar.
I'm starting to slowly put together, uh, more of a compendium on, on physiology.
I never really, uh, when I speak on the body, I never say this is medical or whatever.
It's really physiology, you know, which is how the organic biological things really work.
Right.
It's, uh, by the way, just to interject that someone sent message the other day, archaic
said his last show with mud flood did announce on September 10th, he's going to have uncommon
sense radio.
Right.
Okay.
Uh, so I guess we're on, and I did cut confirmation just to let people know, but then some people
are suggesting, you know, what to talk about when I go on a first time interview, like
something, uh, uh, that I haven't been on before.
And I would suggest that most of the people are not familiar.
I'm going to do what's called Greek speak, baby speak, you know, which is the stuff I
talked about 10, 20, look, I've been doing this for three decades.
Now.
So the early, since the early two thousands, the tens and the twenties, that's one, two,
three decades.
It doesn't mean full 33 decades, but four through crossing into a third decade.
So what I first started speaking on is what I always do when I start somewhere, but it's
always with a variation, right?
Right.
So I predict we'll hear something about the real meaning of the word nice.
And uh, yeah, the direction of heat, the intestines, you know, the Bay it's baby speak, but it's
not, when you say baby speak, it sounds like you're doing it in a baby voice, but it will
not be a baby voice.
It'll just be baby topics.
Anybody who's been on this planet for at least a month, uh, can and should know is the topic.
You know how that's the slogan and the heading for it.
Greek speak.
Anyone who's been on this planet for more than a month can and should know.
Right.
Warm, warm, warm feet, cool head, this kind of thing.
And uh, by the way, he does that live on YouTube, I guess.
Is that what's going to happen there?
So September 10th, you'll be doing that with them.
Yeah.
2 PM Texas time, which is, uh, I don't know if it's an hour now or so central time or
whatever it's called.
So yeah.
An hour difference from the East and uh, yeah, right.
Exactly.
Yeah.
So what else you got?
Oh, Hey, look, the other thing was, uh, you had mentioned that you got some, uh, feedback
regarding, uh, the bills.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Let's go into that.
I'll go from memory.
Because looking at it, you know, is, is that to, to be more, I don't need to be specific
on it, but someone sent in a bill of exchange, uh, to a, um, utility company.
And they basically, actually there was done in person and they tried to play hot potato.
They told me like they passed it over and they said, it's not mine.
It's yours.
Meaning the clerk.
Right.
Cause they've been told they're getting thousands of these now.
And, uh, I got a copy was made back and essentially it basically stated, uh, you didn't really,
it's not a payment.
You just sent us the voucher on the bottom where the clip off or cut off at the bottom
of the state.
Right.
And we take cash, blah, blah, blah.
You know, the standard thing, you know, cash credit card check, I'm just paraphrasing.
Yeah.
Well, the thing is, that's fine.
And a lot of these, uh, things are happening, but we utility companies, it's pretty interesting.
Uh, I don't know where to start with this bill, do like several things parallel.
Let's just do the overview.
Okay.
All right.
So you could look up something called, if you go to a browser search, look up, uh, what
is in fine, you know, in the world of finance or finance, what is a C T O. So you look
up CTO and they'll tell you, Oh, that is called a CTO stands for a confidential treatment
order.
And that is where a company that is publicly listed or publicly is, is has to show it's
a finances publicly can engage in a confidential treatment order CTO, where it keeps certain
transactions with certain people secret completely, and they can actually deny that it ever happened.
Okay.
So what's going on with all utility companies is this, they all have CTOs.
That's okay.
Do you notice after COVID people say, Oh, our utility bills went up 10, 20, 30%, right
across the board.
Okay.
What they did was, uh, let's say pick the electric company.
And what they do is they go to a securities, they were actually solicited security company
and says, Hey, uh, uh, what's your average billing?
What do you get per year?
We'll give you this much over it, but let us, uh, all the billings from now on come to us.
So they start raising the prices.
So when you see, I got into this before utility companies raising the cost of, uh, let's say
electrical power, it's cheaper to produce electrical power now than ever.
So why are the bills going up?
Because they're selling the future earnings to a private securities firm.
And guess what?
It's under a CTO.
So no matter how much you do with, what do they call it?
Freedom of information or whatever they're, they don't have to answer.
And they've got the securities exchange commission behind them.
So what's the solution for that?
That's what I like to get solutions is you have to get enough people, cause this is not
going to happen, but you can try it.
I'll be surprised.
Uh, you get enough people that have the similar billing and you strike, you strike for one
or two months, just don't pay your bill and tell them why.
And if enough people do that, the security company that is receiving these payments will
say, Hey, this is a bad deal.
You said everybody pays on time.
Most people pay on time.
Oh, we want to go back to how it was.
And then when it goes, we don't want to deal.
We don't want to buy your future earnings.
Right.
And then when it dumps back down, they, the prices you tell you should drop, right?
Because they're not the, now the utility company controls it again, you see?
So that's, what's pretty much going on with utility companies.
Now let's go back to the bill exchange.
You've got to find, I think it's UCC article three, read it that covers, I might be wrong
on this.
There are other articles, not wrong, but there are other articles that cover what's called
bill of exchange.
The primary one is the bill of exchange act of 1882.
The other thing you should be very familiar with is title 12 of the U S code and some
other corresponding codes.
This, I don't have any of this in front of me.
I'm actually standing in my kitchen making some coffee.
And there are many other, cause what, what this would be a research done on this.
Cause there are many codes that have not been brought up that also pertain.
That's why I've been putting mentioning Brandon Joe Williams as a good primer.
He does go into the UCC and several things and reads them out very well.
So what I would suggest is find out, do your research on what, what codes and laws articles
of UCC and U S codes and code of federal regulations.
No one's talking about the CFR have to do with bills of exchange.
In essence there's two aspects to it and I'm not going to get into it.
One is that, you know, you're the beneficiary of the trust known as the social security
number.
Anyone who asks you, actually I should go into it.
Social security number is a trust and you are the beneficiary.
Now you, someone could make you the trustee, but that's reverses the role, right?
Because when something goes wrong in the trust, who takes the hit, who goes to jail, who pays
for it?
The trustees.
So that's what they're always trying to make you do.
Yeah.
So when you, okay.
So anybody who has your social security number and you acknowledge that you're the beneficiary
and you look at them and you say, Oh, I'm the beneficiary trustee.
What are you going to do?
Right?
That changes it.
Uh, I've done this, for example, uh, this is going to be all over the place, but someone
had, uh, uh, was picked up on a domestic violence charge.
Uh, the girlfriend called up and they picked him up.
He had, uh, already a bench warrant out from, from two years before he had a DUI.
Uh, I mean, he wasn't looking good for him.
They had him in jail overnight.
He goes up in front of the judge and, um, he, he was, I used to talk to him a lot.
So you got to clear up that stuff.
And he goes for the judge and judge, they did like arraignment sentencing all at the
same time.
It was very strange.
You know, judge is a prosecutor.
I'll get into that again.
How the system works.
We've been doing that a little bit.
Anyway, he reads off all these things about doing jail and fines and all that.
And he looks at Ben, Ben, the judge needs your response.
So he looks at me, he says, no, I don't think that I don't see how any of that's going to
benefit me judge.
And the judge like stares at him, puts his glasses on 10 seconds later, he goes, okay,
case dismissed.
Right.
Because he made the judge a trustee, right?
That's why judge Bork said when he was addressed on public, on public, on CBS, like 1981, it
wasn't when Reagan, the 82 or whatever, judge Bork for being reviewed for Supreme court
justice.
So one of the reporters asked him on TV, what are you going to do about the growing prison
population?
He says, absolutely nothing.
Everyone's volunteered to be there.
Right.
And they cut it right there.
So, yeah.
So, so, okay.
So anyone do the utility companies have social security number?
Yes, they do.
So they're trustee.
You shouldn't even be getting a bill.
The bill should be going to the treasury.
How's that going to happen?
Because it's open.
You can act as a trustee and take the hit.
In other words, go to jail or go and get other notes and work for it.
Or you just solely act as a beneficiary.
And anyone who has that number is now a trustee, right?
That's why like if you get a letter from the IRS, why am I getting a letter from a, I shouldn't
even be known.
Right.
Anything that is titled with the old caps name, they're taxing the trust.
They're putting the trust in jail there.
The bill, the water bill goes to the trust, not you.
Start off.
I mean, you just don't say it like this, but the thing that she's always running your mind,
why are you giving me the bill?
I'm a beneficiary.
I shouldn't even know about it.
You have social security number.
You're a trustee.
Handle it.
You got the access to the trust.
I shouldn't even know there's a water bill.
I shouldn't even know there's a tax bill.
I shouldn't know there's a car bill.
I shouldn't even crank our company.
Why are you sending to me?
So the old caps trust your trustee, do your job, trustee, you see?
But that's not going to happen that easy, right?
Because of the population doesn't know this, by the way, as I mentioned, the entire system
is set up with a dead man's switch.
Once people find out the laws, the whole system falls apart.
It was set up that way, right?
Just like the speech in trafficking, he said, basically, the whole bankruptcy and Congress
being trustees is a coroner's report, or the new budget was a coroner's report.
Yeah, I've said the country was killed in 33, it just hasn't been buried yet.
So the burial happens when enough people realize what the laws actually say, what they're supposed
to be doing.
Am I all for it?
Yeah.
Cover your ears.
Hell yeah, I'm all for it.
All right.
So because how much more do you want to live like that, right?
So some people don't mind and don't care.
That's not me.
But here's the thing.
With the bills, there's so many ways.
You can do what's called a conditional acceptance.
I'm not an expert on it, but there's a lot of conditional acceptances that I've seen
are 25, 30 pages long.
It could just be one paragraph.
All you've got to do, and I'm not saying this is in any order.
You'll notice when you do sign, I think two or three sonics ago, we did go over how CHAT-GBT
tells you that a bill is actually a check, right?
And now, here's the thing.
Let's just go back there.
When you get to that point, when you're writing out the bottom of the voucher of a bill like
a check, do me a favor.
Have a check.
Just go online and get a sample check, and look at it well, and look at the voucher.
You'll see it has a routing number with a code on the bottom, right?
Just like a check does, right?
And try to suss out, you know how a check is laid out.
It's the bank, and then who the customer is, who it's going to, the amount, and it's also
written.
Look at a check, and then look at the voucher that comes to the bottom of the bill.
Don't start writing on it the third-grade penmanship all over the place.
Try to make it look like what you put there corresponds geometrically.
It kind of looks good, right?
It doesn't have to be that big.
It has to look clean.
Handwritten, always, by the way, trumps printed or typewritten, always.
This is in the code as well.
So basically, words trump numbers.
When you see numbers and it's written in words, what's written in the words is really
what's followed.
And then handwritten is more important than typewritten.
That's why when you have a contract, and you don't like something, you cross it out, put
your initial there.
That actually is more important than what's typewritten or printed on the contract when
it's handwritten.
That's why you don't hear this much, but if you listen to some YouTube channels about
litigants and attorneys on both sides or whatever, or judges or legal staff or whatever,
they'll mention, they said, I got a correspondence from so-and-so, and it was handwritten.
You hear that sometimes.
And they wrote it by hand.
It's a big deal.
It is a big deal.
You don't have to write it by hand, but if you do, make it look presentable, very neat.
It should be good penmanship.
You could practice your penmanship.
There are printers now that you, by the way, it has an AI element in it where you feed
it.
It scans.
You have to sign your name, anything, seven or 10 times, and it scans it, and then it
has a fountain pen in the printer, and it actually signs for you with a pen.
These printers exist.
High-end brokers use them.
And Wells Fargo, I'm sure.
Yeah.
I've seen those.
They actually duplicate the signature and that.
Right.
That's why they need you to sign seven or eight times, so it kind of sees the variant.
Okay.
Now, let's go back to the conditional acceptance.
What you do when you do give a conditional acceptance is basically setting them up.
We were growing up with, have you stopped beating your wife yet?
That's a setup.
Have you stopped beating your wife yet?
If you say no, it means you're still beating her.
If you say yes, you're still beating her.
Then you were beating her before.
So conditional acceptances are like that.
By the way, the bills of exchange are like that, too.
But, okay.
Conditional acceptance could be, to start off, a question.
Records show that you are a legal corporation, legal municipality, legal utility, whatever
foundation, organization.
And you send out billing through the mail, electronically, whatever.
When you send out your billing, is it per United States laws, codes, and regulations?
And commercial codes?
That's a question.
When you send out your billing, do you do remittance also according to the United States
codes, laws, rules, regulations?
Remittance is when you accept something back for payment, right?
Right.
Typically, remittance is used when you have coupons.
When you go to the store and you have $5 off of whisked laundry detergent, and you give
the coupon to the cashier, that's called a remittance.
It's not a payment, but, right?
Right.
Okay.
It's like a redeeming.
All right.
So basically, you could set up a utility company.
Are you following all these laws?
And you put Uniform Commercial Code, United States Code of Federal Relations, United States
Code.
What are they going to say?
No?
We don't follow them?
Nope.
They're going to admit to that?
Now, if they admit that they do follow the law, well, you got them right under your fingertips.
The Uniform Commercial Code tells you, just like CHAT-DBT, how to turn a bill into a check.
You just turn it into a check.
Pay to the order of, they already have the utility company, right?
And you write the, let's say it's $123.40, one, two, three, four.
You write with your hand, 123, right?
Just like the, I think in the fourth or fifth grade, they do check writing in math class
here now, right?
They used to.
I don't know if they still do.
Okay.
Well, yeah.
But you see, so you set it up just like the check.
So if they say in the conditional acceptance, yes, we do do everything under United States
Codes.
Are you able to cite the codes that show you and tell you what a bill of exchange needs
to contain?
Easy peasy.
It's the UCC Article 3.
It's in 12 U.S.C., you know, Title 12, United States Code.
It's in 411, 412, right?
You have the Bill of Exchange Act of 1882.
You don't have to go back that far, but you can pull some verbiage.
It's the same exact verbiage, just like if you look at Title 12, Section 411, it's the
same.
Where did they get the verbiage out of that in the U.S. Code, 12 U.S.C. 411?
Where did that verbiage come from?
It came directly out of the 16th Amendment.
Look it up.
They do a lot of copy and pasting, right?
So when you look at the UCC Uniform Commercial Code, like Article 3, basically, it's all
over the place.
I think it's Article 3-301, 302, 303, 304, all the way, 308 goes with reserving rights.
When you look at those, it's cut and pasted from where?
The UCC cut and pasted from where?
The Bill of Exchange Act of 1882.
You might have noticed, anyone who's studied law sees a lot of cut and pasting going on
between codes and laws and things like that, right?
So it'll make it easy.
Yeah, it'll make it easy.
So basically, you basically ask whoever you're planning on sending a bill of exchange to,
first, you have to establish that they send out bills and accept remittance and payment,
right?
It seems like you do.
They're not going to say we don't, because they do, and then you ask them, do you follow
the laws of the United States, codes, rules, regulation, and commercial laws known as the
Uniform Commercial Code?
Do you follow that?
And you just send that letter out.
What are they going to do?
If they say no, well, now you go to the attorney general and say, look, these guys are running
utility companies, so they don't follow the law.
You got a confession, right?
But if they say, yes, we do follow the law, can you copy and paste how all the codes actually
tell you a bill turns into a check?
Yeah.
And you're done.
This is a simplified thing.
This is kind of like when I talk about scalier, just wrap a pipe around the part of the magnet
that doesn't stick to iron sticks to the block wall, and you're done.
Well, it's not that simple.
I had to do like a nine-hour seminar, right?
Right.
And people still don't get it.
So the same thing with this, this might require a seminar to be more pointed, but you got
to take in, at the same time, this is what, I don't endorse Brandon Joe Williams because
he never brings up conditional, he does bring up conditional endorsements with an I, or he
doesn't matter, but he thinks so, without recourse.
But I'm telling you, that still creates a tax liability, even though you think you hopped
it out.
Because I know people that have YouTube channels that live in England, and they get IRS forms,
they say they have to fill out.
So it has nothing to do with being a citizen or not, like they're trying to.
So what's important is a conditional endorsement where you're still making a demand for lawful
money, right?
That's the paramount thing.
Now, I don't know how well the two would mix.
Someone who really is doing Title 12, 411, lawful money only, I don't think that type
of person who's doing it from a moral point of view or an ethical point of view is going
to want to jump down and grab those bills and sign them, send them in, because now you're
acting like a Federal Reserve Bank.
So I have to ponder on that to see if there's a commingling, like on one side, you're acting
like a bank, and the other side, you're not.
But making a demand for lawful money doesn't mean that you're acting like a bank that's
bad or they have any more jurisdiction over you or creating any liability.
You have to think about that, but you should always include that.
Right, because looking through some of this stuff, I mean, it says the SEC issues certain
things, you know.
Well, hold on.
The SEC is a real bullshit company, by the way.
They are a company.
They're the easiest thing to get rid of, and they make these big deals about them, right?
The SEC is like any other of the agencies or corporations, but the reason they seem
so big and bad is because people let them be big and bad.
But you could spank them around and get them out of the picture real fast, but that's okay.
Go ahead with your example.
Well, no, I was just saying that with the confidential treatment orders, they're just,
the SEC is part of it.
They issue these, it says.
They're the ones who are supposed to issue them.
So that's why.
Yeah, you go to, let's say the utility company, they go to the SEC and say, we want to do
a confidential treatment order.
So the SEC has it on record, but no one else knows.
But it's interesting because it's almost like, you know, with using the Federal Reserve notes
effectively, what do they say?
The only people that are supposed to use those are what?
Agents of the Federal Reserve, right?
That's right.
So the problem.
Now, anyone could use them, but you're not authorized to use them.
And what happens when you, you're found with something that you're not authorized to use?
What is that thing called now?
Contraband.
Yeah, that's contraband.
Right.
And so, but therefore not, it's not useful to you.
It shouldn't be useful to you because you are not authorized to.
Well, yeah.
Okay.
But once we go into the codes, we Federal Reserve notes are any bills, any bonds, right?
Any bills of exchange.
What's a bill of exchange, right?
Mm hmm.
Okay.
You see?
Now here's the, okay.
That was kind of like a messy tangential over the place.
So here's the second part.
So let's say you get a bill from utility company and the bottom says, detach this voucher,
send it in with your payment.
And you fill out that voucher like a check.
If they tell you whether they give it, okay, they usually, by the way, in this case, they
kept it.
They kept it.
Right.
They send you a copy back.
Yeah.
Which means that's okay.
Well, the code says that if it's refused, there is no debt, the debt is cleared.
That's why I mean, this is all like, have you stopped beating your wife yet?
You damned if you do, damned if you don't.
So the minute you, it's like stepping in poop.
Once they get a bill of exchange, they're done, they're finished.
Because if they refuse it, there's no debt.
Now if they don't send it back, means they used it.
They literally deposit, made a deposit.
They ran a transaction number on it and they deposited it.
They never give them back.
I have never seen one come back.
They send a copy back.
Now I was in a, uh, it was hanging around this people in a court case for a bad check.
It was a bad check for a million bucks and they got the 10% initially they pulled it,
pulled it anyway.
And they kept it and they were like, Oh, you, you, you gotta, you gotta come talk to us.
Well, why?
Well, we got a bad check.
Oh, give me a check back.
I'll make it right.
No, we can't give it back.
Cause the bank was able to use that million dollar check, even though there was zero in
the bank.
Right.
They don't want, right anyway.
So, uh, we never got the check back.
Judge says, yeah, they gave you a check back.
So they gave you a legal copy, legal copy.
It said, right.
You know, Xerox copy of it or a copy machine.
Is that okay?
Is what you do need a recess?
No, no recess.
I need to really need a recess.
Okay.
Run down in the court building.
Find a copy machine.
Took about 20 minutes.
Take a $10 bill, make a copy of it and then bring it back.
All right.
What do you got?
Let's continue.
Okay.
Uh, judge, can I spend this?
And you give the judge a Xerox copy of a $10 bill.
Obviously not.
Yeah.
So that, that's what, that's how good the legal copy of the check is.
I need the original check back.
Right.
They won't do it because they used it.
It's the same thing.
So that was done very often after that, by the way, in a lot of bank cases.
So at this point, um, they're damned if they do damage.
They don't.
Now I know on another side note, the utility companies, credit card companies and all that,
they're getting them by the thousands.
Now what I would do, let's say I wanted to mix, I'll tell you what I would do, but don't
do what I would do.
What I would do is, uh, be prepared to have another party.
Uh, you could shut down the account when it goes sour and then they say they hold you
for an unsecured debt, just like not paying a phone bill or whatever, right.
But what I would do is if I was messing around, let's say I had an account with the electric
company yesterday.
I wanted to really do this and experiment with it.
Um, before I even started messing around, the first thing I would do is get another
party that would back up.
So if I close the account, right.
And it doesn't mean that they won't think I still owe it.
That's okay.
In other words, you could rack up a hundred thousand dollars in, uh, uh, electric bills
in three months and then close the account.
You can do that, but then they're going to send it to a collection agency.
You see?
So let's say you need the power on in the building.
What I would do is get another party.
So as I'm messing around, I could shut the account anytime and then have the other party
just put it in their name, right?
So have someone else that you could put it in their name or their trust name.
It's never in your name.
So, um, so let's say you, you know, you have a, uh, not a wife, but someone else, because
they, you know, whatever, if you, if you have a marriage license, that's like the worst
thing in the world.
But yeah.
Cause then you have your wife, you have a corporate attachment, you have a corporate
attachment that way.
That's right.
In the computer, you're the same entity, right?
So another party to completely different address and everything like that.
So anyway, uh, cause they asked for previous address to sometimes anything that's verifiable.
So what I do is I line up, uh, what do they call it in football?
When you have a player that, uh, in case somebody gets knocked out, you bring in the other guy,
what do they call it?
A backup?
Uh, yeah, there you go.
Reserve player.
Reserve.
Okay.
Sure.
I would have a reserve account holder somewhere in reserve.
Okay.
So now here we go.
So first thing I would do is send a conditional acceptance to the utility electric company.
Uh, I noticed you guys are electrical company.
You put down how many years they've been operating.
You sending out bills and remittances, people are paying them.
When you send out your bills and all that, do you, is it in accordance with the United
States laws, codes, uniform, commercial code, all of a question mark.
That's all.
Put an envelope, send it in.
And if they don't answer, you send them another one.
Hey, this is a number two.
I need, I need to know.
Have you stopped beating your wife yet?
So now here's the thing.
When they see that they know what's going well, they usually don't.
They're so stupid.
Like I'll talk a little bit about identity theft, so I'll show you how stupid that is.
By the way, if anyone has your social security number and first name, last name and address
and phone number and you didn't give it to them under FTC PA and FICA, that's a identity
theft.
I'm going to go back to the, how would you like to, let me just to the tangent here.
So right now, anybody can go look up their credit report and you're going to see like
Nexus, Lexus, Experion, like three or four credit reporting agencies have your information,
right?
Uh, did you give it to them?
Now, if someone wants to put something up there, they have to send you a letter 30 days before
they publish it or make it accessible in the credit report.
Did you get that?
Did you ever get, right now, if anybody, you go look up your credit report, right?
Uh, and you see it's listed.
All these things are listed.
Now, it's not only the people that are listing it, but whoever, it doesn't matter, a dentist,
a back rent, um, let's say you didn't pay a credit card and they put it on your credit
report.
That's normal, right?
That credit card company has to send you a letter, uh, 30 days before they give it to
the credit card company that they're putting it on your credit report.
Did you get that?
And you have to ask them, say, Hey, listen, I had a fire, you know, I lost it.
Can you show me proof that you sent it to me?
Uh oh.
You know, it's $500 each time.
So if you, you could rack up, so let's say, so let's say you go to Experian and they got
like a credit card company, dentist bill or whatever.
Did any of those people send you a letter 30 days before they put, and they have to
prove it.
Just say you lost it.
Uh, can you prove that you sent me the letter?
I never saw any of this stuff.
Yeah.
Each one is 500 bucks.
So you got three reporting agencies with five things in that's 15 times 500, 6,000 bucks
right away and they don't argue.
And because, because, um, you saw that and you didn't get notice you're into mental anguish.
So now you want $1,500 treble damages on top of the 500 of each one, right?
So very quickly, what's 1,500 right times.
So now we're up to 40,000 and you notice each one and it's very, you cite the FICO law.
Usually they don't fight it.
They do fight it.
They're so stupid.
Like LexisNexis is free.
Oh no, we don't have to do that.
Oops.
You show them the law.
They screwed up.
Usually you get a check from an attorney.
The attorney will call you and they'll say, yeah, we saw your letter.
How, what does it take to settle this matter?
So usually most people could rack up between 20 and $30,000 in fines and you just get on
the horn.
And I assure you 90% if you could show 20 or $30,000 is out, you're going to get five
to 10,000 from attorneys, no court case, nothing right away.
Now, if most people did this, that would be great.
You know, I mean, now anybody can do this because right.
If you go look up anyone, I tell them, look up the credit was a free credit report doesn't
whatever.
I said, I had like six things.
Do you remember getting a letter from all those, uh, you six things on each reporting
agency?
That's three times six.
That's 18.
That's $500 for each one.
But treble damages.
Cause did you get mental anguish when you found that out?
Yeah.
Well, that's treble damages.
Right.
You go to credit karma.
That's 1,500 now.
You go to that credit karma company or whatever, and they'll show you like a three different
reporting agencies.
So all at once, each one, each one, each reporting, each one.
So if one, let's say the dentist, you didn't pay the bill and reports it to three agencies.
That's not $500.
That's 500 plus 500 plus 500, 1,500.
Yeah.
Right.
But, but were you, did that give you mental anguish when you saw that?
Well, yeah.
Okay.
So I'm upset about it.
So that's treble damages.
So I want another 1,500 on top of that.
So now multiply that times like 18.
Whoa.
So now you got three grand.
Yeah.
You got three grand by a right.
Okay.
So you got three grand by six.
I mean, that's a lot of people.
Not a lot.
That's 18,000 to start with.
Yeah.
Okay.
There's a few.
And guess what?
When they do it, cause they're so stupid, they don't communicate.
They'll do it again.
And then next year you go after him again.
So anyway, and then by the way, when they all, everything comes out, if your credit
score and your credit score goes up to like eight 40, plus you got like 10, 20,000.
From the attorneys in your pocket.
Now there's people that are doing this and they're waking up and they don't know what
to do because it's too late.
It's too late.
Just show them a lot.
Now this, okay.
Why did I give this as an example?
The same thing with the water company, electric company, telephone company, do a conditional
letter, conditional acceptance.
I noticed you're a business established.
Make sure, let them know you did research when you signed a letter, conditional acceptance.
When you say you were the electric company, it was established on May 13th, 1938 by so
and so.
And you've got this many customers and you send out Billy.
That's like, Ooh, this guy, why is he giving us all these details?
He's very detail oriented.
Oh, it's not, it's mostly, it's not going to go in the trash.
Right?
Cause if you're that detail oriented on the, and then you say, I noticed while you're billing
us up, do you follow the laws of the United States, the commercial codes and that's, you
know, all the state laws and all that.
If they answer yes and they reject your bill of exchange later, well you answered, yes.
Now, you know, if they say no, you don't have to go any further.
He's going to attorney general say, have a contract with these people.
And uh, I was expecting to spend $10,000 with them, you know, a thousand dollars a year
in 10 years.
Now I'm totally mentally, mentally anguished.
That caused me mental anguish.
Right?
Anyway.
So you trap them and that's how you do it.
Right?
Cause right now they're doing the trapping on you.
How dare they send a letter that we only accept cash.
What's cash, corn, potatoes.
It's so, but remember they're stupid.
They're really dumb.
They don't know.
I've spoken to attorney generals before and talk to them and they don't know anything at
all.
They go, Oh no, just, I know what you're saying.
You just have to be a good citizen.
You can't ask them questions at all.
They're like monkeys swinging from a tree.
Yeah.
Well, that's the problem.
Now you go to the attorney general to go ahead and look for what they call relief on this.
Right?
Uh, what happens if he doesn't know what the hell you're talking about?
You're not going to the attorney general who doesn't know what you're talking about.
You're going to the office of attorney general.
All you have to do is show them that you noticed it.
It's the office.
When you, okay, when you, you'd have the elections coming up for various things.
You're not voting for Trump or whoever the other one is.
You're voting for the office of president.
Right?
When you, right, you see what I mean?
When you go talk to your congressman, you're not talking to that idiot.
You're talking to the office of the Congress.
It's called the office.
Guess what?
The people hold an office also.
It's known as the people and they've abandoned that office.
Wasn't there a TV show called the office?
Yeah.
Yeah, there was Scott.
You notice how they, uh, how they, uh, what are they underscored?
The characters, the office has nothing to do with the character.
It has to do with the office being noticed and what liability does it carry to go against
what that office means.
And if the office doesn't do their job, you do their job for them.
That's in, that's their titles for that.
By the way, if you go, let's say to an office, any government office, and they don't do what
they're supposed to do, you have to wait 180 days.
I know it's a long time.
And then you take it on yourself as what's called a private attorney general.
Are you familiar with this?
Have we ever gone over this before?
No, I don't.
I don't recall this at all, but 180 days, six months, what they would say basically
with you, they only give you 10 days or 21 days, but then you got to give them six months.
That's okay.
Play by the rules because remember, did you have a lot of mental anguish for six months?
How much is six months worth of mental anguish worth?
Well, it racks up.
Remember you got to add that on.
Hey, look, every day I'm losing sleep over this.
Yeah.
Right.
Okay.
Wow.
Yeah.
So I don't know.
These Sonics might be worth it.
This is like, you know, there's no attorney.
You can go to a $1,500 an hour attorney.
They don't know this.
What we just went over in the Sonic.
So.
No.
Not at all.