Sonic Event 207, Rated Y, here
we are and you know, I was just
thinking because my head is kind of ringing
and hurting, I remember some cool advice you
gave me a while ago about headaches and
I want to point this out real fast.
Sometimes when you get a tension headache, it
is good and I just did relieve a
little part of it with my thumb in
between where my eyebrows are.
Or if you take that and sort of
go vertically upward, it does help with certain
kinds of headaches.
Yeah, that's the liver line, you know, I
mean in between the over the nose.
Yeah, but that's not the only way to
go.
But that is one of them that does
help.
Headache is expansive energy running towards the top
of the body, right?
So yeah, so that means the pressure, pressure
would be at the joints would be at
the base of the jaw, anywhere on the
neck, because it's vertebrae, right?
As long as the neck is relaxed, tilt
your head slightly to one side, you know,
you want to close the joint, you bend
the joints.
So yeah, well, when you do that, we'll
get into that some other time.
Well, we are going to get into the
body toward the end of this one today,
but I just figured I'd mentioned that.
We'll preface.
Yeah, we'll preface it because this one's going
to be a little shorter.
So you can get some rest and the
next one will get more into the body,
which is going to be more of the
usual, right, right.
And, you know, the reason why that works
for me, though, also is because I have
expansion in the eyes a lot.
My eyes actually change size.
They swell a bit, which I know sounds
weird to people.
But everybody's don't do that.
But mine's a little more extreme.
So that's why that works.
Marty Feldman style.
Not so bad.
No, it's it's this little deformity where my
eyes are slightly misshapen for the socket.
It's an odd little genetic defect, apparently.
Yeah.
Anyway, putting all that aside, I got a
couple of questions from the Patreon people, and
it is weird.
A couple of questions, a couple of comments
real fast, and they are inspired by some
of the stuff that was said during some
of the sonics.
But this one is not.
And I'll start with this one.
Could the Greek discuss underground beings and civilizations?
Now, that's a wide open question because you're
always talking about the surface dwelling inhabitants.
Obviously, that's the majority of people listening to
this.
We think.
Yeah.
No, I can't.
I have no firsthand anything.
Well, we could not really know.
They would come up if they would come
up to the surface and they look almost
sapient.
I would if I were them, I would
put on like electrical service or, you know,
civil workers with the vests and the hard
hat in the streets.
No one notices you.
Right.
Or look homeless.
That's the closest I can discuss them.
There's a lot of testimonies.
And believe it or not, the more mythological
and the older the story is, the more
accurate for the general situation, you know, because
there's tendencies, you know, like now everything's a
reptilian or a gray or whatever.
You know, when they talk about little gnomes
and stuff like that, you may not want
to go with how they're featured, you know,
but the idea that they're a foot tall.
Yeah.
Go with that.
And their characteristics, you know, because they definitely
change the appearances when they put them out
to the public or, you know, a red
haired giant, six finger giant living in a
cave in Afghanistan.
Yeah.
You know.
But, you know, I have no I you
have to scour everything that's out there with
a high level of discernment and intuition.
Right.
You got to have intuition.
Speaking of discernment, weird thing happened this week.
And I know you don't watch the news,
but you know how you talked often about
how everybody you see out there is actually
a clone.
It's not the real guy anymore or anything.
Oh, Trump is putting out Trump's people that
Biden is a clone.
Yeah.
OK.
So you know about that.
And he supports that idea.
Of course, these people are doing it for
very weird reasons.
But do you think they're right for the
wrong reasons?
Because they got the wrong evidence.
But are they right?
Yeah.
Well, you can't show that.
It's like 9-11.
They say, well, it's an inside job and
they use thermite and they got the wrong
evidence because thermite is so slow.
The towers would still be burning with thermite
20 years later to get 200000 tons turned
into dust.
Thermite, by the way, not change the subject.
That's a very I first hand experience with
it.
If you know people who have been on
the railroad or if you have a heavy
piece of steel, when they have to mend
a piece of the railroad, you know, you
know, most people have not seen a railroad
rail up close, you know, one foot section
of that weighs like twenty five thirty pounds.
Right.
And when they need to weld them, they
put this green it's called green clay or
very fire proof clay around the joint and
they pack it with thermite and set it
on fire.
And in about forty five minutes, it's welded.
Right.
So let's go back to the evidence about
clones.
They're never going to put out how simple
it is to clone.
Right.
They always you need a special lab and
special whatever.
No, what I'm saying is even their proof
for saying that he's a clone is B
.S. Like they've got this thing of he's
taller.
He's so much taller than Joe Biden.
You know, he's like seven feet tall.
They didn't do that.
That's a weird look at the camera.
I didn't get any of that.
I just saw.
I kind of look for what Donald Marshall's
been posting and there's SWOT or something.
If you don't have a Twitter account, someone
has it closed off this thing like bores
in there and you could it acts as
if you have a Twitter account to view
things.
Oh, yeah.
And I saw the posting there and I
was like, great, you know, he's vindicated.
But they're never going to get into any
legally.
An accusation is considered prima facie evidence.
Right.
That's why, you know, if something is put
out and it's not rebutted.
Here's the here's the thing.
If you want to see validity, more validity
in the issue, did anyone on the Biden
camp rebut it or is it just one
sided?
Well, they, you know, they kind of have
laughed at the official Biden camp.
No, his defenders are.
OK, so then we have to take it
as prima facie evidence.
Now, the media laughing at it, whatever is
not whatever is, in other words, there's clearly
an opposition here and the opposition would be
the Biden camp, because I think most of
this was put out by the Trump camp,
maybe not Trump himself.
So he just reposted it on his truth
social thing.
That's what he did.
All right.
Hmm.
Yeah.
So.
So is he's acquiescing to it?
Right.
But we've we've discussed it in cloning.
Just to recap on cloning years ago, there
was a Midwest nightly news, 6 p.m.
local news about a center that grew skin
for people.
And the reporter goes in there and basically
says it's basically cloning their own skin.
And he has these flasks, the kind you
see in eighth grade science.
And his table is vibrate is not vibrating,
but it's rotating.
It's on an eccentric gear.
So it goes back and forth in a
circle at about one inch, you know, off
of center.
And it's just rotating.
Look, you see mixers in labs that rotate
right or mix, you know, by moving the
beaker.
He has all these beakers on there.
And he says we put a special it's
mostly water with a special solution of minerals
and other things like that with some cells.
And within a few days, sometimes a week
or two, we have a skin sample and
he shows the skin sample.
It's like a translucent piece.
He stretches on a thing and he cuts
it.
And it's basically cloning.
This is not something you get at a
regular hospital.
It's more of an elitist.
You know, it's like the kind of people
that, you know, they can be considered on
the level of plastic surgery.
Right.
It's like in the 30s and 40s, they
did the thing where they grew, you know,
where they actually scrape the skin off you
with something that almost looks like one of
those cheese knives that like literally scrapes the
skin off.
They would take that, grow it and put
it on a piece of a burnt skin.
That kind of tech wasn't available to the
general public for a long time, but was
available if you had the cash.
But this was not scraping.
And they typically take it off your buttocks
or your thigh or something.
That's been around.
I remember a while.
Right.
But this is literally cloning from, you know,
undiscernible, you know, very small size cells.
And it's very simple.
And also there was another news thing in
the early 2000s where they found an Egyptian
mummy that was a clone.
Right.
And then most people took it that they're
cloning Egyptian mummies now.
No, no, no, no.
The Egyptian mummy did not have, you know,
born from a woman type genetics.
It was cloned back then and mummified.
And that was and then it was erased.
And so the technology is very, very, very
rudimentary.
And it is something you can do in
your kitchen.
I'm very big on, you know, promoting techniques
and things.
You know, years ago, we were doing Skype
groups, a guy from Australia.
I don't remember his name.
Doesn't matter.
He was an IP guy.
He would find like intellectual property and try
to find investors.
And he would always be excited to tell
us about all the latest IP that was
not, you know, secret.
And I was like, wait a second, tell
me something I could whip up in my
kitchen.
Not not like, so you need a three
million dollar or whatever.
You know, they always tell you these new
scientific things are always coming out.
Oh, MIT lab or this or that, you
know, all this specialized equipment.
What about stuff you can do at home?
They never discuss that.
And by the way, cloning can be done
at home.
Right.
Because the only things they would try to
show you is stuff like like, look, if
you had a server farm, you could become
a millionaire overnight with, you know, and it's
like, yeah, but who has a server farm,
you know?
Well, yeah, it's a matter of, you know,
what can you do?
That's why, you know, practical stuff.
So what else you got?
OK, so let's see.
Gender switching, because we talked about that recently
a few times.
Gender switching is the priest class.
It's always men to women because that's the
ritual.
Europa, the last battle, speaks about the times
after World War One that we never hear
about.
So they were starting this back then.
Everybody thinks it's a brand new thing, but
it's not brand new.
Yeah.
Well, no, yeah, it's no.
The whole thing about conquering the sex is,
you know, the idea of why having sex
is by conquering it simply by just switching
it.
Right.
So you have a group that, let's say,
has the concept on display of conquering, you
know, the natural male female counterpart.
You know, we're going to conquer that by
just simply having a male dress up like
a female and a female dress up like
a male.
Typically, it goes male to female.
Typically.
Right.
That was the easy way to start with.
But now we've gotten into the surgeries and
the whole bit, you know, with surgeries have
always been around also to a degree.
OK, that's a good degree.
That's the underground.
There was castration and there was full castration
where the penis is cut off to write
a lot of a lot of I think
the Knights Templar had a ritual for that
and whatever.
There was castration and full castration, which is,
you know, the organ itself.
Right.
I didn't ask you about the bunions last
time, did I?
No, no, as in somebody.
Yeah, well, somebody asked to avoid the involvement
of any medical technician.
Does Greek have any experience to share with
correcting bunions?
No, no.
And that's a very broad subject.
OK, very broad.
And it would be no, I'll look into
let's just say this.
I'm not going to make a note of
it, you know, write it down, but I'll
make a note of looking at it and
bring it up again.
I got you, because in the medical technician
field, you know, it's it's all about nowadays.
They they break your foot and they correct
it and then they say, OK, now that's
how we get rid of the bunion.
You know, they actually cut the extra piece
off and they break it.
They break the bone and reset it, which
seems actually sensible in a way.
But it also means that it's going to
come back.
Most likely.
Yeah.
Or you can have a bracing system.
It'll be very, very uncomfortable.
Yeah.
And that takes a lot of races and
all that.
You know.
So, yeah.
Yeah.
The same thing happens with people with the
hump on the back to, you know, like
where they get the the back and they
start bending over more and more to a
question mark as they get older, especially taller
people.
Yeah.
It's always self-esteem and sort of like
anger manifest like it's held in internally.
By the way, if you want to counterbalance
anger issues, fermented foods.
Hmm.
Give you an example, like if someone's holding
a grudge, right.
What happens when they drink alcohol and get
drunk?
The wine.
Yeah.
They they want any kind of fermented food.
We'll do that.
Yeah.
So anyway.
OK, what else?
Nice.
OK.
Last thing.
And let's talk about depression.
As I know, it isn't what we think
it's.
It is, you know, mentioned in previous sonics
as unmet expectations.
So how do we just get over the
reality of and the reality of depression and
be happy?
This is what I've been saying about depressions
for 40 years now, is when people try
to mix cognitive mix, a cognitive mix of
fact and fiction.
And we're going to give you an example.
When you get too much of this stuff,
like if the bank lends you money, where
did the bank get it from?
Don't ask that.
Right.
Because, you know, but if no one wants
to talk about it, it means it doesn't
exist where Santa Claus and, you know, the
children, you know, Santa Claus, this and Santa
Claus, that.
And then they're told to ask for Santa
Claus when they reach a certain age.
Don't ask for that anymore.
What's wrong with you?
Right.
You're an adult now.
So when you're mixing cognitively, forward thinking, mixing,
asking questions about things that are fictional or,
you know, you won't get an answer for
because, you know, it's the liability is the
biggest source of depression when you try to
mix the two.
Yeah.
Fair enough.
So meanwhile, you also said you were going
to do a sort of a a preliminary
on the on the body to get us
started before we actually get into it during
a sonic.
So, yeah, where would you begin with that?
I mean, I guess you begin with the
most relatable thing, like you say.
But yeah, anatomy, you got to look at
anatomy.
Like, for example, if you I don't have
it from sitting outside in a pergola having
a smoke and some coffee.
Sure.
I was I was going to do this
one dry with no smokes and no coffee.
I said, no, let's get it.
So look, it's what's called like a sweat
duct.
It's in the form of a coil.
Looks like a little spring, OK, because you
need that surface area and that shape to
create that counter space for water to be
created in the duct.
Right.
They also they do show sweat ducts and
they avoid showing that coil.
And so, you know, if you show too
much right and you see people start seeing
patterns and they're going to see that pattern
actually belongs to a certain function, then they're
going to try to associate the functions.
And we were not supposed to do that.
Right.
Meaning induction.
If you look at anything that generates liquid
has to be done with this coil.
And right.
I mean, mostly not always.
But but in this case, it's so efficient
to do it that way, because how long
does it take for someone to start leaking
pretty quickly?
Sometimes, you know, I mean, sweating.
Right.
You know what they call you're leaking, right?
Well, you leak with the sweating, but you
also leak with what they call the milk
ducts, you know, with women.
And sometimes men do that, too.
They call it a witch's milk or whatever.
Milk ducts.
Yes.
You'll find those are more glandular looking like
cauliflower bunched up again, large surface area.
And those require a different form of energy.
Right.
So the the sweat duct is is a
very from universal principles.
It's narrow.
It's very young, very focused and very, very
neat little spiral.
You find that in small induction.
Look, look, look up mini inductors for electrical
circuits.
Is this identical?
Right.
It's a very inefficient system if you're going
to pull liquid from the blood or the
skin.
And also you see the dermal layers around
the sweat duct.
There's no way moisture, water will be going
through that because the interstitial spaces are so
tight.
Right.
It's it's pretty much like a low durometer
rating rubber.
There's nothing that's going to go through that.
So you can see how that's produced.
The other thing is to look at how
the organs are packed together.
There is a sequence there.
You know, it's very when you look at
I remember in grade school, we had the
the disassembly person remember was a torso and
the organs came off and they snapped back
on.
Do you remember that?
I didn't see him in school later, but
yeah, yeah.
Yeah, it was a physical or you said,
oh, you see everything neatly snaps together.
Now, one thing that I when I saw
that at a young age, I said, oh,
look, it's a whole bunch of aliens that
are in contract to work together.
I mean, because the liver couldn't be more
alien than your, you know, kidney and more
alien than your pancreas or more alien than
anything else.
There are many different cells.
Any of those things are completely different.
Yeah.
Each organ comes from another planet, you know.
So, you know, so to speak.
So they're all in concert working together like
off the shelf parts, right, that were made
to work together.
And the way that they're all nestled together,
it has its own little Fibonacci arrangement, golden
mean.
And that's because you need that or it's
almost a requirement to have that golden mean
proportion to take advantage of the energy, right?
That's how energy flows.
Anyone who does ham radio understands the length
of the antenna is critical to your tuning
and all that.
So, yeah, I think any woman who's ever
had a C-section is fully aware of
how weird it is when they put things
back in.
They kind of don't do it exactly the
right way.
You get problems later because they literally take
your organs out to get toward, you know,
where the sack is, where the kid is
or the child is.
And it's this whole thing.
And then they just sort of put the
organs back in.
I don't think they always put them back
in exactly right.
Yeah.
And what is it like?
90% of them are are unnecessary now.
Yeah, just do it because the hospital bill
and the, you know, keep the doctors working,
you know, right.
And it's quick, quick recovery, allegedly, you know.
Oh, my gosh.
Yeah.
So it's it's a horrible.
But, you know, here here's the thing.
You don't have to say the medical industry
is horrible state right now.
And this is how it's going to get
worse.
You don't have that much time for it
to get much worse, which is a good
thing, right?
So, yeah, when you look at the human
body and the way it's assembled and the
structure, by the way, one thing I mentioned,
I did plug into chat GPT a while
back is water.
Water is not H2O and chat GPT agreed
only for certain chemical.
Right.
Whatever.
Anyway.
But if you put in the human body
or any biological organism has a biological vacuum,
it emphatically says, no, there is no biological
vacuum.
There are pressures in the right.
So then how does if you ask the
how does all of the fluid, you know,
stay in equals, you know, stays in pretty
much equilibrium through the body, right through the
pressure of the organs?
You know, it gives you a really ridiculous
answer.
It seems like they really picked up on
that and fed the A.I. something to
emphatically disagree with.
I couldn't get around it.
You know, so they really don't want you
sort of like if you ask the question,
all debts belong to show me, you know,
don't show me the laws.
All debts belong to United States says no.
Actually, there's about a dozen laws that say
they do.
So there are certain things that are put
in there to whitewash or block, because typically
all it does is it tries to rephrase
its rephrase what you're saying.
It doesn't really give info.
I mean, unless it's you're looking for reference
material.
But there's a major denial or non acknowledgement
of the biological vacuum.
And once you start, we're aware of it.
And the basic principles of everything being sucked
inward by, let's say, a force, whether it's
moving or not in motion or not is
not relevant is that that that vacuum, that
negative pressure inside all living things, even seeds
exists to a degree that it shouldn't be
ignored.
And it needs to be acknowledged.
And understanding how to work with the biological
vacuum, of course, will lead to, you know,
I guess most things miraculously healing or, you
know, advantageous to like very, very rapid healing.
Yeah.
And they they have some, you know, they
the the legal system, the medical system, the
monetary system are interlinked, right?
Very much interlinked.
So certain things are verboten, right?
Forbidden to discuss in general queries is with
the eye or on the Internet.
You know, they're hidden.
They what do they call it?
The algorithm.
Yeah.
Right.
And you can find that when you go
and you try and do the Google and
it gives you the answer to anything that
you ask.
Like if you ask a general question to
Google, you're getting an A.I. driven.
Yeah, they want to get away with.
So, you know, years, let's say 10 years
ago, you did a question and it did
it statistically when, you know, your question showed
up in websites and all that number crunching.
Yeah.
They eventually it'll be you're just dealing with
an A.I. like Star Trek.
There is no other websites.
You don't get websites or whatever, only the
featured websites.
And it'll get to the point where because
A.I. is intellectual property or whatever.
If you want A.I. to access your
website, you have to pay a fee.
Kind of like teams and Skype, right?
It's already like that kind of because if
you place the you really do have to.
And by the way, Google will happily send
you a thing about it.
If you own any sort of entity on
the Internet that, you know, is registered.
Yeah.
They'll send you a thing saying, you know,
your website is not working right because blah,
blah, blah, blah.
And at the end of the day, they
want you to buy stuff is what it
is.
Yeah.
But but here's the thing.
People don't read anyway.
The level of consensus today, I was having
a discussion with a medical person and they're
saying, what about this vitamin in this vegetable?
So let's take a let's take an orange.
You know how they say there's vitamin C
in an orange, really?
OK, what's going on is most people will
agree to that and they think it's just
good science.
But what's not being given is when you
get a scientific answer for something, they always
omit the process.
They exclude what it took to get that
answer.
And once any reasonable, semi-intelligent person is
told how they came to the point where
this exists in a fruit or vegetable or
whatever, you're like, how can it be the
same?
Because the way they see vitamin C in
an orange to just get the vitamin C
is they crush the orange center, fuse it,
separate everything, dehydrate it and burn it or
combine it with other chemicals.
Then you give the example, you know, at
a hamburger shop.
You know, no one when they no one
knows what the hell you're talking about when
they said, do you want cucumber with your
hamburger?
No.
What?
Never.
No.
But they ask you, do you want pickle?
And most people will say yes or no.
They know because cucumbers don't are not pickles.
Right.
What they are, but they're not.
No, they are.
But after a certain process, they become something
else.
It's changed into something else completely different.
So when you're given an answer about this
or that, like, for example, the fluoride argument
is to get fluoride.
Elemental fluoride is almost impossible.
I don't think it might be a specimen
in some reference museum, but fluoride would most
likely be found as calcium fluoride or sodium
fluoride.
Right.
So calcium fluoride would be like carbon dioxide,
you know, in your soft drink and your
pop soda.
And sodium fluoride would be like carbon monoxide.
Right.
So no one says you want carbon in
your drink, you know, carbonated drink.
You see carbonated.
But is it carbon carbonated drinks?
Are they carbon dioxide or carbon monoxide?
Right.
So it's the same thing with the fluoride
argument is we say fluoride.
First of all, I don't think elemental fluoride
is available anywhere.
Only only the calcium fluoride would be in
small amounts.
But the prevailing quantity is sodium fluoride, which
is the carbon monoxide version of fluoride.
See.
So, yeah, so the science behind it, simply
saying fluoride, for example, omits the practicality of
it.
Right.
Where I would I would be OK with
a supplement or toothpaste with calcium fluoride, but
not sodium fluoride.
Just like I enjoy a cola or a
lemon soda with carbon dioxide, not carbon monoxide.
Right.
Like hydrogen.
Hydrogen is an absolutely necessary element to a
whole lot of things.
Right.
But, you know, do you want to drink
hydrogen peroxide?
No, you don't.
Right.
That would be H2O2 or something.
Yeah.
So that's another.
But then it's not hydrogen.
It's.
Yeah, it's it's it's not about the hydrogen.
It's about the compound.
Right.
So this thing, you know, about some people
when I have a discussion, I say, oh,
so you're holistic.
Well, is that what's the opposite of holistic?
Fractional.
Right.
So we could talk about the value.
They're both quantitative.
One is the whole quantity of the one's
partial quantity.
But qualitatively, looking at all of the quantity
is qualitatively better than looking at only some
of it.
Right.
So what I call, you know, the opposite
of, you know, a lot of the alternatives
call holistic medicine.
That was a big thing in the 80s
and 90s.
There's not much talk about that.
Maybe there is.
I don't know.
I don't watch, though, because it's just frustrating.
Any any medical stuff that they put out
early, early, early 2000s, it was still prominent.
Yeah.
And it's sort of faded.
But yeah.
So the accepted medicine is all fractional.
It's not holistic.
I mean, it's not it's only looking at
parts just like, right.
You know, oh, this has got, you know,
oranges of vitamin C.
So let's just give vitamin C in a
packet or supplement.
It's you can't say it comes from oranges.
You can say it's derived from oranges, just
like a pickle on your hamburgers derived from
a cucumber.
Even in the world of medical technicians, what
do they do?
They fractionally handle things.
They say, OK, you had a problem with
your heart.
Now you need to go to the heart
doctor who is a doctor who just focuses
on that, which means that he doesn't pay
attention to anything else that's going on.
He's just focused on your heart.
And that's kind of yeah.
Legally, legally, none of them hold water.
In order to be legal, they have to
have a sworn affidavit.
And no doctor will ever do that.
But they get you to consent and agree
to it.
So they always put it on you.
But the whole thing is I brought this
up because it's very important.
Yeah.
To the legal stuff and law stuff.
It's all about swearing or affirming.
You know, in the biblical, it says don't
swear.
Right.
But you can affirm under the penalty of
perjury, let's say, you know, even as a
child, yours, I swear I didn't do it.
Right.
A little child.
So from just like I brought up the
metaphor, the last sonic with the voices minimize,
you know, the computer is mimicking what we
can do for the mind, which is when
you have the voices or the let's call
them intrusions, you minimize and then hit the
X, you know, on the whatever to close
it.
So you don't try to close it when
it's in full view, minimize it and then
close it.
And that's how you stop the intrusions, whether
it's temporary or long term.
I wouldn't expect more than temporary because we're
swimming in it.
The same thing happens with with anything else
that you do.
Minimize it and close it.
There's there's a metaphor that can be used.
The basic metaphor is that to carry over
on many, many topics.
And yeah.
But anyway, maybe I got off track on
that.
But the idea of swearing has been instilled
in us as children and in the legal
field due process.
For example, if you're given a ticket going
150 miles an hour over the speeding limit
in order for it to people are arguing
like I don't need a driver's license or
any of this stuff.
There's no due process in order to be
charged in law or even legally.
The opposing party has to have a sworn
document.
In other words, they're putting their nuts on
the table under the penalty of perjury.
Otherwise, there's no due process.
There's no case.
And no one really pays attention to that.
All they do is is cite, well, I'm
allowed to go 150 miles an hour.
I have a right to travel or this
and that.
No, they just it's due.
Or they say the court doesn't have jurisdiction.
Forget about all that.
Do you want to bring something into a
peanut court or a kangaroo court?
Whatever the rules are, you still have to
have a sworn affidavit from the opposition.
Right.
Or rebut with mine.
And no one there's a minimum majority.
And that is the the the real success
of the matter.
And if they don't address it, there's no
case.
Right.
So and this is this is very much
the idea of swearing or putting your nuts
on the table, as they say, and all
that is the basis for all this stuff.
And how do you do that with evidence?
Right.
And and it's and if you don't have
the evidence, your word is enough.
That's why we said earlier with the Biden
thing, when that was put out that he's
a clone, what did the the Biden being
the opposition now or however you want to
see it, what was their response?
If there's no response, we have to take
the statement as being truer than no than
no response.
So the more true what makes something true
is how it's affirmed and put forward.
That's why so many people are so misled.
Right.
Like with the Kennedy assassination, with 9-11,
with all that stuff.
Because, you know, when 9-11 happened, they
just put up a picture within 30 seconds
of Osama bin Laden.
They suspect him.
But if you ask people on the street,
they swore it was Osama bin Laden.
You see.
So they were trying to see what you
swear to.
It's kind of like I lie and you
swear to it.
That's what makes it true.
Right.
That's what magicians do.
They they lie by, you know, cutting a
woman in half and putting her back together.
But because you don't know how that happened,
you swear that you saw a woman cut
in half and put back together on stage.
And that makes it true.
So this is the world that you live
in.
It's actually what I'm saying.
This is to simplify everything.
Just like you can affirm or swear that
a cucumber in your hamburger is not very
good, but a pickle is.
Right.
And you can say that they're not the
same.
You can affirm and swear that a cucumber
in your hamburger is not, you know, a
firm or swear that it's not the same
as a pickle.
And guess what?
It's not.
And not everybody.
Not everybody likes a tomato, but most people
will put ketchup.
And that's not the same either at all.
The same.
But it is.
I once had a McDonald's burger in recent
memory, like a year.
Then they didn't put ketchup on it because
and it was unedible.
So it's very important.
It kind of reminds me of an old
cartoon in a newspaper where the bears are
over an animal that has been in for
a long time.
And like, I think this one's going to
need ketchup.
You know, ketchup makes really poor meat quality
things more edible.
It's it's necessary.
But everything is about your condiments.
And we'll get into that when we get
more into the biology.
That's why they put most of the same
reason.