This is Jason Horsley with part two of my conversation with the Greek, or the Liminalist, the podcast
between.
I mean, would that, is that a good thing?
I mean, this is...
Yes.
Back to this point, I keep trying to reiterate, but I'm not sure if you're hearing it, but
the, um, like, like you were saying that in order to define things and, and, and get to
grips with concepts, that's necessary to actually embody them.
And my, my experience is the reverse, is that the definitions and the concepts have actually
come between myself and an embodiment, a relationship with my embodiment, with my body and my reality.
And I would say that goes a thousand times more for the gods, like they don't want, uh,
to interact with me, presumptuous to say what they want, but anyway, through a filter of
my ideas about what they are.
And, and, and so I don't, I don't see how you can represent the gods through language
without...
That's fine.
...missing so much out that you're inevitably going to be misrepresenting them.
And I think that you know that, that's my sense, is that you're actually kind of consciously
misrepresenting truth, knowing that you can't avoid doing that.
So trying to do it consciously, that, that's my impression thus far.
Well, the representation, the, what you're discussing is the stuff that romanticism and
art and, uh, uh, human, uh, culture is based on.
That's not what I'm going after.
What I'm going after is, are we looking at what's been memorialized about the gods?
And when we do look at it, we'll see that it is, it is extreme, it is very detailed
in many cases, even though the narrative is, is a void of many of the things that we consider
to be important.
You know, you won't find, uh, airplanes, rockets, and iPhones in there.
But, uh, no, what I'm saying is that there is no examination of what has been written
in the past or memorialized about them, as if everyone has recreated this environment
that they're living in.
Like everything sprang into existence a hundred years ago.
No one is going back and examining, they're just trusting what is being said about the
biblical text, about the Mahabharata, about the, uh, Prakrit and Sanskrit.
So there's no accurate evaluation of it.
There's no accurate evaluation of science.
All of the scientists in the 19th century called magnetics the dielectric field.
Wow!
If you start teaching that to young people who have a scientific mind, they're going
to make progress in magnetics that you would know, you wouldn't know what to do.
It would push society 500 years into the future in less than a decade.
So, but it seems you don't really want people to think about this stuff, because you jump
horses so rapidly, you know, even in a single sentence, that it's impossible to really
keep up with all the correlations between what you're describing.
That's fine.
You're recording it.
Much less unpack one particular one.
Yeah, right.
But, so, um, oh shit, see, now I lost track.
So let's go back to the gods.
Representing the gods, there is no representation of what's been memorialized about them, at
all.
Sorry to say that.
There's no representation of what's been memorialized in the culture.
About the gods.
In the culture.
Yes, because the culture...
But you're doing that.
I mean, you're aspiring to do that.
Well, you're...
Am I doing it?
Apparently.
Because you're saying, this is what's going on with the gods, you know, in their lateral
sphere and all the rest of it, and this is referring to scripture.
But you don't, you don't actually cite the scripture.
Like, for me...
Why should I?
For me, it would be much more helpful if you were to say, this is what I know about the
gods, and this is why, and this is the passage in the scripture that I have extrapolated
this from.
Oh, but it doesn't work that way, because it's an entire picture.
Just like, for example, it's a jigsaw puzzle.
I understand, yeah.
Various passages.
But at least give us something substantial to work with.
Okay, I understand.
I understand that.
I have done that in the past, but not as much, maybe, recently.
Let me give you an example.
For example, this is called the Christian era, and it's been dubbed so by atheist historians,
so you can't say that it's a religious term, strictly.
This is the Christian era, the past 2,000 years.
Whenever you run into these critters, that species, let's say, they start doing what
I call the McDonald's commercial, two old beef patties, special sauce, semi-semi-bun
on a...
Well, you know what I'm talking about?
Ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba, like some kind of jingle.
They start saying, well, Matthew, Mark, ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba, 24, 15, verse 19, 17, follow and say, you
got to do...
You're a sinner.
Yeah.
I'm like, whoa, I didn't get any of that.
You know what?
As soon as I hear that, I am so turned off, and I don't mean in a sexual sense, but yeah,
that too.
If I...
If that would just be death to me, you know, I mean, death to me, cognitively.
Okay, but that's, again, that's pretty low bar, and it's the other end of the spectrum.
It's all low, but it's all low bar.
I was recently in an interview, and someone said, it's low-hanging fruit.
I said, no, there is no low-hanging fruit.
It's all fallen to the ground and rotten at this point.
Here's an example of looking at, and I say so many things, it doesn't matter if you're
looking at what's been memorialized in the past about any subject, because most people
say, oh, that's old.
They were primitive.
They're...
See, we're much smarter now.
We're modern.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, really?
Yeah, I know.
I know, but, I mean, we share that dissatisfaction, frustration, and even contempt for our society,
so why address that, you know, if we're already on the same page about that?
Well, because the mindset...
The mindset is very different.
I dare anyone to go look at an eighth grade final exam from 1890s.
A college professor can't get maybe two or three out of the 50 questions.
I dare anyone to go look back.
There are pretty good archives.
Read the newspaper from 150 years ago.
Look at the level of communication that's being illustrated.
Okay, but that's gone.
I mean, it's past, right?
Yes.
This is where we are now.
This is the reality of it.
Yes, but it's the same thing.
Look, you were saying earlier, it's a continuation of the ancestral, right?
So you're addressing the ancestors as well.
No, not really.
That leaves a bad taste in my mouth, because there's something called ancestral worship.
And they're dead and they're done and they're irrelevant at this point.
What's relative is how much of it that you're holding on.
There's something about, you know, they can't handle meat.
They can only handle milk.
That means like they're still on the mother's teat, you know?
In other words, what they're speaking and spouting is what their parents told them.
You see, versus, right, they're not, yeah, okay.
Okay, so looking back is very important, not because of the way, the style, and even
the quality, but also the quantity that you can bring forward.
Because when something is irrelevant or wrong, how much of the quantity do you have that
is relative or right?
It doesn't matter.
If you ordered a truck full of beans and they brought you a truck full of strawberries,
it's still a truck full, but how many beans do you have?
Zero.
That's not what you need.
So you're talking about getting to the root, like addressing the root of the delusion.
It's a delusion, but it's also put on by the gods, because have you heard of the Tower
of Babel?
You know, they were doing something, and they were confused, and their languages changed.
What, they couldn't do hand language and sign language to communicate?
We do it here all the time.
They couldn't develop a method of universal translation, although it put the project back
a week, a month, or a year, and then resume it?
Why not?
Well, they did, I guess.
No, they didn't, because it confused their ability to rationalize why they were doing
what they were doing.
Yeah, but we're still building a Tower of Babel, is what I mean.
No, we're not.
And it wasn't even really called the Tower of Babel, it was a tower in Babel.
It's just like there is no burning bush.
You know, if you read the text, there was an angel that had fire, and he stood behind
a bush.
It didn't burn the bush.
No, it wasn't even a symbol.
It never happened.
No, the Babel.
But the Tower of Babel is a symbolic language, I mean.
Yes, symbolic language, but then again, when you say apocalypse, it just means to reveal.
When they say Armageddon, that just means Har Megiddo, the mountain of Megiddo.
When you say the word nice, that means foolish, stupid, senseless, the way it's being used.
In some cases, the misappropriation of something might be appropriate.
Like I said before, a poor mechanic blames his tools, but a good mechanic can do a lot
of work with kitchen utensils, right?
I've seen that.
Use a butter knife as a flathead screwdriver, we'll get the job done, as long as it's not
too critical.
So I'm not saying the misappropriation of the language is essentially the cause of it,
it's all of it.
That's why I keep saying, why bother food, clothing, and shelter?
You're not going to be concerned about, you're not going to err philosophical even in the
slightest if you have no food, clothing, and shelter.
Because you're not going to have the luxury, you mean?
Well the body, the corpus, the carne, is going to overcome the spirit and the soul to the
point where its needs will be primary to the other things, you know.
And that would be awful, you mean?
Yeah, you're not going to be thinking, the example is a man that's dying of thirst, walking
down a road, he passes a guy standing on a pallet of gold bullion and money, let's say.
He'll keep walking.
And the moment he sees the guy with water, he kills the guy to get the water.
I was going to say, yeah.
It might not be lawful.
And then he goes back and gets the money, right?
So being, yeah.
So it's not really lawful, necessarily, if you're reduced to a primal state.
Yeah, but even in a sense, some primal state might say, I'd rather die than kill the man
who's refusing to give me the water.
That's primal also, so, you know.
Yeah, that would be a pretty high.
I would rather die than kill the man to, you know, it's not a personal thing, but I'm just
saying it as another perspective, right?
As a possibility, yeah.
Yeah, than kill the man for water, yeah, that would, that means that, you know, because
you know, ultimately, have you, in the book of, I'll cite something, in the book of Daniel,
there are three characters that are to be thrown into the furnace because they didn't
bow down to an idol, Shadrach, Midrach, and Abed-Dinogh.
And they said that our God can prevent us and protect us from your fire, but if he chooses
not to, that's fine with us too.
Mm-hmm, yeah.
You see, to me, that's like the ultimate trust in them, you see.
Yeah, but that's a very high aspiration, right?
We don't know until we're starving to death, really, like how surrendered we are to that.
You transcended the psychophysical, then, completely, and that's all misunderstood,
a lot of the Eastern philosophy about transcension, ascension, that's all, that's actually, when
you read the ancient prakrit and all that, it basically tells you that you are outside
of yourself, and don't, I'm not going to tell you where it is exactly, but this is
the concept, and you're not going to find it because most of these gurus and people
that, as sages that talk about it, don't care, they don't know either, right, just like Christian
gurus don't know that the Christ was not crucified, was stoned to death, because they don't read
the text.
But basically, in the ancient prakrit, it says you are outside of yourself, and when
you transcend what you feel, in other words, your feeling and your opinion, and you keep
that as your model, you will see clear enough to understand that when you lose the ability
to see everything, it's still okay, because you're always outside of yourself, you see.
Anyway.
You know, have you ever heard me give the metaphor of the Buddha, what it's about?
It's about living a life of integrity, when he was approached by a woman, because he was
known as a man of wisdom, the woman wanted the Buddha to speak to her child who was eating
too many sweets, and the Buddha said, well, come back in a month, and I'll speak to him
then, and she leaves, and she comes back in a month, and he does speak to the child a
month later, and then she returns to the Buddha and says, why did you tell me to come back
in a month, and you didn't speak to him then?
He says, because when you first came to me, I was traveling and eating too many sweets
myself.
You see, in other words, talk your walk and walk your talk.
How genuine would he be, even to a child, if he was eating too many sweets himself,
and told the child eating sweets, too many sweets is not good.
That's kind of disingenuous.
Why?
Because the child, you see, would the child know that?
No, but you see, there's an air of integrity that goes beyond, that measures what we are
actually doing, is the measurement and the reference of what we are doing.
So I got the impression that you smoke cigarettes, is that right?
Oh yeah, I do enjoy tobacco.
I suck on cigarettes, I don't smoke, but smoking hurts, because where there's smoke, there's
fire.
What do you mean?
You don't like them?
No, no one is really smoking, let's say, because if you're smoking, it means that you're burning.
Yeah.
So I'm sucking on the cigarette.
The cigarette is smoking, I'm sucking.
And then you're flicking a lighter, because I hear a lighter flick from time to time.
Years ago, when I would go on an airplane, people would say, smoking or non-smoking?
I'd say, well, the one that flies better, of course.
All right.
Yeah, I enjoy coffee, I enjoy good teas, I enjoy tobacco.
But how do you enjoy tobacco, if you're just holding a cigarette?
Oh, a cigarette, yeah, I enjoy the organic variety.
Wait, but you're smoking it, or you're not smoking it?
Yeah, well, I'm just baking, I'm being facetious about it, yes, what you call smoking is.
What I call smoking?
Well, what is called smoking, but because you're not really, well, in order to be smoking means
you're burning, right?
You yourself, oh, I see, you're being facetious.
You're being facetious, yes, that's all right.
Well, I just brought it up, because...
It's like the airplanes, you know, the airplanes, you know, smoking or non-smoking back in
the 70s, they would ask you that.
And the answer to that, you know, most people think is, you know, which one do you smoke,
cigarette?
And I would say just the one that flies better, of course, because if a plane is smoking,
you know, it's usually a hint that it's mechanically in trouble.
But, so how does that square with your philosophy about health and maintenance of the body and
all that stuff?
Well, that's an interesting psychophysical question that might air philosophical.
Where does one complicate, negotiate, or compromise their known physical ability for their likes
and wants?
Oh, I know it's hurting my health, but I like it enough that I'm willing to put up with
it if it does.
I'll give you a personal example.
If I find that it causes irritation and compromises my health, I stop.
But if I stop completely, would I be much healthier?
Yes and no.
I've spoke to some medical researchers, the kind of research you'll never get, not even
on the stupid rectangle.
You know what I mean about the stupid rectangle, yeah?
Yeah.
They did an experiment.
They strapped some tobacco.
They subjected various mammals to smoke, and some of them, about 12% came down to what
they call irritation in the lungs and what they call cancerous tissue.
And then they had the ones that didn't ever have that and were sequestered, and they had
less than 0.5%.
So you have 25 times more chance when you smoke.
But the ones that did not smoke the tobacco and they just had it strapped onto them as
a harness had an 8% irritation of cancer also.
So if you just walked around with a pack of cigarettes on you all day for 10 years, you
have an 8% chance of getting cancer.
That's weird.
Well, because it's by induction.
How is it by induction?
Because the body doesn't absorb anything, according to you.
Right.
So it's induction.
No, according to your body, and I'm just the only one speaking on it, sorry.
You say that.
It's pathetic to say that.
Define induction, then.
Have you ever seen an electrician come into a house years ago?
If they wanted to probe the wires, they had to open the outlet and stick a probe directly
on the wire.
Now they just have this pocket handheld thing, and they hold a button and they go into proximity
and then it starts beeping.
Oh, they have an electrical wire here.
Yeah.
Have you ever seen the...
Now I know the cars and the cell phones, you don't have to plug them in, you just put them
on a pad and it charges the phone.
Or the toothbrushes, the Sonicare toothbrush, you put it in a charging dock and there's
no obvious terminal contact.
Two coils work that way, transformers that take high voltage and reduce it to low voltage
work through induction.
If you understand the term, if you heard of a man called Rudolf Hoschka, the term vitamins,
vitamins that people are touting, he was the father of that research that we know about
and he came about it by stating that certain foods prevent certain illnesses like scurvy
and things, you know, like people on ships, we know if they didn't have citric, right?
So he said that certain foods have a certain vitality.
Maybe I can just extract the vitality of that food by making extracts.
And he would apply them to certain creatures that had deficiencies and he noticed that
the extract, not only the food, was where the vitality was.
And then he noticed that if he didn't even apply it to the creature but just kept it
near, very close by, it almost had the same effect.
Right.
Through glass.
You see.
Right.
So that indicates that the body is antipathetic to tobacco or vice versa.
Not only tobacco but to anything.
The body, okay, have you ever heard of a blood alcohol level?
Mm-hmm.
That's ridiculous.
That would be what people think about it.
When you drink alcohol, your body recognizes that it's something that it could reproduce
internally and it reproduces it internally and it shows up in the blood.
If it were to go through the intestine or the stomach, you would die from sepsis,
which is sepsisemia, which is a medical condition, internal poisoning, internal bleeding.
Mm-hmm.
Right?
Okay, and also you would lose your vacuum if it was porous.
Just like if you have a porous bicycle tire or car tire, it ceases to function, does it?
Right?
A flat tire is not functioning.
Yeah.
So the process of the body creating the alcohol is what gets you drunk.
For example, have you ever heard of someone drinking another person under the table?
They can handle their alcohol much better than another person.
Mm-hmm.
Well, they're biologically the same, pretty much, except for various obvious physical
features and blood types, maybe.
But one person is not as susceptible to the effect of the body producing alcohol than
the other.
The other person, when his body produces alcohol internally, is highly susceptible to that
reaction, which makes them drunk at a lower alcohol level.
Right.
Native Americans, supposedly.
Sure.
Just like, for example, if you know this is all electrical function, you can stand in
front of a monitor with one of your feet exposed on a particular plate of metal holding onto
another piece of metal, and you could actually pulse that monitor with a certain frequency
and a little bit of sound, and someone who's never smoked marijuana or cannabis in their
lives will show THC in their blood, and they will feel high.
Mm-hmm.
And also you will see blood alcohol, a very small amount, of course.
You can induce this into the body.
Just like you can induce a live band onto magnetic tape.
Can you not?
Right?
Right.
Microphone takes an apparatus.
If I give you the Beatles' White Album, what does that mean?
To a material scientist, he'll look at it and say, I don't understand what you're
talking about.
I see a disc of plastic with grooves of this material composition.
I don't understand what you're talking about, if he's just a material scientist.
Yes.
But you could just take it to any teenagers, put it in the computer if it's a DVD, and
he'll say, yes, this is the Beatles' White Album or something.
You see?
Mm-hmm.
Because he's not interested in the material.
He's interested in what the material is carrying on an intangible level.
If I took the label off of DVDs or on a format and I showed you all these, can you tell me
what songs are on there?
No.
Without playing them, you can't.
I've seen enough clinical research studies that they actually deny things that they cannot
reproduce or produce in a clinical study in a laboratory.
They actually will deny the sky is blue because they cannot reproduce it in the laboratory.
I know this sounds ridiculous to you and I, and if you start studying what's called legal
or the justice system, they have some legal concepts that are quite ridiculous as well.
If you might be familiar with some, maybe not.
It's just like when you go to a physicist to find a field, tells you it's a wave.
What's light?
It's a wave.
A wave is not what something is.
A wave is what something does.
If I'm waving at you, what am I doing?
I'm waving.
Am I a wave?
Mm-hmm.
They cannot explain anything because it's against your mental model.
You will not be able to grasp it.
For example, the reason you will not have real education is because no one will go and
will never be recognized as real education.
It will be recognized as something so far and irrelevant to the current mental model, you
see.
Mm-hmm.
That's why you can't, that's why I keep saying everything now has gotten to the point of
irreparability, unrehabilitatable.
People talk about fixing this, fixing that.
It's gone a little late to fix it now.
It has to be replaced.
Mm-hmm.
I'm not saying this.
This is a fair objective evaluation.
I'm not promoting its replacement because no man can do it.
Mm-hmm.
But you have talked in such a way that you want to introduce information to people that
they can apply it and improve conditions.
For the sake of efficiency.
If you're inefficient, let me just give you a hypothetical example.
I'll stay very general.
If you're inefficient with something, does that even sound good?
No, it doesn't even sound good.
Inefficient communication, you've seen, we have ditzy blondes back east in New York.
Oh, she's a real ditzy blonde.
She talks and talks.
She doesn't say anything.
Mm-hmm.
You know, right?
It could be any haircut.
And that wasn't that funny.
That's inefficient communication.
She's saying a lot, isn't she?
Yeah.
Points like, Ross, can you be inefficient with an automobile?
Yes.
Can you be inefficient with the way you prepare things?
Yeah.
It's for the sake of efficiency.
Right.
So it seems that was something Sam was trying to address with you in terms of him feeling
that you weren't being as efficient as you could be with your streaming, for example.
No, not at all, because this is not, albeit how much I disdain the concept of a group
in this society, like as illustrated by Gustave Le Bon and being a moron magnet, I have seen,
I have worked in industry where when you're given a task to solve a problem, using simple
terms here, you're given enough support to do so.
Mm-hmm.
And I have no support in this, and I never expected it.
Well, even without going there, even without going to the group thing, just in terms of
how much attention, time, and energy you put into...
Hundreds of hours.
...claiming about morons, complaining about morons, and so on and so forth, as opposed
to other things that you could be addressing, how scattershot your presentation is.
It doesn't seem to be streamlined or structured in such a way...
No, it shouldn't be.
...for maximum efficiency, for maximum efficiency.
No, it shouldn't.
No, but here's the interesting thing.
You could read any scripture, from the Hopi Indian to what they call the Bible, to the
Prakrit, to any language, and you will see that it is a redundant, albeit coherent once
you look at it in its totality, but if you take little pieces of it, it keeps changing.
Mm-hmm.
And it's, yeah, it's pixels.
You know, if you start looking at something very close, it doesn't make sense.
If you're in front of a monitor and you start looking at pixels...
Right.
...you don't see it, yeah?
But you cannot deny that a high-definition monitor has more pixels than a less-definition
monitor, so I'm putting out a lot of high-definition pixels that you're going to have to put together
and stand back and see the image.
Right.
Why would I, though?
Why would I want to?
I don't know.
Maybe it's not for you, then.
It just so happens the way that I'm doing it, because it's just about covering everything.
Well, yeah, but why would people want to?
I mean, this is back...
I don't know.
...to this point about my comments about cult, which weren't, to be clear, that I wasn't
suggesting that you were trying to create a cult or even that you were in danger of
creating one.
I was talking about the way in which what you do affects the individual, like if it
actually impacts them in such a way that they begin thinking cultishly, let's say.
I'm oversimplifying now, but...
The control that they have.
Yeah.
I have no control over that.
Well, you have control over your expression, though.
Well, then we go into what's called neuro-linguistic programming, where you always have to be
correcting what you're saying so it comes through objectively, and then you'll be
garnering another cultish group that likes that, like the Vulcans.
If you have a group of Vulcans, using a Star Trek analogy, if you're always bringing up
logic, eventually you'll open the door and you'll see they'll all be all Vulcans in there,
very few humans.
Mm-hmm.
But if you always bring up emotion and altruism and hope, you'll open the door, there'll
be no Vulcans, they'll be full of humans, you see?
So again, why do you want to be a moron magnet?
And I'm using moron as a medical term, a technical term, you don't really want to
hear me use pejoratives, right?
And no one does, it doesn't sound good.
Well, let me give you an example.
What inspired me to just say things like that is I've been in the company of what you
call chiefs of industry, politicians, leaders, and things like that.
I'm not going to state who, and people, you know, I don't need to prove anything,
I don't even find it distasteful to even say that.
Give you an example, here in the American Midwest, I was at someone's house, and
they were having a gathering, and they were using a certain language I didn't
understand, and I asked someone to define those terms.
And they were calling people, they have names for people, you know, the masses,
like we would say, if I say the great unwashed, yeah, you could say that's what
they think of the common people.
But they were using terms that I'm not even going to use, because I needed them
to be defined.
And I said, everything that's coming out of, these are people that are running
what you consider to be industry, right, and finance, and things like that.
They think so little of you, and at one point I said, why do they speak that way?
They said, oh, when you start, you know, dealing with things that they have to do,
you'll be using the same language.
And I said, no, I won't.
And I haven't.
I'm not.
But I do bring across the air that, very similarly that you'll find in scripture
as well, you won't find any scripture that says anything positive about mankind.
There might be some individuals that, through their actions, deeds, and they've
been chosen, have been spoken of as being positive, right?
Besides the part about being made in God's image, at least.
The God's image, plural, yes.
Yeah, yeah.
Right, and I've discussed that also.
That's misunderstood.
Okay.
So, but bringing it back to this thing of how you address people, your audience,
and...
I don't have an audience.
Sorry.
Well, you do.
You do.
I mean, technically.
You've got people who listen to your streams, and then you've got the people
that you're talking to or talking at.
Do you factor into this the question of how we address people and how we
interact with them determines how they experience themselves, not just you,
and what you draw out of them.
Like, when we speak to people, like, you're, to some degree, I would say,
to less a degree than I would like, you're responding, you're expressing
yourself in different ways than you normally do just because you're talking
to me.
Right?
Very, very marginally, but to some degree or whatever, what you're saying
is going to be a response to me, and what I say is a response to you.
So there's a potential within that, that space of dialogue, for the
transmission to get stronger, for the signal to get stronger, and to reduce
the noise, the delusion, the bullshit, the moronic, you know, whatever
limitations I have, you know, whatever category you want to put me in.
It doesn't help if you address me as a moron, obviously, right?
You've got to factor in that I've got limitations and all the rest of it,
but you also, I would hope, want to speak to the best in me in the hope
that that would actually bring it more out, bring it more to the surface
by bringing it more into my own awareness.
Sure.
So what I would suggest on that is if you feel inclined to do that
and invest in it, you should wholeheartedly do that.
Yeah, well, that is what I do. I work in a thrift store,
so I have to deal with morons, in your vernacular, every day.
Well, I didn't make up the word moron.
I know, I know, but you employ it in a way that I wouldn't.
I would have done when I was 20.
That's fine.
But now that I'm 50, I've felt that I needed to go in the other direction
and just try and see the value in every individual I speak to
or interact with and, well, I don't know, let them know
or communicate to them that they have value in some sense.
That's fine.
And that's for my own sanity.
That's not because I want to be a good guy or a saint or an altruistic person.
That's fine.
It's because I've got to get through four hours of shift working in a thrift store
and I can hide behind the laptop and just be like a machine,
but I don't know that whoever comes in the store isn't a god in disguise.
But that's personal.
I'm not addressing the...
You know, if, for example, if we have a truck full of grey marbles
and there's a blue and a green one in there also,
I could say that pretty accurately that's a truck full of grey marbles
and it's not pure, it's not reagent grade
because there might be some other colours thrown in there
but you can sell it as a truck, for example, as a grey marble.
But if I'm addressing the blue...
If I pick up the blue marble and I hold it up or the red marble
I won't tell someone that it's grey.
It's foolish.
No, I know, but human beings aren't marbles
and human beings aren't just one thing.
But no, human beings are moronic
and there are a very few that are not.
They're traumatised.
That's how I look at it.
They're heavily traumatised.
I'm stating a fact.
I'm not going back to their history.
I'm not representing them as their attorney in court.
Yeah, but it's the fact that they're traumatised too
and that's a root fact.
They wouldn't be moronic if they hadn't been traumatised.
Sure, but I do get into the trauma
and I do get into the aspect of people's refusal to address it.
Yeah, okay, they have a responsibility.
I'm not denying that.
But when I say they're not marbles
I mean that they're not fixed entities that are just one colour.
Sure, but those traumas I view as tools.
You're familiar with the Pavlovian training.
You ring the bell, you feed the dog.
Of course.
Okay, but are you familiar with the history of that?
That was near a river that overflowed
and the dogs were below level
and they nearly drowned
and they actually had to save the dogs
by putting them underwater and pulling them up.
If you've been around dogs you know how traumatic that could be.
And then once they had restored them into another laboratory
they noticed that all of that Pavlovian training was gone.
They'd ring the bell, none of them would salivate.
Because when you subject someone to training
or Pavlovian conditioning
then to erase that you subject them to a high level of trauma
and it erases all that.
That's why the media does what they do
regarding each modality through history.
Say more about that?
Well, for example, if the Americans want to go to war with the Japanese
the American government wants to go to war with the Japanese
and the American people are not having it
you just make some movies showing
Japanese actors raping American women
and all of a sudden the recruitment rate goes up 90%.
Right.
Because it's traumatic for an American
who's nationalistic
to see one of his own nationalistic
I mean nationalists being raped
by another extra-national
so that's trauma to them.
Mild level, but yeah.
Yeah, but if you showed them the Japanese were having tea
then that's not trauma
they say, oh fine, even more reason not to go to war.
Yeah, yeah.
So you can use trauma to manipulate people
Right, that's why they keep showing what they do
in media and in church
why do they just have a guy nailed to a cross wearing a diaper?
But I'm not sure you can use trauma
to straighten people out
I don't think that's an illusion.
No, but I'm saying it's a very real thing
that affects the psyche
and it's being used on you
Yeah, but that it can be used therapeutically
I'm saying
I think is a lie.
Well, therapeutically
a lot of what they call therapeutic
is actually quite destructive
Do you think taking
experimental drugs is therapeutic?
Do you think electric shock
is a lot of the things that it's doing?
Yeah, of course not.
You know, I might say
someone
in jest again
someone says, well Greek, I like listening to your stuff
even though I don't understand it
I say, well then it must have a therapeutic effect then
not a cognitive one, you see.
You know what I mean?
So that's fine too.
I'm still on the fence about that
because sometimes
it matters to me
where I put my attention
whether it's nourishing me
and enhancing my experience of myself
which is back to my point about
human beings not being marbles
the way we interact with them
the climate that we provide
for them, the psychic climate
determines how they experience themselves
and how they are
not in a massive way
They're not marbles, but factually
you're either someone's pet
or you're someone's dinner, spiritually
factually
the majority of people are someone's dinner
in other words, they're feeding off of you
your energy
or you're someone's pet
that's what the group or the cult is
you've heard of teacher's pet, right?
the leadership returns
with gratitude for their presence
and their interest
It's still circumstantial, isn't it?
I mean, there's still aspects
of the totality
of the gods
There's a hundred shades of grey
but let's not forget that grey
is a compound of white and black
and if it's dim enough
the grey does look very dark and be black
and if it's bright enough, the grey could appear to be white
so, you know, the ultimate
thing
is are you doing the right thing
for example
I've gotten about 900 emails
in the past year and a half
almost 900
all but 2 or 3 have been positive
all of them are positive
but what kind of positive is the thing?
Oh, I heard
I never considered, for example, the body having a vacuum
and I understood that
now it made sense to me when I have a wound
to wrap it really tight
almost critically tight
to the point where it's not good
and then release it
and I see the healing happening very quickly
I'd never thought of that
Thank you very much
Oh, I never knew how to cook rice before
I was always afraid of it
as a matter of fact
I didn't even like rice
and I listened to you talk about
making rice
and now I make the best rice
Even someone from a restaurant
said we've improved
Timekeeping
I do planting or I do fishing
You know, the fish migrate
on a time schedule
that's not the Pope's work schedule
You've heard me say the Pope's work schedule, right?
Obviously, yeah
And these people, these commercial fishermen
have developed radar to follow these
fish, but they've noticed that within a two-week
spread during the year, they come across there
Is it because your calendar
could be off as much as two weeks in a year
meaning the real day where the
position of the earth is to the sun, to the moon, to the stars
The fish don't care about what you
call a day, but if you record
the day that you've encountered that
school of fish
using the moon phases
and the month count
you'll go back there next year, and I had someone report
back, they were doing cod fishing
they were going to go out in a few
days because it was approaching that time
and he had heard what I was saying
we're talking about
a 400 foot boat with a crew of 30 people
it costs a million dollars a day
this is not trivial
maybe it is to some
a million dollar day operation could be trivial
but I don't know
depends who's relative
he says no, tomorrow
is the day that we found them
we need to go out right now
and the captain says
you know what, I wanted to speed up
this operation in a way to test these new pumps
so let's go out by tomorrow
and guess what
they got the front end of the school
not the second or third one
that passed by
and they can tell that by the material
fish have a culture
they have the alpha dog lead
fish also have
there are certain fish that go first
like tuna
anyway
so he emailed me back
and he's saying
Greek
this is the best catch we've ever had in history
thanks to you
and I'm like, thanks to me
let's be real rash
about it and rationale
what am I getting for it
do I get a cut of the catch
oh no, I think if I brought that up
that would never fly
yeah, thanks
you see
oh, are you doing it for money
no, how about
when I have a used car
and I get another car
I give it away
people say I'm going to sell the old one and offset the cost of the new one
why go through all that hassle
I don't want to start meeting people
and telling me what they like or don't like
about the car and haggling on the price
I've gotten 8 years or 9 years use out of it
it's paid for itself to me
and recently
I was doing that and a neighbor was laughing at me
he said we got another car
what are you going to do with that one
give it away, ha ha ha
you're really stupid for giving it away
I shouldn't even be saying this
these are personal things
now I'm being mocked
by those around me
because I'm giving a car away
who are you going to give it away to
someone in need
but someone in need who can care for it
not someone who's broke that's going to run out of gas
and leave it on the side of the road
you have to give it away responsibly
to a responsible party as well
don't you
yeah
so I have a lot of
background
experience in history
that I don't bring forward
why don't you like to talk about
personal stuff
why should I
why don't you want to
because it's not relevant
I'm addressing
you've heard of like would like
the concept of parody
if you're addressing a culture
you address it on a cultural level
so you're talking to the culture
you're not talking to human beings
no, no, not at all
you're not
it's you and the culture
it sounds pretty lonely
no wonder you're so pissed off
you know some people
I've had some people do pilgrimages
they say I'm in Tucson or whatever
that's close enough
and they fly in from different parts of the world
I'm serious
and I've had four in the past two years
and they just call me
I'm at the airport in Tucson
I said what are you doing here
he said I wanted to come and see you
I said why
and I do spend some time with them
they're like you're completely different
you're like so whatever
very different
you're not mad
you're very kind
now it sounds like I'm
I get it
I'll throw another thing
it's like wow you've paid for everything
and I send them off with gifts
but why do you address
that baffles me
why do you separate human beings from the culture
or vice versa
you don't separate them
and you do separate them
in other words when you're addressing a culture
of headhunters
if you're going to start addressing that they have
purple polka dot wallpaper in their kitchen
that's only relevant
to those that have that
but if you're addressing shrunken heads
you're addressing all of them
why would you want to talk to shrunken heads
no you're addressing the issue of shrunken heads
to the society of headhunters
the main points
that I bring up
is that your body is not a filter bag
you're on the pope's work schedule
you don't even know how to keep time
you have no money
you're on a credit based economy
because all of your governments are bankrupt
and they have to give you credit to function
but the attorneys have determined
that if they tell you that no one's going to want to work
that's how piss poor
in terms of responsibility
you've been determined to be
whether you are or not
is not the point
those that lead you have determined
that they have to lie to you
you know nothing about your history
you don't want to go back more than 100 years
you don't know how to manage water
you can't even define the weather
birds don't fly
birds are flown
a bird will not fly in a vacuum
you put a little gasp air mask
on a bird
he'll flap his wings
he's not going anywhere
and if you leave him in there long enough
he won't even try anymore
this is the list of radical info
that each one is a rabbit hole
unto itself
but from what you've said
the reason you're presenting all this stuff
is basically so that you
have got a clear record
that you can say
I told people so don't blame it on me
yeah that's true
because if you're doing good for selfish reasons
you're still doing good also
aren't you?
she gave a million dollars
let's say Canadian or American
what they call dollars
to an orphanage
because if you spent a million
on advertising in newspapers
no one would look at it
but if you got the publicity
that you gave
everyone would consider
you see
the reason the company
gave a million dollars
to the orphanage
is not because they're
charity
it's because they'll get more out of their advertising money
than if they spent a million on front page cover
it's debatable that that's doing good though
it depends on where the money goes
then it depends on the orphanage
we'll pick something else
let's say starving people
let's not call it an orphanage
I'll use our example
we have this thrift store
once a week we buy food
and we feed it to the hungry and the homeless
that's a good business policy
although it makes a lot of people in the town dislike us
but nonetheless
are we doing it good
because what are our reasons
they're all kind of mixed up together
but the end result
one of them is that people are getting fed
well the competitors
will not like it because they didn't pull a stunt like that
you know the corporation that gave a million to the orphanage
their marketing people
didn't determine that
marketing people wouldn't determine that
because they can't collect fees for that
but here's the point
years ago, more than 15 years ago
when I was discussing these things
or about that time
people would say you need to start telling
you need to write a book
I said well in order to write a book
I have to presume that people can read with comprehension
writing a book is a good thing
but when you put that out
you're presuming that people can read with comprehension
when you talk and stream
you're presuming that people will be able to
flatten this stuff out and apply it in a way
that is rooted and grounded
not all people
very few and very few do
exactly my point
that's why for me
to make an arbitrary distinction
between personal information
and impersonal
can be self-sabotaging
because I actually want to know stuff about you
or get a sense of you
not because I'm curious
but because I want the context for this stuff
that to me
it roots it
in something that is real and tangible
however mundane
or trivial
other people see it right away
other people do some research
some people want it given to them
like you're asking
that's up to you
well no it isn't
it's up to you
how you present it
and then I'm one of your listeners
who's saying
I don't really expect to change what you're doing
by making any of these suggestions
but that's how
I have a dialogue with you
by sharing my experience of what you're doing
that's one aspect
the focus is on you and the information
and so on and so forth
there's so much of the latter
the information that we could
have a three hour chat
for a year
and we wouldn't get through all of these bullet points
that you're presenting
so then I want to keep bringing the focus back to you
which ironically is where you don't want it to be
in a sense
or at least not the personal you
it's not like I want personal
information about you
I'm not like Yo-Yo Ma the cello player
who has mastered the cello
at nine or ten
you can just put the cello up on stage
and anyone try to play it
no one's going to play it like this cello master
I'm not
producing anything that is unique to me
other than the
persona
I know but it's coming through you
the other medium and the message in the medium
are pretty hard to extricate
I don't think they can be
I happen to be a point source
for it at the moment
a small point source
that emanates a field
in a more 360
or 180 degree cone
or view
so
that might be
and it's unfortunate
and I'm embarrassed to be human
because most of the stuff that I mentioned
you can access immediately
as a source
say for example timekeeping
in the Pope's work schedule
some people like it hits them across the head
like a baseball bat
how come I never saw that before
so simplistic
other people want to go and study
the fine detail of the Papal Bull of 1585
and other people start
looking at various calendrical systems
and how it evolved
and that's fine, that's their prerogative
but I'm telling you, you don't know how to keep time
period
other than the subject
bullshit
and it is bullshit
not because I say it, because they say it's bullshit
so
on the example of timekeeping
that is an area that I'm interested in
we could talk about that for many hours
I do want to find out more
but before I jump down that rabbit hole
or commit to it
I want to find out more about you
I have a history of following
dodgy leaders
of getting sucked into dodgy information
matrices
which you know all about
and whether you like it or not
you're participating in that
this is a leader list
and that should be obvious
you're on the internet
you're disseminating on the internet
so when you say everything on the internet is bullshit
you have to include yourself
it's not as though there's a dividing line
you've been on the Freeman show
for fuck's sake, pardon my French
but that's about as moronic
alternative media
as I could think of
so you chose not to bad mouth anyone
I don't personally like to do that
but seeing as you do
talk about that a lot
why don't you walk your talk
why would you do the Freeman show
when you must know that that's
just as big a bullshit matrix
as any of the other ones
that you're not naming
well because why
then I'd have to get into what was going on
before to get me on the Freeman show
and
what makes you think
that I didn't tell Freeman that it's all bullshit
and he agreed to it anyway
but you didn't tell him on the show
well
maybe it was edited out
that's possible
but he invited you back
and he's not airing anymore
he has more interviews
because it's not conducive to
accommodating the audience
and it shouldn't be
but the reason why I say
it's just like I say
I'm taking a cross section
of it right now
of the internet
why I'm on the internet
because it's efficient
I would rather not be
but it is the most efficient way to do it
in terms of doing it in print
and sending it out
and publishing it on pulp
physical pulp paper
this seems to be the convention
just like for example
money is now electronic convention
versus paper convention
or substance before that
so
what I do say is
it is all crap right now
just like this is a truck
of grey marbles
there might be some others
in there whatever tolerance
based on the tolerance that if you were to put
a wide brush statistically
if you ask someone
to count all the grains of sand in the beach
they're going to give you a statistical count
because if you give it accurate
to the grain
what if you're challenged
and you have to go recount it
so you have to say statistically
I've been saying for years statistically
it's all bullshit
there's some exceptions
but the exceptions are so minimal
if you said all of it statistically
it's very accurate from a statistician's
point of view
you see
and that is a fact
what the internet is good for
it's a hybrid of the telephone book
a reference manual
years ago I used to carry a little blue reference
manual that had conversions and charts
and things right if you work in engineering
or whatever you know
melting points of metals hardnesses
now you do it on the rectangle
the phone right it's a convention has changed
from paper
what the internet is really
I've mentioned also it's a microphone test
before the show goes on
the crew comes up and says microphone test
that's all you've gotten on the internet
the purpose of the internet
is to evolve audio and video communication
cheaply and instantly
so in the future
anyone and everyone in the planet
will have access to events happening
anywhere in the world almost with immediacy
that's the purpose of the internet
it's not the information age
right
that's bullshit
just like the space age
how many of you went into space
that's a whole side track
how many of you are being informed
you're describing the internet as a platform
for a grand deception
is that right
no a grand deception and a grand evidentiary
no one can say
I didn't see or hear about this event
in the future
remember the last thing the gods want
after reincarnation or resurrection
is a bunch of sniveling humans saying
you came and mopped us up
with great force and destruction
you didn't give us a chance
you see
that's a metaphor
it's a powerful one
whether it's powerful or not
I'm sticking to it
so you're applying that to your own function
or whatever
as in if you're going to disseminate stuff
and say I've disseminated what I had to know
you want it to go out to the whole world
like you don't want it to fly
and post them on the telegraph poles
in your local community anonymously
I have done that before
in the past by the way regarding issues
in the community
so you do want to reach more people
it's not just about covering your ass
no I don't want to reach
once I've established that
I want to do it organically
do I want to go out and buy
a four section file drawer
to file all the stuff that I need
yes that's beneficial
but also do I know for sure
if I have a table with all the papers
stacked organically
I know that the lower I go on the stack
it's in time
and I know if it's important
I'm going to set it in a separate basket
you see
which one has more organic
or natural immediacy
is what looks like a messy desk
versus the triple collated
file cabinet
you see
so in other words
reaching more people is irrelevant at this time
because I've always said
there's only going to be a small handful of people
that can use or grasp any of this
yeah understood
but if you want to find those people
or rather if you wanted to reach those people
then presumably you need to reach more people
because they're all scattered
about the globe
well yes I know for sure
over 100,000 people have heard at least
one hour of
Greek speak
and only about 4 or 5 have made an attempt
to contact
out of 100,000
so if you multiply
that times 10
that's a million
so it's 40 out of a million
ok
so you've got the numbers there
yeah those are
pretty good numbers
here locally I've spoken to
several thousand people
and only 2 were interested
afterwards
after I gave contact information
right
so it's a very small percentage
I'm quite satisfied with the
number
from a responsibility point of view
if I knew more people were
interested I would have to do
what you mentioned earlier
about the lack of being streamlined
the lack of coherence
I would have to be put together
in a more coherent
format
that people are used to seeing
with contents
and more development
like a really basic
thing and I don't necessarily want you
to follow this because I don't know
whether what you're presenting is positive or not
but it's simply to
have somebody do the notes for each streaming
so then you've got
a list of the content for all of your archives
that would enormously
then it's cross referenceable
that's a really basic
I've several people offer
that and they all fell to the wayside
right they didn't follow through
no they didn't follow through I'm not going to do it
because like for example
by another hour or two I have to go pick
up a box of things that are being
sent to me an industrial thing that has to be
modified because the engineers don't understand
the drawing and I
said well it has to be modified a certain way
and they had the brilliant idea then why don't you do
the first one and then we'll copy it I said that's a great idea
why don't you ship the device
to me I will do the modifications
I'll include notes and
do a follow up on it and then I'll
send it back to you right
you understand what I'm saying right
so
yeah and that's where I'm dedicating my
time to
it's work you know
so in other
words for me to start putting
it all together myself I'm going to have to sit down
an hour or two or three a day until I get enough
of it put together edit it
polish it up put it together put it
up and then maintain it
right
fine if you want to do it fine
like I told Sam you set it up you tell me
what you need from me and if I can do it
time wise allotted or anything else
financial whatever I'll do it oh yeah
Greek I'll do it I'll go set it nothing
right
other people have said it too so it's not worth
much
that's not where I'm
positioned myself
obviously I'm an outsider
who's interested in what you're doing
and wanting to
find out more about it and about yourself
even before putting this on
a podcast or whatever I mean you can certainly use
it but I'm undecided about
whether I want to make more
people aware of what you're doing not that I've got
some massive platform or anything like that
but I've got some very serious minded
people you can probably laugh internally
at that but anyway
by my gauge
who give positive feedback to what I'm doing
that's good
makes the earth go round right
keeps me feeling like my life is meaningful
anyway and rain
and bullshit keep the flowers going
and to me I mean
like where I'm
coming from talking to you about these things
is obviously from where I'm situated
and why I do what I do so far
as I'm conscious of it which is
making connections to other living
beings other humans
meaningful connections that enrich
my experience of myself let's say
so yeah I can do that in the thrift store
in a very superficial way
as in I can just
develop more
tolerance for my fellow man let's put it that
way whereas what I do on the
internet does seem to lead to
much richer deeper connections
that bring about
some sort of understanding
of stuff I don't know what
it's worth but I
I'm not going to
provide that because now I'm going to have to talk about
the things that I do
and that's not why I'm
speaking public
you're not going to provide what?
personal aspects
of what I would like to see in people and how I'd
like to help people because that is
secondary to the people being able to help
themselves well no I think
you're again you're making a categorization
that I wouldn't make like you and I
I think you said this in the conversation
you and I it doesn't
really matter to a great deal
what we're talking about what we're focusing on
verbally or mentally because
there's some connection that's occurring just by
us hooking up would you agree?
yes it's beyond
what we consider to be
psychophysical yes
so that's the thing I'm talking about
something can happen when two sentient beings
come together and have a dialogue
that may only be
dimly observable on the
surface of the dialogue itself but it'll
be tangible in some way
it's tangible although it's purely spiritual
right now because I mean there's no physical
interaction at all other than
the devices that we're using
well you know I was thinking about that recently and that's
actually not true because we're
we're both situated on the
earth and so we're
connected just as if you know my leg
brushed against your leg we were wearing
trousers you would still say we've made
contact right? but we're not because then
we would all be connected on a seven and a half
or eight billion level
I'm saying right now the interaction
qualitatively and quantitatively that we're
having is purely spiritual meaning non
physical but we are connected
to the seven and a half billion
you speak for yourself I've
been working on the past decade to disconnect
myself well but I okay
but whatever deep level
I mean however deep you have to dig
on the deepest level possible because
for example when you're part of
that group or on any level
you end up communicating on the level that
they've been manipulated to do
oh how are the meds? how's the weather?
how's Donald Trump? how's this
new drug? how are the vaccines? all
bullshit right when you pull yourself
away from them when you come back you could
no longer communicate to them on their level
you can only inform them
or you can pretend to
not pretend but you can communicate
to them on their level while being aware of what's
going on at the deeper levels
it's disingenuous to me
this is what I've had to be
trained in working in the thrift store
I mean imagine have you ever done retail
work? oh yeah I've had retail
businesses it's the hour after hour people
coming in saying how are you?
not wanting to hear the answer
they'll start talking to you about that stuff you don't
want to hear it right? that's culture
in Japan they would never do that
in Bushido when you ask someone how are you
even if they're dying of stomach cancer
they're going to say I'm fine but I'm not
in Japan I'm in British Columbia
that's the culture that's why I'm saying it's cultural
you're around the headhunters they want
to know about how many shrunken heads they can catch
they're treasure hunters coming into the thrift store
I know the analogy
and they're seriously damaged
people and if I treat them
with contempt it's bad for business it's also
bad for my soul let's say
you know I so
for me it's always
finding that possibility of connecting to
people at a deep level regardless of where
they're at in awareness it's not disingenuous
because I know that there's
a living soul underneath all
that trauma crust
that's fine that's
on a personal level of course
yeah I do that often here
and locally you've heard me say
that if half of the people in the world
each helped only one person
it takes care of the whole rest of the world doesn't it?
yeah
if half of the people of the world just helped
just one person each that means everyone's
taken care of now that's not a lot
to ask for if you ask for one person
to help one person
is that too much?
that's all that's required
it's very simple right but it's not easy at all
it's not easy to meet somebody in that distorted
cultural monster self and actually
be open to
when you understand that they rely on food
clothing and shelter instead of bombing a country
why don't you send them food packets
you were just saying
you want to disconnect from human beings
that's the part that's not easy
is staying connected
to human beings no matter how
distorted they are
you can disconnect from the culture but never from the
human being because right now I'm having
some coffee and that was
roasted and delivered and packaged
and grown by humans
their energy and their essence
for example I've worked in a lot
of the healing arts in the past
and if you go to a restaurant
and you don't feel good could it be that the cook
was angry
scientifically you can't prove that his
intent and his anger has a
field around his body that the
food is within that field and the food has memory
just like magnetic tape
and records that and it can affect you
negatively
if you want to go more chemical
if I eat at a place
and the food is across
very salty I'll tell the waitress
you have a new cook and he likes
eating sweets and she'll
drop her little menu
her little ticket board and say
how do you know that
I'm like well the food is salty because he eats
too many sweets so he has to compensate
so he's throwing salt around him and everything
and it's
not just eating sweets like he had
for dessert but he's constantly eating
sweets
elementary my dear Watson
you just cut out
change the
password
we'll go to wifi
connection problem
ironic timing
the connection
is bad
ok that's the end of the second part
parts 3 and 4 are also
available so just scroll down
past the show notes and you'll find
those there
I did decide to air these
after all based on the
comments it wasn't a voting
system I'm not a democrat
but just to see
if there was enough interest
and not too much
absolute aversion or
probably about
40, 60,
for and against and
no unequivocal
for's and some very
unequivocal against
and some quite funny comments too
if you do want to find the grease
just do a little protective work
there's enough information in these
conversations
ok so this is
Jason at the Limitless, the podcast between
support this podcast
donate, put some
funds into the pot
and buy Prisoner Infinity
read it, damn you
ok that's it, thanks for listening
till next time