This is the Liminalist, the podcast between C.C. and Horsley with part 3 of my conversation
with the Greek.
It's a bit crunchy. Keep talking.
All right, it's still crunchy?
No, I think it's back. I think it's good.
Okay, so instead of telling people to conserve water, make it so they have to. When the bathroom
sink, the water comes out of the bathroom sink. It shouldn't come out of a round spout.
It should come out like a thin, wide ribbon. It takes the soap off the hands four times
faster and the waste water from the bathroom sink goes into the toilet tank.
Right.
Don't tell people to conserve water. Make it so they have to. When you have a sign on
the road that says, slippery when wet, why don't you bond an abrasive to the road so
it's not slippery when wet and then take the sign down. Do you see?
Yeah. This is a personal question, so you might not want to answer it, but do you get
stressed out? Do you feel stress around people's ignorance and all the knowledge that you have
that is not being received?
Well, here's the thing. When you take an average person and say, we're being threatened
as a society, grab a gun and protect yourself from the enemy, is he going to be stressed?
Yes. If you grab someone who is a trained special forces combat and he's at home and
you say, hey, we're being attacked, take a gun, is he going to have the same level of
stress? No. To him, it's going to be going on a turkey shoot. The other guy, he's going
to be afraid for his life because he doesn't know what he's doing.
If you know what you're doing, the people don't stress you. What I do with people is
I try to leave them off better than I found them. I see what their concerns are. I don't
need much to know what they're concerned about. I can tell if I go to the hardware
store and I see a woman at the cashier, I know she's only one paycheck away from being
homeless with her children because she's a single mom. She doesn't have to tell me
that. I could read that accurately. This is the kind of stuff I do. Years ago, there were
people of high net worth that would send me their sons, 18, 19, to live with me, not live
with me, but they would report in the morning and spend the whole day with me, as if they
were going to work for about six months so I could mentor them, if that makes any sense.
I'm not going to talk about this publicly. You mean that you don't want people to know
or you just don't want to get into it?
Yeah, it's irrelevant. It's irrelevant to say, oh, we've got to listen to this guy.
He mentors the sons of this blah, blah, blah. I'm not going to say. You have to listen
because of that. I don't know what he's saying, but I like it.
Yeah, but it still begs the question of how you know what's relevant to your listener
unless you know your listener.
I'm broadcasting. In farming, the plane flies over with seeds and it drops it on the field.
It's called broadcasting or fertilizer.
Yeah, I know, I know. So you're deciding what's relevant, but based on your own criteria.
I do one-on-one all the time. Right now, I'm waiting for a shipment in the next hour
or two for something that I'm going to hopefully be able to ship out tomorrow, what they call
Monday, because the post will receive. I know they work on Sunday, but they receive Saturday
and Monday to get it out. That's a one-on-one, very specific. Can this project that I'm talking
about in real time benefit someone in the audience? Oh, heck yeah. Am I going to bring
up what it is? Heck no, because it's irrelevant to the general broadcast, you see, whoever's
picking it up.
Oh, here he's talking. I've even had Sam, for example, oh, when you talk about food
and clothing, I don't want to know or time, I turn it off. I don't want to hear about
that.
Who says that?
Sam and other people. I'm just bringing it up because you might have a communication
with them. I don't care about the food or the time. No, that's not what I'm interested
in.
Oh, really?
Yeah, I only want to listen to this or that. Many people say, oh, I don't want to hear
about this and that. I'm Christian, I don't want to hear this. I just want to hear about
the food.
That's interesting, because I don't find that listening to you. I find that it's all of
a piece, really. It's kind of you that I'm listening to as much as the information. Your
level of interest doesn't seem to vary much. You know what I mean? You put as much energy
into whatever you're talking about. I'm hearing that as much as anything. I mean, yeah, you
repeat yourself a lot.
Everything is interesting, if you find it so.
I'm more concerned with how you're framing or the context you're putting the information
in, which, as I put in my email, it has the similarities with the SOP of cult leaders,
which, again, I'm not saying that you're aspiring to that or that you want to be, but...
Quite the opposite.
Quite the opposite, right? But you know that we often become the thing that we most don't
want to become, right?
No, but I never said I most don't want to become. What I said is irrelevant to me.
Okay. Well, it's not irrelevant to me, because I've studied this stuff a lot, and as I say,
I've fallen into those mouse traps, those guru mouse traps quite a few times in my life.
It doesn't have to be a guru. For example, if you look at Scientologists, do they talk
about L. Ron Hubbard or do they talk about the Scientology?
Well, this is the context...
When you go to physics school, university, they talk about the cult of bumping particles.
Well, they would if they were being honest. They would. I mean, it is a cult, right?
Yeah, the medicine, the legal system, it's all a cult.
It's all a cult. It's culture, right? And the context in which I came to you was somebody
who's your follower, and I guess she does look to you in a kind of guru-like way. So,
that has framed my experience of you, I guess. That's a relevant detail.
But then again, that's the personal side that I would like to disconnect from, because if
she was listening objectively, she wouldn't recommend me to you, because she would listen
to you and say, well, you guys couldn't be more different. Basically, you're doing the
bullshit that everyone likes to hear, and this Greek is doing the stuff that people
don't want to hear. I would never recommend him to you. But anyway, I'm not saying that
you are doing the bullshit, but I'm presuming you are.
You're presuming it, right?
It's a safe presumption.
Well, it's...
It's not a put-down. Okay, when you say bullshit, it doesn't mean bovine excrement.
No, no, no. But it's not a safe assumption. I mean, it isn't for you. I don't have to
get offended by it, because I know you think this way about everyone, and you're just talking
technically, but it's not a safe assumption, right? There's no point in me saying I'm not
doing bullshit, but the context of this conversation, the context that I'm trying to keep drawing
us back to is that dissemination of information isn't enough. So yeah, if I was just disseminating
information for its own sake, I would agree. I'm just, you know, piling on the bullshit,
but I'm not doing that.
Information is not the key. If you... a computer, you have to have an operating system, then
you have a program, same with people, and then you have information. If you bought a
brand new computer out of the box, just blinking, you can't download files without a program,
and you can't put a program without an operating system. I talk about the operating system,
the programs, and then the files are last. How to make perfect rice is in the file. How,
you know, many of the things, when I talk about a moron, I said that's the file label,
right? They're a moron because their programs are moronic, and their operating system is
deceptive and malevolent.
Right. Well, you know the expression, to a hammer everything looks like a nail?
Correct.
Right? So if you assume that everyone's a moron, then obviously everyone you encounter
you're going to see as being moronic, or you're going to increase the chances that
you won't see the aspects of them that aren't moronic.
No, they are not.
The evidence that they're not actually, they don't fit into your categorization system.
I don't have any categorization. I'm talking about their categories.
Well, yeah, you do, because you say a moron is a medical term, and it relates to development
and so on and so forth.
Yeah, lack of development.
They don't have a mental age over the age of nine, right?
Right, later nine or 12 maximum.
So maybe that's true in my case, and maybe it isn't. I don't know, but you sure as hell
don't know, unless you're enlightened or something or beyond that, right? Maybe you do know.
Maybe you're the god. I don't know.
Let's go back. And I'm speaking statistically.
Yeah.
Not everyone exactly fits the moron profile, but if you were to go to a planet, this planet
from another world, and say that these people are moronic, that would be so...
You wouldn't be wrong, yeah, absolutely.
Yeah, you heard me give the analogy about the Kevlar underwear is the largest industry
because these people have a custom of placing a thumbtack on their seat before they sit.
It's their custom and tradition. So the largest industry on that planet is Kevlar underwear.
Now, a logical, rational person would say, well, why don't they just stop placing thumbtacks?
They don't need the Kevlar underwear.
But if you start promoting that they stop doing that, the people that control the Kevlar underwear
have so much power that they will... you see?
Yeah.
Does that sound like a metaphor?
Yeah, you've abstracted again into metaphors. It's like you like to take refuge in these abstractions.
No, not refuge. I try to illustrate it.
Well, it seems like it, because we were talking about your listener, who I won't name in case
this goes public, but who drew my attention to you and how that's a frame of reference
in which I'm approaching your material, and you made the assumption that she made an error
simply because I don't see...
Not an error. Not an error. Not enough objectivity.
You did say that, because you said if she had known that I was just, you know, another brush
If she were more objective.
Yeah, which is a big if and not a sub. But the assumption there is that she did make a
mistake, rather than that there is a reason for you and I to talk, and that she sees
something that you don't see about you and about me, I see something about her, about
you, that you don't see, that we have pieces of the puzzle that we can share and actually
put together and we will see more than we saw before.
Sure. Every elephant is different. I'm not looking at, you know, looking at an elephant
too close syndrome. I'm looking back saying, this is an elephant.
Mm-hmm.
You know, one might have some...
Yeah, you don't want to get your hands dirty.
Yeah, here's the thing. It's ultimately about being efficient. Like I said earlier,
if you... most of the people now, because of the rectangle, are affected by geopolitical
and national things regarding health and politics and things, you know, economics.
And I'm telling you, don't get caught up in those upwinded and downwinded realities,
meaning they just pass, right?
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Because what is coming, what really matters, that when you start seeing these things, A,
B, C, D, or 1, 2, 3, 4, down to 400, these are the things that are going to lead to this.
Then pay attention to that. That you should be concerned about.
Yeah, but getting caught up in the Middle Eastern Union and the rise of a world leader who's going to...
That's much later.
Yeah, I know, but it's definitely something that people can get caught up in.
If they get caught up in financial crises and environmental threats,
they're certainly going to get caught up in grand narratives about the Antichrist and the gods.
So how is that better?
Yes.
How is that better?
But it's a much higher... What hierarchy are you working on?
Well, it's more fascinating as well. It's more easy to get caught up in it.
To some. To some they don't care.
I've actually... I don't care about the gods. I don't believe it and I don't want to know anything about it.
Okay, bye.
Yeah, yeah.
But I do want to know about rice.
I want to know about cooking rice, though.
Okay.
So I have the, yeah, the cooking rice and all the way down to...
I don't get into many of the industry things.
Once I was working with some consulting and the person said,
I heard you do radio. We don't want to work with you because you might speak on some of the things that we are doing.
And I said, I won't.
I said, well, it's too late. You're already public so we don't want to work with you.
So it has cost me quite a bit from opportunity cost, you know what I mean?
Maybe they did want to work with me and it wouldn't have worked out anyway, but you see.
How do they know you do radio if you do it under a pseudonym?
Oh, it's someone in the groups that he does. You should listen to him on radio.
Hmm, I see.
Someone I'd already known.
Someone that introduced me was friendly and he says, well, what do you do?
I said, I talk to people.
Well, why don't you do something? Why don't you do a radio on the internet?
I said, I already do that.
Oh, really?
And then that just kind of stuck there and they brought it up. Do you see what I mean?
Right, yeah, yeah.
Does that make sense?
No, it's just a detail.
Yeah, in other words, people that do work together also have non-work related conversations and it will come out.
And now will I hide it from anyone?
You know, if they ask me, is there anything else you do? What is your personal life? What hobbies do you have?
Whatever. I said, well, I have a website named Forbio.
Okay, fine. I'm going to supply it if they ask.
But I'm not going to say, hi, yeah, I'll help you with your ignition system and I do on Common Radio.
Yeah, yeah, sure, sure.
I'm not going to, but if they ask me what other hobbies, they do ask that, by the way.
If you've ever seen like, quote, unquote, this is not a job, what other hobbies do you have, you know,
or what else do you do on your free time when you're not designing ignition systems, let's say.
Right.
Right? Simple.
I had some born again Christians wanting me to do some water processing stuff and I declined right off the bat.
No, I'm not going to work with them.
You know, because they were so, they even have the crucifixes on their water website kind of thing.
And I said, well, these people are going to find out eventually that I'm doing radio.
You know, this is a one year thing they want me to get involved in, you know.
And they're not going to, it's not that I don't want to work with them.
It's that they're not going to understand what I'm saying, you see.
Mm-hmm.
Right?
You've heard me say that there's no Christian that knows the Bible and there's no Muslim that knows the Koran.
Yeah, yeah.
There's no Jewish person that knows that.
And there's no Buddhist that knows any of the Prakrit or Sanskrit scriptures, none of them do.
Because once they read it, it'll condemn everything they're doing.
So, okay.
You see, scientists, there's no scientist that knows the works of who came before them.
See, this blanket statement, this is what I mean by the context in which you provide your information.
Part of it is the context that nobody knows anything.
No, no, no, they do.
They do know what's based on keep maintaining their food, clothing and shelter.
I've heard of several people in, let's say, law enforcement and others say,
well, I'm going to wait until I get my retirement, then I'm going to bust this whole thing open that's happening in this town.
Mm-hmm.
Wow, so you're putting money over it.
Right?
You see?
Okay, but my point is that when you overstate your case, you undermine it, at least for me.
Because it's not credible that no Christian interpretation or no religious interpretation of the scripture
has anything in common with the scripture, that it's all completely wrong.
Oh, no, I'd never said that either.
In order to make something counterfeit, you have to look very close and keep people ignorant of the detail.
Right, so like disinformation being 90% true, you mean.
Yes, and there are Christians right now, as we speak, that are studying the Bible and they're in a neutral zone.
They're like, holy shit, this is really bad.
And then they make an exit strategy, and they get out of it, and they renounce it.
And then there are Christians that know that it's wrong, but they do it anyway because it keeps them going.
Right.
Just like doctors that get the quarter of a million a year because they're prescribing this drug.
They know it kills people.
Mm-hmm.
Right?
Right.
Just like the police that know their chief of police in this is dealing drugs and spiriting children from child services to another, you see, to be sold.
They know that.
Yeah.
You see.
So you have the ignorant.
The majority are ignorant.
You have the mid-zone, the people that are looking for an exit strategy because they've noticed they stepped in shit, basically,
or they're doing what they've been told they believed they realized isn't good.
And then you have the ones that are evil that will keep going along.
They know what's going on, you see.
Yeah, I understand.
So like when you were talking about giving money to charity, that was what I was thinking of.
It's not necessarily a good deed.
If you're acting unconsciously or acting for self-interest or whatever it is,
and you're not in tune with the reality of the present moment,
then the chances are very, very high that your good deed will not only be punished,
but deservedly punished because you will end up complicit with some fucked-up system, right?
So information and knowledge is like that, as I see it.
Like 90% truth, 10% lies means that actually it's kind of 100% lies
because that 10% influences the context in which you understand the other 90%, right?
So then it all becomes bullshit.
That's how I understand what you're saying,
but in which case the question is why do you think that you're exempt from that?
How can you believe that your stuff isn't becoming bullshit by taint of association?
That's irrelevant. It's whoever is listening to it.
Right, which is back to my initial point.
They ask Sarah Vaughan what makes a great jazz musician.
She says it's the audience that makes you great.
It's the audience that knows whether what I'm saying is the truth or bullshit.
Well, that contradicts what you positioned earlier though,
which is that you're just too into the culture,
that you don't care about how you affect the listener,
and that you don't have an audience.
No, no. If you present to a common person something that looks as thin as a human hair
and say this holds a thousand tons,
they're going to say, oh, no way, you're full of shit.
But if you approach an engineer with that,
they'll say, okay, what material is it from?
What alloy is it? Can I do a stress test on it?
What's its thermal coefficient of expansion?
You see the difference in language?
Most people will say, oh, this guy's talking about religion.
That's all bullshit. No, I'm not talking about religion.
Or the opposite. They will drink it down.
Or the Pope's work schedule. I don't know about that.
I calendar when it's Friday, it's Friday.
You see? I've heard that too before.
I don't know what you're talking about, Greek.
When it's Friday, it's Friday.
Someone else will say, wow, no wonder.
I knew there was something wrong with this.
Right.
It's up to you. It's up to them.
But do you care? Never mind that people reject it.
Do you care if people ingest it without understanding it and misapply it?
If they make it conform to their own mental models
in such a way that your apparent truth becomes their bullshit that they believe in.
I don't have an apparent truth.
What I'm doing is just bringing up the obvious that anyone can see.
Yeah, but that's part of the cult leader dynamic thing again.
No, it's not. There is no cult that brings up anything obvious.
No, but they tell their followers that they are, that this is obvious, this is true.
I never say that this is true.
No, you say that you will find out that this is true, which is equivalent.
That's even more kind of…
Yeah, I don't promote myself as a truther or having the truth like that.
I don't promote that at all.
You will find these things to be true if A, B and C, of course.
If you're mentally modeled.
Not all mental modeling is bad.
How is that not saying that they're true, though,
by saying you will find these things to be true at some point?
Yeah, or you might have found it to be in the past, and here's a little more on that.
Not all mental modeling is bad, by the way.
If you don't know a particular language and you're operating what they call an engine-driven wagon,
and you come to an intersection and you see a red octagon with some scribble language you don't understand,
the mental model is that that's a stop sign in any country, you see.
You see what I mean? That's okay, isn't it?
I suppose, but it's within the context of the whole culture, so is anything okay?
No, it's the context within the driving culture.
If you're behind the wheel of a car, which is basically a moving weapon,
if you don't think a car is a moving weapon, you're watching misfortunate things that happen with them.
No, I know that painfully from experience.
No matter where you are in the world, the car being a moving weapon is agreed upon,
even though it's not discussed, right?
No matter where you are in the world.
People will get out of the way of a car, regardless of what race, creed, color or age you are,
so that's understood.
You don't need to see it happen.
No.
So in this case, what I'm saying is that you are being run over with doubt,
with things that are doubtful, like the Pope's work schedule, that you're a filter bag with pressure.
You want to go on and on and on, eating seasonally, by the way.
I don't know if you've ever heard me describe that.
Yeah, I have.
Very important.
It cannot be proven in a lab, by the way.
It can be, if it's done relatively so, but not under a microscope.
So these things that people consider – see, again, if your physical body is in shambles,
you're not going to be concerned about anything else.
That's why torture is effective, right?
That's why they use torture, you see, because they know that they can overcome the being
if they submit them to trauma and pain.
So you need to be comfortable.
You need to be in a comfort zone and healthy.
Relaxed.
Consider, yes, or actually excited.
For example, in sports, you're very excited if you're playing the sport
and understanding a higher level of the gameplay while you're under tension.
You ask a footballer or someone, is he relaxed?
Hell no, when he's running for the line.
If he took a class on how to be a better runner, he's going to try to recall those things then under stress.
Like, for example, the police never talk to the police.
I mean, you just be polite.
You never interact with them on a level that, you see, is that stressful or relaxed?
Well, it's stressful, but you seek being relaxed because they're trained to sense tension.
So every situation is different.
That's why I bring up the things that I do and the modalities that I do in a shotgun.
What do you call it when one thing gets hit after another?
Shotgun style or buckshot, you know, when it's just…
Spray and pray.
Whatever, yeah.
I bring that up just to show that none of these things can be compartmentalized exactly,
with exactness in reality.
But, again, if anyone wants to do the effort, again, I do reports and put things together,
and I know how much work it takes.
When I mentioned to you when you sent the email, someone had actually done a 24-page with a table of contents critique.
I'd say about maybe 100 words were accurate, and the rest was what he heard, not listened to.
But you know what it's like to write 24 pages, finally edit it, and create a table of context?
Even a professional writer, that's more than a day or two's worth of work.
And an amateur could take a week or a month.
I don't know.
So I didn't really poo-poo the person because of their accuracy, but I actually admired the effort behind it.
This person actually could have been doing something else with that much energy.
How much energy?
So that means that this really affected this person enough to dedicate that.
And I was impressed by that, you see.
The email's rubbish.
Well, is it, though?
Because they may have misunderstood, but nonetheless, you communicated that to them.
Technically speaking, you can, but it might not be the best idea to just put it down to their impaired faculties for understanding.
You see what I mean?
Whatever the person hears is what we have communicated.
So if everyone that was listening to your stream came up with the version that this person echoed back at you, you would want to know that.
If everyone did, I would apologize for being alive.
I would actually get my vocal cords torn out so I never sound the same.
Years ago, I had some friends, acquaintances that were police.
And the uncle had a retirement party, and they invited me over.
And they said, Greek, when are you going to have a son?
So we'll take care of him.
We'll bring him into the force.
We'll make sure he's a cop.
And I said, if I had a son and he grew up and told me he wanted to be a cop, I would cut my nuts off and donate them to science for them to tell me what went wrong.
And they all just looked at me, and some of them smiled.
Now, did I mean that to offend them?
Mostly, yes.
I didn't mean to offend, but I was so taken aback by the thought of that, you see.
Sure.
But somebody else might have said that they would have kicked his ass, right, like they say, right?
I don't know.
But I know for sure there's about a half a dozen people out there that are able to implement what I'm saying to their benefit.
Right.
Right?
Okay.
So I think I've given the example with the fishermen and others with cooking and healing modalities.
Once you understand the body is under a biological vacuum, you can do a thought experiment.
You're familiar with synthesized materials that appear to be, like, organic, like carbon fiber could be bone.
A sheet of silicone of a certain durometer rating could be like skin.
Certain silicone tubes could represent arteries, and certain silicone with fibrous material could represent muscle.
And certain warm liquids with 40 percent solids could represent blood.
Go ahead and assemble a figure of a human and put all those together with a pressurized pump in the middle.
You know what it's going to look like?
It's a massive mess.
It will not function.
Now, if you put a vacuum on it, yes, it will appear more like you see.
Are they applying this with their synthetic sex robots, do you think?
No, those are just the skin, I'm presuming.
No, they don't.
These people, you know, I've heard someone ask, what about artificial intelligence?
They don't even have natural intelligence.
You're concerned about their artificial?
It's a malevolent tool.
Just like they have lasers that if you put it on a human, it senses the temperature.
You pull the trigger, and it shoots.
But if your laser is not on the human, it senses the temperature.
You pull the trigger, no bullet comes out.
That's so you don't waste bullets.
Right.
Oh, that's so smart, is it?
What benefit is that technology to what?
Save bullets to kill more people?
You're sick people.
You see?
How about putting that same sensing technology in all your cars, so there are no more car accidents?
Even if you want to go ram the car into another car sideways, the car will not allow you to do it.
Right.
What about that?
You ever think of that?
Yeah.
No.
Why?
You're sick.
Sick society.
So how would you define benefit, then, in context of what you're doing?
Like, what benefits?
I hated eating rice.
I never even thought of cooking it.
I heard it.
I tried it.
Now I love it.
Not examples, but a definition of what you hope to achieve.
Living a life with more efficiency and with less pain, suffering, and ignorance.
Because, like, what's the benefit of that?
Do you remember I mentioned earlier, some people eat at a restaurant and they don't feel good
because you find out that the cook has an anger problem?
Yeah.
Well, you can't show proof scientifically that an angry cook will make food that will make you sick, can you?
No.
Okay.
If you know a certain knowledge, if you know that you can't keep time with the Pope's work schedule,
then the plants, the bees, the whales, everything, the bacteria, nothing works on that,
and you are working in that field, this is an example again, perhaps,
you need to start recording moon movements to understand how these plants are going to repeat on their cycles.
You had no clue about that.
Yes, you had a clue about the moon and you had a clue about time, but you didn't know how to put it together.
You know what it's like?
It's like the Rubik's Cube.
Do you remember that?
Yeah, I remember that.
How about I gave you a methodology that no matter what position it's in, you solve it in less than 30 seconds every time?
Mm-hmm.
You could probably make some money as a teenager.
Not even that.
In other words, does that seem like a problem to you?
No, never.
In other words, people buy it because it keeps them busy for a long time.
Look, I did it.
Got you.
Or look, look what I could do.
I could do it faster than you.
After a while, it just becomes, let's move to the next thing.
Mm-hmm.
You know, if you've got a sore throat when the winter comes or the weather is changing,
do you have that little think bulb with a question mark like they do in the cartoons over here,
or do you have to say, I better stop eating tropical foods right now?
Okay, you kind of lost me with the thread because of the tune there.
Bringing benefit, bringing harmony, peace and harmony to the planet.
It sounded like...
No, the planet doesn't want you here.
That's the thing.
You're an unwanted guest at this point.
Not because you're drilling and toxifying the planet and all this.
It's because of the way you deal with each other.
I don't think you've...
I haven't talked about that.
This is more of the spiritual side in the years ago.
The reason why the earth is the way it is negatively is because of the way people treat each other.
Not because you're drilling oil and polluting.
The earth can transmute that.
If you're a real evil society, the earth will create pollution even if you never lit a campfire.
The earth is a sentient being.
I'm not going to get into that right now.
That's too evolved.
I'm not saying that you can't handle it, but you have to give background from scripture on that.
You know there are scriptures that address the earth and the moon and the sun and do not address you?
The scripture is for them?
No.
Why would you write a poem to a doorknob if the doorknob couldn't understand it?
Yeah, I don't have a problem with the earth as a sentient being,
but neither do millions of people that you would scorn as new age morons, probably rightly.
See what I'm saying?
It's not exactly radical.
It can become radical in the right context.
Not that I'm in favor of radicalism either, but this was all about a harmonious existence.
It sounds as though what you want to help bring about is a harmonious existence for human beings,
like you said, a reduction of suffering.
So you're certainly not going to find any argument from me with that.
The way you help is by first stopping them from complaining and taking control with knowledge.
Why does this car not start in the morning when I want to go to work?
Well, maybe because the spark plugs need to be changed.
Okay, practical knowledge, but at what point does practical knowledge...
It's all practical.
Well, knowledge of the gods is not practical for most people.
It's too bad.
There's an overlap there, for sure.
Obviously, you're talking out, you're pointing out with the scripture,
but if you give people knowledge about how to cook rice, they can apply.
It's very simple.
It doesn't become this big identity thing of I'm the guy who cooks rice properly.
It's just a thing, right?
Same with the car and all the rest of it.
But if you give people knowledge about the gods, the lateral realm of the gods,
the end times, the Middle East,
that's definitely something for the identity to hook into and invest in
and spin a whole narrative that makes their sense of who they are
much more exciting and meaningful, illegitimately, I would say.
Maybe I'm one of the chosen few.
I know that you try and counter those delusions,
but you may be feeding them with one hand
and then trying to take away that with the other hand, is what I'm suggesting.
Back in the days of Florsheim Shoes, when I walked in New York,
we had a meeting with some of the corporate.
They said, we're never going to replace our inventory boys with a real-time computer.
I know it sounds ridiculous, right?
Yeah.
So your point being that knowledge of the gods is not something to be skeptical about.
It's going to happen anyway.
The CEOs of that shoe company said we're never going to fire the 2,500 people
whose task is to do inventory, to replace it with a machine.
But did they?
Yeah, but that came about through people applying themselves and creating the hardware.
The Middle East Union will come about by people applying themselves to it, yes.
Right.
And the intervention of the gods is going to come about regardless,
regardless of what we do, I presume.
That's right.
Right.
So why do we need to know about it?
I don't know.
That's a personal problem or a personal interest.
Well, I mean, I'm very interested in it.
Like I said, I love this stuff.
I'm like a pig in shit in this stuff, right?
It's not hard for me to believe and even try and live that belief, but I question the value.
You know what belief is?
Yeah.
Belief is based on knowledge, yeah.
And action.
Yes, if it doesn't take place, that was not a good belief.
If it does take place, that was a good belief.
Okay, well this actually points to one of the questions in my email,
which whether you considered it relevant, I don't know.
We'll find out.
But about prophecy and how you said that prophecy is the way to confirm the reality or the validity of the scripture.
And I asked, well, how do you know the difference between, you know,
the gods predicting the future and human beings believing in the scripture
and therefore bringing about the prophecy?
Oh, easy.
Easy.
And I've said that before.
It's because the human beings don't understand the scriptures.
Well, what if they do, then?
How do you know that they don't?
Yeah, that's a what if.
What if pigs would fly?
They don't.
No.
You can't answer that.
You can't answer it in that way.
They don't understand the scriptures.
How do you know that?
That's clear.
How do you know that there aren't social engineering groups that have done the work that you've done and applied it?
They don't know.
They're not out there.
They don't.
It's very simple.
Okay, explain it.
Because what you do, Sherlock Holmes, is you go, you hear about the condition.
Let's say the condition is the humans are using it as a blueprint, I believe is the terminology used for memory.
Yeah.
Then let's start investigating.
Let's start calling these groups.
And who do you know that might be able to get you information on that?
How would you know who the groups were, though?
And after about five years of researching that, I found out that they don't know anything about scripture.
But you're assuming that all the groups are public and they're in the phone book.
No, I didn't.
No, not at all.
What do you mean?
They're actually quite easy to contact.
Yeah, but what about the possibility of groups and individuals who are not?
Public knowledge, who are operating secretly.
They don't know.
In other words, the people that are captains of industry and the different various levels of government you have,
you know, the public one and the private one and then the very deep one that's heavily occulted,
that's been continuous for thousands of years, they don't know scripture either.
How do you know that?
Well, let me just say I'm going to keep those cards close to my chest until the future.
And how about if I say if we get to know each other a little bit better,
I'll share some of that validatable information with you.
That's a big carrot.
Yeah, it's a big carrot, but let's just say even if we're not in touch, you will find out on your own.
I mean, why take that position at all?
I guess you could say, being honest, if you actually know this, this is a conundrum with a lot of your stuff.
Well, what I will tell you, this is what I have discovered.
Let me just give a little bit on this.
What they do know is that the gods do exist and they have primacy, they are in control.
But they do not know anything about the gods in terms of what's going to be happening in prophecy.
And the ones that do know are ignored and it's viewed as a pet.
Oh, pat you on the back, that sounds good, we'll consider it and it goes off to the side.
So do you see a problem in presenting knowledge of this kind and then basically falling back on,
I know and you don't, but eventually you'll find out.
Or if we know each other well enough, I'll tell you how I know.
Never.
You don't see that that presents a problem?
No, like for example, some of the things that I'm speaking on now,
I would have never spoken about five years ago, or three years ago.
Right.
Ever, at all.
But in the meantime.
And if I am speaking in the future, I will say things that I would not say right now.
But where does that leave me, for example, in the meantime?
Like either I trust you, slash believe you, or I don't.
Yeah, that's fine.
There isn't much in between, right?
That's the same thing when you go to these big movie cineplexes.
Which movie do you go and sit down?
The one that you like and trust will give you a good time.
Okay.
I mean, you're talking about why do I need to convince someone
whether their personal preferences are viable or valid to them.
That's irrelevant.
No, why you feel the need to assert that you know something,
and then withhold any kind of explanation about how you could know it.
No, I'm not withholding it.
You could actually look and see the scripture itself.
Wait, wait, wait, wait a minute.
No, no, because you're talking about actually being in touch with the Illuminati.
What you do is you glean from it.
Like I have them in my cell phone.
There is no such thing as Illuminati by the way.
Yeah, I know.
I was being ironic.
There is no such thing as Freemasons.
A bunch of people like to take pictures with an apron and eat pork at a banquet.
Did you grow up in an environment of social engineering,
let's say aristocratic social engineering or anything of that kind?
I'm neither going to confirm or deny that.
Okay.
Well, I did.
I mean, I'm public about it.
I grew up in a Fabian environment.
I didn't know it.
It was all kind of under the radar.
But eventually I found it out.
Yeah, and they don't know much.
They know enough about their traditions.
But if you ask them what their traditions are based on,
it falls apart very quickly like a cheap sweater.
You know a cheap sweater, if you find one thread,
you keep pulling on it, the whole sweater disappears, right?
Okay.
Well, I don't know.
I don't know how much they knew.
My impression is that they were just drunken, traumatized, dysfunctional human beings,
basically groping their way through.
So now there is specialized information.
There you go.
Yeah, but that does tell me that the mainstream alternate media narratives about Illuminati
and all the rest of it are both bogus and true.
Those are traditions now.
A lot of the data points are accurate, Tavistock and so on and so forth.
I've more or less confirmed them myself.
But the actual narrative is bogus, right?
Yeah, but hold on.
Let me interject while this thought just came up from the ether.
Go online and put in on YouTube.
I call it YouTube University sometimes.
The New Order of Barbarians.
Dr. Day did a speech in 1968 to a group of pediatricians in Pittsburgh,
and it was very prophetic because he was discussing about what the future of this culture will be like,
and he's mentioning things like videotapes, which didn't exist to the public at that time,
and various things that you see happening now.
And he didn't want to state the people.
And these are basically industrialists, right?
In other words, homosexuality was going to be used as a method of population control.
Food was going to be used as a method of population control.
Human rights, diminishing certain things and accentuating others, right?
So in other words, if you want to do population control, you promote sexuality, not diminish it.
Yeah, I understand.
This is part of the Fabian thing, and that was my family business, was the food industry.
So anyway, yeah, he's definitely talking about stuff that's relevant to me.
Listen to The New Order of Barbarians, 1968,
and you'll see these are things that have been happening in the past decade that did not exist in 1968.
So there is a group behind the scenes.
Yeah, okay.
And they're very efficient in terms of social engineering, let's say.
Not very efficient.
But they do get the job done.
Well, okay, so what's the difference?
Oh, I see.
The difference is your car is broken down, it barely got you to work, it's overheating and all that.
It got you to work inefficiently, not like a new...
It took you twice as long.
Okay.
It's taking them twice as long to get it done.
But they're getting it done.
It's like beating a nail with the heel of a thick shoe instead of a hammer.
By the standards of the average person about what is possible in terms of social engineering,
they're unbelievably efficient, hence you have these exaggerated narratives of the Illuminati
who micromanage every aspect of society, right?
They're not micromanaging it.
That's what I'm saying.
But they understand certain levers in the human psyche and the crowd psyche by which you push the levers.
Eventually you get this result, like you said, about promoting sexuality as a way to have a counterintuitive result.
If you can push it for long enough, then you'll see the results.
Yes, because in certain cultures you had sex to procreate.
Now they wanted more sex, but distract them from the concept of procreation by making other things more available.
Also, if you were to consider, let's say, how efficient is it being done, it's not going to be done, whether it's inefficient or efficient,
to disturb what I've been laying out about the coming Middle East Union and the arrival of what I call the mop-up crew, right?
No.
It's not going to affect that.
Have you ever heard me say when you go out in public and say you're doing this to make the world a better place,
you have both the malevolent entities against you and the benevolent against you?
The malevolent because they never want to see it, but the benevolent because they know it's time to wrap it up and shut this guy up anyway.
You see?
Yes.
So that's being objective. That's neither here nor there.
And that's something that people can only contemplate and cannot promote as forming a group or anything around that,
because it sounds irrational to an irrational group.
See, when you go to a group that's irrational, not capable of rational thinking, anything rational will seem irrational to them, right?
It has to be irrational for it to resonate, like two tuning forks.
A 400 hertz will not resonate a 432, but you see, 432s do.
It still seems there must be an element of faith in your position.
There are many faiths, and then there is the faith in what?
The faith in what?
The faith in what is that there is a realistic attitude one can take that based on one's relative length of their life, right?
That you seem things are a long time, and to an oak tree that's 400 years old, it's not.
Can you transcend your own sensory and temporal limitations by doing what?
Considering what's been memorialized from the past.
Consider it first.
Scientifically, you must examine without contamination, right?
You don't mean by contamination.
Bringing in things that will change what it's supposed to be.
And the answer is, I'm telling you, very few people and statistically no one is examining what's been memorialized in the past with objectivity.
Yes, you could say, well, Greek, there's a lot of history and universities that do teach all that, but I'm telling you, it's all revised and it's bullshit.
You know, when you go to university, the real stuff is in the library archive.
The textbooks are bullshit.
They change from season to season and from decade to decade radically.
And you know, one of the inspirations of speaking and using the term moron was when I was involved more in the physics side of things about a decade ago.
They started hitting all these young students, graduate students, with stuff like muons, leptons, bouons and gluons and all this.
I said, that's for morons. Rhymes with morons.
The cult of bumping particles.
I had Bruce recently read the curriculum at MIT nuclear physics.
He was kind of all over the place, but if you poignantly look at the graduate program, it's all about that Schrodinger's cat, Schrodinger's equation.
That's like cheap mysticism.
That's like gumball machine level mysticism.
This is your future.
In other words, that the society, yes or no, does it or does it not expect the new crop of university graduates to be the leaders and workers of cognitive thinking and industry?
Yes, they do.
Believe it or not, in large industries, especially that are important, they won't hire you unless you have that background.
Then once you get into higher level stuff, they spirit you away or whisk you away for training to get all that shit out of your mind and show you how it really works.
What really is going on.
The other thing I've mentioned is that the common man, the average man, you brought this up, they have their own personal interests, whether they're a mail carrier, a cook, work in a thrift store, whatever.
When they want to learn about the solar system, they are trusting that the specialists in that are giving them correct information.
I'm telling you they're not.
When the average person wants to know about the human body, I'm telling you the medical technicians you're going to do not know.
So where do you go then?
I go to their stuff. If I want to know about astrophysics, I don't listen to what publications they're putting out in Astrophysics Daily or what they're in the textbook.
I want to go back to the archives. Very simple.
When you look at the NIH, National Institute of Health, on viruses, they have a very long PDF, almost a thousand pages.
You think if you read that, you'll know everything about viruses.
Well, hold on a second. I'll look at the illustrations, then I'll go to the conclusion.
If the conclusion states, even after all this research, we still do not know what a virus is, why the hell would you put your faith in that document?
Right.
You see?
I'm not talking from a heuristic point of view.
Certain developers, let's say in the early days of rocketry and airplanes, they used to use heuristics to make as many failures as possible, quickly, and document them.
So when they're developing, they know not to do those things because it leads to failure, you see?
Right.
So actually they're being paid to fail, to document what doesn't work, to start narrowing it down to what might.
So is that what the gods are doing now?
Beyond that.
Well, the gods have declared exactly how it's going to go down before they even started.
And then they're making adjustments.
Just like an airplane going from London to New York knows exactly where they're going and how they're going to get there, but they might have to make some adjustments, you see?
Well, because it corresponds with my own... how I look back at my life at 50 is basically a series of failures, like just a string of...
If you remember what they were, you'll recognize them if they were to appear in a way that they were effectual, in other words, going to affect you, right?
You're going to compensate, aren't you?
Yes.
Course correction, you mean?
Yeah.
But also there's something to be gained simply from failing and accepting failure, you know, as distinct from regret or remorse or recrimination.
It depends what accepting is.
Well, accepting is something that's determining my orientation as much deeper than my conscious decisions, let's say.
Have you memorialized enough details about that failure so when, if you were to approach it again, you have enough detail, so now knowledge of the failure is beneficial by avoiding it, you see, versus a general wishy-washy,
well, this might lead to failure, I've seen it before, but let's do it anyway, you see what I mean?
Yeah. No, I think to testify to that, that's why I can't separate the personal from the not, because my testifying is a lot about my personal.
You can never separate the personal, but what I'm saying, what I have, one of the crux of the Greek-speak is that take control of your personal attributes.
How many times have you heard me say that any field you're interested in is wide open?
I've heard you say it.
Yeah, and it is. But if you start looking at all the bullshit they're putting in front of you, like in science,
oh, you can't do this new thing because it requires a million-dollar laboratory. They're pulling the wool over your eyes.
Yeah, but in another sense it's not wide open because it's so tightly controlled in terms of how to actually...
Ah, I'm not talking about the social aspect, I'm talking about the field itself. How many times...
Exploring it, you mean, yeah.
Where knowledge is its own reward, like a wealthy guy says, Greek, you know, when you, when the Middle East Union comes together,
I'll back you up and we'll do a major thing, and he says, by the way, if you're so smart, how come you have no money?
And I said, by the way, you have so much money, how come you're not so smart?
Right, that's funny.
You see?
Touché.
Because knowledge is its own reward.
Yeah.
Knowledge, and this is what the ancient Platonics and a lot of the ancient philosophers, if you look at them in proper context,
now there is none, by the way. Students and people of philosophy now are idiots, and I could say that proudly, by the way, that they are idiots.
Not to their personal fault, they've been hoodwinked.
Proud of what, though?
Proud to say that these people are morons. In other words, the... your head intellectual...
In other words, anyone can say this once they've researched it.
When I say this, it sounds like this is a real cocky guy, and he doesn't know what he's talking about,
because we're a modern society, and our intellectuals, philosophers, and top scientists are brilliant.
I'm telling you, they're not.
Mm-hmm.
And I could say that with confidence.
Right.
You see?
Easily.
With yourself as a counterpoint, you mean.
Yeah, well, can you... do you remember... well, not only myself, a child can do it with a minimal amount of tools.
Have you ever heard of the Emperor Has No Clothes story? Are you familiar with that?
Yes, of course.
It was the... who was it that exposed what was really going on?
Yes, it was a child, yeah.
Yes, not the officers and the wise men, was it?
Mm-hmm. And I don't think the child was making a big to-do about it either, and thinking how smart he was.
No, but his reward was the given.
What was his reward? I don't remember that.
The given. Well, the reward was a self thing that you know that he's naked.
You know, yeah.
He's naked.
So he would have known that without pointing it out, though.
Yeah, where's the reward in going to a restaurant and having a meal that's too salty,
and telling the waitress, you have a new cook that tends to eat too many sweets constantly? Where's the reward in that?
Well, you know not to go to that restaurant again, and you know that you have the sensitivity to notice something like that.
That has value. And you've done your civil duty.
Yeah, but the meal was not pleasant, though, was it?
No, but that was a mistake, right?
Well, it was unforeseeable.
Yeah, it was unforeseeable.
Because you didn't know until it was too late.
Just like I used to have a saying, what does Greek-speak and heavy artillery have in common?
Once you hear it, it's too late, right?
Mm-hmm.
Okay, anyway.
Right, once you hear the guns going off, then you don't have time to, yeah, it's too late.
So I give my time generously when I can.
If I can't, I let you know I can't speak or I can't be around or whatever.
But again, I think what's been put out is whether it's for someone's benefit or not, I cannot be attached to it.
And what I can report on is that I have gotten reports back that it has benefited a handful of people.
Now, one might even go to the extreme and say, well, those are not real people.
That's actually a bot AI computer from NSA playing with you Greek.
Mm-hmm.
Right?
I suppose, yeah.
You suppose, right?
So how much are we going to speculate on and how much are we going to really take as fact?
It would still be a response, even if it was a bot.
Yeah, so in the meantime, food, clothing, shelter, why bother?
Don't get caught up in all of these mass cultish things that if you have the choice.
See, what I'm doing also is allowing people to – you know how many times you have so many choices but you really don't have a choice?
Like you'll have one food conglomerate that owns many other food, right?
And you think you're going to – but it's really the same.
What I'm doing is showing people that in a world where you think you have choices where you really don't, you really do.
Right.
Because now you're operating parallel to it and not in it.
There's a big difference between being on one of the lanes in the highway or being on the footpath parallel to the highway.
Right.
You'll get run over and you see on the other one it's more pleasant.
It's still pretty unpleasant, but yeah.
Yeah, because of the pollution, yeah.
The noise.
But you know when the rush hour is over, right?
It never is.
That's right.
It's 24-7.
Because when you're sleeping someone else is going to work on the other side, let's say, right?
And this is a constant.
It's trampled on.
The reality is being trampled on.