I wasn't so sure about this RKX thing, but AIX is certainly worth looking into.
I'm most impressed that Jason is not going to tell you something, he's going to show you.
RKX shows us if you record enough facts, the answers just stare you in the face.
A man who knows the facts is unafraid to joust with contrary opinions. That's Jason.
I can't have that dude on my show.
You know how many guys I've had on here who are running from that dude? Be a mess.
Jason says being wrong gets us closer to being right.
You've got to break free or die trying, guys.
RKX showed me how to see if there was a tater in them onions.
Listen, RKX isn't one guy against the Matrix, that's dumb. No, it's a family of souls waking up.
If I've learned anything since finding RKX, if something is true somewhere, it's probably true everywhere.
Jason said if it's true, we can see it from multiple different vantage points.
So, I broke pattern and went up there and slapped that guy. Total pattern break.
If you get stumped, you've got to break pattern.
Jason says you don't need to know how to read, you need to know how to think. I think that's where I went wrong.
Jason figured it out. People are smart and they can decide for themselves if something is true or not.
No, I don't have anything to hide. I just don't want Jason anywhere near my accounting files.
There's a bunch of us who don't listen to RKX. We signed a different deal. I think it's AIX or something.
We block all those who claim we are censoring content.
We are not harvesting your data, creating dossiers on the public, and selling your info.
Why would we do such a thing?
Seeing the Easter Island pictures of art next to the Gobekli Tepe art is all I had to see.
As a chief legislator, that's all a trier fact needs to see to know Gobekli Tepe is nowhere near as old as they are claiming.
That Jason showed that the Zodiac isn't even old, that the Greeks invented it, blew my mind.
I'm a Christian now and our scriptures tell us that stuff's evil.
Jason was publishing about the Mayan long count not ending in 2012, way back before 2012.
This dude is shaking the nest.
His discoveries on calendars and ancient moon and day count calendars is putting some of these guys to shame.
Remember, we are actors. We are paid to lie. We are rich because we are good at what we do.
Anyone at this point who can't see that the Jews copied Babylonian tablets to write Genesis is blind.
Jason's Dark Scriptures playlist shows this perfectly.
The New Testament is a collection of forged texts put together centuries after the events they depict.
This guy has called the entire ancient aliens community to debate.
Like Tyson, they ain't getting in the ring.
Jason says one who is properly informed is not easily deceived.
I would like to see Jimmy Corsetti or Matthew LaCroix debate Jason about this Atlantis dating issue.
No one's real key interested in Bill Carson's opinion anymore.
His findings on the procession hoax, the change of the year from 360 days to 365 man,
this changes everything in archaeoastronomy.
You know, I'm not a doctor. I have no medical background. I'm an actor.
And even I know Atlantis was the 13th century B.C.
Jason has dropped massive data sets on the Old Testament, not even being old, but from the Greek era.
You think we took you for a ride? Wait till the new Christian Reich takes control.
It won't be American, and it sure ain't Christian.
I couldn't believe it. I mean, you know, when Jason showed that the Jewish calendar was completely made up,
I mean, you know, damn, how are we going to know what year it is now?
Yeah, the shah being a day and not a year totally murders a lot of books out there.
That's the reason these guys don't want to talk. Jason killed their little pet theories.
It all came true. Jason said I was going to be a part of fake news, just like Billy Carson.
I tried to sniff Jason one time, but Big John stopped me. I think Jason would have been into it, though.
Don't forget we are actors. We are paid to lie. We are rich because we are good at what we do.
Hello, family. Let's get that audio check done real quick. Got a special guest in the house.
I'm eager to bring him forth. He came with pretty high recommendations.
I know there's some crossover. There's several of you that already know who he is.
Sounds good. Thank you. Awesome.
Hiya, Victoria.
Victoria, I could not believe on Twitter that you did not make a comment
under that little discovery I made in Hesiod's Theogony.
Come on now. Hesiod specifically said 27 centuries ago
that the Phoenix duration was nine times that of the life of a raven.
You better look up how long a raven lives because we got 138 again.
How did you not see that, Victoria? How did you not comment on that?
You of all people. That's all right. I forgive you.
Without further ado, guys, the audio is great.
I'm going to introduce the Greek.
He's got his partner. He's got an online buddy. They do a lot of presentations together.
I can't remember exactly what they call them, but they're unique.
A lot of people tune into this. We're going to go ahead and introduce him right now.
His contact information is in the description box.
Several people have mentioned that he's very knowledgeable on the topics he discusses.
Out-of-the-box thinker. That's exactly what Archaics is about.
We don't give a damn about people being right or wrong.
It's all about thinking outside the box and making people stretch out of their comfort zones
to look at some of the information that has been presented to us
so we can understand the difference between fact and fiction.
Or at least when we're being told something, we can always understand that there's more to the story.
Without further ado, we're going to add the Greek. How are you doing, sir?
Oh, great. Greetings, Jason, and greetings to your listenership.
Thanks for having me.
Awesome. I see you have Charles Ocelli, somebody you've done many presentations with in our chat right now.
Can you give us a little background about what you and he have done before we go into other topics about just your work?
Sure. On the work aspect, we started a project about eight years ago called Ocelli and the Greek we met on American Freedom Radio.
I've been calling in and was a fixture on many of the early radio platforms in the heyday of the Internet, like 2010 to 2013-14.
So we met later on and decided to do a little collaboration. We're kind of like Laurel and Hardy and Abbott and Costello.
People listen and they wonder if these two guys really like each other, but they sure put on a pretty good sonic event, right?
And there's no rules. We pretty much covered our first series was about, I think, 20 or so presentations on 20 different subjects, two hours each.
And kind of like shook a lot of people and how the moral of the current.
OK, the current project you will find on Ocelli.com. It's called Rated Y, the Unculting of Humanity.
Right. And we can explain that. And that's pretty much the project. I'm very much not a public figure. I don't want to be.
I have all of I think we have all of like six listeners. It's more than that.
But, you know, and I believe sort of like, you know, the word coincidence, coincidence means to coincide with.
If you're meant to hear what we're talking about, you'll you'll be there. We don't really promote that much.
I'm not saying don't come. Of course, come. But, you know, it's it'll just if it happens, it happens because I'm going to be doing these things anyway.
I'm not doing them to make public presentations. So it's a very different point of view.
The main crux, the main crux of my discussion is that everything you need to know, you must start with an arm's reach of five feet of within your reach, visible reach and just reaching out your arms and gain and gain and glean as much definition of that around you.
The other basic premise is that all subjects, all fields of study are still wide open medicine, law, science, chronology, every all wide open.
What's been going on is the common people have their common jobs. And if they want to extend and learn about another field, they go to a, quote unquote, expert in any field.
And I found out more than 30 years ago that these experts don't know any more than most people. And they're telling you a story. And we're going to you're speaking my language.
And now we're going to uncover that simply by going back to the reference materials that have been memorialized that they're supposed to subscribe to.
We're talking about medical, legal, scientific, cultural history.
Another thing we do.
I use a lot of the term lawful people you know they don't understand that when I'll be bringing that up if something is lawful or not lawful is an agreement, and a body of work even an idea that you can gain without engaging in commerce you don't have to buy anything right.
So for example, once you learn that a triangle has three sides.
And that's how it's defined and you pick up a book on geometry and it's telling you it has four sides well that's not a lawful book.
Right. That's right. Now, one of the main things that I've been doing is lawful timekeeping and this is your, by the way, by the way, okay.
I just I just want to stop for my got to say this.
The crux of your work that I've noticed that's that I need to just say the periodicity of the Phoenix the periodicity of what might be called nemesis x and what and the periodicity of what might be called the dark satellite.
Okay, let me just say this. Thank you.
Okay. When I heard that and they saw what you presented I said okay, I don't know what else he's doing but he did that work for me.
You know, I mean, when you hear something that you you know has been checked out like a math problem you can run it backwards and forwards.
And it's like you actually I don't know the guy but he did that work for me so thank you.
So, basically, lawful I got into a lot of lawful timekeeping because I also get into a lot of biblical stuff, and not like you know what you're talking about which I might contend with to a small degree but overall I see what you're doing.
When I get into biblical stuff it's not from a religious point of view, maybe we'll continue that. But what's interesting is I found out that right now in terms of timekeeping.
You know I joke around with people like you don't even know what day it is if you ask someone what day it is.
And they say anything between Monday and Friday, you know, Sunday and whatever, and January through December, that's the Pope's work schedule.
I call it the Pope's work schedule. Right, because you have work week and weekend. And in terms of what time it is time of day, they rely on this wind up toy called the clock or the digital derivation you know that thing on the wall that tells
you what you should have time for. Right, that's, that's okay those are not lawful, because let's say you go underground and you come up to the surface or in a coma for three months what day is it.
Can you go outside and see or figure it out or do you need a calendar that you have to buy right or use. Same with the clock. So, from the biblical, let's say, economy and ancient economy, this is what I came up with.
And also I found out that it transpires and crosses over in what's been memorialized in academia. By the way, if you have a secret, and you want to keep it secret, go ahead and publish it and put it in the public library.
That's how you keep it a secret right. Yeah. So, yeah, so what I what I found out was very simple. And this I'm going to give you some old examples and then we'll cross over to academia how it's in their own texts.
For example, for thousands of years, people settled their debts are typically returned home. When the full moon came around.
Right. And it was it was a commercial beacon.
And today, don't you get your billing cycle on a monthly cycle.
Right. It's pretty close.
Because it turned. Yeah. And let me just include this again I'll bounce around a little bit because it's a very parallel thinking kind of thing.
Not only are we looking for something that we don't have to subscribe to some man made thing let's say, or that we have to pay for.
Are we looking at it from a point of view.
That is that that it actually works and is viable.
And what time is for there's no such thing as time time is just how you record events right you could record them however you like.
It has to be also have the timekeeping method you use must have the ability to attain a certain precision and accuracy.
Right. So, how this was done was visibly by putting a stick in the ground.
Right. And when the shadows moved like a sundial is how you kept time, and you can actually keep time this way with shadows. If you extend that stick or lever.
The more you can graduate it. For example, a sundial and you can actually record down to 10,000th of a second and millionth of a second the longer that line extends right you just graduated into more fractions.
So the reason I brought up the full moon, which is the new moon because this is how it was done, because how do you measure the moonlight with a stick in the ground the same way and academics say well you can't use that well of course you can because you
could actually go outside on a moonlit night.
And you could see you know for people that are visually impaired actually see better.
And the shadows are sharper.
So, the full moon is actually the new moon when the month begins.
Right. Now, let's just move forward, what do they call the, the new moon the dark moon.
Now, back in the, from the mid 80s to the early 90s I used to spend a lot of time at the library reading room the main library in New York City and I found out I was in the mezzanine reading room librarian that I was hitting on real cute girl once she says you know this is the room where she
says this is where Tesla used to sit same place. And then this guy Charles Fort used to sit here.
So I was like, Oh, cool. And so, you know, maybe a force that there for 20 something years. Yeah, he was a fixture, and she's a here 14 times because you know you didn't have to buy magazines the library used to have me put them in a big bar you know along the binding part.
So, anyway, I started looking at all these references and part of me was like you've got to have a good memory see most.
See, it's kind of like if things are important you'll remember them, taking notes is important because that's memorialization.
And I started going over this chronological stuff.
And what it seemed like was there was a big diversion a big break, and a turning point.
And I found out just with all my research that everything that could have been known was known by the late 1890s.
And I'm going to get to that. I'll show some proofs on that. Let's go back to lawful timekeeping.
So the full moon is the new moon and why it was called why the dark moon is called the new moon essentially is because in certain Babylonian Egyptian, you know, parts of Egypt and Babylon like sister cities.
And they had the priesthood had degraded to the point of superstition. And when the moon disappeared.
And it was dark. They went to the leader let's say the Pharaoh or the king and kept him in his chambers he wouldn't leave until the Crescent reappeared, because if it didn't reappear what are we going to do.
What if the Pharaoh was out on a trip. Right, so you had to stay in the palace and watch Netflix or whatever, for two or three days till the Crescent reappeared.
So when the Crescent reappeared it meant that the cycle was still going and they called it the new moon.
But the actual way measurements can be taken is only with the full moon, because that will actually cast a shadow over a sundial and then you have its own alignments.
And if you actually look at the Pope's work schedule there's a bunch of drift and intercalation and all that. But if you use the full moon as the first day of the month.
Now you're on your way to how to reckon your months. Now here's one thing that leads to another time must be broken up with precision and accuracy. When does the day start.
Well, I'll just give the day starts at noon.
Hi noon, it doesn't start at sundown doesn't start at midnight, and some Islamic cultures they think it's a dawn.
And how do we how do we reckon that I just without giving an explanation I'll tell you the, the level of precision, again, that is attained at the marker is the most high at noon.
The other thing is if you look, let's say from things that have been memorialized go to the book of Genesis.
There was evening there was morning the first day and that's repeated.
Okay evening or the word edit, let's say, when does it, when does evening begin or the evening when things are even. And when does it begin at noon, and it ends when morning ends when does morning end at noon.
And pretty much when you carry over on other cultures, you will see that everything of all of this has been put away and it's either sundown.
Now when you see sundown like for example in the Jewish economy. They consider sundown to be the end of the day but how do you reckon that there's, there's no way to precisely reckon that.
For example, in India, even today you could look up India sundials and some of them are as big as a house to measure moonlight and daylight.
So, if you look at the academic vernacular in astronomy one on one.
They will say that the day starts at solar noon. But for the people, it's civil midnight. That's kind of like when they started writing dictionaries, they didn't know how to define words.
So they wrote something like for example in the old dictionaries oats. It's what we feed the horses in England but it's the staple of the people of Scotland, right, so put down right.
So, when you look at any of the timekeeping authority websites is think it's the one in Colorado Springs Naval Observatory, and then Greenwich meantime, try to find where they talk about Julian calendar time and you will see that they profess the day starts
at solar noon.
So basically the lawful timekeeping works around that. Now if you want to go back to a biblical reference let's say in the book of Nehemiah I think it's chapter seven and chapter 13 you get two examples of it being at solar noon.
The first example is Nehemiah is complaining that the people are still coming into the city with commercial activity on the Sabbath has begun, because look under the gate, it's dark under the gate.
Right, so the Sabbath started now most people will say well that's just a gate well the gate meant the city wall and those walls are about 12 foot thick, and it's oriented east, north, south.
So the only way you can have darkness under that shadow that archway that masonary archway is if the sun is directly overhead, because if it's early in the morning the sun is coming through.
And if it's late in the afternoon at sundown the sun is coming through again. Right. Only at noon. Now, how do we look at it on another chapter.
He says, Do not open the city gates until they get hot I want them to get hot, and the Sabbath will be over then open them right and that can't be sundown because the heat done already came and went, and it can't be morning well if you saying that in the morning you have to wait around till noon again.
So there's these little hints that you'll find in literary works have been memorialized a very popular one that gets people sort of in the generation that I'm in I was born in the mid 60s, is when you before the electronic banking convention.
When you went to a bank bank and gave a check to the teller. After 12 o'clock.
She counted it as the next day.
I don't know if you ever remember doing banking before any electronic convention but anyone who's more than 50 or 60 years old will remember that.
So these, these, this is more of the lawful chrononomy like you're a chronologist, which is knowledge of time.
So let me interject because you are saturating us with so much information, you're like me on my presentations on thing when I'm when I'm going off.
This is it's awesome but I need to interject on one thing there is confirmatory evidence and what you're saying, at least in some cultures of the world that that noon was the beginning of the day, in that people went to sleep.
When the sun was the highest and hottest in the sky in Middle Eastern cultures. That's when people went to sleep, they went to sleep during the day. And when the when it started getting cooler in our evening, the, the progression of their day.
That's when they got up. They all had their little their meal, they got they got a whole lot of work done. And then, um, it was the siestas they still do them in Europe.
Yes, many, many parts of the world just too hot, too hot to be active, active, or from noon to six o'clock in the evening, and that's when they actually slept. So it's a, it's very interesting.
Absolutely, if you if you observe the culture will always reflect what's being taught.
Give you an example in the Pacific Rim islands in the turn of the 20th century a lot of Christian missions were going to these islands.
When they landed they discovered the population, everyone was topless. By the way, in a society like that the men.
Just look at the women in their eyes. Right.
And anyway, they're a Christian mission so they set up these church tents and they saw the women and they handed out t shirts because they want them to show up on Sunday morning in the church tent wearing a t shirt. Right.
And these are topless women, so Sunday morning comes.
Let me show up they got the t shirts on but they got holes cut out with the breasts hanging out.
You get the point. The culture is so important that that will override anything new that comes right.
So, the condition that we're in we'll talk about a few other things that we're in right now in terms of what's knowledge base and how we see things has to override a very very strong cultural undertone.
Because humans.
By the way, I can go on and on about the lawful timekeeping I just want to give a throw down a bunch of hints and cover a few subjects that might be even more critical if that's all right with you.
Oh yeah, go ahead. I'm all ears. Okay. Okay, great.
The cultural overtones are the hardest thing to overcome right and you can see what humans because we're subject with the only creatures that are subject to all external input, what I mean by that is this.
Let's say you got a little puppy dog you know about those.
And after it weans from the mama, it gets adopted by a band of gorillas, and you go back and retrieve that puppy after five or six years.
Guess what that puppy comes pre downloaded with everything it needs to be a dog. You throw a stick it'll chase the stick it'll bark at the squirrel it'll act just like a dog even though it was raised by gorillas.
Now you take a baby human baby. And after about three or four months given to a band of gorillas by the way you could probably nurture off a female gorilla, and it go adopt that baby, that human baby after 567 years living with gorillas.
You let them in your house he's going to jump on your kitchen table and throw a pool right there. He won't resemble anything like a human, because all of his tendencies, his mannerisms his gestures are guess what, just like a gorilla why because it's all external input.
Now, we do not we get very little download.
When we come into this world everything has to be copied and learned.
And the animals seem to have. Look, I had a litter of kittens, and they would eat, and they would all walk outside after the eight and they all synchronously wash themselves like who taught them how to do that.
You know who teaches the see they come debt pre download we don't. It's kind of like a computer. You've got the hardware, and then you have the operating system.
Then you have a program, and then you have files.
So let's mix it up. If you have files and you put it on just the hardware, it won't take you need.
Right. You need the program and you need the operating system.
So the culture is our operating system. So you can understand the culture and still have no programs and no files, you know, we're talking about descending order operating system, then programs and then the files the files would be a little things that we take in and hold on to because if someone asks you what color is that car and you say it's blue or you just needed a small minute impulse of blue, and then you compared it to before you said BLUE.
You compared it to everything that you have downloaded or filed away as being blue and that file cabinet called called your head let's say.
Right. And that's what we very, very rarely see things we just try to do a quick comparative analysis to the stimulus we're getting something that's been stored in there.
By the way, you know, memories not in your head at all. It's all remote.
Just like if you just like let's say you're at the beach, or the park and someone's got a little radio, and they're tuning into a jazz station. You think if you go bust that radio open there's a little jazz band in there playing.
Not at all. It's picking up and receiving as the ability to do that. So the cultural aspect is so powerful that, for example, again if you go to something biblical it says well don't make fun of those people because you were like that once to write there's a there's a culture that we have some good quote unquote moral aspects that you always have to follow.
And very often when you start learning and more and more and you want to share. You wonder why it's being rejected right that's one of the hardest things to to throttle and manage within oneself.
But when I give a lot of examples of these things I have to show how it's in the culture, because it's very some things cannot be objectified what I'm saying is trying to objectify.
And just some things cannot be objective objectified, like the ether for example the substrates of this of this construct cannot be objectified it would be like let's say your existence is a video on a screen.
You cannot it's very difficult to objectify as a video character the pixel.
Very difficult, right, you have to come outside of that con construct. So what would what Greeks with some people call it Greek speak I was going to do a interview about 15 years ago, a very long Greek name if you say it backwards you get a hernia.
So she said I'll just call you the Greek, and that it's stuck and other people say Oh, have you heard any Greek speak so this is the basic Greek speak what we're speaking on now.
I started in the early 2000s, the 10s and the 20s so it's cracked three decades, which by the way just in terms of timekeeping and keeping age. When you're born.
You're in your first year aren't you.
Right. Even though you're a day old when you're born you haven't even reached your first year, you haven't read completed it but you're borrowing those days from the first year you're also in your first decade.
You haven't completed it but right so this when you read a lot of old older things he said he was 20 is actually he just turned 19, he just turned 19 so 19 plus one day you're taking it out of your 20th year, it's more, it's more physical related right.
So if you need 13 eggs and they only come in 12.
You know, one dozen packages but you got to go home with 13 eggs you're going to open another dozen package and take an egg out and he's gonna say hold on a second you got to buy that you can't just take one egg out right right kind of like a physical
reference.
So, the timekeeping there's there's many let's see I don't know what where can we go next because we cover medical law, we cover physiology.
Hey, let's do one thing here. This is a secret everybody cover your ears actually the first part is not a secret. The second part is a secret Jason I'm going to share something with you.
Okay.
We live on this earth now I'm just visiting here taking notes.
Okay, so I can't talk about my preferences or opinions, by the way, you're in front of a computer stupid rectangle.
I call it the stupid rectangle.
So, if you have browser access I want you to look up the word nice because I n i c e in etymology et y m o l o g y the first website, type in the word nice and read the definition.
And I could tell you what it is but when people look it up themselves. Let's say someone's driving along they, you know, that's why I don't do screen images and things.
When you look it up yourself. It has like 70% more punch I don't know why. But if you're able to do that etymology look up the word nice and I see and read the meaning if you can.
I'm doing it right now. Okay.
Because we're going to, because I was going to define the word opinion and I said you know, because I hope we're not having a nice conversation.
And you tell me what the word actually means he words are tools and what their definitions are is how that tool is supposed to be used. Would you like me to read what the what what an online search of the word nice produces an etymology go to etymology.com et y m.
Well, I didn't I just I just googled etymology of the word nice and instantly gave me the Latin word.
Oh, yeah, they don't like to. If you just click on that what's this I didn't. Did you get asked about AI taking over Google searches I didn't get a memo on that.
No, but it's definitely doing it. Yep. Well if you go to etymolo etym online that web. Oh yeah I'm there, I'm there I got I got it right here.
Type in the word nice and what's the definition first three four words of the definition foolish ignorant and frivolous. Yep.
Now have a nice day. What are you actually telling you your cohort or whoever you're seeing, how did I not know this, how did I not see this I studied dictionaries hell I damn near wrote a thesaurus before I even knew what it was, I wrote one in prison, you probably yeah but the thing is, yeah, you weren't you you had seen that word was too familiar so you're relying on previous concepts of that word.
Right, let's say it's an analogy of the word nice is foolish ignorant frivolous senseless from the old French dicey careless and clumsy, but we're, but the reason I picked that word is, if you did a transcript of the words that people use every day I think that word pops up more than a few times every day and people's vocabulary.
Yes, it does. Yeah, so I hope we're not having a nice conversation. And when people that know what that word means we can be standing in front of other people says how's that guy jack you met he was very nice and like really I'm sorry to hear that, you know, man, all this time, I've been saying nice, and I'm.
Wow, I'm just, I'm really kind of worried about you telling me about other words in my common we're going to get. Well, don't get worried as long as you have internet is I'm going to ask you to pull some things up because it has more punch you when you do it or whoever.
Now here's the thing.
This is just like the, the girls in the islands that cut the holes in the t shirts.
Right, no different. So, all right, the word opinion.
I'm saying I'm just visiting here, and I don't want to give opinion or like tell anyone what what's my favorite color or I like strawberry ice cream or whatever because opinion is a judgment or decision based with no knowledge.
Right. That's why when you go to these courts the judges can only give opinions because they don't know any law and we're going to get into that.
So, when we start looking at how things should be defined I want to go back to the secret I wanted to actually the second half is a secret.
The first half is this we're all walking around in this realm whether you believe the earth is flat around or whatever you know the new, the new round is flat. By the way, I do have firsthand experience with both of those I'll give them real quick.
Back in the early 80s, there was a construction boom and they were looking for surveyors you know they go out with transits and Theodolites and you measure elevations and layout highways and all that stuff.
And at the time they gave you a two week free course and it was 25 bucks an hour which is almost 100 bucks an hour today.
So no yeah I'll do it. I'll free course and all this I'll try it out was boring as hell I didn't do it but I got I took the course. So we went out and started shooting angles to lay out roads and we found out that we couldn't shoot a triangle.
That was less than 180.5 degrees you know triangle is supposed to be 180. It was impossible to do that, using benchmarks and things that were there for many years, and the instructor says yeah because you're what you're measuring is the Earth's curvature.
And I said, Well, let's try it again. Oh, and we had a formula for the curvature. Okay, so I did notice that.
All right, in architecture we threw what's called a plumb bob a vertical line.
You look out the window and you look at a building across the street a stone building, and, and down the street, another stone building in New York City on Fifth Avenue, and it lines up to that plumb bob there should be a curvature but there ain't that that plumb bob that vertical
plumb is vertical so that means the Earth is flat, man I've never even thought about the plumb line the plumb line would be a frame of reference against several miles away there's no way that architecture can be vertical.
That's right well what would happen it would exaggerate just like the sundial if you want to measure the people figure shit out before I do.
Well, we're all here.
Yeah, and everyone's listening. This is not the secret part yet so. Wow.
That's amazing. I'm not gonna well the plumb bob also exaggerates the curve right because it's an it's a lever, it's coming off the curve so it'll make it seem even.
Okay, here's the other thing I was in Blythe California.
There's a master machinist, and he also grew barley feedstock, and he had a lot of acreage. And this is the border of Arizona and California and they had these ditches irrigation ditches running for miles more than eight miles, and you couldn't see the water
moving but it was moving because of a very very gentle slope there's irrigation dishes. I was like, if the. What about the curvature of the earth if you're going against curvature of the water is going to run the other way so no we never figure that out we could run
these ditches for 4550 miles. We just level them out one eighth of an inch every 30 feet in the water move. And I'm like gosh darn it what happened to the curvature of the earth now.
So I've experienced both.
So, but the realm but here here is it a duality it's not a duality, it's a perceptive experience is based on filtering and and perception.
Now here's, let's go back to what leads to a secret.
You ever noticed when you heat or cool a room, whether you're heating or cooling the heat always goes to the ceiling and the cold always goes to the floor. Always.
Right. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. So,
here's the secret. When you're down in the valley.
And it's real hot.
Don't you if you climb a mountain, same day, same location.
It's colder and colder.
Ah, because in nature and all natural systems. You have a densifying heat that goes down and a rarefying cold that rises.
Now, let's go back to the human body, and I'm using this as an analogy.
Let's see you call them.
They're called doctors I don't think they deserve that title I just call medical technicians.
I can't see you're not feeling well I can't see you have to make an appointment what's wrong with you. Well I've got cold feet and a hot head.
Oh, you're not feeling well, because you're supposed to have a cool head and warm feet.
But wait a second. I thought he's supposed to rise and cold supposed to go down having a cold feet and a hot head is not a good health condition is it.
Not at all.
Right. So, but someone will say hey Greek I want to debate you on that because when there's a campfire I put my hand on there that heats rising up through the chimney.
I said, that's right. Because when you have a natural system that promotes life by taking by increasing compounds and making more complex systems you know let's say from a small simple compound to a more complex one.
The energy emitted from that will always be a rarefied rising cold, and it just a dead supplying heat that goes down.
So let me ask you there. That campfire are you building up that wood or breaking it down in that campfire which one's going what process is going on there.
Oh, I see what you're saying it's breaking down the wood right. So the heat's going to rise. So, what I used to do is call the university physics labs and the air conditioning engineers through town every day I say hey has anybody called
you guys yet you design HVA systems right heating and cooling yeah yeah we do I said how many calls did you get yesterday for people demanding a unit that puts out a rarefied rising cold and identifying heat so they don't have a hot head
and cold feet all year round, you know for their boats planes homes and all that says one nobody ever called for that.
Oh my gosh, this must be a planet of morons I'm in trouble.
Right.
You should be demanding that right you should be demanding that you're into your, your.
What do you call it your units you know the HVAC makes a rarefied rising cold I'm not talking about a fan blowing the cold up and that's what you do for ceiling fans you know you change direction right during the seasons right.
I'm not talking about that something that would work like an artificial sun when you say artificial sun they think bright light has nothing to do with light, because when you go into high altitude the sun gets dimmer and dimmer and dimmer.
It's a transformer just like the transfer anyway that's another situation we'll get into that real quick later.
So that is the secret, by the way, whenever you have a rising coolness and a descending warmth, that is a system that is engaging in processes that are creating complex molecules.
What's another way of saying that growth.
When things are growing and when things are vital and alive.
Right. You will have that energy exchange working in that direction.
Now, why isn't this brought up more and demanded.
Right. Now what do you think will happen if I build a unit that you put in your room that all year round keeps it the same temperature the cold goes up and he goes down you'll get a knock on the door and we'll say, son, if that works you're a dead man.
Why, because it leads to other things, other ways of thinking, like one thing I get into a lot is physiology in the human body. Why, because that's HQ that's your headquarters.
If HQ is full of deception. Anything that could anything you know HQ is where everything comes out of.
So if headquarters only allows deception coming in and deception going out that's that ain't good can't be good.
So, one thing I get into is the definition of words and terms. And I asked people do you know the difference between the soul the spirit and the body.
And they're like, yeah, soul and spirit of the same as you know they're not the body let's set that aside that's the ancient Greek would be the socks. Right. And, or, we'll leave that aside the the carne, let's say right because it has its own virtues like I just mentioned.
Let's talk about the soul and the spirit etymologically very quickly when you look up soul it'll in any dictionary it'll tell you it's a spirit when you look up spirit any dictionary tell you it's the soul.
It can't be, by the way, by the way, dictionary, dictionary. Those were put out fairly recently in the scope of time. Why the elite wanted all the subjects, their subjects to speak in a uniform way.
That's why dictionary is about your diction that's why when you look up a word the first thing it shows is phonetic spelling pronunciation.
Yes, and then it shows the common usage. Right. So we're not when we say definition we let's go back to how it was you so very simply let's do let's use the soul. The soul is simply the metabolism of the living body so when you look at the ancient languages whether it's
so that was the nef or the nefesh in the Greek, it was the pneuma, the metabolism, the actually the act of being alive and functioning as a living unit.
One of the first things to find out if someone's in trouble is are they breathing or not, that's the pneuma.
Right. So that's why for example, the PNU prefix, you'll see the words like pneumatic has to do with the movement of air pneumonia PNU means soul so it's your metabolism so in order for someone to die the soul has to die first, your metabolism you know in other words
your nervous system the cardiac system the pulmonary system has to fail. When it fails the body starts to go into decomposition chemical reduction.
Okay, so the soul is interchangeable for example, if a dog gets hit on the head and it passes out.
You can actually go to that dog let's just maybe, or someone in a swimming pool perform CPR. You can put your soul meaning your breath into that body.
And once they can do it on their own now they have their own soul working it's very simple so all of our souls are transferable. You can do CPR for a dog by the way in certain veterinary thing that's taught.
Right.
You can transfer so anything that is breathing the same air as you has almost an interchangeable soul based on the body design for example, so the soul is the metabolism.
So when you see a bird that's alive. That bird has a soul when that bird is taxidermy and up on your shelf, it doesn't have a soul, it just has the body.
What the hell is the spirit.
Now the soul is tangible, we've got stethoscopes you can measure breathing temperature you know you fog up your glasses right.
Okay, so what is the spirit. Well, the spirit would be the rook or the rock in ancient Semitic languages, or in Greek, it would be the psyche.
And it's intangible the spirit is the mind is nothing tangible. That's why the PSY prefix psychology psychotic psychopath.
That is all of the mind that's what the spirit is so transferring of spirit is intangible, give you an example.
If I have let's say the Beatles white album on a CD or record. I'm going to give that to a materials analyst and he's going to analyze it, give him a few hundred bucks, couple days later he gives you a three page report on what that CD is all about and he's
going to see the types of materials, the reflectivity the grooves cut in it but he can't tell it's the Beatles white album strictly by looking at the mature.
If he has the proper equipment to play it like a CD player he'll put play and guess what you're going to hear the Beatles white album. It's completely undetectable the spirit is not detectable by physical means it's completely intangible it's
what makes you you me me, and every creature that has its own personality. You know it's the hardest thing for me is to eat chickens, because if you raise chickens you know the answer to their names, and they have personalities.
Right.
So that would be there's the individual spirit.
So anyway, the spirit is the PSY prefix, the psyche or the psyche and the pneuma is the soul which is your metabolism.
So I've been on calls and someone passed away and says I wonder if their, their soul and went on I said no their soul had to pass first before the body could be declared dead.
So in other words we're not speaking, it's very hard to speak the same language when people once you know, right, if you go to a transmission rebuild shop, I don't care how familiar you are with tools automotive tools, they're going to have tools on the wall hanging
that you ain't never seen before because not many people rebuild automatic transmissions right.
I'm not talking about something that far like defining words in a far off way. I'm just saying why don't we just take common words and use them how they're supposed to be used if a word is a tool the definition is how to use that tool, essentially.
Now, on the basis of the human body because that's headquarters.
Okay, I want to get into the body it's very very important, very, it's paramount, because that's how we perceive things from. Now, Jason if you came over and you got in the car with me here you can say what's this map taped to your dashboard rolls red dots on it and what the
hell these bright orange earplugs for you got them all over the place I said yeah let me tell you. You see this map right here.
Each red dot in this in this area represents where there's a hospital, a medical office or a doctor's office. So what's the purpose of those, those earplugs they're real heavy duty earplugs I said well, when I'm driving down the street and I see I'm near one of these red dots I got to put the earplugs
in because if I don't the quacking is so loud my ears are ringing for three days.
Okay, and that's, that's why this is what I'm going to show you something here. If you're on the internet.
Type in, for example, watch it let's let's give us, let's give a story before we do this, right. I happen to go to a medical technician, and he says I want to diagnose I want to take your vitals, I will take your vitals just sit down over here right
wearing the white coat and all that.
By the way, you know when they say we're waiting for the doctor to come out the door opens you see have some man or woman standing there with a white lab coat and all that.
And you're so happy to see them you might be nervous they call it white coat fever you know you get nervous you know what would happen if someone came to the door he had a bone in his nose and body paint, what would you do then wouldn't you run away.
Right, most people in this culture would.
So why don't so I'm going to before this is over you're going to see something very similar to that. So anyway I go to this medical technician. I got my earplugs in by the way.
And he says I want to take your vital so he has me sit down and he takes out a piece of string it's not a regular piece of string it has to be a medical FDA approved piece of string.
And he wraps it real tight around the end of my finger digit.
And he has a medical clock is a regular clock won't work it has to be FDA approved.
And he hits a certain timer, and then he looks at my finger and it's about bluish kind of purple, and he holds it up to a chart with blues and purples and he says you got type two stupid itis.
I'm going to give you a prescription for that. Now I'm like, wait a second, I see what you're doing here but what if, what if I never tied a string on my finger what I have that condition.
The answer is, you know, figure it out on your own. So what they do now for diagnosis is I want to take your vitals Jason sit down, they inflate a cuff on your arm, they inflate a cuff on your arm is what's that for blood pressure, blood pressure.
Yeah.
So, you know, you can look up what blood pressure is supposed to be, and then he says oh your blood pressure is high your blood pressure is low.
How could you tell blood pressure if you never put that cuff on me that restricted the flow of blood, how would you tell what you can't son.
Ah, okay. Now if you start looking at how many people are in blood pressure medication you understand what marketing is okay we're going to get into this a little bit more.
You're going to be like, okay, things are far worse than we've been told way worse.
But now that you know it you don't have to participate is my point.
You can still can it's all voluntary.
Now, there's, do me a favor, Jason, go, go to your browser and go to images type in cross section of intestines and blow it up and look at it.
You know it'll be an anatomical drawing.
Okay, you got it now once you study that now do, do a split screen or whatever and do a cross section of a steel belted tire for a car, steel belted tire for a car, do a cross section just type in cross section steel belted radio whatever.
Look at that. And well of course they're, they're they they both serve the same function.
Now, you say a cross section of a, you want a specific tire. No, any tire just put in a cross section of automotive tire, any tire doesn't matter.
All right.
And look, I actually put the images on my desktop if you want me to show them. Yeah, if you'd show them that'd be great. Yeah, in case someone's driving down the road, right, you know, but if you're in front of one of the stupid rectangles you'll see it.
If you look at those two you'll see structurally they're almost identical.
And in purpose, what is the purpose of a car tire keeps one type of pressure in and the other pressure out right when that wall is breached the tire is rendered useless.
Okay, so now when you look at the cross section of the intestines I want you to look at the actual materials of the walls they'll show you cells with no interstitial spaces the cells are completely tightly packed.
How does anything get absorbed through that.
Does any material go through that ever. Now if you do a cross section of the skin cross section of skin and anatomy cross section of lung tissue cross section of the stomach cross section.
What I'm going through is this, our bodies are completely sealed, but we have a pathway that goes from the mouth to the anus. There's like a tunnel that goes through your body.
Everything else the intestines is that I can read you a dozen letters from cardiologists neurologists and nurses actually I have one recently. Basically, I'll paraphrase.
It's a Greek I heard from your sonics what you said about the human body we've just analyzed intestines and stomach and not only are they completely sealed their hydrophobic hydrophobic they repel water.
And what you've said is true against all of our training.
Now, if you look at that if you look at the cross section of lung tissue so how what are they saying nothing is absorbing, by the way, in medical parlance, if you anything passes through the skin wall.
The long wall the intestine or the stomach you end up with a condition called sepsisemia.
When you will probably die. You're completely sealed so what holds everything together.
Again, do you know how just you had to just the discrepancy between rising cold and descending heat with what we're used to everything alive has a biological vacuum some kind of a negative pressure that holds it all together.
It's so when something comes alive, it has an inward pressure I call it a biological vacuum I'm the only one speaking on this.
And when you look at the intestines or the lungs or the skin when you see material. For example, when you eat the food passes through the intestines and you gain nutrition through that, let's say, in the inside of the body, how does the food do that.
Well, it's done by induction.
That's why when you remember it earlier I said that everything that could have been known would have been known by the 1890s ago look at medical books in the 1890s, things were done by in all health concerns were by what induction, what is induction Okay, I have this induction stove cooktop it's a, it's a stovetop it's glass.
It's got a pot of rolling boiling water. Okay, I move the pot to the side I put my hand right on the glass room temperature. I put the pot right back on, it starts rolling boil again that energy is good right it's non physical it only affects certain things.
So, the same with air when air goes into the lungs.
You know, by the way, they say we're oxygen breathers. By the way, I want to say this, I don't think you know how right you are when you talk about vapor canopy biology.
What I'm saying here. Well, I'm gonna tell you, I just use you moving so fast that I literally started taking clip notes, so I don't interrupt you but I gotta interrupt real quick, because I was about, I was about to write a vapor canopy statement here, because if what you're saying is true the heart is not a pump it's a vacuum.
That's right well hold on, no, it's not something different let's jump to the heart and anyone who wants to check out what the heart is a guy named Frank Chester, like Chester drawers Chester, and he look at his old videos.
Now, the heart I could tell you fly out is not a pump it's a break. Because if it were, if it were a pump, it's a real shitty pump because you know when they put one of those stimulators they put on people's hearts.
They inject to put them in their body they run off a battery. One pacemaker. Yeah, they've done with volunteer subjects with pacemakers they have a remote control and they speed up the heartbeat, and every time they sped up the heartbeat the stream of blood that went through the heart, slow down.
And that what kind of fucked up I just use the medical term. Anyway, what kind of messed up pump is that the when you speed it up it slows things down now, what it is is, if you look at there's over 40,000 miles of blood vessels in the body, about 2500 are pertinent that you
could see with your eye.
Now if you go to a finite analysis computer the big supercomputer that you use to design jet aircraft and bridges and whatever.
And you start putting in the human body.
So many liters of blood 50% solids 98.6 2400 miles less than a millimeter in diameter average, it'll tell you you need 1200 horsepower pump just to move 20 miles.
What happened to the other 2400 whatever miles.
So what it's actually doing as the biological vacuum is naturally pulsing one of my mentors Trevor James Constable wrote about the cosmic pulse of life.
I read it, I read it and I promoted on my channel. Yes, very good. I'm one of the few last people that worked with him directly on the weather work.
You know Paul Tice personally.
No, I don't but I know he was very close with Paul Tice is okay someone asked people are asking me to write a book I have 12,000 pages right now.
And I said I really don't want to write a book and put it out because when you're an author and you put out publications, you're presuming that the audience has reading comprehension.
Right.
So, for me to make that presumption would be silly. So I just stick with sonic events I'll throw a hint out you listen, I've done 24 hour lectures on all this stuff to people perfect.
Here's the thing. You know how we talk you've often I've heard you speak about challenging the the nice, let's say the standard people having a debate with them right right.
Okay, now I've presented to doctors lawyers and perfect no one everyone has agreed. They've all acknowledged it so I never had to say I'll debate you on this except for a few academics.
Now, when you challenge someone in debate, and they don't answer it's essentially an academic duel in dueling under the postal code means you got the memo.
If you refuse a debate or a duel, you lose by default, but the price of losing is shame. You're publicly shamed if you backed out of a duel.
So, an academic wanted to debate me and I said no I'm just going to coach this 12 year old for five minutes and they're going to debate you and said you can't do that you have to debate me.
I said how about I just grant you the win.
And they're like, you can't do that you can't do you know I just like I can mess with them. But here's the thing.
They so they they've actually they're in shame because if under the postal rule if they got the memo whether they admit it or not. Right. They lost their their old testicle and no shaft anyway.
Anyway, you know, you know people say, you say they have balls Greek I'm like no well balls make you know Betty White said balls, make it tough but a vagina and that could take a pounding.
But anyway, that's, that's the medical talk coming out of me, little lascivious but whatever. So, yeah, Paul takes no he would be the book tree, San Diego.
I have, I have earth for dummies. I don't know, I don't know if you were the one he was referring to, but recently, when he and I were discussing Trevor James constables working if there were any follow ups, because we were discussing Andy Lloyd, Andy Lloyd wrote dark star the
And the only Andy Lloyd research is very profound and it supports simulation theory but he would never admit that he's a uniformitarian, but it's cool I'm very, I love his work, even though he does he's not interpreting it the way I would.
Well, Trevor James constable is somebody I promote, and when I'm when I'm telling my own community about the work of Trevor James Constable and listen guys there are things in our skies that can be photographed and have been photographed and Trevor James constables work is profound.
He shows pictures of these things. They're like living amoebas organisms in our sky that that create phenomena. So, we're talking about somebody followed up that research, and I'm guessing he was referring to you.
Oh, I don't know.
And he published some stuff I asked him not to publish online.
I main thing I've been doing, even though I don't want to do it anymore because people love disasters if they don't have a disaster they got nothing to talk about hurricane abatement, when a big hurricanes come in and they evacuate everyone and all that we can make those go away.
And it's funny watching the weatherman in the lake well why did that hurricane just stop. It's not moving and then it just, oh it must be wind shear that made it go away.
That's like saying a four year old put his hand out and stop the semi truck.
Yeah, so we play around with that the last one I did was Hurricane Lee if you. And that was that was quite a fight because it was completely artificial there's some good guys that sent some of the resources to do it and it's a lot of work.
Yeah, the weather is is engineerable and weather, and I'm continuing Trevor's work and also Wilhelm Reich's work. My first mentor and around the year 2000 was a guy named Joe Blankenship and he was Wilhelm Reich's driver when he was here.
And I learned a lot and a lot of his personal stuff I have a lot of Trevor's personal stuff. Before he passed he sent me boxes and boxes of his paperwork his own personal stuff.
Your version to being a public figure is now explainable to me.
Well yeah we'll get into a little more with some stuff that you could do is look if you can't build it in your kitchen you shouldn't be building it at all that's what the professional people.
The academics trying to play oh we just made this new discovery this material new material but you need a $200 million lab to make it that's totally senseless to me.
So anyway, if we look at the human body.
It's completely sealed you could just look at all your cross sections and it's working by biological vacuum now a plant you know you got to water plants because they absorb water through the roots.
Do the same thing cross section of risology you know which is root study, and you'll see the roots are completely sealed as a matter of fact go out and pull yourself a green onion or something out of the garden.
Clean all the dirt off and get a fine water bottle sprayer and spray the roots while the plant still alive. Do you, you see them sucking up the water like a sponge or does the water beat up on the roots like a freshly waxed car.
It beads up.
Right, so there's no absorption going on now well the part that's important is this when you get a cut or wound in the body.
Just like a car tire, you suffer loss of vacuum, and the faster you can make that tight and increase the pressure there, the faster that will heal. And let's just go this to for a moment.
I've had people send photographs of little girl goes out the back door you know those security screens with the welded screens and sometimes they leave a sharp edge you got her foot caught on the tour the tour her big toe completely open.
Everyone's like take her to the hospital take her to the hospital. And he says no no we're going to try this and they wrapped it real tight the next day it looked like a scratch in three days it was completely healed under a lot of pressure but you have to know how to do it you have to wrap it very tight and let the blood, you know, how do you let the blood flow back in right you don't want to wrap it like a tourniquet.
There's techniques that we get into for that.
So the other thing is this about the human body.
Oh, one more thing.
The vacuum. Okay, when people are feeling sick you notice how they get mucus and congestion in their sinuses and all that they if someone's really congested with mucus in their sinuses they also have a lot of mucus in their colon area, by the way.
Anything that's completely open what the body saying is hey dummy I'm losing vacuum so I'm building up this mucus to increase vacuum, and the medical technicians they prescribe things to break up that mucus.
Now give you an example Jason look up well what holds the baby in the woman's cervix when she's pregnant. You know when woman's pregnant baby could fall out if right.
So what's keeping it closed what's keeping everything in there. I'll tell you it's called the mucus plug.
You could look it up it's called a mucus plug. And that's keep the baby in the womb.
Now it's not stop you're you're overwhelming me hold on. No, we shouldn't be overwhelmed just flow with it but go ahead.
You're in your flow.
But I'm hearing, listen, I process information a little bit differently than most people, but once I have it I've got it. I got to wrap my mind around a concept. I'm not saying you're wrong.
I'm saying this is new to me, and the whole mucus deal.
It does make sense. So I have to ask you to take it to a more explanatory level as to what, what is the remedy, because mucus is my problem.
All right.
A couple times a year. What is the remedy if I got a vacuum. What can I do so I can have some so I can breathe.
Yeah, well here's the thing gosh darn it, you're going to say to yourself I was more right than I thought I was. By the time we finish.
It's all about you just keep the vapor canopy in the back of your mind, you know, keep that file drawer open because you're going to be reaching into it a lot more than you have after this.
Hopefully.
This is how we remedy something without even having it cause you know the allopathic medicine treats the symptoms, right. Okay, so how do we prevent that from happening give you an example.
You're living in a cold place. Okay, let's say northern latitudes or something. And suddenly you start eating food that's grown in a warm place you like bananas you like tropical fruit sugar.
That food that you start intaking was grown in a warm place and it's going to adjust your body chemistry to living in a warm place, thin blood looser cellular functions, and all that.
So your body's going to start the food that you're eating, because it's not grown in that latitude will start adjusting your body to living in the lower latitudes and you're going to start losing vacuum.
Now let's do the opposite.
Let's say you live in the tropics, and it's trendy to eat salmon I want some of that salmon I'm in Ecuador. So you get it imported from Alaska. Right.
And you start eating that salmon, you're in a tropical place that salmon is going to start changing your blood chemistry to living in the Arctic you're going to turn that AC way down it's still going to be too hot for you.
Give you an example. I met a lady 20 some odd years ago she's my wife now. And it was fall here in the southwest which is not that cold but she's wearing a jacket I'm out in just a long sleeve shirt.
And she always complained about being cold well I go over to her house and she's got a banana on her counter you know a couple of those little things you hang been that's called a banana tree you know.
Anyway, I said what's that she goes bananas I like eating for potassium Oh boy, got rid of the bananas went out and bought some salmon poached it I said eat this for the next couple of days How are you doing now she goes I'm coming over I'm in a t shirt now.
Right because so let's say it's getting cold where you are start eating things that come from a cold place. By the way, when you go, it was popular to go to Alaska and work on the pipeline back in the 70s and before when you were hired to from the lower 48 to go work in Alaska they gave you a cut sheet instructions for two weeks before you come up here we want you to get some cool whip and corn oil, pour it in there and eat two tablespoons of that a day three times a day to adjust yourself to the climate.
Because what do they eat up in the Eskimo Eskimo the in you it's fat.
Right. And, but if you eat that in the tropics, right so what you eat so, for example, if you have an all year round perennial thing of mucus, something is disturbing your ability to create a vacuum or you were born that way in other words some people just have trouble with that just like one leg might be shorter than the other or whatever right slightly.
So you have to work on that so the easiest way to increase vacuum is to be in harmony with your environment so when it's warm outside, you eat food that is grown in a warm latitude or you can always eat cross latitude, get on the map and run your finger across the latitude all across the world and you can eat all that types of food stuff that's grown there.
Now what's going on things get worse like we live in let's say someone lives in New York and it's wintertime and the children got the sniffles and the medical technician or the news says that vitamin C is good for that.
Well, what happens when they take the oranges and the tropical fruit makes them worse. Oh, so now you got to take this deep congestion. Right.
I want to go back to also food is your, you're not, you know how they say you are what you ate what you what you eat. It's more like you are what you ate 10 days ago.
Right, because it has to get processed. So basically eating seasonally is a cure for many many many ales, a lot of diseases in the body things we talked about it are no you like tumors and rashes and things like that.
Those conditions, by the way, and maybe for more of a private talk I can get into what's really going on in the medical and how heinous it is.
But things that develop in the body are no different than someone setting up a roadblock to prevent traffic from passing through.
Now when you see a roadblock do you say oh let's get an armored vehicle a bus through, or let's go find out why there's a roadblock and mitigate it so we can freely move the traffic again you see.
So the CA and CR word is no different than a roadblock being put up, because on the left side of the body the energy moves down on the right side it moves up and certain foods will change that you know the principle of yin and yang.
Right yin is expansive and dark and soft and young is contractive and sharp and, and hard.
This is everything we'd has a counterbalance like that. So in essence, what would be a remedy is no remedy. What you do is watch what you eat. So in the summertime, you eat cross latitude latitude foods and foods that come from warm places in the wintertime.
What happens when people get sick around what they call the holiday season.
A lot of sweets and candies and stuff like that where sugar and chocolate come from.
And where are they eating it, they're eating it in cold places right.
So they're not feeling that well.
That's a really good point. It's a also another one supports what you're saying is, is a honey is good, but if you really want to get the maximum benefits you need to focus on local honey.
More local but across latitude cross latitude is the key.
We are a latitude range for example let's go to the real high latitudes go around the map everybody wears the same stuff looks, you know, they're right, eat the same stuff, go along the tropics all around the map, they eat the similar, it's cross latitude eating I call it.
And that will that will pretty much take care of 99% of people's ills now you got the school teacher that comes home and she says oh I caught a cold from my children right in class you hear that all the time I caught a cold right now.
Now, there's something called germ theory that virus stuff is anyway, something called germ theory. Now if germ theory were true that it's a little bug called a germ that makes you sick.
Listen to me carefully, listen carefully. Wouldn't that render all refrigeration useless and redundant. Hold on, because don't we put things in there in the refrigerator to retard the growth of those little things called bacteria.
Yeah, and it works. So why do people get sick in the winter, when all those little germs are dormant.
It doesn't make any sense. Good point. And that's why it's not that it's so third grade comes home teacher I got a call from one of my students well what's really going on on the weekend they don't have school on the weekend I want you to hang out where they all shop.
And you'll see the school teachers pushing a cart and she's getting in the wintertime she's getting bananas and tomatoes and things. Right. And you see all the children's moms and shopping the same stuff but oh, you know what the math teacher from India.
Didn't get sick, and the science teacher from China didn't get sick. Let's go follow what they're eating. Hmm. Are they at the supermarket getting bananas where are they eating more cross latitude food that from where they came from a strong culture, you see.
So, also when you talk about breaking pattern like, for example, I caught something called the circus flu because I have a nice she's a sword swaller in the paranormal circus, and the conditions that they live in are very harsh and when I met her.
Give her a big hug and all that I started not feeling well because of the way you're most likely going to get sick from someone that has the same blood as you genetically brother, mother, father, cousin, niece, always that way because that's how plagues are created by the way when they said they.
Anyway, I broke the flu by just having a very high quality piece of chocolate like one of those $12 candy bars, you know, and when I ate that high quality chocolate it just changed my entire system.
It just zapped me like getting your finger in an outlet, kind of thing. That's the that's how I, you know, change pattern, right because I never eat that kind of stuff. So sometimes just a rapid intake of something very different will help.
That's why for example someone will try a new remedy let's say a normal American who's used to popping pills and things like that gets a Chinese remedy some kind of route, they boil that really worked.
But the next time they need it didn't work the next time because it was really changing the pattern in their body, not the route itself so you have to learn how to discern that we get into that with the sonic events we do.
We have tremendous success.
And the stuff I'm talking about on the human body again I have spoken to maybe several scores of professional doctor and none of them all of them are in agreement.
And what they will, I know I'm not going to ask them why don't you do it, they just tell me I just can't acknowledge what you're saying.
They cannot acknowledge it.
The legal stuff is even worse but here I don't know if you want to get your, your, your channel canceled so we can continue on the medical stuff.
If you got some really intense stuff to talk about that needs to go to our cakes TV. That's what yeah just tell me when to stop I think we're going to stop on the physical physiology right there because what's going on, I could tell you right now the di be
ETS you know type one type two type completely fictional a IDS completely fictional does not exist in the PPCR does not exist.
It's just as fictional as anything.
But to make a long story short when they were doing the injections.
I went out with someone and there was a table set up with nurses in public. And he started saying oh what you're doing is this that you know the typical anti Vax stuff right.
And they were laughing at him. Oh this guy wants to get people killed.
This is one of those wacko loose nuts anti Vaxxers right and they're all laughing. So I go up to the nurse quietly and I say, before you administer that are you taking into account body weight, gender, blood type and race.
She within two minutes she goes to her assistance we got to pack up and leave right now, and they close that shop down.
So when you get a whatever are they taking your blood type into account your body weight, and, you know, for example, why did I mention race. If you know any anesthesiologist you could run this by them.
I got a 300 pound black man, and a hundred and 20 pound redhead with freckle woman. They're both coming in, they're both coming in for an appendectomy.
Do you know that the anesthesia dose that's required to put the redhead hundred 20 pound girl with freckles down and anesthetic for the operation would kill the 300 pound black man.
Wow, why is that. Well it has to do with blood type has to do with race there is such a thing as racial medicine.
For example, when they started putting out Prozac and certain other things like that here in the US was quite popular but you know if you're in Korea, Japan you took that you died.
Wow. Yeah, look it up, it's medical racism. It's very real. It's very very real. There's also blood diseases between different quote unquote races now I'm not.
Now fortunately I grew up in Brooklyn, New York, or unfortunately and I was told by some very wise people at a young age that race doesn't matter.
And, you know, it's a very racist place I was, I was called a n lover n word lover I was called, you know, Asian love, you know, at a young age you people bothered you if you didn't hang out with just, you know, if you didn't hang out with your own kind.
You're a lover of the other kind and I never understood that. So I got over that at a very very young age. And it was easy for me to accept the medical racism when I saw it, instead of it being dismissed right.
Well, we could do if you want to get into what really the ideas has nothing to do with what they're calling a VI r us is nothing but mitochondria.
It's inside the it's basically the part of the cell that holds the DNA, and they tell you it mutates mitochondria has got a pretty definitive shape and if you want to get into some genetic theory.
You know dendrochronology is bullshit it has rings right that they count total bullshit. Yeah, but if you've got a big tree or whatever you versus a small tree of the same genre, you could say the one with more rings is a little bit older right.
Yes, you can human mitochondria has the same thing we have rings in our mitochondria. Some people got four 5000 rings some people got 30.
And this is not discussed on another level we all have the same DNA just shows we came from a same mother, really, on another level.
By the way, the right now DNA testing is only being used by the legal community because it's all presumption.
It takes over a month to do the 111 comparison test. And so they go into a legal thing and after 10 days oh we got DNA testing.
It's all BS. Okay, we can get into the technical making the technical easy my whole thing is if I cannot explain it to an eight or nine year old or fifth grader I don't want to talk about it.
That is absolutely what I promote on my channel is something cannot be simplified to its lowest common denominator you don't know your material.
That's right. Well, yeah, and also you're not communicating it well you know in war, in war, save the bullets, how do you be defeat the enemy by preventing them from communicating with each other.
Right. Right. And another thing in war, how do you defeat an army by killing them or injuring them injuring them each injured soldier takes two other soldiers to so incapacitates the the field.
Right. Now, we don't have to get into a bunch of stuff with legal and law but if someone wants to know what's going on in this country write this down it's called the Lieber code or general order 100.
It was you've heard about executive orders and all that right likely executive orders is for the executive branch of government, general, the last general order was in 1863 by Lincoln.
And it's called general order 100. Now, if you didn't know when it was written, or what it was called and you read it.
You'd say this is a transcript of everything that's going on today it's called operations of armies in the field, how do you deal with a civilian. When you're military, how do you deal with civilian population, and that's everything that's going on.
For example, what it did also got rid of the judicial system which we do not have one of the three bench branches of government corporations media and pedophilia pedophiles. Anyway, no it's supposed to be.
It's it's it's the three branches are the executive judicial and legislative. Well, that was done away with because right now, if you go to court, it's all basically a military tribunal.
What's going on is all the courts of police and all that are under the Attorney General which is the executive branch, and they are conferred and confirmed by the legislative.
The only place you will find us a little smattering of judiciary left is in the Supreme Court. The problem with the Supreme Court, it's not a court of record it's an appellate court.
People say, well Supreme Court said the Supreme Court said that so who cares but the Supreme Court gives its opinion and decision and then kicks it down to the district court, where they finalize it, they never tell you that right it's not it's an appeals court it's not a court of record.
You're absolutely speaking the truth, because my own prosecuting attorney was named Mark Vincent, I went to court to go sign for 90 days boot camp.
My judge had just let a cop killer go named Marvin bill it was all over the news. I haven't really told a lot of this story of what happened, but I went to court to sign for 90 days boot camp victims family was cool with the victim was cool with my participation was minimal.
But Marvin bill killed an HPD officer, and my judge judge Norman Lanford was a liberal, and he let him go on a Miranda right violation and HPD Harris County Joe other judges law enforcement, they were in a rage.
So the day I go to court, my family couldn't even find a place to sit down because all the news agencies from the United States were all in there going oh wow that he just let a cop killer go is he going to let all criminals go so me in about 250 people were all given hyperinflated sentences, because he was trying to save his bench.
His name is Norman Lanford all this is verified in the news, but Norman Lanford was removed from the bench because he just sent everybody to prison after after that, but what's interesting is what you said my own prosecuting attorney Mark Vincent said.
Oh, you really need to appeal this because this is isn't the agreement that you and I had, and when I hired an attorney and we went through the appellate process they literally told me we're sorry, but the Texas Court of Criminal Appeals does not does not review matters of substance.
All they want to know is did they procedurally F you in the right way right because we are not going to look at any matters of substance, we do not care what the issues were, and they sent me to prison.
So anyway, that's that's when you say that because it's absolutely precise.
This is how it works and people how is it a military tribunal Greek well this is how it's a tribunal you have the judge the prosecutor and the clerk, and they're working together to get you to agree to everything that's on that penal bond.
And what once you agree to it you're supposed to sign it off and go home, and they get paid because it's a public debt now one thing I had an attorney, by the way, I get into a lot of law stuff.
And the only person I wanted to debate who did not want to debate me, he was a total agreement. I had lunch not once but twice with a Supreme Court justice his name is john Fitzgerald Malloy now why are you name name dropping that I don't know who that is well guess what john Fitzgerald Malloy pen the Miranda rights you have the right to remain silent that guy.
And he was in his 90s this is over 20 years ago, and he basically said yeah that's right it's not law at all.
If you're in my courtroom I have jurisdiction I do what I want to do now the judge is also the prosecutor but what people don't understand how we got into this position, I had an attorney once a friend of an attorney told me that this guy was studying the money system all his life and he heard Greek, the Greek and he says the Greek laid it out in 10 minutes so easy.
Now I finally understand it. If you I want to just do that because everybody talks about for money and all that very simply. Absolutely. You have a private banking cartel, however you want to define them.
And they've been trying to get under the United States and get over on the United States for a long, long time, not until around the early 20th century, did they start playing with this banking cartel over the 1913 or so Federal Reserve Act they let him in, but by 1933, the government lost the card game with the banking cartel and the banking cartel bankrupted the United States and put them under receivership.
So, if you say the United States is bankrupt lot of people say no it's not what it is, well it's in receivership after the bankruptcy procedure. Now, just to interject something everybody's celebrating the fourth of July, June, was it July 4 1776.
Okay, that's when the country was born. Well, when was the corners report written. Look it up March the ninth 1933 no one's talking about that that's the corners report March the ninth 1933 is when the country died, and it went into receivership what's receivership.
Okay, Jason you own an ice cream shop on Main Street, and you've been there for generations everybody defines Main Street as your ice cream shop, you get into some dealings with some people and you lose the shop, let's say in a card game or you borrowed money you can't pay back you go into bankruptcy.
But the people now that took over your shop they're like hey, why do we shut down this business which is put it in receivership now Jason it's not Jason shop anymore we'll make him the manager and give him a little salary, we keep everything going, just the names change, just like for example PepsiCo they put out Pepsi but they also got Taco Bell Kentucky Fried Chicken.
So, when someone says I went to talk about so you went to Kentucky Fried Chicken. No, I didn't. It's the same company you know these companies have subsidiaries right.
So, the United States government now do they didn't let anyone know that they were doing this kind of dealing so what they did is they put everything in trust in 1990, James trafficking on Congress said addressing Congress which are trustees of the largest bankruptcy in world history the United States government.
Now the government did not know to tell people that they were doing this they were sending all the gold off in the 1930s to Germany, but they didn't tell the people.
That's what I've been telling everybody on Archaic's TV. That's what I've been telling them. They bankrupted us the Great Depression was refunding American wealth to finance the German war machine.
Well, how did they, how did they bankrupt very simple they went into a deal that they will the private bankers will print the notes at 6% interest and once they gave all the bankers, all the gold and all the silver, they still owe the 6%.
And that's how they bankrupted them. But anyway, the government didn't tell everyone what happens what they did is they set up a trust commercial corporation that started off with your name and all capital letters and they give you a number, social security number.
And you could look up or it's kind of hard night right now but there's over a dozen in the United States code in the CFR the Council of the codes of federal regulation and the uniform commercial code, there's at least a half a dozen sections in there and say all debts
belong to the United States that means all bills notes bonds payments to be made Dunning's all these things belong to United States so essentially, when you deal with anyone corporate that asks for a social security number they want to tap that trust.
And since the money is fiat, whatever they bill they send that trust through the Treasury at 1111 congressional way or whatever that's true, they will pay it within 40 or something days well there's a lot of technical stuff that's involved but what I'm trying to say is, when, let's say you get pulled over a traffic stop or you have insurance or utility bill if they have your social security number.
They're tapping your trust and they're making you double dip and pay for everything twice now people don't know this, give you an example on how the money works it's created off your signature, Jason let's give you this example first and you'll see why we have the inflation real quick.
Jason I got a bank account, and it's minus $100. Can I write you a check for whatever. No, can't do it.
Now if I put $100 in there to make it zero Can I write you a check for 10 or $20 still can't do it.
Right, so if you go to the US Treasury website they're 30 trillion in debt so how they how they sending out 1200 $1500 checks to people every six months during the thing.
They're okay what's going on is this, you get the check.
And when you sign the back the money is created 10 times, because it's fractional reserve banking so you get $1,000 check the bank creates 9000 out of it.
The bank keeps 30% they send 30% to the government they give you just the 1000 and the other 20% that's left goes into some fund.
And this is why they've created so many trillions of dollars by sending people checks it doesn't make sense.
But it's all in the codes, there's actually the Bill of Exchange Act 1882 you could read that and you'll be like, Oh my gosh, money comes from my signature all I got to do is write a number down and write it in words and sign it and it's good.
That's right.
In law, by the way, if you're in a credit based economy, and I'm asking you for money, do you know that I have to send you the check to pay for it also you sign that check it's called a voucher.
That's why when you get a utility bill or a credit card bill on the bottom doesn't say detach this and send this in with your payment that's a check, you just don't know how to fill it out.
So that's the crux of the money system, money creation. So, basically, there's a verse that says it's the love of money that's the root of all evil. That's got to be true because there's no money anymore it's all credit and people still love it, they're not
paying any attention at all.
Right. So we can we get into the money talk a lot. Now I want you to. Okay, pull this up type this in and read it it's real short 12 us see 411 so it's basically title 12 United States code for one one you just type in USC, or 12 USC for one one.
You don't know lawful money.
Yep.
Cornell go ahead and click on it and read it real quick. Cornell it's a lawful going to read that it's about two sentences.
You see this section of the US code defines Federal Reserve notes as obligations of the United States that are redeemable in lawful money lawful money is not further specified in the text.
Okay, no. How about just 12 USC for 11.
Okay, 12 us in other words it's a title 12 section 411 section 411 issuance to reserve banks natural obligation. Read that. Yeah.
So the Federal Reserve notes to be issued at the discretion of the Board of Governors of the Federal Reserve System for the purpose of making advances to Federal Reserve banks through the Federal Reserve agents as hearing after set forth and for no other purpose are authorized.
Stop right there.
That's written in eighth grade English Federal Reserve note is a check cash, whatever, doesn't it say there that you're not authorized to use it, you ever wonder why you ever noticed that if you get pulled over and you got a bag full of cash they take it and say it's contraband.
Now what you're, why do these serial number why are there serial numbers on the cash and on checks every financial instrument has a serial number, because what you're supposed to do if you continue reading it.
Continue reading it.
Okay, the said notes shall be obligations of the United States and shall be receivable by all national and member banks and Federal Reserve banks and for all taxes customs and other public dues.
They shall be redeemed in lawful money on demand at the Treasury Department of the United States in the city of Washington, Columbia, or at any Federal Reserve Bank.
Excellent. Okay, so the reason you have Social Security numbers. I mean, a serial numbers on all the instruments no matter what they are, you're supposed to keep financial records and write down the denomination or amount and the serial number of that instrument and show that you made a demand for lawful money.
And you're supposed to go to the Treasury and they're supposed to give it to you but they don't do that anymore so if you do that now you have no, they can't ask you to do duties taxes and all that if you have that on demand you have to have it on record.
You know, for example, a lot of people fear and talk about the IRS, it's the only agency that actually follows the law, believe it or not.
Do you remember Charlie Brown, Charles Schultz.
They used to do comic strips in newspapers. Of course. And there was one comic strip in the 70s where Snoopy sitting on his house with the typewriters is DR DR IRS please unsubscribe me.
And that was he was giving public notice what's going on.
IRS has a form. I'm not going to mention its number it's actually form 56. But anyway, you could download that fill it out and send it in and you just unsubscribed.
It's that simple. Now, but how come they're beating people up they have a tendency every decade or so they pick a famous person.
Oh, I get it. Yeah, yeah, but it's. So anyway, if you make demands in many, many ways to the IRS, they're not going to do that.
with everything that's going on.
So, I gave a little smattering of hints and things here and there but one thing I didn't get into was the biblical biblical perspective that we get into I know you've been leaning on that heavily lately, for good reason.
And if we have a little bit more time I'll get into what I've been teaching on that.
Yeah, the. Yeah, I'm a.
Listen, a lot of my material in archaics is straight out of the Bible because it does have historical value it's got philosophical value, even though it even has spiritual value, it probably has legal value as well, but there, but there's also narratives been attached to the Bible that were completely fictive and made up.
That's right now here's the point that this is a partner I use the word pagan with certain adherence, usually means ignorant, typically, and it's been kept that words been captured and used as very denominational purposes of political purposes all religions are political economic systems.
But here this is the point. I'll tell you how I came through the door. Right. I was born in a Greek family which is Eastern Orthodox a lot of iconography and all that I'd never thought it was true.
The first impression I got as a child I walked into a church and they had a big crucifix by the altar with a guy nailed to it, wearing a diaper.
And I saw that and I was like, well they're saying that this guy was all about the truth so I guess that symbol means that if you're all about the truth that's what they're going to do to you.
Right. As a child, that was my reasoning. That's some good reverse psychology if it's true.
Well, that's what I recently I got as a child I said that's all bad shit.
Now, fast forward 25 or so years. I went to this place seminar guy was talking about law and money and government.
And he says well we have all these corporate codes that we follow as as well where you get law from this as you get it from the Bible and I was like, the Bible don't you know that was written by Shakespeare, but you know, I never but I was like, I felt kind of bad told my old man that because I never read the Bible.
So I said he said it's about law so I'm going to go in there and find out where the laws are and I'm gonna start reading it. So I took it aside I started reading. Now I know Greek and I learned the Hebrew, and I started reading it, and I was like, nobody ever told me this was in here.
And the stuff that they're saying is in here is not in here. So what what I talked about on the Bible is not whether it's true, or who wrote it, or whatever, do we know what's in it.
Because it's got this pagan aspect to it okay you go into court, they have you put your hand on a King James Bible and you swear. Okay, so imagine this, you go in there and say, once you swear on the Bible say oh you know what, I got the whole thing downloaded on my phone can I swear on my phone.
No, you can't do that. So it's become like this rabbit's foot right.
Right. The other thing is it's being used like a baseball bat give me an example you know the Louisville slugger those baseball bats they're canon. What I mean by canon is they're made by a certain specification and licensed by the baseball authorities right at a certain weight and length right.
But you know that more than 80% of baseball bats sold or not for playing baseball why because they make a damn good club. They make a cheap club, and that's when you see someone walking with a Bible under their arm that's what they're using it as you, and they come at you.
I never liked the stuff to say well that's Mark 1739 Isaiah 46 was to all be patty special sauce.
You see, I'm like what the hell what kind of racket is this what the hell's going on. Why don't we just read it and say what it says. So what I've been talking about is the identity crisis with the Bible and it's this.
I go and interview a whole let's say 100 people on the street. This is the identity crisis here, and I said you know who Batman is talking about comics now right yeah I know Batman is okay I got a picture of various cartoon characters here on the wall.
Can you please point to Batman and all 100 people point to Mickey Mouse.
And I'm like, what's wrong with you. That's Mickey Mouse. Oh no, that's your opinion man that's not how it is a misinterpretation. I said, as far as I know, that may not look like that that man didn't do right you see what I'm saying we have an identity crisis.
So, so for example, if you go through the, you know, the first will be last and the last will be first revelations the first book of the Bible, what I get into.
And Genesis is the second.
Now if you get into the Hebrew, you know they got seven days or so right.
Well you got ordinal and cardinal days in there so let's say I got seven, seven cars in my driveway right Jason.
And I point to the first car is the first car but this is the third car I bought.
You see, so the ordinal and cardinal. Right. So in other words I got seven cars that I bought consecutively but they're not in order of how I bought them they're not parked that way.
So when I'm describing them this second car here well that's the fifth car that I bought.
Right. Ordinal and cardinal. But here's the point. When man is created very simply in that man and woman are created together.
They're given a blessing, and they're told to repopulate the earth.
That's the sixth day, a day supposed to be 1000 years let's say the seventh day.
There's a Sabbath. Now we got after the Sabbath. We got this creation, actually it's a formation, not a creation of this guy called Adam, and he's made alone.
He's by himself.
And he's given a task he's got to cut the bushes take out the garbage manage the garden. Right. Now when the woman comes up later, after they made him from him.
Are they given a blessing or is the earth cursed.
Totally different story.
In the, in the first two chapters. So we got I call it six day man and eighth day man cane goes out there he's terrified he's sent to a city of refuge, because there's the places populated already.
Now, why the garden.
You ever noticed no matter how many stories you read even the Mahabharata the Bhagavad Gita that man always starts in a garden always ends up in a city.
When you ever hear of a story of a city being destroyed. Gosh, that's all the time. When is the garden destroyed.
Hardly ever.
Right. It's someone wrote to me earlier in the chat.
It's better to be a warrior in a garden than a gardener in a war.
But anyway, so there's this stuff going on, you know, so you've got to be able to so when you say like better sheets but I had the audits and you start reading the Hebrew to someone, you can you can back up that you've done the research right.
And you're not just reading it from someone else now here's the thing.
The biggest identity crisis that we have.
This is what I found by the way, the Bible is kind of like K through 12.
You know, education, by the way they K through 12 is 12,000 hours of education if you figure out the time and you know you're off for summer, all that crap could be taught in less than 300 hours away they keeping you in there.
But anyway, the Bible is like K through 12 the Old Testament it's like first grade all the way to third grade or fourth grade fifth grade the prophets, get you out of high school by the time you, you go into college you're reading the New Testament.
It's all cumulative. So when you get to college for math, Jason, you got your first year in college math does your first day in class they say okay class what's one plus one.
What's two times two no, you're supposed to have that under your belt already right. So here's the big catch the identity crisis and I'm not getting into who wrote it or why but but do we know what's written in there.
It's kind of like those, you know, they got those Haynes manuals for cars you know how to fix your car you know on your own. You got to pay attention to what it says to do in there you know it doesn't matter if the car is, it doesn't matter at this point so let's get let's identify what we're saying here.
So, when you get to the New Testament, it's pretty much given that you know the laws and all this stuff so let's say the who I'm speaking to and presuming they know all the biblical law let's get into the New Testament for a minute.
So, you notice that the Christ character is brought up throughout the in prophecy throughout the scripture right all the way on. By the way, let's do let's just do the Christ thing because everyone be here for too much I could talk eight hours just on this identity.
Let's get an identity. Okay, so we get this. Let's just fast forward.
The Judean I didn't say Jewish the Judean authorities the southern part of Israel the Judeans, their religious authorities arrest this guy.
Okay.
And because of certain reasons that were he was deemed to be heretical.
But because they're under occupation of Rome.
They have to follow the pecking order was a chain of command.
So they can't just go knock on the Caesar's door. So they go up to the occupied. The king.
The suzerain king right he suzerain to the Romans, but he's still their king.
He laughs it off, gives him a robe or whatever you know, whatever.
And then they go to the prefect governor Pontius Pilate right prefect governor. Now, he's there to run Judea.
And let me let me mention something, he's a military actor he's military branch of the military. Okay. He happens to be a historian just like Tiberius Claudius Caesar was at the time.
But here's the thing, if you're a colonel or military attache of any kind right now and you send you go to a foreign country. They give you something called an area book, which describes, you need to be well studied in the cultures and laws of the people so you don't go there and create an international incident look like an idiot, right.
That still goes on today so Pontius Pilate was special in this appointment, whether he existed or not because he was very well read in those cultures. That's why he was sent there.
There are records of him being close friends they had history as a hobby with Claudius Tiberius Caesar when they were young but anyway, they bring them to Pontius Pilate Pontius Pilate sees what's going on paraphrasing here and he washes his hands with a lover and he says I don't see this man being guilty of why you're sending him here to me.
I'll, you know, do the typical Roman thing. Now washing the hands publicly is the ceremony of the red heifer in the law in the law the reason the red heifer was when the dead body was found the, the elders of the area had to wash their hands to show that they didn't know anything of it or they were absolved of anything if found later and took a leak loop loophole.
So that ceremony where he washed his hands was actually performing the red heifer ceremony. And then they still wanted to put to death, and he goes to the Judean authorities you could read this in the book of john the book of Mark, and he says, you have a law, I know you have a law, use your law, the response from the Judean authorities is how can we under Caesar he says you have a law I know what it is under, yes, do it.
Okay, so what is capital punishment under Judean law, it's not by crucifixion can't be.
It's, it's stoning.
But here's the thing. If you go to Deuteronomy 29 what was he accused of one of the most heinous crimes murder and blasphemy were the most heinous things you could do in Judean religious economy.
But when I say economy I mean in terms of laws of the rules. So, if you read and Deuteronomy 21 even says the word son, you're to be nailed to a tree.
Okay, so when you see that he was nailed to a tree.
During the stoning. And there was one man on his left one man on his right now they can't receive now the crowd passed from the third to the ninth hour doing what hopscotch patty cakes throwing dice what were they there for so many hours, passing through.
He, or the flesh was torn off of his body because he was front and center, but the guy on the left and the guy on the right of the almond tree we know it's an almond tree because there's over 15 references to the almond tree in the Old Testament.
Not the olive tree, the almond tree. As a matter of fact, Moses was told to make a seven branch lampstand, because it had a certain symbology, and you lit the top right, and it was the likeness of an almond tree with its blossom so it means it's in the springtime.
Anyway, he was given a robe from Herod a purple robe but why before all of this started the Romans cast lots for that robe, because these men were killed for an accursed thing any accursed thing is to be burned to Clint to cleanse it.
So they were given the, the whole round about what's going to happen. And they knew that robe would be piled up there and burned and they cast lots to take it home.
Now he was not burned he was spared that that's why when you go read the part of the New Testament about the Last Supper there's no last separates the Passover.
If you know the ordinance of the Passover what you're supposed to do in that you will see the conversation that went on during that time made complete sense about fire about blood and about this.
But if you don't know what the Passover. Okay, so when they. So what's going on. It's called lapidation by the way stoning, right.
There's a lapidation that took place, the body was taken down yes there was a pyre built up and burned all of his possessions were taken up and burned also because, hey Jason How about this we're, we're there, and they killed this guy for stoning the most accursed thing.
Do you want his TV Oh no that's an accursed thing that should have been thrown in there and burned with him.
That's why when he was up on that tree says take care of my mother because anything you had to be taken away and burn to see. So once you understand the laws you see the extension of the story.
And you're like, wait a second, but what happens is we're so flooded with television churchy anity images, all this other stuff. Right. And when we read it in the Bible like oh I saw this part of the movie, I saw this part of the movie and we're not really reading what it states.
My favorite is this movie, what's actually a terrible movie. The only thing it showed was the right phase of the moon was the 10 Commandments, remember the 10 commandments.
Yes, yes, Jello to open in the Israelites cross they walked. Okay, hold on a second if you go to Exodus 15, and you read that, and actually 13 and 14, they're, they're the part of part of the world you know southwestern Asia, Middle East, and they're at a confluent point known as the Sea of Reeds that's where the saltwater mixes with the freshwater and it says a strong easterly wind blue all night.
Now if you go look at meteorology report and around that time in the spring, and you will see that the temperature could go down to 20 degrees Fahrenheit or minus six Celsius.
Okay, and the end of the wind blew all night and but and the Israelites were able to walk on that it was divided and they were able to walk on it as if it was dry land.
Okay. Now, what were they doing, they were walking on an ice bridge. Now what when you're walking on ice.
Aren't you walking on water. I've walked on water before. What steam water and ice is water.
Now that follows through now. Now hold on if you keep reading the story morning came, the sun was out Pharaoh pursued, but they fell to the bottom like a stone, wait a second, and it says they fell to the bottom.
Now, how can you fall to the bottom if you're already walking on the bottom. Can you answer that.
You can't fall to the bottom unless you unless you're up top.
So what's crazy about it is when you read that text now they don't have words for ice and snow. Very, very good point.
I'm on board with all that because in my own research, I have found three separate bodies of groups of people leaving Exodus at the exact same time. And one of them went over land and yes they did cross that they did cross.
There's plenty of evidence that they crossed over.
Yeah, but my point here is, let's just take what's out of the text. Right. And can we is that usable what picture do we get you know what storybooks are you get a script, and then they do a storybook which shows that, can we do a storybook, can we do a storybook from what is written and yes we can like, for example, I could hold this true, there is not one image of the Ark of the Covenant online under images that is accurate that you see the directions of what it should look like.
Not at all go back and read it with an eighth grader that could draw and Thomas sketch it out as it gives the specifications and will look anything like it at all there's actually a seat or a chair on it for us very small person.
But anyway, and, and there ain't no. Anyway, you give an example.
Two, two more things. You remember a few years ago, because by the way I subscribe to the Old Testament that's my law form, right.
Like, you know, learn how to keep time I'm not religious or anything but it's my law form like this is lawful this is unlawful right because the New Testament is all about how to keep time, not how to keep that but how to go into contract how to run your family how you deal with government how you deal with money all this stuff you know there's 600 laws in there, about 400 have to do with the priesthood so not that many apply to you.
But that's my judicial economy. So, people knew that and they call me the Old Testament kind of guy and a few years ago remember they were allowing.
They were they were taking the 10 Commandments out of courts right and they thought I would have a lot to say about that right. Right. Remember, and I said oh yeah you mean the 10 Commandments on stone written on stone.
And they say oh yeah those I said well what does it say, and they started reading off what the Christians think the 10 Commandments written on stone I said they could take those out those were never written on stone What do you mean Greek respect your mother and father don't wear I said that that's not in the 10 Commandments on stone.
If you want to go look up the 10 Commandments what was written on stone when Moses came down them it's completely different as a matter of fact, you know what the last commandment is the one written on some do not see the goat and its mother's milk.
All men are to appear before me three times a year. How about this one.
Well, one of the I think the seventh commandment is, you must ransom a donkey with a lamb and if you don't you're to break the donkey's neck.
This is what was written on the stone. This is in the book, this is in the book of Exodus in 38 Exodus 38 commandments but the English French German Portuguese translations they all have what we've been told.
Well actually hold on if you go to the Exodus 25 I believe where, where the Christian 10 Commandments that everyone repeats you know should not worship any other God mother and father don't murder the ones that the Christian say, okay, those were never written down on stone.
What what happened if you read the setting, the Israelites were gathered at Mount Sinai, and he says, you all to come up with me to Mount Sinai so you're a nation of priests and the people said oh hell no Moses.
Are you kidding. No way you go, you go, we're staying down here, and Moses says okay don't touch the mountain if anybody touches they die with an animal. And by the way, no shoes no shirts no service.
No, you're so you're talking about the second series of commandments not the first there's only okay there's only one set that was written on stone the one the Christians use are the first set that was never written on stone there were verbal commands given to Moses because the people didn't want to go up with him.
Completely different door. It's just like no different than no shoes no shirt shirt no service. Right, you've seen like very short. Yeah, they were never written down well they're written down in the book of separate shot in the Exodus right there written down there.
But if you look at what Moses brought did brought down it says you broke the first set now right on the second set what you wrote on the first set, you read those 10 community like those 19 commandments at all.
So here's the thing, whether you believe in it or not, how do we have. In other words, do you know Batman is, and you say yeah and you come up here and point to Mickey Mouse you don't know who bet well you've been trained wrong.
Okay. Now, right. So, this is what I'm saying, it doesn't matter if it was written by Shakespeare doesn't matter when it was written, who are we talking about what's in the text.
Are we talking about what's in it and the answer that is no. Now, once you understand this for example when they said, Are you accept or take and take I said no they're not written on the stone here's another thing that I get right.
When you go you're an Old Testament kind of guy, you know when Obama you know so they legalized same sex marriage aren't you pissed about that. And I'm like, No, why should I be pissed about that.
And they're like, Well, because you know you're an Old Testament guy and, you know, that's a death offense you know and I'm like, Why, why, why are you pissed Greek supposed to be pissed.
And I'm like, No, I'm not pissed because what they're doing when they make a law like that every they all go and register that they're same sex. When the law flips when it flips and they start applying biblical law because like you say the Christian right
Hey man, they don't have to go knocking door to door do investigations, they got your ass on a roll down in City Hall.
Do you see the point. Yeah, I do. So people that are like that don't not register or say that you are because when it flips, and they're going to start applying biblical law the way like water, you know you can't live without water but you know that most more
deaths and property damage is caused by drowning, you know, flood damage.
Right, you can drown a man face down in two inches of water.
Right, but you need water to live, what they're going to do is they're going to take the biblical law, and they're going to apply it so harshly.
Right, misinterpreted so when you talk about the Christian Reich, and they're talking about 10 commandments, and they're not talking, they're talking about the no shoes no shirt no service, they're going to use things so harshly, you get this is one that gets Christians.
This is one that gets Christians, with the open bleeding. By the way, when they say Jesus, I get confused, because it's like 13 of them. When you say Jay anybody says Jesus, I'm like, which one are you talking about the one that if you don't believe in me going to hell, or the one with the
bleeding heart you could do anything you want because the blood of the lamb, or the other one that came off a spaceship, which one are you talking about.
Right. You see, so the word interpretation has to be accurate version doesn't.
One thing when I start speaking on the Bible, I have to say, by the way, we're going to talk about the Bible, which there is no translation of the Bible. There is none, they're all versions, I just want to say that.
And you know that Jason when you look upwards you recently been talking about the seals and you brought up. It's not properly translated there is no translation.
Now I'm not religious. I don't even believe in it I use it as my law form.
Right. Now here's the thing I got an eight guys I'm an atheist Greek I tried to do what you said but I'm an atheist I don't want to go to that book. I said okay, so you're an atheist so do you believe in the laws of the state.
And they're like, yes I do. Okay, then the state is your God and April 1 is your holiday.
You see where you get your law form, and it's been accepted so this is the interesting point there's a so many points there's nothing here's the thing, less than one, if I said without it with very little exception there are no Christians that know what I just said here at all.
And I've gone into many, many, many, many, many hours and examples and showed how it was sewn together.
Now, the first five books of the Old Testament you would need us, whether it was done 300 BC or back then or whatever you would still need a supercomputer to put together what's in there.
Every 49th letter spells Torah, in one direction and then it doesn't reverse in another book and in the middle book by Yika, which is Leviticus it spells YHWH every seventh letter.
And in order to do that kind of code where every 49th letter repeats, and every seventh letter, you know, code you know series repeats in another book, you would need a supercomputer to do that even that would have a hard problem so I don't know how these guys figured it
out but one thing I do know Jason, is that mankind did not start off in a cave we start off very very high, very very high technology. So either way.
Yeah, that's why here you know we talked about the underground a lot. Okay, I'm gonna give you a scenario I just built a new house, and I bought new furniture to go with my new three bedroom house right does that make that okay with you, right.
Okay, so got the new house and here comes all the new furniture. Here comes all the new furniture and I'm going to direct that all those furniture movies put all the furniture on the roof because I'm going to be living on the roof all year round.
How's that sound. It sounds like you're fucking crazy. You live inside the house. Why, because you're sheltered from your protected your shelter from weather, and all that. So when you see a surface of a world, and you've got inhabitants living on the surface freely.
What a bunch of idiots, the advanced society goes inside the house, you see, and this is some of the stuff that I've been talking about for a long time.
Yeah, this is all very fascinating and you have completely fried my circuits I'm overwhelmed.
I can tell a little bit. There is no, there is no.
There, it's not a situation where I'm not comprehending what you're saying it is a situation where my mind is entirely absorbing each independent fact and I'm already drawing all these necessary connections from my own material from my own knowledge base, and yet before I can actually put a full picture together you've moved on.
So I'm going to fully admit that this is probably one of the few videos that I'm going to watch multiple times in order to fully process everything that has been said, because, oh, but I do want to stick to my little two hour venue here because you are packing way more information in than the average person is going to be able to assess, I know that the people listening right now are going to be listening to this video, multiple times, and your email is probably going to blow up.
Well, like I said I'm only used to having five or six listeners so you know, that's fine. Yeah, I usually try to if someone emails I try to get back within 24 hours or the most 48, and I don't have a crew to assemble stuff we have a crappy internet presence.
But you can contact me, and it's a, this is not what we get into is not for public consumption whatsoever, not deeper stuff, especially when we get into the Greek speak what I call it what I do is for doers.
If you're just sitting on a keyboard all day and that's your job you can't don't I, if you got dirt under your fingernails you know how to use a wrench, you build stuff make stuff.
You listen to a lot of stuff that goes on in Greek so you could use it. Right.
And the main thing that I would leave off with is you know when you live in a neighborhood you go to this guy he makes a good barbecue this guy could fix your car, all this right.
What I suggest is people learning how to fix your body is what's called physiological medical stuff you need a dentist.
You know how they said people died at a young age years ago. That was because if someone insulted you you had a duel with them. People I went to a lot of ancient cemeteries and people are tagged off 8090 years old nobody died.
There are a lot of people that died off young because someone insulted them, and they went out and duked it out you see, that's why you had what the reason why people are living longer is because sewer water and freshwater lines have been separated enough that even though the tap water sucks you still get fairly clean water and the sewer water is way and and dentistry.
If you go look at a late 1800s death certificates cause of death poisoning of the teeth poisoning of the teeth. So it's actually the dentists, and the separation, you know all the cholera breakouts were so simple to fix because the sewer line and the water lines were running one was infiltrating the other right.
So, we, no matter how bad the tap water is. So when they said they had a pen whatever I said that's bullshit because we got running water and sewer. There's no way you can have that. And if you want to know how to do a bubonic plague it ain't the way they're saying.
So, anyway, what I suggest is people start learning. Find who in your neighborhood is good at like if you broke a leg or got cut open or dentistry or whatever, because in the future, infrastructure goes down, you're not going to wait.
You're not going to get the little yellow book it says health for medical surgery for dummies then know you want to start now.
Absolutely correct. Yeah, and I'm maybe I mean I'm gonna be pretty soon going to be in my 60th year. Right. So, whether I'm around for that or not now I've been giving a different, a different thing by the way the Christ was when he was born it's not December 25, it was the third, it was the 11th
day of the, of the September, three BC. That's an in the astronomical thing. That's why they, they had that big birthday party for him on September 11 right. Are you familiar with that astrologically astrologically.
No, I have like, I have like 11 or 12 different sources from the ancient world that show that Jesus was born between three and two BC. Yeah. Well, in the book of Revelation it gives a very specific astronomical alignment.
Five astronomical bodies which gets it down to 20 minutes, you know to astronomical bodies gets it down to half a day. One gets it that well I'm sorry to astronomical bodies gets it down to a week.
So the more astronomical bodies you have the finer it gets. So anyway we get into all this other stuff now I'm not saying you should I believe in it you should believe in it it's true or not but are we talking about what's in the book itself.
No different than, you know, don't tell me you know who Batman is and you point to Mickey Mouse on the wall that we got a problem there but you go ahead with your friends and you think that we're not talking about the same thing.
I agree 100% I believe 100% Jesus was here. He walked this earth he did that thing but we do have I know historically of three separate Jesus's that we're all living at the same time.
None of them really have a life like the gospel Jesus. Well here's the thing. I'm not saying he was here or not I'm saying are we talking about what's memorialized in the text there's a lot of info in there.
Yeah, if we read it objectively and I find no one is and that's what we get into I'm not telling you know the answer is when they asked me they thought I'd be upset taking 10 commandments and what they're doing seems like I couldn't care less, but I'm telling you why it's being done, kind of like what you do.
You know, so that's why I think a lot of our lot of the narrative that I have and what you have dovetail well together. And thanks for having me.
I agree. Listen, I there's a few takeaways here. I just want to itemize just to show you and my community that I was paying attention.
One of the first things that drew my attention was your mention of the kittens, and how the kittens seem to already have their programming, and by extension that would be all of nature and we're talking about visceral pro programming we're talking about things that the animal kingdom seems to already I nately know, and yet, humans babies were babies are absorbing from from, you know, their, their environment and they're watching their analytical, but it almost you almost are promoting simulation theory without saying it.
Other than the observer, everything else is a part of the environment. So, we could further this on some other time, I have a lot of in depth analysis on what electricity is what they're calling nuclear.
Oh yeah, we definitely have discussions in the future I'm just doing some bullet point takeaways, like simulation theory is what came to my, my mind when you were talking about that I just didn't want to interrupt.
I had a, an addition of that and I put Emerson's Moby Dick in there and it did the same thing it did for the Bible I'm talking about a different kind of code with just letters specifically not words.
Right. It's a mathematical.
The other thing is with the 2178 as some kind of a fantastic number that we're in a simulation before I heard you on that. I thought it was a Capricor's number I don't know if you're familiar with Capricor's number it's with a cake, look it up.
That was a magic number that any for any four digit number you through seven steps always goes back to 6174. So that number 6174 was considered a magic number and you brought up 2178. Anyway, we can go on and on and on.
Yeah.
window in a, in a building, looking at other architectural constructions miles away, something so simple because we're truly on a sphere, the plumb line will show it
exaggerated big time. Wow.
I say, how come no I've never seen anybody not even the flat earthers told me anything like that. So, it's amazing. Also,
what was that.
Oh, this has nothing to do with you, but a Bob Collins I saw you in the chat from Moscow, Texas, I passed through Moscow, Texas, all the time to go visit my buddy Barry a part of the office project, reach out to me man would drink some coffee or something.
Also, the, the, I just want to make the words nice and opinion you educated me on some things I'm eager to learn more about how we've been deceived in our vernacular in the meanings of words, and I want to sum up.
And I want to sum up this entire video with with a message to my community that guys listen I'm not easily impressed I'm not easily impressed you know my history, you know the breadth and scope of my of my material, you also know my shortcomings.
But I'm going to tell you that the signature of genius is always the ability, the art of abbreviation, the ability to not only condense a tremendous amount of information into a small period of time but also the ability to communicate it in comprehensible terms.
And that's exactly what this man has done. So I want to close this video and thank you for being my guest. If there's anything that you want to say before we check out. Now's the time to do it.
Oh no, we're good. Thanks for the flowers.
Yeah, well we're not dating but yeah you earned it.
All right guys I'm gonna check out. I got some food on my mind, and we hit this beautiful outro, and I will see you guys next because tomorrow we're going live. We're going to be talking about the Shroud of Turin.