Okay.
How's my sound quality, by the way? I'm on a different machine, different headset, everything.
Yeah, you sound much better.
More like I should on radio, yeah.
Absolutely. There's more bottom end to your sound now.
Yeah, and no crackle and the consonants come through clearly, right?
Absolutely.
Absolutely. So, here's the thing.
I'm just going to provide a quick little thing for the...
Actually, I won't even provide a quick little thing for the listeners
because I already set the recording for automated, so it's going right now.
Well, export.
Okay.
All right, and you're going to probably do whatever you have to do, right?
To edit or whatever?
Yeah, well, I won't edit very much, but what we'll do is just take it from here.
I mean, obviously, we talked about doing this on the show,
and this will go into the ocelli.com member section.
So, there you go, and I'll let people know that it's there,
and we'll see what happens from there.
Obviously, this is content which is not normally heard on the air
and, therefore, kind of exclusive to the website
because, well, it's not a show that's been done publicly.
So, there we go.
Yeah.
And I don't think I need to edit this at all.
Hell, we'll just let it run as it is.
Yeah, and since it's in this private arena,
we can really open up and discuss what's going on.
That might sound truly fantastic or truly ridiculous to some.
It depends on how much training you have, formal training, you know,
because what we're going to be discussing doesn't go along with academia,
but it goes along with what anyone can perceive.
That's what makes some of the comments might sound ridiculous, right?
Well, you know, that's the thing is that a lot of fantastic claims
are made by individuals, you know,
well ahead of when it becomes acceptable to what they call academia, right?
And quite often, it's really amazing to me
when some of those things become part of the reality
without ever being part of academic structure.
They can't.
They can't because by definition,
academics are supposed to be impractical, theoretical, and non-conclusive.
Exactly.
Never coming to a conclusion, that sticks with me.
When you passed along that etymological breakdown of the word academic,
not coming to a conclusion is just...
And you know what?
For me, those words sum it all up right there
because regardless of the exercise,
they don't seem to come to a conclusion.
They can't.
You know, the thing is people are afraid of absolutes.
How many times have you heard people shy away from discussions
that mention things in an absolute fashion?
And everyone likes to stay in that presumptive or opinionated realm.
And people one day will find out that there are absolutes.
And one absolute that can be made is in fields of the legal society,
academia, the medical society.
All of the people, not some of the people in there,
are not contributing to the benefit of mankind.
They're all on the agenda.
This is because of the time period we're speaking in, right?
And the agenda is not that they're going to get you,
they want us all dead, or this or that or the other.
The Illuminati or whatever, that's not the agenda.
The agenda is they all provide very, very low qualitative work.
The quality of what they do is so low at this point
that it's not even worth revisiting the entire institution.
The whole thing needs to be scrapped
and restarted as if there was no wheel.
Right.
And in a practical sense, to be honest with you,
starting with this particular subject
for the consumption of the members only section,
and by the way, in case you're listening to this
and not sure what's going on,
of course this is my partner on the Ocelli and the Greek show,
The Greek, with me.
Of course, I am always on this website.
But this is the other end of the sonic entity
known as Ocelli and the Greek.
And we're going to have a rare discussion about something
that really does bring us back to the beginning,
the bare minimum, the basics of life itself,
water.
That's right.
What is water?
Quite appropriate.
And how about we start with an interesting observation,
which I find, you know,
it seems like it's one of those relative discussions
that's not necessarily essential
when talking about what water is
and the fact that it is one of those essentials of life.
I'm sure you wouldn't dispute that, right?
Mm-hmm.
It's more than essential of life.
It's a mother substance, as we'll get into it, yeah.
Right.
And so let's start off with an interesting kind of question,
which is, why does the bucket of water weigh
more than a bucket of air?
Right.
It sounds like a ridiculous question, doesn't it?
Yeah.
It seems really innocuous.
Right.
Because I've got a bucket of water
and a bucket that's empty, right?
But it's not really empty.
There's air in it.
Mm-hmm.
You know, it's open to the atmosphere.
So clearly, if I lift the bucket full of water,
it's going to, to me, weigh more than the bucket of air.
But it shouldn't.
If the periodic table of elements is accurate
and if water is called H2O,
a bucket of air should be about 40% heavier
than a bucket of liquid water.
Now, listen to this carefully.
Mm-hmm.
If water is H2O and the periodic table of elements is accurate,
then, let's go back to the question,
then why does a bucket of water weigh more than a bucket of air?
Let's take that apart for a moment.
And this is a two-fold answer and a two-fold question.
Well, right.
Because part of it, you'd have to,
in order to qualify that statement,
to really make it, you know, scientifically replicatable,
why is it you have to understand both substances also a little bit?
So air is actually made up of what versus the water?
Exactly.
And hold on, Chuck.
When you look at it,
remember the part of the question is not only why does a bucket of water
weigh more than a bucket of air,
being the, let's say, a proverbial question or a rhetorical question.
Typically, you'll have academic scientists, people in the industry,
anyone with any form of training laugh,
or even no training in the field of science or physics or materials
also laugh, right?
Mm-hmm.
Now, that's the first part.
The second part is if water is H2O,
because that's what everyone assumes it is,
and the periodic table of elements is accurate.
Now, let's look at that point.
I've been on conference calls with,
because I've been working with water for over 10 years
and I'm known in that industry as the go-to person
for covert type of cleanup projects.
Let's just leave it at that.
Because not using conventional means.
And whenever you get thrusted into a new group,
you have these things called conference calls and meetings
and video Skypes and things like that.
And typically, there's scientists, engineers,
people in the water cleanup industry,
from the fracking industry, nuclear, drinking, municipality,
all these kinds of, you know, anything that water,
bottling, I've run into them all,
MIT professors, Stanford professors.
Now, typically, when you get into a meeting,
they like to go across the table
and they each introduce themselves with their names
and what their education was,
what university they went to,
what level of degree they have,
and their work experience.
And then they go to the next guy in the table.
And they go all...
So, it's like I'm Dr. Smith
and I have a PhD in, you know, XYZ field,
and I have also been someone who's been employed
under that office, you know, via XYZ industry
and blah, blah.
In other words, their credentials.
Yeah, their credentials.
So, they get around to me and they say,
well, I'm known as the Greek
and I'm just visiting this planet taking notes.
And by the way, why does a bucket of water
weigh more than a bucket of air?
And they all start laughing, right?
Right.
And then, you know, we get over,
I'm just visiting, taking notes,
but they all start laughing about
why does a bucket of water
weigh more than a bucket of air.
And they say, if water is H2O
and the periodic table of elements is accurate,
that shouldn't be true.
And then they start chuckling a little bit more
and I say, well, let's look at it.
If water is H2O,
on the periodic table,
hydrogen has an elemental weight of 1
and oxygen has an elemental weight of...
I'm rounding off these numbers here...
16.
So, a mole or a molecular weight of water,
if it were H2O, would be H2,
which would be 2 plus 16, 1 oxygen,
would have a weight of 18,
a molecular weight of 18.
Right.
Now, if we look at air,
we look at all the major five
or let's say major nine constituents in air,
a couple of them being noble gases.
If you...
I was thinking of pulling it up for you to see it,
but I can just tell you,
you can validate this,
if you do a search
on what is the molecular weight of air,
guess what it is.
It's 28.6 to 29.
Well, now hang on a second.
That's a far cry from 18, isn't it?
Well, certainly it is.
It's not quite double,
but getting there.
And, of course, air,
just quantitatively,
let's think about this for a moment,
there are two essential elements, right,
that are contained in water,
but air actually contains both of those things.
Plus, I mean,
that's a real simple way to look at it, right?
I mean, and if you're saying
there are nine constituents to it,
then that means...
Well, there's more.
The primary ones are the nitrogen and oxygen,
and then they start becoming into the...
Then you start going into groups of inert gases
and carbon dioxides and things like that,
which, again, are molecules,
other combinations.
But the general soup,
the main ingredients,
are basically three or four.
You can say go down to about nine.
They'll typically list five
as the main constituents for air,
and we don't need to get into the air part
specifically too much.
But generally,
when I do mention that the air
is much heavier than the water,
quite almost double on the molecule,
the response I get from these water experts is,
well, one is a liquid, one is a gas.
And I'm like, well, first of all,
we're looking at one molecule
irrelevant of phase, right?
So it doesn't matter.
The other thing is,
water doesn't have a gas phase.
It has only a liquid or solid phase, okay?
And now they stop laughing.
Now they start to sober up a little bit
because they know I hit them
on something that is so obvious.
Now, when I say periodic table,
we're discussing, oh, I don't know,
when do they start throwing in
the periodic table in the public fool system?
About eighth grade, ninth grade, around there?
Yes, somewhere in there.
I would say what they would typically describe
as the later part of middle school.
And again, I say, well, hydrogen and oxygen
being what water is supposed to be
according to what they teach us,
I mean, that's one of the first things
they show us on this periodic table
is stuff like that and salts
and other common sort of combinations, right,
that make up what is allegedly,
you know, that allegedly make up,
I should say, very common things.
Isn't it true that, you know,
hydrogen and oxygen are part of
the main constituents for air as well?
So, it changes, though.
Oxygen probably more than the hydrogen,
but as we progress,
let's just bear this thought in mind.
I'm giving the setting here,
let's say in a conference with these guys
that are captains of industry
and the heads of where anyone and everyone
goes to get knowledge on water for.
Now, just to continue on this thought,
because this is important on the,
on what can be imparted from one's experience
when you start learning about these things,
is they no longer are laughing,
these professors and captains of industry,
but they still stick to the idea
that one is a liquid and one is a gas,
or a density, okay?
Now, you can go and get what's called
an A-tank at a welding shop
and tell them to fill it with compressed air,
which is now in a liquid form, okay?
And then you have a corresponding
equal-sized tank filled with water, okay?
The one with the air in liquid form
is still lighter than the one with water,
but it shouldn't be.
So what is going on?
This is the point where they start to get really upset,
because with the listener, or just you and I,
I've never introduced this to you, by the way,
and before this is the first time
I think I've brought it up and we've discussed it,
none of these concepts that we've brought up so far
are complex, ethereal, or academic,
or esoteric.
It's very simple for anyone to look up.
Why does a bucket of water
weigh more than a bucket of air
if water is H2O
and the periodic table of elements is accurate?
It shouldn't.
So now this is not such a ridiculous question.
The important thing here is
how can we have senior people in this field
procuring knowledge on water
and have missed such a fine,
but yet important detail
that water, being H2O,
just simply doesn't add up
according to their own memorialization of the science,
meaning the periodic table.
So the importance of this, Chuck,
is that if this question,
which seemingly seems ridiculous on its face,
the bucket of water, bucket of air question,
if it is pressed,
it has enough legs
to tear down the entire scientific community
regarding water.
That's why I said, hold on, this is real important here.
This is the thread
that unravels the cheap sweater
if someone pulls on it.
And it hasn't been done yet.
And it will be done.
Well, you know, I have in my mind
an idea of how that could be answered
by these academics
that I'm imagining sitting around this table.
Of course, I am not an academic
and did not receive any training
beyond what they call high school.
You know, but...
Be thankful you didn't.
Yeah, I should be thankful.
But at the same time,
I actually have an idea
of how that could be answered.
So I don't know if you want to get to that.
Yeah, let's do it.
You know, here's my answer.
Wouldn't the shape of the molecules
dictate how much space they could take up, right?
So, if you, for instance,
were to come up with, you know,
20 cubic yards of something
that is lighter by nature,
you know, and it takes up more space.
Like, for instance,
a 3x3x3 block of styrofoam
is not as heavy as
a 3x3x3 block of cement, right?
Now, why is that?
Is it simply the nature of the material
or is it that the material
at its most basic form
is simply spread out
over a greater amount of space?
Like, in other words,
even if the molecular weight differs,
okay, even if air should weigh more
on the molecular level,
if the molecules are in
a greater amount of space...
Right, but Chuck,
doughnuts to doughnuts,
apples to apples,
liquid air and water
both being liquid form,
still the water is heavier
and it shouldn't be.
Well, that's where the stumper is
because, yeah, the compressed air
should sort of equal it
because it will take up...
Or weigh more.
It should actually...
According...
Now, this is the whole thing.
Let's just repeat this.
If water is H2O,
remember, not that it is,
if it is,
and if the periodic table of elements
is accurate,
why does a bucket of water
weigh more than a bucket of air?
Let me just preclude something here.
I've been on several chats
and late-night call-in shows
since roughly what they call 2010
on the Pope's work schedule.
Right.
And I would always introduce that question
and there would always be
at least anywhere between
one and five people
that would try to chase me around
to answer that question
for months or years after that.
For a while on the Internet scene,
I was known as the guy
who was always asking the question,
why does a bucket of water
weigh more than a bucket of air?
And one guy got tired of other people
talking about it
that he got drunk and called in
and he says,
hey Greek,
why does a bucket of shit
weigh more than a bucket of air?
You know,
just because I'm tired of that stuff.
So anyway.
That's pretty funny.
So anyway,
so the whole thing here
is very interesting.
We can look at it very closely.
Well, maybe why,
let's just look at it this way.
Why do they say water is H2O?
Well,
let's take it apart
because it's kind of difficult
to wrap your head around the question,
the bucket question,
until we start clearing up
the H2O part.
Okay.
And the H2O is easy to clear up.
What happened was,
generally,
what was memorialized
or canonized
as the holy grail to water
was a guy,
one of the people,
was William Grove
in the early 1800s,
late 1700s,
decided to put some metal plates
in water and electrify them
and he noticed hydrogen
coming off of one side
of the container
off of one plate
and he noticed the oxygen
coming off of the other.
So the hydrogen
coming off the negative
and the oxygen
coming off the positive.
And he kept doing this
and the water volume
started to decrease.
And what he did then,
he called a bunch of his friends
and they did a peer review
within a week
and said,
oh look,
he's breaking up water
into hydrogen and oxygen.
And they wrote a paper on it
and that's it.
So they basically did
three days worth of research
and it hasn't changed for over,
I don't know,
what's about 1811,
1813,
let's say 200 and what,
three years?
Right.
Right?
So there hasn't been
any more research
on that subject since then.
So how difficult would it be
for anyone to pick up
research on this?
So we're talking about
three to four days worth
of research,
200 years ago,
it's been left at that.
Wouldn't be that difficult
to pick it up right now
and further that, right?
Oh, it shouldn't be.
And nothing has been done
since then on this,
I assure you,
academically or scientifically,
that is told to the public,
let's say.
That's why in the beginning
we're doing,
I said,
let's discuss water
off the air
and see how it goes.
Right.
So here,
this is the rest of the story.
As they kept applying
electricity,
the water volume
would decrease
and more hydrogen
and more oxygen
were being given off,
right?
But what they noticed
is that when you got
to a certain volume,
that process ceased.
In other words,
there's something called
electrolysis
where you convert
water into hydrogen
and oxygen
and it tricks you
thinking because
the water volume
is decreasing,
that water,
you're breaking it up
into its main constituents,
right?
But no one in the history
of mankind
has ever electrolyzed
an entire volume
of water
into hydrogen and oxygen.
Once you get past
a little bit more
than halfway,
that process stops
and other things
start to happen.
Different gases
start to come off
or no gases,
right?
Then they have to add
electrolytes
and the water starts
to get hot
and it boils off.
But what happens there
is when this electrolysis
process stops
because in reality,
let's give the spoiler,
what's happening is
you're not breaking up
water with electricity
into its basic forms.
You're actually
creating that.
You're disintegrating
a component of the water
into hydrogen and oxygen
but it's not what water
is made of
because as we continue
this process,
the gas stops coming off
and that given a volume
of water
is still water
but it has an interesting
quality to it
and it's used
in certain industries
and when I give you the name,
it'll ring a bell.
That water
is called deuterium.
And if you continue that
under a vacuum,
you might get some more gases
and then it stops again.
And then you continue
and you get something
called tritium
which goes for about
100,000 bucks
for a 55 gallon drum
of that crap.
So this is how these things
are made very simply.
Now you see why
I don't want to discuss this
on open air really.
So no one in the history of man
has ever,
if water is H2O,
no one has ever proved
that they could take
a given amount of water,
meaning drink the whole glass
or the whole bucket
into hydrogen and oxygen.
No one was ever able to do that.
It cannot be done.
So water stops
and at that point
that's when all the physicists
and the scientists
turn off the lights
and leave
and try to find an interesting
party to go to
because they can't look
at the subject anymore.
Well, and that's really strange
because that would indicate
that there's actually
more to it,
wouldn't it?
Exactly.
And in addition,
you know,
another strange thing
that just sort of
comes to my mind
is I don't know
if you remember this
from a few years ago
and I'm not sure
if this company
is in business anymore
but there was a company
that claimed to add
additional oxygen
to the H2O,
you know,
and that was sort of
a weird health water thing
that sort of came and went.
I don't know
if it still exists now.
We'll go down the line
and you'll see
if that makes sense
later on
as we keep discussing
what's going on with water.
Okay.
Now,
what's interesting about water
just to, you know,
because this can be
many, many hours
just discussing
the nature of water
but just to show
how fantastic water is.
Now,
what has happened there
is we just showed
how the oversimplification
of the label H2O
is not true.
Right.
Well, then what is true?
Well, what is true
is why don't we
start discussing
things that appear
and disappear in reality
right in front of us
that no one discusses.
Like, for example,
if you ever see
a thundercloud come in
and one that potentially
will drop a lot of water
on an area of a city
or in the country
or wherever you might be,
with your own eye,
after the storm is over,
you can see there's
millions of tons of water
if it covers many square miles
because what I'm saying
is roughly
a gallon of water
weighs about eight pounds
or it's a cube
that's about six and a half
by six and a half
weighs about eight pounds.
And if you've ever seen
how much rain can fall down,
if you measure all that
over the square area,
that is millions
of tons of water.
Okay.
Let me ask you,
when you look at those clouds,
do they look like
they're being weighed down
by millions of tons?
Well, no.
No, not at all.
And I've got to tell you
something that's even
more observable
in case somebody
might have missed
what you just explained.
If one just takes a glass
or a bucket,
some kind of container,
and puts it outside
during rainfall,
you collect, you know,
a certain amount of inches,
let's just say,
in your bucket, right?
And if you put out
like what they call
a five-gallon paint bucket,
you know,
during a decent rainfall,
you might very well
pick yourself up
a couple of pounds of water
during a good, you know,
substantial rainfall, right?
Now, if you extrapolate from that,
that over just the area
of your town,
or the area of the nearest
square mile,
and you multiply it
by the amount of water
that's collected in that bucket,
which could have only grabbed,
you know,
what are we talking about,
a one-spoil meth,
you know,
a circular,
and you think about it,
the amount of weight
that that water would carry
would be, well,
greater than...
Two Titanic's,
about maybe a hundred Titanic's
or Lusitania's
over being held up
by the clouds.
Yeah,
and I'm just talking about,
you know,
a square mile or two
that would be this immense,
you know,
you want to say Titanic's,
we could talk about
Mack trucks,
or buildings,
the weight of buildings,
you know,
multiples,
like more than
the weight of the buildings
that it's falling on,
even,
if you think about it,
so you look up
at these clouds,
and that doesn't make
any sort of sense.
And there's no water
in the clouds,
and any pilot
flies into the cloud
to avoid the storm.
And it is not condensation.
here's an interesting part.
I was thinking
maybe keeping it practical,
because anyone listening
should be able
to walk away
from this conversation
we're having
and be able to improve
their water quality,
but here's something
to consider
more on the
extreme esoteric side,
is that typically
the forecasters
and the weather people
tell you that the rain happens
by moisture
condensing around dust.
And that,
of course,
doesn't make any sense,
but that's what people
have bought and believed.
Now,
there was a recent study
a few years ago
in Jerusalem.
A few scientists
decided to
get the latest
and the greatest toys,
you know,
scientific sensors
and things like that,
and they measured
the dust particles
in the atmosphere
and the amount of moisture,
and when the storm ensued,
there was no correlation
between the moisture
in the air
and the dust particles
at all whatsoever.
There aren't that many
dust particles
or that much condensation
to make that much volume
of measurable liquid water.
Now,
just to finish off
the esoteric side
a little bit,
that's the practical side,
and the esoteric side
was that they actually wrote
in a paper
and published it
that it appears
that a few nanoseconds
or microseconds,
which is not milliseconds,
microseconds,
prior to the water forming
it appeared
that the water
came out of nowhere.
It just formed
out of nowhere,
and this was
on the internet
for a little while,
and they pulled it.
The entire thing
has been pulled.
The people have been redacted.
You know,
their names have been pulled
and all that,
and they had spent
over five years
studying this.
So,
this is very similar
to the discussion
you and I had
about the container,
the human body,
as the body is under
a slight vacuum condition,
and people,
maybe,
I don't know
if I'm speaking too fast
or these are new ideas,
I've seen in the chat once
someone saying
on a replay on AFR,
the Greeks said
the body's under a vacuum.
How come when I cut myself
I still bleed?
Well,
the thing is,
we say the body's under
a slight vacuum condition,
right?
So,
when you cut yourself,
the vacuum is broken,
and when the vacuum
is broken,
you wait for it
to equalize,
and then the blood
starts to flow out,
right?
You see?
So,
I just wanted
to bring that up,
but the reason
I brought up the body
is because
when you sweat,
see,
your skin is not porous,
even though you have
these things called pores,
they're only skin deep,
you know,
no pun intended.
They're small
ovoid-shaped
depressions
under the skin,
and they stop
right there,
and the moisture
forms in them,
and then it's ejected
out of the pore
in the form of sweat.
Where does the water
come from
if the skin
is impervious,
you see?
And this is the entire
crux of the matter
is that when mankind,
I used to always say,
when mankind
masters water,
he will master
the physical world.
And it's astonishing
to see how people
have fallen
for the H2O idea,
and all of the reasoning
and folklore
surrounding
what water is.
Now,
I want to get
maybe
further on
down the road
on the other things,
because we've also
covered the idea
of what water
may not be H2O,
and maybe get
into some
of the meat
and potato
or the actual
wet stuff
that people
can grab
and use.
Because at this point,
I think we've
done enough
to kick
the establishment
and the shins
about what nonsense
they're procuring
about how water
is perceived
or their science
around it.
All right.
And at this point,
we could get into
the fact that people
do collect
and store water
for various purposes.
I mean,
there's a lot
One might collect it
for drinking,
or, you know,
it's collected
in your water tanks
in your house
or whatever
for various purposes.
But, I mean,
there has been
a lot of things
that have gone into
the way water
is stored.
Or not stored.
Right?
And pretty interesting
that, you know,
I'm still fascinated
by the idea
that a cloud
contains no water.
You know,
how does it actually
produce?
And, of course,
they scrub that,
because
that's
Yeah.
We could spend
another quick second.
There's something called
field effects.
You know,
not baseball
or football field,
but a field like,
you know,
how people are worried
about Wi-Fi,
you know,
microwaves,
cell phone towers.
You know,
you don't see it,
feel it.
There are devices
that can measure
these fields
that can be harmful.
Right?
Electromagnetic radiation.
Those are fields.
Water is a byproduct
of a biological
field effect.
And it's a,
well,
it's called,
the ancients called it
the ether.
That was also part of
the science
up until the 1920s.
And then it was just
squashed with relativism
with Einstein.
Right.
Where, you know,
everyone went
really dumb.
That was the main
dummy load.
And it's basically
a field effect.
Imagine the world
of Gene Roddenberry
and Star Trek.
It's not that difficult
to imagine
the kind of
of field effects
in science fiction.
Like,
we're being attacked.
Turn on the force field.
Right?
Right.
Okay.
Or the food replicator
or being
beamed
aboard ship.
These are fields
that do these things,
right?
Right.
So, generally speaking,
what it is
is something that
affects the environment
so that
things don't behave
in precisely
the way they would
in an unaffected
environment.
Whether it's
the force field
or something else.
In other words,
it interacts.
It actually changes
the environment
so that
different constituents
once again
participating in that environment
would then
have different results
to their motion,
to their interactivity.
Things like that.
For instance,
the idea of shields
or the force fields
or whatever.
You know,
you haven't changed
the weapon being fired.
You haven't changed
the ship.
But you have
erected a field
as a buffer
because that's
the purpose of it.
But not every field
is necessarily a buffer.
It may actually change
what's happening.
And it interacts
and the force field
can actually
stop physical matter.
Right.
But yet you don't see it.
Very similar to
magnetism.
You can have two magnets
in your hand
and you can feel them
either attracting
or repulsing
if you flip them around.
And it's almost like
when you have them
in repulsion mode
and you push them together,
especially if they're
weak magnets
or most magnets,
you feel like there's
like a jelly substance
in there.
You know,
it's like a jelly
kind of feeling
like you're pushing
on a soft rubber
or some jello or something.
And when you pull
the magnets apart,
that jelly doesn't
fall to the floor.
You know,
it's just gone.
You see.
So these are all
field effects
that create
the water
from basically
nothing.
But it's not nothing.
It's just like
when electricity
will be understood
in the future
as it was
100 years ago,
that it's all
field effects.
I've cut wires
many times
very carefully
while there was
electrical voltage
and current
going through them.
I cut them
very carefully
one at a time
not to short them.
And I was always
prepared with a dustpan
for all the millions
of electrons
that were going to
fall out of the wire.
I still haven't
found them.
Right?
So you see,
it's a field
that runs between
the wires.
Yeah,
so once we
as a society
and I say we
because I'm still
here,
as a society
decide to accept
the obvious,
what is really
going on in front of us,
not what we're just
being told
about these things,
we'll be able
to group together
and then have
a true consensus
on reality.
But right now
everyone is just
very glad
to do about
what they're doing
which is nothing
wrong with that.
Everyone has their
own pursuit
and when they
want to know about
water or electricity
or anything else
they have to go to
these quote unquote
experts because
that's their field
and they have to
trust them
because people
are too busy
doing what they
want to do.
And right now
all of these
experts don't know
what's going on
and they're deceiving
indeliberately
in most cases
the population
and to actually
get into the
field science
and how water
is produced
is quite esoteric
but if one
understands the
analogy of the
Gene Roddenberry
Star Trek idea
how there were
things behind that
to do that
when man
understands the
field sciences
then he can
synthesize the
field and execute
the field,
you see.
And some of us
can do it
at this point.
Some of us
meaning surface
dwelling earth
inhabitants and
it's not good
for one's health
to do even
on a call like this
to discuss too much
of that side
because you know
what I mean
that's not good
for your health,
right?
Yeah.
So just moving on
one of the other
items here
I was thinking
about getting
to the nuts and
bolts of things
where people can
actually hear this
and walk away
with something
practical
is what I always
like to do.
It's kind of like
if you see someone
with a bleeding thumb
you say well wrap
this around it
instead of saying
hey your thumb is
bleeding,
yeah I know,
jerk off,
what do you got?
Help them.
You got to say
something,
you got to do
something when
there's a need.
And the reason
I'm saying it that
way is because
you can go on the
internet right now
and you find all
kinds of stuff
about water,
heavy water,
light water,
structured water,
oxygen water,
miracle water,
healing water,
living water,
it's all garbage,
it's all rubbish.
None of them get
into the nuts and
bolts.
You even got some
old guy running
around talking about
whatever,
and some young guy
that looks real
earthy,
crunchy,
and anyway these
people are water
experts supposedly
and I've listened
to their stuff
and tried to
communicate with
them and said
why don't you
just mention some
of the basic points
and they never
answer and just
like the scientists
who cannot explain
why a bucket of
water should weigh
more than a
bucket of air.
So one of the
reasons I think
we're doing this
also is so people
can walk away
with some basic
knowledge that works
in a very simple
approach.
Now I think we
over maybe beat
that esoteric
course in the
beginning but I
think it's important
for people to get
anything,
any information
that kicks academia
in the shins is
worthwhile.
Right.
Yeah,
I have no problem
with you know
doing multiple
angles of the
establishing shot
for the short
film here because
it is necessary
to be sure
that it has been
covered from as
many angles as
possible so that
no one is shocked
by the information
which is meant
to follow.
Yeah.
So that's why I
think it was worthwhile
to beat that horse
a bit.
Oh yeah and the
thing is there
criminality,
so whenever you
have a high level
of criminality and
misdemeanor the
language is very
strong and it's
not that I'm
angry at them,
actually if there's
going to be any
anger or discontent
it should be to the
masses.
Why are they still
supporting these
academics?
All the colleges and
universities should
become homeless
shelters,
museums,
or storage rooms.
There's no purpose
for them or
entertainment,
whatever.
There's no purpose
for them anymore
in this society.
They are nothing
but a parasitical
entity and that's
the Greek's opinion
and it's been that
way for 30 years.
I hope it becomes
more of people's
opinion,
we might actually
end up with
something which I
discussed will be
coming in the
future,
a short age of
reason,
but to go back to
reason.
Back to it,
we did want to
make sure we
discussed storage
because this is a
practical thing.
After all,
water must be
stored in order to
be utilized,
no matter what
its components are,
what its constituents
are.
As we said at the
very beginning,
it's one of the
essentials to
efficient living.
One must have
water in order to
preserve life,
essentially.
Not to mention
the fact that
it serves many
other purposes,
but the fact is
it's one of the
staples of life
that is often
overlooked,
especially in
what they call
more civilized
modern society,
etc.,
etc.
It's certainly
one of those
sort of given
staples,
and the storage
of it is worth
examining,
I think.
The history needs
to be examined
first.
Whenever I come
across anything
new,
I always try to
find its history,
right?
Very young children
that play video
games now,
if you ask them,
they don't know.
They think video
games have been
around always,
right?
Until they learn
the history of it
and its development.
Now, when we look
at the history
of water
storage,
and what I mean
by water
storage,
it means that
the water now
is not flowing
from point A
to point B,
as simple as that.
If water is not
going from point A
to point B,
it's in storage
mode or in
non-movement
mode.
When mankind
interacted with
any liquid,
as a matter of fact,
not just water,
but oils,
milk,
perfumes,
any kind of
liquid matter,
throughout history,
they kept it
in vessels
that were
ovoid-shaped.
Ovoid is just
a term describing
something that
might appear
like an egg.
Not a cube,
not a pyramid,
not a sphere,
but egg-shaped.
One can
reference this
by the
ancient amphoras.
You can
go on the
internet
or any
reference material
you so choose
and look up
what an
amphora is.
Amphora
A-M-P-H-O-R-A
It's just
a Latin or
Greek term,
actually,
for a vessel.
These vessels,
if anyone
has ever
had any
memory of
looking at
any ancient
shipwrecks or
museums,
you would see
these vases
that didn't
have flat
bottoms.
They had
pointy bottoms.
They couldn't
stand up on
their own.
They looked
almost like urns.
Right?
And, you know,
the common
modern person
would say,
look how stupid
the ancients were.
They couldn't
design a vase
with a flat
bottom so it
could stand up
on its own.
Why did they
have to have
a pointy
side on the
bottom?
Very interesting.
And also,
you'll notice
that in nature,
whenever water
is not
flowing from
point A
to point B,
and water
is in,
I don't like
to use the word
stagnant,
but it is
proper to say
in a stagnant
mode,
it is contained
in a ovoid
shape.
Like, for example,
the eyeball
is slightly
ovoid.
Right?
The eggs
are ovoid.
Right?
There's liquid
in eggs.
The testicles,
the ovaries,
some of the
organs in the
body tend to
take on an
ovoid shape.
In the plant
kingdom,
you will see
seeds take on
an ovoid shape.
What that means,
essentially,
it is roughly
circular,
but it is
not symmetrical.
One end is
slightly blunter
than the other
that is slightly
pointier.
So you have a
pointy end and
a blunt end.
That's what makes
the ovoid shape.
And this is
what was thought
after to
store liquids.
Now, the question
is why did they
use ovoid shapes?
Because when
you have something
that is a
sphere,
let's say,
let's stick with
the round stuff,
not a cube or
a box or
just like the
square rectangular
containers you get
milk and juices
in the store now
or clear plastic
or glass bottles
with flat bottoms.
Let's get away
from that concept.
Right.
And stick with
the concept of
the ovoid for a
minute.
Well, why not
a sphere or
a ball?
You see,
because when
you have a
sphere,
by definition,
the center point
is equidistant
from any point
on the outer
part of the
sphere.
So any movement
that takes
place
inside the
sphere will
always find
a resting point
in the center
and then stagnation
sets in.
You see,
so then you
have the water
being stagnant
because even
if you kept
it moving,
once the
movement stopped,
by the symmetry
of the shape,
everything would
stop moving on
its own.
Now,
if you have a,
let's say,
let's make it
elliptical,
let's just pinch
the two ends,
well,
you still have
an asymmetric
point.
The center
moves slightly
and the
material
inside the
elliptical
container will
move from
point to point
back and forth
and then eventually
find that
adjusted center
and settle in
and become
stagnant again.
When you have
an ovoid shape
where one end
of the
circular or
curved container
is slightly
pointier
than the
opposite side,
you still have
a geometric
center
but not a
true mass
center for
energetic purposes.
So if you
got liquid
moving,
well,
what would happen
is the liquid
would move
to the blunt
end,
come back to
the center,
move to the
pointy end
and it would
change its
form
because it's
in a 3D
manner.
Try to move
back to the
center
but then
pass the
center and go
back to the
blunt end.
So there would
be this
asymmetric
reflection
that would
keep any
liquid or
gas moving
and avoid
stagnation.
The slightest,
even a tenth
of a degree
temperature
difference
anywhere on the
container
will set the
liquid into
motion if it's
ovoid,
very simply.
Because of the
lack of symmetry,
the energy,
the liquid,
the gas
in an ovoid
shape will
always be in
constant motion
with the slightest
impulse from
the exterior
environment.
Now,
that is why
they always
thought ovoid
containers because
stagnation,
absolute stagnation
or stillness
is where things
start to breed.
So they were able
to keep water
fresh.
And also,
by the way,
when you have an
ovoid shape,
you'll always
notice the
liquids in the
container are
always slightly
less than ambient
where if there
are any other
shapes,
the liquids rush
very quickly to
stabilize into the
same temperature
as the ambient
temperature,
which is very
interesting as well.
Now,
this is the
concept of the
amphora,
which is what
the ancients used
and even up until
I would say
the 19th century
it was considered
a standard way
of storing liquids.
Well,
actually,
no,
I would say
about 17th century
it started to go
away.
By the 19th century
when the
industrial revolution
came in,
that standard
was still kept
to some degree
but they started
introducing
flat bottoms
so they can
stack things,
right,
because they had
big wagons
and trucks
and trains
to move things
and they found
that they needed
the volume
of space.
Things now were
being transported
greater distances
so they wanted
to be more efficient.
So,
they started
eventually,
that's why
when you look
at the
older bottles
from the
19th century,
that Coke bottle
shape,
you see,
they knew that
the flat bottom
in it was bad
but they put
a double curve in it
hopefully that would
mitigate some of
the flat bottom
or the wine bottle
as a curved top.
Like the bottom
sort of puckers up
a bit
and in that way
you don't have
an absolutely
flat bottom
but you have
something that
can stabilize itself
at least the
container can
on a flat
surface
but you still
have that
sort of arch
that's there
and I guess
that's meant to
partially mitigate
the problem
of stillness
in the liquid.
In the beginning
the bottles were
more curved
when they introduced
the flat bottoms.
The pucker also
depends on the amount
of pressure
that would build up
and also just having
the bottom edge
of the bottle
making contact
so it doesn't
slide around.
If you look
champagne bottles
have an extreme
pucker so they
can get to
the 100 psi
in there
pounds per square inch
but the idea
of compressing
liquids into a
small space
not compressing
them in
themselves
but stacking
as many containers
as possible
and going for
that efficient
stacking
has ruined
the ability
for liquid
to maintain
a certain
quality level
and it does ruin
the quality
because even if
you keep the
milk at a
certain temperature
milk in an
ovoid container
will taste better
and also won't
spoil as quickly
even if it was
not refrigerated
so one has to
keep in their
mind that these
ancients were not
primitive or savage
for understanding
the concept of
the amphora
or the ovoid
or the egg shape
they were basically
taught this
from time immemorial
and they kept
it until they
forgot the
importance of it
and it was
overshadowed by
the importance of
modern industry
let's say.
So the
water storage
idea
is something
that would be
difficult for
anyone to
let's just
say incorporate
in their lives
by going out
to the store
and buying it
it's very difficult
to go out and
buy any liquid
already in that
shape or even
finding containers
in that shape
but it is good
to know that
it is the optimum
size because
within your life
you might
make a decision
to either
pursue that
and find ovoid
shaped containers
and prop them
up on stands
or such and
do your own
experimentation
because part of
what we're
discussing here
is foreign to
the modern convention
and would require
some experimentation
for the user.
Well right
like instantly
I'm thinking to
myself to have
a container
that you know
that is useful
and in that shape
I imagine
to myself
that I would
have to create
a rack of sorts
to put them
in a place
so that they
were less
cumbersome
as far as
taking up
additional space
and things like
that and I
could stack
any shaped
container that way
onto the
flat surfaces
the shelves
etc of
whatever it was
I was trying to
stack them on
but that requires
a little extra
work because
I dare say
they don't offer
anything like that
at your local
Walmart.
Nope.
Or even
in the decorative
let's say
one goes out
and says
well I need
let's say glass
or porcelain
or metal
or whatever
containers in that
shape
you're going to
be pretty hard
pressed to find it
on any search
I'm just
referring to
the marketplace
now.
Right.
They're going to
be difficult to find
but this is
very important
to understand
because it is
one of the
principle
geometric forms
that is required
to maintain
high quality
liquid storage
and this is
not only for
something that
reflects man's
good stewardship
of these liquids
not just water
oils or milks
and things like that
but it also reflects
what is going on
in nature
with the egg
itself and
parts of
you know plants
and parts of the
human body even
which have that
ovoid shape
where water is not
moving from
point A to point B.
And it does give me
a sensible understanding
of why an egg
is shaped the way
it is
because you know
I often wondered
that actually
you know
it seems rather odd
that an egg
has that shape
it must be
for some practical
purpose as I observe
in nature
the things that do
prevail
and continue
to
exist
are always
the things
that
you know
persist based on
the fact that they
are the most
effective and efficient
so you know
if a chicken was
born and it was
somehow
dropping square
eggs
I dare say
it would not
survive into the
next generation
or something
it would disappear
as an aberration
so the things that
do seem to have
longevity in nature
have a practical
sort of
you know
a practical
basis
to them
in their functionality
so that's why
the egg is
shaped the way
it is
kind of deal
ok
yeah
and these are
creations
you know
if you subscribe
to evolution
or whatever
you know
have fun at it
good luck
as they say
and you know
see you later
but if you see
that there is
a commonality
like all biological
things
all machines
even songs
in music
literary writings
anything and everything
that is created
has a basic
fundamental
common denominator
in it
you know
like for
let's go to music
for example
it doesn't matter
what music
you're writing
or genre
there are
fundamental
common denominators
in terms of
timing
and chords
and things like that
that all musics
share
or musicians use
or composers use
or even the people
performing the music
must be familiar with
right
even if you've never read
sheet music
there are fundamentals
in making music
that all genres
share
you'll find this
in machines
also
all machines
whether it's
you know
a car
an airplane
a railroad
an old typewriter
any machine
you can imagine
they all share
certain fundamental
common denominators
in how mechanisms work
and you will also see
these common denominators
in nature
and wherever
there's a liquid
in nature
that is not moving
from point A
to point B
you will always find it
in an ovoid shape
and a liquid
when I say liquid
it could be something
that is
like a seed
as well
which is not liquid
now
why would a seed
also take on
an ovoid shape
to some extent
if there's no liquid
in it
and that also explains
the
what we consider
to be hydrodynamic
you know
within the egg
is that way
because there is
an incoming force
that also affects
things that are
you know
like seeds
because seeds
still have
some liquid matter
in them
so it could even be
a semi-liquid material
in an example here
just to
send this idea
home
in another way
is I once saw
an image
of a
I think it was
up by the Arctic
somewhere
north of Norway
where they were doing
a
a worldwide
universal seed bank
to
in case there was
a worldwide calamity
they were storing
all these seeds
in a mountain
under the ice
are you familiar
with that story
maybe about five
six years ago
oh sure
they still talk about it
from time to time
the heirloom
seed vault
yeah
the seed vault
now when I
I really laughed
my ass off
when I saw
what they were doing
because they had
these cubical pallets
of seeds
that were stacking
and I was discussing
this with someone
and I said
when they
if they ever
pull those
cubical pallets out
only the seeds
that would be
within the pallet
an imaginary egg
if you were to
let's say
use a computer graphic
and do a dotted line
of an egg
inside of that pallet
only the seeds
in that zone
would be viable
all of the other seeds
like in the corners
of the pallets
of that cube
would not be viable
why?
you see
because the
not only is the
egg
shaped container
being imposed
to hold the liquid
important
but it also plays a part
in these field effects
that we were discussing
earlier
right
so this is another aspect
of
understanding the
ovoid shape
so
right
now how does
now I've heard you
mention several times
before
a guy named
Victor Shawberger
yes
right
now
how does he come
into this discussion
okay
Victor Shawberger
is important
to consider
because if we
speak about
electricity
and we bring up
someone like
Thomas Edison
or Nikola Tesla
it seems the
conversation
seems to flow well
because those are people
that are well known
in that field
but when we bring up
the concept of water
still
when you've mentioned
Victor Shawberger
out in public
most people have still
not heard of him
not that he
deserves fame
or infamy
but he has
pretty much
gained the ranks
of a Nikola Tesla
or let's say
Thomas Edison type
person
in the field
of water
okay
and what's interesting
about this
and ironic is
you know
you can live
without electricity
right
and that sounds
like a ridiculous
question
or a statement
to some
but yeah
I assure you
people live
quite well
without it
but can you
live without water
well no
as we stated
at the very beginning
of this discussion
it's one of the essentials
yeah
so part of
part of
human society
is certain people
might gain
certain knowledge
and it's
through duty
and responsibility
to themselves
and their creator
and to their fellow man
to share that knowledge
when they see
it's not available
right
and that's why
we attribute
fame to
Tesla and Edison
and people
like that
well right
because they were
the individuals
who sort of
codified
certain bits
of knowledge
at least
that's the way
it's understood
it's not necessarily
they were the people
who you know
originated the idea
or anything like that
but they are the ones
who sort of
put it together
in a digestible format
in one way
or another
and that we can use
now Victor Schauberger's
work has all been
set aside
but the work
that he did
nonetheless
was very important
and critical
if anyone can access
his work
and Victor
would be spelled
with a K
and the Schauberger
would be
with an S
C-H-A-U
B-E-R
G-E-R
and he was
an Austrian
came from a long family
of foresters
he lived
he was born
in the
late 1800s
and lived
till the mid
20th century
and he
and being
a forester
he had discovered
that
certain things
that were not
being discussed
that certain
qualities
of water
that were not
being discussed
or acknowledged
as being significant
and being
a forester
he was able to
walk through
the forests
in the mountains
and view
undisturbed
water courses
and he discovered
certain phenomenon
now
some of the
phenomenon
that he discovered
regarding water
he was able
to apply
and transfer over
into
the physical
realm
in terms of
technology
and
copy
water movement
and
the geometric
forms that
formed when
water moved
and make
machines
that mimic
that
those movements
and found
that those
machines
had a
let's just
get technical
for a moment
an incredible
hysteresis cycle
that allowed
them to
once they were
cranked up
and ran
and began
to run
they seemed
to have run
almost autonomously
right
and they would
actually
keep accelerating
on their own
without any
extra input
it was based
on something
called a
biological
vacuum
that he
described
now
that is not
why
essentially
we should
discuss
Victor Shawberger
but that was
pretty much
his whole
all of his
endeavors in a nutshell
it was his observation
and then his
accomplishment
his technical
accomplishments
but before we get to
his technical
accomplishments
some of the things
that he laid down
that were quite
important
about water
is that
the quality
not just the
quantity of
water
but the quality
of water
must be addressed
and what I mean
by that
and what he meant
is that right now
mankind
even today
and even back then
was always addressing
the quantity of water
in other words
if you're a farmer
you needed x amount
of millions of liters
to water your crops
and it was the quantity
if you were going
on a camping trip
or
you know
you needed x amount
of water
to go camping
or if you were to
build a house
you need a water heater
with this many gallons
of water
but no one
really discussed
the quality
they always discussed
water in quantity
well right
even when they talk about
you know
droughts and rainy seasons
and
excessive saturation
of certain
land masses
and things like that
it's always about
the volume
and the effects
of the volume
of the water
quite honestly
yeah the quality
of the water
is
never discussed
it's only discussed
in that
you know
purification
is something
that's necessary
that's about
the extent
of the discussion
of quality
is
purification
now
that's kind of
an odd
sort of
way to approach it
being that it is
one of these
you know
very essential
things in life
one would consider
that not only
is the quantity
important
because you do
need a certain
amount
I imagine
in order to
create certain
effects
in order to
you know
produce a certain
living
organisms
you know
to be able to live
efficiently
etc
but you would think
that the quality
of the water
would also be important
yes
and the purification
part of the water
again
they only address
the absence
of certain chemicals
or the presence
of other chemicals
as being quality
right
which I don't see that
as being qualitative
again it's
quantitative again
because they'll tell you
well if you have
this much
uranium or arsenic
in the water
you know
then it's bad
and you should have
none of that
and you should have this
again it's quantity
quantity quantity
and directly
it's quantity
as in the contaminant
versus the water
it's how much
contaminant
right
and the percentage
of contaminant
and how much
you can remove
is acceptable
and things like that
so it is again
a quantitative
look at water
as opposed to
a qualitative
look at water
yeah
absolutely
now I'm
going through
the computer file
because I want to
bring up some
ideas
and I've got to
or something
people can look up
and maybe through
this conversation
I will
and one
one of the ideas
I want to bring up
and this is a fact
and I'm just going to
throw this in
before we get into
the quality
that when water
reaches a certain
quality
it becomes
levitative
ok
yes
not necessarily
like
you know
you would levitate
from the seat
you're sitting in
but
what I mean by that
is
there's
I think it's
the Czech Republic
there's a certain
region in the
Czech Republic
where they have
their own
secret
top secret
facility
their own
area 51
if you will
ok
now it has
nothing to do
with aliens
or flying saucers
or anything like that
you'll find it's a
fenced off area
heavily guarded
and it's a
linear area
and what you will
discover is
they have
fenced off
a river
and no one
can approach it
now why would
they have to
fence off this
river
because over
it's water
course
of several
kilometers
it actually
flows
uphill
yes you heard
me right
uphill
and
slightly
over several
kilometers
I would say
it's over a
dozen or
two dozen
meters
uphill
over that
distance
a very
slight slope
it would
look pretty
flat
by the eye
but if you
were to
come out
there with
a surveyor
you know
a theodolite
or a
laser
and do
a topographical
map
you will
see that the
elevation rises
in the
direction as
the river
in the direction
that the river
is flowing
which is
completely
contradictory to
what you know
one of the
most basic
phrases I've
always heard
which is
water flows
downhill
that's right
that's why
it's fenced
off and it's
their area
and I was
going to give
the exact
location I'm
looking at it's
on another
computer and
maybe we'll just
put we'll
write it in
I'll supply that
later underneath
the audio file
I don't seem to
be pulling it up
here and it's
I don't think
it's on the
internet I
just tried a
few searches
for it
so how can
water do
that how can
water be so
enlivened and
so levitative
that it would
do that
right that's
an interesting
question Victor
Schauberger had
observed these
things now the
main thing that
he observed is
that water was
most active
when it was
cool and in
the shade not
exposed to
sunlight and
even further
active at
certain times of
the month during
a full moon
in the cooler
times of the
year what I
meant the water
being more active
as the streams
and the brooks
and the rivers
ran quick quicker
without eroding
their banks
and the
wildlife was
more lively
and the
water quality
was better
and what he
surmised also
by watching
water is that
water tends to
be self-organizing
into a vortex
that funnel
shape that we
call a tornado
let's say
very common
geometric form
that we are
used to
recognizing
that that
is the
self-organizing
condition that
water takes
when it is
moving from
point A
to point B
as the water
is flowing
it will form
vertical vortices
or horizontal
depending on
the terrain
and also the
quality of the
water
so his main
attribute that
can be shared
with anyone
is initially
to recognize
the quality
of the water
is depending
on its
surrounding
features
if it is
being stored
it would be
in an ovoid
container
in the dark
and kept cool
and if it is
moving
from point A
to point B
the water body
is being
accommodated
what I mean by
the water body
is he pretty
much discussed
something called
the water body
for example
if you walk
to a clothing
store you
recognize the
clothing based
on the human
anatomy
a glove
a hat
a shoe
those items
of clothing
are designed
with certain
geometric shapes
to accommodate
the human body
the anthropomorphic
form
now if you were to
study all fluids
in nature
if you were to
look in a mirror
and look at the
blood vessels
in your eye
or if you were to
uproot a tree
and study the
geometric
patterns of a
tree root
or if you were to
look at a map
of a undisturbed
river
you will notice
that the geometric
forms of those
three things I
mentioned
the blood vessels
the roots of a tree
or a plant
and natural river
courses they all
share almost
identically the same
geometric forms
right
okay
now that is not
what people say
it's a coincidence
but it coincides
with what
that is the
shape that the
water body
has
fluids tend to
assume
that body
shape
when they're
moving
so when they
move from
point A
to point B
they do it in
a meandering
course
very much
as a snake
would move
or an inchworm
or a worm
you notice how
they contract their
bodies and then
they stretch them
out for forward
movement
and there's a
breaking action
in the back
and a sliding
action in the front
to move the body
forward
and if they want
to move in reverse
they put the
breaking action
in the front
and the sliding
action in the
back for a snake
or a worm
or an inchworm
you see
that's how they move
now water moves
that way as well
so now if you
were to
push something
uphill
Chuck
and you want
it
let's say you
start moving
a third of the
way uphill
and you want
to take a
break
you need to
no pun intended
here
have something
that would act
as a break
on what you're
pushing uphill
so you can stop
and continue
forward
right
or let's say
you were rolling
a cart
that can only
move forward
and if you
try to move
back it would
stop
like it had a
gear that would
stop it from
moving back
like being in
drive in a car
versus reverse
so when water
has this
meandering
feature
it creates
a force
behind it
that is a
braking action
that prevents
its reversal
and the front
part of the
water tends to
move it forward
when it's in a
very high state
of quality
now what we
just did there
is explain how
the river can
flow
up an incline
it's almost
like it's a
living
it takes on
the most
primordial
and most
basic
of living
what would
you say
mechanics
of mobility
is exhibited
in natural
water courses
now
and also just
to go back to
the ovoid shape
real quick
a raindrop
is the only
liquid
that takes on
that classic
raindrop shape
which is ovoid
it's pointy on
the trailing end
and on the
leading end
it's more
round
yeah
and well
even though the
water itself is
moving from
point A to
point B
within the
raindrop
it is not
moving
but kept
enlivened
by that
raindrop shape
now why did
I bring up
the raindrop
shape
just to go
back to
the ovoid
is
what's interesting
about that
is that you
could spill
at high
altitude
any other
liquid
whether it's
oil
paint
ink
anything
that's not
water
it will not
take that
take on
that raindrop
shape
only water
takes on
that raindrop
shape
any other
liquid
dropped from
altitude
will fall
to the
ground
as a
mist
very
interesting
okay
so there's
a specific
quality
with
what we're
discussing
here is
the water
body
and this is
what Victor
Shawberger's
work was
based on
and just
like Edison
with the
light bulb
let's say
he did
many other
things
but let's
say when
you say
light bulb
you think
Edison
right
or Tesla
wireless
transmission
of power
Victor
Shawberger's
claim to fame
would be that
water actually
has a body
and this is
what it looks
like
now
one of the
commentaries that
he made for
example is
if you look
at how mankind
is handling
water right now
if you look at
the canals
or the channels
or the plumbing
that he builds
you notice that
all the pipes
and the canals
and channels
and things
that are made
through engineering
are straight
yes
all the plumbing
in your house
well that's like
putting water
in a straight jacket
right
and you end up
the water
can no longer
have this meandering
effect and what it
ends up doing
is it ends up
eating away
at the walls
of the pipes
or whatever's
holding it
whether it's
a canal
that'll have
erosions
if you have
plumbing
it'll start to
eat away
at the pipe
you see
just like
if you put
someone in a
straight jacket
they might want
to start
gnawing away
at it
and also
if you try
and say
you put
your foot
into a shoe
which is not
properly shaped
for your foot
what'll happen
is eventually
the force
of just your
physical body
being in that
shoe
will begin
to create
pressure
on the garment
that will
the garment
will either
take the
shape of the
shoe
or it'll
burst eventually
and this is
why we have
erosion and
the breakdown
of plumbing
I think
based on what
you've said so far
it should not
run in a
straight line
because it's
not in accord
with the water
body
and it
sounds very
simple
and it
sounds very
contradictory
to basic
engineering
because we just
want to move
things from
point A to
point B
as long as it
doesn't leak
it doesn't matter
this is the
attitude that's
being taken
and another
thing Shawberger
discussed is
when water is
moving in this
straitjacket form
it starts to
create negative
or let's
say negative
fields
negative being
not in charge
but that are
not conducive
to a
healthful condition
in the environment
and he had
done an
interesting chart
back in the
40's that
he was
he noticed
that some of
the government
officials were
quite upset
that 3%
or 2%
of the population
was coming
down with
cancers
it was just
over 1%
it was between
1 and 3%
and he said
the more
of this type
of strait
canal
strait plumbing
that you're
doing the more
your cancer rates
will go up
and he actually
did a chart
where he showed
by the 1950's
it'll be 5%
by the 60's
it'll be so much
and by the 80's
and 90's
it'll be 30%
and by the year
or 20
or so
he said it'll
be about 50%
of the population
will be coming
down with cancer
and by 2050
90% of the
population
will have cancer
because the way
water is being
handled
and if you actually
look at a lot of
the
academic
works
on how many
people are getting
cancer today
in the early
2000's
and look at their
records
what they have
in their records
you know the
quackademics
it's almost
identical to what
he predicted
in the 1940's
well yeah
I've observed this
several times
and wondered
why actually
there has been
such an exponential
increase
in what they
call cancer
you know
and it is
it's apparent
I mean
there's no way
to argue
that it has been
increasing exponentially
this would be
a really
almost laughable
simple answer
as to why
it is increasing
so rapidly
if we can
if we were to
find one
constituent
that needed
in society
in the physical
world that needed
to be addressed
immediately
would be how
water is handled
first
forget about
the fluoride
the chlorine
and all that
other stuff
that they're telling you
are the bad stuff
in the water
you must change
the way
the water is being
handled
I was once
doing some
correspondence
with a pretty
high muckity
muck person
in Australia
minister level
type person
and he said
what can we do
in Australia
to improve
the water
quality here
and I said
you'd have to
pull out every
piece of plumbing
and redo every
canal so it
meanders
like it does
in nature
and he says
that's never
going to happen
and I said
well you just
answered your
own question
you're never
going to improve
your water
quality then
there you go
and that's why
very often
when I speak
I don't
like discussing
things that are
hopeful
because if I do
discuss things
that are hopeful
they sound so
foreign and so
bizarre
so the chances
of
all the plumbing
in the world
being replaced
with pipes that
look like blood
vessels let's say
or roots of a tree
is pretty much
null to zero
there's no hope
in expecting
the water quality
to get better
so let's move on
to the next subject
but within the
same subject
what can
one do
within their own
environment
to understand
how to mitigate
this
and just to
touch back on the
cancer idea
when these
fields are being
emitted by water
moving as it
does and
conveying the
quality because
it's not been
handled properly
first
you know
that affects the
field in the body
now there's
something called
cancer and what's
not being discussed
in mass
but has been
known by some
and discussed by
some
is what are called
cancerous tumors
and cancer conditions
are things that
appear
in
can appear
in a body
in minutes
or hours
you know
it's not something
typically that
yes
takes years
of let's say
poor health management
to lead to
or bad food
yes
it's that as well
but the actual
physical condition
of a tumor
and things
those things can
appear overnight
or in minutes
where they were
you know
we're talking about
you know someone
getting a scan
of their brain
and then five
minutes later
getting another scan
and there's a walnut
sized tumor there
it's like how
where did that thing
come from
you see
this is the idea
of field science
the concept of
things appearing
very quickly
and disappearing
that's why
there was someone
called Likovsky
back in the
early 20th century
had this thing
called Likovsky coils
he built these two
antennas that you
sat between
and he basically
pumped very high
pulse type
voltage
through these
antenna rings
and people that
had very terminal
diseases
either got better
or rid of them
within hours
or days
they just
disappeared
now what do you
think is
what are you
impressing on
the individual
if you're sitting
imagine sitting
in a chair
and there's an
antenna
something like
a circular
antenna
four feet to
your right
and another
antenna four feet
to your left
and nothing is
touching you
and this type of
therapy is applied
for let's say
a few minutes
a couple of times
a week
and your condition
just reverses
that is a field
effect
it is a field
therapy
there is nothing
no one is poking
or prodding you
or administering
there's nothing
to rub on
your body
or drink
or take
you see
so we're
looking at
Giebelikowski
as an
idea here
because
if
he had so much
success with
field effect
therapy as such
could you imagine
the
negative consequences
of the fields
that are coming
out off of water
running through
straight pipes alone
it's massive
and
if one were
to really
contemplate it
and
be able to
discern it
it would be
almost like
the industrial
world is a
nightmare
reality
and
meanwhile
like I said
earlier
when
you started
to say
what can one do
about these
things
obviously
you provided
the concept
of what
might be
imagined
as far as
affecting fields
and what
could be
changed
about water
and if it
was changed
the way
it was
handled
through the
plumbing
etc
well that
would be
great but
it seems
rather
impractical
and one of
those things
that can't
be realized
at this
point
no
but you know
I did
bring up
earlier
this concept
of adding
oxygen
to the
water
and
people have
talked about
the different
properties
and qualities
of water
because there's
minerals in it
and all these
other things
but those are
really additives
the gas
and the
minerals
yes
well
let's just get
into the proper
handling
enrichment
and health
let's say
those other
items we
wanted to
discuss
you ever
notice
when you
put a
glass of
water
on the
table
you come
back half
an hour
or so
later and
there are
bubbles stuck
to the
glass
sure
that's
because
of
dissolved
gases
in the
water
so when
you're
holding up
a glass
for a
container
of water
there are
dissolved
gases
in there
and when
the water
stops moving
a lot of the
gases kind of
settle out
there's
not a
photosynthesis
but a
photo
there's a
technical term
for it
when light
affects water
or any
objects it
changes it
slightly
right
we're not
talking about
plants now
we're talking
about just
water and
liquids and
things like that
like some people can
get a dental
treatment where
they use
light to
set the
epoxy and
things like that
light has an
effect on
water that
will either
change its
quality bring
out dissolved
gases and
such now
when we're
looking at
the water
body in
its purest
form for
for human
consumption
we all
say spring
water right
like the best
water to
drink is
spring water
from the
mountain spring
well water
okay top
water whatever
you know
bottled water
you know however
but the
source is
always touted
as being the
highest quality
from the
spring now
what's interesting
about the
spring water
quality now
listen it's
not the
location but
it is the
location in
other words the
spring water
itself has a
quality that
can be
synthesized in
other words it
can be recreated
but right now
because of the
way commerce
industry
understanding
education about
water people
are still
pursuing the
spring water
because it was
known throughout
humanity that
was the highest
quality water to
drink now the
many springs that
existed and
still do the
highest quality for
drinking water
would be
typically two
thirds up a
mountain not
at low elevation
lower elevation
springs tend to
be warmer and
carbonated now
what is drawing
the water out
of the
high altitude
and makes it
such a high
quality when the
water passes
through the
earth and by
the way if
you ever see
some spring
water companies
that say well
this is like
5,000 year
old or 10,000
year old artesian
water that's all
crap water
tends to move
healthy water
or water in
good condition
tends to move
at about 10
feet per second
or 3 meters per
second underground
if water is
moving faster
it's doing
something else
and probably
causing earthquakes
somewhere and
if it's moving
slower it's
becoming heavily
acidified and
it starts to
warm up so
there is no
such thing as
a 5,000 or
7,000 year old
water or
anything like
that because
there is a
tremendous
lattice and
plumbing underneath
the earth the
water is constantly
moving at a
pretty good rate
and what I mean
by 10 feet per
second if you're
standing by it
you threw your
baseball cap in
the water count
one second the
baseball cap is
10 feet away
from you it's
pretty quick so
this is the
condition of what
we consider good
spring water
underground and
by that point
it is degassed
what I mean by
degassed it is
absent of gases
so this is maybe
indirectly addressing
what if we pump
oxygen in the
water what are we
doing are we
increasing the
quality of the
water or decreasing
the quality of the
water you're
decreasing the
quality of the
water right now
on one side they're
telling you oxygen
is good and
that's why you need
more of it but in
the future mankind
will discover that
you are there's
oxygen yes it's
necessary in the
air as a catalyst
but you're really
breathing nitrogen
and the lungs
convert nitrogen
into oxygen in
situ which is
kind of strange to
discuss maybe we
can get into that
some other time
about the health
but you're really
the only oxygen
that you need in
the air is a catalyst
to stimulate the
pulsing gas known
as nitrogen and
the oxygen is
created in the
lung so
similarly to
water
water sheds
itself of all
dissolved gases
and once it gets
to that point
it becomes more
resistant and
also when it's
at four degrees
Celsius or
39 degrees Fahrenheit
which is its
optimum temperature
and we can get
into that as well
it becomes resistant
to a magnetic field
and it becomes
what's called
diamagnetic
diamagnetism might
be something that
people see in
super conductive
experiments where
they freeze a piece
of where they put
an iron or a
magnet over helium
and it tends to
float over the
liquid helium
okay that is
diamagnetism where
it kind of does
not want
magnetism
it doesn't want
magnetic lines to
pass through it
and now we have
this diamagnetic
water that is
flowing underground
that has no
gases dissolved in
it and as it
sees the mountain
crevice
the gases are
actually in the
atmosphere actually
sucking the water
up out of the
mountain very much
like one would use
a straw to suck
liquid out of a
container like a
soft drink or
something and
this is the
apparatus of how
springs work
now what they'll
tell you is
in academia is
that springs are
geothermal but
how can they be
geothermal when they
come out almost
ice cold at
four degrees Celsius
zero degrees Celsius
would be freezing
or 39 degrees
Fahrenheit is
four degrees Celsius
which is only
seven degrees away
from freezing again
right where it
begins to freeze
so water
to judge it if
it's in good
quality would be
absent of light
and at 39 degrees
Fahrenheit
now fortunately
most refrigerators
in the western
world if you were
to hang up a
thermometer in
most refrigerators
guess what they
read
39 degrees
and when you
shut the door
it's dark
right now
this is the
idea of
spring water
now personally
myself and a
few other people
we were studying
Schauberger
about
while we've
been studying
them for over
12 years but
we studied
oh I brought it
to the table that
they wanted to
start a small
business and I
said why don't we
get into synthesizing
spring water we can
take any water and
turn it into the
highest quality water
on the planet
bar none
and we did that
successfully
and we built the
apparatuses to
actually mimic the
way the earth
creates spring water
you know degassing
the water
in an ovoid shape
and creating a
biological vacuum
go figure
okay
so we
succeeded at
this point
so from this
point on speaking
from experience
how can we
practically impart
information that the
listener can use
with just
regular household
daily
things that they
come in contact
with without
having to build
special apparatus
as we did
that we actually
mimicked Victor
Schauberger's
equipment which
some of the
equipment took 15
years to build
back in the
1930s that he
did
we were able
to achieve that
in a matter of
a few months
and we actually
achieved the
water quality
that he was
speaking of
now how can we
take the
principle that
is not
almost seemingly
not discussed
by anyone
you know
they want to do
all these funky
things to water
you know they want
to structure it
or they tell you
about pie water
or I don't know
if that's a brand
name I shouldn't
have said it
or just this
ridiculous bunk
about water
you know
elixirs
things to put in
your water
all kinds of
strange filters
additives
filters
various
treatments
of all sorts
which either
add or allegedly
extract things
from the water
again though
this is a matter
of quantity
as opposed to
quality
as we discussed
earlier so
there you go
now I also
wanted to ask
could we take a
five minute
break and come
back to pause
the audio
or would that
be alright
well yeah I
could probably
just cut it out
you know
I don't want to
interrupt the
recorder but I
could just cut it
out
yep so we'll be
back in five
minutes
sure
okay
can you hear me
yes
alright
so where were
we
water quality
and let's tie
all of these
things together
quantity
quality
Victor Schauberger's
ideas
and maybe even
not discussing
Victor Schauberger
so much because
I think if you
say his name
twice backwards
you get a hernia
right
so the
idea here
is to
not necessarily
sum it up
because this
could be a
very long
discussion
but let's
just at this
point maybe
someone who
could be
listening on
what they
can do
within their
proximity at
very little
or no cost
depending on
your resources
right now
how can they
improve the
water quality
that they have
and this is
mainly for
consumption
and what we
talk about
tuberculosis
which was the
old name for
consumption
but the
actual taking
in of water
by the way
when they
call you a
consumer
what do you
call someone
who has
consumption
they're a
consumer
so at this
point
regarding
how does one
tie this
concept
okay we're
talking about
water
what can
anyone do
practically
now one has
to consider
there's a lot
of talk
and it's
more than
talk about
what the
municipalities
are doing
with water
adding chlorine
and fluoride
and there's
a new nasty
thing they're
doing now
where they're
adding also
ammonia
which creates
with the
chlorine
which creates
a chloramine
compound
which is
pretty nasty
as well
and also to
address various
well waters
or rain
collection
waters
I've been
discussing
with some
people
they say
they collect
rain water
only because
they have
no choice
or
off the grid
let's say
or any
water
what can
one do
well the first
thing is
to consider
that
water's
anomaly point
is 40 degrees
Celsius or
39 degrees
Fahrenheit
and what I
mean by that
is the
human anomaly
point is
98.6
okay
well what do
I mean by
that
well let's
say I
say
Chuck
you know
my body
temperature is
102 degrees
how do you
think I
feel
well probably
a bit too
warm
or 104
or 106
as an adult
you'd probably
say you're
you're not
doing well
you're probably
hurting yourself
at this point
yeah at this
point you're
going to start
to feel
as if you're
freezing by
contrast with
your environment
because
you're definitely
running a
fever let's
just say
yeah well you
know what's
interesting about
that is
just a little
short thing
in colder
climates
fevers are hot
in warmer
climates fevers
are cold
to the touch
so this is
another thing
about the way
biology works
but okay so
so if I said
Chuck
my body
temperature is
about
internally
is about
you know
we've got
hyperthermia or
you know the
opposite of
hyperthermia you
know I'm not
doing well
again so I
want to be
around the
98 98.6
right to be
in a healthful
condition where
I feel good
and I can do
things because
if my temperature
internal temperature
is 90 or
105 I'm not
going to get up
I'm going to
probably be
horizontal right
or you may be
a cooling
corp
yeah
now
water's anomaly
point
is
39 degrees
or 4 degrees
Celsius
okay so
if water is
at let's say
50 or
degrees
Fahrenheit
or 10 or
15 let's say
10 degrees
Celsius
it starts
it's no longer
at that point
where it's the
most healthful
or it will do
work or comply
to doing
anything right
that's why for
example when you
look at a
lot of basic
carbon filtration
carbon filters are
the most common
whether they're
pitcher or inline
filters or whatever
and they tell you
they have a do
not use above
80 degrees
right because
the water
the efficiency
of the filter
drops to
nothing
now if you're
have the most
basic available
carbon filter
whether it's in
line they have
these canisters
or they have
these things called
pitcher filters
now right
little cartridge
sock in the
middle
right
you want to
start off with
water that's as
cool as possible
now when I say
as cool as
possible not with
frost in it
because what's
interesting again
is we want to
stay near 4
degrees Celsius
39 Fahrenheit
now here's
the interesting
thing about that
and it's
efficiency
at 39 degrees
Fahrenheit or
4 degrees Celsius
water is its
densest condition
if the temperature
is higher than
that water begins
to expand
and take in
gases
now if the
temperature drops
from 4 degrees
Celsius or
39 degrees
Fahrenheit
it starts to
expand again
and if you
don't believe me
take a jar of
water
put a lid on it
stick it in the
freezer
wait and
what happens
right
okay
so yeah
so at 39
degrees water
is its
densest point
and one of the
things I like about
a very old
encyclopedia
Britannica that
I have is
back in the day
when encyclopedias
were written
there were
encyclopedia
writing companies
there were people
that did that
for the academics
and they didn't
like the academics
because they didn't
get to have
fancy parties
in the towers
or you know
these were just
the encyclopedia
writers like
they didn't
have anybody
wanting to
hang out with them
you know
so they always
wanted to
put in little
digs
towards the
academics
and you could
see it in their
writing
the old
encyclopedias
and when you
look up
pre-1913
encyclopedia
definition of
water
these
encyclopedia
writers like
to make fun
of the
scientists
and they
said well
they said
you know
one gram
is a cubic
centimeter of
water
you know
in the metric
system
but that's not
really correct
because they
measured it
at room
temperature
so really
it's a
centimeter of
water
at room
temperature
is really
0.999
grams
and we'll
leave it
at that
you know
so the
guys
you know
so in other
words the
guys that
wrote the
encyclopedias
were making
fun at the
scientists
overlooking
the fundamental
quality of
water
so
that's
interesting
yeah
so
if we
had more
time I'd
pull it
out and
read it
but
anyone could
look it up
in an old
encyclopedia
so the
idea here
is
let's say
you're
passing water
through what's
called a
filter
and in
the industry
they call that
scrubbing
believe it or
not
you know
when you
scrub
something
it's like
not someone
on their
hands and
knees
let's say
on the floor
or something
but it means
cleaning
in general
terms
now
when you have
water that's
above 39
degrees or
4 degrees
celsius or
below that
it's in an
expansive mode
and it likes
to take in
gas
and when you're
passing it
through a
filter medium
that is
scrubbing
the water
cleaning the
water
you have all
these other
things in there
like gases
that prevent
the full
contact with
what you're
trying to
clean it
with
you see
right
it's like
little
micro
bubbles
in the
water
so if
you're going
to increase
the efficiency
of any
filtration
system
you have
to have
the water
as close
to 39
degrees as
possible
now that
will not
be achieved
in 99%
of cases
unless you
have an
inline
water chiller
or you
live in
an area
where the
climate
or the
weather
permits
I say
more
climate
than
weather
permits
that water
to be so
I've seen
some artesian
wells
or some springs
that have been
tapped into
where the water
comes out at 39
degrees or
anywhere between
39 and 41
degrees Fahrenheit
or 4 to 5
degrees Celsius
all year round
those are the
most fortunate
people
so if anyone
starts to get
interested and
wants to do
more experimentation
just get a
waterproof
thermometer of
some kind
and go to
your tap
and whatever
and start
becoming more
conscious of
water temperature
right
just like for
example when
when someone
goes to be
examined by a
doctor
what are one
of the first
things the
doctor does
to examine
the quality
of your
health
takes your
temperature
it's one
of the
primary
things he
does right
so the
temperature of
the water
must be
considered
the other
thing is
absence of
light
if you ever
notice that
water being
stored in
containers
where light
affects that
you get things
like algae
and other
things growing
in it
right
so you have
to keep it
absent of
light
these are the
first two
things to
consider
your
water
temperature
and absence
of light
now without
really focusing
on the
municipal aspect
where they're
actually pumping
in chlorine
ammonia
fluoride
and all these
other things
we need to
discuss
if we're going
to discuss
what anyone
can do to
increase the
quality of
the water
let's consider
all the
waters
whether it's
that I would
suggest
is get
your
masks
or the
amount of
volume of
water
that you
would like
to process
into a
higher form
of water
into a
refrigerator
okay
and when
I say
that, fortunately I can say that in common terms, most refrigerators across
the world are either at four degrees or 39, four degrees Celsius or 39
Fahrenheit. Right. So get your water either for a few hours into a
refrigerator in the container that you're going to use. This is in an
unfiltered state now, okay, for a minimum of two to four hours. Overnight is best,
okay. Once you remove that water, and this is now discussing people
that are going to topically process the water, not an inline filter that you
might see in a restaurant or many houses or things like that, because there you're
going to need a pre-chiller to do that, okay. But if you were to process water
topically, meaning in your kitchen counter area or somewhere like that, you
would get the given amount of water again in a refrigerator overnight would be
best. What you do then, the simplest thing to do is obtain what's called these
pitcher filters. I've seen them at these big Wally World, you know, big department
type stores for as little as ten bucks these days, okay. Okay. And what you do
there is you would pour that water through one of these pitcher filters at
the 39 degrees Celsius. And the reason why you do it at that point is that
water is at its anomaly point. It's willing to do work. The filter
will be, efficiency will work up in the 99% efficiency, right, versus the 8% or 60% or 40% if it's regular warm water or water that's been exposed to light. So now you're going to get the most out of whatever you are doing to process the water. Now, a lot of these pitcher filters are made of plastics. What I suggest then is if you have some old beer bottles or wine bottles or that type of bottle, glass bottle that is
amber or dark blue or dark green, regardless.
After it passes through the pitcher filter, funnel it in or decant it immediately
into these glass bottles that are dark, that obscure light.
Either amber color, green, blue, purple, anything that is
not clear. And then immediately place that
water again into the refrigerator overnight and let it sit.
And now you will have a higher quality water than you've ever had. It would
actually rival most bottled waters at that point, simply by processing the
water at 39 degrees and then letting it rest after that. Now the enlivenment of
water is also very important, which is called like a hydrodynamic action,
which is, you know, the meandering through the river or the blood vessels or the
roots of a tree, that geometric form, or a vortex or a tornado. Fortunately,
when you do a pitcher filter, the very act of the water running through that and
dripping out of into the pitcher allows the water to self-organize in droplets
and things and will charge the water from the environment. And that's why,
again, I am suggesting that this type of water processing, where the water is
processed near 39 degrees Fahrenheit or 4 degrees Celsius and then allowed to
rest overnight or for a few hours before taking, you will notice the quality of
water is very high. Now sometimes if you're very athletic or so, they say
don't drink very cold water, it could cause cramps in hot weather. That is true,
it could, but I would still drink it cool. I wouldn't let it go more than, let's
say, 50 degrees or 45 if you're looking for a high-quality drink of water, you
know, Fahrenheit or 5 to 8 degrees Celsius. Now for someone who wants to go
a little bit further, now what I mean by further is a basic pitcher filter like
that. Typically, most of them are made up of carbon,
coconut shell carbon, and excuse me, I think I need to drink water. Well, go ahead and take one because, you know, this is
interesting to me, the fact that the pitcher shape itself would sort of
imply that, yeah, it gives it that opportunity to go into the vortex sort
of shape, and you know what I keep thinking of is water going down a
drain, it's allowed to collect and go into that drain, but it doesn't get to
stay in that shape, and yet creates sort of a natural vortex. You see it
spinning. Of course, I've heard discussions about it spinning, you know,
in different directions, in different parts of the planet, and things like that,
but yes, at this point for the quality wouldn't, yeah, even just the fact that a
drop of water would fall into another body of water, that toroidal action, which is
that it moves the water aside, it folds onto itself, is again a vortex, because a
toroid, a toroid would be a smoke ring, for example. There you go. That is another form of a
vortex also. Let's not get just stuck on the standard tornado vortex, which is that
axial, radial to axial, you know, it's a wide funnel at the top and it comes down
into an axial, you know, vertical skinny portion at the bottom. That's the radial
to axial form of vorticity or hydrodynamic action. Another hydrodynamic
action is the toroid, which would be someone blowing a smoke ring. Looks like a
donut, or a truck tire, truck inner tube, let's say, and that is also very effective,
another hydrodynamic action, and the very fact that water dripping out of it would
form some kind of action as such is beneficial. Now, if someone wants to
take this a little bit further, and has, and the reason I brought up the pitcher
filter is most people have ready access to that. Right. Now, if you want to, if you
have a little bit more resources and want to go a little bit further, there, on
the quantity side of water, there is a lot of discussion of heavy metal in the
water. There's a lot of discussion of arsenics and things like that in the
water. Fluorides, mercury, things like that, that could, that need to be addressed.
Your carbon filter that you will find that is the most common, when you say
water filtration, if you were to buy it at a standard department store, hardware
store, they're only going to supply you with carbon and particulate filtration,
and that is only good for most of what's called organic materials. Okay, certain,
you know, what we find in petroleum products, let's say, and chlorine and
things like that. Now, if you want to go a little bit further with heavy metals
and ammonia compounds, let's say, and other things as such, and you want to
invest a little bit more, what you do then is there's this thing called zeolite.
Zeolites are basically an alumina calcium sort of compound that is basically
ancient riverbeds or ancient lake beds that have been dug up, and it's a very
soft porous white material. It's called a zeolite, Z-E-O-L-I-T-E, and it's a very
inexpensive thing to get. Why do I say that, and why am I even bringing up, if
this is going to be something practical, why do I bring up zeolites? Well, if
anyone who walks into what they call a pet shop or a pet supply place, which is
very common, aquariums are very common for people to have, you'll find a product
on the shelf, and it's usually zeolite. They're white minerals. They call them
ammonia pellets sometimes, because they take ammonia out of ammonia compounds and
nitrate compounds, because ammonia is basically a nitrate, right, or trite, out
of aquariums, and this can be gotten very inexpensively. Your supply
used in this fashion would be less than ten bucks. As a matter of fact, more.
Maybe a five-year supply would be less than ten bucks, right, so we're
talking about not much of an investment here, and you buy some of these zeolite
material, and do what they say on the package for cleaning it. You really want
to clean it very thoroughly, because even after five rinses, you still see it
releases a cloudy water, right, so just take your time, and how to clean zeolites
is usually on the package, because you have to take care of it if you have an
aquarium. You wouldn't want to cloud up all the fish water, so usually the
instructions, they're sold as ammo chips or ammo pellets, meaning ammonia
pellets, or just zeolites. Any pet store or pet supply will have it on the shelf,
or discount department store has it. I've even seen it on regular supermarket
shelves, where you might go to buy some fish food, okay, so what you
would do is purchase some of these zeolites, and zeolites are very
effective in removing any ammonia compounds, which would be these
chloramine compounds that are put in municipal water now. Very effective at
removing heavy metal, any heavy metal. As a matter of fact, all of the NEST teams,
NEST stands for Nuclear Emergency Safety Team, or NEST teams in the U.S.
These are nuclear safety cleanup people. When they show up to a site, and they
usually close it off, and tell you, you ask them, why is the road here closed,
and they say, well because there's a meth lab here, we have to close the road, and
you're like, well there's no houses there, you know, what are you talking about, you
know, it's always secret. When these guys show up to do a nuclear cleanup, guess
what, they show up and guess what follows them, a big truck of what, dump truck full
of what, zeolite, to absorb all the material. That's interesting. So, you know,
not to get too far off, you know, because we were talking about, you know, the
filtration, and yeah, that's one of those things that would be, you know, accessible.
But it almost sounds strange, really, to think that you might be able to get ahold
of something like that in order to improve water quality. You know, but this
would contribute to the better health of someone who, pardon the phrase again, is
the consumer, wouldn't it? Right, right. Now, the reason I bring it up is because,
simply because, let's say through industry, the very fact that industry
sends stuff up a smokestack and cars have exhaust pipes, there's really nasty
stuff in colloid form in the environment that settles in water courses that are
eventually processed and given to the people to drink. So, a lot of these things
will not be handled by your typical carbon filter with little ionized, they
usually have small ionic resin beads in them as well, that doesn't really handle
this stuff. So, the heavy metal and ammonia constituents, when I say heavy
metals, I mean the entire spectrum, will be handled by the zeolites. And the
zeolites, you know, even on a cursory search, look up, you know, we're not
talking, you know, look up zeolites. Now, we're not talking about a lot of people
promoting it for internal health reasons. I'm not promoting it for such. I'm
strictly promoting it for a quantitative reduction of nasties in the
water. Right. Yeah. And we remove some of these heavy metal constituents and other
things, radionucleotides and things like that, you will notice that the
water is more refreshing, more vitalizing, and eventually, as you've heard, you know,
these heavy metals, without getting into what, you know, the entire broad spectrum
of them, can be damaging to the organism, you know, the body, you know, and animals
as well, humans and animals, and fish. And they tend to not hurt you
immediately, they tend to be damaging through the cumulative, you know, they
tend to stay within the body, right? And, okay. So, this is one way the zeolite
would be a thing that I would add to the pitcher filter. Now, how would you add it
to the pitcher filter? Simply by putting a few tablespoons in the pitcher filter
itself, because remember, it has a small filter module in it, it will not allow
the zeolite to pass through. So, the stock filter module that comes in the
pitcher will actually contain the zeolite, or you can put it in a painter's
strainer bag or cheesecloth, if you wish, because it comes in pea-sized
granules, typically. Okay? Now, if you, for those that, so now we're talking about an
investment of roughly 10 bucks for a pitcher filter at a discount department
store, and even not at a discount department store, they're roughly between
10 or 20 bucks. And we're talking about an investment of anywhere between 3 or
10 bucks for a zeolite, which the amount of zeolite that would get
you would be about the size of a half-gallon container of milk, and that
would last you a pretty long time. I have some that I've been using a container
that size for five years now, and it's still about half full, just to give you
an idea. So, five people can go in on a $10 investment, and that'll be enough for
five years. Two bucks or three bucks worth of zeolite. Okay, so this gets rid
of your heavy metals. Now, in some places there's something, there's an arsenic
consideration. Arsenic cyanide and things like that traces in the water. At Southwest,
a lot of municipalities were heavily fined by the federal regulatory
authorities because of the high arsenic content in the water, and the only way
that they know how to remove arsenic from the water is by very expensive,
what's called ionic, cationic resin beads. And these beads cost about 500 bucks a
pound, and they're very difficult to get. And they also remove the arsenic, but
they also introduce other polymers into the water which have to be removed. So,
let's just say, how do we remove arsenic from the water? Well, you do it through
something called adsorption. You've heard of absorption with a B, where, you
know, a towel absorbs water. Well, there's another concept called adsorption with a
D. So, it would be AD instead of AB as an absorption. What adsorption does is, when
you have one material that has so much affinity for something, that as the
liquid passes or the water passes over this material, that material, what you're
trying to remove out of the water, sticks to the surface of this other material.
That's called an adsorber. That adsorber would be something called
magnetite. M-A-G-N-E-T-I-T-E. Now, what that is, is basically, another term for it is
black sand. What is black sand? You ever go to the beach and notice that the sand
is white, but when you look at it really closely, the little black specks in there?
Okay, that is usually iron crystal. Magnetite is Fe3O4, is what they call the
chemical combination, which is three parts iron, four parts oxygen. Fe2O3
would be hematite. You've heard of, like, hematite. They use it in jewelry. It's
like a grayish material. Actually, I wore a vial of magnetite and actually had a
crystal shape hematite before around, you know, I used to wear both of them as
jewelry at one point in time. Okay, great. So, people can look these things up.
How do you get magnetite? Well, if you're near a water course, a beach, a river,
or whatever, you could just drag magnets. Take a 15-minute walk with a magnetic
strip behind you and you'll notice all these little black sand particles, you
know, pick off all the staples and rusty nails and things, right? You'll
notice that this is the type of iron that does not rust, does not combine with
oxygen. It's in crystal form, and as a matter of fact, if you were to look at
it under a microscope, it would look like a double-sided pyramid. It would have
eight sides, four sides on each side, and the angle of that pyramid is 51.4
degrees, which is basically 360 divided by 7, and also, what do you think the
angle of the Great Pyramid of Giza is? 51.4 degrees. Right, and interestingly enough,
when they made this type of jewelry that I'm talking about, they would
terminate on either side of the crystals. Try to approximate that symmetry as
well. When they terminated the crystal or the container that the smaller
pieces were in, both of them were designed with that same principle in mind. Yes, yes,
very interesting. That's part of the common denominator of geometric, you know,
fundamentals that underline anything, whether it's man-made or in nature.
Certain things tend to follow certain geometric forms. So, what you do with the
magnetite is very simple, very much like the zeolite. At the top of the pitcher
filter, you would just put a tablespoon or two of magnetite there, and the water
would pass over and be an adsorber to the arsenic or arsenide compounds. Now, the
way you would treat that is maybe every three or four or six months or once a
year. It's easy to separate the zeolite from the magnetite. You would just soak
the magnetite in hydrogen peroxide and the zeolite. And when I was doing this in
Los Angeles, by the way, we cleaned out some canisters. We were cleaning out, we
were processing LA tap water. We stripped the materials and we got this really
bright, you ever see the energy drink? I think it's called Gatorade. They have one
called Lemon Lime. It's like a yellowish, greenish kind of color to it. When you
strip the magnetite and zeolite of arsenic used in hydrogen peroxide, the
water turns that color. That is the sign that you have arsenic in the water, by
the way. That's why I could never drink that flavor. I think it's
called Lemon Lime. There's several companies that put out sports drinks that
have the same color and virtually the same flavor. It's like a common thing now.
Much like raspberries, often colored blue anymore. Yeah. Okay, yeah. Well, if you ever
see that Lemon Lime color in the convenience store, that's the color of
arsenic when it comes off from an adsorber. And yeah, so right there, the
combination of a basic pitcher filter, where the water is processed through it
at 39 degrees or as close as possible, with zeolite magnetite, we're going to
show you a good way that is better than anything you could buy for a
buck bottle. It doesn't matter from what artesian well you're getting it from.
This is a very simple way to process a very high quality water. And essentially,
a lot of people don't drink water these days as much as they should,
let's say. They tend to get their water from other drinks and their food. This
information hopefully will be more helpful to people that are considering
drinking more water, or will be. You know, eventually maybe we can start
discussing this more, maybe create some water connoisseurs, which I think are
lacking in the world. But if anyone wants to understand more about the concept of
hydration, there's someone out there called Dr. Batmangala. They used to call him
Dr. Batman, the water doctor. And he wrote a book, You're Not Sick, You're
Thirsty, Batmangala. And he was an Iranian-Persian doctor. He was also
imprisoned in Persia for his writings and other things. He was healing people
with water. And when his sentence was over and they told him to leave the
prison, he said, no, I want to stay a few more months and check on some of my
patients here, right? He was that kind of guy. And he died recently. But if anyone
wants to look up You're Not Sick, You're Thirsty, Dr. Batman, Batmangala. I don't
have his spelling in front of me, but You're Not Sick, You're Thirsty is one of
his publications, if you're interested in what water consumption can do. Right, I'm
sure that'll be enough praise for them to find it. So, yeah. Yeah. So we can then
discuss, if anyone wants to go to a higher level than that, any other water
treatment. If you believe your water is good enough, let's say, if you're going to
go on a higher level. See, what I mean by that is, if you think your water needs
filtering, you're already dealing with water that you know needs
filtering. It's suspect. It's not a high-quality water, right? But on a higher
level would be, is if you are near in proximity of a good water source. And
that doesn't mean a store-bought water. Now, let's just digress for a second.
How many times have you gone to the shops, any shop, and they're
procuring water, how many times have you seen the water being stored absence of
light, absent of light, and at 39 degrees? Or do you see the water on the shelf in
clear plastic bottles at room temperature? Most of the time, yeah. It
doesn't require refrigeration, so therefore it's put on a shelf, yeah. But I
think we just brought up the point that it does. No, I know. I'm just stating to
you what the... I know. Yeah, exactly. So you see how contrary this concept is? It's
very difficult for anyone to listen to what we're discussing and then go out
into the world. They'll see that the two don't match. They don't agree with
each other at all, you see. No, no, and you know, there's more than one reason
why chilled water that's been refrigerated is pleasant, you know. It
makes more sense to the body. It's not that it tastes any different, really. It's
just that it's in its more correct, effective, efficient form. It'll be more
refreshing initially, and then after a few minutes, it'll be invigorating. So
there's two ways to test the water quality with your
biological sensor, which is your body, would be how refreshing it is initially,
and then how invigorating it is following that, let's say, within a few
minutes, even up to 20 minutes, if you feel invigorated or so. Now, again, for
the people that have a higher calling or a higher source, the primary thing there
would be to avoid contact with metal, metal containers or metal fixtures, and
to keep it in the dark and keep it cool. So if you're, let's say, fetching water at
a spring, an organic material, let's say plastic is considered organic material,
it would have to be a high-density polyethylene or glass or terracotta, but
avoid metal if you can. Now, a lot of canteens for camping and things as such
are metal. A lot of these, there's been a water bottle phase in the past decade or
so where you see people carrying water bottles around like it's a baby
wherever they go. In that case, they're selling stainless steel now for that. I
would avoid any metallic container at this point, simply because
from an ethereal point of view, when I say ether, I mean how the
initial people that discussed electricity considered electricity to be
a form of the ether. There is an interaction between water and the
environment and water and when it makes contact with most metals,
especially ferrous compounds, iron compounds, it discharges the quality of
the water. Now, if you have a silver container or gold-plated, actually
silver-plated would be best, or perhaps a stabilized copper, that would not
affect it as much as a stainless steel or iron. So, you want to avoid metal in
general because even though silver would be favorable, how many people have access
to silver containers? It wouldn't be very affordable. So, look, in the past two hours
here, we've covered a whole lot about water that I dare say has not been
spoken about in public in one place, certainly, all these aspects. Wouldn't you say?
I would say so, yes, absolutely. So, I think, yeah, it's quite a big
journey. As long as we feel like at the end of this two hours or two hours
passing, if you feel like there's anything else that we could say along
these lines that people can walk away with and feel that they can implement in
their lives immediately. Yeah, no, certainly, and you've given people a much
more refined way to look at how they could increase the, well, the efficiency
of the water they consume. We've given them the idea that, you know, consumption,
excuse me for using the term again, of water is one of these things that they
need to be concerned with. The why, the how, and a great deal that is never
discussed anywhere has been discussed here. So, I don't know if you want to
close it out at this point, or I think we've done something
pretty good here, and tell you the truth, I've heard some things here that I have
never heard before and had some other things that presented themselves to me
in the past. For instance, you know, just to harken back to one point, the
concept that an egg has a certain shape and there is a logical, sensible purpose
for that, you know, now makes a whole lot more sense to me and now that we've
discussed it. So, you know. Oh good, yeah, absolutely. That's one of the great
things I take from it is that, you know, an egg makes sense the way it is shaped.
So, sure, yeah, these, the people, those who put it all together, yeah,
they don't act in futility, as I've said before. Exactly. So, I guess we'll
leave this be here, and I hope that you guys have gained something from it, and
obviously if you have access to this, then you have access to replay it, as I
suggest you do, because quite honestly, I'm gonna have to listen to it a few
times myself in order to really sort of internalize all of the
information that has been given here. And remember, there is a great deal more to
be learned. This is merely like the primer or the primer, depending on how
you want to pronounce it, for some information that should be obvious,
should be sort of self-evident, if we were not under the cosmic censorship that we
have been for so very long. Wouldn't you agree? Oh, yeah, certainly. And again, the
point is, you know, two hours invested, can people, can anyone listening to this
walk away and do something immediately? Perhaps I'd say yes, and I think we've
done some good with it. Absolutely, and I want to thank you for taking this
time with us, and thank you to you guys who have decided to subscribe and
listen. There will be more in the future, not sure where it's all going, but I
guarantee you that if you continue to remain here with us at this website, you
will learn more than you have elsewhere. And hey, I've done that alone with just
the shows that I've done with Ocelli and the Greek, which is also available on
this site, as well as at American Freedom Radio. So there you go, guys, and hey,
until next time. Thanks, Chuck.