You're listening to Platinum Radio.
Welcome, everybody, to another episode of the
Pateo Radio talk show.
The guest of tonight is Stelios Tapinakis and I've heard him talk on the American Freedom
Radio with Santos Bonacci.
That show was recorded on June the 9th of this year and I was really flabbergasted by
so many important things that Stelios said there.
So I was really eager to get him on the show and I'm really happy that he accepted the
invitation.
So I welcome you very much to this radio talk show, Stelios.
Well thank you very much.
Thank you for having me, Johan.
Yeah, to me it's an honor that you're here, but let's start with the show.
Can you please, for the listeners, introduce yourself so that they have a little bit of
an idea who you are?
Well, I look just like everybody else, but I'm coming to the conclusion that I'm just
visiting here, taking notes to be as objective as possible and to perhaps help others on
the way, if that's possible.
Yeah, exactly, because everybody is responsible for their own journey, but somehow it can
be helpful to give some ideas and some directions, but it's not your responsibility to help others.
That's what I see too.
In that talk show with Santos, you mentioned a lot of things.
Can we start with the fact that you mentioned that there is no real basis for, yeah, I think
everything we have in this so-called world.
Can you elaborate a little bit on that?
Yes, the concept of having an organization or having a body of knowledge or having something
material, even something such as money or law that affects the material world, must
be based on something.
In other words, whether it is a body of knowledge or something physical, if it's material, or
what have you.
Now we have the systems, when you debase a system, in other words, you pull from under
it the foundation of a building, let's say, or you pull from under it the knowledge base
that supports the system, whether, again, it's an organization or law or anything, medicine,
science, religion.
You now have what's called a debased system, you see.
System without a base.
Yes.
In a debased system, you create a mixture between what is real and what is brought
in that can no longer be described by laws that reality follow, you see.
So by looking at pretty much everything across the board, because we need to look at how
everything is connected, right?
And then we look to see what makes things different, but we always find that everything
is so connected that everything is really the same.
And across the board, I have found out that almost everything that man interacts with
right now, whether it's a religious institution, monetary, medical, scientific, social, it's
in the realm of, like again, like we said, debased.
It is not backed by anything.
And I would introduce the element of hypocrisy as well as something that people should consider
where you have, you say one thing but do another, right?
Give you an example, like the religions of the world are organizations, and when you
examine these organizations, they immediately show you a text that they supposedly base
the religion on, some ancient text or a prophet or a god or what have you.
And when you actually go look at the text that they allegedly are subscribing to or
adhering to, you will find they're doing the opposite or disregarding it entirely.
Or what they do is they pick and choose a few things and use it out of context, you see.
And the same thing I found out with the monetary system, the same thing with the medical system,
the same thing with the scientific system.
And to go as far as even to say mathematics, outside of using mathematics for commercial
means, for let's say quantitative means when you're counting or doing commerce, it falls
apart very quickly as well because, for example, they have the concept of zero.
Can you show me anywhere in the universe where there's zero meaning nothing?
You can't.
There's something everywhere, yeah.
So maybe zero is an equilibrium point, you see.
So again, what are we basing it on?
Because you ask seven billion people, what does zero mean?
They say nothing.
That's probably true.
But you can't show me anywhere in the universe where there's nothing.
So once we go back to looking at the base of what these systems are based on, one will
find you'll be alarmed, you'll be disappointed.
I used to say that you need not visit a madhouse to meet disorderly minds because the earth
is the madhouse of the universe.
And I found out that that was a quote, I've been saying this for a long time, but I found
out that was a quote from Goethe.
And when I found out he had already said this almost 300 years ago, I was both happy and
upset.
I was upset because I thought I was being original, but I was happy, at least I felt
like I was in good company.
That's the German philosopher Goethe you mean?
Yes.
Yeah.
Okay, great.
Yes.
So you then make, you have a choice because the truth will not make you happy, I tell
people.
And what is truth?
If we look at how to rationalize a system or a body of knowledge, and within that system
or body of knowledge, again, there is an intent to adhere to a particular body of knowledge
or subscribe to a work.
One must follow that, just like in a construction site, you follow the plans of the architect,
you know, in terms of how the building should be built.
So we have a deep based system across the planet.
And how do you reckon that with what is going on?
How do you find a midpoint and how do you communicate this?
Well, information I found out, just giving information is not very helpful, even though
it's good if the information is valid and based, again.
But it's not good if the recipient doesn't have, let's say, an operating system to run
the information.
Just like a computer, you need an operating system before you run.
Yeah, it has to be compatible.
That's what you're trying to go at ahead, I think.
Yes, compatible, but compatibility also is achieved within the operating system because
the operating system will have protocols and programs that will send something that's incompatible.
I'll give you an example.
One way to really help people is to have them use already what they have.
They don't have to go out and get anything else, you see.
In other words, they already have achieved everything they need.
You see, there's nothing more empowering than showing someone that they already have everything
they need.
It's not out there.
You already have it.
For example, I tell people everyone has the same intelligence.
Again, just like the computer, if you go to a warehouse with a thousand computers and they
all have the same specifications, they all have the same ability, you see.
The difference between people is their ability to perceive and discern the information.
Some of the texts say those who have eyes to see and ears to hear.
And then you have discernment.
Is this valid?
Is it invalid?
Is it good or is it bad?
So, a lot of the initial approaches I have are, for example, to let people think.
You see, there's an old saying, you can bring a horse to water, but you can't make him think.
The saying is really...
Think or think?
Think.
Well, they say, the old saying is, you can bring a horse to water, but you can't make
him drink.
But don't worry about making him drink.
He's going to get thirsty eventually.
The question is, can you make him think?
Because he can go from cradle to grave without thinking.
You're going to get thirsty in the 70 or 80 or 100 years you're on this planet.
But will you be able to actually think?
On your own.
On your own and with others.
It's important to also think with others.
It's called an assembly because through the counsel of the multitude comes wisdom.
So, for example, I'd start and say, when you heat or cool a room indoors, the heat always
goes to the ceiling and the cold always goes to the floor.
So all year round, you have a hot head and cold feet.
But when you're outside in the low elevation, when it's hot, you go up towards the mountaintop
or into an airplane towards the sun that is allegedly a heat source.
It gets colder and colder.
Because could it be in nature that heat becomes dense and it goes down and cold is rarefied
and it rises?
Have you ever?
You see, this is a secret, of course.
Yeah.
And the same we see with the corona.
The corona is much more heated up to 200 million, 20 million degrees Celsius, for instance,
compared to the surface of the sun, which is only about five and a half thousand.
So it's strange that if it is really a source of heating, then the further away, the hotter
it becomes, which is totally understandable.
Are you still there, my friend?
I don't hear him.
Okay.
What shall we do?
Yeah, it's a good idea because we're in the middle of something and yeah, I can, I can
elaborate a little bit on it, but yeah.
Yes, I'm back.
It says here I have a problem with Skype.
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's try again.
Yeah.
Please continue where you stopped, if you remember where the disconnect generation started.
Yes.
We have a natural phenomenon.
Let's say where natural and artificial heat go in opposite directions, for example.
You've heard of a question and answer, multiple question answer test, where you're given the
question and you're given four possible answers and you have to pick one.
Now, if you've done your homework, you'll see the right answer.
And let's say A, B, C, or D. One of those is correct, but you'll also notice that some
of the answers that are incorrect next to the correct answer are structured so they
seem correct, but they're not.
You see?
Now, if you haven't done your homework, you will guess.
And then you're into the guessing game and now you're wondering, are you going to look
over to see who has the right answer?
Or is it a good idea to do some homework?
Another example would be the multiple choice question and answer example would be septem
means seven, octo means eight, novum means nine, and decem means ten.
And everyone is writing December as 12, when it means 10.
They're writing November as 11, when it means nine.
They're writing October as 10, it means eight.
You see?
Now, is that a multiple choice question and answer test question?
You know, you see?
It could be.
Yeah.
But originally, the month of March was the first one.
And that's why February has the least amount of days.
It was the remaining month, so to say.
Yes, but also there's the possibility that can you even keep time with that calendar?
Could it be possible that that calendar is a work schedule?
For example, pick a day like April 30th.
On one year, it's a Monday.
The next year, it's a Tuesday.
The next year, it's a Sunday.
So is April 30th a Monday, Tuesday, or Sunday?
Or is it neither?
Yeah.
That's not the answer.
You see?
Yeah.
Another example would be, let's say, in science, I ask people, why does a bucket of water weigh
more than a bucket of air?
According to their periodic table, water, if it's H2O, has a molecular weight of 18.
Oxygen being 16, hydrogen being one.
And air has a molecular weight of 28.5 or 29.
Now many people say, well, because if one is a liquid state in the phase and that they're
not listening.
This is a molecular weight, just one molecule.
It doesn't matter what phase it's in.
And if you don't believe that, you can go to the welding shop where they have the compressed
air cylinders and weigh one cylinder when it's empty and then weigh it when it's full
of liquid air.
And you'll see there's very little difference.
So maybe is it possible that water is not H2O, that not much research on this has been
done since a man named William Grove in, I believe, 1811 took two metal plates, put them
in water, put electricity through and saw hydrogen, oxygen gas coming out of the water
and that was enough.
So if you know not much progress has been made on this since 1811, how easy would it
be to start researching water from an objective point of view and make some serious advancements
if no one's looked at it in almost 300 years or 200 plus years?
It's very easy, you see.
Okay.
So there's many aspects.
That would be a scientific aspect.
But there are social aspects that are more important that perhaps people can grasp much
easier, you see.
Yeah.
Well, one of the things you said in that radio show with Santos, which was very intriguing
to me, you say that the aging process is created by warmth, by heat.
So can you explain what you were trying to say then?
Yes.
Well, the aging, you have what's not just heat, you see, because there's a cycle between
heat and cold.
You have cold and then cold becomes warm and then it goes back to cold and then cold becomes
... See, heat comes from cold and then it goes back to being cold.
For example, you can have some wood or some oil or something, you see, you can touch it,
it's cold, room temperature or lower, and you ignite it, you have fire.
And then once the fire is consumed, everything cools down again.
And that what's left goes back to feed the soil, which can feed the tree.
Another tree grows and you start the process over again.
So you have the cold going to heat back to cold, and then there is a biological process
on the planet that completes the cycle.
It's almost logarithmic.
You have very close cycles and then the next part of the cycle is stretched out much longer.
If man understood the vegetative layer on the earth, he would understand the earth itself
and science and have real science.
Not that the science that we don't have is real, it is real.
And I believe on one of your talks, you mentioned the science without spirituality.
And may I offer another point on that?
Yeah, please do.
Spirituality is something you cannot avoid.
The science that is present today is very spiritual.
The thing to do, though, is can you discern what spirit it is following?
You see, when you start speaking of these things, people think that it's a matter of
religion.
Well, religion is a term that just means something that you do devoutly with regulation, with
and with regularity.
We do many things religiously.
We get up in the morning, we get dressed, we go to work, we do things like that.
That is a religious act, believe it or not, because it's done frequently and it's done
with regularity.
When you look into the spiritual realm, there's a lot of confusion because, again, there lacks
the foundation.
It's been debased.
One of the things I like to offer to people is consider when you look at the ancient texts
of the world, let's say we call the book, they call it the Bible, and then you have
other texts.
And let's just use the Bible as a reference because it is the most common one.
You have the three aspects of the body, which would be, you see, the physical body, which
is the flesh, or the carne in Latin, or carne.
You have the soul, which is the breath, and then you have the spirit, which is the intangible
essence and personality and characteristic of the being.
An example would be, for example, you have the body, which is the flesh component.
Now, the next component for the flesh component to live is the soul.
The soul is nothing more than the breath.
If you look in the Hebrew, it's the nefesh, and in the Greek, it would be called the pneuma.
That's where you get the P-N-E-U prefix, where you get pneumonia, pneumatic, you see?
So when, for example, when the body dies, the soul dies.
For example, another example would be if someone drowns in water and you pull the body out
and they're not breathing, they don't have a soul.
Now, you resuscitate them by putting your breath into their body, and now they start
breathing again.
Now they have a soul.
We've mystified the soul when it is nothing more than the breath.
Now, this is not my opinion.
This is basically what I'm reporting on what I found out, and it goes contrary to the interchangeability
of the term soul and spirit.
They use it in the same way, and it's not.
No, I fully agree with that, yes.
Yes, now the spirit is the intangible aspect.
For example, if I gave you a DVD with a movie or one of your lectures on it, you see a plastic
disc, circular, metallic, with grooves in it.
If you gave that to a material scientist, he would give you a report on its weight,
diameter, and material content, but he will not see it's one of your lectures on a DVD
unless he plays it in some equipment that is compatible to read the information or the
inforometry that's on the disc, you see?
So the spirit is intangible because it's primary.
It still is tangible.
People very often use the term energy in the New Age movement.
They say, well, that's materialistic.
I deal with energy.
Well, energy is still materialistic.
Primary forces are not part of the materialistic or energetic world.
They're primary.
And that is something that has been put away by science.
Yeah, you call them the primary vital forces, or the forces of life.
Are these also the five elements, or is that related to them, or how do you see that, Stelios?
The five elements are manifestation, and the energy from the elements are manifestation.
It's interesting when fire is considered an element in the alchemic or partial alchemic
texts because really the information that's out on the market today, especially the internet
on alchemy, is very heavily redacted and censored.
Is fire a material or an element, or an energy or a element, you see?
So they're the same.
When you see light, visible light, that is material, all of your energies are still within
the materialistic realm.
The primary forces produce the material and the energies.
Mm-hmm.
Okay?
The primary forces are responsible for if you were to get up from your chair and walk
across the room, ask any scientist what does that, how it allows you to breathe, how does
a plant grow, what is growth, what keeps the earth rotating in space.
You see, these are primary.
So if you eliminate the primary element in any field, whether it's law, medicine, or science,
now you're dealing with the symptom, the cause.
And you go into the realm where reproducing things become mysterious, right?
You go into, you see, because now you don't know the actual cause.
So there's a lot of literary mechanisms and a lot of literary terms that reflect the primary
forces or primary, yeah, let's call them forces because they are a force.
They're very powerful in a very subtle way.
And all of these things that we manifest or see manifest as energy and matter are secondary.
So when you go back to the ancient texts, very often there's a misinterpretation again
between the soul, the spirit, and the body, the primary, and the secondary, which is energy
and matter.
Yeah, I fully agree with that.
I tried to explain that using the famous allegory of the cave by Plato, where he talks about
that we perceive only a shadow world, and those shadows are projected by something in
front of that.
I call it the proto-world, the world that is in front of the so-called real world.
And yeah, I think what you mean by the vital forces, the primary forces, they are the forces
in the proto-world.
We are not able to perceive them or have equipment that can detect them, but they in fact create
everything.
And our science is not aware of that, the universities, and that's why they can't really
explain anything.
They can only describe, but they describe it in such a way that most people think it's
an explanation, but that's really a trick to put sand in people's eyes.
So that's the main problem.
They focus not on where everything is really coming from.
So I think we're on the same page here, Stelios.
Yes.
There's an interesting phenomenon that happens socially with that, with those that do have
the knowledge and maintain it and hide it, or do not make it clearly known.
You see, because the definition of a genius is someone who can explain the obvious in
simple terms and anyone can understand it.
When they put a scientist in front of you with complex formulas and language that people
don't understand, that is not genius.
That is there to hide something or confuse you or allow you to compartmentalize that
information so you can reject it or not allow it to come in.
What happens though, whether it's political, scientific, religious, when this base knowledge
is withdrawn from the people, the people's behavior change.
They become less civilized, for example.
Like for example, you live in a society, it doesn't mean that it's civilized, right?
Mm-hmm.
Civilization is not, is an aspect of society or a level of society can reach.
So what happens is these small groups of people that hold this information back, they notice
the main population starts to change its behavior and become more, let's say, the common term
would be barbaric or violent or ignorant.
And the more ignorant or barbaric the population becomes, those that have the power and the
knowledge become more oppressive and more separatist.
They say, look at them, how dangerous they are, they need to be controlled.
But if they had shared the information, given the information, that would have not happened.
But then becomes a vicious cycle because the more they withdraw the information, the worse
the society gets and then the more oppression and control has to be put on them, you see?
Yeah, that's exactly what's happening.
If you look at the general level of, yeah, intelligence or whatever, ability to understand,
it's rapidly decreasing.
So what you're describing is what I see happening dramatically.
When you look at the level of television, for instance, I remember when I was a child,
I was a student, the level was much higher than nowadays because it's becoming totally
stupid, totally zero content.
So it's really alarming.
Yes, I usually give, when I speak to someone that I haven't met before, let's say, I have
three things to describe the current state of humanity, perhaps four if we have time.
These three things have five aspects to them.
If I can just go through them, it might also help with a good introduction of where this
thought process can go.
Yeah, please go ahead.
Okay, the first aspect is you understand that when a woman is pregnant and she has come
to full term, full gestation, over nine months, let's say, that child needs to be born.
If the woman does not bear the child and expel it from her body and it's kept in her body
for much longer, she can experience what's called toxemia, where her body becomes very
stressed and the baby now becomes a deadly poison to her.
And that can also, the mother can die and the baby can die, right, if she does not expel
the child.
Another example would be, you understand there are certain manufacturing processes, like
for example, the manufacture of solar panels or certain metal alloys like titanium.
When you produce, let's say, one pound of solar panel, you have two pounds of toxic
waste and there's a toxic side effect of certain manufacturing processes.
So one might want to ask the question, is the manufacturing of human beings leave one
or leave a society with toxic side effects?
You see, if you look at human beings being in an evolutionary state, not an evolution
as the way Darwin says, but in an evolutionary state where you actually are growing or manufacturing
a being, okay, that would be one thing to consider.
The next thing to consider would be when you are going into the wilderness, for example,
into a natural state, whether it's a forest or a desert, with the intention of building
a village or a town, you have to go in first and clear an area because it is a wild area,
let's say, right?
And you level it and you make a plan and you then start to build your village.
When you look at the nearby planets in the solar system, the moon, the Mars, Venus, Mercury,
you see barren planets and the scientists tell you all of those features on the planets
are impact craters.
Now wait a second, when a small object impacts a larger object at velocity, it usually leaves
a parabolic bowl shape on the surface.
If you look at most of the features on the nearby moon, Mars, Venus, Mercury, there are
some of these impacts, but most of these features, they're not impact craters.
You'll see the surface is still round and maintained untouched, but a rim, a round rim
blown around and a center peak.
Could it be that that was, let's say, an electrical discharge?
Could it be a neutrally charged plasma that when it hits the surface becomes positively
charged that forms that feature on the planet?
And isn't it unusual when you see how all of these barren planets are around us and
then you see this beautiful blue marble they call the Earth with all of this life on it?
Do you see that?
Okay.
Yes, yes.
Something to consider.
And I'm saying these things in a way that these are all common things that we can maybe reconsider
and reapply to our existence.
I just find it very unusual that all the planets around us have been cleared away and when
we are so unique, and they have been cleared away in a fashion that is not exactly how
it's described to us, because if you again look at the features on the planets, they
are not impact craters at all, the majority of them.
The third aspect is, let's say, for example, you are going to rent or lease a piece of
property, and you have one billion roommates or seven billion roommates, and they send
you to meet the landlord and to sign the lease agreement so you can take control of
the property.
Now, you go to the landlord and you see the lease, and it's about a thousand pages long
with all of these terms and conditions, and you make the agreement and you come back,
but you don't tell any of your one billion or seven billion roommates any of the terms
and conditions.
And everyone goes off and doesn't know the terms and conditions and is doing what they
want, and some things that they do might follow the terms and conditions, but many
others don't.
And then your roommates or the people you are sharing the property with are wondering
why the water is being turned off, why the power is being turned off, and why there is
an eviction notice, or why, you know, but you have not told them the terms, you see.
Could that be another way to look at our existence here?
That's an interesting thought.
Would you like to go into that, or do you want to first finish there?
Absolutely.
So those are five aspects of, you know, three aspects with five components to them.
When you look at that, for example, if you look again at the ancient texts, the ancient
texts are there to give us a high vantage point.
What I mean by that is, let's say there is a celebration or a holiday in a city, and
you have a parade, okay, and there are people on the sidewalk, and they see the floats, they
call them, you know, they go down the street, okay, all of the procession, and let's say
it's a four-hour long parade, and you're there with your friends, and you say, look at this
one, look at that one, and they start guessing what the last float is going to look like.
What is the last object in the parade?
Well, that's three hours from now, let's say.
You have to wait on the sidewalk and see when it comes by, if you're going to make a bet
or a prediction.
Or if you have a friend in a helicopter, and you have a cell phone, and he has a cell phone,
you can call him up in the helicopter, and he can see the beginning of the parade and
the end of the parade all in one shot, you see?
And he tells you, for example, the last float in the parade is going to be a pink elephant
with a green hat.
So you say, thank you very much, you tell all your friends around you, well, in three
hours you're going to see the last float is a pink elephant with a green hat.
And everyone around you says, oh, that's ridiculous, you know, no such thing, you know, I mean,
nah, nah, nah.
Well, three hours go by, and here comes the pink elephant with the green hat.
Now are you psychic?
Absolutely not.
Do you have access to information that has a high vantage point that can see the beginning
and the end at one time?
Absolutely.
So can a helicopter be a time machine?
You see?
So these ancient texts give us a perspective from a high vantage point.
Now, of course, I found to make a criticism on the inhabitants of the earth right now,
it's not that they're ignorant or not intelligent, it's they're very stubborn and rebellious.
There's a difference, you see?
So when you start speaking of these ancient texts, the first thing is, I'm not religious.
I don't want to hear it.
Or I don't believe that, or that was written by man, or whatever, whatever.
They don't go and check the information, you see?
So when you check the information of the ancient texts, they're all in agreement.
But the followers of these ancient texts that follow religions are not in agreement, right?
No.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
So there's many, many interesting points.
For example, if you take the book, the Bible, in the first verse in English, it says,
In the beginning God created the heavens and the earth.
I think there are 10 words there.
If you go back to the original Hebrew, you're going to see,
Bereshith bara Elohim etah shemihim behet ha'aretz.
You're going to see seven words there.
So someone's going to say, well, they added three.
Well, no, they actually added four because they took one away.
They're not translating one of the words there.
Because when you look at, for example, in the first verse of the Bible, you say, it actually
would say, Beginnings created Elohim.
Elohim would be the mighty ones.
It's plural.
The Aleph Tav and the heavens and the earth.
Now what they're not translating in any translation is,
In the beginning Elohim, the mighty ones, created the Aleph Tav.
They translate the heavens and the earth, but they don't translate the Aleph Tav.
The Aleph Tav, Aleph is the first letter of the Hebrew alphabet, and Tav is the last letter
of the Hebrew alphabet.
Or you can say the A and the Z, or you can say in Greek, the Alpha and the Omega.
Now when you go to, let's say, the book of John, it says, In the beginning, which means
Bereshith, beginning, which is Genesis, was the word, and the word was with God and God
was the word.
Now someone in the Bible describes himself as being the Aleph Tav or the Alpha and the
Omega.
He says, I am the word, I am the Alpha and the Omega.
You see, and he's right there in the first verse of Genesis, but you will never see it
in an English translation.
Now why am I giving this as an example?
Because now we created a loop.
When you see the information in the first verse, you really don't get a definition until
you go more towards the end of the book, and it brings you back, and it's all connected,
like tendrils or roots of a tree, how they spread out, but they all come from the same.
So these books, these ancient texts, are preserved, even today, in mostly their original form.
And not only are they preserved in their original form, they are written on what I would call
a 30th or 40th grade level.
Like, for example, education is rated from kindergarten through 12th grade high school,
and then 16th grade would be bachelor's degree, 18th grade would be master's, and 20th grade
would be Ph.D., right?
So these books are written on a very high level.
Now, like you mentioned earlier, how everything is getting stupid in television,
today, even someone graduating from college is really 8th grade level or 6th grade level
from 100 years ago.
So their ability to take current knowledge or current level of education and go and look
at these ancient texts, the gap is even becoming more and more wide.
And they're less and less easy to understand.
So my point here is, if you look at any of the ancient texts, you will find that there
is information that brings you back around.
The texts always define themselves.
You don't need to go outside of the text.
And the purpose of the text is to give three things.
One is to give you an operating program.
Like when you buy a computer and you plug it in, it's just blinking.
You have to put in the operating system, whether it's an Apple or a Microsoft,
the main operating system disk, before you can process.
The second thing these ancient texts do is they give you a set of laws from a high vantage point.
When I say laws, I mean what to eat, what to wear, how to farm, how to do business,
how to treat your family, how to treat your neighbor.
You see?
All of these laws.
I'm not talking traffic laws.
Even though you can find that in the behavior aspect.
And the third aspect is to show you what's to come.
And all three aspects can be proven of that.
So, because the interesting aspect of it is, even if you don't want to adhere to any of
these texts or understand them or follow them, you're going to anyway.
Because if you look at, for example, all of the secular culture and secular rules and
secular science, they're still based on information that is in these texts and documents.
So, you see, it's not that you're escaping it.
It's that, is it possible that humanity is being manufactured right now?
And there are toxic side effects.
Is it possible that this part of the solar system was cleared so we can have the very
habitable planet where we are right now?
And also, is it possible that these very important agreements in terms of being stewards on this
planet are being withheld from the many?
The irony, though, is the many do have access to them, right?
But no one is reading it.
No.
They lack time.
They lack interest.
They lack energy.
Correct.
Yeah.
And also, when you look at these ancient texts and you look at science, current science, very
carefully, you'll see they're also in agreement.
But on the surface, they're not.
You see?
I'll give you another example.
The very orthodox Christians, when I say orthodox, meaning they adhere to Christian principles,
they always say, well, creation happened 6,000 years ago.
You've heard that possibly.
Yes, yes.
And that is one of the main contentions between them and the scientific community.
That doesn't make any sense, because when you look at the biblical definition of time,
it says that one day is 1,000 years and 1,000 years is a day.
So, for example, you have the seven days of creation.
That's 7,000 years.
And you have a character called Adam that came on the 6,000th year.
And that was roughly 6,000 years ago.
So, the first chapter of Genesis has a minimum of 12,000 years.
But in the first verse, everything was created.
In the second verse, it says everything became weltered and wasted.
And then it had to be remade.
So, there's an undisclosed period of time there.
It could be in the millions.
Actually, there are some very good Hebrew scholars that have shown a 4.5 to 5 billion
year time period between Genesis 1 and Genesis 2 based on the numerology of the letters.
So, when you start saying that the Bible possibly shows 4.5 to 5 billion years in the first two verses
and then 12,000 years ago there was a big cataclysm,
is science in agreement with that?
Sure?
Science is, yes.
Did you say 9,500 to 13,000 years ago there was a major solar system-wide cataclysm?
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
So, where the Orthodox version of creation that Christianity professes
being everything was created 6,000 years ago,
where did they get that from?
Because it's not in the text.
No, it's not a genuine interpretation.
It's just a...
It's not even an interpretation.
It's completely foreign and accepted.
Yes.
It's a dogma, yeah.
And it's debased.
It's not based on anything, is it?
Well, it could be based on an idea that someone had and everyone decided to follow.
I'll give you another example.
For example, in the Christian faith,
they celebrate December 25th as the birth of Jesus Christ.
I'm using their terminology, right?
Mm-hmm.
And almost everyone knows that is a traditional aspect
because no one really knows when.
Well, I can show you a place in the Bible where you can see
when the character known as the Christ was born
down to the minute accuracy and the day.
And if you go to the book Revelation 12,
you will see an astronomical sign.
It says there was a virgin about to give birth.
I'm paraphrasing here.
She had 12 stars at her head.
She was cloaked with the sun with the moon at her feet.
Whoa, wait a second.
That is the constellation Virgo.
With the sun on her chest and the moon at her feet.
So that means it's in the late afternoon, sundown.
And the moon is only there in the west in the middle of the month.
So that is an astronomical alignment,
which is extremely precise, by the way.
Astronomical alignments are very, very precise.
Mm-hmm.
Now, when anyone sees this,
they need to go to an astronomical observatory
where they have the proper computers for this.
And I recommend you go to what they call a planetarium
where they do the shows, the laser shows on the ceilings at night
because those guys are there all day.
They have nothing to do, right?
So you give them the information and they'll say,
well, yeah, this happens X amount of years.
It happens every 14 years here.
It happens every seven years here.
It happens every 10 years here.
When do you want to know?
And you say, well, if we look at the text,
you know the concept of triangulation.
You have two points.
You find the third.
If you look at the New Testament,
it says that we know that was the year
that Caesar proclaimed a census of the empire.
And we find secular records show us it's between 2 and 6 BC.
And also we know that Herod the Great died two years,
two and a half years after that time.
Again, secular records show it's between 2 and 8 BC.
So you go to the astronomical observatory
and the computer and tell them,
when does this event happen?
According to the Gregorian calendar,
the modern calendar now,
between 2 and 6 or 2 and 8 BC.
Do you have anything?
And they come back and they do their thing.
You know, the computer has all of these alignments.
It can produce the alignment.
And it says, yes, we do.
And it says, what is it?
It's September 11, 3 BC.
You're kidding.
No.
Whoa.
And it's around 640 PM.
And if you look biblically,
it would be the 15th day of the seventh month,
which is the day of tabernacle,
because he says he came to set his tabernacle amongst us.
Now, have you ever heard of the term September 11th before?
Yeah, I think I've heard a couple of times.
Well, is it possible that someone has this information
and we don't know it?
It's very well possible, yes.
Now, is it possible that the Christ in the text,
whether you believe it or not or know it or not,
go look it up.
He says, think not I came to unite.
I came to divide with the sword,
father against son,
daughter against mother-in-law,
brother against brother.
And in another verse, he says,
I will bring terror upon you.
Now, is this the Christ that is projected in religious circles?
No.
Yes, thank you.
Another aspect would be the nativity scene
where they show the three wise men in the manger and all that, right?
Well, if you read the text,
we don't know how many there were.
We knew there was more than two.
And we know that they came to him
when he was in his father's workshop
when he was around two years old.
So are we talking about the same thing here?
This is the text.
This has nothing to do with what I believe in,
what you believe in,
what anyone should believe in.
I'm talking about when we look at the text.
You see, and here we have billions of people basing,
they say with their own volition,
with their own mouth,
their faith is based on this text.
Right?
Is it really?
No.
I think you've got a point here, Stelios.
Yeah.
Now, I'm not any more intelligent
or less intelligent than anyone else.
We already established we all have the same intelligence.
Wow.
Time is running out
and I have so many questions.
I don't know where to start.
What is your idea?
For instance,
who wrote the ancient,
the Old Testament,
for instance?
When you look at the first five books of Moses,
for example,
they came 2,500 years after.
There are books older than that.
Let's say the book of Job.
So there's a specific order there.
Who wrote it?
Let's say men wrote it,
just like you would dictate to a secretary.
Who wrote that?
My secretary wrote that, right?
If we have a being
that is intelligent enough
to design and build everything,
are they intelligent enough to communicate to us?
You see?
So was it written by men?
Absolutely.
You can see the writing.
Is it a form of dictation?
Absolutely.
Even in modern history,
you hear of people who have
channeled information
and they wrote it down.
The reason you write something down
is to memorialize it in written form.
You can memorialize in oral form.
There are many traditions
in many countries of the world
that still retain oral memorialization,
like the ancient Greeks
with their iambic pentameter.
Homer wrote
the Iliad and the Odyssey
to be oral
with a certain rhythm
and the information was retained.
Yes, and the same is true
for the Gilgamesh Apostle
that was given
many generations long
just orally
because it had rhyming
so it was like a first
to be proclaimed.
The original texts
of preservation
which currently today
is the Hebrew and the Greek
you will find
there is series of number
and logical formations
underneath the text
that adhere the text
and it's an error correction system.
I'm not talking about the Bible code
you've heard of where they take diagonal cuts
through the text and they come up
with predictions, right?
You've seen that aspect?
Yeah, I think but
it doesn't feel good for me.
Because I had once downloaded
this program and I pulled up
predictions and I showed them to someone
they see the Bible code works.
I said, well the program works
but is it valid for the Bible code?
And they say, what do you mean?
I said, I did all this from the book Moby Dick.
And I got
OK
Yeah, alright
so, again
we don't have
a lot of time
and I touched on these points
because in the future
this topic that we're basically talking about
the spiritual aspect, the body, the soul
and the ancient text, there is going to be a big revival
in the next decade or so
to go back to adhere
to these ancient texts or what people
allegedly say they subscribe to
and when
that happens, your current
institutions that are in place
will no longer be able to stand
and also the people
and the scholars in these institutions
will not have
any answers
No
In other words, do you remember back
in the 50s
and 60s, everyone wore a hat
all the men wore hats
and they wore jackets, right?
Yeah
Look at the movies from 50 years ago, everybody wore a hat
Well, they say here
in the US, John F. Kennedy was the first president
not to wear a hat and everyone wanted to be
fashionable so the men stopped wearing hats
What happened to all the hat shops?
You had a hat shop in every corner
Yeah, they had to search for another business
Thank you
How many Christians do you
know or heard of that know that
Christ was born on September 11th
3 B.C. according to their own text
Yeah, I don't think anyone
can validate
So if anyone can validate, and I don't like to
give opinion, I'd like to share information
that can be validated
Exactly
You mentioned briefly
that we are in some kind of
manufacturing process
Have you any idea
what we will become
as mankind?
Absolutely
We are part of a family
and it's very clear in the ancient text
that the mighty ones, we call them gods
are a family
There are men and women
If you read
in the writings
I believe it's in Proverbs
and Ecclesiastes
that wisdom is a woman
and she is a spouse
We have other characters
that are both male and female that are not
benevolent
For example
all of the military
ranking on earth
you have general, colonel, admiral
going down to the private
That is not something man invented
That is a copy of the other realm
also
Oh, I didn't know that
You are in the military part of the universe
Let's just say for now
the universe is divided into 24 sectors
and this particular one
is the war aspect of it
In other words, you are in the middle of a
cosmic war
What are we going to become
is we are going to join the family
of these mighty ones
But can you give
the analogy of the caterpillar
forming a chrysalis and becoming a butterfly
Can you give the example
of a full metamorphosis
Will we still
retain an anthropomorphic
aspect? Absolutely
Because when you read in the ancient texts
these mighty ones are gods
They like planting gardens
They like drinking wine
You know, they planted the Garden of Eden
Do you see?
All the wine press
You see, they have very much the stuff
We are a reflection, as above, so below
Exactly, it's a kind of mirror
And we are in a very, very special location
Again, I urge anyone and everyone
to look at the nearby planets
and look at how barren they are
and then look at how lush and beautiful the earth is
comparatively
Does that look natural
or is it artificial?
Let me just finish off maybe by saying this
that everything is artificial
Nature itself is artificial
because by definition
in order for something to be artificial
it must have an artificer
or an artist or a creator to make it
So the problem is not sharing the information
or giving the information
The problem is how does one get over the stubbornness
and the rebelliousness of the people to see it
Yeah, some expect some big events
to happen
and maybe people will
become more curious than they are now
and start to redo their homework
Exactly
But you're going to have to really do your homework
not copy someone else's
No, that's what I refer to
and it's also the process of studying
that helps you
to become
or to do the
transformation
the inner transformation
You can't cheat with this
for instance
You have to do your own process
Yes, so in essence
everything is the way it's supposed to be
lawfully, according to the laws of nature
Is there suffering?
Yes, the only reason we consider it evil
and suffering
is because we don't understand it
But if we understood it
would we be in such a miserable condition
on the earth right now?
No
If you go study the medieval ages
around the year 800 to the year 1000
almost three quarters
of the population of Europe
was eliminated through plagues
and natural disasters
So currently, where you are on the planet
even though it is the credits part of the movie
you know, when a movie ends
you still have the film holding the credits
basically
the earth is a paradise
comparatively to how it was in the past
even with all the
environmental saying we are destroying
the environment and global warming
the level of
to habitate
the earth right now is almost like a paradise
compared to how
do some research and you can see
So there are
many good points
I don't think that the
heat comes from cold and it goes back to cold
you have the good and the bad
back to good
positive, negative, positive
Yeah, it's an ongoing cycle
So
again I would urge anyone listening
if you believe in something
or if you know something that is
based allegedly on something
else, whether it's a
body of knowledge or something material
do five minutes of homework
to see is it truly
based or debased at this point
And how
can I do that because I don't think everybody
speak the original languages, I think you speak
a lot of languages, Hebrew and perhaps
Greek too and maybe even more
but how can you study the original
writings from the ancient
The work already has been done
you have what's called
interlinears where you have the
language of your choice and then below it
the original languages of preservation
Okay
and then you can actually see what each word
means. The beauty of these
of Greek and Hebrew
though
is that you don't really need a
dictionary, if you know what the letters mean
you can figure out what the word means
Yeah, but then you have a word but then you
have to also find the meaning of the word
interpretation of that, of those letters
Yes, but also remember
in interpretation there is only one interpretation
There are many translations
and many versions, for example when an
ambassador goes to the UN
from Japan, he has to bring an interpreter
and that is to make the effort
to interpret
from Japanese to English, let's say
in the most precise way possible
there is only one interpretation
that uses accuracy and precision
but you don't have
you have versions
don't believe me, it says it right on the
books you have
is it
hearsay
The quality of the
connection is not too good, Stelios
a lot of words are not coming over
at least I don't hear them, I hope the listeners
do hear them
so maybe you can repeat the last question, last remark
if you want
Yes, interpret, can you hear me now?
Yeah, I can hear you now, but sometimes it's very soft
and it's coming back again
An interpretation must be accurate and precise
where a version is basically hearsay
Okay, yeah
So we should
find solid ground
to put our belief system
our understanding on
Yes, whether it's scientific, medical, mathematical
if you read all of your
scientific books, it doesn't say
anything ever is, it says it appears to be
you ever noticed that?
I've not noticed it, but
it's not a surprise to me
Yeah, we're actually doing
the same kind of work, but
we come from different directions
you really go to the foundation
the writings
and that's why I invited you
for the show, because I've not met
anyone who was so thoroughly
on that subject
so I think I will
have to ask you to come again to the radio
show Stelios, because
we've only touched a lot
of issues, but I think there's
much, much more to discuss
Sure
So anyone
and everyone can understand it
if an 8 year old in the room cannot understand what you're saying
you're not saying it right
Exactly, that's what I also say
I've read a lot of books, mostly in Dutch
and every time that's what I try to
explain to people
it's in the simplicity, and if you make it complex
yeah, then you
only put sand in the people's eyes
that's the story of
Hans Christian Andersen, the fairy tale
of the emperor who wears no clothes
but nobody can see it
because they're blinded
with all kinds of
not real issues, but a little child
is able to see the truth
so that's what we should do, I think
Very good, thank you for having me
Yeah, thank you very much Stelios
for being my guest
I'll contact you to
ask you to come back one more time
or maybe even more times
so thank you very much for being my guest
all the listeners, thank you very much
Thank you very much for listening
and I hope that you join the radio show next time
Bye bye