Hi, I'm Mitch Santel and you're listening to Remnants and Luminaries on American Freedom
Radio.
You can reach me each and every Saturday night from 9 p.m. to 11 p.m. Central Standard Time
or 7 p.m. to 9 p.m. Pacific Standard Time.
If you're new to the show, each and every Saturday night, I explore a unique dialogue
with another human being on this planet who has a unique point of view.
You know, in my humble opinion, American 2015 is really not at the end.
I feel like the country's sort of like at the beginning of the end.
And sometimes I ponder at night, am I who I say I am?
Will I do what I say I will do?
And what is the legacy I want to leave behind?
You know, at the age of seven, my father, Richard Santel, gave me my first Sony transistor
radio.
That was back in 1964.
Within the days, weeks and months ahead, I became what is now called a talk radio junkie.
You know, throughout my childhood years and throughout my teenage years, I had my trusty
Sony transistor radio under my pillow at night where I would pretend to be asleep whenever
my mom or dad would come to the door.
But as soon as the door closed, I had the radio on quietly listening through the pillow.
Throughout the years, I heard many amazing talk radio voices.
As I shifted from AM talk radio to FM talk radio, I started to listen to Elliott Mintz
every Sunday night, first on KMET in 1969, and then I started listening to Elliott Mintz
on KLOS from 1970 to 71.
Then during the day after school, I'd switch back to my trusty AM Sony radio and I'd hear
Bill Balance on KGBS and the hullabalooer David Hall and Dr. Tony Grant.
After that, when I became a dad in my 20s, I started listening to Tom Likas and then being
a chronic insomniac, I started listening to Art Bell.
If you had a chance to hear American Freedom Radio's Marathon, it was really incredible.
On that show, there was a particular episode that I kept listening to and that was when
I was listening to Acelli and the Greek and Jack Blood.
Then I started listening to the Greek.
Then there was a show that was aired on November 7, 2015 called The Dummy Load.
If you haven't heard The Dummy Load, you have to go back to the American Freedom Radio archives.
Thank you so much, Danny.
It's phenomenal the way you archive this network and listen to The Dummy Load.
Every once in a while, you get to hear a unique point of view.
You get to hear someone who is a real contrarian, who doesn't go along to get along, who doesn't
worry about anything.
Every time that I've had those moments of stress, where do I turn, what's next, what's
going to happen in humanity, and is this big ball that we love, our planet Earth, going
to spin off its axis into a big black hole?
As Woody Allen once said, about every hundred years, the world sort of flushes out the previous
generation who are just visiting and moves on to the next generation.
So tonight, without further ado, there was no other person I could think of on this particular
Saturday night as we sit here quietly on November 28, 2015 and talk to the Greek.
Welcome to Remnants and Luminaries, young man.
Hello, Mitch, and thanks for having me.
I'm so happy to have you on the show tonight.
I have wanted to have a conversation with you since I first heard your show, but I decided
to follow your lead, and I've listened to your show many times, and I've listened to
the archives many times, and I decided, you know what?
Rather than do the normal Mitch Santel, let's over-prep everything, I just figured we'd
just have a dialogue.
So how do you feel in 2015?
What is your perspective on the planet?
Has humanity lost its mind, or are we just changing hairsprays?
The latter.
And it appears that they've invented the hairspray before they invented the wheel, as another
writer might have written once.
Yeah, it's just to start off, you know, I used to have a saying, and when I discovered
it was the same saying was said by a man named, I believe, Wolfgang Goethe, and the saying
goes like, you need not visit an insane asylum to meet disordered spirits, because the earth
is the insane asylum of the universe.
So once you internalize that thought, you know, whether you believe it or not, but internalize
the thought, what that actually means, everything's okay, you see, because it's kind of not supposed
to be this way, but that's how it is, like if you visit an insane asylum, there's a lot
of very strange things going on in insane asylums, but guess what?
It's an insane asylum, so what's the problem?
You know, it's interesting that you say that, because I often tell people that crazy is the
new normal, and I sort of sit and watch people, and I've become much more of a people watcher
than I used to be.
My big transition was sort of in 2006, when Apple introduced, you know, this little thing
called the iPhone, and I started watching people like texting with it, and not looking
at each other, but sort of being addicted to looking at the phone, you know what I'm
saying, and getting their little buzz every two minutes or so, and so I've never really
used a smartphone, and I did not become part of the texting generation, even though I will
admit to being a bit of a technology addict, and Dr. John Coleman wrote the most incredible
article in the late 1990s called Terminal Madness in the End Times, and then I started
watching all of the Black Friday stampedes, you know, of people trying to get the latest
TV, or the vegetable steamer, or the blanket of their choice, and just people going nuts
over stuff, and realizing that how you do anything is how you do everything, and that
humanity, like you always say, the boogeyman is in the mirror when you look at yourself,
and you've got to laugh and get out of your own way.
Yeah, there's a sense of purpose that we have, when I say we, meaning each individual, man,
woman, and child, and then there's the, what we might call the main ecosystem, or the main
environment, on a micro level would be the earth, on a macro would be the cosmos, and
all that's in it that can be perceived, or even imagined, so the purpose of the individual
now has been distracted by the me devices, see, they call them I devices, but what is
I, me?
You see, you're into, it's the narcissistic aspect of humanity that's being taken advantage
now, and see, I yearn for the days when people are smart and phones are stupid again, but
nonetheless, it's all about one sense of purpose, and you know, just as you see, there's a lot
of conspiracy theories, you know, groups like, oh, the Illuminati, or this group, or that
group, they're going to get you, those are, in retrospect, it'll be seen, or it can be
seen as a bunch of people that just create that type of fear, because they're actually
afraid of the people next to them, you know, to distract them, so once you actually internalize
these things that people are considering behind these global conspiracies, there's really
nothing there, if it doesn't affect you, it doesn't exist, you see what I mean?
I understand, in my view, what I realized at the end of the day is that in the grand
scheme of things, people really don't care, and I'm thinking, now it's a hundred years
from now, and someone finds this dialogue, this interview in the archives, what would
you tell someone that was walking around the earth a hundred years from now about your
reflections on 2015, what would you say to a future generation?
I told you so, it's very simple, it's sort of, here's the interesting thing, you ever
notice how people don't look up anymore, how they're always looking down when they're walking
in the street, looking at their devices, for example, you know, they're really not looking
at the floor, they're looking at something that they're holding, but their head is in
a posture where the neck is bent forward, and they're slouching forward and looking
down, they're not looking up, you see, where if you look at paintings from let's say several
hundred years ago, whenever you would see a crowd of people, or not necessarily the subjects
of the paintings, the people were looking forward or looking up, typically, so there's
something called vantage point, and it's always best to get one's information from a high vantage
point, because the beauty of a high vantage point is you get to see more of time in less
of a space, just as if there was a parade on the street that takes four hours to pass by,
you don't know what the last float's going to be unless you're on the ground waiting for four
hours, but if you have a friend in a helicopter, you can call him with your cell phone and ask
him what is the last float, and he'll relay the information back to you, and now you have
information that the people on the ground level with you would have to wait three or four hours
to get, you see, because when you're up in the helicopter, you see the front of the parade
and the end of the parade all in one view, so it's always good to get information from a high
vantage point, and so from that point of view, a hundred years from now, if one looks at the
clockwork of how things are moving, it's going to be a very different society, and just to sum
that up, it'll be a society where entropy will begin to be reversed. Interesting. Yeah. Interesting.
My take is, you know, you often hear people say that, you know, those who do not remember their
past are doomed to repeat it, and the reality is that those who refuse to study their past
are doomed to repeat it, and so I can't... Somewhat. Yeah, it's like an eight-track tape from 1968 that
keeps repeating itself. One of the... Yeah. One of the challenges that I have is watching a society
that is no longer morally bankrupt. I'm watching a society that's culturally bankrupt, and when a
society becomes culturally bankrupt, they no longer remember their own past, and so it's all about the
latest jolt. You know what I mean? The latest thing. It's all about the coliseum. It's all about the
bread and the circuses and the beer. It's not about having a perspective, and what I see is an
environment where things are now moving so fast where people literally can't slow down, and
for me, I'm always looking to get out of the line of fire. You know what I mean? And so I simply
observe what's going on in the moment, step away from blame, criticism, or judgment of what that
is happening in that moment, and just observe it. What I've noticed in your observations and in your
dialogues on your own show is that at the end of the day, all these little petty fights and
misunderstandings, really at the end of the day, they don't mean anything, do they?
No, but they are cumulative. They're cumulative in the main movement
that where society is going to. In other words, these things we call maybe axial periods. Have
you heard the most recent axial period would be post-911 world. Have you heard that?
Oh, sure.
Yeah, that's an axial period in history. Another one would be what they call BC and AD.
There are other axial periods for the Industrial Revolution, let's say.
So there's going to be another axial period that will change the way people perceive things,
not too far from now, what you call the early 2020s.
So yeah, but just to address the way people are now, this is just the way the culture on
society has been. For example, back in France, 200 plus years ago, when Ben Franklin was
putting out his lightning rod, it became a fashion where people were putting small,
little lightning rods on hats. So this kind of like trinket and adornment and trivialization,
those little trends have always been around. So the thing that I tend to look at is not
necessarily addressing the purpose of each individual because how many times have you
heard in society about jobs? You know, the job reports are bad. In employment, you should get
a job or what kind of a job do you see? Whenever you hear that in a society, you're in bad shape
because people should not be encouraged to get a job. They should be encouraged to discover what
their natural purpose and talent is and then have everything around them, meaning their families,
friends and education system support that so they become the best at their natural talent.
So these are the types of criticisms of things that I look at that people are missing that
need to be comprehended because if you were the best street sweeper in the world, I assure you,
even before mid-career, you would have the house that you always wanted and the car you always
wanted. And you see, if you're the best at what you do, regardless of the category,
you will always be successful and you will never have any, all of your needs will always be met.
So this is not discussed or even brought up in mainstream or alternative. So I have to say the
things that I say because simply because they're not being said. I totally agree. I have found in
my own life and observing people that many times that someone may have a dream in their heart
of something they want to do in their life that is so much bigger than themselves that they can't
do it by themselves. And a lot of times their own family, you know what I'm saying? They'll say,
well, not you, not now, can't happen, won't work. And they end up sort of adopting strangers who
become their family so they can then go out into the world and do what it is they really want to do.
And the reason that I share this with you is that my observation of the society
is that the people that seem to be the most empowered and enlightened
are really doing something that they love. And they've sort of let go of this need for approval,
you know what I mean, from other people. They're just, they're going about doing what they need to
do. And I found within the alternative media, or at least how it started for me,
which my sort of quote-unquote awakening was probably around 1993, when I met one of the
co-founders of Ashton Tate Software. And I met Jay Lashley, and he and his team did the original
Lotus 1-2-3. And he sort of mentored me into this concept of, you know, if you sort of think
like the elite think, then, you know, the next car you buy, you don't have to have it in your name.
You just sort of put it in a trust, and the trust lets you buy the car. And so you let go of the
need of having to own things. Because what happens is people have this philosophy, I find,
where they sort of think they're going to live forever. And they don't realize this is a very
temporary situation. And that situations repeat themselves. In other words, I've never gone to a
funeral and seen a U-Haul truck behind a Hearst, you know, a Hearst limousine. You know what I'm
saying? Or an armored car with money, yeah. Correct. So it's like, what is it that you want
to do in the moment that's going to leave a change? I'm finding now a lot of people that are
sort of in three groups. I'm finding one group that's sort of stuck right now. They wish they
could have their old life back. They wish it could be like it used to be. Oh, it was so much better
back in the day when blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, whatever it is. Then I find a second group of
people that are what I call the new sociopath. And they've sort of stepped out of the circle of
mediocrity. And it's totally about them. And then there seems to be this third group. And I must say,
I think you're part of the third group. And the third group is what I call the walkaway civilization
where there's a group of us that sort of have, you know, like you said, a helicopter where,
you know, you fly over a situation and you look at something and you realize that
if you keep doing the same thing over again, it's not going to work anymore and that we've
got to find a better way to be a humanity together. Does that make sense?
Yeah, that seems to be the question of what is the meaning of things. And I believe in the first
episode, Chuck and I got together and we didn't know what to discuss. And we figured we'd just
discuss the nature and reality of what we call humanity. And one of the interesting points that
we brought up was, and it's also the title of the first episode, is 100% external input.
And what I mean by that is that men and women and their young, I don't like calling them kids
because kids are goats, right? They're just small people. We are distinct from all of the other
creatures on this earth is because we require 100% external input. And the analogy was, if you
had a small puppy, six-week-old puppy raised by a family of gorillas to maturity, and you adopted
that mature dog, it would still chase a squirrel, fetch a stick and bark. You could not tell it was
raised by a family of gorillas. But if you had a six-week-old child raised to adulthood, man or
by a family of gorillas, and you adopted that adult, they would act identical to gorillas.
See, so we are the only ones that require education, schools and social groups to impart
just about everything we know and do and think about, where all the other animals don't do that.
You won't see a school for dogs or birds. You'll see a school of fish, but that's in a different
context. So this input that we are subject to, I find that many people are wrestling with the
concept of what is our purpose? Why are things this way? We really don't have to figure anything
out because it's all been figured out for us. But what I see going on is that someone complaining
about their, you know, in general, and what I hear in the mainstream alternative or wherever,
family, friends, let's say society, is what is, you know, where are we going? Where are we from?
What's the purpose? How are we going to fix this problem? And I just keep saying it's all
been answered before. But so that would be the metaphor of someone who's hungry and you lay,
this is where the food is, but I don't want it. It's better to complain, you see, because it's a
very tough decision to go back and look and see what has been set before us. And that led to the
other part where this is a matter of law. When I say law, it's not traffic law, criminal law,
or well, you know, or tax law. I'm talking about your law is, you know, what you eat, how you keep
time, what you wear, how you go into a contract, how you treat your people around you, how you
raise a family, all these things, you know, how you operate, that comes from your God.
And this is not my opinion. This is something that I've deduced by looking at as objectively
as possible. Now, this has nothing to do with the current religions in the world, because
they've actually gone away from law, you see, because now they've stepped in. So in that respect,
what I'm trying to do with Chuck is I say, I wouldn't be doing this alone. It's very important
that I have a sonic counterpart. And the only reason, again, I'll just state this, that I'm
speaking is because I've been looking at this for over a decade now, almost full time, as objectively
as possible. And I don't hear any of this being discussed at all. And it needs to be discussed.
So I do appreciate Chuck as well for being a sonic counterpart, because I do need that adult
supervision, you see. So these are the basic things that we're going to progress and discuss
as we have and as we will, hopefully, with Chuck on the Ocelli and the Greek show.
We are struggling, when I say we, the collective we, with things that have already been met,
you know, things that have already been satisfied. But you also have to understand the sign of the
times. You can't force these things on someone, right? But you have to say them. It's kind of,
you know, if you blow the horn, and if no one decides to listen, and something happens, well,
you know, if they don't take it seriously, at least you've done everything you could.
But it's better than being reserved and not saying anything. And then later on,
people find out and say, well, you knew these things, why didn't you say anything, you see?
So you have to be detached from the message. And honestly, I do wish there was someone else
saying this, because I am not a radio type person. And I like my anonymity. But I believe
we're in a time right now, and I say I believe because of time reckoning, that now is a window
of opportunity, and next year and the year after and the year after just a few more years,
where these things can be said and heard, because there's going to be a wind up, like I said,
a new axial period coming on, where there's going to be a very large concentration of thought and
focus on a certain part of the world that is going to bring forward this new type of culture that
people will be witnessing in the next decade or so. I contend that that year is 2018. And it's
my own delusion, and I stand by it. Okay, that's fine. But also, you know,
you've heard us probably discuss the Pope's work schedule, you can't keep time with the calendar.
That's not that is a work schedule for the Pope subjects. You know, it's funny, when we look at
documentaries, and they start mouthing off, you know, 200,000 years ago, 60 million years ago,
this, that and the other, well, how come it's not 60 million 2015. This is a work schedule. So we're
talking about a society that has lost their ability to even reckon time, whether one sees
that as being significant or insignificant is irrelevant. If we were to visit this planet and
go back and report about, let's say, the column that says about timekeeping, how they keep time,
we would easily say, the society on this planet has lost their ability to reckon time naturally.
And that would be a fact. Because they're all on the Pope's work schedule right now,
you know what I mean by January through December, Monday through Friday, all that.
Yes. And the way I answered that call is I will, I would like to give some confessions tonight,
if I may. And you're probably the only one I could confess to. So it'll just be me and you,
of course, on the radio tonight. There may be a few other people listening. But I sort of took the
path in New Zealand and in some ways in America of being what I would describe as a social recluse.
And what I mean by being a social recluse is there was a time in the life of Buck,
Buckminster Fuller, where he was literally so down with the society and the way it was going
in his 20s that he literally just unplugged himself from the society for literally two years
and became a social recluse and basically shifted into reading as much history, as much philosophy,
as much mind thought as he could. And then his brain sort of flipped and he came out of that time
with with sort of a different mindset. I'm viewing a world in which what I'm seeing shift more than
anything else is human communication. And I look at the technologies and I have never seen
mankind so distracted. It's it's it's just fascinating to watch being able to have an
exclusive dialogue and be able to talk to someone. The reason I say that I think 2018
is is going to be a tipping point or a shift point is simply because I'm watching the governments
of the world, which is basically a big show, all following the same script with a lot of
different language, but each country not looking at the other countries,
thinking that it's only happening to them when it's sort of happening to everybody.
And I always like to ask people, and I know it kind of sounds like a seminar when I say this,
but I often ask people, if you could do anything with your life and money wasn't the object,
so you had all the money that you wanted, right? So you could just, you know, spend all your time,
you know, in the trees writing a philosophy book. What would you do?
And then they share with me what they would do. And then my response is always, let's go do that.
So exactly. Yeah, it always what I'm doing. That's personally, I'll just share with the
audience and yourself as well. That's exactly what I'm doing. That is awesome. And and guess
what? That is why your work on the radio on American Freedom Radio is so profound.
And the reason that I will confess and openly admit that I've listened to the dummy load about
six times because it's, you know, watching watching stampedes of people try to get a vegetable,
you know, vegetable steamer or big screen TV. You know, I wanted to go pop some popcorn,
you know, and just watch the show. And I, I'm often reminded of something my son told me,
God bless him. He's 28 years old. He said, Dad, I thought that when I grew up to be an adult,
that, you know, I would be like, you know, drinking wine with other adults. And we would
be discussing philosophy. But he says, I grew up and I realized that everyone is basically a big
child. And there's been some event or something that's happened in their life. And they're like
stuck. Have you met people in your own life where they just they're stuck in a time or in a place or
a situation? And it's very it's very bizarre to watch. A much simpler example of this would be
going to the grocery store and watching people where they don't know if they need to pass you
on the right or on the left. So I think the work that you're doing on the air is is crucially
needed right now. Thank you. Well, the thing that we also discussed is setting oneself apart.
There's no need to really have the frustration if you realize, again, what we started off by saying,
it's sort of an insane asylum here. So why would you expect something different? But the part that
requires some remorse is as if you ran into someone who says, I have a Ferrari 355 with a
Rosetti engine, and I can't go over 40 miles per hour. And you find out that they they only pull
the lever to second gear. Well, actually, it'll do 40 in first, but you see what I mean? They have
everything they need, and they're just not utilizing. Now, why is because something we've
called cosmic censorship. The population of the earth has been very heavily censored,
because these things must take place. Just another thing I want to throw out,
since you brought up the internet and the communication and the distraction,
there's some talk about the shutdown of the internet and things like that, and that will
not happen. The reason why it will not happen was because the very emergence of the internet and
its growth and proliferation through handheld devices is one of the requirements in the future
that everyone on the planet is able to witness things in real time, meaning by sight and sound.
So as this technology progresses and becomes, quote unquote, cheaper and more available,
there could be an event anywhere in the world, and within 20 minutes, it could be up on YouTube,
and everyone can access it, let's say. That is the purpose of the internet. It's not really
for what people think. It's not really a technological marvel, as people would require
to explain it as such. So I just wanted to throw that out there, because as we get more used to
this, there's always going to be, again, the fear side. They're going to shut it down with laws and
things like that. It might be slightly limited, but it will be more prolific than it is today,
even in the future. When I look at events, I don't look at the actual event that's happening.
What I look at is three things. Who profits from it? What is the long-term strategy?
And what are they trying to get humanity to do? So I'm often reminded of an incident that
happened with the retailer Target. So they had 100 million customers that sort of had their debit
card numbers stolen, right? And they created this big fear porn storm of, oh, all your bank
account information has been stolen, so we're going to create these brand new cards, and it's
going to have a GPS device, so you will always know where it is, and we'll always know where it
is, and you will be very, very safe. And so what I see is that with each new technology, it creates
an illusion of more security, but it's really more about control. And the control that I see
people say is, well, I'm not really doing anything wrong. I think what's so amazing,
and I never thought I would witness it in my lifetime, is the lack of privacy. And for me,
where my studies have been as a researcher is a lot in mind control and a lot in predictive
programming, because I remember so many of the films that I saw as a teenager, like Colossus,
the Forbidden Project, which is a film about where the U.S. military decided they were going
to let computers sort of run our military, and then the computer decides that man is basically
in an insane asylum and is going to blow himself up, so the computer is going to have to lock
everything down. Then I fast forward to the 1990s, and I started looking at films like Enemy
of the State and looking at, again, a story where that story that was in Enemy of the State,
where everything is surveillance, we now live in that world. And so I don't know if people realize
we're there now. There is no Orwellian state. It's here.
Okay. Well, do you feel like you're surveilling yourself when you're looking in the mirror?
Yes. Yes, of course.
That's why you do it. Now, let's harken back to the black and white films from the 30s,
40s, and 50s or so, or prior to that, when you made a phone call, there was a switchboard
operator, and it was a row of women sitting in seats with wires, and they would patch you in.
And there was an old film, I think it was Paper Moon or something,
where a president called a town, and all the switchboard operators gathered around,
and they weren't doing their duty, and no phone calls were being patched in,
because the president called this one individual, they were all listening in.
So we've always been listened in. And like I said earlier, if your law comes from your deity,
the deity, the deific, or let's say the quote-unquote gods, they're always listening in.
So it's more important about what they hear than what another man hears in one aspect,
right? Whether you believe in this or not, a god would be a much higher social order.
On the other hand, if you look at the way the modern, this is just out of left field,
but still on the subject, this is a credit-based economy. And there's something called monetization.
And all they're doing is monetizing the surveillance. It's not about your privacy,
it's about monetizing your privacy. If you look at, for example, the majority of the NSA
information, the NSA is distributing the information. It's garnered from army intelligence
and other places like that. Fort Huachuca, people think it's NSA doing the listening,
but it's not. NSA distributes it to billionaires like Mr. Slim and places like that, people like
that. So one aspect, they have a client list. So this is all about monetization.
Like with the debit cards and credit cards, there's really nothing there. You know how
little children ask mommy, daddy, where do babies come from? You ever notice how adults never ask
where credit comes from? Correct. Well, I usually tell them the banks, what the banks do, honey,
is the banks create money out of debt. Actually, they don't. That's a joke that the attorneys have
played on people for plausible deniability. The attorneys are the go-betweens, the public and
those that hold these trusts. And there's a schizophrenia regarding that because they say,
how many times have you heard in all circles of discussion, well, they create money out of thin
air or that's your taxpayer dollars at work. But wait a second. If it's your taxpayer dollars at
work, there's another discussion that says that the taxes barely pay the interest on the debt.
So how could it pay for that? And if it's all debt and notes, how can you pay a debt with a debt?
And there's this massive schizophrenia, which is from what I call the cosmic censorship.
And this, like you mentioned, 2018 earlier, and that's very good in the fall or springtime around
that time, there's another cycle. And what that cycle will be is this period of tension that's
been on since what they call 2011 or so, 2010 is going to start to be throttled back. And there's
going to be a building up period again for this new society, which is people are not going to
really see it coming. But if you know it before it comes, then it's very clear. So I'm glad that
you're also saying it because it's actually very prudent and wise to look at that time period as
a focal point of certain things to change. But right now, it's still this cosmic censorship
is very heavy. And around that time, 2018, some of it will begin to be lifted. And what I mean by
that is where people will start to go back and say, Well, you know, how come if the universities
are so good, why are the children not being able to read? You know, not children, but you know,
graduates, right? If the doctors are so good, why are there over 4000 medical deaths in the
United States every day? Right? You know, people complain about, oh, look at you know, how many
people were killed here or there? I said, Well, it hasn't topped 3500. Today, the doctors are
killing every day. And you don't even you know, it's not even mentioned whether people are aware
of it or not. You know, it's kind of hypocritical. You know, it's sad when anyone loses their life,
but it's very hypocritical to read about a train wreck with 30 people dying. And yet, every day,
there's 1000s of people being destroyed by the medical associations. And then you have the
millions that are being locked up in cages by the legal society, right? Do you know, there hasn't
been one lawful court in the United States, it's been held for over 70 years. But you've got all
these people in prison. So this is part of the thing that people are going to look at and say,
what's going on here, we need to go find out a little bit more. So it's going to be a little,
it's going to be interesting. Well, it's interesting, because we're living in many ways
in I totally agree with you, by the way, about the censorship society, because one of the guests that
I had on my show early on was Pam Killeen. And she shared with the with me in the audience that
basically 50% of all pharmaceutical drugs manufactured in the world are taken in the
United States, 50%. And 80% of all antidepressant or SSRI drugs are taken by the American society.
So basically, what the average American may not realize, and again, I was watching this from New
Zealand, you know, I'm viewing our own country in the United States, is as we're all under
post traumatic stress syndrome, the entire country is. And it's Yeah, in terms of the
pharmaceuticals, it just means that they have the most expensive urine in the world.
Exactly, exactly. And we also have the richest drinking water in the world. Because if you can't
afford the pharmaceutical drugs, of course, you can get it in the drinking water. So
I know that may be too off topic, but it's, it's, it's so interesting,
you know, to to in the medical world to watch a system that God bless him saved my my father's
life in 1956, who had cancer. And the doctor who saved my dad's life was a pediatric surgeon.
And he told my dad, you know, first off, never let a doctor tell you you're going to die or give
you a death sentence. Number one, number two, you can be cured from this. And, and number three,
you just, you know, you just have to follow your own path. And my dad was 24. When when this
happened, and he lived all the way to the age of 72, and ended up having two kids and six grandkids.
The reason I share this with you is now it's like everything is flipped the very
medical system that saved my dad in 1956 would would probably kill him today.
So it's, it's a cosmic problem, which is difficult to discuss, because people are very
tangible. You know, if I told someone, you know, there's something called a smartphone
20 years ago, and you touch the screen and all this, you're like, well, it sounds great,
but show it to me, right? They want to see it. Right? Where if you discuss the cosmic reality,
that's been memorialized, you don't have to make this up. It says nothing to do with anyone's
belief. And it's not anyone's opinion. It's just what's been memorialized.
Over the ages, you'll see that it's really intangible. You know, in terms of direct
tangibility, it's all based on effect secondary effects. So this is this is going to be more in
the conscious of people's minds and the entitled classes like the attorneys, the doctors and the
scientists are going to start taking more of a backseat, like you said, they're going to realize
that the people that would offer cancer treatment today versus 50 years ago would find it to be much
more lethal today than 50 years ago. So this, there's no way that a population can can can
allow such a degradation to happen without them being censored. You know, in other words,
their perception being thwarted, to perceive it, it's not has nothing to do with their intelligence,
has to do with perception. That's the reason that's the reason I was sharing with you that I
think that you're part of this third group, which is the breakaway group. I'm reminded of Dr. Mark
Circus, who's a medical doctor who lived and worked in the United States and had to go to Brazil
in order to do baking soda and magnesium, magnesium therapy for cancer. And and also
realizing that people want to believe the systems that we're in, but those systems actually
don't work anymore. And the reason they don't work anymore, in my humble viewpoint, is that it's more
about maintaining the system than it is about solving anything. I think it's that as well as
just taking up time. It's what do you do with this time where the quote unquote dummy load is
put on society, you know, the definition of a dummy load is something you put on a system to
drain away all of its energy before it you know, it's actually put out in the field. So these
things are need to be discussed as we are. But at the moment, very few people can actually piece it
together and not only take the information for what it is objectively. But also, the purpose of
giving the information is to those that have the wisdom to be patient. You see, this is there's a
concept of like a frenetic sense where people find out a bit of news. Those that are say we're waking
up, you know, and they'll read something on the internet or hear something. And they feel like
they have to do something right away about it, right? And it doesn't work that way. Because it's
important to have the wisdom to see when it's the proper time and the proper place to do things. So
the thing about this waking up also I've been speaking about it's not the waking up that's
important. It's getting informed. Because if you if you roll over in bed at 3am, you're not awake.
You're moving. And if you're not informed, and you're, and you're awake. Actually, I used to
send out emails back in 10 years ago saying that telling people, don't say you're waking up because
it's going to enact a police state. More than 10 years, I'm sorry, like 12 years ago, because if
the those that are assessing the society say we have ignorant individuals, how do they know the
people are ignorant? Well, where did where did the people go to school? Their schools, the last
thing we want is an ignorant society that is awake, they need to be informed first. So there's an
aspect to what people are saying and thinking that is not congruent with, you know, be having
harmony. That's why you see some disharmony in the in the geopolitical and national scenes across the
world, because it's not just the US, you know, what you see going on in the states is also going
on in Brazil, it's going on in Europe, you see, it's a global thing right now. I watched in New
Zealand when they brought john key in as the prime minister, who is the head derivatives manager for
Merrill Lynch, in London and in New York, and watched him take the New Zealand debt from $5
billion to $80 billion. And basically, he was doing his job. So everything that's happening,
everyone's just sort of, you know, doing their job. And everyone is doing what they can,
they get into this, you know, the survival mode. My intention has always been to thrive when other
people were surviving. But yet at the end of the day, what a survival you see, because just being
alive, and being pain free and being above ground. To me, that's a good day. Okay, because food,
food, clothing, shelter, is survival, food, clothing, shelter, those three things like a
mantra, if anyone is ever questioning things like national debt, just tell yourself 10 times food,
clothing, shelter, food, clothing, shelter. And if you have a fair assessment of those things being
taken care of, you're doing excellently, not just well. So and I just want to go back to the debt,
you know, the the vice president here. So when he was asked about the debt, he says, Oh, that's good.
That's the national debt is good. It just it means that we have more money.
You see, and Wow, you ever heard that? No, that's, that's correct. Now the debt is hoisted upon the
media through through the media and society by the legal society. The national whenever you hear
national debt, you want to cover that in 30 seconds real quick. Sure, absolutely. We can go
anywhere that you want to go because no, no, no, I'm fine with that. Yes. The national debt is very
simple. Let's just use the car metaphor. Let's say you have a Ferrari and I borrow the Ferrari and I
and I park it here by the house and and people are saying, Wow, look, the Greeks got a new car,
but he looks real nervous. The reason I look real nervous is because is the Ferrari that I'm
from you an asset or a liability to me? It's a liability to me because it's not mine. It's yours
and I'm just using it. See, it's interesting. I got to interject one of the one of the awakenings
my wife and I had was when I did have a Jaguar and I was living in a 5000 square foot house.
I realized I didn't own anything. I was simply buying a lifestyle in that moment in time.
Somewhat, yes, but you're using it. Now, in this case, I don't want anything happening to the
Ferrari. So I insure it day by day for everything. That insurance is going to be very expensive,
especially when the when the underwriter asks me, Are you the owner? I'm gonna say no.
Well, you know, we're talking a premium that could be in the hundreds of, you know, per day.
Right. So it's very okay. So now what the national all the national debt is,
is credit on the books that the government has. Now the Federal Reserve does the books for the
government. And at the end of the day, at 2am, they look at all the excess credit,
the credit comes from your signature every time someone signs a piece of paper,
that is front end loaded with at least four to six zeros. So they collect all this,
you know what I mean? Government offices, hospitals, driver's licenses, checks,
right? Now, at the end of the day, they have, let's say, a surplus of several billion.
Does that belong to the government? No, it belongs to the people, right? Now,
they can't give it back to the people. Because if they do, it'll be like the Weimar Republic
in three weeks, you'll need a wheelbarrow of cash to get a loaf of bread or a bottle of wine.
Because it would mean if they would return the national debt, if they treated the national debt
properly, every man, woman and child, that is a citizen of the United States would get a check
up over $100,000. This month, the next month, it'll be 120. That the month after that be
probably about 150,000. Do you think anyone's going to go to work? No, they're not. Yeah,
okay. So what they're doing is they're holding this credit now, because it doesn't belong to
anyone within the trust or the government. It has to be insured. And that's what the public that's
why it's called a debt. It's not the actual amount, the amount, it's the amount of insurance
that's being held there. And no one owes anything to the Federal Reserve, you can call the Federal
Reserve Administrative Offices and ask them, does anyone any entity, corporate, government or
private owe you anything? They'll say, No, they're just a broker. You know, like stockbrokers,
whether it goes up or down, they get a they get a percentage of the transaction.
Absolutely, absolutely. And that's what the national debt is. So in a sense, is it a debt?
Yes, it's the government's debt. Don't they say it's the government's debt to who to you?
But they can't give it to you because it'll collapse the economy. Here's another example.
I think in Zimbabwe, they have a 1 billion note, don't they? Right? Yeah, there's an example. Could
you imagine if every man, woman and child in the United States of America received a check for
100,000 tomorrow or next week? Do you think what do you think a one note or five note will be worth?
No. Yeah, correct. Also, you're going to need you're gonna need 10 million notes at least,
you know, to buy a loaf of bread. Yeah. Well, there was a major shift in 2003, 2002, where everyone,
you know, the price of real estate, the value was going up so much that everybody was using
their house as a piggy bank. But then you had to sort of go back and pay the Pied Piper,
if you know what I mean. They can't prove that there's a debt, but the illegal society has to
keep that going because they also make a piece of it. See, I look at that. I look at the words
like, you know, in 2008, when they had, you know, the financial crisis with the bank,
and they created something called a tarp fund. It was like putting a tarp over the economy. I'm
always fascinated with the words that they create. It's it's by design. But you have to realize
there's no conspiracy of these super intelligent individuals that are crafting some evil plan.
If you end up ever meeting any of these, quote unquote, individuals that are supposed at the
top of the conspiracies, you're going to have to say, wait a second, there's something wrong here,
because this individual is just as common as everyone else. That's why I refer back. There
is a cosmic force that is in charge here. What I what I find so fascinating is that
if you study and I'm sure you do words and what words mean, I'm always fascinated with whatever
crisis or whatever issue is going on, that there's always a word for it, like calling,
keeping the stock market going, quantitative easing. You know what I'm saying? Which is really
just printing seventy five billion dollars every four weeks to just keep the Ponzi scheme going
so that the show can go on. Well, you see, what's happening is what people have missed
sight of is that there's no substance behind the money. So the money is actually generated
by the transaction. I understand. So and you're saying it's still not creating money out of
debt, so they're just not creating that. They're just creating it and it's just becoming more and
more and more than what it was. Correct. Well, ladies and gentlemen, hold that thought.
I'm Mitch Santel. You're listening to Remnants and Luminaries with our very special guest,
The Greek. Get out your yellow pads, because when we get into our two boy,
have I got some questions. We'll be right back.
Hi, I'm Mitch Santel. And if you're just joining us, you're listening to Remnants and Luminaries.
On American Freedom Radio with our very special guest,
The Greek, who's visiting us from another planet. Welcome back to the show.
Oh, OK. Thank you. But listen carefully. I'm just visiting here, taking notes.
Never said I was from another planet. Well, it just it's implied, though. I love the I love
the implications, though. Well, it's kind of interesting because your approach is very unique.
And I'll tell you why. Because from from for the years that I've been on radio, when I wasn't
producing other shows, I always invited my audience to get out a yellow pad and take copious
notes because they might hear something new, you know, that they hadn't heard before. And
yeah, visiting the visiting, taking notes is in essence being set apart.
Exactly. And when we before we when we went to break, you and I were having a bit of a dialogue.
I openly shared with you that in America, I don't really walk into any temple or church
because I always feel that religion was created by man, not God. And I don't really belong in there.
And you mentioned something about demons and things like that. And I didn't know.
Spiritual. Yeah. Do you remember in the first hour we discussed that
mankind is subject to external input and you get the law from your deity.
Now, it's interesting. And when someone says the word God, it's like the word army. If you say the
word army, do you think of just one soldier standing there or do you think of a multitude
with many rank and then there's many ranks within the system? I think of many. Yes. Yeah. The many.
And also there are ranks. You have the the grunt boots on the ground and then it goes all the way
up to the sergeant officers, generals, and then the emperor or the king or the president at the
top. Right. Right. That system you'll notice is paralleled through all societies for all time.
The ranking system. That's because man did not invent that.
So it is actually a mirror of another society that man defines to be intangible at the moment.
Now, here's the analogy with what you see in the world religions today. Not some of them,
but all of them. Let's say the West Coast of the US is going to be invaded by a foreign country
and it's going to be a boots on the ground infantry invasion. And you're living on the
West Coast of the US. Is the first of that army that you're going to encounter going to be the
general or the emperor? Or is it most likely going to be some enlisted guy that got in there because
he couldn't do anything else? Let's say. Right. It's going to be an enlisted guy. Enlisted guy.
Yeah. And what are the chances, even if you're occupied for one or two or five or 10 years,
what are the chances that the common person living on the West Coast is ever going to
meet a high ranking individual from that invading force?
This is exactly how the spiritual realm works with mankind at this time.
So all of the religions on the world bar none are based on these low level entities. Now,
it doesn't mean that the texts that they allegedly subscribe to are because there's not any religion
on the planet that knows or does anything that's in the texts that they allegedly subscribe to.
Because if you look at every major religion, it has a text that they say it's based on. And even
with a cursory examination of the text, you will see that that particular religion that professes
to follow that text doesn't absolutely nothing or knows anything in that text,
whether it's Christianity, Judaism, Islam, Buddha, all the ranks all the way down.
So this is this harkens back to the insane asylum aspect, right?
So what's interesting is when you look at all of the ancient texts,
you will see that they are all congruous in agreement with each other. But you know,
what's interesting when you look at the organized religions, they're not congruous,
which makes sense. For example, if you encounter two people and they both profess to have the
truth and their stories differ, well, only one of two things could be true. Either they're both
wrong, or only one is right. They both can't be right if their stories differ.
And this is exactly what you'll find in all of the ancient texts that all of the ancient
texts are congruent. There's a multitude of spiritual gods, there's a multitude of
entities that interact with humanity that are not of the higher ranks. There is a timeline
in all of the texts, whether it's the Mahabharata, the Rig Vedas, the Koran,
the biblical text, you see, but none of the religions seem to get along. So which makes
sense, because none of them are based on anything that they say they are.
Just like, for example, with the legal system, if you go to court, start saying in the American
Court of the US Constitution, the judge says, if you say that one more time, I'll throw you in
jail, or we don't use the Constitution in the courtroom. Or, you know, if you bring up a law,
it's not what it says. We don't use the law in this courtroom. Or if you go to a doctor,
and you mention, have you read all of the fine print on that drug you just prescribed? No,
I haven't, you know, it doesn't matter. See, so no one at this point, I say no one, I mean,
statistically, you know, 9.999% is actually going and referencing anything that what they're doing
is supposed to be based on. And this is... I wanted to ask you this. Do you think
that modern religion is a bit like modern medicine, where modern medicine doesn't actually
cure anything and only cures the symptom? Is religion that way, too?
Well, you know, let's not to nitpick, but the word religion just means something you do regularly,
like brushing your teeth, tying your shoelaces, and combing your hair, let's say.
And that goes back, the definition of the word religion goes back to what we were saying earlier,
that your input, your law comes from your deity. And when you have a law system, and I don't mean
legal, like traffic law, tax law, I mean, law would be what you eat, what you wear, how you keep time,
how you raise a family, how you go into a contract, how you deal with a neighbor. You see,
all these things are your law, you know? You've heard of like the laws of physics, right?
Right.
And thermodynamics, and you know, they tend to, within this quote-unquote sciences,
they have codified a series of laws to explain the natural world. Each and every man, woman,
and child on this planet, the way they interact with their natural world is based on their law,
and their law comes from their God. Now, what's interesting is I used to be confronted to debate
this, and it was very simple. Someone said, well, I'm an atheist, and I don't have a God. I said,
well, that's all right. Do you believe in the laws of the state? And they said, yes, I do. Well,
then the state is your God, and April 1st is your holiday. No debate necessary. You see?
That's great. That's great.
It's very simple. Yeah.
So, well, it reminds me of two famous Hollywood phrases. One is just because you're paranoid
doesn't mean they're not going to get you. And the second one is if you can't dazzle them with
brilliance, baffle them with bullshit. So at the end of the day, what I found in terms of a mass
consciousness, that for most people, if you simply tell them what they want to hear,
they'll go along with the program.
Yes, they do. And then there's another way to do it. Like, for example, again, with the debating,
you know, the right thing to do is hit and run for information. I don't like to debate,
for example, personally. I like to just impart information and leave. It's just like leaving
seeds, you know, like planting seeds. Some will take some. Some will be eaten by birds. Others
might grow a little, and then the weeds will overcome them, you see. But it doesn't mean
you don't cast seeds out to see if they grow. But then the psychology aspect, like you mentioned
about the people discussing or debating, like I brought up, is if someone adamantly wants to
debate me, I usually confront them and say, well, what is the purpose of the debate? And they're
like, well, to have a debate because I can win the debate. I said, well, if the purpose is for
you to win, I grant you the win right now. And they're like, you can't do that. You have to do
the debate first. And I'm like, you see, well, I'm granting you the win and just walk away.
Well, I can tell you the biggest shift that I found between the United States and New Zealand,
it was very cultural, you know, going from a big country with over 300 million down to a country
with only five million. I noticed that in America, we tend in terms of our society to want
to be right. And so what we do is in order for me to be right, I have to make you wrong, which we
use like a drug. And then when I went to New Zealand, it was very shocking and very refreshing.
It wasn't about being right to make you wrong. It was about doing the right thing. And I had never
experienced that before, really, to be honest. That's a refreshing change to see that. Yeah.
And then I learned a philosophy in New Zealand, which I still hold to this day in New Zealand.
They always say, why put off until today, which you can put off indefinitely. So,
you know, there is very much part of the Maori, the indigenous, you know,
people that lived in New Zealand before the British came in and decided to turn everything
into a colony. But yeah, it's that there's a I do believe there's a there's a natural rhythm
to things. And like there's been certain key events, like when we had the British petroleum
oil spill in 2010. And so they had to spray core exit like a core exit, you know,
into the water, millions of gallons. And then on March 11th, March 10th, 2011, they had Fukushima.
And so and I was living in New Zealand when Fukushima hit. And of course,
my youngest daughter was in school and they were letting the kids know that within 30 days,
it would be really appropriate for them to not eat any fish caught from the Pacific Ocean.
And I was just, you know, as a third generation native Californian living in Auckland, New Zealand
was fascinated with the fact that they were actually willing to tell the kids the truth.
You know what I'm saying? Just give them a little logic so they would understand what was going on,
where in America, it's sort of like Nestle is of the opinion that, you know, they should have the
rights to sell us a natural resource. I'm just fascinated by it. I really am. And I'm watching
America so much as a police state. And I'm noticing sort of a rise of what I call the pejorative
class, which was very popular in the Roman Empire, which was sort of this group of very privileged
people. You know what I'm saying? That would just sort of entitlement. Yeah, just sort of do the
work. You know, you just do the work of Caesar and you'll be fed. And my wife, God bless her,
had a chance to go down to Mexico City for about three and a half, four weeks.
And she had such a lovely time. And she said, honey, what I was most shocked about was sort
of like the people would stop each other on the street. They'd have real conversations.
It's a very poor country, but the people are very happy there. And then she came home and she was
like, you know, people in America have no idea how lucky we are, how much we have or, you know,
it's so easy here. And so it's like going into a Starbucks and the woman having an emotional
meltdown because they ran out of cream. You know, it's like, please, can we have some
logic at the end of the day as to what's important? Well, if you look at the initial history
objectively of this part of the world known as the States, North America, it was settled primarily
because of the cheap resources. Europe had been deforested. You know, when I say Europe at large,
you know, not the forests that were preserved, let's say, in the central part of the continent
there or that part of the world. There was a lot of cheap resources. Just for example,
when if you remember homes that were built in the 30s, 40s and 50s, there's no insulation,
meaning you had a heater and you just burn all the oil or that you wanted to keep the house cool
and uninsulated house here in America because energy was cheap. Right. So basically, the this
part of the world was settled because of cheap energy, whether it's, you know, the oil from the
ground, meaning up until World War Two, the United States of America supplied 98% of the world with
oil. It was very abundant and easy to get to the forests, the the what is it three to six feet of
topsoil in the Midwest to grow food. All of this was because of inexpensive resources. So when you
look at the culture of people, various cultures to come here and form another culture based on the
desire to come here because of cheap energy doesn't really give the fortitude of a strong
element in the in the culture itself, you see. Well, I find it's the biggest shift that I'm
noticing. And this is where a society really changes is the amount of millennials and young
people that have made a conscious decision to not have families and not have children.
And I've been very fascinated with that answer. It's a very, very simple answer for that. And it's
very heavy. And I'll share it if you like. I would love it. You may you may even share some of your
philosophy that you want to share in 2008. We're going to try to get you to say it on the air
tonight. Well, actually, it's not much of a philosophy because I really have it. There's not
you don't really have to think about it much. It's a matter of just seeing what information has been
held for thousands of years and reporting on it. So no one really has to do the work. It's kind of
like, you know, giving it out for free. But but the family being broken up is a cosmic reason.
And and this is why is because if you look at the majority of the quote unquote holidays
that people come together on. OK, this is across the world. They're actually based on cannibalism
and ancient rites of mysticism that were the destruction of children.
So the benevolent side of the cosmos, because remember, it was the malevolent side that
enticed men to perform these things. And I get into asking people what two cannibals, birthdays
and dolls have in common, because they're really from the same type of religious worship that's
been changed. So you have how many times have you noticed, for example, in America,
people traveling great distances during these, quote unquote, holidays?
Yeah. And yes. And also the the the trauma and the drama of getting to wherever they are,
to some place where they spend all their time traveling. And they're stressed when these
seasons come on. And they should be because they're based on rituals that go back pre ancient Canaan,
parts of Babylon, parts of Sumeria that are all based on human sacrifice. And they've been
disguised as various holidays. Now, when I say various holidays, just about all of them,
including the times when they're held. Now, this is a very strong statement to make.
But I assure you that the reason the family is being broken up is because if there's no family,
then there's no occult, let's say, almost satanic event to take place, you see.
So it's in reverse. Cosmically, there's a different type of logic where I've noticed from reading
ancient stuff, that double negatives work. Like an example, an example would be like,
if you're reading ancient texts, and you see something like death will be put to death.
What does that mean? Well, if death is an entity and death is put to death,
that means that there's no more death, right? So if there's no more death, there's only
life. Wow, that's like, that's like calling putting death to death, like real imitation
cheese. You know what I'm saying? Yeah, well, no, it's a little different. Well,
real imitation cheese would be that it's tangible versus intangible. And that's another thing
in this culture, meaning this Western cultures, people have accepted
synthetic food synthesized. I used to say that it's very rare to meet an American who's had
real cheese or real bread. Yeah, you see, that hasn't been processed, you know, where you can
go to other parts of the world. One of the commentaries I hear, even today, people that
travel abroad is the food is incredible. You can just go and get street vendor food. And it's just
wonderful. And yeah, so that happened to my wife in Mexico City. She said, Honey, the food here is
just like unbelievable. It's just like so fresh and so real. I'll tell you, I'll tell you a little
secret about our family. We started this tradition a long time ago. And you'll laugh. You know how we
just had Thanksgiving in the United States? We did our Thanksgiving dinner the week before
Thanksgiving. So on the week of Thanksgiving, everybody could stay in their robe, drink coffee
and not be in the traffic. And yeah, we told everyone the way we could show our love to them
was not to force them to get on a plane and go halfway across the country to go somewhere to eat
a piece of meat and a piece of cheese and be all stressed out. Yeah, well, when the people find out
that Thanksgiving has to be on what they call a Thor's day, it's to honor the god Thor and the way
honor the god Thor. I think it's blunt, I think was the name of the day is you have to slaughter
a winged creature. Wow. And when they discover that, I think they're not and there there was
no pilgrims and Indians doing whatever they say. Yeah, it's going to be quite interesting.
And right now, it's part of what we call the dummy load. So it's okay. You know, the purpose
of a dummy load is if you're building electrical circuit, and before you put it in the field,
you want to test it, you put a resistor or something that's just going to, you know,
get it to spin its wheel in place, it doesn't do anything. It's kind of like putting your car up on
jack stands and going inside, turning it on and hitting the accelerator pedal to the floor and
burning your entire gas, all the fuel in the tank, and you're not going anywhere, because
the wheels are not meeting the road, right? That's the dummy load.
You know what the dummy load reminds me of? The dummy load reminds me of someone seeing someone
fall down on the street. And instead of going up to that person and helping them up,
20 people get out their smartphone and start filming it. And you're like, well,
could one of you like go over and help that elderly man up because he kind of fell and he
needs some help? No, we want to put it on our on our smartphone. I want to put it on Facebook.
So and they're dummy loading the phone also. Yeah, it's very it's but see, once you understand
this, like, for example, if you had to get a quote unquote job to work in the public sewer,
would you show up to work naked and drink the water or would you wear a full on hazmat suit
with breathing tanks? I'd probably put a full suit on with breathing tanks. Yes, sir. Correct.
So, you know, you have to go do the job. So why don't you actually set yourself apart and protect
yourself appropriately? So living in this society is if you comprehend the times and you comprehend
what is going on, you set yourself apart from it. You see, how did they create a society?
I've always wanted to ask you this. You know, Edward Bernays was the nephew of Sigmund Freud.
And one of the things that he learned by watching his uncle
was, you know, this whole psychiatry, the whole therapy movement,
Edward Bernays watched his uncle treat patients. And then he wrote this book in 1928 called
Propaganda. And he realized through his own research and analysis that people could be
talked into buying stuff they don't need. And then that could become a whole industry. So,
of course, he was hired by the Palmel Cigarette Company to convince people that, you know,
that even medical doctors love Palmel cigarettes because they're, you know, they're really good
for you. So, yeah. And I think he also popularized eating bacon, I think, with eggs or something,
correct? He was hired by the dairy industry, correct? To show that that would be pork.
Yeah. Because it was rare that people had eaten pork at such extremes or things like that. Yeah.
It's very interesting how and the whole thing, when you hear the term psychologist, psychology
or anything with the PSY prefix. Right. That is the word for spirit. So they're actually
spiritualists. You could look up. That is the Greek prefix. In other languages, it would be
like in Hebrew, be ruach or Arabic, it would be ruach. That is the spirit. So whenever you see
the PSY prefix, that is the Greek prefix meaning spirit. So like psychologists, psychopaths,
a psychiatry is a spiritualist. Yeah. It's very interesting where whenever you see the P-N-E-A-U,
like pneumatic, pneumonia. Right. That is the breath or air or the soul. Wow.
So that's why it's very difficult to have a conversation regarding the spirit, the soul
and the mind of man, because these terms have yet to be defined. And it's very easy to define them,
but just by looking them up, they're either a click away or a reference away. So this is also
what's coming when you ask me about the philosophy of 2018, there's going to be more of a grounding
in what things really mean. Again, going back a while back, I was in what they call a grocery
store, a large one, and a woman was giving out samples of cheese saying this cheese is made with
real milk. And I was saying it was taken aback. I was like, isn't cheese supposed to be made with
milk? I understand. I have a very dear friend. His name is Ricky Ray, and he's a really incredible
musician and a researcher. And he often talks about the cloning off of mankind. And when he
talks about the cloning off of mankind, he talks about television, which, of course, I call tell
vision, and the whole process of the programming that's going on. Now, I'll tell you a dirty little
secret that happened when I came back to the United States, because we don't have cable
television in our house, although we do watch movies. So what I found was I actually had to
find, you're going to laugh at this one, one or two really popular American television shows,
not because I had to sit there and watch all the episodes, although I will admit to being
addicted to one of them. I actually had to watch these shows so that I would be able to
converse with the cloned off humans, because I couldn't really sit there and talk about normalcy
bias and cognitive dissonance and the Hill Gillian dialectic. And they would sort of look at me like
I needed to go see a therapist. But if I could tell them who did what to whom on scandal last
Thursday night on ABC television, then all of a sudden I was their buddy. So I don't know what
your take is on that. It's sort of the cosmic censorship again, because no, you cannot imagine
a rational individual looking at the information and levels of magnitude, like what you've discussed
might have been more important than what they saw on TV, but they can't hear what you've discussed
because their perception has been blocked. Wow. And would you say the perception is being
blocked by the chemicals in the food, by the spraying in the atmosphere, by the just the toxic
environment that we're in? Or no, it's none of that. That is secondary because you have to realize
the spiritual realm manifests physically by using physical things. You see?
I will tell you, I got to tell you something that's really interesting. My wife and I were
listening to a late night show one night on the radio, and my wife within like five minutes said,
honey, you have to turn this off. I can't listen to it. And she couldn't listen to it because it was
some new age cycle babble spiritual thing that just did not resonate with her, if you know what
I'm saying. Oh, it's about mostly anything spiritual discussed in public, but go ahead.
Yeah. So it's about labeling things. You know what I'm saying? It's sort of like,
if all of a sudden I came up to you on the street and I invited you to have a cup of coffee and we
sat down and we had a conversation, and I started going down a train of thought of who you were in
a past life and who do we, you know, it's like, who are we? You know, I have to interject whenever
you hear past life, it's bunk. There is no such thing. And that's what I've always believed that,
by the way. I don't believe that. I've never believed in that. And because it's been it's
not qualified or quantified anywhere. It's been made up. It's been it's come out of without giving
a history or giving a credence. It's come out of poor, poor versions of translated documents
and then just people wanting to be opportunists, you see, and capitalizing on it as gurus,
teachers and what do you call them? What other word are they? You know, I see.
So now I will tell you the key to happiness, if you'd like to know that, because I have a very
simple answer on that one. And you may or may not be like minded with my answer. Are you ready?
Happiness, being happy in your life, I discovered is just a decision that you make.
If you decide you're going to be happy. You're happy if you decide you're going to be miserable
and no matter what happens to you, you're going to be miserable. You're going to be miserable
to some degree. Yes. And again, that's a basis. It has to have a basis in the law that you follow,
you know, your program. But in that case, it's perception. You know, I'll give an example here
in the southwest. It's known as a snowbird town when the rest of the states are buried in snow.
People come here for the 70 degree Fahrenheit weather. Right. And I was in line once at a
hardware store and the cashier needed to change the tape. And I was there was a lady in front of
me and said, you know, I'm from Ohio and thinking of moving here. How is it here? You know, how are
the people here? And I turned around and asked her, well, how are the people in Ohio? And she says,
well, they're like this or like that and like this and like that. And I said, what's exactly
how the people are here? Wow. You get it? Yes. Because how she sees the rights, how she sees
them. Right. You see, it's it's it hasn't. Yeah. That's why I always contend that perception is
reality, you see. And so if someone has a certain perception, if they see that perception as the
reality, guess what? It is the reality. Well, it's it's actually how they adjust to what they perceive
as being reality. Again, it's a series of adjustments and navigations. You see, when an
airplane flies from, let's say, from London to New York, it doesn't fly in a straight line like
they show you on Google Maps. Let's say it actually makes adjustments based on jet stream,
weather, altitude and other planes. Sure. And and people might tell you a little bit about themselves
or how you might perceive someone. But everyone is constantly making adjustments based on all
the previous input that they've got. The thing that I'm that I'm fascinated by is is how someone
will get sort of stuck in one mindset and they're unable to change. In other words,
if I've researched something or I've read something and maybe I've had a mindset,
let's say, for eight years, you know what I'm saying, that on this particular topic,
this is just the way it is. If there's a new piece of information that's discovered,
I'm willing to do a 180. I'm willing to go in a totally different direction. And yet I see so
many people who get stuck in a mindset and it's almost like I can't talk to them after a while.
Well, yes, the thing is, because they tend to lack an operating system. You see, when you
buy a new computer, use that as a metaphor and you plug it in, it just blinks at you.
You can't download files or programs. You have to download the operating system first.
Right. And then and then the program and then the files. The operating system, again,
comes from your deity, you know, who you see as your highest authority. And another example of
that is when children are in their formative years, you know, up until, let's say, eight years old,
they view their parents as their deity. They have no concept of a higher authority in the cosmos
unless they, you know, some might at a younger age than others. So that's why, for example,
you have the quote unquote rebellious teenagers is because the they've realized by the time they
passed those formative years and they're in their adolescent years that their deity had lied to
them. And if your deity had lied to you, where else can you go to? The highest authority has
deceived you. And what would that deception be? Tooth Fairy, Easter Bunny, Santa Claus, you see
these these might sound very mild and trivial, but they do embed themselves within the psyche
of the individual. How many times have you heard of a child reach a certain age and the parents
will turn around and say there's no such thing as Santa Claus? Right. Well, they never apologized
for that. You see, and then they carry that over and or something like the tooth fairy.
See, that's for little babies. You're not a little baby anymore. But they never apologize
for lying to the child. Right. Now, my parents did the opposite. One night I'm my mom was making
dinner and there was some news story about all these new Santa Clauses. And I turned to my mom
and I was like a 12 year old boy. And I said, Mom, this Santa thing, it's it's kind of consumerism,
is it? I mean, it's it's not really a real thing. And then my mom said kind of like, well, what do
you think it is? And and I said, I don't know. And then my mom said, you might be on to something.
Let's go look it up. So it's like, do you want to disclose that real quick? The Santa
Clause? It's very easy. In the ancient Canaanite culture, in the ancient Sumer culture, they had
an entity called Moloch. And the way Moloch was typically in the public square. So you would have
like a mall area out outside or in open air. And at the end of the corridor, there would be a larger
than life bronze statue in a seated position. And they would they would either be a furnace
underneath it or in its belly. So at a large belly, and it would be stoked until it was the entire
bronze larger than life statue was glowing red hot. And the people were told that the way you
would get prosperity is by offering a young child to Moloch. And if you didn't want to offer your
young child, there's a store here that has little children in cages because people would sell
children if they were too poor. And they would go buy a child or use their own child and they
would place it in the lap of a red hot, you know, 2000 degree bronze or 1500 degree bronze statue
and sear the child alive. And it was to make a wish of prosperity. And because this was in a
commercial square, it's very difficult to talk to or to speak to someone to do business. So they
would ring bells to drown out the screams of the child. So now you today you have a bright red,
larger than life individual that the child is placed in his lap. And there are also bells
involved, jingle bells. So there's your history of Santa Claus. Isn't that wonderful? Oh, that's
such a wonderful thing. I will tell you openly one of the most controversial books in New Zealand
and New Zealand when I lived there was the history of cannibalism in New Zealand. And one of the
things that came out in the book is that can cannibalism was still very popular about 50
years ago in New Zealand. So, yes, it still is. It's just not it's underground. But the people
are doing parodies. There's a fascination with it. And the word cannibalism comes from the ancient
word Kahan, meaning priest and Ball, meaning the Lord. So cannibalism literally means priest of the
Lord. And if that doesn't put a twist on things, there is a weird anomaly that's going on, which is
and I've always wanted to ask you this. And that was they really pushed ahead in the United States
and globally sort of the whole homosexual agenda, normalizing it and legalizing it. And then as
the ink on the homosexual agenda was barely dry, then the pendulum sort of shifted into something
called transgenderism. And then all of a sudden they were telling small children that you you
have a right before the age of 10 to let us know which sex you identify with. And if you were a boy
and you feel that you really identify as being a girl, we will help you with that. So it seems that
with each agenda that gets pushed, I don't know if I'm making sense with what I'm saying. It is.
And it's it's it's been going on for a very long time, not only with the media and the legal.
When you said it's accelerating, it's accelerating. Yes. And it will. But it will not. You see,
let's look. You want to look at it. And one aspect is you said the before the ink was dry,
that would imply there was a legal society, the quote unquote, what they call the justice aspect
of society approving it. Right. OK. Now, you also have to look at the scientific and medical
society and political and religious society also pushing it because it's part of the goddess
religion that the planet has been under for a long time. And you hear a lot about, well,
we need to go back to being matriarchal instead of patriarchal. But they forget
that the earth has been under a goddess religion whose priests are male, by the way,
for a very long time. That's why when you see the word justice or justicia, it is a revival of D.K.
D.I.K.E., which is the Greek and Mott and all that is a goddess religion.
One of the ancient teachings of the goddess religion is that man was in a godlike state
at one point. And the way that man goes back to a godlike state is by having male with male union
and the males become sterile and female with female union and the females retain their
fertility and they procreate offspring that are asexual or hermaphroditic. This is a very
ancient mystical teaching. And this is an agenda that started in the 50s with test tube babies.
Do you remember growing up hearing about that in the 70s? Yes, I remember that.
It's all about creating, getting men back to a godlike state, which is a false premise,
by the way. Now, that's on one hand. On the other hand, they're doing this in the name of rights,
right? We want our rights. Have you heard that? Right. Yeah, I've heard that. In fact,
I contend that the biggest challenge that humanity has right now is do we as human beings even have
the right to our own body? Because for me, I have not had a vaccine in 30 years and I refused to
take a mandatory vaccine. There's never been a study, by the way, a random placebo or any kind
of standard medical study that could hold water on vaccines. It is also another ancient ritual.
Anything injected under the skin, even if it's water or saline solution, the body views it as
a toxin, as an invasion. So it's kind of asinine. But I just wanted to mention something about the
rights aspect. Do you remember before the women's rights movement in the 50s and 60s or let's say
60s and 70s? Let's say the father of the house was able to work a menial job and have the house and
send the children to college and the woman didn't have to work. But after the women's rights movement,
now the family is diminished and no one, the level of creature comforts has gone down.
And now both the man and the woman, the mother and the father, have to work. Have you noticed how
the rights movement did not actually offer a better life for the people involved?
Absolutely not. It just offered the illusion of a better life.
Yes. Now, this is a forewarning to the rights that are being asked for the quote unquote
people that are quote unquote homosexual in the future will backfire as well.
Mm hmm. So we're to the wise caution. This has nothing to do with people's desire
for who they desire. There is a massive agenda which is cosmic here. These are very heavy topics
we're discussing here, Mitch. So I know that's why I wanted you on the show, because I appreciate
having an authentic dialogue rather than discussing which laundry detergent I need to go
by on Tuesday of next week, because and again, I'm speaking these things because no one else is.
And I believe that there is somewhat of an audience out there that is willing to hearken
to what's being said. I think what's really interesting is there is a much larger audience
that you realize that that that wants to know this, believe it or not, because I think there's
a growing group of people and I don't know which country or what age group or what religion or what
color that just looks around them. And like you said, they feel like they're living in an asylum
and they look at the lives of the people around them that are so busy and so, you know,
there's no downtime. You know, it's like when I was 20 years old and I got to go to New York City,
I'm so excited because the whole city was like they drank about eight pots of coffee and everybody was
buzzed on caffeine out of their mind and running around. And then and then when the smartphones
came out and with the five hundred channels of nothing on television, it's like now we're in
a society that that never that never sleeps. So it's it's watching the shift.
Well, people also people of wealth a hundred and some odd years ago were people of pleasure.
Now, people of wealth have no time whatsoever. So what good is it serving them? You see,
I have met more people, I must tell you, who have substantial sums of wealth
and are miserable. They're miserable. And you because they have no leisure.
Wow. Relaxation where years ago you saw the wealthy class were people of leisure, right?
Wow. To a certain degree. Now, in terms of the television, you know, Philo Farnsworth,
the quote unquote inventor of the electronic or the electric television, when he was asked
why did he invent the electric television is because he said it would it would lead to a
fully literate society and no more war. And when he had lost all the patent wars and was pretty
much rendered into poverty, he did never watch television in the latter years of his life and
also banned people, family members from watching it. So can you imagine the magnitude of such a
disappointment? Wow. Yeah. And the interesting thing, too, is I know for a fact that the
television we have in America was originally developed in Germany. And during the Olympics
in the 1930s, I've seen videos in the 1930s of the Olympics that that look is clear,
if not clearer than old. I love Lucy shows. So the color. I think it was Westinghouse that gave
the National Socialist Party a camera that was about eight feet long, six feet tall, took three
people to operate. And two years later, they returned another camera that did the same thing
that was the size of a shoebox back to the Americans. Wow. So do you feel that a lot of
the technology that is being used with the public now was actually around a long time ago and is
absolutely. And it's being reintroduced into the public mindset. Correct. Absolutely. Like
there's Charles Ford. Have you heard of Charles Ford? Forty and times he early 19 early 20th
century, he would document paranormal events and he had gotten it from, let's say, the police in
London and notable citizens, you know, let's say not people trying to make up a story. And they
asked him, well, you know, the ancient Greeks had the hero's engine, the steam engine 2200 years
ago. Well, why do we rely on Fulton's engine now? Like people think it's a new invention. This is
he said, well, now it's steam engine time. You see, the ancient Greeks had the steam turbine,
which is more advanced than the piston driven modern steam engine. It's called hero's engine.
It was more it would be more like to a jet motor turbine. But it was not until Fulton until it was
brought back because it was steam engine time. See, right now it is mass media time on the planet.
And this is also noted in your ancient texts. If we fast forward to where we are in 2015,
I contend that the majority of the UFO sightings and I saw UFOs when I was in New Zealand is
basically technology that might be 100 years ahead of what the average human is allowed to see.
And 400 years ago, 1903, JJ Thompson wrote that when you feel mass or weight, it is not in the
weight is not in the mass itself. It's electrical lines of force that connect to it.
So if you know how to neutralize those electrical lines of force, everything
can you can render anything weightless or get it to stop instantly or start instantly. And this was
in 1903. And this went underground. And JJ Thompson lived another 35 years after that and never wrote
a thing. I wonder why. Wow. So yeah, and Tesla also had benchtop working devices of this nature.
So what I mean by electrical lines of force, you know, when you if you place a five pound
brick on a scale, you'll notice that it moves to five pounds on the scale and you think it's
the mass in the brick, it's actually lines of force attaching itself moving it. That's why
if you drop the brick from a two story building, it'll register 300 pounds on the scale, it's the
same brick. More and more lines of force attaching. So this technology was around 100 years ago. So I
think there, when we say 100 years in the future, it's really from 100 years ago in the past, let's
say. Why is technology always suppressed? And why is everything now become a conspiracy in 2015?
It's like, well, it's Yeah, it's not steam engine time. And also a lot of these conspiracies are
drawn up by nerds that are afraid of you. So once you go for the conspiracy, they've done their job.
Wow, interesting. Interesting. Well, I think sometimes it's not a conspiracy. I think sometimes
it's simply critical thinking, another point of view, another way of looking at something
that may not be part of the mass consciousness. So if the mass consciousness is censored,
why would you want to be a part of it? Correct. That's why I think that that you and maybe me
are part of this third walkaway group. You know, I mean, perhaps, but it's also not to walk away,
but to be in it, but but be set apart from it. There's an old saying that says be in it,
but don't be of it. Oh, yeah, to be of a culture of a society, but to correct.
One of the things that I had to learn and took me a very long time was to let go of the fear piece
to realize that the fear is also a manufactured event. And they have to manufacture these fear
events to feed the system. So but that's what you the only place you see the fear is in the mirror.
If I don't see it in the mirror, then it doesn't affect you. It's see fear. All of these terms
have been twisted because they could be used to our advantage. Like you can love someone so much
that you have fear that something bad would happen to them. Right. Like if you have a newborn child,
you fear for them because you mind them every minute of the day because you love them so much.
Right. Another word that's been hijacked is judgment. Don't be judgmental. I'm extremely
judgmental, especially when I'm behind the wheel of a car and I stop at a four way intersection.
I look twice. That requires judgment, because if you abandon just judgment behind the wheel of a
motorized wagon, you probably won't make it home that day. Certain things you know,
even are you walking on a slippery surface or are you firm footed requires judgment.
Yeah, exactly. I also will contend that there's a there's a lack in the society now
of simple discernment. And absolutely, that's the the nature of all information.
What why have we why is humanity lost? This discernment drives me. I hate to say cosmic
crazy cosmic cosmic censorship. Okay. Now, what causes what causes the cosmic censorship? That's
what I want to know. What started twenty five hundred years ago when prior to twenty five
hundred years ago, the predominant cultures and all the people on the planet were quite aware of
of the other side, the spiritual realm, quote unquote, the gods around twenty five hundred
years ago. It coincides with, let's say, in the biblical text where the diaspora, where Israel
was banished to Babylon. It also coincides with a lot of major movements that happened to other
places of the world where all of this knowledge that went back to the days of, quote unquote,
flood. Even you'll find the flood in mythology and every culture up until twenty five hundred
years ago. All knowledge before that for mankind was pretty much known and easy to access.
Library of Alexandria. You've heard of that, right? Right. Okay. All of these things around
twenty five hundred years ago, there was a massive axial period that lasted about a hundred years
where mankind was essentially cut off from all knowledge before him. And coincidentally,
that's when all of the religions that have survived till today also started.
People think that Christianity started with, quote unquote, the biblical Christ, but it actually
started around that time period also. So this is a very interesting dummy load that has been put on
just because mankind needs a curing period. In other words, there was twenty five hundred years
to go and we just needed filler time. You know, it's kind of like think of the past twenty five
hundred years is like waiting in an office, people sitting around and they're flipping
through magazines. Right. It's kind of a tall statement, but I. I happen to agree with that
statement. I totally agree with that statement. You're in a waiting room for twenty five hundred
years. I I feel so blessed to be alive during this time. This time just feels like so exciting
that that the more I ask why and the more I go down the rabbit hole, the more I realize that
that everything is something else. And yeah, yeah. And what's interesting in the next decade or so,
you're going to see the concept of the superhuman, not not the what is it called now where they're
trying to integrate man and machine. Ray Kurzweil is so addicted into this, you know, and they're
showing it in movies like Transcendence or they're showing mind control in the Adjustment Bureau
with Matt Damon. So they're showing that, you know what I'm saying? These. Yes. Scenarios,
Siri, you know, Apple, Siri, where you ask it a question, which the word Siri backward is Iris.
So it's, you know, there's the it's an interesting mind control machine. It really is.
But it is mind. Remember, mind and spirit mean the same. And the spirit guides the body.
Now, what you will see in the future is a lot of the things that were reserved for mythology
and ancient folklore is going to manifest in the physical realm. And it'll be it won't be amazing.
It'll just happen gradually enough, even though it'll happen quickly. And that will be part of
the society in the next decade. What I mean by is the middle 2020s. Wow. And what's good. I'm saying
these things now is because not because anyone needs to do anything about it. There's nothing
you can. It's because hopefully what I'm saying is memorialized and just file it away for later.
And when you when these things do happen, there are many other things that will coincide that
could probably discuss in public in the future, but not now. Well, it's interesting because I think
that that karma, consciousness, humanity, whatever you want to label it. Dr. David Hawkins, who
originally lived in Sedona, Arizona, wrote a magnificent book called Power Versus Force.
I don't know if you ever had an opportunity to read that book. No, actually, it would be a book
that you would really love, because in the book he openly talks about the different vibrations of
of words and what words mean and the vibration of those words. So he often describes the U.S. military
at being at at a vibration of pride, which is 175. But if you go up to the Magna Carta now, that's
600. But then if you go to the U.S. Constitution, now you're at 950. And if you go up to the Bible,
it's a thousand. So you might find that book really fascinating. The other the other book
that I constantly go back to is is a book called The 48 Laws of Power by Robert Green, where he
takes a particular law and then he connects it to a piece of history because it just it's like
with each generation, they tell us it's the end time. And I don't think it's the end time. I just
think it's the next chapter. Correct. Well, listen, young man, it was awesome having you on the show.
Thank you for being a part of it. You're welcome. Thank you for having me. Fantastic. I'm Mitch
Santel. I'll be with you next Saturday night. You've been listening to Remnants and Luminaries
and I'll be back next week. God bless. Bye bye now.