As soon as you're born, they make you feel small.
By giving you no time instead of it all.
Till the pain is so big you feel nothing at all.
A working class hero is something to be.
And welcome to American Freedom Radio.
You're with Sam Tostinacci.
And it's a nice cold, cold Sunday morning, the 10th of June here in Melbourne.
8am, and very nice to be with you folks.
Thanks for tuning in.
Today I have, as promised, I have the Greek special guest today.
And the Greek has called in many times in the past with great comments.
And I thought, well, I've got to have him on.
So without further ado, are you there?
Yes, I'm here, Santos. Thanks for having me.
Yeah, thanks.
Now, I've enjoyed your comments in the past too, by the way.
We've had some great comments and we've had quite a few chats over Skype, have we not?
Absolutely, yes.
Yeah, yeah.
Now, today we're just going to be talking about miscellaneous subjects
because, first of all, what we need to do is introduce yourself, the Greek, to the audience.
Can we do that and tell people what you do?
Because I find it fascinating what you do with weather.
Can we share that with folks?
Yeah, yeah, it's possible as well, yes.
In short, the only thing I really like to tell people is my perspective
and what I try to achieve or do here on this planet.
And the simplest way to say it is explaining my approach.
And my approach is that I'm just visiting here taking notes.
I'm on an adventure.
And the reason I say that is because the many years that I've been here,
looking at all of the systems in place, the way people think, what they worship,
what they believe in, what they think is real is actually an engineered reality.
And all of their beliefs, all of their sciences are completely debased.
There is no basis.
There is no foundation or substance behind pretty much any system that I see on the planet today.
And it's very easy to speak on the money system, how it's just based on nothing.
If you look at science, it's based on observation of effects, not causes.
You look at the medical system, the same.
Mathematics, the same.
So with that, I've found out there is nothing to learn here.
It's just we have to come here to taste this.
So we have the taste of what it's like to have an existence like this
and have a great adventure at the same time.
Wow.
Beautiful.
Well said.
Very enjoyable to have heard that.
Thank you.
Yeah, so true.
Well, Plato, one of your countrymen, said many, many years ago
that we are here to experience anamnesis, the remembering.
Yes, and I can comment on where we're going to be remembering things we should be forgetting
because apparently if you look at all of the ancient scriptures,
there will be no memory of this when we go to the next cycle where we're going to be doing.
Right now we're in the cycle of experiencing and tasting what it's like.
Let's say one can say how not to do it, but you will not remember much as this is passed through.
As you can see, all the misery that's going on in the world has seemingly been perpetual,
and this will all end, and we have actually a tremendous, very optimistic,
and very, very, very bright future ahead.
With that said, you mentioned touching on a lot of miscellaneous subjects,
and if we can do that, I'd just like to cover maybe a quick, broad base of beliefs
that are taken as truths in science, society, religion, and things like that.
Yeah, great place to start.
I love this sort of stuff.
It's certainly interesting, and it shatters people's paradigms.
I did a presentation last night, and a couple of people walked out
because I touched on the body and how it's made,
and how it is the temple of God, etc., the temple of Solomon,
and I'm afraid I lost a couple in the audience.
I always do, every presentation I do.
I don't know what people expect when they come to see my presentations,
but there's always one or two that walks out,
and they make sure they walk out early in the piece,
so they let me know that they're not happy with the information.
But anyway, 99% of the folks were very happy, so shoot away, please.
Yeah, that's interesting, and there's many levels to that as well, of course,
them walking out.
But yeah, in terms of the, when I say debased,
whenever something is presented as truth in this material realm,
we have to have some substance or basis behind it,
and if it's a body of knowledge that's being interpreted or spoken of
or believed in even, one must adhere to some form of study
or revealing what they're subscribing to.
So, for example, what I've studied, if we start off with the,
let's go with the lighter side, physically, which would be the spiritual side,
let's say, the religious, I've looked at all of the sacred texts,
for lack of a better term, and scriptures of all the religions in the world,
what they call the Bible, the Bhagavad Gita, Mahabharata, the Koran,
and I've looked at them very, not carefully, the Bible I've looked at the closest,
but just read them.
After many years, I came to the conclusion that none of the followers
of the so-called religions that are supposed to be subscribing to these texts
are adhering to anything in those texts, whether it's Hindu,
whether it's Muslim, whether it's Christian, whether it's Jewish.
Now, there are doing it, let's say, in color,
or they'll take a few aspects of it that resemble,
that is, come from this particular body of work, let's say.
But when you actually look at the substance, there's nothing behind it.
Quick example, if you go backwards, let's say the Hindus,
they say, don't eat meat.
Well, their text says that if Brahma appears to you,
you are to slaughter a calf and serve it with curds.
Yeah, so, and then if you approach a Hindu,
it says, well, we don't go by the Mahabharata, the Bhagavad Gita,
we go by tradition, you see, so that's, you know, okay.
So if you approach a Muslim, for example, and you say,
well, right here in one of the Suryas, it says that a Muslim,
which just means believer, will do and does acknowledge
that the law was given from the Most High to Moses,
and will do what Moses says.
Well, the first five books of Moses, the Pentateuch and the Bible, let's say,
have a very specific list of days, let's say what they call holidays,
and there's not one Muslim that does that when their own book says
that they should follow everything that Moses said to do.
And then if you go to the Jews, well, that's, you know,
a lot of people, again, are saying, well, that's Israel.
Well, no, not necessarily.
The Jewish religion is a religion that is fairly new.
It's, let's say, less than 2,000 years old, or just a little bit over.
And if you look at the practices, the way they keep time,
and the things they do, again, do not adhere to the Bible.
And last but not least, the Christians, I have not found anything they do at all
that subscribes to anything in the Bible whatsoever.
Again, just groups of names and characters lifted and cut and pasted.
So this might offend people.
Second, why is this guy, am I saying this as a criticism,
as something that I know, something that I found out by doing some research?
And again, all these statements that I just made are by examining the texts
that these religions allegedly subscribe to, and looking at, let's say,
the ordinances, the codes, the commandments, the rules, and the stories
that are in these texts, and then looking at the corresponding religions
which are supposed to be adhering to them.
And I find there is no religion on the planet today that adheres to anything.
So that's one example of how it is debased.
So if you ask anyone that is religious in any religion,
what are you basing it on, and they go back to any of these texts,
they'll be actually dumbfounded if they actually studied the text,
because they're not going to what the text says.
They're relying on someone's interpretation.
Yeah.
Yeah, they're written very plainly, actually, all of them.
Yeah, I remember when I stopped going to the Jehovah's Witness meetings,
I was accosted by some brothers, and they were trying to encourage me
to go back to the meetings and back to Jehovah.
And they quoted the scripture where the Apostle Paul says,
Do not forsake the gathering of you.
And they said, You are actually, you know, breaking Jehovah's wish
that he wants all of us to be gathering regularly at the meetings,
and you're not there, Brother Santos.
And I said, Yeah, well, there's another scripture where the Apostle Peter says,
Greet each other with a kiss.
And are you doing that, literally?
Yeah.
Yeah, that would mean that I don't remember in the 20-odd years
that I was a Jehovah's Witness, I don't remember a brother kissing another brother
when they greet each other.
I mean, that is a no-no.
You know, they don't even touch each other.
There's no touchy-touchy, because they consider that to be all that's very worldly,
that's fleshly stuff.
You don't touch the brothers and hug them.
Excuse me.
Right.
So it's very, very cold.
You know, it's an atmosphere so cold, and yet the scriptures say,
Greet your brothers with a kiss, a holy kiss.
None of that's going on in church.
Yeah, that's the emotional armoring.
Each society has its type of emotional armoring.
I mean, if you go to England, the bus driver will kiss you, you know.
So it depends on the society, right?
Yeah.
But then again, you know, if you look within these texts themselves,
you will always see that it is given.
In other words, there is a group called the elect.
You cannot elect yourself.
You're elected by someone else.
All of the texts say that the truth is hidden in plain sight.
And without going down a rabbit hole, there are characters in Scripture
that we are warned by the Scriptures to basically avoid or look at very carefully
because of their sly and cunning ways of operating that seem good and actually are not.
And without catching flack, there are several characters in Scripture
that are shown as being, let's say, malevolent, right?
The one shows up in Genesis at the tree, right?
And the other one shows up at the end of the New Testament,
who actually wrote most of the New Testament, and they call him apostle Paul,
who was neither an apostle, because to be an apostle,
you have to be in the presence under the tutelage of the master, number one.
Number two, I'd say most of what Paul is saying is in direct contradiction
to the ultimatums and the things that the Christ had said.
So you have a little bit of everything there,
and it's just like when you think you have a choice, you don't have a choice.
And there's no mystery to why most of, or if not all, of Christendom isn't based around Pauline doctrine,
where if you actually study what the Christ had said, for example,
the Pharisees will not enter the kingdom, Paul says, I'm a Pharisee.
Christ said, follow me, Paul says, follow me.
Christ says the law has never been done away with, Paul says the law has.
So it's a very, very, very tricky situation, and again, I don't want to go down this rabbit hole,
but I need to mention that, because within each book itself,
you have the right hand and the left hand, right?
And the majority will always follow the one that is easiest.
I found the human brain right now is wired to accept the lie.
It is just wired that way.
When I say statistically, everyone is like that.
Statistically, there are a few that will go be on a different path and be wary of that,
and it will wear you out when you're seeking the truth,
because you see, everyone has the same intelligence.
The difference is the perception.
Everyone, I assure you, has the same intelligence.
So all this IQ stuff is completely ridiculous.
What they're basing that on is a form of emotional armoring and degradation that has been done.
Like, for example, sometimes it's shocking to people when I say,
do you know what the most degrading thing you can do to anyone is, especially a child?
And they say, what? What's that?
And I say, that is grading them.
Any form of grading is degrading.
You know, how many times do you see people are impressed,
well, this guy has a degree from Oxford or a degree from Harvard, or he's a doctor,
and I just have to laugh, because I'm like,
if you haven't realized that you are in a trauma-based mind control system
that is designed to destroy your ability to think,
by the fourth or eighth grade, you're going to have problems.
In other words, you're going to fall for this engineered reality that brings nothing but death and misery,
because, again, it is not a system of edification, it is a system of degradation.
Just like in the military, you're broken down.
So we have a society that is following these people with degrees,
and none of them have ever stopped and thought that they've been degraded since kindergarten, you see.
So does that mean we should not have schools? Not at all.
But if you look at the ancient schools, there was no grading in them.
There was an instructor, someone that wanted to share something,
and he shared it with a small group of the class that got it,
and then that small group went ahead and taught the rest of the class in many different ways.
There was no grading.
Everyone had to make the goal that they were there for, which was to learn what was at hand.
You see, we live in a society that is motivated by punishment, by penalty,
instead of being motivated by doing the right thing.
So, again, that's one aspect.
So the grading system, any form of grading.
So the higher up you go, the lower you're actually going in terms of what we call consciousness.
Yeah, education and enlightenment are two different things.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
I explained that in my presentation last night.
For instance, an enlightened person knows that aspartame is made from E. coli feces,
so they won't give it to their children.
But an educated person will say, oh, no, aspartame is sugar-free,
and it's an FDA-approved alternative for sugar.
If they approved it, it's got to be okay.
Take as much as you want of it.
Big difference.
Yeah, the whole system, you see, when I say system, again, it's anything,
religious, science, math, medical, everything,
is based on denial of the primary vital forces.
Oh, look, that's the music for a break.
So, excellent.
All right.
Great start.
Thanks, folks.
You're with the Santos Bonacci and special guest The Greek,
and we're talking about deep things and metaphysical.
Back after the break.
Hi, and welcome back to American Freedom Radio.
You're with Santos Bonacci and special guest The Greek.
So we were talking about how everything is upside down in the world.
And debased.
Yeah, and debased.
There's no basis behind it at all.
Actually, if it was upside down, Santos,
all you had to do was turn it upside down one more time, and now it's right side up, right?
But what I'm saying is there's nothing there to turn upside down.
If you turn it all you want, you'll just be spinning a wheel and not going anywhere
because it's not touching the ground.
It's not grounded or based on anything.
For example, I want to just touch on the primary forces and how I mentioned earlier,
everything is based on denial of the primary forces.
And when I say primary force, a lot of people say energy.
And I say I'm still not talking about energy because energy is still a form of material.
I'm talking about the primary forces, which is based on geometric positions
and also classifications of what the ancients used to call the ether, let's say.
But when I say nothing is based on anything, for example,
when people go to what they call a medical doctor, a priest in a white robe,
and they look for your vital signs, the first thing they do is they put this cuff on your arm,
and they call that, you ask them, what are you doing?
He says, I'm taking your blood pressure, your blood pressure, okay?
So they put this cuff on your arm, and they keep inflating it until it blocks the flow of blood.
And then the circulatory system builds up a pressure, which is unnatural, behind that cuff.
And then the blood bursts forward, and they measure that, right?
And they say, ooh, your blood pressure is high, or your blood pressure is low.
The whole thing is based on an artificial premise that there is a blood pressure.
The blood is not being pushed. It's being sucked through the body, you see,
because the heart does not pump the blood. It is physically impossible.
And they're basing all these things on presumptions and creating, like I said earlier,
these engineered realities based on nothing at all, based on not the cause, but the symptom.
And then the medical industry, you've got to love them.
They've got this thing they're terrorizing everyone with called viruses.
Oh, these viruses, you've heard that before, right?
Germs, viruses, yeah, it's a whole bunch of shit.
Yeah, first it was, you see, if you look at all of the medical journals from the 1800s,
90% of it was hygiene, the other 10% was first aid.
And the people got sick because of poor engineering.
They would put their freshwater lines near their sewers.
Nothing to do with these fictitious diseases.
So after that, they found there were parasites, things called worms and amoebas and bacteria.
And they kind of couldn't really conquer them either because it was all based on sanitation, you see.
But later on, things were getting kind of doldrums, so they have to invent something.
So they invented this thing called a virus.
In reality, a virus is nothing more than the mitochondria of a cell when it's broken down in the body.
And if you're not able to eliminate these broken down cells properly
because your intestines and your bladder is not working properly,
or you're eating too much and not eliminating enough, these things will back up into your blood.
And they're calling these things viruses.
And even if you go on a Wikipedia article and look up the word virus,
you'll see one of the definitions for it is that it is a poison.
It is a poison.
And they tell you these viruses mutate.
Oh, so scary, they mutate, you know.
The reason they say they're mutating is because when these cells break down,
they apparently do it in a random fashion,
just like if you were to take an apple and smash it with a hammer,
examine the pieces, when you repeat it by smashing another example,
smashing another apple and examine the pieces, you're going to see the pieces are different, right?
That's because they're mutating, right?
It's so ridiculous.
These are nothing more than fragmented cells because the body is not eliminating.
So every aspect, I've looked at the medical industry.
The medical industry, again, it's all about hygiene and first aid.
And first aid should be based on trauma, usually, or a burn or an accident.
And the rest of it is all hygiene.
But there's not a lot of money in that, right?
If the medical industry focused on just first aid and hygiene,
how are they going to sell you a pill for $40?
So they can't do it.
But, again, no one's putting a gun to your head to go there to do it.
Now, we could touch on the legal and the law system,
and we know you've touched on that many, many, many hours already,
how that is not based on anything at all.
If you want to look at science,
they're still teaching the planets are going around a thermonuclear sun in neat elliptical orbits.
That's like saying the Earth is flat.
There's nothing in nature that does that.
Have you ever gone down the street, Santos, or at home and seen anything orbiting anything else?
No.
I've never have.
No, no.
See, it's a universe of scale.
These things don't happen.
And we've discussed, I guess, before, the sun is a rock, just like the Earth, let's say.
It's most likely a ferrite sphere made of calcium and iron.
And as it's moving through the, not the vacuum of space,
through the fluid medium of space,
which there are 24 other elements of gases above hydrogen there,
that are not found here,
when it reaches a certain velocity,
it gets vortex shedding behind it,
and it lights up like a meteorite in the back.
Inductively, it's electrical.
And all of the planets are not orbiting,
but they are circling in the wake, behind the sun, vertically, perpendicular to it.
And they're in a falling pattern.
They're not orbiting.
A falling pattern.
These are large objects.
And the most ridiculous stuff, you know, I mean, gravity is based on mass.
Last time I was on a little motorcycle on the highway,
a big 18-wheeler that weighed a thousand times more than me passed by,
I didn't stick to it like a magnet.
It's the most ridiculous thing that gravity is based on mass.
We wouldn't be able to move,
because right now there's about 10 objects that have more mass than I do in this room,
and I'm not, there's no attraction.
Or repulsion.
And these are so simple.
You see, when you heat or cool a house or room indoors,
the heat goes to the ceiling, and the cold goes to the floor.
So you have a hot head and cold feet all year round, indoors.
But outdoors, it's hot in the valley.
You go up to the mountain to cool off,
because in nature, heat goes down and cold rises.
You see, so everything, so this is like a little bit of a mental floss.
And the last thing I want people to do is,
hey, the Greeks said this, so it's got to be true.
No, you've got to back up and do and look and study a little bit on your own,
so now you make it your information.
But the thing is, how can you discuss with people
what is coming around the horizon, we call it prophecy,
or what is coming in the future, which is fully disclosed,
how can you discuss anything when they don't even have the ability
to perceive what is happening even five feet away from them,
or to discern the information?
Again, so there's a lot of alternative thinking,
there's a lot of alternative news, a lot of alternative science,
but it all goes back to the same aspect of negating the primary forces.
And what I mean by that is they all teach we are in a dead universe
and everything is chemically based or energetic.
Again, energetic is a material form.
Here, another thing, another example, everyone is saying
you have to raise your vibration, raise your vibration.
Wait a second, as you start vibrating something faster and faster,
it degrades the organic cell wall.
As you go to the microwaves, which is a very high vibration,
you degrade and you destroy living cells.
So all the new age people are saying raise your vibration,
in other words, put your head in a microwave, put your head in a microwave.
We need to lower our vibration to the frequencies in nature,
which are all low frequencies.
The earth frequency is between 6 and 14 cycles, that's the extremes,
usually between 8 and 10, 8 and 11.
And what they do, they say, oh no, the extra low frequencies, the navy and harp,
they're using that to do weather and make earthquakes and all that.
So we're really, the problem with moving forward and improving anything on this planet,
any form of this existence, regardless of the subject matter,
is to A, get out of this engineered reality,
because you're living in an engineered reality which is working against you.
And B, to acknowledge that life comes from primary forces, not energies again,
these are primary forces in the universe that are streaming through the sun,
through the planets, through us, through everything.
And again, negate the aspect that we're living in a dead chemical universe,
because the matter, the physical universe,
is nothing more than a manifestation of these primary forces.
Mind thinking, Walter Russell says, this is mind thinking, the creator thinking,
producing all the effects, motion from those forces.
Can you explain, you said before it's a universe of scale,
can you please talk to that?
Yes, yes. Everything is the same.
Everything is a manifestation of similar primary forces.
For example, Rudolf Steiner said there are seven ethers,
four we can come in contact with,
one being the warmth ether, the other one being the light ether,
the other one being the chemical ether, which is matter and water,
and the last one being the life ether.
And these are vague at best to describe them,
but once we start seeing these primary forces are responsible
for all the physical manifestations, we see that all the physical manifestations,
whether it be energy or matter, are bound to laws and behaviors that are of scale.
In other words, if we took a boron atom, or a hydrogen atom,
or an iron atom, or a calcium atom, and expanded it to the size of,
let's say, the sun, is it still a hydrogen atom or is it a sun?
It's the sun now.
The same thing if you take a galaxy and you shrink it down to the size of an atom,
is it a galaxy or is it an atom?
You see, that's what I mean by scale, it is all the same.
So it's as above, so below.
Absolutely, and it's of scale.
In scripture it says most of everything is made of things that we don't see,
and it doesn't mean that it's small, it could be very large as well.
So the scale element, and also the manifestations,
for example, the planet.
Why does the planet rotate?
What rotates the earth?
Now, if you go to the scientists, the orthodox science that's based on death,
that nothing is alive, they don't know, they have to talk about some theory.
My favorite one is, in a lot of fiction, whistleblowers, alternative black ops,
all this stuff, they talk about time travel and space-time.
How many times have you heard people say, oh, they're changing space-time?
Well, you ask them, especially if you look at the three stooges,
which I call Stephen Hawking, Einstein and Carl Sagan, those are the three stooges, right?
They use the term space-time, space-time.
If you look a little bit, spend five minutes researching it,
see, people are too intimidated by them because they take the position of the high priest, right?
So how dare you question the high priest?
Let's not question these high priests, let's just look at what they write.
If you look at Einstein, Hawking and all these guys they put in front of you, right?
They define space as a series of coordinates, and that's it.
Now, it's like saying, Santos, you are, let's say, 5'8 or 5'10.
So you're 5'10, that's what you are, that's it.
Is that all you are, you're just 5'10?
Well, how about we go to meters, let's say you're 1 3â„4 meters, that's what you are, right?
Isn't that the most ridiculous thing you've ever heard, you know?
Yeah, so what rotates the Earth in space, what they call space?
They don't know, and they will never find out.
They will never know in this continuum that we're speaking of.
The Earth is a living, if we look at it as a living being, just like a rock is alive, for example.
Its lifespan is different.
And if we look at the Earth having a vegetative plane,
there is a vegetative surface on the Earth where things grow, let's say plants,
from sea level, and even in the sea you have seaweed, let's say,
all the way up to the tree lines, you know, 7, 8, 10,000 feet, several kilometers up.
That's what we call the vegetative plane or vegetative surface of the Earth.
We look that everything on the Earth has a living, aerobic and anaerobic quality to it.
So if we look at the Earth as being, let's say, a single-celled plant,
in terms of vegetative in behavior, when you put a plant in the light,
you notice how it turns towards the light, or if you take it away from the light,
it wants to turn towards the sun, right?
It will actually bend the trees, all the plants.
Bend to the sun.
You can finish that thought off and then we'll go to a break.
Welcome back. You're with Santos Bonacci and The Greek.
Stelios, would you like to continue on from where you left off
that was a really, really good place?
Yeah, sure. What makes the Earth spin in what they call space?
And where I left off was if we look at the vegetative plane of the Earth
and look at how things grow, we can look at the planet as, let's say, a single-cell plant.
And just as a plant moves into the light, when the Earth is in darkness,
it wants to rotate towards the sun.
And when it rotates towards the sun, the forces on the Earth start generating in the light
and the atmosphere expands upward, becomes agitated, wants to rest.
But remember, there's now a side in the dark that wants to rotate towards the light again.
So it keeps it moving in that fashion, almost in perpetual motion.
As long as one side of the Earth is in the dark, that always wants to go into the light.
The side that goes into the light then wants to relax.
And the cycle repeats and we call that day and night.
And that is a very simple application.
And once we look at that application, again, by going back and seeing it as a universe of scale,
we can then start to get a more profound understanding of what's going on around us,
develop real science based on living principles, not dead principles,
that the Earth is just a dead rock that evolved from some explosion.
You see, and then we can go further and further and further and further and expand
and actually take control of the environment as good stewards
and not act like a bunch of squatters tearing the place apart
with our minds and what we're physically doing.
Yeah, yeah.
Now, you were discussing with the solar system as the planets rotate and orbit in the wake of the sun
and you mentioned the downward falling movement of these orbs.
Can you just elaborate on that a little bit?
Yes.
What's interesting about that is we have to look at time.
What is time?
Time is nothing more than the recordation of events.
And as the sun is moving through the fluid medium of space,
it is dragging these planets behind it in a wake,
just as you would be drafting a truck on the highway or drafting a cyclist.
You know, you're in a vacuum, but at the same time you're being shed.
It's a very complex form of geometry because it is also a vortex.
You see, it is rotating.
And the planets are in a vortex behind the sun,
just like you would have particles going down the drain in your bathtub
or the particles being flown about in a tornado or a hurricane.
Everything spirals.
But because of the incoming forces,
the primary forces on that scale in the fluid medium of space,
what we view as time is stretched out to the point where we can actually say
these are definite orbits when they are not.
The Earth is never in the same place in the universe twice, ever.
It is constantly moving.
Just as if you look at a lot of the popular talk now,
we're moving into the galactic center, you know, and all this stuff.
So it is acknowledged that we are moving,
but we are being dragged behind the sun in a falling pattern.
What I mean by a falling pattern, an easy way to describe it would be,
let's say you take a 10-story building
and you throw something off the top of the building,
and as it's making its way down to the ground,
you're on the fifth floor and you stick your hand out
and hit the object that's falling.
It will go slightly off course,
but very quickly resume its falling pattern towards the ground, you see.
And that is exactly what the planets are doing behind the sun.
But you also have to combine that.
They are in a vortex behind the sun, and the sun is in another vortex,
and that vortex is in another vortex.
It's almost like a fractal.
And all of these, let's call them laws or levels of scale,
are noticed by anyone.
Just like I asked you earlier,
have you ever seen anything orbiting anything?
And you said no, because it just doesn't happen.
And if you try to orbit, let's say, run around something or someone,
you get quite dizzy and it has to stop, you see.
It just doesn't, it's not a natural movement of things.
Everything is in a spiral vortex.
So the falling pattern is,
the reason I said that is because nothing is definite
in terms of it orbiting, let's say, like a train on train tracks.
There's any falling pattern,
because if it were to be moved from that position temporarily,
it will quickly resume that pattern of falling.
And I use the word falling because there's an easy way to describe it
as not being definite.
As scientists say, that we're in definite orbits.
Yeah, yeah.
And of course, that's due to the study of effects rather than causes.
Absolutely.
See, they can't touch the causes,
because in order to touch the causes,
they have to admit that everything is alive in some scale again.
And also you hear in the alternative a lot,
alternative sciences,
oh, this is another dimension or this is interdimensional or something.
The concept of dimension is fixed,
because if you change one dimension, all of the others change as well.
Now, the dimensions again are the path of creation,
where you start from a certain potential
and then move to another potential.
And what I mean when you change one dimension,
you change all the others.
Take a circle, for example.
The circle is proportionately dependent.
In other words, the diameter, circumference,
and area of a circle are proportionately dependent.
If you change the circumference, you also change the area and the diameter.
And the circumference, area, and diameter are the dimensions.
So when you change one dimension, all the other dimensions change.
So right now, this is a dimensionally stable universe.
So it leads you back to being one of scale.
So that's why, I guess we're having this discussion,
let's call it a form of mental floss.
There's so much information out there,
what they call, let's say, alternative versus mainstream.
But if you look very closely at what's being projected in the alternative,
it's still very deeply rooted in the orthodox aspects of the mainstream,
which teaches a dead, chemical, materialistic, non-existent...
Gravity.
Yeah, all these things, yeah.
Now, Walter Russell is spot on.
Everything Walter Russell speaks of can be reproduced in a laboratory,
a benchtop.
You can read, for example, the works of Victor Schauberger.
Read the works of Rudolf Steiner.
These are men that have had breakthroughs and always had small followings
and were always tormented.
Another one is Nikola Tesla.
Nikola Tesla said, if you follow Euclidean math,
and you follow what modern science teaches,
you will never understand how to work anything that I'm working on
or any of my devices.
You see, Tesla talked about accumulating the luminiferous ether.
Tesla never spoke about generating power.
See, everything now is power generation.
How are we going to generate power?
We have alternative fuels, this, that, and the other.
Why do we have to generate power?
We just need to accumulate it.
We're like a bird sitting on a 50,000-volt high-tension electrical wire.
It doesn't get electrocuted, but you cannot deny that it is sitting on a hot wire.
You see?
Yeah.
Yeah, but once you short that out, the bird will completely become dust.
It will vaporize from the power going through it.
So what we want to do is accumulate the power going through the earth
and not short it and destroy the dipole, but use it and send it back responsibly
so it can do work for us based on the potential of where the earth is
and what they call the solar system.
So that's why there is no work being done on Tesla stuff
because the majority of the people trying to look at Tesla's devices,
they have orthodox training.
You can never understand anything Tesla.
You see, they talk about free energy, free energy, free.
The word free is an acronym.
It stands for from revenue emanated elsewhere.
So you're really still accumulating.
You're not generating.
There's no free energy.
The devices that we have are all based on the destruction of the dipole
and the manifestation of electricity that has a main component of electricity is heat
and it basically accelerates the aging process and living things.
Wow.
Yeah, fantastic.
Folks, I hope you're enjoying the conversation.
We're at the top of the hour now.
And we're going to come back with some calls.
We're going to throw the lines open and I'll share that number with folks.
Access number is 218-339-8525.
Please call in and shoot some questions away at the Greek and see if you can't answer them.
Thanks.
Stelios, we'll be back after the break.
I just don't want you to know I can see through your masks.
Oh, yeah.
You can see through those masks a lot, lot clearer these days.
The masters of war have had their way for a long time on this planet, the banksters.
But we are beginning to see through their masks, as Bob Dylan sings.
Welcome back to the second hour of American Freedom Radio.
You're with Santos Bonacci and special guest, the Greek.
Please continue on, Stelios, with those beautiful points.
You're talking about rocks and how they breathe.
Please.
Oh, thanks.
Yeah, we were speaking on the break.
Again, everything that orthodox teachings have in place for the people is that we are in a dead universe
or dead substances or chemicals.
And when you put a rock in front of someone, you know, these universities and sciences,
well, you know, granite is azoic.
You know, I mean, there's no life in it.
It's just minerals.
Well, I'll give some references.
If you go study the work of Wilhelm Reich back in the, let's say, 30s to the 50s,
they would take pieces of granite, azoic rock, meaning there's no life in it at all.
It's pure mineral, let's say.
And they would heat it to incandescence, meaning red hot with a torch.
And in a sterile environment, put it in sterile water.
And within two or three days, 72 hours or more,
you would see small little organisms growing out of the rock itself and moving.
And some of them would actually grow to the size where they developed appendages
and would walk right off the slide on the microscope.
Another thing, now, by the way, I'm mentioning these references because you can do it yourself.
You can actually, you need a magnification of, let's say, 70 to 100 times to see this within three or seven days.
Another thing you can do is take a piece of granite and cut it in half
and take one half and coat it with an epoxy or a lacquer so no air can get to the rock.
And within three days, examine the half that you had not suffocated or coated and the one that you did.
And you'll notice the color of the granite has changed internally.
Its strength has changed.
Its electrical conductivity or resistance has changed.
So it is possible to suffocate a rock.
So we're seeing that everything has its own life cycle.
And the other thing we mentioned is how all of these truths are implanted in our language.
The word petroleum, petro meaning rock and oleum meaning oil.
And when you think of the oil they're pumping out of the ground, you know, if you say to someone,
well, this is olive oil, where did it come from?
Well, olive oil comes from olives.
Or this is corn oil, where did it come from?
It came from corn.
Or this is fish oil, came from fish.
So petroleum means rock oil, comes from rocks.
And it's reproduced by the earth when the earth is left in the right condition to reproduce it.
Yeah, and the Russians have been teaching for a long time, since the 50s,
that the earth produces these so-called fossil fuels.
That's all she does.
So there's not going to be peak oil.
That's another shortage myth.
Yes, the problem with the oil, this is it.
And this goes, let's tie this back to the divine teachings.
When I say divine, all divine teachings share the notion, Santos,
that we need to gravitate and go to the light and not in the dark.
Right?
And when you actually look at a lot of the ancient languages, dark is a substance.
Darkness is not only absence of light.
It is a substance in itself.
And without getting into that, I just want to reflect on what's going on in this society.
And it's a very simple metaphor.
Years ago, mankind was more agricultural and relied on plants,
which are produced in the light, for his food, for his oils, for fibers to make clothing,
for feeds, for building their homes.
Right?
The art of life, of our life, was based on substances that were produced in the light.
Plant matter, you see.
Now, this society is based on substances that are produced in the dark.
Most of everything that we touch and interact with is oil-based,
petroleum that is developed in the darkness.
And even if you have a truck full of organic lettuce making its way to the market,
it is in a diesel truck.
You see?
It is not being pulled by a horse who is eating vegetable.
So, you might think you're in the light, I tell people, but you are in complete darkness.
Because if you eliminated the petroleum variable,
you would pretty much bring the entire society, the developed quote-unquote society, to a halt.
So, it is a very, very simple way to look at, when you look at that word light or darkness.
Now, also, what is produced in the light will be destroyed in the dark.
If you put a plant in the dark, and even if you water it, it will turn yellow and rot.
Right?
Now, what is produced in the dark will be destroyed in the light.
If you take, let's say, a plastic chair or a car, paint on a car,
you notice how it fades in the sun?
Or the plastic chair will break down in the sun?
So, these are just little rules to remember.
This society, when it says your society is going in darkness, what do you mean?
I'm not in the darkness. I've got plenty of light.
Here, I can hit this light switch right here, which is made of plastic and is powered by coal,
which are all things that came from the dark, because darkness is also a substance and a product.
So, that is, you know, not speaking out against using petroleum or tars and coals from the ground.
They have their place.
But we need to reflect on what we've, you know, created a major, major pervasiveness,
where it's completely overcome the light-produced aspect.
Yeah. And is that darkness in any way harmful, that substance?
It can be. Too much of something can be.
It's like, what's more harmful, an overbearing father or an overbearing mother?
See? It's that neither one is overbearing but in balance.
You know, another thing the alternative teaches, oh, we need more women in charge.
This is going to get me in trouble, baby. I hope it doesn't get you in trouble.
But they say, we need more women in charge, we won't have any wars, you know, or whatever, you know.
This and that is too much masculine. That's actually the opposite.
Very simple. When was the last time you've been to someone's house and saw a urinal designed into the house?
Women got their women's lib, right, in the 60s and all that, right? What happened?
The family's destroyed.
You know, you have all these female goddess religions that are based on the destruction and eating of children.
You know, we don't want to get into that because people will think, well, that's anti-feminine.
No, it just so happens that there is a particular feminine entity that is ruling the earth indirectly with other entities.
And this entity just happens to be feminine.
And you look at all of your divine writings and it talks about, let's say, the mystery Babylon, the harlot, right?
What does a harlot do? She puts something that can be set apart, lovemaking in commerce, right?
So isn't everything in commerce?
You have this, law has been replaced by a goddess religion called justice.
Justice has nothing to do with law. It's a statue of a woman with scales and a blindfold.
It has nothing to do with law, I assure you.
You could look up, justice comes from an ancient religion called Dike, or the goddess Dike in Greece, and justicia, Roman emperors, you know?
So right now, there's an overbearing feminine side right now, and it's going to be balanced by the father side, which is coming.
That is on the way.
But you see, everything is backwards.
See, that is one thing you can turn upside down or inside out and show that it's, you know...
For example, again, there's too much feminine.
If you look at all the gender-bending chemicals, they're all estrogen mimickers, all the phthalates and plastics, the BPAs.
You know, you end up getting women getting ovarian cancers because there's too much estrogen from the chemical, and men getting various feminine traits.
So now we have gender-bending based on too much.
The chemical world is using, again, the feminine against us.
It's always the feminine being used against man right now on the spiritual side, on the mud-level and spiritual side.
Because there is a cosmic war, we do have cosmic enemies, and they do have agents, boots on the ground right now as we speak.
And I'm not talking about all these aliens and stuff, because we are the aliens.
They were here first.
So, you know, going down that road, you know, again, speaking to people who, you know, you have to have your feet firmly planted on what's going on around you.
When you speak to people who don't, they quickly want to grasp at things they've heard without proving or studying, and it's a very difficult topic to discuss.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, that's for sure.
And the difference is left brain and the right brain.
The right brain is intuitive and is connected directly to the source, and the left brain is logic-reason based.
So, not that it's wrong, but the logic and the reason, and it's not inferior at all.
We need both.
But good old Rome has found a way of keeping people away from the intuitive, the source, and speculating with their logic and reason.
Yeah, pretty much.
The logic and reason doesn't work if you're in an engineered reality.
How can you logic and reason when you think the planets go around the sun in neat elliptical orbits and the sun is thermonuclear?
I mean, you know, they're teaching you that everything is dead, so now you're using logic and reasoning in death in an orthodox teaching that negates the living force.
And you need both.
You see, the Father is light and the Mother, matter, is material.
If you look at the ovum and the sperm, the rays of the sun look like, you see, like the sperm, and the Earth looks like the ovum.
Again, it's scale. Everything is scale.
The light of the sun inseminates the surface of the Earth, and we have growth.
You see, so you need both in balance.
Yeah, exactly. Both in balance.
And what a beautiful point that the sun is the inseminator, because that's how the scriptures, all of them, refer to the sun as the bridegroom.
And the brides are the beautiful magnetic planets that orbit and rotate in the wake of the sun.
Now, an interesting gentleman was Edward Leedskellner from Coral Castle, and he explained, very similar to you, why the Earth rotates.
And it has to do about with magnetism and the light, as you say.
So, he was very revolutionary in his thinking, and of course, he built all of Coral Castle with the technology on magnetism that he discovered.
Yeah, he was a master of, I don't know if I should actually, not that I know the secrets, but I can tell you what I found out about Edward Leedskellner, and nothing is on the Internet about it.
The magnets are still very, very misunderstood.
They're not being looked at objectively.
But what I found out with Edward Leedskellner is that he had discovered that all motion is based on the displacement of the center of gravity.
And what I mean by that is when you stand up, and you are about to take a step forward, as what we call walking, one foot in front of the other.
The first thing you do is lift one foot up, and you are displacing your center of gravity.
You're actually falling forward, and then you put your other foot in front of you to stop that fall.
It's a controlled fall, and you repeat the process, and we call that walking.
That's why if you throw a piece of ice or a slippery banana peel in front of that foot, that person will fall.
They will slip, because they lost the ability to stop that controlled fall.
You see?
And he understood this very well, and he was able to move very, very, very heavy objects using, you know, you can move a ten-ton block of granite using a few pea-sized pieces of gravel, if you know how to use that principle.
And it's easy to demonstrate as well.
Yeah.
What is it that you do, Stelios?
Can you please explain the weather modification that you do in your line of work?
Let's call it that.
Oh, absolutely.
Yes.
One aspect of it is I encourage anyone to go and study the works of Wilhelm Reich, the works of Trevor James Constable.
And to say that, you know, I do weather modification is not necessarily as accurate as saying that what we are doing is using very, very simple concepts, devices that allow us to technically access these primary forces that determine whether or not you have rain,
whether or not you have a hurricane, whether or not you have a windstorm, whether or not you have pollution.
And what, because of the situation on the planet right now and the inconsiderate development of so many structures on the planet, electrical devices, the living, these primary forces that flow through the earth and at the earth's surface on many levels are being disturbed.
Now, you don't disturb them the way we consider disturbing.
You temporarily block them and the blockages are created.
So what one can do, as you and I have spoken before and I mentioned, once you understand how to remove these blockages, just like a chiropractor would, let's say, if you had a stiff back, realign you.
What you're doing is actually allowing, you're creating a device that this ethereal energy or primary force can technically access, recognizes it.
And what we have to understand is these forces move from low potential to high potential.
Everything that is taught about energy in the orthodox teachings is that all potentials move from high to low.
Meaning if you have, let's say, two buckets of water and one has more water or a higher level than the other, if you couple the two buckets together, the high level will drop to the low level and they will equalize.
Or if you have an electrical circuit, the electricity flows from high potential to low potential, which would be ground.
The ethereal and the primary forces flow from low to high potential.
For example, let's say, if you look at politics, for example, when you look at a...
There's a break.
Yeah, okay. Well, keep that thought. We're looking at politics and we're talking about high and low potential.
Callers, if you'd like to call in after the break, feel free to do so. 218-339-8525.
And it's all over now, baby blue.
Oh yeah, it's all over. It's all over for the controllers. That's what it is.
And hallelujah for that.
You're with Santos Panache and special guest The Greek.
Would you like to please continue from the thought about politics and high and low potentials, please, Stelios? That was fantastic before the break.
Yeah, sure.
Explaining the vital forces go from low potential to high, where the orthodox teaches all energy systems go from high to low potential.
For example, in politics, you have the political leader. He's high in status and he gets his power from the people who are lower in status, your common man.
See, they're feeding him, right? And they're discharging into him. The stronger he gets, the weaker the people get, you see.
You're right. So that is an example of primary force.
Another example would be, if you want to go to a scriptural example, the Christ said,
Those who have little I will take away, and those who have much I will give more till they're full.
Yeah, so these are all examples on the ether.
You see, that's why, for example, if you have orthodox teachings in Christianity or Judaism, you will never understand the scriptures.
Because it is speaking of primary forces, which are not based on the teachings.
And we're also warned in these scriptures not to observe the teachings of men, meaning these engineered fictional realities.
Do as I say, not as I do, right?
Yeah.
So, the aspect of, as we mentioned, weather.
If we look at a cloud, for example, it is not water vapor.
It is a form of, let's say, a biological plasma, would be a simple way to describe it.
And an easy way to imagine it as being a biological plasma is, if you went to a planet, let's say, that did not have any clouds,
and you sprayed billions of tons of water in the atmosphere, it would all just fall to the ground.
You would not get any cloud formation whatsoever.
It has to do with the unique vegetative plane that the Earth has, and it is actually,
the clouds that you see are actually emanated from the ethericities or the things, the quality materials that are emanated by the Earth towards the sky.
And once you understand that, again, we were speaking of how to look at the weather,
there are technical devices that you can make.
These are not powered by anything.
There is no electrical power or anything behind them.
They are based solely on geometry and layering.
And you can technically access these primary forces by creating a low potential in the device that will emanate out if it happens to be low.
If you create a high potential, it will emanate in and accumulate.
You see, and this is what Tesla was doing.
But, you know, again, drought conditions, hurricanes, tornadoes, pollution are not material energetic aspects.
They are all manifestations of the primary force.
For example, another topic to look at is, if you look at all of medical science or psychology or science in itself,
they never ever studied or have an explanation for what we call the orgasm.
And when I say the orgasm, I am not talking about expelling fluids and all this.
I am talking about the actual state of orgasm is a release of these life forces or these primary forces.
And if anyone is interested in understanding this a little bit more, they can study some of the work of Wilhelm Reich,
who, of course, was thrown into a federal prison and died there.
And there was a huge book burning right after that.
They ordered all of his books burned.
This is in 1957.
He had shown that he was one of Freud's students, and he was actually second in line of a lot of Freud's research,
which we haven't gotten, by the way, directly.
We talk a lot of Freud's stuff, which is not really what he was basing his work on.
But Wilhelm Reich was a protege to Freud, and he noticed when he would be, let's say, examining people in psychotherapy,
sometimes their bodies would go into these convulsive states, so then the people would be in a form of terror sometimes.
And he noticed that if you looked at them objectively, you would think they were having an orgasm.
But they were in terror.
So he noticed that this is not being produced by the body, but something flowing through the body.
And through many thousands of experiments, he found that this can be technically accessed by devices,
a series of tubes and special geometries.
And he also discovered that it flows from low to high.
And the reason I'm reiterating these things is because if anyone listening is interested in studying Wilhelm Reich,
you must go and study Wilhelm Reich.
Not, for example, there is a large movement today on what they call orgone or orgone energy,
and these little organite devices that people are making, and chembusters and things.
This has nothing to do with the teachings of Wilhelm Reich.
It's a spin-off, and actually I wouldn't be playing around with any of it.
99% of the stuff on the internet, when you look up Wilhelm Reich, will steer you to what's called orgone, organite, or ethereal.
Yeah, I would not deal with any of that stuff.
It is not based on Wilhelm Reich, just like we started off the program.
If you look at anything that's going on right now, it's based on nothing.
If you look at a lot of this stuff that's being done in the name of Wilhelm Reich right now,
it has nothing to do with what Reich was talking about at all.
And I would not encourage people to play with those things,
because any time you're trying to access the ether, you will have consequences.
They may be direct or indirect.
So very often when I do have discussions like this, some people say,
No, have you ever heard of organite? Have you ever heard of this? Or chembusters?
Or all these copper tubes? And I'm like, yeah, don't do that.
I've heard of it, absolutely, because that is not based on any science.
It is an engineered reality that has no function.
Now there's a lot of people that say, oh, I feel better, or this, that, or the other.
But the more of these devices that are being made unresponsively,
without understanding the core of the living aspect of these primary forces,
it's pretty much being reckless.
Because you may not actually be doing harm, you might be doing good, or vice versa,
but you don't know what you're doing unless you actually study what these men,
such as Wilhelm Reich and Trevor James Constable, have discovered.
Wow. Wow. Fantastic.
Can you talk about the planets Mercury and Venus and their figure-eight shape
that they ascribe toward each other?
Yes, yes. Very interestingly enough, I had studied some of the Ptolemyan
and other Greek and Egyptian writings, and they had always stated, whatever I can get,
I shouldn't say always, but I had found enough clues that these ancient writings
had stated that Venus was the planet closest to the Sun.
So right away, if you go to that with orthodox thinking, you're going to say,
well, how could that be? You know, NASA says Mercury is closer, right?
Well, let's look at it objectively.
When you look at Venus, it's hotter than Mercury. Okay, number one.
Number two, if you look at the Sun moving through the fluid medium of space
and its vortex shedding action behind it illuminates it,
and it is creating a suction or a spiral where all the planets
are being dragged behind it in its wake,
if we go and study very closely vortex shedding,
there's a fellow in the 1920s, his name is Carmen, K-A-R-M-E-N,
Carmen Vortex Shedding Principles, and he took spheres and put them through water
with powders in them, so as he dragged the sphere through the fluid medium,
you would see the vortices that would develop behind it.
You will see that particles directly behind the main object that is inducing the wake
will follow a figure eight pattern behind it.
And I started looking at a lot of things in literature, a lot of things in ancient studies
that always reinforce that the orbits of Venus and Mercury were not fixed,
but were in a pattern where they interchanged,
and you can say that predominantly Venus is closest to the Sun.
And that's one of the things that I'm still working on.
It might be a little premature, but I at least brought the audience
and yourself up to speed on my most recent endeavors.
And looking at this in more specific terms, this is the most I can come up with,
but if I had to put money down on Las Vegas, what the ancients taught
or what this modern orthodox science is teaching, that's a no-brainer.
Yeah.
You see? Yeah.
Yeah, for sure.
And thank God we have guys like Emanuel Velikovsky and Wallace Thornhill
and David Talbot and these guys from Thunderbolts
with the Electric Universe Plasma Cosmology,
true teaching of the universe.
Thank God we have these people who are resisting the fraudulent science
of study of effects from the institutions of this Roman world.
Good old Rome, she's got her tricks.
She loves the fictions.
Love a fiction or two.
And they'll put it right in front of you, and they're hoping that you're so blind
and you're so, you see, they've already got you so indoctrinated,
what they'll do is they'll hold up five fingers until you say there are three fingers,
and you'll say there are three fingers.
Now, if you don't say there are three fingers, they beat you over the head
until you say there are only three fingers, even though they're showing you five.
You see, an example of that would be this new collider they built,
Hebron or whatever ridiculous thing.
They spend billions of dollars to smash atoms together to study them,
looking for a God particle, right?
And it is the most ridiculous thing, and it actually,
if you look at some of the images where they smashed two gold particles together,
it reveals the fraud right there on what they're producing in their periodic tables.
For example, gold is an isotope of 196, let's say 200 rounded off, right?
That means it's made up of a combination of 200 particles,
you know, protons and bisons and neutrons, all these ridiculous things, right?
So if you smash two of them together, let's see, that's 200 plus 200,
it should be about 400 particles visible in the image, right?
But if you look at the image they produce,
there are thousands of streamers and particles coming out of there,
thousands, thousands of thousands.
So right away, these people are so blind, they can't say,
wait a second, these are two gold atoms, we should have 400 streamers,
or 396, or 380.
There are thousands of streamers, because they're not particles at all,
they're vortices that are collapsing.
So what I'm saying is we can spend hours, Santo,
showing the fraud in every aspect, every field of study.
It doesn't matter if it's science, religion, medicine, mathematics,
all of it is just completely debased, and they're showing you,
I mean, I don't know if they can be that blind, you know,
that they don't even see the evidence in front of them,
but that is another discussion entirely.
Wow.
To me, it appears that they have detached themselves
from the natural intuition that they have,
and they have just sold themselves to the authoritative information,
erroneous though it may be,
and they are quite happy to go with the authority that stands behind it.
It's official.
Yes.
It's like Aspartame is officially approved by the FDA.
Well, that's a relief.
Oh, what a relief.
The FDA have approved it, and they've done some tests,
and this alphabet agency is just like unto God.
Yes, but you see, if the people, again, it goes from low to high,
if the people didn't buy it, there would be no issue with it, you see.
You know, very often I do get people saying,
well, you know, we're being destroyed, or we have a corrupt government,
there's an evil New World Order,
and I'm like, it's all backwards, man.
All of the ruling classes and every authority figure on the planet
is nothing more than an image or reflection of the people,
and it is the people's behavior that is creating that,
and I can be very specific with that.
When we look at all of the divine texts of the world,
they state that there is a creator and there is a set of rules,
and one of the rules there is do not destroy your own kind and eat its flesh, right?
We call it cannibalism.
Now, for example, in the divine world, intent is very important,
behavior is very important.
How many people actually put a birthday cake in front of their child
and go through that whole ceremony?
Lighting the candles, you know, bringing gifts, you know,
which, by the way, the word gift means poison.
Presence and asking the child to make a wish of prosperity.
You know, how many parents gave their children dolls to play with, right?
How many parents put their children on Santa Claus's lap?
You have a large, a big belly with a red colored figure.
You put the child on this figure's lap to make a wish of prosperity.
All these...
Please, hang on to that beautiful thought,
and we're going to be coming back to the last break,
so if anyone wants to call, please call in,
and we'll take your call.
Thank you.
After the break.
Make me proud to know you're one of them
See what the captain says
Adam Radio, and we are on the last portion of the show today.
We have a caller.
Before we go to the caller,
can you just please elaborate on what you were talking about before the break, please?
Santa Claus and the fictions, etc.
Yes, yes.
I'll make it short, Santos, because anyone wants, they can research it.
I would say just about all of the quote-unquote holidays and celebratory events
that people are on the planet are engaging in right now are tied in
to elements of human sacrifice,
particularly the sacrifice and eating of the flesh of children.
And like I said earlier,
we are being engaged by a cosmic enemy,
and these cosmic enemies have placed boots on the ground.
They are on the ground, and I'm not talking about strange-looking people.
What they have done is they have simply taken control of the minds and hearts
of those with authority,
which the people on the planet right now,
I'm not talking about any specific society.
I'm speaking on a planetary level, okay?
Our view as authorities,
specifically in the medical, religious and scientific and political authorities,
are being guided by these boots on the ground,
by these cosmic enemies.
And how many times have you heard,
it's voluntary, right?
Right? By all of these authorities, it's voluntary.
You must consent, whether it's medical, academic, political or legal, right?
They tell you that, right?
It's voluntary.
It is by your consent.
You must sign here.
But if you don't sign, what do they do?
They throw you in a cell, or they beat you over the head, or they kill you.
So that's why I say it is a cosmic war,
and maybe one day we will go into more specifics with that.
And they have invited everyone through pleasurable, seemingly pleasurable, carnal events,
birthdays, religious holidays, national holidays,
are timed, aligned and parody the eating and destruction of human flesh.
And that is maybe the general around-the-block description
of one of the main reasons why there is so much misery on the planet right now.
Yeah, yeah, for sure.
I've discussed a lot of that in my astro-theological presentations.
Let's go to a caller.
John, are you there?
Hello, John.
Yes, you recognized my number.
I was wondering if you would address the issue of consciousness.
It's the one thing I didn't hear you talk about.
All right, let's define it.
Very, very, very, very, very simple.
Most of what I've been talking about is exposing this engineered reality.
Now, if we look at consciousness,
let's talk about very, very simple.
The opposite of conscious is unconscious.
In a carnal sense, in a physical sense, when you're awake, you're conscious.
When you're asleep, you're unconscious, right?
Whether it's voluntary or involuntary,
you can be unconscious from a traumatic event as well,
and conscious from a traumatic event physically.
On a spiritual level, meaning, for example,
we're all having a spiritual discussion.
The word spirit means not of the physical realm.
We're communicating through telephony, internet, sound.
It is not physical in the flesh, so it is spiritual, meaning unseen.
From that unseen point of view, from a spiritual point of consciousness,
without getting too specific,
you have to, it's a very broad way of explaining.
The actual, to get into explaining it would be very broad
and discuss more background,
but a simple way to explain it would be using a computer.
For example, when you have a computer,
you just bought a new computer, you take it out of the box,
you plug it in, and the screen is blinking at you.
It has no ability to think or process anything at the moment.
You have to first download an operating system,
a set of rules that it can function with,
and information that is inherent to the hardware.
So consciousness, the way I would define it,
is what operating system are you running?
Very simple.
Very interesting.
Do you even have an operating system?
Let me just make a comment.
I see that most of the inhabitants of the earth right now
are running around with blinking screens with no operating system,
waiting for some form of RAM memory.
They have no program.
You see, they work purely by stimulation.
Yeah, a lot of people do not think.
Well, the thing is, do you have an operating system?
In other words, that is the purpose of all of these divine scriptures
that have been put out for thousands of years.
And, you know, some people will say,
well, I am Christian, I go by this, and I am Jewish, I go by that,
or I am Muslim, I go by that.
Well, if you do not see that they are all saying the same thing,
you missed the point, you see.
All of these ancient scriptures were an operating system,
a set of rules and guidelines, a user's manual.
Well said.
Thanks, John, for your question.
Can we go to another caller?
Do you have any other questions?
No, that is it.
Thank you very much.
Yeah, thanks for the call.
Very much.
And I am going to the next caller with the number 4571.
Caller, are you there?
Yes, hi.
My name is Dave, and I have a quick question or two.
Can your guest speak to, he had touched upon it a little earlier,
about the matriarchal patriarchy,
which is kind of an imbalance of the energies in our duality,
or I should say complementary world, should be complementary world.
And then also could he speak to how technology is based on the human body
and how it has been usurped and used to hold back the evolution of us as humans
or as beings, both spiritually and physically, in this realm?
And I take my answer off the air.
I appreciate you both.
Thank you.
Yeah, sure.
The first part about the matriarch and patriarch,
there are some fundamental aspects, again, in the way the primary forces move,
the fertility and the aspects and the growth aspects.
Right now, without elaborating too much, without saying maternal or paternal,
let's say male and female, and as I've touched on very briefly,
we have a cosmic enemy, malevolent forces that are affecting us,
and albeit it's temporal, it's not permanent.
But right now in this particular state, we can go back millennia,
one of the main particular malevolent entities happens to be a female entity.
Now, it doesn't mean that females are bad.
It's like, for example, if someone put on a ski mask and stuck a gun to your side
and said, give me your money, and they got away with it,
and then the next day they get caught, and you pull the ski mask off,
and you see it's a woman, and you say, well, this woman robbed me.
Well, are you anti-feminine, or that particular robber or assailant
happened to be a female, you see?
So it's very difficult for people to objectively see what is going on,
because there are other aspects of this cosmic war, let's call it,
that are not part of this female entity, or let's call her a deity.
And that's why I like giving the example to cut to the chase.
I asked Santos, when was the last time you've been to someone's house
and there was a urinal in the bathroom?
Never. It's just a very simple way to bring some light to it.
The other aspect of technology being part of the body, yes, it is.
In other words, you have the ergonomic aspect.
Does something fit in your hand comfortably?
Is a chair designed well?
But the aspect of the type of electricity that's being used
does nothing more than age organic and living organisms.
We are looking at petroleum-based technology,
which is coming from the darkness, and it's destroyed by the light.
You also have to consider that over 5,000 years ago,
there was an industrial revolution that makes the one that is known
in modern society look like pittance.
And this particular society is still around,
and they are a parallel society to this one.
Just like, for example, there are millions of people on this planet
who don't have electricity or even use the telephone,
be a parallel society to this one.
If you hear me, you probably have a computer or access to a telephone or electricity.
So there are parallel societies on Earth.
There was an industrial revolution that happened almost 5,500 years ago,
and that parallel society is still on the Earth.
Santos and things that he's touched upon,
you might be able to integrate into what we call the Roman death cult,
as well as many of the other religious cults.
I don't give much credence to the academics,
because the academics are a buffer zone between these powers and the people.
The academics are pretty much worthless,
because they're focusing on everything being dead.
There are no primary living forces.
So I guess that's the long-winded answer to that.
Yeah, and well done.
Just a quick one. We'll go to another caller,
and really quick, because we've only got a minute or two.
Caller with the number 2841. Are you there?
Hello?
Yes.
Hey, Santos, this is Fernando.
Hey, Fernando.
Hey, how are you doing?
I have a question for the interviewer.
I'm not sure what your name is, because I sent in a little late to catch your name.
Okay, it's Stelios from the Greek. Go ahead.
I just wanted to ask if you have any knowledge on Taoism,
on chi energy that people are able to generate an enormous amount of electricity?
Yes, yes.
The primary forces that I'm speaking of in what we call the Asian cultures is called the chi or the chi.
Absolutely.
Exactly.
Yeah, you can access it technically as well.
Is it?
Guys, sorry, that's it.
That's the time up.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, man.
But that's how it goes.
We'll do it again.
Thank you, the Greek.
Stelios, I really appreciate you talking with me.
I always love talking to you.
It's just so inspirational.
We'll probably do this again another time.
Thanks, listeners.
Stay tuned next week.
We've got a great guest.