Coming to you straight out of the Bronx, New York City, good evening and welcome to the
latest episode of the Infinite Fringe.
My name is Billy Ray Valentine and tonight, tonight we have a free thinker, a philosopher
of sorts to talk to us about etymology, to talk to us about the nature of life, the human
body, the container we call the human body.
His name is the Greek.
Get ready for some next level thinking with the Greek right here on the Infinite Fringe.
Hey, don't forget to subscribe on iTunes.
Go ahead and subscribe on iTunes, man.
We appreciate it.
We need it.
Thank you so much.
Go subscribe on iTunes.
The Infinite Fringe, also on Podbeam, theinfinitefringe.podbeam.com.
Follow me on Twitter, Obiwan, you know me, Billy Ray Valentine on Twitter.
Let's get into some news bits.
And we have a lot of them since we missed last week due to audio difficulties, technical
difficulties we had to miss last week.
So we have a lot of news, but I'm not going to give it all.
We're going to have to space it out because it's so much news.
So next episode, the episode after that, we'll sprinkle in some of this news.
But let's get into it right here on the Infinite Fringe.
Some fringe news before we get into our interview with the Greek.
All right, let's talk about the Mothman.
You ever heard of the Mothman?
Anyway, Mothman's back.
A legendary creature from back in the day.
They've even made movies about the Mothman.
Anyway, he's been spotted in Chicago.
It's a giant butterfly, owl-looking humanoid type thing.
And they've spotted, three different people have spotted this thing in Chicago.
MUFON reports.
Maybe we'll get somebody on from MUFON to talk about this.
But this isn't anything new.
Mothman has been spotted all over the place.
And who knows what the hell this thing really is?
Is it a hybrid animal or is it an alien from another planet?
This is, what is it?
Express.co.
It's a British publication that is publicizing this.
Go ahead and go check it out.
The Mothman Prophecies.
Dread as legendary man-sized bird seen by three separate witnesses is the headline.
All right, go check that out.
Mothman's back.
So be careful.
Emmanuel Macron has just won the French elections.
He is the new president of France.
A 39 years old, defeating Marine Le Pen in what is described as just about a landslide.
I don't know about these polls.
If they're anything like American polls, you can't trust them, but it is official.
Emmanuel Macron, the new president of France.
Let's see where this takes us.
I remember Marine Le Pen promising to take France out of the European Union.
A lot of Trumpian ideas from Marine Le Pen that has been defeated over in France.
The new globalist president of France, Emmanuel Macron, 39 years old.
Let's keep an eye on that situation.
Did parallel universe open up hundreds?
See floating city filmed in the skies above China.
Now, if you're into this, you know, this isn't the first time we've seen something like this.
Yes, I know it sounds crazy.
A floating city in the skies over China.
The fact is it's the fifth time in six years that a floating city has been spotted over the skies of China.
This is incredible.
Go take a look at it.
You can see video of past of past instances in which this has happened.
And you can see video of the most recent one as well.
If you look it up on YouTube, floating city in China, all types of theories about this stuff.
People are saying it's a view into a parallel universe that we are looking into a parallel universe when this or a parallel universe is manifesting itself in front of our eyes.
It's a tear in the space time continuum.
People are talking about Project Blue Beam, that this is another test of Project Blue Beam.
Either way, however you slice it, it's happening.
Something's up there and it looks like a city.
I don't know if it's a rare cloud formation that we're not aware of or if it's something completely different, completely artificial, alien.
No idea.
But five times in six years, it's no coincidence.
This thing looks like a city and it keeps popping up.
People are recording it, speculating about it and analyzing it.
Go take a look.
It's definitely worth your time because it's interesting as hell.
It looks like a city up in space.
It looks like heaven is breaking through the sky.
OK, so definitely go take a look.
So are we ready for lab grown hamburgers?
They're coming. They're probably already here.
But, you know, for argument's sake, the Washington Post reports lab grown meat is in your future and it may be healthier than the real stuff.
Scientists and businesses working full steam to produce a lab created meat claim it will be healthier than conventional meat and more environmentally friendly.
Listen, I don't know about this.
All right. Now, there's no way I can't say there's no way because I've probably already eaten lab created meat and don't even know about it.
I'm guaranteeing you this stuff is on American shelves, on American supermarket shelves right now, guaranteeing you lab created meat and the deal with this.
It sounds great, but just like everything, it's a double edged sword.
Right. Who the hell knows how this is going to interact with our body?
The jury is still out on whether or not the humans, human beings should be eating meat as it is, you know, and that's natural meat.
Imagine lab created meat.
What the hell is that going to cause?
What kind of mayhem is that going to cause?
I don't know about this, man.
The Washington port is reporting it.
Go check it out. And I'm pretty sure people are going to flock to it right now.
It's super expensive.
It's like three hundred and thirty thousand dollars a pop or something like that.
They made one and they had a taste testing and the whole deal for artificially bred hamburger.
I'm not trying to mess with this and neither should you for that matter.
Just letting you know.
All right, now let's get into our interview with the Greek, our conversation with the Greek.
This is interesting.
It's listen, bear with the audio.
It's good for a while.
Then it starts getting choppy and then it's good again.
But you can still get the gist of it and you can still take the good information, take good notes as usual.
There's a lot of it here.
And I got to tell you, man, this this turned from an interview to a lecture really quickly.
I, I was not ready for this.
It's the best way I can describe what happened with the Greek.
But it was so interesting for me to sit down and interview this guy and talk to this guy and kind of pick his brain.
So I'm sure you guys are going to get something out of it.
Go look him up.
He gives his information during the video, during the interview, I should say, so you guys can take it down and go look up what Greek speak is.
Go see his website, his radio show.
It's definitely interesting stuff.
This guy's a philosopher, man, of a modern day philosopher.
We get into the meaning of words and how they affect society today.
We get into the human body and what its purpose here is.
We get into a lot of things, a lot of esoteric things, a lot of things that people would call fringe.
But that's what it's all about, right?
Right here on the infinite fringe.
Let's get ready to dive into the murky waters.
With the Greek.
King or the queen or some kind of position, it's a social rank, but for the servants, but when you're on your own and you got skills like and you have mastership, you're called master.
Here's an example.
Remember the Bruce Wayne, Batman and all that?
Yeah. Remember Alfred?
Yeah, definitely.
Mr. Wayne or what did he call him?
Master.
Master. Yeah, you're right.
Master Wayne.
Yeah. Yeah.
If you look at the old, yeah, there's just these little points in there.
So what's on your mind?
Are we are we ready to do maybe something on a podcast?
Yep. I am actually recording right now because you were dropping you were dropping a little bit of knowledge there and I wanted to record that and I got it.
So this is the infinite fringe.
It's the name of the podcast.
And you are the Greek, which is super cool.
I'm a big fan.
Um, on you, you just you just redid your website.
I see.
Yeah, the one that's a courtesy site.
Like, you know, when you're working on something and you meet somebody in the street and they say, well, I do X, Y, and Z, you know, like you got a card.
And if you don't have a card, you look unprepared, you know?
Yeah.
Remember those days if you're old enough?
Well, now if you you know, so well, you know, I do some radio, you can hear it on.
Well, what's your website?
Well, I don't have a website.
You look unprepared, right?
So that's the only reason it's there just has archives.
But 80 hours of archives, you could turn your your brain or brain you're using, hopefully inside out like a sock.
Most of the stuff keeps being repeated, just like you repeat the third grade.
If you don't know what one plus one equals two or ABC or D, you'll be left back.
And that's why I don't go forward.
And I'll talk about grading, how it's so degrading that they do that.
But I'm using it as a metaphor.
I'd like to speak about more.
There's much more to speak of.
I've only spoken about a handful of things, but and it's just not time yet.
Well, you have you have an open you have an open forum here to talk about whatever it is you wish.
But when I logged into your site today and it says discover the obvious about the past, the present and things to come.
I thought I found that ultra interesting.
You mind elaborating on that?
Oh, easy.
Well, you know, first of all, you know, let's just you're always in the past or the future.
I know everyone says you ever hear these new age idiots and I use terms like idiot and moron, but not as a pejorative or as a put down.
I use it as an accurate term because it's actually a medical term.
You know, now the majority of the people that look at this stuff about alternative media trying to get out of the box, even though there is no box, they'll find out.
They hear about you're in the moment, right?
You hear that be in the moment.
It's that's an impossibility because of the fraction of time you're ready.
Let's capture the moment.
You ready?
Three, two, one.
Did you get did you get it?
Okay.
So you're either you're either discussing it in the future or you're discussing about in the past.
You could never perceive it as it's actually happening and which you see.
So the present would be the condition that, you know, how are you?
I'm feeling fine.
Or how are you?
My tooth hurts.
I have a stomachache, right?
That's the present.
The past are things that have come.
And of course, that doesn't need much explanation because pretty much everything you've told about the past is a lie straight up.
Whether you're patriotic about of winning a war, which you lost and you were told you won or the history of mankind or the history of the animals or the history of some ship, it's all a lie.
Now, the other thing about talking about things to come in order to be to have mastership and to properly navigate, you have to know some elements of the future.
Airline pilots do it all the time.
Everybody gets on the plane.
They bought a ticket to go somewhere and we don't know where we're going to be in two hours.
Bullshit.
We're going to we know where we're going to be in two hours and we're going to make sure we navigate that we get there.
Why? Because it was predetermined before we even stepped foot in the plane.
You see, and that's how I always describe free will.
This ties in with humanity at large.
You know, you have free will to do whatever you want.
Just like if you're seven billion people on a cruise ship going from London, London to New York, everyone's going from London to New York.
But while you're on the cruise ship, you can lay in the cabin, take a nap, go to the theater, go have dinner, go to the video game, whatever, you know, play skeet, go on the deck, whatever, whatever.
You get the picture. That's the free will.
But what I like to discuss is where the ship is going.
So you asked me about time and I told you how to build a watch.
What else you got?
Where is the ship going?
Oh, well, there's some metaphor here.
Humanity. You're a you're a you're a product.
Humanity is a product.
It's a you want to call you want to say a bioengineer, whatever.
We are part of a fair humanity.
We are. You know, look, I'm embarrassed to be called human.
And so I got to try to figure something out.
Maybe I stick with the Greek, but I am.
You guys are on your own because your behavior is so poor, you know, that I'm not better than everyone else.
I've just discerned that that's not what I want to do.
Right. Understood.
So where are you? Yeah, there's a difference.
Like people ask me all the time, is this wrong?
I say, well, it's not wrong, but it sure ain't right.
Yeah. You see what I mean?
I got you. So.
OK, so where's humanity going?
You know, if you've heard any kind of Greek speak, which you could go to uncommon radio dot com and get archives, shamelessly put that in, because that's all I you know, there's just a hundred hours plus maybe of stuff you could listen to.
Um, let's just say let's just say this.
When you look at a racetrack or an event that is circular, you know how they say things come around, you know, go around.
Right. Yeah.
What goes around comes around.
I hear. Yeah.
Yeah. That's one aspect.
But the other aspect is a circular racetrack, horse, horse racetrack, velodrome, you know, you can imagine a track where competition is being held or an event is taking place.
I want you to look at where the starting line is.
Do you see it in your mind?
Let's say that.
You imagine that.
OK, now I want you to imagine where is the finish line?
Can you tell me?
It's the same place.
Same line.
Very simple.
All the prophecies that have, you know, you know, those ancient people were so modern.
We're so smart because we've got silly phones, you know, smartphones.
I'm waiting for people to be smartphones to be stupid again.
By the way, I always talk about this when he's, you know, when he's young jokers that all they know is these little silly pods.
You know what I'd like to do?
Give them a real retro dial phone.
Remember those?
Not the push button.
The old ones, the rotary ones, you mean?
Rotary.
I watched Joker try to use that.
Anyway, I don't know if we get lascivious, but it was funnier than a monkey trying to F for football.
But anyway, let's just go.
But let's go back to the to where you're ending.
Basically, mankind, even in the in the total garbage education system, I mean, education, I'm not talking about what the common oafs and the common people
get. I'm talking about Ph.D.
graduate, the university idiots.
You know, it's horrible what they're doing, because, look, I tell people, if you've got more than eighth grade education, you got irreparable damage.
You hear people, alternative media.
Oh, I got this guest.
He's a Ph.D.
Oh, geez, I got to turn it off.
I got to turn it off.
That guy's that guy's got serious damage.
It's a joke.
And a Ph.D.
in indoctrination is what you mean.
Well, if you ever listen to all the stuff I got a Ph.D.
in studying the asshole of a Moroccan housefly, you know, I mean, they got.
It's just it's a joke.
The whole thing is a cosmic joke.
I talk about pranking and joking.
You know, the thing is, it's been outfitted in a way that you believe that it should be whatever.
That's why. OK, let's go back to how things end.
OK, even in the bullshit education system, they tell you everything started in Mesopotamia region.
OK, all your ancient writs do that, too.
You know, you got a lot of these fruitcakes.
I mean, I talk a lot about breakfast cereal.
You know what I mean? Breakfast cereals, fruits, nuts and flakes.
OK, OK. So so I'll be references to that.
But a lot of people say, oh, I've read this aborigine stuff, you know, and they said the world
started in Australia or it started over here or it started over here or on the bum of a Moroccan
housefly. Oh, no one is paying any attention to what these things are really saying, you see.
So what you're going to do as a society, let me there's something called the gods.
Laurel, you will never only in religion.
They talk about God or in literature, the legal society.
It's a hiding. There is no such thing as God singular, plural.
And within that plurality, there's a hierarchy and the gods have a God.
And he is the one that is referred to as the most high.
OK, that's why that's why, you know, we get into.
Well, let me give you an example.
They're coming back, but they're coming back in a way that it's different this time.
And here's the interesting thing.
No, I'm not crazy. I have invisible friends and all this other stuff has nothing to do with
belief. And we can talk about belief.
What's interesting is when man does battle with man, you know, he softens up the opponent
first, brings him down, then he comes in with the kill shot.
Right. You know, typically when the gods do war with man, they prop you up to your highest
possible level technologically, socially, economically, judicially, everything.
And then they come in and they do the kill shot.
Why? So you can never say later you had an excuse.
Oh, well, we were down in a low situation.
We weren't doing so well.
And you guys came in with that kind of force.
No way. So what you're going to be experiencing and starting in about a year or two is the
formation or the precursor, not the formation, but the precursor.
Everything needs to be put together for the formation of what I call a Middle East Union.
It's not like the EU.
It's different because the EU is basically Europe united under Germany.
That's what the National Socialist Party wanted to do.
What you're going to see is a little different.
You're going to have basically no specific headquarters, but everything in the world,
economic, judicial, religious, political, education, entertainment, scientific, you get
the point, is going to be headquartered there.
OK, it's kind of hard to see that right now.
It's irrelevant, though.
OK, now this requires a certain amount of belief.
Now, why? I'm not asking.
I'm not convincing. I'm not selling.
I'm telling. But here's the thing.
You heard that term belief.
Belief means you have good knowledge about something that is going to happen.
And when that thing doesn't happen, that was a that was a bad belief, wasn't it?
But if it does happen, that was a good belief.
So we ask people, do you believe in God?
It's like, OK, that's the stupidest question you can.
That's like the typical human surface dwelling earth inhabitant moron question.
Don't answer that if someone asks you that.
Don't that because that's like, you know, I got mental damage.
Glad I didn't ask that question.
Yeah. But what I'm saying, though, it's that's a metaphor.
The whole thing, of course, you're going to ask.
And of course, you're going to be asked.
Yeah, because what are you going to do?
I mean, this is this is the culture you're living.
It's crap. No one knows anything.
And they don't want to know anything.
That's that's the hard part now.
So you see, you see these all these things are connected.
All these things are, you know, I've done some archives
and we've covered every aspect of being a surface to earth inhabitant.
You know, like everything is 100 percent input.
You know, you think your brain is your the thoughts that you are occurring are yours.
Well, you take they're not they're being the human.
There's nothing in the head.
You could even look at the scientific research.
They're afraid to talk about it.
But all I see is neurons flashing.
They don't know where the memory is.
They don't know.
You know, they know if they cut out certain parts of the brain.
You lose certain faculties, right?
Hey, but look, remember the old days you took a TV out of the
out of the closet, you plug it in and it's just you turn on,
just rasper that snow and you like, oh, get a clothes hanger, stick it in here.
Boom. We got picture.
Why? Because the picture is in the clothes hanger.
No, it's an antenna receiver.
Yeah.
You see someone on the beach with a little radio with a jazz.
You think you can open the box and there's going to be a little jazz band playing in there?
No. Right.
So this is the this is what happens, though, when you think about the brain.
I've ever heard of, you know, once you learn how to ride a bike,
you never forget how to do how to walk.
Yeah. It's like riding a bike.
Yeah. Yeah.
You're taking it for granted.
These thoughts are not your own.
Dreams are not your own dreams or you're being plugged by spiritual entities.
That's why, you know, if you start learning the truth and you address it, they go away.
This is, you know, the other thing we discuss on the archive
that I've had various collaborations is the human body.
I call it the container because you're made up of three things.
The spirit, the soul and the body.
By the way, you go ask anybody to define soul and spirit.
Watch what happens.
Oh, boy. Talk about tying the mental faculties into a knot.
Well, I heard you talk about this previously.
Can you explain that to us?
Sure. Like, for example, it's very simple.
And because you've been polluted and corrupted as a society
and which is possible, by the way, but it's very simple.
Whenever you see the PSY prefix, PSY like psychiatry,
psychology, psychotic, psychopath, psycho, right?
All this PSY.
That means a spirit in the Greek psyche is the spirit.
So when you see a psychiatrist, he's really saying he's a spiritualist.
Do you really want to see what a Ph.D. is worth?
Ask him what some of us what do you do?
I'm a psychiatrist. You're a spiritualist.
Watch what happens.
Good guy. You'll see that he's really operating on a third grade level.
And he won't go beyond that.
OK, now, when you hear the term pneumatic with a PNU prefix,
pneumonia, pneumatic, you know, it's funny, you know, PNU, the P is silent.
Yeah. OK, that's pneuma, which means the soul.
And it's in your nostrils, in your breath.
So, for example, if you're breathing air,
if you're a living being that breathes air, all of your souls are interchangeable.
This is a far stretch from what the way it's been used,
because you got to realize that the mind and the culture
and the tradition and the society, all the religions, all the cultures,
all the universities are being controlled by an adversarial power.
Right. It's not like Hollywood, you know, when someone adversarial
just means if you say good, they say bad.
If you say ugly, they say pretty the opposite.
And they just keep kind of keep you away from what's going on. Right.
So back to the soul.
Every look, for example, if you have a dog in the room, he's breathing.
He's got a soul.
And if you if the dog drowned, you could pull him out of the water.
If he's not breathing, you could administer resuscitation to the dog.
I know it sounds funny, but it can be done. Right. Yeah.
Right now, you put your soul into that dog's body.
And once he started breathing autonomously again, now he got a soul again.
You ever see a baby being born when it comes?
That's kind of gray and pale.
When it takes its first breath, it goes flesh tone within a few seconds.
All right. That's when the soul goes into the body.
OK, now how people are using it is irrelevant.
I tell people, go look up. Are you a nice guy?
Have a nice day. You've heard that word. Nice. Go look it up.
I like to tell I don't like tell people what things mean,
because it seems like if they look it up themselves,
it's got like 70 percent more punch for some reason.
You know, the light bulb goes off for some reason.
You know, but if you go to etymology, which is the root use of words
like a dictionary, the reason they put out dictionary for all the subjects
is because they want them to behave well, like they want to say the word.
Well, diction means how you pronounce the word.
That's why when you look up a word, you got that little funny phonetic spelling,
you know, and then they give you what they tell you.
It means, you know, right now.
Addiction is there.
If you want to know words, I mean, go to etymology, e t y m o l o g y.
There's one website they hammer on on the Internet.
There's not much they they've they've shooed this away.
Put in go to the search box. Put an N.I.C.E.
Do you want you want to do that right now, maybe?
Can you do it live? Sure.
Let's do it online.
Yeah. Put in etymology, e t y m o l o g y.
And first site is Adam online and you'll see a search box
in the search box. Put in N.I.C.E.
Enter. And I want you to read off what it means according to etymologically.
You know what it you know.
And let's let's see.
Let me see.
Because I have I'm sure you I'm sure you think you're a nice guy.
Go ahead. I have online etymology dictionary.
Is that what you're talking about?
Yeah, sure. Any one of them. But go ahead.
All right. I'm in search.
And I put it in there in the search box.
What do you get? Oh, gosh.
Let me see it on the top.
You know, I got it. I got it.
No, I got it.
I'm just anxiously awaiting what this is going to be.
All right.
Oh, foolish, stupid, senseless.
That's what it means.
Nice adjective.
So so people are telling the truth, aren't they?
When they use that term, usually.
But I'm not a nice guy.
Are you I hope I hope that this is not a nice, you know, podcast.
If you know what if you know what I mean, as of as of this
as of this moment, it is no longer a nice podcast and I am no longer a nice guy.
All right. Well, put in.
You know how it's prestigious to be academic.
That's insane. Insane.
All right. That's beautiful.
OK, so you want me to look up academic now?
Yeah. Put an academic A.C.A.D.
However you want.
You have to spell it correctly and that doesn't have a spell check.
So academic and if you go past the usage of the word,
you'll find out in the middle somewhere it means it's a very long.
It gives you the history of how the word came into society also.
But if you look down there in the middle, it's it's theoretical and practical,
never leading to a conclusion.
Do you see that in there?
I don't, but I don't know exactly where you're looking at.
So it doesn't matter. I'm sure it does.
OK. When you when you say academic, they'll give you three paragraphs
of the definition somewhere in the first paragraph in the middle,
because it also shows you how the you know, when you speak English,
you know, here's the thing.
I tell people you speak English.
You got your you're about one third fluent in Greek.
You don't even know it
because English is made up of Greek, Hebrew, Latin words, right? Yeah.
You know, what's that thing hanging in the you know, it's got all the lights
in the dining room.
What do they call that?
You know, chandelier.
Well, now you speak in French.
See my point? I get you. I get you.
So English is about how the words came in to be used, where, for example,
if you look at a lot of ancient what I call the scripture or is called
the scripture, it's preserved in Hebrew and Greek.
Forget about the Bible, what you got in English.
That's not a translation. That's a version.
That's a political tool by the legal society.
Now, the reason one of the reasons why it was preserved in Hebrew and Greek
is because you don't need a dictionary for those words.
If you look at the word, it's made up of certain letters.
There are 22 letters in each alphabet.
And if you know what each letter means, you see a word.
You don't know what it means.
Well, you can you figure out the meaning by the meaning of each individual letter.
Yeah, we have that with prefixes.
You know, when you say anti-depressant, you know, the prefix anti means it's not.
You see, but imagine that every letter had a specific meaning.
You know, it's very precise, very precise.
Not English.
Let me ask you a question.
Back to the nice thing.
How did that get twisted?
You know, well, Nietzsche, Nietzsche, naive, ignorant
science is the opposite of naive science.
Wow. Which is knowledge.
Yeah. Yeah. But here's the thing.
The planet humanity went under.
If you listen to any of the archives on Greek, I called loosely Greek speak
out on common radio that you'll see that humanity went under a cosmic censorship
around 2500 years ago, around 500 or 600 BC.
You'll notice that all the public depositories
of knowledge were pulled, withdrawn.
Like, for example, you heard the the burning of the Library of Alexandria in Egypt.
You've heard that. That's around that.
That's around that time.
OK, all of your modern religions, as you see them right now,
were structured around that time.
Now I say, wait a second.
Greek Christianity and Islam. No, no, no.
Have. Their structure, right?
If anyone wants to, if you, for example, if you go to a modern Christian nation,
they were crucifixes around their neck, right? Yeah.
You can go do a search and image search right now.
If you go to images, put in a Syrian A.S.S.
Y.R.I.A. and not Syrian, a Syrian king wearing a crucifix.
And you'll see a stele, which is a a stone.
Real. If in the Museum of London, I think,
and it's an Assyrian king dated about 860 B.C.,
and he's got the modern regalia of Christianity.
All right. Because remember, there is no religion on the planet, bar none.
Doesn't matter if it's Christianity, Islam, Buddhism, Hinduism, whatever
that does anything that's in the text that they allegedly subscribe to.
I'm not saying that they should.
I'm just saying that they don't.
And here's the problem with that for the people that subscribe
to these religions, any of them.
Once they go and study the book that the religion is alleged
to to to subscribe to, what I mean by that, let me just say it for dummies.
If you say Christian or Jewish, it's the Bible.
If you say Muslim, it's the Koran.
If it's Hindu, it's the Rig Vedas or the Mahabharata on and on and on.
OK, none of those religions do or know anything
that's in any of their corresponding books.
Here's an example, just like the legal society,
lawyers don't know anything in the law books.
They just talk to you. Did you do what the judge said?
Did you do what the police said?
Well, what do you mean?
You know, they look, they search for your heart
and then they use your own words against you.
They don't know any law. Why?
Because if you're a member of the Bar Association and you study law,
you will find yourself selling used cars.
You will be disbarred.
That's a joke, too, and it's a pun.
That's interesting.
A lot of lawyers have been disbarred recently
for trying to do what I just mentioned,
and they always end up being used car salesmen or new car salesmen.
It's a funny thing. OK.
Back to the religions.
All of these things started around that time.
Even the legal society started around that time in ancient Greece.
So this is a time where man was cut off.
Why were they censored?
No knowledge of pre-flood man.
Boom. That's it. The flood.
You know, they call it the mythical flood.
Every day, every society.
Isn't it funny how every culture has its little flood myth?
Yeah. Doesn't matter which called Native American.
Anywhere you go to Asia, anywhere, anywhere.
OK, why? All right.
Now, at that sense,
your ship time at what happened at the flood and prior was cut off. Why?
That's something that will be answered in the future.
Great specificity.
And I always answer it.
And that's very simple.
It's the frog in the pot.
If you heat up the pot too fast, the frog jumps out, right?
OK. Now, when you can't just throw the frog right back in there,
you got to start all over again.
Yeah. Got to ease them into it.
If you knew your origin, you wouldn't be here now.
You would already want to jump off this rock.
So you have to spend seven thousand seven millennia on this rock.
Six thousand actually ended in 1998,
you know, undisturbed as a number.
Here's the thing.
When it comes to creation,
even if you read about evolutionists, they use the word design
and creation a lot in there.
Can't escape it because your law comes from your God.
You know, when you're a child, your parents have that position.
You know, it's funny when you bring this to an atheist, they say,
well, I don't have a God.
Greek, well, that's easy.
Do you believe in the laws of the state? Yes, I do.
Well, OK, well, the state is your God.
And April 1st is your holiday.
And not only that, they even have a goddess for you.
It's called justice.
It's the revived goddess religion.
And she's blindfolded with scales.
That's got nothing to do with law.
It never did. It never will.
But because it's a God, it actually, you know,
they personify it as where you get law from.
It's the revived goddess.
What do people know about the revived goddess religion?
Nothing. Go ahead and do some research on that.
What people know about it? Zero.
There's nothing on it on the Internet.
You'll have a couple of breakfast cereal type say, oh, the divine feminine,
divine feminineness in that, right?
The same with the legal society and the money system.
Very important credit system.
There is no debt, by the way.
Anybody that tells you that you're a slave and there's debt is
and all that is just in that M.O., you know, moron category.
But, you know, you spell you got to spell more with a capital R
because you got to emphasize it a little.
It's a credit based economy.
It's like when you go to a casino.
You can't go into the pocket and go to the blackjack table.
You got to get the chips. Yeah.
Right. You got to get when you when you're born,
they give you a birth certificate with a credit line, but they can't tell you.
All you got to do is sign the name because then no one's going to go to work
when you get a utility bill every month.
Doesn't matter what utility that that you can't pay that.
That's just telling you how much of the credit that you have that they're using.
But they're going to cut it off if you don't act on it,
because could you imagine your average surface
dwelling earth and having found out that everything was paid for
through the birth certificate and the credit line they have?
And, you know, everybody leaves the house and all the lights
and the water's running, say, hey, why don't you shut it off?
Hey, screw you. It's paid for.
Can you elaborate on that?
Yeah, very simple.
When you hear about the legal society, the governments, the banks,
you know, you know, forensics are forensic when you look really close for evidence,
you know, when the police show up, they can't find anything.
Forensic crew comes and says, guys, go get some donuts.
We're going to find out what happened here.
Yeah. Right. Because it's not evident.
OK, when you do forensic auditing, forensic accounting
and the history of the country, the United States and most countries,
the government is in bank, went into bankruptcy
and is now being held in receivership. OK.
You familiar with that? Anybody could look that up.
Very simple. OK.
Let's say a country is like a fixture, like a business.
Have you heard of multigenerational deli or business?
It's been around for generations.
Everybody likes it. They use it like a business.
OK, well, they they they they go into
into the red and other creditors come in.
They're ready to shut down the business and they go into bankruptcy.
OK, that most people have an idea of what that means, but they really don't.
OK, now when they now they say, hey, look, instead of shutting you down
and liquidating you, we're going to put you in receivership.
So all you guys are call yourself owners and take the profit.
You're going to go on a little salary and every day we take the whole till.
OK, so they leave the shingle up, you know, they leave the sign up,
the business stays there, but it's changed under new management.
Right. That's receivership.
And they keep it there because it's better to do that than to liquidate it
for some reason.
So all of the governments in the world that have credit right now
are under receivership.
Now, you cannot operate lawfully, so you have to be given a credit line.
Just like when you go to a casino, not a line of credit,
a credit line.
And all you got to do is sign the name when you get a loan, a credit card,
anything, anytime, anywhere there.
They these institutions that have cage codes,
CAG, which is corporate and government entity codes,
can access credit from the Treasury.
You can't. Why? Because of human nature.
You know, how many times have you heard of like a golden ghetto, you know?
No, I have no idea what that is. Tell me.
OK, golden ghettos, the rich people neighborhood,
you know, the five million dollar homes with the 11 11 car garage.
OK. All right. Or eight million dollar home, let's say.
I mean, there's no dollar, by the way, to credit units.
All right. So some poor slob over here knows he could go to the bank
and sign and get a house for.
Twenty million, you know, let him do that.
Just because he's got a sign, that's it.
The whole thing part. Why? Because of human nature.
If you are familiar with the Gene Roddenberry Star Trek's,
when they bring someone
the past into their world in the Star Trek thing, they say,
what do you guys use for money? We don't use money anymore.
We all realize we have to do what we need to do.
We don't need it anymore. Yeah.
Yeah. This is you're in that you've been in that since the 30s.
But you're not going to get it.
You're going to get it later, way later when you're in a different position
and then won't matter again so much.
And what is money?
A lot of these breakfast cereal types are like, oh, money doesn't exist.
Bullshit. Money is portable land.
That's why it's always gold or silver or something of high value,
because in a perfect society, you get everything that you need from the land,
whether it's minerals, building materials, food, on and on.
But if you're going to travel, you can't take it with you, can you?
So you have to take a representation of what wealth you have with you.
That's why money is what? Portable land for exchange.
That's all it is.
Here's the thing. I'm just going to digress.
I know we're all over the place.
You got to you got to really hold on.
I like taking people for a ride if they're listening.
I want you. I want you to go everywhere you want to go.
Just go ahead and do it.
Everything is attached.
You know what? Parallel processing like supercomputers,
a parallel process, not serial processing. Right. OK.
You're doing it all the time.
When you get up, when you're let's say you're talking to someone
and you get up to walk across the room and you scratch the head and all that.
You're doing so many functions right there
that someone who designs robots or computers will have a headache.
They couldn't. You know, it's amazing how many just balancing.
OK, standing up, learning how to walk.
Tremendous amount of functionality.
But you've been shut down cognitively on a social, economic
quote unquote, religious, spiritual.
You've all been shut down.
Humanity has been shut down for twenty five hundred years. OK.
Now, here's the other aspect of it.
What's great about it is you're going to be opened up here coming soon,
but for the wrong reason, just so you could be propped up.
You're being set up. Why?
Because you're in the credits right now.
As a society, what does that mean?
Greek, what does that mean?
You ever see you?
Let's say we want to shoot a two to two to shoot a two hour film.
Do we go out and buy exactly two hours worth of film?
What do we need to buy two hours and ten minutes?
Because it's credits in the end. Right.
So that's where you're in right now.
You want to talk about the human body real quick?
Yeah. Let's jump around the container.
Yeah. You ever you ever notice when you put
you ever notice when you put your fingers or your the feet
you're using in water, they shrivel up? Yeah.
Yeah. You ever notice what?
Because what the skin is a soft membrane, isn't it?
Let me let me you know, you ever you ever put a piece of meat
or some food in one of those Ziploc bags?
I don't mean to use the bag and you put a draw vacuum on it.
What happens is a puff up when you suck on it a little vacuum
or does it shrivel up just like the fingers and toes, right?
Yeah, it shrivels up. Mm hmm.
Yeah. So how the hell do you have blood pressure?
How that what is that thing?
They call them pressure in the body.
You notice if you go research the intestines
or any of the lungs or anything like that, go to anatomy books.
The Internet's pretty easy.
Show me where it's porous, how anything passes through.
They've got everyone convinced that you're a filter bag.
You're in a complete vacuum.
That's why when you cut the skin, it takes
the vacuum has to be broken before any blood comes through.
All right. Yeah.
You know, it's interesting about they got this thing called the common cold.
You know, you know, it's interesting.
They blame all these diseases or whatever on bacteria
when the wintertime comes around.
Doesn't that kind of logic render all refrigeration useless?
Because the reason we get refrigeration is to put things in the cold
so they don't break.
So bacteria are inactive, right?
Yeah. So it doesn't it doesn't spoil.
Right. So how come coal people get the cold when it gets cold out,
when it's more sterile than the summertime?
You ever walk down the city street in the winter?
Do you mind the garbage smell if they don't pick it up for a week?
No. You ever walk down the summer, a hot summer
when they don't pick up the garbage, what it smells like?
Yeah, you're right. See? Yeah. Yeah. Why?
So how so it's totally in your face, in your face.
We're going to tell you the opposite of what's going on,
that the cold season is coming and you're getting sick from bacteria
and these little critters.
What the hell these little critters do to you?
You got to blame them.
Leave them alone.
They're so small. You got to pick on them.
Go pick on someone your own size, like the devil in the white lab
coat down the street with the M.D. up on.
Look, this is what I tell people.
You know, when I convey myself around town, I got to like GPS
where the medical offices and the hospitals are, you know,
just a little medical office that says Dr.
M.D. on the outside.
I got to I got to locate those places before I travel.
Why? Why is that?
Because I know when I'm going down the street,
there's going to be one of these medical establishments
or a medical office down the street.
I have to slow down and put those ear protection things in the ear.
You know, those little or some wads of cotton.
Yeah, because if I don't do that, the quacking is so loud.
I go deaf for a week.
My ears are ringing for a week.
That's how loud the quacking is.
You're a comedian, aren't you?
Right. If I don't put the cotton in, you know,
I lose hearing for a week.
That's how bad it is right now for me.
Yeah. All right.
I mean, OK, well, is it I don't know.
It is what's sad. You got to cry.
All right. You want to cry about it?
You want to laugh about it?
No, no, no. I'd rather laugh about it, please.
I don't I don't feel like crying today.
Yeah. So here's it.
Could it be that when you when you live in a cause is the short
and long and short of it, it's about quality of life.
OK. All right.
When you're living in the cold climate or a cold season,
let's say, right, they got the little children,
you know, they get the sniffles, you know, in the winter in the northeast.
And could it be that when you eat something that's been grown
in the tropics, it adjusts the body chemistry to living in the tropics,
like thinner blood and different metabolic rates?
And when you eat that tropical fruit in the cold, it changes
the body chemistry to adjust to the tropics.
And now you're out of sync.
That makes sense. Yeah.
That's why these idiots, they tell you, but vitamin C is good for cold.
Nobody even knows what vitamin C is.
It comes from oranges. Sure, it does.
You know, the only way you could realize there's a ascorbic acid
or anything like that in oranges, if you pick it,
pull it apart, juice it, dry the juice into a crystal and burn it.
Do you know that every time you do a process like that, you're changing it?
Yeah, you change, you change the structure of it.
Of course. Yeah. Yeah.
To say there's vitamin C in oranges, it's like, wait a second.
I need a piece of paper.
And you go up to a tree and you start scratching the bark.
Are you joking?
What are you? What's wrong with you people?
You have to change that tree so much to make paper that it no longer.
Hey, I got a better one.
Take a piece of paper, put it in a glass of water.
You expect it to grow roots in about a week? Of course.
OK, I've tried it many times.
It does. OK, you get roots coming out of a piece of paper.
Clearly not. No, no, this is this is what the associations
that people are making in your face every day and that none of it makes.
You got to I mean, you've got to just really say what? OK.
Is there any blame? No.
Well, there is a cosmic force that is to be blamed, let's say.
But can you blame these morons? No.
You set yourself apart from them.
OK, and you help them, you work with them.
It's the other thing I said.
You got cosmic forces that are monitoring the earth, both good and evil.
That's why whenever you hear about these people who come up with genuine,
you know, they've been given genuine knowledge.
And when they go out in public
and they say, we got to do this to make the world a better place.
They always fail.
They're either they're either killed or they end up, you know,
living a life of poverty, living in the park, you know,
eating out of garbage cans or whatever. Why?
Because the malevolent forces don't want to see.
Mankind do better.
And they and they pinch these individuals,
but also the benevolent forces don't want to see mankind do better
because they have to do better the way they have to do lawfully
before the kill shots come.
You see, so back to the the body, this is all tied in together.
What you're going to discover in the future
is that your body is under a slight vacuum condition.
All living things have a vacuum condition.
That's why you want a cool head and warm feet.
But wait a second.
I thought he's supposed to rise and it's supposed to go down.
That's only when you have degeneration,
when you have formative forces at work, all natural living things,
just like the weather.
You notice when it's hot in the valley, it's cold up on the mountain. Yeah.
That's why I start off.
I do some radio and I say, well,
listen, I called the physics department today
and I called the air conditioning guys today and I asked them,
how many people called yesterday about
designing air conditioning systems for houses, boats and cars and whatever
that has a rarefied rising cold and a densifying
descending heat like the human body or like the earth.
And the physicists or the air conditioning, the HVAC tech is none.
So I hang up the phone and I say, OK, there's a bunch of idiots on this planet.
Because of that, it's so obvious, isn't it? Yeah.
So so that's why I think discovering the obvious is very important.
Wow. And it's right there in our faces nine times out of 10.
It's just you know what it is, Greek coming coming from
from a layman, let's say.
It's the words have been
changed to a point where we don't know the definitions of them anymore.
So anything can be said to us and we'll we'll believe it's one thing
when it's really another.
Hmm. But when you do believe in something, it has to be based on an act
or an event that is either to take place
immediately in the near future or later on.
You always have to view it that way.
You can't be lazy. Well, I believe in this and I'm good.
The way that people run their lives because they've been pranked by their parents.
But, you know, you're not just being pranked by the doctors
and the attorneys and the, you know, all. Hello.
Because all. Comments are representational, believe it or not.
OK, but anyway, and I'll get into that, like even if you look at a really bad
government when they come.
When I take people and throw them in camps, who did that?
They got people from Mars to do that or their own people.
Their own people, all governments are.
Relational, don't buy anything else other than that, even a monarchy,
a king won't sit on a throne for one hour if he's not representing the people.
Now he could rep now maybe, but he has to represent enough people
that are willing to do his way.
Well, they put on uniforms, they got heavier ordinance,
they got camp, you know, whatever, or they could go the other way.
Right. So the thing is about either way you look at it,
it's it's about pranking at this point.
But the thing is, you've been pranked since you were in the crib
as a child in swaddling clothes by your own parents.
Santa Claus, Tooth Fairy, they lie to you about everything.
Why? To prepare you for all the lies you're going to get when you're an adult.
Think about it. But is it good?
Well, is it bad? Well, let's just do it this way.
Is it bad? I don't know, but it definitely ain't good.
OK, I see your point. All right.
Because, I mean, you know, a lot of people get a lot of enjoyment
out of something like that, you know, like pranksters do.
I mean, the person being pranked, you know, like I enjoyed it
when when I was lied to about Santa Claus, you know.
Well, you didn't know better.
So there's a lot of doctrine written about don't corrupt the children
into that kind of stuff.
Well, how about this?
If if you were shooting up heroin at two years old,
do you think you would feel pretty good?
Of course you would.
But should you be doing that?
Absolutely not. It's a hell of a way to put it.
What do you think of artificial technology?
Well, it's all artificial.
Let me give you an example.
Let's go back a few years ago.
There was all these idiots were doing a craze about the moon is artificial, right?
Because it doesn't orbit the way you know, whatever.
Yeah. By the way, the Earth doesn't.
You don't see the backside of the moon.
Very simple, because it's locked into Earth's orbit.
Duh. It doesn't have its own orbit.
These people, I mean, anyway, so
so the moon is artificial, blah, blah, blah.
It's a planet. I say, wait a second.
OK, is there a creator? Of course, there's a creator.
OK, well, then that means he's an artificer.
Anything the artificer does is artificial, isn't it?
Yes, it's all artificial.
It's all made and they have like this moment of clarity
and, you know, like the flat earth or the black goo or this and that.
I mean, get a life, people, you know, watch it.
You do have a life.
But, you know, here's you know why?
Another reason why things are like this, because you could go to the archives
and hear all the things.
One of the things that I do say, though, that I haven't been saying frequently
is that you need to know the character of a certain being or whatever.
If you're going to interact with it, you may not ever know all about it,
but you're going to know enough to identify it.
All right. What I mean is like we can all say we know what a bear is,
you know, because we know he's big, furry, could be dangerous.
We see him and so we've seen a lot, but we really don't know what a bear is.
Unless you sit down and have an eight hour conversation with him,
you're not going to really know, but you know enough about him
when you say that we know what a bear is. Right. OK.
Well, when we talk about the gods, we don't know a lot about them,
but we know enough about them from the Holy Ritz
and all these other things we've seen.
But what we do know about them that take this when they create,
they create in very, very large numbers.
You ever look out in the sky at night, tons of stars.
I get it. Yeah.
Ever look at how many grains of sand on a beach, how many cells in a plant
or the body, how many?
OK, so don't be impressed by the big numbers
because that's part of their character.
Like if I say, you know, here comes this bear and he comes in, you know,
I was like, wow, he's so big.
I said, yeah, man, that's what bears are. They're big, man. That's right.
Look at his claws. They got big, you know, big claws.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, that's right. He's a bear.
You know, we know that about him already.
What do we know about the gods?
For sure. When they create, they create in very large numbers.
So when you hear about everybody, give you an example
where I'm tying this into.
I was looking for some like bug lotion.
I went to a health food store, right?
OK. You know, when the bugs don't bite, you know. Yeah.
And the lady comes up to me, she goes, this is the one that everybody buys.
And I'm like, oh, that's the one I don't want.
And she goes, why? She goes, you do retail, don't you know?
Don't you see all the people that come in here?
Do they look like they can make good decisions?
She looked at me like I was nuts, you know, right?
I don't want that one if everyone wants that one. Why?
Because it's very, very large numbers.
There's always a very, very, very, very small group of people
that are held on this planet for every generation.
What do you hear in the media, both alternative mainstream or whatever?
Oh, everybody's so wonderful.
Oh, everybody could do what they want.
Oh, if they only had a chance.
But if you ever deal with a university person,
a law enforcement, a legal person, medical, what did they tell you?
The opposite. You got to do what everybody else is doing.
Right. It's the opposite what they're what they're right.
Yeah. Most people.
This is this is the truth about all people.
Now, how are you going to separate them is up to you.
Everybody takes up some kind of volume or space, don't they?
You know, you could do the Archimedes method where you
you put some liquid in a tank, make a line, don't come in there.
And the amount of liquid that it goes up, that's how much the body volume is.
Right. Because they're not cubes.
They're not that easy to measure. Right.
You do the Archimedean method of displacement to figure out the volume,
because so this way, you know accurately how much space someone takes up.
And then the other thing when you're alive is you give off heat.
Most people that have ever come to this planet
and will come to this planet in the near future are space heaters.
They take up space and they give off heat until they die.
Then they're cold.
But you have you know, you have smartphones.
You got smart space heaters, too, right?
You got the smart space heat, right?
They do a couple of funny things, you know.
It'd be us. I don't know.
You know, people say, Greek, who do you think you are?
So who do you say I am?
It's none of your business.
I'm saying this stuff.
I'm saying this stuff because nobody else is.
What's wrong with you people?
Look, I know what's wrong with you people.
Do you know what's wrong?
So, you know, so you could live a life more of efficiency.
Look, I throw this other little thing in here.
September means seven.
Yeah. Octo means eight like octagon.
Nova means nine and decim means 10.
How do you guys get off as writing?
December is 12. It means 10 every year.
How do you get off as writing November 11? It means nine.
How do you get off writing October 10?
It means eight every year.
You get four chances a year and you fail miserably every year.
Oh, but Greek, everybody up with the everybody.
Here we go again.
You're not going to change it.
It will change with dynamicism that you have never imagined.
You meaning surface dwelling earth inhabitants.
So so there's many again, there's many, many, many levels in it.
The crux of the matter is that I always like to set yourself apart from it.
Don't change it.
You know, look, there's many, many.
There's a better life that's coming that look.
There's no such thing as reincarnation, plurality or right.
You will be brought back, but no one has been brought back.
You will not find that in anything memorialized in ancient history.
That kind of stuff has been made up by the Gnostics and all these other idiots
around the 2000 years ago.
And it still follows through some, you know, Hindu jokes and stuff like that.
Right. All right. So explain Lazarus.
I heard you explain it at some to a certain degree.
But alias are OK.
Lazarus was was brought.
Well, he was he was brought back to life, but he wasn't given a new body.
OK. You know, there were many people in ancient history
that were brought back to life.
But that's not what I'm talking about, where you're no longer subject to death.
Even though he was brought back to life, he was still subject to death.
So how about Enoch?
Same, he was killed and he was he was.
If you look at the now, here's the thing.
When we discuss anything like this.
Oh, I don't want to. Oh, that's the Bible, man.
No, I'm not religious. Right.
You know, when someone says that, by the way, let me translate what they're saying.
Is it so disgusting what religion has done with that?
I don't want to hear anything that has anything to do with it.
Right. If you look at the script, he was and then he was not.
Now, there's good. Here's an interesting thing.
And that's if you want to stay on that topic.
But whatever you want in the future, you're going to notice.
I've been saying this for almost a decade.
More and more people are going to take interest in the Bible and that kind of talk.
But none of it's going to be accurate.
But their interest is going to increase.
You see, I've discussed this. Why?
Because the biblical text, not King James and in the beginning,
God create the heavens and the earth. It doesn't say that.
Sorry, folks, not even close.
There's twenty seven thousand critical mistakes in the book.
That's not even worth
looking at. It's not worth admonishing as anything or whatever.
Just leave it alone and go to the language of preservation if you're interested.
But if you want to communicate with the people that do know it,
you have to know it also. Right. Yeah.
So but what's interesting is to go back to the gods.
They have a hierarchy just like man does.
You've got the street sweeper and then you've got the king atop. Right.
The thing is, their kingdom is lateral.
Man's kingdom is vertical. You know, street sweepers at the bottom.
The king's at the top. That's why they say, oh, you think you're better?
They're higher than me. Right.
Well, so the spiritual king is lateral.
You got inner circle, outer circle, left hand, right hand.
You notice that? Yeah.
It's kind of like with Eve. She came out of the side of Adam.
They say a rib came out of a student, come out of his feet or his head,
like in the Greek myths, Medusa, you know, one of the goddesses. Right.
You know, give a little bit more since we're on the comedy thing.
This I borrowed this from an old skit.
And I don't know who wrote it. It was all in the family skit.
Do you remember that? No.
With Adam and Eve, the lady, she worked at a well, this lady comes in
and she's worked at a warehouse as a forklift operator.
And she said they got some new hires and they started them at a few
few dollars an hour more. And she's been there for five years.
You know, and there's no explanation she got for that.
And the guy says, well, look, these are guys are getting paid more.
And even though they have less experience, she goes, that's right.
He goes, well, that's easy. She says, well, he says, that's simple to see,
because when God created God created man, but when he made woman,
he made her from a rib and you see a rib is a cheaper cut.
But anyway, so so so it has nothing that's a bad joke,
because actually the reason I brought this up is to throw a little dig in there.
If you look at all of the ancient texts, even the Koran and other things,
women are held in a very, very high position.
The religions and the patriarchy you see in the world, which is atheist or pagan.
All the religions are pagan by far.
That's when someone says I'm a pagan.
I'm like, well, that means you're Christian, Muslim, Hindu or Buddhist
or one of the main.
There's no, oh, these guys say they're pagan.
Now, that's just a fashion statement, like in the 70s,
where they wore the polyester and the funky haircuts.
These people today that say they're pagan, they don't know anything.
They you know what makes them pagan?
They wear sunglasses at night.
They get a couple of funky tattoos and they let the hair grow a certain way.
And they paint their fingernails and toenails black.
That makes them that's just the fat, stupid stuff that people do.
But in essence, the people are so far removed from any reality of the gods
and the hierarchy of the gods, which is based on the most powerful.
You know, here's the thing.
You know what makes the most high God the most high God?
I'm just going to answer rhetorically.
He's not subject to death.
Hello, people.
Gods are subject to death.
Go look at your ancient history.
Well, actually don't because you won't.
Here's the other thing.
I never recommend people go read the Bible or these ancient things.
You ever hear a lot of these religious types.
You got to read your Bible every day.
You ever hear that?
You got to go study this.
Right.
You hear that all the time.
Or if you go to.
Yeah.
But you know, you'll never.
Did you ever hear me recommend you go read anything?
Why?
Never.
Because you're not going to understand a dang thing in it.
So why would I tell you to go read it?
So how do we get including me?
I'm just saying we.
When the time comes.
Right now it's a lot of work.
It's kind of like, you know, when people go out and they want a new house.
How many times have you heard that?
I want a new house.
I want to move.
You know, let's say a new apartment or I got to get a new car or I got it.
I got to get, you know, I got one now.
I want another one.
How many times do they think they're going to go and build it from scratch?
Or how might they get it pre-made already?
In this society, it's pre-made.
I mean, yeah, there are people that build houses.
There are people that build cars.
You look at the custom stuff.
But no, what I'm saying is the majority of the people.
Oh, I need a new pair of shoes.
You're going to go make some shoes.
No, you're going to go get them pre-made.
This is going to come to you pre-made starting in the next seven years.
Now, that sounds exciting.
Like that sounds promising.
It is.
But remember that as you promised this perfect society, you're only a few years away from,
you know, 90% of the people will not be here right now.
If you put this is not doom and gloom, by the way.
This is real talk.
This is from mature, non-carnal minds.
Because anytime you talk about doom and gloom in man's history, it sounds like, oh, yeah,
I could fit.
I could see it.
Bullshit.
What I'm talking about is right now, if you put 10 people in a room, only one of you is
going to be alive in 15 years.
Yeah.
That's very important to know.
Let's say you got a two year old.
So, you know, he's got a life expectancy, 90, 10% life expectancy is going to go beyond
17 because two plus 15 is 17.
So that's what I tell parents all the time.
All right.
So if he's going to be around until 17, be around until 17, what would you have done
different or better in your life up until you were 17?
And then you don't make the child do that, but just let them know.
I mean, right now, saving for college.
I mean, this is ridiculous.
First of all, the interesting part is the majority of the people will not know as we're
going into the future.
This is a time, interesting.
Talk now, now in the next few years, because in the future, when this new world order is
put in place, when I say new world order, I'm not discussing the stuff that's in now
that you hear about.
Illuminati is going to get us in Rockefeller and Rothschilds and all these Illuminati's,
you know, families.
No, no, no, no.
They're, they're going to play second fiddle.
They're going to support all of their wealth is going to support a new emergent group.
Okay.
And when this new emergent group takes power, you're going to be promised a thousand year
perfection on this planet.
And it's not going to be propagandized like in the Soviet Union, who I tell you was a
perfect society.
You got 3000 people waiting neat, deep in snow for toilet paper.
Come on.
No, not like that.
It's going to be very different and you will not be able, because as you get closer now,
what's going to happen in the future, when they start, this starts happening, there'll
be some major, major glitches in society.
And the high command is going to make some very unusual requests from the people to put
them back on track, which they will never go back on track, but everyone's going to
follow with a fervor.
This is what you're going to see in the mid 2020s.
And I'm not channeling this from some, you know, the bum of a housefly or some ridiculous
stuff.
This is in all of your ancient writs.
But of course, do you think you're so advanced and smart now, you don't want to look there?
And if you tried, you wouldn't understand it.
We just did that little bit of exercise with etymology on what words mean.
Yeah.
So now I'm not, this is not, this is, this is real talk.
People don't want real talk, by the way.
They like, when you say wheat, they don't, oh, I don't want that.
I want puffed wheat, rice.
I don't want, I want puffed rice, you know?
Yeah.
They don't want, they don't want, they want talk.
Oh, that's real talk.
I don't want that.
I can't have that.
No, I gotta, you see, I love her.
They can't even define any of the terms that they're using.
Oh, I love everybody.
Oh, can't even define that.
They don't even know what it is.
They think it's some esoteric feeling.
There's no, love basically means doing the right thing, even when you don't feel like
doing it.
That's why, you know, you never want to fall in love, because, right, it doesn't sound
good.
Hey, man, I just fell.
Does that sound good?
No, it doesn't.
No, not at all.
Yeah, and infatuation's even worse, where they start off real hot, and then it just
cools down after that.
You ever notice?
Anyway, what else, what else do you want to get into?
You know, the only thing I could say is, unless we're going to be on here for a very long
time, unless you give me some adult supervision, I would just suggest all the archives, and
of course, this is a new thing that you are beginning to venture off into getting your,
let's just say, a form of media that you would like to do presented on the internet.
So, and I think you'll put this up, and whoever's listening to it, I don't know what
you have, I haven't looked at it, what you have preceding this particular podcast, but
I'm sure.
It's funny, because it's a lot of the things, you know, I had a flat earther on,
and I know how you feel about that.
No, no, no, it's not about our feeling.
Take your feelings out of it.
Well, it's...
That's hypocrisy.
No, it's a part of the language, it's just the way I say things, or the way people say
things, and I mean, I guess we would all like to get to the level where we mean what we
say, you know, but...
You will later.
I guess so, but it all goes back to not knowing what we're saying at the time, or just
hanging with whatever the word means, or how the expression goes for whatever we're saying.
You understand what I'm trying to say?
Yeah, the thing about the flat earther, all these other movements that happen, even...
You remember, if you're old enough, somebody pulls out some photos of the 70s, and how
cool they thought they looked then, when they got those ugly polyester patterns, and the
funky haircuts, and the bell bottoms?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And now, does that look good to you now?
Oh, no, not at all.
No, not at all.
Yeah, but everybody did, then why?
Because it looked good?
No, it didn't look good either, because it was the crowd mentality.
Gustave Le Bon wrote about the crowd.
He's Gustave Le Bon, 1905 or something, or even earlier.
And he says, when people gravitate into crowds, they usually go for a certain reason, but
that reason that creates the crowd has to be so oversimplified, or dumbed up.
I don't use dumbed down, because dumbed down means less dumb.
Dumbed up means more dumb, right?
So, it's so dumbed up that to get the average person to believe it, or go for it, it no longer
resembles its original science, or its original thing.
That's the same thing with the flat earthers.
They're very simple.
I mean, this is not the flat earthers are bad, and everybody else is good.
No, they're idiots like the rest of the people, right?
Idiot is a medical term I'm using here.
It means you stop developing around 12.
I'm more, you know, actually 12, if you develop beyond 12 years old, that's really good,
because most of your college professors stop developing around 8.
Wow.
You know, I'm serious.
I believe you, man.
As soon as you get your...
No, no, no.
Well, if you believe me now, I'll prove it in the future as we get down.
But that's no reason to do that.
I mean, it's the degeneration of humankind as we know it right now, and even like half
of the things you're talking about, I'm like, okay, I got to sit down and go look all of
this stuff up, and it's probably third grade knowledge.
Yeah, you know, there's many levels to it.
I mean, I think once we had a conversation briefly, you talked to do something about
the Pizzagate thing also.
I've been discussing, not that specifically, but how critical cannibalism and the destruction
of children...
Oh, man, let's talk about that before we get off.
Can you elaborate on that?
Please tell me.
Yeah, let's just leave it, because I'm coming up on a sixth episode on something, and I
try to number things, like six is the number of man, right?
All these idiots like 666, they think it's satanic.
No, that's the number of a man.
All the spiritual beings are seven.
You see, all of them, good or bad, is seven.
Five is the animal, comes before man, right?
That's why all of the generals, they're stars.
How many stars are there?
What's the most amount of stars you can get?
Five, right, before they form a new society.
So I tell people, if you are traveling through the universe on the mothership, they send
you down for three days, you got to come back with notes, and you got to tell the captain
briefly what you saw objectively.
You can't go back to the captain and say, well, I like strawberry ice cream.
He's going to say, well, what's the matter with you?
Give me some objectivity.
What the hell is ice cream?
It's cream, eggs, and it's cold.
Okay, you can't, you can't, you got to leave what you think out of it.
If you come to planet Earth, if you had just a few minutes to describe what is going on
on this planet with every culture since time immemorial, is you have to be able to explain,
as a question I'm going to give it, what do cannibals, birthdays, and dolls have in common?
And if you comprehend that, you will understand everything important, everything you need
to know about this society, because everything else that they do will, will be either as
a justifiable punishment or justifiable reward around that, and there's very little reward
to do that.
So let me ask you, what do cannibals, birthdays, and dolls have in common?
I have no idea.
Have you heard, have you heard this before in Greek speak?
I've heard it before, yes.
Okay, let's bring, well, if you, then you've got to remember it, man, you see, I'm not putting
out the spot, you want me to, you want me to, you want the Greek to say it?
Exactly.
Okay, but you, when you first heard it, you got a little bit of a gist.
No, no, nobody wants to hear it from me, they want to hear it from you, sir.
I know.
You say, you notice how I don't want to say it, right?
I want you to say it, please.
Okay, years ago, do you know earlier how we mentioned even the idiotic education
system said that everything started in the Mesopotamian region,
we were talking about the starting line and the finish line, remember that?
Back then, you know, the people there spoke a Chaldean Hebrew language, just like right now,
if you say most of Europe speaks a Latin language, you know, French, Portuguese, Italian, so,
right?
It's not, they're different languages, but they're based on Latin, just like back then,
everyone spoke a Chaldean Hebrew tongue, okay?
So, the people, they had a priesthood and they convinced them, and that, by the way,
that priesthood were called the Qahans.
Okay.
Okay, and they had convinced the people to worship the Baals, which were the lords.
That's why today, when you go to church, they tell you to worship the Lord, same thing.
So, the way you worship the Lord, or the Baals,
is that you brought a child, and the child was put up on an altar, and it was slaughtered.
And everyone partook a little bit of the flesh and a little bit of the blood.
Disgusting.
Okay, I got you.
A little bit, it is touching.
That's why eating human flesh is called Qahan Baalism, or cannibalism.
Wow.
This is not a twist in words, like,
Talil vision means Talon lies on your vision.
That's the origin of it.
Yeah.
Okay, now, when the parents go back to the house, the other children are like,
where's our brother, where's our sister?
Typically, it was a boy they did.
Now, what they did then, the altar boys, they put together an effigy of a child, and they said,
if they ask you that, give them this thing called a doll, this effigy, or whatever,
and have them play with that until they forget about it.
Now, you know the history of dolls.
Now, it doesn't matter, well, I played with dolls.
They were fun.
Not me, but little girls, you know, they still give them.
They got a whole industry around that.
It doesn't matter if you like it or not, or whether you care or not.
This is the origin of it.
Actually, right now, it's interesting.
I said, this is going to come out more in full force.
That's when I saw the Pizzagate stuff.
It's no big deal.
I've been talking about stuff even worse than that a long time ago already,
just by looking at the ancient writs.
You see?
Now, obviously, you know why they did all this?
Because they made a wish of prosperity.
They said, if you do this with the child, you're going to please this ball, this lord,
and you're going to have prosperity.
It didn't bring prosperity, right?
So they ran these guys out of town after a while, and that's why you've heard of the druids.
Anyway, that's where a lot of them went and ran back there, up there.
Anyway, one of these days, I'm going to get into the real history and give references and all that.
So, but they said, well, if you want that wish of prosperity,
why don't you do a parody of the event, instead of really sacrificing the child?
Take the child that's next in line, or you were going to bring,
and put him in a high chair, give him a pointy hat like we wear,
and bake a loaf of sweet bread, and put lights in the sweet bread,
and have him blow out the lights, which represents blowing out the life.
And then everybody eats a piece of this sweet bread, or cake, to represent eating the body.
And to show that the ceremony works,
whoever's participating in the ceremony brings a present for the child.
Now, when I looked at this, I sat around for like six months and said, what the hell is that?
And then I said, whoa, whoa, wait a second.
That's where the history of that is.
It doesn't matter if you have a good time.
Don't you think the people at Pizzagate or whatever,
raping and killing those little children, are having a good time?
You think that you have to force them to do it, or you think they're seeking that out?
They're seeking it out.
Now, this is the level.
Now, you want to hear something?
When it comes to the gods, even if everyone stopped doing this,
if one person was doing a birthday cake, it's as if you're all doing it.
Because you're all considered the same.
When you deal with the gods, it's all or nothing.
That's why in some cases you heard of certain people that were
separated or chosen for a certain thing.
Right?
They weren't chosen because they were better.
They were chosen to be separate from the rest.
So this is the humanity.
So you think you're going to have industry that matters?
You're going to think you're going to have laws that matter?
You think you have religions that matter?
Governments or money that matters?
Or medical system that matters?
When you can only be described at this point and have been described as
what do cannibals' birthdays and dolls have in common?
And this is the way that I would put the cap on the description of
the typical surface-dwelling earth inhabitant.
Greek, thank you so much for coming on the infinite fringe with me.
This wasn't even an interview.
It was more of a lecture and I appreciate it.
Tell people, I know they're going to be interested.
There's going to be someone out there that's going to be like,
wow, I need to get more of this and just keep digging and digging and digging.
So just reiterate to people where they can find you and
where we can continue to expand our knowledge on everything you've spoken about.
Oh, that means you really want to get in trouble.
Yeah, yeah, big time.
All right, Uncommon Radio is the easiest thing.
Now it shows up if you do whatever browser you put in Uncommon Radio,
it'll be the first site up there.
Fourteen and a half million hits, right?
No, I'm only joking.
I only have it up there as a courtesy, folks.
And when you go to Uncommon Radio,
if you can't find it, it's www.uncommonradio.com.
Do the whole thing, you'll get it.
And it's the only one discussing sonic events with the Greeks.
And all that's up there is just hours and hours and hours of archives.
Very redundant, very repetitious.
It's all being spoken of on a fourth grader level.
But the problem is all the information is pieced together in a way that you're not used to hearing
it.
It's very useful, I believe it is.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be doing it.
And it's all free at this point.
It's all available.
You will see where to be directed also to a radio that I do once a week.
And that I call the open members area.
But just for yourself at this time, everyone, let me just say it this way.
Let's just say we're having a private conversation that's being recorded in public.
Let's just say, I don't know how much longer this information is going to be
in public, whether it's voluntary or involuntary, because I would like to get into more deeper
informational stuff.
And I don't think the public at large is ready to hear it.
And there's going to be some kind of a vault type thing set off to the side where the
real stuff, the real references and more how to's are going to be put on.
So that's a project that's coming in the future.
But for right now, it's www.uncommonradio.com.
And I appreciate the time.
Thanks for having me on.
If there's anything else I could do for you, let me know.
I appreciate you.
Thank you for coming on.
Hang on for just a second.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
So that was our interview with the Greek.
Very, very, very interesting guy, to say the least, right?
I mean, if you didn't completely understand what was going on there, just make sure you
go back and look up every little thing he says, because it's all eye opening.
Awakening stuff will definitely be turned on to knowledge that you did not know about
previously.
And that's what the Infinite Fringe is all about.
We appreciate the Greek.
He will be back.
You know, he even stuck around after the show and showed me a few more things.
And I appreciate him for that.
I appreciate all our guests, you know, everything they do for us and all the knowledge that
they bring for you and I to listen to week after week right here on the Infinite Fringe.
And I appreciate all of you for downloading the show and listening week after week.
Thank you.
Make sure you subscribe to the Infinite Fringe on iTunes.
The Infinite Fringe on Podbeam.
That's theinfinitefringe.podbeam.com.
We've got some more news coming down the pipe.
All right.
So stay tuned for the evolution of the show and where it may take us.
It's interesting times.
We appreciate you.
Have a good time until next week.
This is Billy Ray Valentine.
God bless.