Mike Adams here, the Health Ranger, founder of Brighteon.com,
free speech platform where we encourage people to speak freely and we invite people
to join us who also speak freely, but think freely. I mean, anybody can speak. The question
is, what mind is behind your words? And today we're joined by two very intriguing individuals
who have brilliant minds. You probably have not heard of them before because it's the first time
guests with us, but they do have other projects that we'll talk about out on the internet.
So we have Sam Friedman joining us from Stockholm, Sweden, and then his associate
known as The Greek joining us. And we're going to cover some fascinating topics today that will
blow your mind. So welcome Sam and The Greek. It's great to have you with me today. Thanks.
Thank you for having us. Yeah, absolutely. Let me just tell my audience that I saw a video clip
from Sam and we don't have to go into details about what project that's for or anything, but it
was just like a little demo clip. And it was so intriguing, Sam, about what you were talking about
and especially being that you're in Sweden and so much of Europe has gone off the rails as
much of the United States as well. So here we are, islands of, I think, reason in a sea of woke
insanity at the moment. So I had to invite you on. So what would you tell people about,
a little bit about your background and also for The Greek, give us a little background so that
people can have kind of a starting point for this conversation. Sure. Thank you, first of all,
for having us. It's always a pleasant surprise when people take interest in what you're doing.
So it's great to be chatting with you, Mike. In terms of my background, I'm not anyone of
any public renown. Most of my work is done privately, though I have been a part of a few
public facing projects with The Greek. I'm not quite an armchair philosopher because that
sometimes implies laziness, but I'm not a public intellectual either. So perhaps I'd call myself an
aspiring intellectual or impromptu journalist, but certainly an all around student of many things.
In terms of background, I'm an interview journalist, mostly with a history in the music
business, running different websites for interviewing people in the audio world,
like studio owners, recording engineers, and then also music executives. But most recently,
I've pivoted from that into producing interview centric video content, podcasts, documentaries,
anything with an interview focus. And that's how that video got put together, which I shared with
you at one point, mostly talking about the media. As far as my associate here at The Greek,
we've worked on a few projects together, and I'll let him talk about himself.
Okay. Go ahead, The Greek.
All right. Yeah, sure. Well, what I say about myself is I'm just visiting this world taking
notes. I realized at a really young age that objectivity and truth was something that was
not either objective or truthful, right? So I started thinking about it, and I said, well,
why don't I make this sort of a sideline pursuit since I was pre-adolescent even.
And at the age of the internet, which I consider, let's say, the heyday was probably about 10 years
ago, many people encouraged me to call in on radio shows or do various conferences or whatever on the
internet. And I found that more people than I ever imagined had interest on what really is going on.
And when I say what really is going on is mastering your reality, just the reality that
is just immediate in front of you within a five-foot radius. Are you just paying attention?
And just briefly, as we spoke, we're going to be coming into an age of competency,
sort of how there was an age of enlightenment, let's say, 200 or 300 years ago attempted.
What I mean by competency is to be competent, it doesn't mean you're intelligent or smart.
It just means that you know what you're saying, you mean what you say, and you know what you're
doing. And that's pretty much what the Greek-speak element, all the elements of Greek-speak are,
and usually cover anywhere between 10 to three dozen subjects and show people how easy it is
to achieve close to mastery of any subject without being a quote-unquote professional,
which I define as someone who's always learning more and more about less and less.
Yeah. Okay. Well, that's really fascinating. I'm really glad you started with that because
both of you are big picture thinkers. You understand the cycles of history,
the cycles of consciousness, the cycles of the rise and fall of human civilization.
So let me pose a question. This will be to Sam first, but I'd like both of you to answer it.
When I look around, I see that we're in the final chapter, it looks like to me,
in the age of incompetence. So we have institutional leaders and government
leaders and media leaders and so on who demonstrate just stunning incompetence.
I guess the most recent example is the Signature Bank that collapsed in New York.
They were experts at making music videos featuring themselves, virtue signaling to music.
They were horrible at risk assessment and managing the money of their depositors, right?
So totally incompetent in the area where they claim to be professionals, but yet they had
this side competency of being pretty good at singing and dancing, which is fine unless you're
a banker, right? So do you agree with me that we're about to switch out of this age of incompetence or
that we're even in such an age? Or how would you describe it? Let's start with you, Sam. Go ahead.
Well, yeah, I would say that there is an age in which we're living that most people don't
know what they're doing, and particularly the people who call themselves the leaders.
It's very interesting how the competency that you would expect these people to display really
isn't there. And you have to wonder if it's duplicitous merely or also malevolent, because
sometimes it feels like that level of incompetency can't be reached without it being evil in some way
or something evil that's animating it. These are things that the Greek has elaborated on
endlessly over the years. And I've only gotten into this line of study in the past four or five,
but I have found that the incompetency is underpinned by some type of malevolence that's
hard to put your finger on, that you have to look into and be wary of not getting spun into la-la
land with conspiracy theories, but actually be objective about. Well, it seems like this age of
incredibly easy money, 0% interest rates, the illusion of economic abundance where at the
courts, not really there, but this allowed a lot of people to pretend like they were competent,
to pretend like they were in business or making money or producing profits, when in fact, you
peel back that layer and you realize, hey, there's nothing there. These people had no idea what they
were doing. Yeah, I mean, what strikes me about the Western world is how its economies, especially
in the 21st century, sort of built themselves, not on the idea of running profitable businesses,
but on the credit system that creates this disproportionate amount of funds from a place
that most people can't explain. And part of the reason I think why the third world stays so poor
isn't just because it's exploited, it's also because their financial institutions don't have
easy access to these credit facilities that grant them seemingly infinite money. So the Western
world amasses all this cash flow and economic activity because of its credit system. And then
it parts billions of it into investment banking to fund all these companies. And I think we see
this development really kick into overdrive in the 2010s with Silicon Valley and consumer tech
startups and a number of these companies pop up around a decade ago and promise to change
everybody's life when it comes to working, exercising, eating, shopping, cooking, etc.
So basically the Ubers, the Airbnbs, the WeWorks, the DoorDashes, and they barely own any real world
infrastructure or assets or do real things, but they control entire industries by monopolizing
information. And to maximize their growth, they suppress their prices enormously through the money
that comes from venture capital, which is effectively a subsidy. And I think one of the
most notable VCs in that space is the Vision Fund, which is this investment company founded by a
Japanese bank called SoftBank. But they have like $150 billion under management, mostly from
sovereign wealth funds of Saudi Arabia and UAE. A lot of their money gets invested into these
companies like Uber and DoorDash and WeWork. And so the brands are able to take over the market
because they're so much cheaper than their competitors, but most of them are never
profitable. They're just surviving on this Middle Eastern oil money and whatnot.
And SoftBank, also Vision Fund, funded FTX too, by the way. You probably know that, but
they were involved in that as well. To the Greek then, what are your thoughts on the transition
of the age here, if that's what you would call it? Oh, great. You know, when you introduced the
transition of the age prior, you said about the age, which is time, and then money, you went right
to the bank. I want to give two compressed versions, two compressed seeds to be planted that
can be uncompressed later. I'll give you the choice. Would you like the dose of
time or the dose of the financial system first? No, let's talk about time, because that's the
construct in which we operate. Oh, sure. Okay. In terms of time, I'm going to shoot a two-hour
film using old film, a movie. Do I buy exactly two hours worth of film, or do I buy two hours
and 10 minutes because I need to roll credits at the end? You need to buy 200 hours of film,
because you're going to edit most of it out. Let's say there is no editing. It's a straight
run. It's like the Hitchcock, The Rope. In this case, what I mean is, it's a two-hour film,
but at two hours, the people are still in their seats watching the credits, but it's okay to speak
over it. People aren't going to tell you to shut up when the credits are rolling. That's where
we're in right now. The credits started rolling around 1998, when you're looking at the ages of
2,000-year chunks. Around 1998, this is from the scriptural, biblical timekeeping. It's also from
your 20th-century prophets. A lot of people in the metaphysical world, the Levatsky's, the Cayce's,
also said this, ironically. I had not gotten it from them, though. I had gotten it from ancient
writs. What's interesting is, since the credits started rolling around 1998, we have about a 40
or so year period. Over a 6,000-year period, 40 years of credit seems to be proportional.
What I mean about it, it's important to view it as you're in the credits, is during the film,
people expect a certain etiquette. When the credits are rolling, the film is still in action,
but it's okay to speak. It's okay to stand up. Some of the lights start coming on, right?
But what you also notice about the credits rolling is all of the stuff that was behind the scenes
that was not on the film itself. They'll do outtakes and things like that.
Sure. Also, just mentioned, during the film, you don't know who was the key grip,
but now you do. After 1998, you're going to start seeing a movement toward,
hey, do you know that this society is being run by secret societies of this, this, this,
and that? Do you know that this was really invented back then? You see a lot of what is
basically the fabric and underpinning of the alternative media, whether it's history, economics,
whatever, even the medical, there's all this stuff that's been coming out,
you know, the, the, the travails of the Catholic church, right? All these things are a religion.
Every topic under the sun now is, is, is, is experienced a minor upheaval where these things
are being brought out into the open. The other thing that's happening right now that,
that I would like to overlap, that it's a movie where we're watching the credits,
the etiquette now has changed. It's okay to stand up and speak. The lights are coming on.
What will happen when the credits are end is the lights come on and the screen comes up and
you see a brick wall, right? Is that, that's the, that's the end of the credits. We're still about
a decade or so from that. And then everybody realizes they've been living in a scripted
Truman show. Right. And in short, what does that mean? It means total collapse of your
infrastructure, meaning none of the government employees are going to work. None of the power
station employees are going to work. None of the water people going to work. None of the road
people are going to work. None of the banks are going to work. Right. Infrastructure collapse.
Right. So, so when you think about what society will be is basically you hit the light switch,
there's no light. You turn on the plumbing, there's no water over a gradual period. Right.
And we've heard the stories of what happens with that right after just about what, 10 days without
power or something. Right. Everyone has heard that. Okay. But what's also interesting, what's
happening is we're having revival of, of philosophies, religion, sciences, perceptions,
ideologies from the ancient, ancient past that has been obscured from our history.
So when you start seeing all this stuff happening, for example, with the, the gender bending or the,
while the medical community is doing, so how government is running things or how religions
are changing, those things have happened way back in the past. And when they, when they happen again,
we think it's something new. No, it's just a revival, right? Of something very ancient.
So I tell people, if you want to really know something new about what's coming, read an old
book. And I mean, really, really old. Basically anything that was written in the past, 1902,
1895 or 1920, for sure, is, is already been censored very heavily. So, you know, if you want
to get a grip or a taste of what, how people thought and what was known to be coming is very
clear in 19th century. I always say that everything that could have been known was known by the late
19th century. That's why you see there's a, I'm not a big proponent of flat earth or mud floods,
but you'll notice there's a lot of talk about what happened in the 18th, in the, in the middle or
end, by the end of the 19th century, all these orphans, all this high tech, we don't understand
the architecture, right? All this stuff. So I, I really like people to have a view on that.
Also, in terms of timekeeping, you're on what I call the Pope's work schedule,
which is a schedule. You have the work week and the weekend and Monday through Friday,
January through December. Let me just bring this up in terms of timekeeping, organic timekeeping,
meaning the time that the planet uses, the whales, the bugs, the birds, the bees, the plants,
they don't go on the Gregorian calendar or the wind up toy known as the clock.
For example, the day starts at solar noon, not midnight, not sundown, right? You can measure it
with a sundial. That's why years ago, if you did regular banking before the electronic convention,
if you deposited a check after noon, it was counted as the next day. In the wild west,
when they had court, they hung you high the next day, they hung you right from whatever it was at
when? At high noon. So the day ends it at solar noon. This is by the way, in your academic
paperwork, if you go to university for astronomy, they tell you that the day starts at solar noon
for scientific and astronomical purposes, but for the people, it's civil midnight.
It's kind of like a put down, right? Like the old dictionaries, when they define the word oats,
they said this, what we feed horses in England, but the staple of the people in Scotland, right?
Kind of a, so, so, so, okay, so the moon, what's interesting about the full moon, most people see
the full moon and say, oh, how beautiful, or it's this moon or that moon, or people tend to act
strange. Do you know, for thousands of years, people settled their debts before the full moon
came or the new, it's really the new moon. That's why today when they, don't you get these things
called bills in the mail on what, on a monthly basis, don't you? Isn't that interesting?
Right? So, so also the full moon is the new moon because you take a measurement with it.
Time has to be precise. You cannot measure any kind of a moon calendar or lunar cycle with the
sliver that they're calling the dark moon. So what's interesting is once you start to put these
things in alignment, so people want to do biblical holidays when it says the 13th day of the first
month, it's not January 13th. You see that these things are all measured by astro, by astronomical
bodies because you don't have to buy a clock. You don't have to buy a calendar and it doesn't
change. See, so time is important. That's, I did a sonic event recently about timekeeping and no
matter how successful someone thinks they are in this society or any society and is basing their
time, which has circadian rhythm, biological clocks and all that, on what I call the wind-up
toy known as the clock or the, or the Gregorian calendar, you will always feel like you're missing
out on something. There is just something that you're not aligned with, right? Yeah. Yeah.
Well, I have a comment on that and I also want to mention your, your website or your, your,
your interview project content, content. Yeah. It's called Ocelli and the Greek O-C-H-E-L-L-I
and that's at ocelli.com. I've got it on, on screen there. That's right. And your show is
called Rated Y, Y for, for, for yes. Or Y for W-H-Y. Oh, okay. Okay. W-H-Y. Okay. But I wanted
to mention, you know. Phonetic Y. Got it. You know, I lived in Taiwan for a couple of years and of
course in the Chinese calendar, the Chinese calendar is, is lunar centric. And I found out
that the Chinese, even, even the Chinese, you know, Taiwanese who are Chinese, even those living in
the city who can't see the moon because of the city, they still know the phase of the moon because
it's their calendar. Whereas I find Americans living in the countryside who can see the moon,
still don't know where the moon is or what it's doing or that it follows almost the same path all
the time, but just on a different schedule. So I found that to be a shocking difference between
Eastern time and Western time. And anyway, and then I found out they keep inserting months into
the Gregorian calendar through history and so on. And that's, that's why September is
nine instead of seven and things like that. That's right. It's very good. Most people,
October is eight, November is nine, December is ten. They give you four months where they label
the numeric aspect correct. Just like when you take a multiple choice question and answer test,
they give you four possible answers. Right. But right now everyone's failing. What's interesting
though, you mentioned about the American here in the Midwest or something, the real savvy ones have
these things called farmer's almanacs and, and they suggest you do certain plantings with certain
phases of the moon. Right. So it's really interesting how this is the, the, the competency
aspect of it. Now, in terms of timekeeping, I call that lawful timekeeping and lawful means you don't
have to involve someone else. Usually means you don't have to go into commerce to get what you
need. You see that's what I, what's why I call it lawful timekeeping, right? Because if you don't
have a phone or a windup toy known as the clock or a calendar, what day is it? Most people can't
reckon that where if you do know lawful timekeeping, you just go outside and you can tell.
And then, and then the ultimate insult is daylight savings time as it's called,
which is a joke. It's wartime. It's wartime. Yeah. It's, it's like psychological warfare.
Well, no, actually it's called day. Sorry. It's called, it's called wartime because during the
war they wanted people to work longer and be able to walk home during the daylight. It's,
it's one of the aspects you could actually look up the history on that. That's wild. But right now,
of course, we just went through that in Western society and it's also a hormone disruption for
everybody to keep you off track. But let me, let me bring in Sam on this issue here again. So,
you know, we're talking about Sam sort of aspects of how the, the construct of reality has been
engineered around us in a way that dissociates us or separates us from the real cosmic reality,
right? So you're not supposed to look at the moon or the stars or the sun. You're not supposed to
even look inward. You're not supposed to realize who you are, where you came from. You're supposed
to believe these artificial systems that are handed to us. This has happened before, but today
it seems like it's, it's gone to a whole new level with mobile phones, mobile devices. What are your
thoughts on this subject? Well, I mean, I think we live in a world where nothing is harder to achieve
than, you know, understanding the truth with a capital T. People are struggling more than ever
to make sense of things. And there doesn't even seem to be a body of knowledge that acts as a
reliable measure of truth. I think that the mainstream religions don't do very well. The
mainstream media doesn't do it. Academia doesn't do it. None of them have really been able to
impart a satisfactory understanding of a lot of the contradictions that we see. That's why one of
the things the Greek used to emphasize when we'd speak some years back was how the normalcy of human
society is actually dysfunctional. You know, the norms and institutions that society encourages us
to place trust in are actually the source of problems. Exactly. And even in medicine, I've
often commented that, you know, when doctors say things like, oh, people just get that at your age.
I think, wow, that's because the population at large is so unhealthy and on so many medications
and processed junk foods that they develop those conditions at that age. And all the doctors think
that that's normal and even just causative because of age, which is nonsense. But that
kind of thinking pervades every area of society, does it not? Yeah, it does. I mean, I think most
people live their lives unaware that entire facets of society are meant to influence their actions
and their beliefs, whether it's your parents, the schools, the government, the media. They all work
together to create this tier of reality that we call the mainstream. The mainstream is just a
place where everything runs on plausible deniability of what everybody thinks that they
know. And so basically, you know, stock conventions about reality that don't make any sense.
I like the way you said that. Yeah. It runs on plausible deniability. Isn't it shocking? And let
me direct this to the Greek. Isn't it shocking that, you know, for those of us like you two I'm
talking to today and our audience, I would consider to be well-informed, people who like to learn,
people who like to understand. And yet we interact with other people in the world around us who are
completely oblivious. They literally know nothing except the illusions that are put in front of them
and perhaps, you know, how to put on their socks and, you know, how to stop by Starbucks and
whatever, maybe how to use a credit card, but they know nothing outside of that system.
How is it that we find ourselves in a society where there is a widespread ignorance, lack of
knowledge, and it seems like there's a sector of society that even revels in that, like they
celebrate their ignorance? Wow. Deep question. I do. I would like to go back to the financial
at some point. That's been in the back of my mind. But regarding that, it's very simple. Let's
just take a broad view. Like instead of watching this four hour parade on the sidewalk, let's go
up in a helicopter. So we see the entire parade in one view. So we don't have to stay on the sidewalk
for four hours to see the last float. Right. So let's take a high vantage point of this.
Humans being, I wouldn't say we're part of the animal kingdom, but we're mammalian. You know,
we have hearts and lungs like other creatures do and all this. What's interesting is that we don't
come pre-downloaded with software where all the other animals do. What I mean by that, for example,
is if you have a little tiny puppy dog and you have it raised by gorillas, and then when it
matures, you take it home, it's still going to chase a bird. It's still going to chase a stick.
You still train it to sit. It's going to act just like a dog would. You wouldn't know it was raised
by gorillas. Now, if you took a human at very, very infant age and you had it raised by gorillas
and you brought him home as an adult, he would jump up on the table and take a poo, right? It
would act just like a gorilla. See, the dog didn't because it comes pre-downloaded, pre-with software
on how to be a dog. So do the birds, so the fish, so do the cats, so do most of the animals. We have
no pre-download. We have no operating system, no software, no programming. So we come in kind
of tabula rosa. You could basically, whatever you input into the human as they're growing,
they will exhibit that behavior. Very simple. So once you know that, how simple is it to create
sectors in society? And when I mean sectors, we're 99.99% of the society is kept in the dark.
Should I say that? How many nines do you want to add to that, right? It's more like 99.999,
that puts it right, is kept in the dark about mostly everything. And the rest of it is what
should we tell them it is? Because all you need to do is look at any reference manual and any law
book, any medical book, and it contradicts what we're told about those subjects.
Yeah, I've used the term PLFs or programmable life forms. And I even wonder, and let me ask
this question to both of you, I even wonder, what do you believe about souls and consciousness? And
are there biological vessels that look human to us that were born without souls and they are
literally incapable of individual self-creative thought? Does that exist in our world? And that
would make them more easily programmable. What do you think about that idea? Go ahead, Sam.
Oh no, I actually think that that's very much suited for the Greek. I do think that though,
I will say before he jumps in, that some weight should be given to this. It's been theorized that
what we perceive to be a three-dimensional universe might just be the image of a
two-dimensional one projected across this massive cosmic horizon. So basically simulation theory.
And that kind of does account for this anomalous phenomenon where you have people that don't quite
seem human or that subscribe to notions that are completely fallacious, you know,
that you wouldn't expect them to, or that act in a programmable manner. I think that there's been
different pop culture artifacts that's referred to that over the years. They Live comes to mind,
the 1985 movie. Sometimes people will go the extraterrestrial route, sometimes they'll go the
simulation theory route. But I think even in 2016, Bank of America or some big financial
institution had crunched numbers and decided that it's a 50-50 chance that the entire universe is
just made up of software. But I'll let the Greek elaborate. Yeah, go ahead.
Well, it goes back to, I would call more that we have a spirit, which is our mind, the soul,
which is our breath, metabolism, and the physical body. When we speak about the mind,
most people immediately go to the materialistic sense that it's all happening in the brain.
What I suggest, and it's actually, I've been suggesting this for over two decades,
and now it's becoming more common. The brain is nothing more than merely a minor processor
that sends and receives, as if our consciousness is part of a cloud system, right? What I mean by
this is, you know, you could look at real scientific studies where they try to find memory and things in
the brain, and it's just nothing makes sense to them, right? Just like if someone was at a picnic
and they had a radio playing jazz music, if you quickly disassembled that radio, would you find
a miniature jazz band in there? No, not at all. So the concept of the soulless people, it's been
popularized, they're called NPCs, for example, or, you know, whatever shells. Yes, yes, it's very
easy to use that reference because it encompasses a very large group, and they all have so much in
common that it's actually quite accurate. What's happening?
Let me, this is amazing what you're saying, because you and I must have had a lot of the same influence.
Guys, show my screen. I did a book called The Contagious Mind, and I'm showing it. Can you see
that on your Skype there, the Greek?
Yes, I'll take a look. Yeah, I'll look at that. Thank you for putting that in there, yeah.
Yeah, absolutely. It's a free thing.
That's exactly the right track.
Yeah, I call it The Contagious Mind because there's so much evidence out there that exactly,
as you said, that the mind is actually a broadcaster and a receiver, and it resonates
with other people's minds. And there's like a cosmic cloud-based network of information sharing
or idea sharing, where a certain group of people come up with an idea, they have a breakthrough or
invention, and then through no physical explanation whatsoever, other people will spontaneously
have the same realization. And this has happened again and again throughout history, where inventors
accuse each other of stealing each other's patents. But actually, I think it's contagion
through this process that you and I are describing. But thanks for letting me interrupt and mention
that. We're on the same track. No, go ahead.
No, that's very pertinent. I also want to, let's say attach this to a very stark example in our
society, a very stark one. If you know anyone who operates CB or ham radio, you know the size and
dimensions of the antenna are critical to the frequencies you're going to pick up.
Absolutely, right.
So when you're an infant, you have this small brain, small body, and it's all working together.
It doesn't pick up much, doesn't remember much in most cases. Then you become an adolescent,
a teenager, which is almost mature size. And do you ever notice teenagers like to stay up
all night, right? They stay up all night and sleep during the day. Why? It's not because it's
just some social thing. It's because all the adults that have this quote-unquote frequency
are now down. They're asleep. They're not receiving or broadcasting. And the new adolescent mind that
is still clean is looking at the field or sensing the field. They're all asleep. It's so clean out
here. We're free. It's like really clean information. Instead of this programming,
you see how they're thriving on that. So once you see that and you start seeing how it can be
applied in many different ways. By the way, a lot of the quote-unquote black projects have taken
advantage of this now for over 50 years, with psychotronics and all that. For example, there's
a concept called chemtrails. So if you do a browser search on chemtrails, all the sites are
going to say, oh, that's conspiracy theory stuff, whatever. But if you put in stratospheric aerosol
injection, you'll see all these legitimate sites with patents and how the same thing.
Yep, exactly.
So the same thing. You do mind control, you're a conspiracy theorist. But if you start getting
into psychotronic influences, you're going to see all the patents. And these are patents,
not just for our entertainment, but they're patents, meaning those patents represent 2%
or 1% of what has really been developed, right?
Yeah, that's what's fascinating. There's a whole realm of technology that has been prohibited
from the masses, but then exploited by governments and, let's say, dark projects,
or globalist institutions to be used against us. Some would argue that, for example,
mRNA technology might be in that same category. Let me go back to Sam on this. Sam, do you have
an opinion on that or other similar technologies that might be used against humanity?
Well, when it comes to the unpacking of black programs and technology, these are things that
I'm actually learning a lot about from the Greek, to be honest. I put my contemplation more into
the cultural side of things and the sort of existential metaphysical aspect. It's hard
to speak on the science unless you're actually involved in it yourself, either in a recreational
sense at home, which the Greek has a background in working on all kinds of stuff. But I will say that
a lot has been written by journalists like Annie Jacobson about things like the extrasensory
projects that the CIA and other intelligence agencies seem very obsessed with getting
involved with. They don't speak on it publicly, but then you'll go back and read during the 60s
and 70s that the Gateway Project, obviously, we all know about remote viewing and things of
that nature. It's quite bizarre that they're obsessed with somehow unpacking the supernatural,
but then pretending like they're atheists or that they're only scientists or that they don't have
any interest in that. I think even in the 80s, there was some type of a run where they were
collecting ancient manuscripts from around the world, occult manuscripts, and giving no explanation
for why they'd be interested in these kind of things. Well, let me give out your website,
by the way, GreekSpeak.com, but it's spelled S-P-E-E-K, Greek Speak, again, double E, so the
word speak is spelled differently than you would expect. GreekSpeak.com.
Let me ask the Greek here about Project Looking Glass, right? That's something that's in the
mythos of modern conversations. Do you think that was a real project, or even that it's being used
now? Sure, sure. It can be done several ways. There are several Project Looking Glasses,
but the one that you might be referring to is the one that makes rounds on the internet,
where they have a device, either found ancient relic or given to men by E.T., let's say,
that would see snippets or larger views of the future of either the collective or an individual.
Am I on the right track? Right, exactly. Yeah, that can be done with a device, yes,
and it could also be done mathematically. There are repeats and cycles, if you understand how to
keep time, haha, right? It won't work if you're using the clock or the calendar. That's why I
leaned on it so heavily when we first started speaking. The other aspect of it is, may I just
give an example of how the time, since ancient Greek philosophers, and before that, and now
philosophers and scientists are pondering what time is, time is merely the recordation of events.
If there are no events happening, if there is no change, and there's no record of it, there's no
time. It's very simple. That's all it is. It's just a record-keeping function. What people
actually refer to as time is change, things changing, even on an atomic structure, you know,
like the half-life of materials is a form of change, which is hence a form of time.
So, in order for something to exist in the past or the future, in an existential universe, it means
it already exists. So, everything that happened in the past still exists, but in a faded, like a
wave that's dissipated at a great distance. And everything that is going to happen in the future
already exists, but in a very proto-stage, right? Almost like in a thought stage. I'll give you an
example. You cannot change the past, but you can influence it. And this is the example that I give
to people. Have you ever been in a tight spot in your life where something went really bad, an
accident, an incident or something, and you were almost in a panic, and you heard a little voice
inside tell you everything's going to be okay, right? Many people have experienced that. What
I suggest that little voice really is, is you in the future recalling that event and sending the
signal back. You see? Now, if you have a... Now, this is something that someone brought up.
If you're in a tight spot or in a bad accident or something, and you don't hear that little voice,
two things are possible. One is you're not going to make it. And the other thing is,
right? Right? In the future. And the other thing is you will probably forget this and not recall
it. So what I'm suggesting is when you hear that little voice in the past or in an event, it's you
in the future communicating with yourself. Maybe your future self hates your present self and wants
you to suffer through the event as a learning experience. Sure, sure. But I don't think we
really... Yeah, I think, yeah, that's a temperance and tolerance aspect. Right. Temperance and
tolerance. You got it. No, but that's a really great example of that. And time is, or especially
combined with consciousness, can be quite fluid, right? So, but when we talk about the future,
you said in a proto-state, doesn't that mean that there are many alternative possible futures that
are in the process of perhaps materializing? They're not quite materialized yet, but then
it kind of collapses into one of them in the present. Is that how that works? Yes, but no.
Like, for example, I have, I open a, let's say I come to the studio and I open a pouch and all these
little black, little seed, look, round objects fall out of the bag. And you asked me what they
are. And I said, they're seeds, they're tree seeds, right? And if I take one as an apple seed and I
plant it, that little tiny apple seed will become an apple tree, right? One is an oak. One other one
is, you know, different types of seeds of trees. You can't see it. When I hold them in my hand,
you see these little black specks in my hand. They're all seeds for trees. You can't see that.
You can't even make the connection, but you can, because you know, you know the process, right?
But if you don't know the process, you didn't know that trees were grown from tiny little seeds
like that. It would, you'd be befuddled by it, the whole thing. And it would be a concept that
would be very difficult for you to grasp as an adult. So I can't help but think in this metaphor
that we are living in a construct right now that is the result of seeds of obedience that have been
planted by the global controllers. Like they know how these things work. They planted these seeds,
you know, in the fifties, the sixties, the 1970s and so on. And they have grown a construct around
the masses that keeps the masses imprisoned in their, the mental prisons of their own making,
where they even enforce their own prisons. Is that, is that a fair analogy of kind of what
we're looking at? Yes and no. It's, it would be more like a virtual prison, prison of the mind.
Let's say it would be, think of it in an old Daoist sense. It's the space between the bars
that keeps the tiger in the cage, right? Because if there was no space, there would be no bars.
And it's the, it's the silent parts between the notes that make the music. So what I'm saying is
if you just, just jump through, you know, when, when, in between notes, when it's silent,
that's where you get your silence in between the bars of the cage is where you see there,
there is no obstruction, right? And I wanted to give the financial example that you asked Sam
earlier. I never, it's still sitting in the back. It's going to be very short.
Uh, okay. But first let me mention, I did, I did disassemble a piano once and I didn't find
any music inside. It was just baffling. There was no music in there. And I'm pretty sure if I tested
the black keys and the white keys, uh, in my lab, I would still not find any music whatsoever. So
how can that be? How can that be? Yeah. Perturbation, uh, everything in, in, in the
universe, the material universe, which is limited. Like for example, if you have an ailment and
someone provides you with a plant that, uh, heals treats or cures that ailment and it works,
um, you will understand that concept, right? If you feel this way, you get this plant and it works.
But if you give it to someone who has been taught that there's only materialism, they will take that
plant, crush it and burn it to find out what effect the chemical is in there. Right. And it will never
work as well as the whole plant. So you have to take it quote unquote holistically, uh, find out
how something works, where it's good enough and just leave it alone because it was put that way
for a reason. You see? Exactly. Uh, yeah. So that these things, this is what the Greek speak is
about. Let's just look really, really close, uh, within your own environment and you will see that
pretty much everything is there. You know, like with the poison Ivy, um, poison Ivy won't grow
unless it's in the vicinity of white Oak. What is white Oak bark? The treatment you see. So like
you said, the prison, I think that if they're creating, if they're going to create a prison
in order for it to be a balanced universe, not just a balanced earth, they have to daily give
you a cake with a file baked in it. But because they're giving you a chocolate cake and you're
allergic to chocolate, you're never going to open the cake to find out there's a hacksaw or a file
to cut through. You see, it's, they're giving you the actual, whoever they are. And that's where
the financial part comes in. Yeah, go ahead. Bring it in. It's such, you see, what is money?
It's very simple. When you have a perfect society, you live off of the land, quote unquote, you know,
mining, minerals, agriculture, water, everything you need is where you are when you want to travel,
right? You're not going to bring your land with you. You have to bring a representation of the
land. That's why since ancient times it was, you mine precious metal, precious materials,
gold, silver, diamonds, whatever. And you use that to trade. It's portable land. That's all it is.
Um, it from ancient times till now. So what was found out by the elite a long time ago is if we
control money, it's also in the biblical texts, I think in Psalms, it says that money will pretty
much fix most problems, right? So if you take control of the money, you take control of all
the transactions, exchange and thoughts and desires of people because of what money can get
you right now. What, what I tell people, especially living here in the United States of America
is you've heard of the 4th of July and everyone says, yes, of course. Some people sarcastically
say, uh, it's just a day after July 3rd. Right. But okay. Well, I said, well, you've never,
that was the founding of the country, but have you heard of March the 9th, 1933?
And most people, even historians say no. Well, March 9th, 1933 was when this country ended as
a Republic, as a country, as whatever, and became basically a bankrupt to the private banking
cabal. And, uh, in bankruptcy, a business is usually liquidated to pay the creditors,
but they decided to not liquidate it. Just like if there was an old store in your neighborhood,
it's best, it went bankrupt. It's called receivership. They come in and they have
new people managing it all. Everything in the till goes to these other people that bought the
business, let's say, right? So the art, this country, United States of America and all the
other countries are in what's called receivership, right? And we have working, we're working on
credit. That's why, when you look on a $20 bill, by the way, who's going to pay those bills,
right? It doesn't say federal reserve bank. It says federal reserve system. So there are
no banks anymore. What I mean by this is very simple. All of the money that's garnered and
used in exchange by quote unquote financial institutions is drawn from your signature.
If you go to a bank and ask, uh, you were approved for a $10,000 boat loan, say,
show me what account you're going to take that money from to give to me to buy the boat. They
can't because they wait for you to sign the paper. They have a transaction number and they enter it.
Now here's, I, some people might blur off over those details, but let's do a real simple, simple,
super simple example. Okay. I'm just going to use common talk here. Okay, guys, I, I have a bank
account, a checking account, and it's at minus a thousand dollars right now, minus a thousand
dollars. Can I write you a check for a hundred dollars? The answer is no, right? Now here's
the interesting point. If someone gave me a thousand dollars to put into the bank account,
that is now minus a thousand. Can I write you a check for a hundred dollars? I still can't. It's
at zero, right? Let's just say there are no fees attached. Okay. So people got a thousand dollars
stimulus check. So I said, go to the computer treasury.gov and it says they're 23 trillion
in debt. How can they write you a check for $1,500 and it be money based on basic accounting?
It's impossible. Now let's just stretch this a little bit more. I'll show you how practical this
is. If some, some way someone deposited $23 trillion with the U S treasury, could they write
one person a $1,500 check? The answer is no, they still can't. Now, as you know, you can go to
treasury.gov and the debt is what, is it getting bigger or smaller? It's getting bigger and bigger.
That is merely a formality. There is no debt because it's already under receivership. It's
already owned by the private banks, the federal reserve notes and checks and using a bank means
that you agree that the federal or the private banks have a first position lean on everything
you do and say, until you say, for example, no, I'm, I want lawful money. I'm making a demand
for lawful money. And this is in their codes. It's 12 USC for 11. Okay. So the example that I
give for money is, you know how people refer to it as monopoly money or whatever, that's pretty much
what it is, but you're living in a society where if you are hungry and you go to a merchant and you
walk out with a loaf of bread, what is he going to say? Wait, you have to what pay for that, right?
So the merchants don't know what's going on. I think that if most people knew what was going on,
sadly, everyone just cover their ears. I'm still not going to do anything about it.
You see, because they're just happy with it. If you, if you get what I mean, it's going to
take a level of moral and ethic evolution, mean a rise upgrade in order to say, this is not lawful.
What's going on. You say, well, right. But what, what's the alternative? Because as a society,
we do need some means of a proxy exchange to represent our goods and services and land and
food and whatever. What, what, what's the system that can work? You think? Oh, simple. You just
basically what they're doing. You see how I said earlier, when you go get a loan from the bank or
the government sends you a check, they draw it off of your signature. Let me just make this one point.
When you get a check for, you know, about fractional banking, anyone could look it up.
It's 10 to one. When a deposit is made in a bank, you get nine times that. Okay.
Let me just expose something here. This is all verifiable and validatable.
You got to check for a thousand dollars. What do they call them? Stimulus checks.
People are 15 or 600 does let's make a thousand dollars. Very simple, right? You go to the bank
and remember this thousand dollars is drawn off an account. That's minus 23 trillion. Okay.
Keep that in mind. All right. All right. So you go to the bank and you hand the bank,
tell her the check and she looks at it and gives it back to you. So I can't use it. Why?
Because you have to endorse the back, right? Duh. Okay. So now we have two signatures on it. It's
a valid commercial instrument. She puts in a thousand dollar deposit, but what the software
and the computer does is creates $10,000. Okay. Uh, they give you the thousand they're left with
9,000. The bank takes a third of that. And the third of that goes to the government.
So the government is actually funding their projects by sending you checks.
How crazy is that? What I just told you is 100% verifiable and validatable by looking at,
let's see the, the federal reserve bank of Chicago, modern money mechanics,
or speaking to anyone that knows the financial industry. What I mean by that is whether it's
medical industry, financial industry, legal scientific, when you have a certain system
that, uh, works a certain way, even though it's unlawful, when you have people that work for you
that interact with the public, the less those people that interact with the public know about
the real workings, the better off you are. Any illicit operation works that way.
But I would, I would, let me add to that a couple of things during COVID,
the fractional reserve banking requirement was dropped, uh, almost to zero for many banks. So
the multiplication factor that you just mentioned, 10 to one has gone even much higher for a lot
of 900. Yeah. 960 in Asia to one. Right, exactly. Right. And then the other thing that I've noticed
is that, uh, the government needs to create crisis after crisis so they can have excuses
for stimulus after stimulus for the reasons that you just mentioned. Right. So as you said,
the stimulus is actually funding back the government. So they have to find ways to
keep pumping money into the hands of the people and look at what just happened with Silicon Valley
bank and signature bank and a silver gate, massive FDIC bailout. Now, now check this out. Don't mind
me. Yeah, sort of. Go ahead. Yeah. Because the federal reserve just changed their rules and the
FDIC doesn't matter. Go ahead. Exactly. But here's what, here's what I want to mention. So,
so Silicon Valley bank had the, the, the customer deposits because they couldn't loan them out
to as many people as, as a bank normally would. They bought these 10 year bonds
with low yields, right? 1.5%, 1.5, 6% yields. And those bonds were losing money because the fed,
uh, raised interest rates. And so they were being quote, bailed out by the FDIC
with its emergency fund. But where is that emergency fund held? It's held by the FDIC
buying government bonds, which are also losing money. So someone's going to have to bail out
the FDIC, which is bailing out the banks. And just as you said, uh, the government's
going to have to print and flood every layer of the system. And it's all going to come back to
the government to keep basically the debt Ponzi going. That's where we, I just wanted to add that
observation. Sure. Sure. Well, there's a big change since the, the United States government
went into receivership. I, I beckon that people please look up bankruptcy receivership, what that
means. I usually use the ice cream shop as an analogy. You have a 70 year old ice cream shop
goes bankrupt. And instead of shutting it down because it's a fixture in the neighborhood,
the creditors come in and they put in their own people to run it. And now you notice there's
some changes. Like instead of it being this wonderful ice cream, you see like a nacho
chips and nacho machine, right? And you see this other thing you're like, wait a second,
why are they doing this? You know that by the way, the chips and nacho machine, uh,
represent agencies that have been put in since 1933. If you know what I mean in air quotes,
things that are not within the subject matter. But I would, uh, invite you to consider that,
um, when you say the government, this it's not the government it's they're using the label as
the government, just like, for example, federal express is not part of the government. You and
I can open a federal hardware store. I, what I'm telling you is, uh, this is really immovable that
the United States government du jour or lawful government don't no longer exist. It is,
uh, under receivership period. And everything that's put out is just put on, on that label.
Very similar to how a car company, car companies were bought by other car companies. I think
Chrysler was bought by Dammler Benz and I have one and it says Chrysler on it. But when I get into
the parts, it says Dammler Chrysler, you see, so it's federal reserve United States government.
So it's very, uh, it's very interesting. Um, it's all, it's all to distract you. Um, not,
not necessarily. Yes, it is a lot of energy is putting into distract you, but now they're
running out of energy to distract you. So they have to start telling you where you're going and
what they're planning on doing next. You see, and it's been done for over 90 years. Um, and,
and we just kind of leaned heavily on the financial, but the medical one is a big one.
And I just want to suggest to anyone listening to me, go online, do a, uh, and type in cross section
of human intestine, cross section of human skin, cross section of lung tissue. You get where I'm
going with this and you'll see plenty of anatomically correct drawings online.
And then I want you to split your screen and do cross section of a steel belted radial tire.
And if you look at the cross sections of all of our human tissue and a bicycle tire, a motorcycle
tire, a car tire, you will see that the structures are the same. Nothing ever passes through. So
they basically have been telling humanity that we are a bunch of pressurized filter bags that
absorb nutrients and all this stuff. None of that is happening. It's all by induction, right? And,
and once this becomes a, sorry, I had to really put this in because once we understand how our
work and what we really need from food and water and environment, that's when this, that's when
we're really going to become like the Jetsons, you know, the futurists, the future society.
Yeah. But as long as we don't understand how our own bodies work or even money or anything like
that, we're just going to be continuing the same way. Well, you just opened a couple of doors
that are going to take, I think, future conversations, of course, but, uh, which
also, I can't believe that we burned through so much time here already. Um, we're going to have
to wrap this up today, but I want to invite you back to talk about especially, uh, anatomy,
biology, nutrition, medicine, all of that, because the medical world is so filled with,
uh, uh, spell casters, almost like necromancers, you know, they cast spells on people like you're
going to die from cancer if you don't start this chemotherapy today. And it's, it's incredible,
the effect that that has on people. But let me, let me ask both of you, Sam and the Greek,
um, give us your, your final thoughts here as, as we wrap this up, we're out of time for today,
but Sam, um, I, I apologize, you know, we could spend hours in these conversations. This is only
a teaser today for people, but what would you like to leave people with in terms of
remembering this conversation? Yeah, um, I would just invite people to consider more this notion
of the world being a fake place, um, in terms, whether, you know, you want to go extreme with
that, with the simulation notion, or just the idea that so many people are censored, that
it's tantamount to something that's fake, that you have to navigate and be very critical of.
It's not so much, I find, losing oneself in what they call conspiracy theories or
these groupings of people, whether it's QAnon or whatever, but it's just being aware that
everything around you has the veneer of being, you know, decidedly fake. Everything is a
contradiction or a paradox. No one really knows anything for sure, no matter how loudly they
profess to. And, you know, beneath the subject, the surface of your public affairs and your
culture, there is this fundamental commonality that this unnamed force keeps people in the dark
about stuff. And this is something that's worth looking at just past, you know, the alt-media
stuff. It's referenced in ancient texts, it's referenced in philosophy, and it's something
that you can be very extensive in your research about. So I would just invite people to consider
that. Okay, excellent. Good information. Again, I want to mention your website,
Greekspeak.com, and the word speak is spelled S-P-E-E-K. And then, to the Greek,
what would you like to say here, wrapping up today's interview? Sure. First, it's a pleasure
to have made your acquaintance. And also, I hope what I have said and Sam have said,
have shown some new direction to your listenership. And we have some, probably some new people
that might want to listen to what we have to say. Indeed, indeed, very much so. And let me give out
where people can find you. Again, it's ocelli.com, O-C-H-E-L-L-I, Ocelli Effect, I guess that's the
name of the site. And then your show is called Ocelli and the Greek, rated Y. And that's a
subscription-only show, correct? Correct. It's the Sonic Events, yes.
Sonic Events. I call them Sonic Events. Yeah, no dogs, no ponies. Yeah.
Okay, all right. All right, fair enough. That's great. Well, to both of you, let me just thank
you for taking the time to join me today and just kind of throw a few teasers out there about this.
I think we live in a time where more and more people are questioning their reality, so-called
reality, because the reality they were taught is, in fact, falling apart right before their very
eyes. So what better time to start asking the really big questions? And I think that's what
we did today. So thank you both for joining me. It's been a pleasure. Thank you for having us.
Thank you. Absolutely. And best to you both on your projects and keep in touch. We'll talk again.
And for those of you watching, I hope you enjoyed this conversation. This is why I
built Brighteon.com, folks, because we want to have uncensored free speech conversations,
and we want to go way beyond just alt media, frankly. We want to go into the nature of reality,
the cosmos, consciousness, all of it. How are we connected, and what's the future of human
civilization? Because, well, frankly, we're shaping it right now, so let's shape one that
we want to live in. But thank you for watching today. I'm Mike Adams. Feel free to share this
interview on other platforms. You have our permission to do so. Thank you for watching
today, everybody. Take care.