Greetings everyone and welcome to Uncommon Radio, Pagan Time, it's March 16th, 2017.
Yes, I did say that P word with a capital G, yeah, just for time marking.
It seems to be a courtesy that helps people when they're looking at archives and things
or knowing if you're getting it somewhere streaming later or live, and this is live
or as live can be, let's say, but in terms of real things, things that are substantial
and lawful, yeah, that's, of course, a foreign term and concept to your average surface-dwelling
earth inhabitant.
Yes, you heard me correct.
It appears to be the seventh day of the first month.
Why does it appear to be?
Now, here's the thing about being lawful, yes, that's a very foreign word and no, it
has nothing to do with any legal society or anything.
Lawful is just what things mean or what things are based on.
For example, I once saw an unlawful carpenter.
What does that mean, unlawful?
He was doing his job unlawfully because carpenters are supposed to build things and this guy
couldn't get stuff built and I was wondering, maybe I'll go talk to him because he looks
kind of dismayed.
He was always either depressed or very happy or always talking about what everyone else
was talking about, but he wasn't good at putting stuff together.
So I said, well, why are you so dismayed?
He says, well, you know, I cut this board three times and it's still too short.
Yeah, that's not very lawful, is it?
Well, if you're looking at stuff, by the way, you ever notice how the sun rises?
Yeah, it's a thing that brings light and heat to the earth.
Yes, it rises in the east in the morning and if you were paying attention, let's say maybe
the way things are lined up or squared, you would have noticed that the sun was rising
cardinal east and I mean due east.
If you live or are familiar with objects that are, let's say, aligned with the cardinal lines,
you know, like north, south, east, west, the sun was very squarely coming up in the east
and so was the moon and you will notice that it will start to drift off of that position
as the year progresses.
So one can say also, if you have these critters or species running around the planet known
as meteorologists and they have websites and they give little courtesy bits of information,
one of them is dawn and dusk or sunrise and sundown and you will notice that even according
to their half-assed averaging system, because they don't give accurate information even
with that, you will find that the days are pretty equal right now and the equinox actually
happened seven days ago.
Equinox, by the way, equi meaning to measure or equal and nox meaning night.
So it has to do with something that has to be measured at night.
Think about it for a minute.
Okay, well, maybe thinking will get people into trouble and we don't want to do that.
So how about we just say it this way.
You know, there's something called the sun and there's something called the moon and
the sun rules the day, like the day starts at high noon.
Look it up.
Have fun with that.
And by the way, when you do discover that the day starts at high noon, who are you going
to tell, right?
But the other aspect is, you know, the moon rules the month.
You know, that's why, you know, for example, if you studied history in some capacity, cultural
history and such, you notice I didn't say anthropology, but you'll find that people
settled their debts with the full moon.
That's why today they try to settle debts with you on a monthly basis.
Don't you get a monthly bill?
So what I like to do is discuss these things and what is lawful and what is real.
You know, here's the thing, folks.
You can approach any topic, even something you don't know anything about.
First go to the source.
Go look at its foundation.
Go look at what it's supposed to be based on, not how it's being, let's say, propagated.
Which speaking of propagation and other things that are proper in their term, not as proper
as in proper as in eubonics meaning proper, but propaganda and other things like that.
By the way, if you're in Europe, propaganda just means any kind of advertising.
But there's a thing that I've noticed, actually maybe, well, I haven't really noticed it because
it's quite invisible.
Let's just put it this way.
It's a ring and it's a ring through people's noses.
It's a ring through your nose, folks, yes.
Now you, you know who you are and you who don't have it know who you are also either way.
Now what this is, it's perhaps maybe, let's call it, let's dub it a cosmic ring.
And if you want to know more about this invisible ring in your nose or through your nose is
probably more derogatory.
That is known as the group mentality, crowd speak.
Ooh, yeah.
What do we have in the news this week that everybody's discussing?
I don't want to get into it because it's all absurd and it has been absurd ever since I've
been on this planet for more than half a century.
But let's just say this way.
Lately, I'm not going to get too specific, but this is maybe thought for food.
Let's just think about it this way.
There's a group of people that have been touted to be in intelligence.
And there's another group that is perhaps taking leaks, right?
And now none of this makes any sense as if it's any news.
I mean, is this idiocracy, folks?
You know, I mean, okay, so you have one organization that is, let's say, relies on the same medium
that's controlled by the other organization.
And this organization is supposed to be giving viable information to the people.
And it's telling you that a bunch of professional panty sniffers are listening and spying on everyone.
That's like what everyone's concerned about.
It's definitely a planet full of morons, times whatever morons with a capital R.
But here's the thing, folks.
I brought this up just as an example recently.
And think about it.
If you ever watch one of these old movies, yeah, old movies, you know, like when Hollywood
really was sort of rational.
I mean, even then it was maybe, well, it's just sort of rational.
Now, Hollywood is just stupid people making movies for more stupid people.
And I have firsthand experience about that in terms of meeting many of them.
So so here's another way to think about it, folks.
You can pretty much say that at some point or whatever, you might have seen a black and
white movie and you might have had a switchboard operator.
And what they did back then is they you called the main switchboard operator and they
patched you into where you wanted to call to until it became more automated.
And they were always able to listen.
As a matter of fact, I was mentioning with someone through history, if someone of great
importance, let's say a president or something, called his hometown, it was very
difficult to get phone calls in and out because all switchboard operators gathered around
to listen in to that one conversation and not manning or womaning their positions.
Right. So so this is very simple.
Also, if you have what's called a cellular phone contract or cellular phone legal
disclosure of any provider, go read it.
It's about five or six pages long.
Very fine print, of course, doesn't matter.
And you will see that they disclose many, many things in there about what is considered
private. And by the way, folks, what you do in private.
You will be rewarded for publicly anyway.
So I don't understand.
I don't want to understand.
And I don't see that anything can be understood through what people are discussing.
And that's just maybe let's just call it Greek speak commentary for the day.
So if speaking of commentary, if you would like to join in some of this commentary or
have a comment on your own, this will this is a participatory event, a sonic event.
And you can call AFR in at area code two one eight three three nine eight five two
five. And it's two one eight three three nine eight five two five.
You will find that number on the left left hand side of the home page in a red box.
And yes, if you don't see it on the left, it's your other left.
So let's do also the Skype convention.
If you do like using something of greater fidelity and you have access to a keyboard
and a headphone and all that other good stuff, you can use the uncommon radio dot com
email. That is the Skype contact also.
So uncommon radio dot com would be the website.
It's a courtesy site that the Greek has for everyone.
So he just kind of looks prepared.
If you're discussing that, you do things about talking at people and they ask if you
have a website, it would be uncommon radio dot com.
It's just a courtesy site with archives.
And the email on that would be uncommon sense.
Radio one at Gmail dot com.
And that also happens to be the Skype contact.
If you put that in Skype, you and in the search context, you will find that and I will
bring you in perhaps and we could probably enrich the discussion hopefully.
So let's just say and also, by the way, there is a chat at American Freedom Radio, which
seems there seems to be eight or so people on right now.
And we're pretty much going to take feedback from that as well.
Let's hope hopefully it'll be a fortunate type of thinking there.
So again, folks, this invisible ring, I kind of threw this a few things out there, lawful
timekeeping, which I'll bring up.
By the way, all of you new age people, these people that you think are so awake and all
this other stuff and you're so knowledgeable and conscious.
Yeah, it's getting kind of old and tired, you know, keep it to yourself because it's
pretty obvious the minute you open your mouth, you don't know anything.
But anyway, let's just keep going.
And all you spiritual types and contemplatives and meditators as well.
So so just go away and you will in the future.
This is not necessarily a commentary that the Greek doesn't like.
Those types is that no one will like those types and there will be a lot of self-loathing
when things are revealed. So what what will pretty much.
Let's just say this as a as a surface dwelling earth inhabitants.
Yes. Yes. You tend to have desires and wants and you think about things hopefully.
And by judging and looking at what is being discussed and what is being what you are
being accommodated with on all of the various, let's say, media outlets.
Right. They could be Visual Sonic, some in print as well.
I think they're left. It's if you look at the information and qualitative
form, what quality is that?
And also, you know, use some discernment and rationalization.
And I don't want to this is the last time I'm going to bring this up.
But if a bunch of professional panty sniffers are being ratted on by someone stuck in some
embassy in another company, country, and it's a big surprise or a big thing for people
to discuss, you're all a bunch of morons.
Yes. And that is the mark of a moron discussing what is in the news.
But anyway, why am I saying those things?
Maybe because they're true. OK, so let's continue.
There are things that that are going to be happening and you may not be aware of it
if you got that invisible ring in your nose, because that ring and that invisible ring in
the nose, I think, is part of the cosmic censorship and you're not paying any
attention. At least it's not missing airplanes and corrupt politicians this time.
Right. Yeah.
Start learning how to think, folks.
You know, it's like a concept of like love.
People say they want love or love is good.
No one can define it.
Try to find find an average surface dwelling earth inhabitant, ask them what love is and
what you're going to walk away is everyone's going to be scratching their head.
Well, I guess it's some esoteric emotion you have to feel, man.
Yeah, right. Try to define something for for for starters.
You know, that would be real interesting to see on this planet.
It's you know, here's the interesting thing.
And I'll just bring up a little bit of politics for a moment.
And in the American what they call the United States of America, which is a defunct
corporation in receivership.
And if you understand bankruptcy law, you could look up what receivership is and the
trusteeship and all that, how all that works.
And you'll figure some things out.
Maybe they have something called Republicans and Democrats.
Now, why?
Why are these political parties the only thing that are discussed?
When is the let's say the founding documents or even statutory and codified laws ever
discussed? Uh huh.
Yeah, that was a rhetorical question.
But I paused like I was waiting to hear an answer.
You would have paused for a really long time, folks, because it's just a show.
Now, by the way, one thing I like to call this Greek speak on common radio, on
common sense. These are sonic events, episodes and such.
I like don't like calling them shows, because if you say what you mean and mean what
you say, look up what etymology etymologically what a show means.
And I know there's someone I'll just give a shout out to Blarg in chat.
Yes, I'll just mention that.
I'm sure it might be the first time someone gave him a shout out sonically.
He's been a wordsmith of to some degree.
Maybe he could throw in the definition of or the etymological meaning of a show.
You'll be surprised, folks, not what you think it is.
So there are many, many, many shows.
As a matter of fact, most of it is a show, but I try not to do it.
So anyway, let's just throw in maybe we'll do it, maybe he can't do it.
So let's just bring up etymology.
And by the way, just put in etymology and etym online.
I'm not promoting it or anything.
It's just convenient. It's not the best.
It seems to be the only one as well.
Go in the search box and put in the term show.
Now, it's a German word from what I remember.
OK, thirteen hundred exhibiting a review appearance put on with intention to
deceive. Yes, recorded from the 1520s, meaning display spectacle, so on and so forth.
It gives certain examples.
It hasn't really. Now, then there's, of course, as in a in a basic metaphor, non
metaphorical sense, let's say material sense.
It would be to gaze, behold, inspect, examine or choose.
But it seems like it's interesting how the deception part comes in very well.
There's a lot of people having shows which are very misinforming, by the way.
So anyway, let's just not be so harsh on reality, but it is a harsh reality.
With that said, by the way, speaking of a harsh reality.
I want to just thank everyone who has taken heed to certain requests, requests that have
been made in the past couple of weeks with Uncommon Radio, but perhaps doing a little
experiment to see how interest can be conveyed in the form of, let's say, exchange
and more directly would be going to the AFR homepage and contributing something and
putting in the box or the title or subject that it is for Uncommon Radio.
That would help quite a bit.
And the reason we're doing this experiment is because I like to do sonic events that
have that have a limited, let's say are terminated.
I don't like to keep things ongoing.
And after the previous one, I was considering doing a membership area or something more
exclusive. And once I discovered the amount of time and effort and cost it would take
to sort of assemble it properly, I was wondering it would be really funny if you did
something like that, like three people showed up.
Right. So how about doing an experiment where people can, let's say, have a pseudo
membership for four weeks openly on AFR with Uncommon Radio and go ahead and donate
what you think listening to the Greek is worth.
Yes. And at least you'll be getting fresh corn here.
You won't be having to sift corn out of anyone's poo.
So hopefully we'll be serving whole wheat, not puffed wheat and whole rice and not
puffed rice. So in this case, the experiment so far, we're about halfway through.
We said we're going to do it about four weeks.
And that experiment is just to see how much attention, let's say, quote unquote,
credit where the financial attention can be garnered and sent towards AFR.
So we have a kind of speaking to AFR and management there and I set a goal for the
four weeks, just a roundabout figure.
And I want to thank everyone because we're about halfway there.
I just pulled a figure out and I said it would be great in four weeks if we could
raise this amount. And I'm not going to say what it is, but I would suggest that
we're about halfway there.
So whoever has sent something, I want to thank you.
Thank you very much, because really at the point that we are right now, let's say
whoever we are, let's say the Greek, on getting things organized to do something
more exclusive, it's not going to happen as I see the input that's coming.
Yes, you sending emails and feedback on everything that's being sent is very
gracious, but it takes a lot more work than that.
So anyway, I see there's a couple of things, your average comments in the chat
and also there's a question, would you briefly discuss fermented food?
Just a moment. Let's just keep that there.
So I just wanted to extend thanks to everyone who has and I wish at some point
something can be done just for those people, because it takes a lot of effort
to go ahead and even just send it, even though it's digital currency that's being
created on the way.
Well, anyway, it just shows that the intent is there at least.
And there's something can be garnered to be used.
But I don't know.
I just want to say we're about halfway at the point where I'd like to be.
And I'd like to see if we can complete the other half tonight and next week, if
not sooner. And that would actually put everything in a place where maybe more can
be done. But there's nothing, no loss there, because I would say that if you've
ever heard the Greek speak for years, I'm saying it's not time yet.
That time will start rolling around, around what you folks call 2018 or commonly
because you folks are not everyone I have found out through communication on email
and things is even considering the calendar as being real anymore.
They've kind of seen things for what it is.
In other words, when it comes to keeping time, the emperor has no clothes in this
case. And these are things that will be considered.
By the way, I just want to bring something up.
I'm going to go to questions and emails and things tonight.
I was recently on a private Skype call, and it was very interesting because there
were I just want to comment on this very quickly.
There was a if you ever heard me say how people that are profess a certain religion
don't know anything about the book that they supposedly study, I had quite a bit of
that and a discussion with someone regarding that and just proving that was true
again. And someone else who was an older person, I'm not going to mention who it is,
who has garnered quite a bit of attention on the Internet regarding certain fields
and also who was very easily complicated with some of the very basic stuff that
you've heard out of Greek speak that should be taught to children when they're at
least eight years old about how to keep time and how everything is kind of skizzy
wonkus and no one is paying attention to anything and there's no accuracy and
precision. So I just wanted to state that I did a little more, quote unquote,
socializing this past week than I normally do.
And I still see that the world is still in a very sad state of affairs, which it
doesn't disappoint because it just has been that way for a very, very long time.
So unless you're over twenty five hundred years old, you haven't missed anything
worthwhile, let's say. So let's just see here.
There's a there's a question just before I wanted to get into emails and questions
as well. But let's just do the question for us to see.
Hi, Greek. Would you briefly discuss fermented foods?
I've heard you mention that fermented foods are very active in adverse effects
on a being's comfort during digestion.
Oh, not really. No, I haven't said that.
But I haven't heard that there is effect can be medicinal.
No, I've never said that if what I would say is the Greek hasn't said that.
Let's just say the the adverse effects aspect.
The only thing that I've noticed other than if you pass gas, it just means the
body's telling you, you know, don't eat that.
But the adverse effect, I did not mention anything about fermented foods being
adverse. I'll give the example.
Let's do this backwards.
Let's see. The first part was fermented foods and it's adverse.
And then digestion, the comfort for digestion and all that.
The adverse would have been raw foods, for example.
There's there was a raw diet practitioners.
And yes, it's it's live food.
It's it's very beneficial if you're active.
You know, look at the animals that eat raw foods all day and coarse things that
people wouldn't eat high in fiber and such.
And they're very active.
Like for an example regarding people surface dwelling earth inhabitants, let's
say you're you're a construction worker, a delivery driver, very active on foot
all the time, aerobics instructor or whatever.
You can you can you probably would enjoy a benefit from a raw food.
But if you are sedentary sitting in an office for eight hours a day, you will be
miserable because just sitting there.
And there's many other aspects to that.
By the way, when you're eating food, speaking of raw, the mastication or
chewing, there's an old saying in certain circles that says you should drink your
solids and chew your liquids.
Yeah, you heard you heard it correctly.
I'll say it again. Drink your solids and chew your liquids.
What does that mean? Well, drink your solids means that when you put food in the
mouth, chew it, chew, chew, chew, chew, chew until it becomes liquefied.
Right. And then swallow it because that's where digestion begins in the mouth.
The the the chewing the solid liquids, it would be don't guzzle drinks, mix them,
swish them around in the mouth because digestion begins in the mouth again.
When liquids are mixed with saliva, they tend to be accepted by the body in a more
favorable fashion.
So let's say we're addressing the question backwards.
Those are the things. But fermented foods would not necessarily.
They actually aid certain digestive processes.
And are they medicinal? Can they be medicinal?
Yeah, well, all of it's medicinal.
For example, if you had aspartame, that is medicinal like a medicine.
It's it was a witch doctor.
Would you give you that to put put to make your brain into Swiss cheese?
Maybe it's some alchemy, too.
Right. I'm just no, I shouldn't say that.
But yeah, medicinal to what kind of a doctor?
Yeah. Let's say you went to this witch doctor.
He might want to give you strychnine.
They might find it very medicinal for you or a poisoner.
Right. A pharmacist.
The word pharmacy means poison, by the way.
Pharmakia or pharmacopeia means to poison.
Yes. That's why they have the little crosses or the hatch hash mark through the R.
Because that's the Rosicrucian symbol, the double cross.
Anyway, look, these people, look, these Illuminati, Illuminati's are going to get us, man.
Right. Uh-huh.
No, they're just accommodating you.
When you change, they will change or go away.
Whenever you see stuff you don't like on a social level, folks,
none of that stuff can exist unless it's accommodating someone.
And they're into volume.
In other words, they like building institutions and things that accommodate many, many, many people.
They won't go after one at a time.
Well, they want to kind of like enforce certain things.
They'll try to come after you one at a time sideways.
But anyway, so the fermented foods.
Now, the thing that I've discussed always or the Greek has discussed on fermented foods,
it's a form of transmutation based on seasonal eating.
And by the way, this is a lengthy, you know, it's more than just asking what time it is
and telling you how to build a clock.
These are things that need to be considered practically and try to give a practical and
rational explanation.
But I think perhaps let's just shoot perhaps the next episode for being a live cooking episode
in the kitchen, making rice and potatoes and roasts and various things for two hours.
And we'll see how they come out because they've gotten very good reports on the two previous
episodes I did about a year ago with Seth Michael regarding food.
So let's just see in terms of fermented foods.
Let's just backtrack even further.
That's not in the question.
You know, when you eat seasonally, like, for example, if you live in a cold climate or cold
weathered place and you eat food that is grown in the tropics, excuse me, you will
experience your body changing to living in the tropics.
And what will happen there is you will feel cold and you might get sick and vice versa
if you're in the tropics and eat food that's grown in a cold place.
And this is an extreme example.
That's why you have people getting the cold in the winter when they're eating all these
quote unquote pagan holiday foods and things like that.
So when you actually have a food that is fermented, you know, I mean, something like a pickle
that in many cultures considered put in their hamburger or a sandwich that is a cucumber.
And when you ask for a cucumber and ask for pickle, you see that they are two very different
things.
But you rationalize that the cucumber is a pickled.
The pickle is a pickled cucumber.
You'll see that they're extremely different.
And pickling or fermenting is a form of transmutation.
You'll see that with the dairy products, meat products, vegetable products, fermentations
change things.
It's, let's say, a mild form of transmutation and it changes the thing.
So you probably could eat it out of season if it's fermented.
And that's the short, long-winded answer to that question.
And food is very important to discuss because it's about food, clothing and shelter.
Let's see.
There's, we're offering samples of the cooking episode.
All right.
So the reason why a discussion of food is important is because it is one of the most
importance for being here on the most important things that you can do being on this planet.
You know, here's the thing.
And you might say, well, Greg, that sounds kind of petty or whatever.
You know, food is one of the most important things you do on this planet.
Yeah.
You know why I say that, folks?
Because I've been watching what kind of news and media you've been indulging in.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
Sure.
Yeah.
Every week, it's just another ridiculous thing.
So you're going to have to get over it and you will because you're being set up.
And here's the thing.
I wanted to go to this email that was sent.
I said I was going to answer a few things on air.
And many of the responses that I give on emails perhaps have already been answered.
But I think that when the questions are brought so directly, that answering them as they come
in perhaps rehashes and re-invites more thinking on these subjects.
And by the way, folks, in case you don't know and you wouldn't know unless I told you,
the majority of the private messaging that I get is regarding things spiritual,
meaning of the mind and of scripture and of law.
There's many things to discuss.
But I would say that the majority of it is regarding ancient holy rites,
let's just say, in common vernacular.
But I love to discuss that.
I personally like to discuss those things with accuracy.
But I found that the public at large, they still find it in bad taste.
And for example, when you bring up something out of what's called biblical
or scriptural or whatever, most people say, well, I'm not religious.
When you hear that, let me translate what that means when someone says I'm not religious.
Because everyone is religious.
If you brush your teeth or tie your shoelaces or anything you do regularly is religious.
So what they are really saying when they say I'm not religious,
I'll translate that for you, in essence is,
I don't want to discuss that because that topic has been made so disgusting
by watching what everyone in mainstream religions do.
And I'm too sensible to be that stupid.
All right.
So that's what they're really saying.
So this is still the point until these mainstream institutions
start falling off to the side a little quicker.
They are right now.
They're all being sort of people just do it in rote.
They don't know why they're doing it.
They just do it.
And I have never heard anyone, by the way, in private,
ever praise the religion that they were a part of.
Whether it's Islam, Christianity, Buddhism or whatever.
In private, they'll always say, oh, yeah.
My parents said, oh, yeah, they're all a bunch of whatever's.
But, you know, but in public, it's like, oh, yeah, I'm this.
I'm this.
I'm that.
Yeah, this is Gustave Le Bon, because, you know, you know,
there could be there could be the guerrilla aspect of it.
Also, where you hide out, you know, when in Rome do like in Rome
or some kind of cosmic spy, you know, you want to mix in with the morons real well.
But but either way, this I just wanted to share that with everyone.
So if you feel that way, you feel like you're thinking that way.
Also, it's totally normal.
So that's that's one way to consider it.
But the email again, the subject is regarding many of the things I've discussed
regarding the subjects of the gods.
When I say spiritual, that is of the mind.
And by the way, folks, I mentioned earlier, you know,
how shameful it is to listen to these new age folks.
The love and light, the intent matters.
The you know, they're just the new age crap.
You know, it's just junk.
And you all know it.
Even those that do it know what it is.
But anyway, they can't define anything.
All these people think they're so spiritual, you know,
the reincarnation ones and all that, you know, they're so yeah.
OK, ask them to define spirit and soul.
And you'll see that they can't or they'll tell you it can't be defined.
Right.
They can't.
They don't want to.
They're lazy because here's the thing, folks.
The people that you're looking up to, unfortunately, are relying on your ignorance.
And they have found you to be so reliable that they're not going to change what they're doing.
So, you know, I spoke earlier before the episode started.
This chapter, let's say a sonic event to one of people at AFR.
And I said, you know, I don't have to speak the way I do.
You know, like I got some messages saying, you know, Greek, you got great info, great stuff.
And really, it's not about the info.
It's about the mindset.
Because I don't have to be this way.
But I don't want people to really listen because they like me.
I've seen that too much.
I've seen too much where, you know, have you listened to this person?
I said, well, what do they talk about?
Well, I really like them.
I'm like, yeah, OK, you really like them.
What are they talking about?
I really like what they're saying.
OK, like, what are they saying?
Well, I don't know, but I really like them.
Yeah, uh-huh.
No, no, you're all a bunch of morons.
Sorry.
And, you know, you statistically, you know, there are a few that are not, but, you know, few.
So the thing is, you've got to latch on to something that is going to create a direction,
maybe that, how about getting an invisible ball cutter to remove that invisible ring
through your nose that gets everyone to sway back and forth about what everybody else is
talking about and not paying attention to what is going on?
Think about it.
Anyway, so, again, regarding the spiritual aspect, when I say that, it means the mind,
like the PSY prefix.
It would be good to actually bring this up every time I would come around here for two
hours because, you know, I found what's interesting.
I once gave the analogy where we're working with someone part-time and they work somewhere
else full-time, and when they came to work with us, it took them about half the day to
get into the schedule of the program that we had, which was always quality-based, and
because they were real crappy because they just came from a regular crappy production
type place.
So really, they're only good for half the time they were there, even though we're part-time,
because it took them half the day to realize that we do things differently, let's say.
But then one day, I ended up speaking to someone who worked at the production place.
I said, I don't know what you guys are doing, but this guy, when he works with you, he comes
back, he's really great, you know?
And I'm like, oh, really?
Because when he comes to us, he really sucks, you know?
Now I realized it.
So what's going on is you folks are being dummy-loaded all week, night and day, everywhere,
and you tune into something like Uncommon Radio.
The first hour is just like getting the dummy load off, you know?
It's like if you have a spouse who teaches grade school children, when they come home,
they continue speaking to you as if you're in grade school or something or you're eight
until they kind of get that out of their system.
So I noticed a lot of the thinking questions and stuff in the beginning, even people that
email, they know there's something wrong.
Well, I wouldn't say it's wrong.
It's definitely not wrong because everyone's doing it.
But I'll tell you for sure what's going on.
It ain't right, that's for sure.
But I wouldn't say it's wrong because what is being done with all media streams, all
media shows, mainstream, alternative, yes, all of them that you have access is they are
accommodating a certain mindset and accommodating a certain audience, yes.
So when you ask one of these spiritual morons to find the spirit or the soul and they can't
and they don't want to, they're accommodating that ignorant mindset, right?
So look, I've had on previous discussions, people go by what's fashionable.
And if you don't think it's true, if you don't have any relatives or old enough yourself
to remember looking at photographs in the 1970s with those tacky polyester patterns
and the wide lapels and bell bottoms, come on, you put that on because you thought it
was good looking or because everyone told you it was.
So anyway, this week, it's not so good because I'm actually looking at what you folks are
doing.
You folks meaning you know who you are and you folks who are not, you folks know who
you are also.
It's ridiculous and it still is and it's going to be for a little while yet.
In about a year, it's going to start changing.
And let me just give a little bit of information here again because it seems like redundancy
and repeating is important because it seems like a lot of the commentators that talk about
the panty sniffer, I mean the intelligence agencies, I mean the propagandists, I mean
the disinformists, they seem to one of the criticisms that is rational is that they always
repeat.
When you keep repeating a lie, it seems to be buried into people's heads, right?
Think about it.
So the thing is, if it keeps being repeated, it gets in people's heads.
Interesting.
Well, I'm not here.
The Greek isn't here to put anything in anyone's head.
But what bears repeating is this, just for the sake of efficiency, think about it.
Let's be efficient.
What is efficient?
It's the opposite of waste.
And by the way, when you're not efficient, the gods take it away from you.
So anyway, let's just look at it this way.
Very simply, what you are witnessing right now is the precursor to the formation, not
the formation, the precursor to the formation of a Middle East Union, not like the European
Union, but the power base of the world, whether it's economic, judicial, social, political,
industrial, intellectual, entertainment, religious, it's all going to be focused out
of the Middle East, what is known as Western Asia, the center part of the center mass of
the earth.
Yes, you may not know it.
You may not like it.
You may not want to like it and you may not want to know it, but sorry folks, it's
coming.
And if you know about it, you know how to make better decisions, right?
So it's about decision making.
Good decisions lead to good outcomes and that's called being efficient because there's
not a lot of waste.
What makes something considered a bad decision perhaps is that it's wasteful or you wasted
time and energy.
And right now is the way that I see it, all of the media that's out there, all of it
is just spinning your wheels.
It's what's called a dummy load.
Now a dummy load is something, it's an engineering term.
I know it's got a cutesy little kind of name.
A dummy load is a load that you put on an electrical system to see if it'll handle
what it's designed for, its capacity in the field.
So if you have an amplifier or a light or something in the bench, you load it up like
you would before it goes out in the field just to see if it works according to its design
parameters.
And right now, everyone has been dummy loaded for over, let's say a few thousand years,
but right now it's being done very quickly and very masterfully through what's called
the streams through smart devices and computers and stuff like that.
But anyway, so you are, keep in the back of your mind, you are witnessing the precursor
to the formation, not the formation but the precursor to it, the next seven years of all
eyes on a certain part of the world and you're going to be looking there and you have been
looking towards that part of the world almost every day.
Let's say on the world scene or in discussions, but you don't know why or you think you
know why because it's evoking or eliciting some emotional thing to you like, oh, look
at all the killing there.
Oh, look at all the war there.
Look at all the suffering.
Yeah, that's all going on.
But that's part of being on this planet, by the way.
And by the way, also, none of this happens without the gods allowing it to happen.
Yes, so yes, and we're not really crazy because I have imaginary friends or anything.
Yes, so the gods, you heard me correct.
There is no god.
It's all gods, plural.
And amongst them, there is a head god, supreme deity.
Yes, sorry to tell you, but that's how it works, folks, and you're going to find out
later.
But everything is going to be going towards what's called the Middle East.
And in the near future, we're going to be discussing greater detail.
But we might actually opt to do some of it now because I kind of mentioned this is an
open members area, and we have 20 minutes before the break.
So how about maybe doing a little bit of that right now?
Because this really just ties into answering what's into this email that I wanted to get
into, perhaps one or two or three.
And they all kind of go around the whole notion on how there's more than just political or
scientific reasons for why things are happening.
And scientific is supposed to be knowledge.
And it's just like any other group that professes something.
There is no knowledge.
And I have someone who would like to call in.
So before I start on that thought, how about I bring them in before we change another
thought and go into another thought.
So let's just see, folks.
I'll bring him in right now, perhaps.
And I believe he's been on before.
Let's see if he picks up.
Excuse me.
So there's much to discuss and much that can be done accurately.
But the thing is, again, folks, I've been watching what you folks listen to and pay
attention to, and it's just laughable.
Otherwise, I want to cry.
Greetings.
OK, I believe it's Sam, right?
And you want to come inside.
Greetings.
Hello.
Welcome to Uncommon Radio.
Greetings.
What's on your mind?
How are you, Greg?
Sure.
Well, I'm sorry that I interrupted what you were about to go into.
I did think that that was interesting.
Perhaps I should have waited a few minutes before.
No, that's all right.
But I did have a question concerning something slightly off topic, perhaps not
slightly, significantly off topic.
That's OK, go ahead.
I will say that it would be nice if you could come back to what you were talking
to later when I hang up.
But I wanted to ask a question concerning the biblical text and try to connect that
to today's times in an attempt to understand how the Christ related to certain
characters at that time.
So when I examine the key, many of the key characters in what is called the Old
Testament, they seem to have a common thread that runs through their narratives in
terms of how they relate to the Christ in the sense that their lives were meant to
serve a purpose in his plans in as much as their positions, wealth, influence and
choices advanced the kingdom of Israel.
Hold on, stop one minute there.
Did you say Old or New Testament?
Which one?
Old, old.
OK, gotcha.
OK, go ahead.
So it seemed as if those characters were very much used to advance the kingdom of
Israel and foreshadow the coming of the Christ himself.
And as much as the example that they set, but it doesn't seem as if the Christ put
that much of a premium on their character or morality.
And I say it seems that way anyway.
The idea of creating or molding those people into exemplary models of lawfulness
seems somewhat absent.
And by lawfulness, I mean that word as it is used in King James speak, thou shalt love
the Lord thy God with all thy heart, mind, soul.
The first greatest commandment.
And the second is love thy neighbor.
These two commandments on these two commandments hang all along the prophets.
And if lawfulness is actually summed up as love thy neighbor, then it kind of feels like
a lot of those Old Testament characters fell short, even the so-called patriarchs.
Yeah, there's many aspects to it, but you have to realize what was dictated to them.
And by the way, folks, before we answer this, I just want to state that Sam, what he just
asked represents 90 percent plus of all the private questions that I get, because people
that are thinking about what's being said have some background in this.
This is not a quote unquote Christian or religious as people would take it.
This is just inquiring on things that are important.
I just want to say, folks, to everyone that's listening, Sam, that this is about 90 percent
of what I get behind the scenes through emails and other messages.
So I'm very happy to discuss it.
First of all, the interesting thing is when you look at the entire text as being holistic,
the dictation that these patriarchs or men in the Old Testament prophets and so on were
getting, it was coming from the Christ himself, right?
First of all.
Second of all, you'll notice that there is an irony that is displayed throughout the
history of mankind in this book.
You'll see that there's always the rights of inheritance come to the firstborn son,
but how many of the firstborn sons actually got a real right to inheritance?
It seems it's either the youngest one or the second one that gets it, right?
There's just a tremendous sense of irony.
Now, the time of discussing the neighbor, if you look at that neighbor, that word actually
means people that live in the same covenant as you do.
It's not just someone like a neighbor.
There's an old saying, I guess, in Western culture.
It says that good fences make good neighbors.
I find that to be the best saying regarding that if you're living in a mixed group, right?
This is a neighbor when you're not in a mixed group, right?
When you're not setting yourself apart from them.
Think about it.
For example, if you live in a big city, there are people that live in big cities, apartment
complexes for years and decades, and they don't even know the name of the person that
lives next to them, if you've heard this before, right?
I've seen that.
I would suggest that also looking into the term of what love is.
I think I brought that up earlier.
When you discuss love with people, they can't define it, just like most people can't define
spirit and soul, all these things that should be defined before we go on to the endeavor
known as life because we can use them properly once we know how to define them.
I would suggest that what you will find when you discuss things like love or what that
word evokes is some esoteric emotional feeling, right?
They don't know how to use it practically.
That's why you see they fail in it.
That's why you hear falling in love or why would you want to fall?
That doesn't sound good, right?
And also when people are infatuated, you know?
So the love aspect is there's the agape, the erota, and the philia, and there's other
aspects of it in the Hebrew.
But basically, essentially, when you're reading the ancient writs, love means doing the right
thing, even though you don't feel like doing it.
And by that definition, we can say that a lot of those people fell short, if not all
of them.
And I did want to point to a particular example that for me is a bit of a conundrum that perhaps
you could shed some light on.
And that is the character of David, who is constantly cited as one after God's own heart,
which I think is almost verbatim of what it says in the Book of Acts, and at least in the
King James Version.
And the same highlights are used to lionize him repeatedly, slaying Goliath, refusing
to kill Saul, writing the Psalms and being a mighty warrior and things of this nature.
Most of those narratives conveniently glaze over his atrocities.
He had no control over his lusts, had multiple concubines.
Unashamedly, he lied to the high priest Ahimelech about being on business from Saul when he
was actually running from Saul, causing the priest and his colleagues to be killed.
He deserted the Israelites, defected to the Philistines, the absurdity of which should
be lost on no one.
He went to live in Gath under King Ashish with the Philistines, became a bandit, raiding
the Gezerites, the Gerzaites, and the Amalekites.
And he also feigned being insane.
Right.
And, you know, he would kill the towns, everybody in the town that he'd raid and things.
Sure.
Let me just stop you right there, because this is the point also that I want to bring
up.
Remember how there's an irony I've brought up.
There's an irony in these things.
And the irony is that mankind is still in an unfinished state.
But what made David so elevated in terms of his persona to the most high that whenever
he realized he had screwed up, he didn't go to anyone else first.
He went to the most high first.
You see, that's why.
So, you know, that's I think I might have mentioned to you or someone else recently
that I even once had a discussion with a, quote, unquote, orthodox priest discussing
political and economic stuff.
And I brought up how this is all being put on by the most sizes.
Oh, this has nothing to do with God.
This is coming from your religious people, by the way, folks.
So this is to show you the opposite of David.
In other words, most people, even then in that culture, if you read about a lot of the
calamities that were befallen in Israel, they had many other blames.
It was the Assyrians.
Oh, it was the Babylonians.
It was this and that.
And the prophets trying to let them know it's your behavior, right?
That's doing it.
And it's the it's the creator that's doing it, not them.
Right.
You see, so the thing about what you will get out qualitatively out of deciphering,
getting information out of it is that man is in an unfinished state that will do
what the spirit is solely when the spirit is solely manifest through material.
It does.
Right.
Because it gets corrupt.
But the thing that elevated the position honorably of David and others that do this, by the way,
not just David, but David is the one that is cited the most or the best citing would be that
when you notice something either good or bad or questionable, you go to the spiritual high
ranking first.
That's what it is.
It's kind of but it feels a bit unlikely that he wouldn't have known what he was doing over
the course of a year.
I mean, he lives with the Philistines for a year.
He went with the best Hebrew thing for more than a year, I think.
Yes.
Well, yeah, it's likely that he knew what he was doing.
Yeah.
Well, no, I didn't say that he didn't know what he was doing.
There's a there's a persistent there's a persistent, I would say, motivation or drive
that the physical body has, you know, the various aspects of the body has upon the
spirit, upon the mind.
How many times have you heard people having or doing things in private that they don't
talk about publicly or that's very common?
And people, you know, having different personas, you know, when you get to know them?
Yeah.
Right.
Why?
Because because there's so many ways to be.
It's more interesting that way to them, it seems, or what if for whatever reason they're
doing it, it's being done at this point.
Because there's another thing that it's granted that people are not omniscient.
If they don't find or if the information regarding someone else's behavior and secret,
whether it's good or bad, is is communicated to them, they don't find out because they
don't have the ability to to find you see.
So they think because no one can see them in a human agency.
They're OK.
Like, for example, when you brought up with what David was doing through human agents
and him being a human agent with other humans, right?
He found that it would be it's what he wanted to expedite at the moment.
And if you'll notice, if you read between the lines and read out of it, he was not I
wouldn't say short tempered, but very dynamic, very energetic and actually thought about
it as he was doing it versus thinking about it and then doing it.
Right.
He was very much like into the moment, but but not, you know, he still understood what
was right and wrong, but he just went ahead with many things.
Also, you have to realize the dynamics of the situation at that time.
That was the height.
I would say, well, it was pre height of Israel in terms of because really they didn't
have their height till Solomon came when everyone did a tribute.
Right.
Very much.
But they were building up to their height and also the surrounding nations at the time
were almost at their height.
Right.
They were very powerful.
They weren't in a weakened state.
They had not been in a state where, let's say, later on, you'll notice historically
what happened is the predominant forces were Egypt, Assyria and Babylon, and everyone
else was subsided or subdued.
This was a time before those forces were risen to subdue the others.
In other words, there was no real superpower at that time.
Everyone is vying for some position.
It's very, very dynamic.
I think of it as the dynamic city states in ancient Greece before the Athenians and
the right took over.
So you have to also look at the conditions.
You know, you also if you look at many of the things that were discussed regarding
David, it was a matter of life and death, just about all of them.
Even Bathsheba's husband was sent to.
Right.
It was very convenient because there was always war going on.
There's always battles going on.
And when he went to the priests and said he was on business from Saul, he actually not
only got them killed and all that, but what did he do?
He took the vestment, the ermine and to communicate whether he should fight with the
Philistines or not.
And he was told, yes, you will prevail over the Philistines.
Why wasn't he corrected then?
You see, because he had divine intervention, by the way, folks, I've mentioned this
before on air and I'll say it again.
These things you call this thing you call prayer or whatever, that is a technical
thing.
In other words, it's just like the radio officers in the military.
You know, the officer has a radio person next to him.
It's very technical.
There are technical aspects to it.
And if you look at the holy writs of the world, they tell you the technical aspects
to prayer.
It's by the way, why do they bring this up?
It's because what you're being shown in the mainstream religions is the opposite of
what you should be doing, by the way.
So anyway, so I throw that.
No, let's get let's let's get into that.
How do you pray in a way that's acceptable to the Elohim today?
Do you direct your prayer to the Christ or to the father?
Does it matter?
That's for the members only area, man.
I'm just joking.
This is this is the aspect.
I said it would get more juicy, right?
These these next steps.
This is how I would consider it.
We don't need to make stuff up.
If you have access to the information, just read out of it.
Don't read into it.
It is to be done in private.
For example, if we look historically, let's go with the biblical convention.
There was no prayer being done at the temple.
Do you notice?
There were offerings.
The temple, by the way, let me just bring this up, because this is the way it could
be thought of.
Let's just I'm going to discuss church because that's the circus.
It means nothing.
It's very important in certain cultures.
If you look at Rome and Greece, so the circus was a central aspect.
If you said anything bad about the circus or don't go to the circus, you were viewed
on very negatively, just like today.
That has that thing you call C-H-U-R-C-H is not in the biblical text, not even close.
It doesn't exist.
Only they just put that word in there.
Somehow doesn't even come close.
So forget about all the stuff that you're you're being told and what you believe in
means absolutely nothing at this point.
You know, meaning the listening audience, what you've been told about it because it's
you can trace its roots where it goes back to.
What we're discussing is what can be traced from the founding document.
Let's say the biblical text.
When you say the temple, people equate it with churches and places of worship.
They was not every the temple is every city has a temple, but it's disbanded.
If you had like every city has a major library, a court and a place where judges are.
And we're going to complete this thought and definition when we come back.
Greetings and welcome back to Uncommon Radio, and this is the second hour and we still
have our caller Sam and we were discussing the technical aspects of prayer, were we not?
Yes, we were.
Yeah, and this is not real.
We're not religious, man.
You know, I don't like to talk religion right now.
I'm just on a side note that this is still what you get in commentary.
It's not time yet, by the way, for this.
But what I was discussing was the definition of these these ancient temples there.
Every city still has them, but they're fragmented.
So if you have a court building, a library and a university, if you were to put all those
three aspects of a society under one roof or one complex, that would be known as a
temple.
Think about it.
And also you had the place where the priests were doing offerings.
OK, which is basically the court building still where the priests are wearing black
robes in the anyway.
Anyway, that's the situation you're in.
They're doing offerings to the justice God, the Babylonian revived anyway.
So why am I bringing this up?
Because most people have still been duped into thinking that they pray.
You've heard this in public.
Let us pray.
Right.
It's like, oh, you want to run away from that, you know?
And by the way, when I hear about all these different groups praying, I'm like, you know
what?
Let's be rational.
Things just seem to be getting worse.
So why don't you stop praying for a little while and see how things get?
Anyway, I was just a little private thing there.
There's more to be discussed about that.
The other thing about that is what you will notice that these temples, they had little
private booths just like the libraries did.
Everything was read out loud and done in private.
It wasn't a big open area.
It wasn't silent.
So some of these private booths were also used for quote unquote prayer.
Now, another thing you'll notice is that the Christ said, don't do like the pagans where
you go into open areas and do all this stuff.
Go into your private room.
And by the way, whenever anything is brought up that is contrary to the churchianity in
the King James, it's translated as something distasteful.
That's why they translate it as go into your closet because that's where the skeletons
are and that's where bad people come out of, right?
You came out of the closet where skeletons in the closet, right?
So you'll always notice that King James always uses those negative connotations to things
that are lawful because, you know, remember this is a political document that people are
studying.
So you would go into a private place.
Now, another thing that I would suggest is that when you're asking, you are going in
spirit longitudinally, meaning instantly, no distance.
In other words, distance is not an object.
No matter how far away something or someone is, it's instant.
Okay, that's what longitudinal means versus transverse where you have what they discuss
speed of light and things like that.
So with that said, instant communication, the Supreme Being has an entourage around
him, okay?
And there are many layers and he tells you how the prayers come to him just like you
would send a message to an emperor, right?
It goes through many layers, doesn't it?
And typically it's viewed based if it's against his will or for his will or whatever and it's
viewed and previewed, right?
And many of them are not listened to.
How do I know?
Well, it states it in the text.
So I don't listen to you, right?
So now, let's say, for example, if I were to say, we're going to go meet the emperor
later and you're there in a t-shirt and sweatpants, barefoot and sandals.
Are you ready to go or are you going to put your best clothes on?
Most likely, because if you show up with sandals and sweatpants and barefoot, probably
the guards won't let you in, will they?
There's a dress code.
The dress code here would be the state of being.
And what is, let's say, clean and unclean.
This might sound dogmatic to people, by the way, because a lot of people in various religions
say, well, I pray and I get answers.
Well, fine.
Good for you.
So I'm not addressing you.
I'm discussing the aspect of what's been memorialized that can be technically accessed,
not some cult or whatever that's been going on for thousands of years that everyone tends
to group together about.
The other thing that you see, and I'm doing some thesis and antithesis here about both
of the aspects of what to do, what's being done, what not to do.
It's all mixed up.
So you want to be in a clean state.
Now, how are you in a state that is acceptable?
Well, he tells you, my people will do these things.
Now, it doesn't matter what you believe in or what you think it's done away with or whatever.
That's just what's stated.
Okay.
And if you want to learn about what that it's like what you eat, what you wear and days
and time and all that stuff, right?
That's pretty obvious.
If you want to go to the next level with that, right?
What I mean, obvious is if you eat certain things, you're not in a proper state.
If you wear certain things, you're not in a proper state, right?
Like mixed fibers.
I'll just give it out.
He says, my people will not wear mixed fibers, right?
You familiar with that?
Okay.
So, you know, when you go to buy a shirt, you know, it's like 20% polyester, 80% cotton
or whatever.
It's either 100% cotton, 100% polyester.
I had someone once say, well, polyester is no good, right?
I said, no, no, it doesn't matter if it's synthetic or natural.
It just should be woven with like.
Okay.
So, you consider all these things.
You also consider the time of day and things like that because there's a time of cleaning.
You know, you are clean until evening, which is noon, by the way.
When you read evening in what's called the King James, it means noon.
It's not evening when the sun goes down because you can't measure sundown.
It's sundown is actually the last hour.
There's no measurement there other than a general, you know, division of the sky.
And also think about it in the desert.
It's warm or hot in the day and at night it gets really, really cold.
Colder than more temperate places, right?
So, imagine washing, doing all this washing at night and then, yeah, right.
Uh-huh.
That can happen.
And the word that's being translated as evening is the word edeb, which means, edeb means
to emanate from the top of the house, meaning the sky, you know, the, okay.
So, we can go on from there.
There's something else that's being shown to people about prayer where they put their
hands together.
You ever see that?
You see a lot of iconography and you see them doing that.
Excuse me.
That is a Hindu convention and that's the left palm is man, the right palm is God and
you put them together.
That is a pagan convention, right?
They usually, when iconography in a lot of the Catholic convention, they have a iconography
of Mithra or Serapis, the guy with long hair kneeling.
He's got a red robe on and he's got his hands together, right?
He's kind of bearded and long hair, right?
The Serapis or the Aescepulus is the other one that they show doing that.
Those are ancient cult symbols.
Has nothing to do with scripture.
Has nothing to do with the Most High.
And it sounds dogmatic when you say it that way because it sounds like, oh, if you don't
believe what I believe, you're not doing it.
You're not saying it.
You know, it's dogmatic.
No, I don't believe in any of this.
The thing is, you either know it or you don't know it because there's nothing to believe
in.
These are things and directions and things that are memorialized in information, the
things you can grasp and know and do now.
Belief is something that you are given information on something that will happen later.
There's no belief in any of this stuff.
You either do it or you don't do it.
And it's voluntary.
And here, I think we had a discussion once, Sam, off air, where you ever notice how in
scripture there is no oppression?
Right.
But all of these religions tend to oppress other groups, you know, the Inquisition, you
know, every religion has a form of oppression on another, even the Hindus and the Buddhists
and that if you look, if you know anyone who's Punjab, you know, they've been oppressed by
these other groups.
So there's in law, there is no oppressiveness in lawfulness.
This is lawfulness.
It has nothing to do with what you believe.
There's a lot to believe when you study scripture.
In other words, prophecy, things that have not happened yet.
That's the only belief that you can have and faith and things that have not happened
yet.
But most of it is very practical.
And it's not to be forced.
It's not to be imposed and not to be convincing to anyone.
It's to be edifying.
In other words, if someone, you ever see people standing on street corners and stuff
trying to convince other people to convert to something.
They knock on dark home in the Jehovah's Witness Protection Program.
You know, those guys, all these people, that's completely unlawful.
All that stuff is.
So it has to be through genuine inquiry and edification and impartment.
There is no convincing of any of this.
That's why it sounds dogmatic, because most people have that pagan mindset.
And by the way, there, let me just define one thing.
There's this thing called paganism now that's supposed to be popular.
That's just another level of stupidity.
It's a fashion thing where you paint your fingernails black and you wear dark sunglasses
and long coats and get a bunch of tattoos.
It has nothing to do with anything.
The entire world is either pagan or atheist.
There is very little knowledge of the gods that is being discussed or accessed publicly.
Now, there are still a lot of divine intervention by lower entities and demons that pretty much
everyone seems to become expert in.
If you look at the mainstream religions, it's all demonology of some respect to
another.
And actually, if you have a discussion with a senior level Catholic bishop, they'll tell
you, yeah, we basically practice demonology.
We won't tell the people that.
But anyway, so basically, in short, I gave a mixed bag of stuff there.
But in order to be in a proper state, there are rules.
Depends on what deity.
If you want the deity that the scripture talks about, it tells you, my people will do that,
do those things.
They're still accessible.
And the other thing is be private, be vocal, and your hands are open, palms facing up,
not closed.
Right.
And here's the thing.
You know, when you have a spouse, they are, you're considered one, by the way.
So if you're a woman and you have a husband and a man and you have a wife, when you go,
you can go into prayer together because you're considered one flesh.
Like, for example, one of the ordinances is on a certain day, if you do any cooking, it's
just for yourself.
Don't cook for a group or cook for other people.
And once I was cooking for myself and let's say the wife, and someone says, well, that's
not really the ordinances.
Well, yes, it is, because we're considered one flesh.
You see, there's definitions here, you see, right, that need to be observed.
You can't say, well, it says do this, and then, well, I'm going to go do this now, which
is all this churchianity, all this institutionalized stuff.
Now, there's nothing wrong with institutionalizing something if it's lawful and positive.
But if it's unlawful and negative, you see, that's why when you hear the term institutional,
it sounds negative, doesn't it?
It's not a negative term.
It's negative because it seems like mankind has taken things that are unlawful, low quality
and negative and made them far-reaching, far accessible and overbearing in society.
That's why institutional sounds bad.
So in essence, folks, yeah, this is the open secrets area.
Prepare yourself.
You do that by reading what it takes to be clean and prepared.
It's what you eat, what time, your clothing, all that stuff.
And hands not closed, but open palms up, and you talk, you speak, and in private.
And who are you directing these prayers to?
Is it the Christ or is it the Father?
Does it matter which one?
They're one, they're one.
Think about it this way.
You know why he's called the son of God?
Let's just use the regular term that most people use, right?
The son of Elohim, Ben Elohim, let's say, right?
The son of the Elohim, plural, or of the Father.
Because this is a communication to man, right?
And in the system that was set up for men, which is sort of copying the heavenly realm,
look at the corporate system, okay?
For example, let's say you start a corporation with a board of governors and all this other stuff,
and it's been around for 20 years, and these are older men and all that.
And here's your son that was born around the same time.
He now is 20, which is age of majority.
He walks into the room, and here are all these boards of chair people and all that.
They're twice or three times his age.
Do you know that your son, who has just reached age of majority,
has more authority over all those other people that helped you start the company
while he was still in swaddling cloth, right?
Because he has the authority, right?
You see?
Look how many times you see the son of a corporate, right?
Because this is corporate, meaning it's a group of people coming together to achieve something.
That's another thing that's achieved.
When you say that's corporate, it's bad.
No, it's just that people, corporations have taken on the suit or the clothes
that basically it's people that want to do things to have...
Basically, what's been going on with corporations
is they've set up corporations to make the innocent pay for the guilty.
You see it all the time.
This is, again, unlawful the way they're being run.
Just saying corporate is being negative right now is, again, another stigma
of proof positive that the way man is doing stuff is not correct, unlawful.
So that's all it is.
It's not a literal son in the sense that we see being born from a woman in that realm.
You see, right?
Because things are made there.
You don't have to be born from a woman.
So basically, just to top it up, you will see that they're the same in authority,
especially at this point.
Think about it for a minute.
I'm not going to get into that.
At this point, they are for sure, right?
Right, right.
In history.
So these are things.
So basically, in private, be vocal, palms up, be proper, be fit and proper.
Now, there are other gods, by the way, that you can pray to that are in groups, by the way.
But those are different gods.
There are many gods, by the way.
And that's the main thing.
You know how young children are told lies?
And then at some point, the parents never say, well, we told you lies.
Now you're too old for that.
Why would you raise someone from a very young age about lies about these spiritual things
like Tooth Fairy, Santa Claus, all that crap?
And then you never apologize.
You just continue.
They're setting you.
You ever notice if you're to objectify what's going on on this planet,
you're being raised with lies because everything else you're going to be told is a lie.
You ever think about it that way?
Just just think about it.
All right.
One last thing on the prayer thing.
So this Christian tradition of praying in the name of such and such in the name of what
they call Jesus, is there any validity there?
No, it doesn't exist.
It doesn't exist.
Yeah.
No, that's in some cases you get a lot of people writing.
You do that.
You go down to the what's called the Bible Belt or the belt buckle of the Bible Belt.
Boy, you can't get out of there fast enough.
Talk about a vile place.
You know, this on this planet.
Yeah.
I mean, this is really we're talking about look, this is a very Earth is very dangerous.
And what the people have you look at how people react when you say certain things that are true.
Right.
They're all vile.
All the religions on the planet right now are vile, downright vile.
All of them.
Think about it.
Now, on the surface, they might seem pleasant.
But when you start to look at what they're supposed to be based on, they're actually
doing the antithesis.
They're actually doing everything that's in the abominations or don't do category.
All of them.
So let me just all of them before Islam, Buddhism, all that stuff.
It's all the same.
They're all this is why?
Because this is known as the man.
Social order on the surface of the planet is known as the world.
Who is the God of this world?
The adversary.
Yeah, right.
But when in King James speak, it says, and I will do whatever you ask in my name.
What does that translate to in reality?
Correct.
Yeah, but there is no Lord in scripture.
Lord is ball, which is the balls or or form of elementals or lower imps and demons.
Let's say that, like, you know, sun gods, sky gods and all that.
So the Lord, when people you hear people using the term Lord, they don't know when you hear
people using G.O.D. solely.
They don't know or J.E.S.U.S.
Those are people that don't know.
Right, so right there, when you encounter someone like that, it's a crossroads time.
You know, it's either do you edify, you know, discuss, see if they're ready for more than
just, you know, 19 Arabs with box cutters.
You know what I mean?
I'm just bringing in another thing where Oswald shot Kennedy kind of thing, because that's
what it's like.
You know, you've heard of, oh, you're a conspiracy theorist.
You know, most people see when they're really ignorant, they're ignorant for a reason.
When you think about it, think about it.
Why are there why they're held ignorant?
Because they're dangerous.
And you have to give them guidelines, you see.
So anyway, if you don't think people are dangerous, you ever see cars with flashing lights and
men in uniform with guns everywhere?
I mean, and major where you have concentrations of people in every city in the world, pretty
much.
Why would they exist if the people weren't dangerous?
Think about it.
Why would they have cages for people if they weren't dangerous?
You don't think they have cages for people?
Sure, they do.
There's something to be said for the fact that they are engineered to be dangerous also.
That's right.
But it doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter the objective report.
If you were to come to this planet just for one day and report back, that's what you would
say.
Of course, they've been led into that position because who's the god of this world?
It's very simple.
All of this stuff is so simple.
Having discussions regarding law, regarding the gods, regarding the human body, regarding
what's called science, which is knowledge, the cosmos, let's say, or the cosmos actually
means the earth, but let's say what's out there, it's not feasible at this point.
Because people have been fed a bill of goods, which is a lie, pretty much everything that
they've been told, or it has a little bit of truth in it, just like something that's
counterfeit.
It appears to be true.
So they're going to always be comparing that.
They hold on to that.
The plausible deniability or the cognitive dissonance, anything that comes in after 12
years old is compared to everything that has come in since you were 12.
You see, it's constantly being compared.
But the thing is, right now, you have to realize that being in such an adversarial situation,
you know, where mankind is adversarial, look, even man is adversarial to man, right?
Right.
And so spirits are adversarial to man.
You have a lot of adversarial conditions right now on this planet.
Now, it doesn't mean predatory.
That's different, you see.
But there's also a lot of predation, there's a lot of pranking.
So there's many aspects.
Here's the other thing also.
Let's say we consider this is the third episode we're coming around and considering it like
open members area to see what kind of support we can garner for perhaps doing something
like that, which I find distasteful, but I'd like to keep it all open.
But let's just see what kind of support we could garner, by the way, and send a donation
to American Freedom Radio at the homepage, if you will, if this is any if helpful.
And if it's not helpful and you don't like what's being said, send a donation also so
you could keep it going.
So you could always go to a place where you could say, I don't like what they're saying
and support that too.
So.
So anyway, anything else, Sam?
Yes.
One last question and then I'll take off.
So I'll sort of just pivot into something completely different from the previous question,
which is the subject of AIDS.
You've talked about the virus being a fiction.
So we know that HIV doesn't cause AIDS.
So what exactly causes AIDS?
Is it a disease that existed historically called by another name?
Or did it really pop up in the 80s?
And does it have any relation to the homosexual community?
Yes.
No, it's well, it's when you said the homosexual community is the lifestyle, not all quote
unquote, homosexuals or sodomites have gotten that because they didn't all go through that.
Do you know how I mentioned there was fashions and trends where certain groups excel in
certain behaviors?
Yeah, there's quite a few people out there that have written about this.
And also, when you look at the story behind DDT or what causes polio, see when polio, when
DTT stopped being sprayed, polio went away.
And then at the same time, the medical community said, oh, it's the vaccine.
And there's doctors that went to Congress and testified about this.
There's a lady who wrote a book about it and all that.
So what is called a virus is simply a form of mitochondria, cell tissue that's broken
up and it's produced and gone through the liver back into the bloodstream, just waste
product.
If anyone can go do a general cursory study on virology, it is a branch of toxicology.
OK, and in toxicology is a branch of the study of the liver function.
There's a lot.
There's actually, I wouldn't say prominent, but semi-prominent German researcher who's
been in virology for 20 something years.
He just threw up his hands.
This is all fraud.
No one's ever seen one.
It's only computer graphics and pictures that are described, but they have no effect.
And he actually has a website.
If you could put in medical viruses or fraud, I forgot his name.
He's from Europe.
And it's a big thing to do that in Europe because they have socialized medicine.
Right.
So there's no reason for him to buck the system.
I mean, because it's not predatory.
You know, so there's many aspects to this that understanding how the body is in a sealed
condition, the only openings from the mouth all the way down through the anus, right?
The two openings, a tunnel in and out.
And the group we mentioned before, they go reverse too.
Right.
But anyway, so the thing is, I would say this is the thing to consider.
If you look at all the layers in the intestine, of course, you know, how does anything get
through there?
Something passing through that tunnel could influence through induction and other things,
the body, right?
Something through the skin can influence the body through induction, can't it?
Something going into the cul-de-sac of the lungs can influence the body, you see?
So there are contagions, yes, but they don't operate and function the way you've been told.
Like earlier on, like I don't have audio listening to AFR.
Someone had put in the chat earlier something about immune, whatever.
There is no such thing as an immune system, period.
What's the organ for the immune system?
You have circulatory system, nervous system, eliminative system, nutritive system.
And the lungs and the skin are both eliminative and nutritive.
Where's the immune system?
These are things that are developed for communication purposes.
And then they take on a life of their own, like they exist.
And people are so lazy.
They say, oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because remember, there's a guy called Gustave Le Bon in the crowd.
You've got to come up with an idea.
And people, you know, they just, oh, this is a great idea.
But the thing is, you can't convey the idea to the people because they're too simple to
comprehend it.
It'll bury them.
So you have to oversimplify it.
And when you oversimplify the idea, very little of it resembles the original idea.
And now you're off into la-la land, which is what you see, you see?
So the interesting point is there is no point to any of this.
It's just taking up time.
That's why the three most important things are understanding what your mind is or the
spirit, understanding your soul, which is the breath and the metabolism, the function
of the body and the body itself.
And then it's food, clothing and shelter.
With that being said, we do want to understand a few other things, too, so that we're not
completely groping in the dark.
But you have to.
Actually, here's the irony of it.
It's kind of like there's a film called The Karate Kid where the young man was put through
these exercises and he didn't know why.
If you pursue mastership of food, clothing and shelter or understanding the mind, the
soul and the body, what else is there to learn?
Because on the path of learning that, you will actually grasp anything that's tangible
and intangible on the way.
OK, that makes sense.
So AIDS.
Can that be?
Automated immune deficiency, whatever.
Yeah, here's the thing.
Actually, you could still do the keyboard warrior stuff on that.
And you'll see there's a lot of back and forth and it shows you the aspect of society where
society is regarding truthful information.
That's a good topic to bring up, not because to bring it up, to discuss what it is, because
many have debunked it.
I don't want to get into that.
There's you know, because then then it becomes, well, he believes this and he believes that
I want to get into that.
This is a planet full of morons.
They they deserve stupidity like that.
You know, I mean, that's one way to say it.
The other way is they deserve the truth.
But the thing is, they want to fight about it and neither one is going to settle in.
You know, here's the other thing about it.
I used to tell people back in the 90s, there was a big thing about selling life insurance
in the insurance industry.
And this one guy wanted to do it and he had these little postcards before they offered
someone a policy was an AIDS test.
And what you're supposed to do is prick the finger, put it on a dot, put it in an envelope,
send it to the insurance company to give you a policy.
Right.
And I used to play a joke.
I say, everyone you're going to test on this is going to have AIDS.
And he's, oh, no, not everyone that they did test had AIDS.
And the way we played with them and did that is I said, listen, before you do that blotter
for the Stanley guy, right, that was his name.
What you're going to do is I want you to go eat some rare meat, like have like a rare
steak dinner, you know, like the real like black and blue rare.
Right.
And within two hours after eating that, go ahead and do the blood thing and you're going
to show up positive on an AIDS test every time.
Just like, for example, another thing is cancer.
Your basic cancer screening is like those dollar store pregnancy tests.
You know, the pregnancy test thing, if you show up positive, if you're a guy or whatever
that you're pregnant, that's a hormone that they test for when they do cancer screening.
I mean, this is this whole medical thing is a is a show.
It's a show.
It's a it's a pranking, you know.
I mean, look, if it wasn't, why would 80 percent, if not more of the medications that
are prescribed rendered illegal or considered illegal, unlawful and dangerous after a decade
or so?
Do you know of any medications that were like fashionable prescription drugs after a decade
that are not deemed dangerous?
Very few.
Most about 80 percent of them are deemed dangerous.
Come on.
They don't know that.
Who's they?
They don't want to know anything.
Who cares?
This is planet Earth.
Don't you see?
Now some people care.
That's not enough.
In other words, they're still accommodating the masses, the space heaters, you know.
And if you guys have defined what space heaters are before, so.
Right.
Well, this is life on Earth.
Yeah.
With regards to AIDS, I've heard this theory put out that it's connected in some way to sperm
in the sense that sperm, which is housed in the testicles.
You take that and put it.
I'm just sort of using loose speak.
If you take that sperm and put it in other parts of the body, it creates a problem, which is.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Yeah.
Well, we'll think about mitochondria is the inside inner part of the nucleus of the cell
of single cells break, broken up into pieces.
Anything that's not in its environment.
I was ready to make a lascivious comment about that, but I'm going to withhold.
I always have to make a lascivious comment every week and some kind of debunking some
cliche, you know, because this is like a non-carnal mature type, you know, sonic experience.
You know all this.
Here's another thing about this fake prudence and fake morality that the quote unquote
Christianity has.
Oh, I said hell.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You ever see that how they do that?
You know.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I said, damn.
Oh, it's not this fake morality.
I mean, how can on one side you say sin is a big deal.
On the other side, you say the law is done away with.
How do you judge?
I mean, this is all this fake stuff.
Put your children in front of Molex Santa Claus.
I mean, this is ridiculous.
I mean, all of it.
And I mean, you know, the public prayer and the women dressed in burkas and other religions
and the worshiping the fat man and this other thing.
And it's all the falseness and all these spiritual minded people telling you about consciousness
and transcending what a pile of rubbish and reincarnation.
And clairvoyance and psychics and intuitives and meditative.
What's going on, Sam?
These people, they've lost their minds.
No one is making any sense anymore.
Statistically, they are, but they're not speaking.
Please, if you are semi rational, semi intelligible and have some information, do a radio show.
AFR has got some open slots.
Come on, speak to AFR.
Tell him the Greek says I want to do a show.
Talking about stuff that people need to know the truth or do a website and send me a link.
Please, somebody, please.
You know, but we digress.
Yes.
Yeah.
No.
So the thing is about the AIDS.
I want to leave.
As you see, I'm avoiding it because there's so much already about it.
I've already directly answered.
Here's the point.
It's kind of like discussing what size shoe Santa Claus wears.
Yes, that sounds like a big discussion, doesn't it?
But Santa Claus doesn't exist.
In other words, you're all right and you're all wrong.
Right.
It's like discussing viruses.
You're all right and you're all wrong.
These things don't exist as they people think they do.
If you actually go back and look at what they call AIDS and what they call viruses and all
that, as it's been memorialized, you'll find all that information is true.
But the way that people discuss it is false.
And all the religions are like this, bar none, bar none.
They're all like that.
What the people think and what they do and what they think they know about it is not
memorialized anywhere other than the allegiances.
Like, for example, if you read the allegiance to the creator of the Catholic Church or whatever,
you know what it says?
I profess to believe or I whatever.
It's a swearing document.
I believe in one holy apostolic what?
Church first.
The circus.
Cirque, right?
The Cirque.
That's where they pledge first.
If you ever read any of the creeds and the pledges to these institutions, all of them
have it.
It's called a statement of faith.
And they have it.
And actually, when you join the church, they send it to you.
And years ago, you're supposed to sign it in various degrees.
But now they don't have you sign it.
Now they just do the administrative default.
If you got it and you don't send it back, they could go back to their administrative
body and say, yes, they swore to it.
You see, they're just playing the game.
Because why not?
I mean, like no one's paying attention.
It's taking advantage.
So basically, you're swearing allegiance to the Cirque, the church or the circus or
Cirque.
You know, so it's like, have you lost your minds?
No, no, you haven't.
Because this has been going on for a very, very long time.
What do you know about a skepulous, the god of health?
What do you know about Serapis?
What do you know about Mithra from ancient Egypt and the collaboration between the
Greeks and the Egyptians?
You see, and this goes on and on.
This is also, by the way, not just a rant on the religious side of it, like we brought
up the topic.
This is also the rant on what?
The medical side.
Right.
We're talking about like in Egypt.
Oh, Egypt was so great.
Really?
OK.
So when a woman had menstrual cramps, they prescribed bat's blood and cat urine.
Mm, yum, yum, yum.
That's really good.
Egyptians.
Oh, they're so great.
If the Egyptians were so great, how come they're still laying in ruins?
Can you tell me?
No.
Better wake up, people.
You know, so and you will soon.
I mean, we've got a roughly, you know, this is roughly I don't call it the new year,
but it's the first week of the first month and we're going forward.
Right.
It's going to be interesting to see what happens in the next year when people start
to get their senses for the first time in over 2000 years.
Can you imagine what a time that will be?
I can only imagine.
It'll be dangerous for some.
Well, it's going to be you see, the thing is, you don't want to scare the frog out
of the pot.
Now, remember, this is the thing that people don't comprehend and don't want to understand
is that right now, humanity for the past 18 or so years has been set up by the gods.
You're being set up.
And part of the setup is that you're going to be lead or led into the finishing line,
which is like the starting line, which is a grand civilization that you read about in
ancient times.
Like I mentioned, Egypt and Babylon and Assyria and all that will be revived in a way that
you will completely accept it.
And then the kill shots start coming because when the gods go in to do war with a society
or to take out a society, it's not much of a war because of their ordinance.
They prop you up to your highest position.
Then they come and take you out.
It's the opposite of what man does in their war where they soften the and lower the tart,
you know, lower the opposition.
So and pretty much the majority, 99.999999999% of the people on this planet are falling for
it, are going to fall for it.
And it's amazing that this can still be said publicly as we are doing right now, because
there are a very small handful of people that are beginning to see it.
And there's nothing that you need to read into it, need to start to read out of it.
And one of the main things that you've heard me discuss is the coming Assyria, the new
Assyria in northern Iraq.
Look at the plains of Nineveh, like Mosul right now is a little bit being discussed
and all that's the concept of ISIS that has been around the all the stuff that's going
on in Syria.
Wait until you see what's going to be happening in Jordan in about a year or two.
Wait until you see what's going to be happening with the Palestinians in a couple of years.
The level of carnage that is going to be put on what's known as the modern Philistines
will be unthinkable if you said what it is now by Israel.
But not this prime minister and not the next, but definitely the next after one after that
and beginning with the next one.
And then you see, we've discussed this and this can be discussed maybe next week.
Let's start giving more specifics.
Now, here's the interesting aspect of it.
What's really fascinating is that anyone can see what or it can be.
Let's say this discussion can be brought forth to anyone that has interest to inquire
on the subject.
And once the interest in the inquiry is brought forward, let's say what's called about
things to come as conveyed to man by the gods, you can grasp it and then you can start
discussing it.
But you'll notice that the majority of the subject matter and its impact and import is
not for your everyday man.
It's really for multinational corporations and monarchies and people that have these
big international interests.
And I'll tell you, it's quite amazing to me to be able to come on a minor internet
platform two hours a week and basically pontificate or just throw this stuff out there like that
that is beyond what most of these think tanks that are getting millions of whatever by these
big international companies are getting false, just crap information that they're gleaning
off the internet.
It's just the irony here is just amazing.
You know, Sam?
So yeah, I hear you.
Oh, okay.
Well, thanks for my questions.
Thank you.
Yes.
So BC, it all ties together.
Thank you again.
Yes.
Thank you too.
Well, we'll see you again soon.
Definitely.
Bye then.
Okay.
Thank you, Sam, for calling and actually having someone to bounce some ideas off of.
So what's going on in chat?
And we have not gone through the emails, but we have indirectly to some extent.
So time travel.
Okay.
Even coded code.
We've got stuff.
So here, there was someone who sent me, sent an email to the Greek following.
This was several questions regarding things that have said in the past, perhaps since
I've gone solo here more specifically on the period of confusion.
I'm just going to preface.
This is not in the question, but discussing how the past seven years or so or six plus
years has been a time of confusion and distraction, because this is a time when basically a lot
of spiritual entities through the cosmos or the universe are being corralled down to earth
where they're being quarantined down here to earth.
So when the kill shots come, they will be physically or in the spirit in this location.
And the question here directly to that comment made a while back is, are they coming to earth
gods or other entities?
Yes.
Do they take human form and can they be distinguished?
No.
They can take human form, but they cannot be distinguished unless they allow themselves
to be, and they usually don't, unless they're one of these lower entities that someone has
some grimoire or some form of incantation or evocation technique to do it.
Because remember, they're very technical.
It's just like, for example, if you're a woman and you go by the name Susan, and you're
in a crowd of people and someone yells out, Susan, that gets your attention.
You turn around.
There might be four or five other Susans in the crowd, but because they've addressed you
with the name, and so that's how these spiritual entities work.
That's why when you've seen in some Hollywood memes and things like that, they have to read
something or you hear about these, quote unquote, Satanists that have to get their
access to, and they're not Satanists, by the way.
They're actually just evoking and reviving ancient gods, dark lords, as they would say.
There's a lot of specifics involved in that.
That's why with Samuel, I want to thank him for coming on earlier and asking what prayer
is because they're specific to that.
It's interesting how people take a lot of interest in these minor pagan demonic kind
of things, the specificity, but when we talk about going on a higher level, no one wants
to hear it.
It's because, again, it's all set up for part of the cosmic censorship.
You have mentioned that there are three bloodlines.
One appears to come from the sons of Elohim and the daughters of Adam.
Correct.
Now, when you read in the King James, it says the sons of gods took the daughters of men.
It does not say that.
It says the sons of the gods took the daughters of Adam, which delineates a bloodline, right?
Because once there are hybrids and other things like that, you cannot delineate.
So the information has to delineate.
So that's very good that you brought that up here.
And what are the origin or the other two or more there are?
Do all humans fall into one of these categories?
Yes, that's right, appearing human.
There are three types that appear human.
It is the descendants of Adam, the sons of gods, and the hybrids.
And the easiest ones to distinguish, well, actually, there would probably be the Nephilim
or the hybrids.
Nephilim just means plural of soul, plurality of souls.
The typical hybrids were large in stature.
Let's say they were called giants.
By the way, the word giants is not in scripture.
It was put in the subteragent only, but it's easy to render the term correctly because
of the descriptions that are given.
But they're also polydectyl.
They have six digits on hands and feet, which are typically removed these days in nursery,
in birthing rooms, what they call them, things like that.
I would say that the third one, the sons of gods, which are not born from women, by
the way, if you remember from ancient literature, people would be addressed as such, you, man,
born of a woman.
I mean, what kind of a statement is that?
Isn't everyone born of a woman?
Think about it.
But they are basically the subcontractors that were part of the remaking of the earth.
And when they have offspring, they are pretty much mimicking what has been developed over
a thousand years for developing Adam.
I know this sounds kind of crazy, but make good science fiction, by the way.
But when they produce offspring, they're male and they come into existence as full
adults.
And you might have seen it in some of your sci-fi also, where they have these breeding
tanks and cloning and stuff like that.
One of the problems with these sons of gods that come into this reality as full adults
and male is that they do tend to exercise, presuming exercise and enjoy the thousand
year lifespan, which would be of Adam also, which tends to be problematic.
Because if one of these cats or guys lived in a neighborhood for 100 years and didn't
seem to have aged a month and everyone else is born and dying around them, they're going
to start asking questions.
So they tend to move around a lot.
They tend to move from city to city, town to town.
And because they're around so long, it's easy for them to get wealth and power.
So actually, a lot of these things have been indirectly described.
You might know of Oscar Wilde, you know of various other stories of nobility, the way
people were addressing each other.
If you read between the lines and learn to read out of it, once you understand the sons
of gods are different.
And but here, because they use the formula or the prototype of Adam or the model to make
Adam, they are fully compatible with women that are descended from Adam, just like Adam
was fully compatible with Eve.
So I'm just addressing that.
I know this sounds like crazy talk here, because when you compare it to what else is being
said, yeah, it's very contrasting.
But I'm just stating it because I said I would probably try to answer this on air and
everyone else can benefit.
So there you go.
And maybe we'll get into more depth and cite some examples on these three.
Well, you know, presuming most people are descendants of Adam and also discuss the hybrids
and the sons of gods, the Elohim, plural.
So this is very hard to discuss, but I would say gods, because most people in the Judeo-Christian
only think there's one.
And there's no such thing as monotheism, by the way.
That's ridiculous.
There are many, many gods.
As a matter of fact, the biblical text of the scripture cites about 36 to 40 of them
by name.
But there is a hierarchy, you see.
So and when you believe in a god, believe in that he's going to do what?
See, so in the faith and all this stuff, it's not just time yet, folks.
But if you're into Uncommon Radio and you're here, you know that maybe the time is now for
two hours a week.
And I'm sure here by we're about an hour and 45 minutes in, the dummy load has been
rubbed off of the minds from being dummy loaded all week.
So we'll see what we can do here for the next 10 minutes or so.
But let's see.
The other question here is, how does one race serve as a clock on this era?
Do certain events with this race signal the end of this age?
Not really, not with the race, no.
It's basically the human race and their descendants and different bloodlines within
that human race descendants of Adam and the hybrids and the sons of God.
So that's sort of like another thing.
So let's go to the next here.
As there is an anti-life agenda with the slowdown, the finale for a certain number of humans
necessary to pass through Earth.
Yeah, yeah, there's actually the finale is very interesting because it's all repeating.
Things have repeated.
Like for example, when you read about the last days will be like the days of Noah.
Well, look around you.
How many people?
About seven and a half billion.
Who knows who's counted, but let's just go with the  by the way, the World Bank,
that's their baby.
That's their puppy.
That's their little function is to count how many products, human products or credit
lines they have to offer.
They are about seven and a half billion right now.
There were about that many around the time of the flood about 4,500 years ago.
So yeah, don't think that you're modern and so expanded and so great right now.
All these things were once but different.
Here we go.
Lastly, is it possible that our perception of time is changing, i.e.
speeding up?
Well, yes.
Time is the recordation of events.
Are the events going to perceive like they're speeding up?
Yes.
I'll give you a personal example.
Like by the wind-up toy, it was two hours before I was to come on to radio and five
minutes passed by.
I look at the clock and it was 20 minutes.
So the hour and a half went by like five minutes.
So I guess it's what you're doing in the mindset.
But here's the thing.
Perception of time, if you're on the Pope's work schedule, you have no perception of time.
You have a perception of when to go to work and when to have a weekend in the dark, by
the way.
So I'm not convincing or suggesting even that anyone should understand lawful timekeeping.
I'm just putting it out there that such a thing exists just like such a thing as rational
and lawful thinking exists.
And it's quite interesting to come here for two hours a week to propose such a thing here,
meaning American Freedom Radio, which I'm grateful that they've given me the platform
to do so.
But otherwise, if you just for both the other hosts and American Freedom Radio, what is
being said and represented by the Greek does not represent American Freedom Radio or the
other hosts, not even close.
So I just want to always give a little bit of a disclaimer there.
Wink, wink.
I just want to also suggest that this is to consider donating to AFR, not only to donate
to AFR, but you're really indirectly donating to the Greek to see what kind of a cause can
be launched.
So just to remind everyone again, this is the third episode or third time around, third
sonic experience that the Greek is trying to perform an experiment to see how much support
can be garnered from the public at large about sending some kind of contribution to
AFR, which will sort of maybe be the measurement of what can or could be done in a private
member's area.
Because many of these things can be elaborated on.
Just like I said, there's two hours a week here.
Pretty much the first hour is to shake the dummy load off, because I know you guys have
been dummy loaded all week.
I know what you listen to.
Why?
Or read.
Because it's most likely on the internet and I have access to it also.
I have not really been looking at it.
This week may be a little bit more than usual, but I'm in touch with enough people that I
ask if there's anything interesting going on, just cite me a notice or let me know and
nothing much.
It's still the same dummy load everywhere, and I mean everywhere.
What about donating here?
What about donating to the meek?
Yeah, it's interesting.
Go look up what that word really means.
I'm not going to give that away.
When I was doing a previous Sonic episode called On Common Sense, very similar to this
with a co-host, Seth, I was trying to dispel a biblical cliche or some cliche every week
and just to show in an indirect way how erroneous what people are relying on is.
But again, remember folks, you all sort of partake in things that you find readily available
and convenient to access.
How many people do you know, including yourself, that tends to go out of their way to get things?
I mean like really out of their way.
If you live in a neighborhood where they have let's say a butcher, a baker, a candlestick
maker and all this stuff, do you really want to go to like five neighborhoods over to get
the best meat or the best bread or the best candles or whatever?
You see, no.
Most people just go what's conveniently, and this is the neighborhood market.
The internet is now the neighborhood market.
So what happens is there's a quote unquote mainstream ridiculous dummy load story that
is best fit for a five-year-old or third grade mentality, which is probably an eight-year-old,
and all of you, and I mean all of you, fall for it and discuss it.
That is pathetic.
I am so sorry for humanity at this point.
Anyway, I just have to say, and this has been going on.
I've been on this planet for more than a half a century.
So I've got to say this is all I've noticed.
The beauty of this is as you're being set up and as we go further into time, yes, the
recordation of time, as we go further and further into these events, regardless of how
esoteric the emotions get, regardless of what you think is going on or what you're being
told or even dummy loaded about or concerned, it's all about the setup of the central part
or center mass of the earth, which is known as Middle East, and if you're going to live
your life with efficiency, you will be able to see what is in that area, what is in that
part of the world with efficiency and clarity.
I'll give you another example.
One thing that I have been saying for over a decade is that the Western world, the Western
culture, the Western convention is going to be playing second fiddle to this new, let's
say revived way or convention, which is all things old, like if you want a new idea, read
an old book, but all these old religions, sciences, conventions are going to be revived
and seen as something new or coming out of the ashes of something bad that is going on
there right now, but the Western world is going to be playing second fiddle.
What a better way?
Look at what's going on with all of the Western leadership, Western banking, Western
industry.
What Western industry?
Where is it all being manufactured?
You can sit and complain and bitch and moan about where you are, meaning if you're in
the Western world, and take place in its inefficiency only to be even more inefficient later when
you see everything going to another part of the world and wishing it was here.
How about acknowledging what's going on and taking part of it with efficiency?
If you want to know what is coming in the future, you better have a pretty good grip
on the past, right?
For example, if someone lights a fuse, I think Alfred Hitchcock in one of his docos or
documentaries gave an example about suspense, and he said if you're going to do suspense,
you can't just have a bomb blow up.
You can't just have something explode and shock the audience.
You have to show the audience that there is a bomb under the desk where the man is
sitting unawares, and it's like the audience is crawling in their seats trying to talk
to the actor on the screen.
Don't you know there's a bomb under your desk?
Get away.
That's how you build suspense.
Well, I'm not trying to build suspense or anything, right?
So this is not like something that's going to be going off like that, but it is going
to be going off in slow motion where it's going to be acceptable, but it's going to
be extremely destructive to your ways, and there is nothing anyone can do.
When I say you, I'm addressing the Western Convention.
Yes.
Well, your mac and cheese and Stouffer's lasagna and your hot dogs and all that crappy
food that's eaten in the West, I mean, I'm not talking about the French and the Italians
and the Spanish, but all that crap that you folks eat might be replaced with falafels.
Ha ha.
Anyway, so anyway, this is just one way to just say things, just keeping it real, like
they say, right?
In the ghetto.
So let's just put this one thing that you folks should look for.
This is a place called Iraq, right?
And the northern part is known as the Nineveh Plains.
Watch that.
Watch that this year.
Do me a favor and watch that.
Yeah, uh-huh.
See what's going to be happening there.
I've been saying this for a long, long time.
Yeah.
You ever notice how there's a lot of turmoil and you're suffering all this, I keep using
this tonight, esoteric emotion about what's going on there and what to think about it?
Yeah.
You ever hear of a place called Israel?
You ever hear of a place called Iran?
Yeah.
Do you know that everything in the Middle East right now is revolving around those two
superpowers?
Well, let's not call them superpowers yet.
Yeah.
Think about that.
Mm-hmm.
But watch Assyria.
Assyrians.
What do you know?
That's Syria.
Assyrians.
A-S-S-Y-R-I-A-N-S.
Yeah.
What do you know about those people?
Better start learning about them.
Yeah.
Talk about efficiency.
So let's see what the chat's doing here.
Oh, yeah.
You love falafels.
Good.
Yeah, you should.
I once made falafels, by the way, for some people that were not familiar with it and said,
what kind of meat is that?
I said, it's the boneless kind.
They said, oh, it's very good.
Anyway.
Yeah.
The end of a plane.
Start looking at all that stuff.
And also, I do see there's a wordsmith.
Yeah.
It's someone I mentioned earlier.
Blog, there's a wordsmith in there that likes to cut and paste etymological terms.
Yeah, that's good.
There's nothing wrong with precision and accuracy.
And I think it's the way to go.
So for anyone, which you won't find, by the way, in any media stream that you're looking at
because you're being accommodated.
No one opens up a gas station in the middle of the desert unless they're going to accommodate
the passersby.
And when that road closes, that gas station has to close, too.
With that said, we have one more week.
Let's see what kind of contributions you folks can bring.
Please bring it on to AFR.
Thank you.
It's the Greek signing off till next week.
Ciao.