Greetings everyone, this is the Greek and welcome to Uncommon Radio, also known as Uncommon
Sense or Greek Speak or other things, but those other things, yes.
So let's just give a little bit of a time marker.
You know, the Pope's work schedule with the conventional marker, the one that the cosmic
censorship allows to be known typically, will be, you'll find it on archives when you look
at this being solo number five.
This is a fifth solo event by the Greek.
And in terms of keeping real time, not Muppet time or pagan time or whatever else
everyone's been convinced of for the past 2000 plus years, really about 500 years, I
would suggest through observation, maybe it could be validated by others as well.
I would suggest today is the 21st day of the first month till noon.
Yeah, you've heard that correct.
You know, the day starts at noon.
Look it up.
Have some fun researching that.
So, you know, have fun because you're discussing the Pope's work schedule as such.
Well, you know how they, you know, your work, you know that no one wants to work.
Right. You want to time off.
You want to have fun.
You want to have a vacation.
So take a break, take a vacation from that work schedule just for a minute in your life,
maybe a day or two or a week.
The reason why I bring this up is even in other conversations that I have off air, people
say, man, I've heard you and, you know, that thing about, you know, the sun and the moon
and keeping time. I just can't explain that to people or I do and people don't want to
hear it. I'm like, yeah, but, you know, you have to consider, you know, it's not just
what's being said that anyone can notice.
And you can wonder why they don't notice these things.
It's you have to everything is strung together and you have to consider the cosmic
censorship. People are censored.
I was just having a conversation about certain things, let's say, about the body and
nutrition and all that.
And, you know, it was like, why don't you do a show on that?
And I already did. I kind of bring it up almost every other time.
And what I've noticed is many of the things that are said here on Common Radio seem to
be still.
Hmm. Let's just say it this way.
It's not checkers.
It's a form of chess.
And it's not because there's an opponent to play with, but it's just like how things really
operate. You know, things operate differently in checkers than they do in chess.
Like, you know, a pawn can take a king, but it usually doesn't because priorities are
considered before movements are made.
But if you actually look at what's going on in the world, very few priorities.
Anyway, before. OK, so let's just let's just get back.
When you hear something or someone hears something through Greek speak or what's being
imparted here, because this is a special kind of thing.
And you will see that it's not that's not to counter a lack of information or something
that may be false or something.
There are many layers that you have to go through before you even consider what's being
said. Hey, it's really simple.
Typically in the chat, I go in there and I say, well, they're so dumb, they couldn't even
pour piss out of a boot, even if their instructions on the heel.
Well, does that have to do with being dumb?
Not really. But it's just it's just showing that, you know, all you have to do is look for
the instructions and the job is done.
So I kind of use that if anyone's been in the AFR chat room, I kind of use that as part of
the nomenclature of knowing that the Greek is coming around to do some kind of a sonic
experience. So many of the things that you hear, like the conversation I had recently
with someone saying, yeah, I've heard you say about the sun and the moon and just lawful
things and just people either they don't want to hear it, they can't hear it or they don't
grasp it. It's because it's not checkers.
This kind of information tends to just stand outside the door of the mind, and even
when it's let in by the mind there, it has to go through many, many entries and egresses
you have to in and out of other things to really get gotten.
It's like you have to crash down walls and doors and perceptions and things like that,
because the reality, again, as can be discussed, even I think AFR has a little promo
spot here where they I think it's Bill Hicks or someone discusses reality, always hear
the question of reality.
There's the film called The Matrix and all these other things that tend to show, well,
what is it even have people that are so removed from reality that even say there is
nothing real. This is all tied in with the cosmic censorship.
What does that mean? There's a group.
Yes, there's a group.
It's not the Illuminati, but it is a society known as the gods.
And of course, you know nothing about them, even though you say you do, because if you
did, you wouldn't do what you're doing.
So anyway, why did I just say that?
Because there's a time that's coming where what people think is going to change.
Yes, of course, there's always change.
Just like if you talk about doom and gloom at any time in man's history, it sounds
plausible. But what's different about what what's being said here at Uncommon Radio is
not just what's plausible, things that are done with great specificity.
We don't get into all the ridiculous stuff that everyone else is getting into.
Yes, everyone else.
You could look up what everyone or who everyone is.
So if there was any sense being made anywhere else, personally, I would just you would
know the Greek existed as a sonic entity.
And I would just be privately referring people to where else they can get the info.
Now, the info is, of course, scattered everywhere and things can be accessed.
But you have to consider the times.
It's just not time yet.
Why? Well, yeah.
You know, what day is it?
Hmm. What about starting with something as simple as that?
Here's the thing, you know, this is the fifth, let's say, a sonic event, solo five.
You know, we've kind of if anyone's gone to the archives, we've kind of gotten the
habit of calling them solo one, two, three, four.
And this is five.
Let's see if we can go through the next two hours and have it archived as well.
So fifth position, by the way, cosmically is right before man.
Five is the number of, let's say, the natural manifestations of the Earth.
Yes. The Earth.
Yes. You know, that thing you're standing on.
I was going to perhaps see if I get any feedback either.
I have the email open and I'll go back to the chat and about what to speak on.
Otherwise, I'm going to go through the usual rantings and asking some what people
call rantings and maybe some chat questions.
Otherwise, I believe the best use of time is to give homage, sort of honor the what's
going on in terms of being in the fifth position with this sonic episode, because the
next one's going to be regarding mankind and that's going to be really, really harsh.
I might give a little bit of information regarding what next time around might be about.
And that is a very simple thing that if you've ever listened to Greek speak before, I
always ask. This is not to confound, but it usually does.
What do cannibals, birthdays and dolls have in common?
And if you are looking to comprehend reality, what's called reality and why people
say and do what they do or don't say and don't do what they do, which is actually more
important sometimes, you must comprehend to some degree the invariable description of
man's society on Earth, which could be invariably described as a question.
What do cannibals, birthdays and dolls have in common?
Because that gives you the mindset of humanity, their level of apathy, their level of
repugnancy, if one can say that, and their vileness, not just some specific group of
people somewhere far away in castles or living under a bridge or underground or on
another planet. Humanity in general, meaning statistically 99.999% of the people on this
planet. It doesn't matter if you live in Russia, America, Greece, Italy, Iraq, Chad,
Somalia, China, Japan, Thailand, Malaysia, go on and on and on and on.
There is a vileness in humanity that will be worked through and worked out in the near
future, near future.
Well, let's just not say this week or next week or the next month, because that seems to
be the attention span of your typical surface dwelling Earth inhabitant.
And you've heard that before.
It's just, you know, well, if it happened last week, it doesn't matter anymore.
This is happening this week.
Yes. But I'll tell you what, get a grip on what cannibals, birthdays and dolls have in
common. And this will be perhaps an explanation that is always given when you might
have heard or have heard sonic events by the Greeks somewhere or anywhere along the
line. So before I continue along the line, speaking of lines, we do encourage or who
we are is to be determined some kind of participation, if so needed or desired.
And the way that could be done through the standard telephone lines, I'll give the call
number and I will pull them up.
I do not have them open yet.
It is 218 area code three three nine eight five two five two one eight three three nine
eight five two five.
You will find that on the American Freedom Radio homepage on the left.
And if you don't see it on the left, guess what?
It's on the other left. So you will look at that.
And now if you like doing a slightly higher resolution, higher fidelity would be the Skype
convention. And an easy way to find the contact request, if you are not in contacts at the
moment, is go to the uncommon radio dot com website.
So you it's best to do www dot uncommon radio dot com.
And as you scroll down, you will see there is a Gmail there and that email is uncommon
sense. Radio one at Gmail dot com.
And the one is numeric.
So and I will if you send a Skype contact and I will accept it and bring you into the
the sonic episode, you know, very often you hear the conversation, you know, through the
years, the reason why I interacted with so-called alternative media and other media was
because I just couldn't imagine that the people believed in what they were saying was
true. Yes.
So what does that mean?
Well, so I would call in and try to perhaps not redirect the conversation, but maybe put
in some info or something that might help them along, because about almost all if you
had the Greek calling in, by the way, it's because the information that was being presented
was erroneous. Yes, folks.
Anyway, so right.
And erroneous, not because I believe so or think so, because anyone can see it.
But no one wants to see it.
So I was trying to participate on that level to bring out information.
So, OK, so let's see if there is anything I was thinking.
How about speak about food is one thing here in the chat.
And could the Greeks speak about the changing times in 360 and 365?
You know, I just jumped into a just Greek speak a blog to Tango and I did a quick little
anonymous thing there. I don't really sign in all the time, even though I probably should
to identify. But there is no change from 360 to 365.
That is, where do you start with that?
There is no change.
Nothing has changed times.
No, the times have not changed.
Well, you know, you have to be more specific, I guess, or to pre-flood having full moons
all the time and how the later moon will go back.
He's been full sighted through the colors of the rainbows.
We go through them and relate to.
OK, that's possible things.
You know, it's interesting. I've even had maybe a slighted joke about speaking about
someone will call in maybe and call about scripture.
Yeah, it seems to be the major topic here.
But there is reality, folks.
The only thing is that you are filtered and fogged.
You know, before I go to this question and maybe explain why the times have not changed
from 360 to 365, Daniel 221 is mentioned.
What's interesting is, you know, if you're, let's say, traveling on a road and there's a
fog and you have zero percent visibility, you are absconded from perceiving the reality
around you. It's absconded from you.
Can't see it. It's taken away almost.
But you know, it's still there because there's a fog blocking your ability to see it.
Right. And this is how humanity has been for a very, very long time.
And anyone can get away from that by just a few little hints and a little bit of effort.
It's set up that way.
It's kind of a tightrope.
Imagine, you know, looking at someone walking, walking on a tightrope, how much balance and
concentration they need.
That's how the cosmic censorship works.
It's backwards. It's a form of counter-spatial relationship.
In other words, one very narrow part of reality is in the reality that everyone is
discussing. And that is censored.
And it's censored by the gods because of people's lack of inquiry and lack of
consideration of even just paying attention around them.
Give another explanation of reality and brought up several issues.
You know, it's the fifth episode.
You know, this is right before man comes on the scene, how there is no reality and the
comments on reality and how fogged people are from it.
The concept of discussing humanity, what do cannibals, birthdays and dolls have in
common? In other words, if you were sent down here from the mothership and you had
three days on the planet and had to return back and just give a brief description of
what the morons on this planet are doing, that would probably fit them the best.
Now, and the other thing is, of course, taking in feedback from chat and other and
Skype and calls.
But I would suggest that maybe we'll do one or two or three things at the same time
because possibly walking and chewing gum is a virtue.
But let's just because let's just say first in line is first in time.
I saw this earlier in the chat and then another chat.
But I think it's just Greek speak blog, Chitango or something.
Someone set up graciously a while back.
The time has never changed from 360 to 365, and I'm not going to explain Daniel to
21. I have given hints about that.
Whenever you take something out of context like that, which is an academic
relationship, you know, chapter and verse, by the way, that was done.
So people communicate certain things and it's become a stylized way to comprehend
what's called scripture or the Bible, which it's not.
And unfortunately, at least Daniel is pretty close to the name that one has not been
changed. But I'd say about 90 percent of the names in what they call the King James
do not exist anywhere.
They have been made up for that and also from taken from different languages.
So, no, I don't think it's appropriate to just explain that particular verse at the
moment. But the hints are always there as keys.
OK, you can have a porter come and unlock, give you keys and then take the keys back out
of your hand, unlock the door, open the door and have you walk in and give you a foot
massage. Greek won't do that.
I'll give you what appears to be a key.
You're going to have to walk to the door and find out which door it unlocks and unlock
it. And very often I'll tell you which door it unlocks.
And then you have to go into the room and go to work and maybe take a hot bath because
you ain't getting a foot massage.
So at least at this point, but let me just throw something out there, because very often
I've said publicly these are just, let's say, private conversations that have to be
aired. I just want to hearken back.
I didn't like calling them conversations.
And I said I used to call in and because it's pretty much erroneous information, I
would suggest that it was talking at people.
So here we have someone.
It's the 17th, not the 21st.
OK, now I'm confused.
By the way, I have not been paying attention at taking measurements, so I'm relying on
you folks right now.
And let's just whoever did that, that's really good.
You know, let's just see how it could be the 17th.
Yeah, it is. Perhaps someone else want to come in.
I'm sorry. Did I say the 17th?
Yeah, so there you go.
It's the third week.
Yeah, thank you.
Yeah, so I'm going to pretty much stick to the 21st unless someone has any other
reckoning. OK, sorry about that little break.
It could be maybe edited out in archives, maybe.
OK, why at the wrong time?
OK, so just to go back with times here, you notice the censorship can affect anyone and
everyone. But knowing that it's there is half the battle, isn't it?
You know, perhaps let's just consider it this way.
Knowledge of avoiding a trap is knowledge of its existence.
So but I will just say that if anyone out there is considering lawful timekeeping, the
full moon is the beginning of the month and the day starts at noon.
And there's other subtleties regarding that.
So that can be observed as well.
I would suggest that, let's say, back to the times that the changing of times from
360 to 365, that never happened.
That is according to what?
The Pope's work schedule that what I'm seeing here ensued is that there is a mention
perhaps somewhere of a 360 days being a year, which it doesn't in Scripture, by the
way, that's implied and ensued.
And to three sixty five, that's three sixty five or three sixty four and a quarter is
what the Pope's work schedule does that that never changed anything.
So.
There you go, it didn't change anything at all.
The Pope's work schedule, and that's that's kind of like a joke when when, you know,
like it's like what color is George Washington's white horse?
It's the Pope's work schedule.
Yeah. OK, so I hope you folks got it.
There is no demarcation of the year as such.
It goes from a certain point to a next point.
Let me get just let me just throw this out.
Last year, being a 13th moon, there was over three hundred and ninety four days last
year. No one no one noticed.
Right. No one really noticed.
So talk about a bending reality.
How can one bend reality to the point where they can miss thirty four days?
Uh huh. Yeah.
So let's just see what else is going on.
What's wrong with the wrong time?
We're going to have to catch up with time again here.
We'll see. We'll see how people can wrestle with that maybe and work it back and forth
as a form of exercise.
Perhaps I would suggest that perhaps getting on with more of the conversation unless
the people just want to discuss time or anyone else wants to call in, because there's
many things also that have been discussed on emails and things that tend to have the
variety that the shows do.
But again, I'd like to suggest that the majority of what they call the show, I use
that term. I don't want to use the term show.
Sonic episodes have are that most of the questions are scriptural or biblical.
And someone once told me, yes, Greek, you are accurate about saying that people will
start focusing on that.
Well, you know, it's not just that.
But, yeah, they'll start focusing on these things, but they will not be accurate.
They will be just focusing in that subject, in that direction.
And the time is coming.
So so we'll see how that works out.
So regarding other things to discuss, no one has called in and we don't have much else
on the subject matter regarding time other than several other.
Let's see what days what day it could be.
So I would suggest that if you want to configure the lawful timekeeping, someone in
chat is putting in when the days begin.
So thanks for mentioning month begins with the full moon.
Yes, it does. And it always has.
We'll give history on that.
Now, if some people have also said, Greek, you got some great stuff.
Some people, by the way, are completely enthralled by the information.
Others are like, these are great topics, but you don't fill them through.
You don't finish or you might skip around in case you've noticed.
I kind of mentioned in many, many other episodes that it's not just time yet.
Not only that, certain things just shouldn't be said in the public forum.
There's just too much to be said.
There are a lot of information, by the way, that can't it's not just information.
It's how you can handle the information, the program or the operating system.
A lot of that has to do with very specific people that have very specific purposes.
Sometimes people bring up asking questions regarding a manuscript or something and
they want to get into it because they think it affects them.
And I'm like, well, what do you think that has?
Why do you think that has anything to do with you?
You know, does it apply to you?
You know, of course, there's the concept of you electing what you want to learn, of
course. But I would suggest that most of the things that can be spoken of are just
simply not appropriate, which I would suggest.
Also, I want to give a big say of gratitude and thanks to everyone out there that who
has contributed to AFR.
This was the open.
This is what considered the open members area was an experiment just to see how much
support can be garnered on whether more projects can be done other than the standard
that has been done lately.
So I would suggest that you pat yourself on the back if you did contribute.
It's wonderful. And if you haven't, it would be great if you did.
Much appreciated.
All of this, by the way, let me just give a little bit of what's going on behind the
scenes with that. We had a goal and we exceeded the goal and in credits.
And the goal was exceeded by about 20 percent.
And that was really wonderful.
It was very, very small goal, by the way, very modest.
But it was exceeded, which is good, you know, making a goal regardless of what the
number is and exceeding it is very good.
But it all goes to AFR.
So you must consider that.
So if you get into the habit of it, it's good because they offer the platform for at
least two hours a week of dummy load free transmission or impartment, at least
minimum, at least of that.
So I would suggest that that's not a bad thing.
But on the other hand, there is a project in the works.
Don't know what it's going to be called yet formally, but there is an informal
decision on what to call it.
And it will be a place that will either be accessed through AFR or somewhere else,
which you will find out if so.
And it will be a place where there will be an unabated impartment of discussions,
information, stories, examples, things, how to's, all these things.
But it won't be in public and it won't be one of these tacky members areas or
something like that, where it's just, you know, a lot of I get so much feedback
about all that. It's just it's just tacky.
This will be the real stuff.
Now, of course, you know, everyone, you know, like that, you know, when you take
out pizza, it says the best pizza in town.
Everybody's got the best pizza in town.
Of course, this is going to be different.
It's going to be very different.
It'll be a first and it'll be a thing where you will decide if it applies to you
or not. And if you are on this planet, most likely it applies to you because there
will be, let's say, things mentioned there that will turn the brain inside out just
like a sock. Yes.
Why? Because, well, why not in public?
Well, kind of giving a little bit of that maybe.
Here's the other thing. There is a short laundry list of Greek speak that anyone can
hear. You know, there is, of course, the Pope's work schedule, how the body works,
the movement of living versus dead energies, all these various other things, how the
political system works, the money system, how the regarding information about the
gods. These are just typical things.
And also, if you're paying attention, a lot of hints on what's called quote unquote
science or technical aspects of things, much of it.
So pretty much cover all the bases of what it takes to be a surface dwelling earth
inhabitant. These things have been given out in smatterings over the years.
And there is going to be a place coming that it will be not open to the public.
Sorry. And it will be pretty much unabated, at least as far as time permits,
impartment of what can be said versus a public forum.
So what can be done, though?
I had once a recent communication regarding that is everything that can be said in its
entirety or as much as possible in its entirety, whatever time is given is always
hinted at in public.
Always, always, always.
By the way, there is a previous sonic event that had 18 episodes and then 12 and such.
And if you they're kind of regarding various topics and depending on your aptitude
to want to know more about what's being said, I would suggest going back and listening
to those with a fine tooth comb.
How do you listen with a fine tooth comb?
Anyway, yeah, because there's a lot of hints in there.
A lot of it is not elaborated, but the hints are there enough like a hint regarding
timekeeping would be very, very, very simple would be like, you know, the calendar,
the thing you use, right?
OK, well, you know, you ever observe a holiday or anniversary or something and you
notice how it's a different day of the week every year?
You ever notice that? Well, you know what?
Because it's arbitrary and they even tell you it's a work schedule.
OK, you know, you ever notice how in nature heat goes down and cold goes up?
You notice how you should have a cool head and warm feet?
You know, well, you know, these are real basic stuff, folks.
And by the way, I do call physicists and heating, cooling and HVAC people, you know,
ventilating, cooling, air conditioning people and ask them how many calls they got
yesterday regarding people asking for equipment that makes a verified rising cold and
a descending heat.
And they said, huh?
I said, thank you very much.
Planet full of idiots.
I'm just hang up. So if you are fine with that, you're doing great.
Now, this is your typical public discussion right now.
Not really. Sorry.
You're always being told how great you are and whatever, you know, how good you are.
And there's always somebody over there.
Some. Yeah, well, he worked for the Federal Reserve or he's part of a secret club or
or, you know, it's just really bad stuff.
Oh, yeah.
Cannibals, birthdays and dolls get a grip on that, folks.
And most of you have probably heard that before.
So this is humanity.
This is where you're at.
OK, so we've got pretty much a half hour of of so far of the sonic event.
And the people are still still speaking on time in this and various other things, very
specific things, by the way, in the AFR chat regarding things scriptural or biblical.
And by the way, I've always brought this up before because of what religion has done,
because it's one of the things that are just what you use the no pun intended.
God, awful. All of them.
Religion just means something you do regularly.
So, you know, you tie your shoelaces.
Well, that's pretty religious if you do it every day.
But what religions have done, if you bring up any unless it's in vogue, by the way, in
style or fashionable or anything, you bring up a holy red and right away people think,
oh, that has to do with religion and say, oh, I don't want to hear about that because
I'm not religious. Well, what they really want to say is those people that do those
things, you know, you know, I've heard of like Santa Claus, you know, anyway, all that
other stuff. It's kind of like, you know, you know, I don't want anything to do with
that. Right. So, yeah, so this is that's why I don't want to discuss too much in
public. There are primers and there's lots of information, just like there's information
regarding the human body.
The human body does not, period, work the way you've been told, period.
You want to empty out a room of academics and doctors with 30 years of
experience or any place like that?
You know, just go in there and ask them, how does the body absorb anything?
Watch what happens. They can't they can't handle that.
What you consider, by the way, the medical industrial complex, they've they're
ledger of domain. Basically what they're doing is they saw a woman in half, put her
back together and you say you saw a woman being sawed in half and put back together
and they lie, you swear to it.
And you love it because, well, you know, I woke up today and the day before yesterday
and these institutions are still there.
So I guess you love it because they wouldn't be there unless they were accommodating
you. But the human body, sorry, doesn't work the way you've been told.
And those that know it are not sharing.
You ever wonder why?
Yeah. What you're called, what you call science, physics, chemistry, none of that is
true. None of it.
It is true enough technique so people can technicians can technically access it when
they go to work.
But it's super unintuitive, isn't it?
You ever heard of an electron or a proton?
Sounds like some kind of Greek lascivious thing, doesn't it?
Yeah. So, yeah, you've been duped again.
Yes. The only thing that seems to pretty much work and is semi-functional is
mathematics. So we get into the baker's dozen kind of stuff.
But all your other stuff doesn't work, folks, and but it well, functionally,
functionally literate means you know how to read, but you don't know what anything
means. You're functional.
You're functional and you're being led a certain way.
And it's fine because you know what?
This was this has all been put in place before anyone was born.
So in essence, there's going to be a place in the future where things will be said
openly and but in private, you're if you want to partake, you're going to have to
join. Somehow, you're going to have to figure that out as it's there'll be
instructions, I guess.
Yeah. And any of those that for some reason can't join or whatever, for some
reason, and there's a dire need to have access to it, you could contact the Greek
at Uncommon Sense Radio one at Gmail dot com at Uncommon Radio dot com and maybe
something can be worked out.
But there is a time coming here roughly next by next spring.
There'll be a time we'll actually see it come around.
Hopefully, if it does, the chronology is in place.
If it doesn't, we'll watch a little closer.
So let's just say at this point, this is the fifth sonic time around and this is a
time before man.
And like I mentioned, what do cannibals, birthdays and dolls have in common?
Now, that's more of a commentary on mankind society.
What I want to just ensue here is that there's a time before.
Mankind, right, and that's time of the earth, that's time of the animals, if you
ever think about that, you're not supposed to, because you were told you came from
the animals or whatever, and you're not an animal, it's very simple.
You can rationalize that in many, many ways.
You you do share the function of many of the organs and certain things, eyes, hair,
things like that might appear commonalities and needing to drink water and breathe
there. But once there's a comprehension, by the way, of what you're made up of,
which is a soul, a spirit and a body.
By the way, you ever hear in adverts or stuff where they say the body, mind and
spirit, don't they?
Somebody got to call them up, tell them, you know, the mind and spirit are the
same thing. Here's an easy way to prove it, folks.
Whenever you see the word with a PSY prefix, that means spirit, like psychic,
psychiatry, psychotic, psychopath or psychology has to do with the mind that is
the spirit. And by the way, folks, whenever you see see a word with a PNU prefix like
pneumatic, pneumonia, it has to do with something going through the nostrils and
ending up in the cul-de-sac of the lungs.
That's that's the soul, man.
Yeah. And the thing is, you can discuss this till you're blue in the face.
And maybe that's why there was a race of blue people.
But anyway, and no one statistically wants to hear it.
Maybe one out of a thousand, one out of a hundred, maybe.
And all these people that suggest that they profess to be guiding others spiritually
can't define anything. And this is not just putting a knock on them.
You guys can figure that out yourself if you so choose to.
But let's go back to the animals, folks.
And that just let's just say.
Yes, I brought up the earth, the soul, the spirit and the body, you're animated, you
what makes you the personality that you have is the mind, the spirit, the Elohim, our
mind, the gods, our mind.
They have the ability to toggle back and forth into the material world where you don't.
And by the way, I just want to throw this in there, all these idiots that do this
meditation stuff and they trust transfer astral and all that.
They're being taken for a ride.
Yes, they are. And if you've heard any of the previous sonic, let's say, layouts, you
know specifically how people are being taken for a ride to believe that crap.
And it's pretty real to them, believe it or not.
But is it you know, what's reality again?
You see, under this censorship doesn't take much to figure it out, folks, or maybe just
a little impetus, a little keys here and there will unlock the door.
So back to the the earth and the spirit, the spirit that you're aware of, your mind is
animated in a physical body that whose elemental constituents represent the soil in
the earth. Yes, they do look it up.
And so do the animals, by the way, most of them, not all of them, some salamanders in
caves with no eyes of different constituents.
But but one thing that humanity is going to find out in the future is all this stuff
around you is like a movie set.
Well, not like a movie set, because movies are not what I'm trying to talk about.
It was all put here in place.
So you, mankind, surface-dwelling earth inhabitants would be more of a reductionist
form of communicating humanity for you.
Yes, for you as well.
You know, initially when you're introduced to it, it was for to steward it.
To be a master over it.
And what was the purpose of all this stuff?
Have you ever heard of one of these terrariums where you put all these things in
there, you know, living life forms and you seal it up and it's sort of like, does it
need much food or water?
It just kind of goes around and around in there.
You know what I mean? It's like sealed up and you don't have to feed it.
It just grows.
Yeah. Uh huh.
That's how nature was set up.
And you're here to steward it and master it, not to process it.
All this processing is done by the animals, the insects, the bacterium, the
weather, the salt, you know, everything that you see around you and you have the
ability to change it slightly through stewardship, but not to step in and do
what, anyway, you get the point.
So what are these animals?
Who are these animals?
You know, when you bring up these, uh, the concept of the, that, uh, that life
form, you know, if you want to reduce it even to the unseen, you know, where you
have the flora and the fauna, you know, the fungus, the flora and the fauna would
say the animals, the smallest little bacteria and things like that, little
critters that move.
And I'm not talking about viruses, by the way.
I just want to throw this in real quick.
How do you kill a virus when they tell you it's already dead?
Are you people paying attention or are they lying and you swearing to it?
Anyway, go back to the animals.
Here's an interesting concept.
I'm going to throw it out there.
And if anyone has any, is familiar with any of the ancient manuscripts, it says
when the spirit of man dies, it goes back to the heavenly realm.
But when the spirit of the animals dies or the animal dies, it goes back to the
earth.
Sorry, let me just go back.
When man dies, the spirit returns back to the hard drive.
Let's say that's up.
But when the animal dies, it's mind or its spirit returns back to the earth.
So how many times have you run into people discussing, oh, mother earth, this,
that, and the other.
Well, you're not your mother.
Maybe it is the mother to the animals.
You can pretty much surmise that from many different ways.
I wouldn't say it directly, but close enough.
When the spirit goes back there.
So that would be very interesting, you know, just getting that little bit of
information.
Let's say you're going to roll along with that bit of information.
That means that the spirit houses, the earth houses all of the spirits of the
animals.
Isn't that interesting?
And you also put the plow into it to make farming and agriculture so you can
support yourself.
If you were not, let's say, consuming animal.
So there's many aspects to that that can be considered.
They're basically, all of this stuff was made, you know, for mankind.
Now, here's an interesting part.
Throw this in here and bounce around a little because the celestials are
important also.
How many times have you heard that the moon is artificial?
This was going on a few years ago.
You know, the internet is full of this in vogue, fashionable crap.
The moon is artificial.
Okay.
Well, okay.
Well, you know, my retort on that was, you know, very simply, you know, they
say it's artificial because it doesn't orbit like anything else.
Well, the moon has a strange orbit because it doesn't have its own orbit.
It uses the same orbit that the earth has.
It's locked into it.
So if you know how vectors work, you can explain that.
But no one seems to.
Tesla had a good little short paper that he published regarding that.
But the moon is artificial.
I was like, hold on a second.
So is this like part of evolution?
They're like, no, no, no.
There's people that make stuff out there.
So I mean, like creators.
Okay.
So, so, uh, if everything, if there's a creator, then, uh, everything's
artificial because in order for something to be artificial, it has to
have an artifice or a creator.
Have you ever thought about that?
If everything is created, it's made by an artifice or the term
artificial has gotten a bad rap.
It just means something bad because when it entered people's vocabulary
back, maybe in sixties or seventies, it meant something nasty.
They were putting in food versus natural, but I assure you, everything
is natural and everything is artificial.
You know, if you look at the formulation of the most toxic chemical
synthesized, that is still garnered and synthesized from natural things
that are found in the environment.
Yeah.
Even transmutation is natural to a degree.
Well, to many degrees, if you understand how human bodies work and the
concept of artificial ties in with nature, because it's all part of creation.
So look at how much of what people think about and talk about.
It's just going to be wiped away by simple different definitions.
Think about it.
That's why, I mean, how can you have a public discussion on this?
By the way, a few years ago, I did some sonic events with Ocelli and the
Greek, and I think there's 18 episodes on there.
Most of the topics, most of the episodes were topical.
And, uh, I do suggest referring those as just like a good base public
discussion on first time things being discussed, I would say everything
on there is the first time it's being discussed publicly, but mostly everything.
Yes.
Uh-huh.
So, uh, I would just suggest here, um, that this being the fifth sonic
episode, number five comes before man.
When you think about it and what came before man is this entire
environment before man is on here.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Uh, as you know, it surface toiling earth inhabitant with the current lifespan.
Uh, I would like to get into more about man like I have in the past, but again,
I'm just going to throw this in again.
What do cannibals, birthdays, and dolls have in common?
And you'll understand the current state of affairs.
So back to the number five, the time before mankind, let's just take a look at it.
What was here?
Let's say if you scrub man from the planet, you still have an incredible, I
mean, veritable plethora of plants and animal life seen and unseen.
Yes.
You know, unseen as well.
You know, can you imagine animal life?
That's not in the visible spectrum.
Yeah.
You can only imagine it.
You might think of a contour or something or something or whatever.
Yeah.
Stories cryptology, but, uh, not to focus on that, but there are things seen and
unseen in that, that pretty much, if you just pluck man away, uh, you'd get an
idea of everything would pretty much be the same.
So when you look at all of these creatures and how many there are in variety,
um, just for a moment, take it out of your head that you didn't evolve from that.
Now the word evolve, it's always being used incorrectly.
It just means to unravel or open.
So even then it's not being, uh, and there's, there's nothing original about
evolution, all that crappy science.
It's just a joke.
It's a prank.
Uh, that started, you know, with the ancient Egyptians, uh, you know, everyone's
had something, it's low level stuff.
I call it, you know, like, you know, when you're going down the highway and they
got some crappy fast food and you're really hungry and you eat it anyway.
Uh, yeah, you're going down the highway of life and all you're given is crap.
You eat it anyway.
So that's your prerogative.
But here's the thing.
People serving crap wouldn't be serving crap if they didn't
have an audience to accommodate.
But anyway, all this stuff here before mankind, look at how different it is.
You ever, you ever really look at animals?
I mean, just really look at them.
Yeah.
We, what'd you notice?
Hmm.
Some fly, some are fast, some are in the water.
Some, again, you don't see, and some you do see, you know, it's
interesting about them, but just keep it real basic.
There's been some discussion about this back in the day, but you know how I
mentioned earlier, the connection, um, if you want to subscribe to a certain
ancient manuscript, the spirit of the animal returns to the earth.
You know, you ever, we ever noticed that most animals, their spine, you know,
which is, let's say a spinal column in German, it's called the spiral column
because the energy is, moves in a vortex.
You ever notice how their spinal column is horizontal or parallel
to the surface of the earth?
And for most people it's perpendicular to the surface of the earth.
Yeah.
Think about that.
Now birds tend to be a little different.
Um, they tend to stand around with a fairly vertical spine.
I mean, on a diagonal, about 36 degrees or so, which happens to
be the diagonal of a cube, by the way.
Let me just get in that for a moment.
Cause it sounds like I'm all over the place, but you know, um, it's like chess.
Each piece has different movements.
Every time you bring something up, it can move anywhere on the board.
You know, when you think of a square and you put a diagonal through a
square, it's at 45 degrees, isn't it?
All day and all night, you know, we do a diagonal on the square.
Yeah.
You Pythagoreans out there know that by heart, but most people haven't
really thought about it much.
In carpentry, you know, when you have a square and you make a diagonal, it's
always at 45 and split that again and get 22 and a half.
And they use that a lot for crown moldings and other things in construction.
Machinists kind of get into that lingo and they get down to breaking up
that 90 degree and 45 and all that.
But you can do that all day long.
You'll find out things that are square, have a diagonal of 45 degrees.
But if you make a cube, which is, let's say, um, a three-dimensional
relationship of that square, and you put a diagonal through that cube, if
that cube were made of glass and you look at, look at it from every angle,
it will appear to be crossing each angle of each side that you're viewing at 45,
doesn't it?
And you could swear to it.
I bet you would.
Now, if that cube, if you could open the top and, um, look at the diagonal
that goes through the cube, okay, from opposite corners, this is three
dimensional now, uh, you will measure that.
You'll see it's a 36 degrees.
Yep.
Yeah.
Gotcha there, huh?
So, uh, start looking at things, uh, in, in, you know, how they're projected.
And by the way, there's only one dimension.
The, the, the reason I mentioned, you know, the square, notice I didn't say
two dimension, but when I discussed the cube, I mentioned three dimensions
because that is a proper way to use it.
The, there's only one dimension folks.
Yeah.
You'll find that out later.
And the dimension is, is, uh, made up of things that you perceive and things
that you don't perceive, period.
All this multiple dimension stuff.
You want to know what a weak minded individual is, but anyway.
Okay.
So you're here, the word quantum people using that or multiple dimensions.
Yeah.
That's really weak and it's getting kind of tired and everybody knows it, but
because there's nothing else to do or say seemingly by a society that is
completely censored, yeah, might as well entertain it, but it's dumb.
And you'll find that out later.
I'm not saying if you gravitate towards that kind of rubbish, not saying don't
do it, go ahead, but you'll find out later.
So, uh, look at back to the spines of the animals, uh, how they are parallel
to the surface of the earth, or let's say, uh, and man is vertical
to the surface of the earth.
So he's kind of like the animals are parallel to the surface.
Man's perpendicular to the surface.
So the, uh, man is, uh, let's say, uh, perpendicular.
The animals are horizontal.
It's not interesting.
There are fields by the way, that move on the earth.
Yeah.
You want to experience one.
It's called a compass.
That is a magnetic field that doesn't have much to do with cardinal north
and south and east and west the planet.
And the sun will dictate cardinal direction, cardinal meaning, regardless
of what your compass or the compass and magnetic field does, and the
magnetic fields are being dubbed in the direction of north and south and east
and west, there are fields that move along the earth and these are considered,
um, by many fields, no pun intended.
And you'll see that the animals tend to be that way.
They're also on all fours and they make contact with all the ends of their
limbs on the earth, usually.
And mostly now the birds again are slightly different.
The birds came prior and the fish came prior to the land animals.
And most fish, by the way, tend to have that horizontal posture as well.
And so what they're doing is, uh, if you can imagine how the lines of force
move along the planet, right?
I would say parallel to the surface.
Uh, you'll see that the, um, the spine of the animals tends to
move parallel to those fields.
But the spine of mankind is perpendicular to that.
And most of his structure, central core structure, right?
Think about that.
You know, the lungs are perpendicular to that field.
Why?
Well, if anyone wants to get a little bit more into what they call physics,
there's some studies in various aspects of physics on perpendicular
lines of force and their effects.
Hmm.
Interesting.
Wouldn't that be interesting for someone who's young actually wouldn't don't do
it if you're in college, don't do it, get out, do something, get a hotdog cart
instead, but anyway, if someone wants to do some kind of a study or a thesis on
that, that would be very interesting, of course, but if you look at the
differences and these things are functional, um, you know, very often, you
know, when people see, uh, let's say you discuss, um, the sun, well, yeah, it's
beautiful, you know, at sunset or at dawn, you know, there's all this poetic
stuff, but they see no lawful use for it.
You know, they have pets, for example, as animals, or they eat them.
Some people eat them.
Actually, most people, so carnivores to a degree, but they're not really carnivores
or carrion eaters.
They don't eat it live.
They eat the carrion.
Uh, so at way after it's been killed, uh, but you look at the animals, uh, and you
say, well, you know, there are just animals.
I'm used to it.
Well, that's maybe part of the problem.
You get used to things and well, I wouldn't say there's a problem with the
animals, but most of the things that people seem to have a headache about and
they shouldn't is because it just takes a little bit of examination and a little
bit of discussion on how things are different.
And I would suggest that looking at these things with a fresh view, with a fresh
eye, and you don't need to crack a book open to look and for it to tell you how
to think in general.
I mean, there's some manuscripts out there that got some very high forms of law.
And you want to approach that and you think you could understand it, have at it.
But the thing is, what do you really see?
What do you really see?
What's going on around you?
Yeah.
So I just wanted to bring that up just to honor the animals a little bit.
They don't get that much, you know, other than the pets, you know, by the way, if
you, was it Gandhi who said something?
I'm not a fan of Gandhi or if you actually find out what he was into.
But either way, I would just say, if you want to learn more about a society, look at
how they treat their livestock or animals and you want to learn even more.
What do cannibals, birthdays and dolls have in common?
So we'll get into that perhaps next week and maybe a little bit before next week,
perhaps.
So I would suggest that look at these creatures.
Yeah, they're very base and also have shorter lifespans in general cases.
And they were here before man was as such.
You know, you can say they came here and I don't want to get into when they were,
when all this happened.
You'll figure that out on your own or you will find out for sure later.
You know, there's nothing here to convince, it's just to impart.
Now, if you understand how things are different, you might also see, understand
more of what makes them the same.
So I brought up how the animal kingdom appears and perhaps maybe in a different
way than you've heard it, maybe to consider.
I'm not going to give away much more.
We'll save that for later regarding animals, the way they behave, who they,
what they really are, their purpose.
I'll get into a little bit here publicly.
I would suggest that they are here to process.
Yeah.
You ever heard of, you know, a process means change things, you know, like I
brought up the concept of carnivore.
And carrion, you know, there's carrion eaters out there, like vultures, for
example, they rely on the scent of a decaying corpse to be attracted.
Not always, typically.
I mean, they can also be attracted to an injured animal and follow it around, but
they also have a keen sense for these, the smell of carrion or decay.
And by the way, a lot of the gas linemen, the people that maintain underground gas
lines and above ground gas lines and places where vultures could be found, they
look for vultures, let's say, circling over there.
They're in some places are taught to identify them.
And typically, if there is a gas line or a gas leak, they will also circle around
that gas leak because it tends to have the odor of such a thing.
If you ever smell like a gas stove or propane, kind of a little slightly funky.
Right.
So these birds have actually become quite useful to people in industry.
So typically, if you're working in that field, you drive up to it and you see if
there's no dead animal and you chose that there might be a gas line there.
It could be leaking because these birds are attracted to that.
So there's a useful consideration on understanding how animals work.
And I give you a simple one just to show you how mankind can work with animals.
And anyone has dogs or cats or birds or, you know, they're working animals.
And you can go to places in the world where they actually help assemble
skyscrapers in places, I think, like Sri Lanka and Malaysia.
They have elephants doing heavy work still today.
So I would suggest that, you know, looking at these things and the reason I'm
bringing it up is I would say it's around the fifth time I'm coming around.
It's a time before man and what was around.
And seemingly there's not much talk about the animals.
There's a lot of animal rights thing people.
Now, I want to bring this up again, because, again, this is this is planet
Earth. But when the concept of rights comes up, by the way, whenever you hear
that, right, other than like maybe right of way, maybe even that might be a good
way to explain it.
But let's just do another way.
It means that something wrong has happened and now you have to go under rights.
So you hear about all these morons, these patriots are going around.
They want their rights or this and that.
You know, what did you do wrong to demand rights?
Rights are something that someone goes under after they've committed what's
called a crime or accused of such.
So instead of being thrown into a dungeon, a windowless dungeon with no food, you
have rights like three hots and a cot.
You know, they'll make sure that you get fed and clothes and something.
That's a right. So when you hear about rights, that means you're presuming that
something is going on wrong, that you have lost the ability to be reckoned through
law. Now you go under rights and you are actually fighting for this.
So we'll continue more on the second half.
And this is Uncommon Radio with the Greek.
Greetings, everyone, and welcome back to Uncommon Radio with the Greek, also
Uncommon Sense and Greek speak to some degree.
And please call in if you do feel inclined.
You will find the phone number in a red box on the left.
If you can't see it on the left, it's on your other left, or you can try the
Skype convention and the Skype convention contact could be found if you go to
www.uncommonradio.com.
It helps to type in the whole thing and scroll down and you will see in red a
Gmail and that Gmail is Uncommon Sense Radio 1 at gmail.com.
It's a numeric one. And that is also the Skype contact and an email to contact the
Greek. So I would suggest that if anyone wants to join and part of this sonic
endeavor, please do so.
And before the second hour started at the end of the first hour was discussing
animal rights. And I just brought up the concept of rights and how it's misused.
And if one thing, if you've heard Greek speak, it's just really trying to counter
the misuse. There's most things are misused, but just like even a large
mathematical equation that you see in the movies, because you probably didn't look
at them anywhere else. There's a small equal sign and a small number to the right.
So it doesn't take much to counter all the bullshit out there.
Yes, I did say that word. That is a biblical term, by the way.
It's called dung. There's another way to say it.
But I would just say that when you hear about rights, that has been misused.
And let me just to recap here, when rights come into play, I'm going to say it
slowly, I'm going to repeat it.
Rights come into play when someone, let's just say someone, has been accused of or
has committed a crime. And the rights are there to sort of have more of a
mitigatable condition for the assailant or the accused so they don't die before
they get a trial. Because typically in certain societies or in times, if you're
accused of a crime, you're thrown into a dark, deep hole.
And when it came time to execute judgment or for you to make it right or go to a
trial, you were dead because the conditions were so bad.
That's what rights are for.
So if you are a ordinary surface dwelling earth inhabitant, rights have nothing to
do with you unless you have been accused or considered to be a quote unquote
wrongdoer or unlawful.
So how do you how do you counter the perception of this when it seems to be the
opposite? You have all these idiots everywhere asking for rights.
And why am I talking about this?
Because we're discussing the point of animal rights that I brought up.
I'm not going to get into rights anymore.
But when you hear people asking for them, they are either admitting that they have
done something wrong and now they cannot be free amongst a lawful condition that
they now have to come up with some form or be subject to some form of retribution
or they have to do some kind of recompense or something.
And they are under rights and people asking for rights just willy nilly like that.
That is the mark of a moron with a capital R.
And you know what? They're everywhere.
So let's just leave that alone for now.
I mean, as much can be said, I have discussed this in the past in great detail as
well. And I will discuss it more in great detail as well.
So let's just say about animal rights.
What have animals done wrong that they deserve rights?
Think about that for a moment.
So all you animal rights activists, stop being so active because really, you know what
real, you know where you really find activism these days?
Take a pause. Anyone want to answer that?
It's a rhetorical pause.
Find it in yeast.
Go get a package of yeast for you and bake some bread.
Very active. The rest of it is worthless.
Anyway, what does that have to do with what you're going to do on the cruise ship?
If you don't like what's going on, it's because of, yes, you guessed it.
I think we need more mirrors.
Anyway, I would suggest, oh, who's we?
Oh, boy. See, it's real easy to fall into this language trap when you get comfortable.
What did animals do to deserve rights?
Nobody want to think about that?
I didn't say anyone want to answer.
That's rhetorical. Even want to think about it.
How twisted communication is and even the concept of it.
Right. What did an animal do to you that it needs rights?
So that's an entire thing that could just be put aside, because right now, I'll tell you,
surface dwelling earth inhabitants are so far removed from what is right.
There's no way to bring them back, but they have still a little bit of a journey to go.
Now, you know, sometimes people will say, well, you know, is this wrong?
You know, this meaning any subject matter that I typically encounter in conversation.
I'll say, well, it's not wrong, but it sure ain't right.
And that gets them kind of wondering, you know, because why?
When you talk about any subject, by the way, it's what everyone has been told to think about it.
That is right. Right.
Does that make it right?
If everyone believes in a lie, does it make it the truth?
Well, if you ask your common surface dwelling earth inhabitant, yeah, it does.
But in reality, it doesn't.
And that is going to begin to be changing soon.
So if you're looking for activism, you'll find it in yeast.
If you're looking for animal rights, what did the animal do wrong that it needs rights?
And I'm not going to talk about people that are asked for rights.
They are just, you know what, with a capital R.
Yeah, there's plenty of them.
There's no shortage of that.
So there's no reason to go on that.
There's many hours of how people are more.
And so that's a technical term.
And if you haven't been out in public lately, and if you like, the best thing to tell young children is if you're not completely disgusted with people around you, you're not paying attention.
Yeah, think about it.
So if you're paying attention, you're completely disgusted.
Yes, absolutely.
So anyway, back to the animals.
I hope we've not beaten that up too much about the animal rights.
But here's something else to think about on the stewardship.
I've had a recent discussion, hopefully a fellow will call in, be threatened to call in, maybe he will, regarding what's called automobiles.
And why am I bringing that up?
Well, they're not automobiles, by the way.
They're engine driven wagons.
And they're not motor vehicles because motors are electric.
Yeah, we just talked about how twisted rights are and look, something like that is twisted.
Now think about modes of transportation where you had beasts of burden, or even horses or mules or donkeys and other things like that.
And by the way, mules are not technically lawful.
Anyway, we'll get into that some other time.
I would suggest that if you were using an animal as a mode of transportation, let's just use them as an animal could be your best friend.
You know, if you just decided to stay home for a week, guess what?
You still have to go out and feed and brush and water the creature, don't you?
But if you've got one of these machines, you know, it can just sit there.
Well, you know, for a certain allotted period of time, other things tend to go wrong with it if it sits too long.
So think about the modalities here that are being used.
You know, right now, there is a going away from using animals for beasts of burden or labor to machines.
What are these machines?
Well, you know what?
They are very, very, very simple form of very similar things that all living things do.
Because even though machines have an archetype, you know, basic, all machines share similar things, just like most living things share similar things.
There is a place where in the living things amongst the living, by the way, things change where you have anaerobic creatures that require breathing of air and the other ones that thrive with less air, which are anaerobic.
There is some discernment to be gotten there.
And I want to throw this in since we were discussing the animal kingdom.
How many times have you heard, is there life on Mars?
Or, you know, I sometimes frequent a space weather research place and because there's weather out there as well.
Yeah, sounds kind of funny.
But is there life on this planet?
And what's interesting is the way academia and those that follow it and or who academia is accommodating, tend to stress that the definition of life is finding some kind of like microorganism in a rock somewhere.
And if you find a microorganism, let's say on Uranus or Uranus, you will discuss that.
You would find that you could deem that there's life that can evolve there, right?
No, no.
Well, you know, here's the thing, folks, and this is this has been mildly hinted at.
The concept of life is not about whether there is a microorganism or a dinosaur or a human, that the actual life force, right?
Well, if you ask any academic or scientist, you know, how how does one walk across the room?
You know, well, you know, he'll tell you the muscles do this.
Oh, yeah. But what enables all that?
They can't. And if you start discussing what the life force is, like in Greek, it was the Zoe or the Chi in Asia or Ki in Japan, let's say, Prana in the Sanskrit.
Right. Various terms for it.
I would say that it makes them very uncomfortable because their job in the entitled classes right now is to avoid that, because remember, they only deal right now.
Humanity and the entire classes are only dealing with a very simple game of checkers.
They can't deal with multiple movements of multiple parts and multiple prioritization.
It has to be a very simple dummy load.
Yes. Dummy load.
I haven't brought that up much because if you're listening to past Greek speak stuff, you've heard a lot.
Look up what a dummy load is.
It's an engineering term and it sounds kind of cutesy and it kind of is to apply it when you say, well, that's a dummy load.
Yeah. Even if you don't really know what it means.
But if you discuss the life force, it makes people very uncomfortable.
Wilhelm Reich discussed the emotional armoring that when you do bring up these core issues, it makes people, them, the entitled classes, the ones that you look up to, by the way, because you are busy doing whatever you find that you need to do on this planet.
And if you have an interest outside of what you do and another subject, you have to trust that what you're being told is true and correct or enough or whatever.
But by the way, folks, when you do partake on the infotainment, I call it, you know, the Internet or the inane net, no matter how serious people are, you know, on the Internet, you know, those that produce and show you shows, when you kind of catch them in the background and how what they're doing is just a dummy load, they always say, yes, it's just entertainment anyway.
So if you're taking it seriously, you take your entertainment very seriously.
But I would suggest that, again, the life force is something that is everywhere, everywhere.
Do you know, I've discussed, perhaps maybe in the future, again, you can suffocate a rock.
Yes, just like you can suffocate a living thing.
You can suffocate a rock.
Yes. And how it can be done is quite simple.
And it's by observation.
And no, rocks are not born and they don't die like you do.
But they are subject to the life force.
Now, just to continue a little bit, this basic life force, which is accessible by everyone that is alive.
And even when you die, that life force continues around you just in a different quality.
Because when you look at something alive, an animal, let's say, or a plant, when it dies or ceases to exist, as it's known pleasantly, other critters move in.
Right. Anaerobic, aerobic bacteria, maggots, things like that.
So it keeps continuing in different forms, in different stages.
But I want to bring up something that I don't discuss publicly, for good reason, is something called the weather.
Now, the weather is also subject to this force.
It is not, I will say this emphatically, the weather is not thermodynamic as you are being dummy loaded.
It is not thermodynamic at all.
Now, most people on this planet will say it is, because, you know, warmer weather makes hurricanes and this, that and the other.
And tornadoes are a function of this thermodynamic.
And rain is formed by humidity forming around dust.
No, it's not. No, none of that is true at all.
It is a dummy load.
It is there to give you a cursory explanation.
I mean, sorry, did I say explanation?
Incorrect. Description.
They never explain anything.
They can't. Makes them very uncomfortable.
Who's they? Everyone out there.
That's why, for example, I'll just jump around a little.
Legal society, they don't care about the truth.
They're waiting for you to say something that they could use against you.
We'll tell you that. When you bring that up, they get very uncomfortable.
Doesn't matter if it's the highest judge or the lowest attorney or the lowest paralegal.
They know it. Anyway, this has nothing to do with the truth.
This planet here on Earth, it's the society built on it is not about the truth right now.
It is a show.
Look up what the word show means.
So I would suggest that the Earth is true.
The Earth does exist.
And several of the things we've discussed, if you subscribe to certain ancient manuscripts,
these things will come up.
And I just give a little bit more explanation on what you can see with your own eye.
Because one of the things that are discussed is what do you see with your own eye?
Right. So just to recap on the first hour,
predominantly just mentioned how the animal kingdom, including,
let's say the plants came even before that, how their spines are typically parallel
to the surface of the Earth and parallel to the field lines on the Earth,
where mankind's spine is perpendicular to the fields that move across the Earth
and the Earth itself, and also the mind of the animal when it leaves,
the animal goes back to the Earth and the mind of mankind or the spirit goes
somewhere else. So, yeah, these things are interesting.
And to be brought up to discuss, perhaps numerologically,
not because I'm into numerology or geometry or anything like that.
It's because proper things in proper time.
And this seems to be the fifth time around.
By the way, it still is the spring season on the northern hemisphere.
Maybe that's the hemisphere that matters.
I don't know.
I should say I don't know, because if you were somewhere else,
you would take it quite seriously and that would matter.
But if you look at where the center of the Earth is,
it is on the northern more tendency aspect of the Earth.
And it is in spring time right now.
The friends that are down under and such,
they're going through a fall, almost winter time.
So I will just perhaps make references to the where most of the events are
happening are considered going into spring.
So you have to understand, again,
many times this has been discussed.
Let's just say the way you gather information,
it's really easy to pay attention to where it's noisy.
It's almost if you want to do something,
a lot of noise and hubbub is made, you're distracted to pay attention there.
And I assure you, that is not where the real deal is,
where it's really going on.
It's always the true power is where it's silence,
where it's silent or where the silence is.
Now, what's interesting about springtime
is that there is a lot of silence once things are prepared and not much visible
growth, but everything is in place.
What is being put in place right now geopolitically and such and everything,
even in your life and a microcosm of the life you're living.
And this will grow in the summer and then be harvested and broken down in the fall.
And this is how the cycles work, by the way.
Man, it's not really a dig.
It's really easy to dig.
It's not fair to shoot fish in the barrel.
What happened to all these idiots talking
about a big financial collapse in the middle of March?
Did it happen?
See, it's in bad taste to say that because
they kind of know they're stupid about all these matters, but they'll never admit it.
But everyone wants to listen to it anyway.
So doesn't that make everyone also very...
I'm not going to say it.
Yeah.
So it's springtime, so pay attention.
And regarding the
the aspect of the animal kingdom, which came before mankind,
I think I'm going to yield at that moment, and I think I gave something to chew on.
And let's see.
Let's see what's in chat.
Let's see, there's a bunch of just basic, basic chit-chatter in chat,
and no one has called in yet and no one on Skype.
And we could just pursue, perhaps, what we would like to discuss next week.
Who's we?
And the reason why is there's a preface that can always be made to things.
And here's an email from someone.
What is in real time?
What can be known about the life force?
What can be known about plant life and microbiology?
Okay.
Thanks for plugging that in.
That was just five minutes ago.
Because these are formative things.
Now, the thing is, the last thing you want to do in society,
if you really want to lose people, start talking about what causes things.
Formative.
And these subjects make people very, very uncomfortable.
And it's not something distant.
You all experience it.
It's just that you're so used to it and you take it for granted that you'd rather
not pay attention to it.
Because if you do find and take a liking to considering these things,
you might get so excited you might want to talk about it.
And the people that are called so-called family and friends and those that you
thought were cordial and friendly to you will not be so much.
So if you want to go ahead and ruin your life, go pursue the truth.
But anyway, I don't believe I just said that.
But yeah, let's just say that is particularly true.
I've once said this before, and I'll say it again just for whatever reason,
that everyone you've ever met, everyone you know,
and everyone you're going to meet is a moron, statistically.
Meaning the majority of the people are.
Meaning they're still stuck.
And this is how things work on this planet.
And not necessarily the planet's way, but the way mankind has set up society.
And I'm going to say this again.
What do cannibals, birthdays and dolls have in common?
And so back to the life force, what can be said about that?
Well, it's the life force.
It's pretty much everything, isn't it?
Right.
And the plant life and microbiology.
Well, the micro is very important.
I mentioned the weather, for example.
Let me give you a quick story regarding that.
And maybe you'll consider, let's say, the microbiology and weather.
The deserts of the planet should not be redeemed.
Why?
We serve a function.
Well, there's some commentary about them, both negative and very little positive.
Why shouldn't they be redeemed?
Well, very simple.
Now, this has been done.
A certain desert in the southern part of the continent of Africa was redeemed a
while back, and when this was done, it seemed too good to be true.
This is not using the geoengineering methods that most people cry and scream
about or dummy loaded about when you understand how to access the life force
time and space, time and distance are irrelevant.
Okay.
So I would suggest that when this desert was mitigated and redeemed, where it had
lakes on it now for a short time, when the people that were responsible for
doing this said, this is too good to be true.
We really need to watch things very carefully because what's the payback for
this? And seemingly what happened is through the news, after about six months
to a year or two, there was a critical demise of the fishing industry near South
America.
There were no fish to be caught and the fish had gone away.
By the way, you do hear a little bit about this now with the Fukushima
disaster and all that.
By the way, people crying about the Fukushima thing, their capital, what the
capital are also.
We can get into what atomics are in the future on another project.
But when this desert was redeemed and the fishing industry went away, it was
consideration that the food chain was disturbed.
How?
These big deserts throw up these huge dust storms and some of them are so
dynamic that very fine microscopic particles of silica go even up into the
stratosphere and descend into the oceans.
What do plankton eat or certain varieties of plankton or small microorganisms in
the ocean?
Yes, you guessed it.
And if they starve out because there's no dust storm, well, guess what?
What eats the plankton gets starved out and the entire food chain or the concept
of the big fish eating the smaller fish on and on and on goes away and you end up
losing a particular aspect of nature.
So consider these things as how everything is tied together.
This was also done, for example, there's some forest research where certain
plants or trees were eliminated and then some animal species corresponded with it
also, but I think the one regarding the weather manipulation and mitigating the
desert led to the loss of the fishing industry perhaps is another connection
with microbiology.
Now plants, plants are very interesting because when you look at plant life,
how it emerges, plants rarely reach around and grab themselves or touch
themselves, they tend to have certain geometric patterns.
There's a book out there on the planetary effect on plants if anyone wants to
get into that.
I have not read it, I've done a cursory review of it, it should be interesting,
an interesting perspective.
I don't have the author, just do a search somewhere, planetary effects on
plants, it's an obscure book, but it's something to look at.
But they have a certain manifestation also and that's something that I would
like to get into, agriculture and all that, perhaps in future projects, because
all of that also ties in with what's called water.
So what can be said about the life force?
Much, but all you have to say, there is a life force and that is enough to get
the passerby mentality with most people.
Yeah, of course there is, but they do not want to discuss it.
Now unfortunately people are still seeking out to pursue what they want to
pursue and are looking for specialists and professionals and all that to tell
them what, and I assure you, you're not getting quality information.
Not everything they're telling you is a lie, but it's so piss poor that it
might as well be.
This is the state that you're living in, folks.
So, uh-huh, that's why your best activism is found in yeast.
So, but here, let's just maybe consider this.
The definition of a professional is someone who's always learning more and
more about less and less, isn't it?
You ever notice how specialized they are?
You ever talk to someone who has a Ph.D.?
What did you get a Ph.D. in?
Oh, I studied the bum of the Moroccan housefly.
Yeah, that's where I got a degree.
You ever notice that when they get these doctorates, it's such a narrow,
specific, and useless topic that it almost doesn't make any sense, but yet
they get all the entitled praise of their social rank of Ph.D.?
Are you folks paying attention out there?
You know why these people get these doctorate and graduate degrees?
To accommodate you.
Yes, you.
Because if these people went away and that entitlement program and the social
ranking system of master or Ph.D. went away, you morons would be looking at each
other saying, we have so few people with master's degrees and Ph.D.s.
We need to do something about it.
They're accommodating you with stupidity.
Now, if you don't believe that these graduate people and doctorate people are
accommodating with stupidity, then that means you haven't spent five minutes
discussing anything with them.
Anything.
And if you have and you haven't realized that it is in that category, guess what?
You're not paying any attention.
And this is a broad blanket statement that holds true almost all of the time.
What is going on?
You know, you want to really just confound them, ask them what day it is.
Anyway, that should be a private joke.
But anyway, going back to the life force, it's there.
Yeah, there it is.
It's everywhere.
It can be accessed.
By the way, with some minor cursory research, anyone can access the work of
Wilhelm Reich and Trevor James Constable and others that worked with what they
call ether.
There's a little bit of fight about what the ether is or whatever.
You got a lot of weak minded individuals trying to look at the label without
defining anything.
And that's the problem with discussing anything objectively in any field or any
group.
So avoid the group and the purely dedicated, methodic, kind of like fanatic
following of anyone.
You know, there's some people out there that have done really good work in the
past.
Their mistake was they wanted to make the world a better place.
That's why they were tossed to the side.
And they said it perfectly.
I mean, they said it publicly.
They should have just not said that and done it would have been more successful.
Because by the way, I've said this before.
If anyone's heard Greek speak, if you have something really good, you know,
that could help anyone, even the animals, of course, and the plants, just do it
and tell others how to do it.
But the minute you go public and start saying with your mouth or in print that
you're doing this to make the world a better place, you're finished.
And the reason why you're finished is because the malevolent forces in the
world don't want to see that.
Yes, and also the benevolence don't either.
Why?
Because the time for reckoning is coming around.
Not next week, not next month, not next year, not even in five years, not even in
ten years.
But it's coming around and you will not recognize it.
I assure you that.
Because you're going down a path where things will be seemingly getting better.
And you will not be able to recognize what's going on unless you know.
So, actually we have someone trying to join on Skype.
What I will do is see if I can add him to the group call and perhaps maybe continue
the conversation.
I'm not sure if you can hear me.
I think we have been joined by someone that goes by Wes.
I guess, but sorry if I say that.
Greetings.
Hey, Greek.
Hey, it's for horses, better for cows.
How are you, man?
I'm good.
I had a total change of subject.
I don't mean to take it too far away from what you were talking about.
But automobiles, basically, I know there are a lot of tricks that can be done that
don't even require new hardware or stuff to do in your car.
And I'm not specifically asking how to do it, but really, if these things are kind
of pretty simple, is it just that car makers don't know about them or is it
something more or less that we are not supposed to know about?
Well, here's the thing.
Do you want the answer that people are used to hearing or do you want the answer
from actually dealing with those idiots?
Can you do both?
Yeah.
Basically, if you talk to anyone that's outside on the market end of it, they're
like, oh, this is the best that we're getting.
That's why if you really want to prank the pranksters, you go to a car dealer.
And you ask them, is this the new car?
They're like, oh, yeah.
Is it different than last year's?
Oh, yeah.
And I'm like, why?
That means you guys just haven't figured out how to make them yet.
You see, because it's based on vanity.
Cars are based on contour, what they look like.
It's the same junk inside.
The best they can do with efficiency is about 20% right now.
25 tops.
So diesels get better.
So what's going on is when you have good intentions to work in the field.
Now, let's switch over to well, actually, should we switch over?
Do you want to talk about the modifications that have been flooded and
what people have been talking about making a car better on the typical
Internet dummy load like HHO and little tornado thing that you can add?
That sounds good.
Yeah, yeah.
OK, just to continue a bit more about how
the ridiculousness of cars, what's going on is that whenever there's
a desire, there's always an opportunity and when there's an opportunity,
there's something called an opportunist and an opportunist.
Usually they're unlawful.
How do I know they're unlawful?
Because they're typical humans are unlawful.
They'll take advantage and put out really
shoddy products and things that don't work.
And you have these phases.
What's in vogue?
So there's been many modifications and
actually criticism on these modifications.
They're both good and bad.
And actually, they never really pan out.
They tend to go away and they're thrown
by the wayside and everyone relies on what the manufacturers are doing,
which is crap also.
So that's a little bit more commentary on that.
Now, we'll finally get to what we've
discussed, perhaps in some in private to some degree.
But let's just say this.
And this ties into the discussion of the animals, because I did mention, by the way,
that, you know, if you had a horse for
transportation, even though you didn't go anywhere for a week, you still have to feed
him, brush him, groom him and all that, water him.
Well, you can have what they call a car and it just sits there.
It's a lot cheaper, ultimately, isn't it?
So it is a much better modality if you look at it strictly from that point of view.
But now, if you want to look, let's go to the other side of what the car manufacturers do.
The car manufacturers is really no such thing.
It's an organization of people from designers to manufacturers to industrial
engineers. You get the idea.
It's an army, battalions of people getting together, each doing different things.
Now, what ultimately the contour or what the car looks like or how it performs
comes from the designer and engineer, typically originates there.
And if you discuss anything with these guys, especially how they got into it,
they all have the good intentions.
And once they get into the field, of course, they're accepted based on whatever
merit they can, whatever they can produce, right?
They're placed in the field, you know, with the corporations to produce these
things and design them actually before they're produced.
And what they do is they start putting blinders and they start steering you into it.
You, first of all, if you've gone into the field, you've gotten a dummy load
education from the university, and then you're going to be subject to certain
laboratories where you see how things physically work.
And then now you have to make them different, not better.
Just because something new doesn't mean it's better.
It just means it's different.
Now, what happens if the issue of efficiency comes up in the field?
They always throw into your face, if you're working in the field,
the EPA recommendations, you know, the environmental protection.
Okay, so this is what we're looking for.
And also how it will process the fuel that it's designed.
Remember, remember, you're designing this engine for a particular type of fuel
and how it addresses that fuel.
And that's it, even though there's many other things.
And here's a ridiculous statement that can be made, and you could play around
with engineers all day long, but they're not worth it.
Do you know that no one has ever burned gasoline in a car, ever?
You're like, that sounds ridiculous.
I mean, in other words, you don't put the gasoline in the car to burn it.
It sounds ridiculous, because Greek, if I run out of gas, it doesn't go anywhere, right?
Well, the reason you're putting the gasoline in is to burn the air,
because you can substitute the gasoline with alcohol and hydrogen and all these
other things, right?
So the purpose of doing that is burning the air, and they're telling you,
you have to preserve all these mixtures.
And so they're putting blind spots on these people that are working there.
And eventually, if you have a sprained leg or a broken leg and you walk with a crutch,
that's fine, but once it heals and you continue walking with a crutch for five
or ten years, it starts to atrophy, and you'll never probably be able to walk
on it after a certain point when the bone mass starts to disappear, you see?
So these engineers have no bone mass left anymore.
They've got nothing, and they just sit there, and they do what they're told.
Why?
Because they're accommodating, again, the mindset that gas makes cars go,
meaning gasoline.
In many countries, if you go to South America, it'll be alcohol, for example,
in Brazil and places like that, right?
So I would suggest that you will notice this modality of dumbing up and limiting
the people that work in the field in any field, Wes, not just in the automotive.
Now, there are many stories that I will share in the future about how many
anomalous things are being discovered or have been discovered through the past
working with what they call reciprocating motors or combustion engines that had
never really made it to the field, and you've heard about the 200-mile-per-gallon
carburetors and all that.
That was very simple to do back then when the formula of the fuel was a certain way.
What they did was they changed the formula so it became thicker,
and they couldn't use it.
But essentially, from, let's say you called in because you have an interest
of certain things, and we've spoken in private, and I'll share this with everyone,
is that what you are now discovering is we had a discussion about increasing
the available vacuum to the combustion part of the engine for increasing
efficiency or really changing it.
Just changing the amount of vacuum that is available to the engine radically
changes the engine, correct?
Have you discovered that firsthand?
Yes, and I'd like to actually, well, share with you, you can continue,
but I figured something out that was causing the issue, and it surprised me.
You had some negative issues along the way, but yeah, this might be something, yes.
Yeah, it was the, I have a gauge, right, that I plugged into the OBD,
and I've kept it plugged in, and this last time, like after so many times,
I would start in the car, and it would like, a check light would come on,
okay, one more time, after doing some changes or whatever.
Started up, it was going great, and it just so happened when I started it up again,
the gauge was just off.
I'm like, oh, that's funny, so I unplugged it and plugged it back into the car.
As soon as I did that, check engine light came on, and then the car started doing
weird things, and then just like, and then I realized this whole time,
it's been this gauge.
I didn't know it had any effect on the car at all.
I just thought it took readings.
Okay, and it was the gauge.
So in other words, there was a two-way street going on.
Right, maybe somehow the gauge was synced to a time when it wasn't working,
and I don't know, I haven't looked much more into that,
but it was definitely the gauge.
You say definitely because you've worked, okay, so in other words,
you say definitely because it's, in other words, if you plug it in,
it comes back, and if you unplug it, it goes away, so it's definite.
Okay, good.
Yeah, pretty much.
Okay, interesting.
So now you're on your path again, and you perhaps might report back,
and I would like to report more on how to modify,
and perhaps since you've called in, maybe you will make more public experiences,
appearances regarding these experiences, and we could continue down the path
of perhaps vocalizing publicly how to make these things work better
for those that tend to be adventurous and know how to operate a screwdriver and a wrench.
Absolutely.
Yeah, but so far the concept of what we're discussing
and the primary source being vacuum or the motive force, let's say,
you're finding that to be true, and it's contrary and counterintuitive
to what has been taught or what you've experienced to be on what's called
the World Wide Web and other mechanics.
Yes, along that same note,
if you were to be pulled over or something, and they saw this,
would it be an illegal modification or would it just be weird to them?
Not at all.
It's not even considered.
It's so minor.
Well, illegal just means that that's the legal society.
There is no right and wrong with them.
They're just waiting for you to see what you do so they can monetize it and blame you.
I think I've discussed what they represent.
They represent spiritual forces on the Earth.
And they won't be around in the future, fortunately.
It's not that mankind's going to change that.
The gods are going to do it.
Because you can't change it because 90% of the population of the Earth
pursues what they do, if not more.
And that's why 90% of them won't be here, one of the reasons.
So that is an interesting concept.
No, I wouldn't be concerned about that.
And if there is anything that has any legal constraint like that,
I always let people...
Actually, I wouldn't communicate it because that creates a liability, doesn't it?
Of course, yes.
So, yeah.
Actually, the most illegal thing you could do is have a car run without any fuel at all.
Oops, did I just say that?
Okay.
Yeah.
I just worry if I take it into the shop to get an oil change and they see it,
they're going to think, oh, I better fix this, you know,
without telling me, thinking they're doing me a favor or something.
That's fine.
It's so simple.
Well, it's really just one little tiny minuscule hose disconnected and capped off.
That's all it is.
It's just basically removing...
The original aspect of that was that was originally designed to work that way
when engines were developed on the benchtop, right?
And when they decided to keep that feature when they manufactured and put it in the field.
And when you are starting to send the vacuum into the other side of the engine,
you get blow-by and you're getting strong vacuum where you don't...
The engine doesn't want it.
The engine just wants to relieve extra pressure.
It doesn't want to be sucked on like that.
So, what we'll discuss perhaps in the future endeavor, sonically,
in great detail on that, and in the meantime,
you and I will privately be communicating on how to further this along
and have you as a testimonial testbed where you can vocalize.
It sounds like you can communicate what's going on
and we'll go through several things as you find them to be applicable.
Yeah, if that's okay.
And I would like for you to report back as you have been on the progress on it.
Because many people may not consider automobiles to be the first thing
that they want to, let's say, play around with to make better.
But you know what?
I said many people don't, but there are many people that do.
There are many people that are concerned about how automobiles work
and how to make them better.
Because intuitively, you figured out that you're being scammed, aren't you?
I mean, if you look at how cars were made
or what they call automobiles or motorized wagons,
you know how like right now, for example,
there is a boom with Tesla Motors, not to plug them,
but the electric movement and all that with the cars.
If you do some research, back in the 1920s and 30s,
one third of the cars on the road were already electric.
And if you actually look at the, let's say, the overall range of them now,
I think there are 250 on average, maybe 150 to 200 conservatively.
I mean, realistically, with a load.
And some of them can go up to 300, 400 miles on a charge,
I should say, for an electric car.
Okay.
Back in the 1930s, you could look this up.
There was a competition on developing a car
to have a 1,000-mile range on one charge,
and they accomplished that.
We're talking almost 90 years ago now, 80-something years ago.
So, didn't I just say earlier that newer is not better, it's just different?
So, these are things to consider.
And electricity doesn't even work the way that we're being told.
That is a whole other concept.
So, yeah, I do appreciate you.
Anything else?
I mean, whoever, yeah.
Sure.
Like, Schauberger, a lot of the stuff that,
I know you say that a lot of the stuff we find out now
might not be true or whatever,
but I know he did have a lot of stuff with vacuum,
and he watched fish and stuff like that.
And does that somehow coincide with kind of how a car engine works?
I mean, we're talking about vacuum here,
and just like a closed or open system, whatever.
Does it correlate, kind of translate to what he was getting into
and discovering about energy?
Yes, but here's the thing.
Have you heard any of the other sonic events
where it discussed how the human body works
and how you're under a slight vacuum already?
A biological vacuum?
Yes.
And nothing goes in and out?
And anything that appears to be coming out
is actually produced on the membrane surface of that,
just like plant roots.
If you pull out a plant, it's a healthy plant,
and you wash the roots and spray the roots with a mister,
a water mister, does it soak in like a sponge
or does the water bead up on the roots like a freshly waxed car?
The latter.
It's hydrophobic.
So everything is sealed up.
So the concept of the Victor Schauberger is misunderstood,
because if you notice,
you can go on hundreds if not thousands of sites
or mentions online and they're all parroting each other.
I think these people need crackers.
You get it?
Parrots, you know?
So they missed the point.
And even here's the interesting thing,
if you've studied Schauberger a little bit,
he also said everyone around him is missing the point.
Have you ever recalled reading that?
Yes.
Okay.
He was very frustrated,
and Wilhelm Reich and other people,
and Tesla and others,
everyone is missing the point.
Everyone meaning everyone that he's come in contact with at large.
Yes.
And there are a few people known as protgs
and others that have come around,
but the mass success of this is not going to happen
in this society, by the way.
But it doesn't mean that there are few that can master it
or learn about it,
because first it's the inspiration to go in that direction,
because you can go to many people discussing implosion,
vacuum, Victor Schauberger, Tesla,
and they don't want to hear it, right?
So there's no inspiration there.
Those that are inspired, then they will get the ideas,
and then they need the knowledge
so they don't have to reinvent the wheel.
Then they need to be directed so it's done properly
so they don't have all failure, right?
Because all failure is very intimidating, discouraging.
And then you build it up, and you go and you go and you go.
And these people are very hard to find.
They're not around.
As a matter of fact, I used to say,
I'd like to interview, perhaps,
there's a possibility since I'm doing these public sonic things,
to interview someone,
but everyone that I think worth interviewing is dead.
What does that tell you?
What do you do now?
They've all died, and some of them even more recently.
So there is a time that's coming
where these things will be known, and they will reemerge.
But again, like I've mentioned,
I'm going to be involved in a sonic endeavor
that's going to be either launched here
or somewhere else or somehow
where all this information can be put together.
And let me just, before we continue,
you brought up Schauberger.
You ever notice, let me just throw this little bit out,
a little gem or a pearl for whoever's really listening.
And perhaps you as well, Wes.
If you look at Schauberger's devices,
one thing you'll find that they all had in common is what?
And I'll answer it for you.
They all ran at what?
Very high speeds, didn't they?
Yes.
Very high.
I mean, in the tens of thousands was normal.
You know, 10,000, 20,000, some 30,000 RPM.
Right?
When you consider how things, how fast things spin,
you know, your average electric motor is 1,500 to 3,000,
and that seems like really wicked fast, doesn't it?
Right?
That's really slow compared to what Schauberger was looking for.
Why is it important that these high speeds were attained
or maintained in order to see these effects?
Okay, I'll answer for you.
And this is the tidbit.
It's because it's a concept called resonance.
Right?
When two things resonate with each other,
then they communicate energetically, don't they?
Okay?
Yeah.
All right, now, if you look at, for example,
how fast...
See, you're standing stationary,
but, you know, the Earth is moving very, very, very fast.
I think it's 66,666 miles per hour around the sun
or something like that.
It's funny how I brought that up, right?
Okay, so...
It might be a little off, but that's roughly it.
Or roughly, you know, the Earth is spinning
at roughly 1,000 miles per hour, isn't it?
Yeah.
Now, isn't that about 1,000 feet per second?
Yep.
Roughly?
Roughly.
Yeah, okay.
Now, when you have one of those turbines
that Schauberger was building,
and it was going, let's say, at 20,000 RPM,
if you cut it loose and let it roll down the sidewalk,
don't you think it would be covering
about 1,000 feet per second?
Yes.
It's funny you say cut it loose, you use that term.
Uh-huh.
Because isn't it something about how it's not really
moving in the way that we think it is?
It's actually kind of being taken there?
What's happening...
Let's just throw this...
You're ready to turn...
Let's just turn some minds inside out like a sock.
Okay.
You appear to be stationary,
but to someone who's normally moving 1,000 miles an hour,
you appear to be moving very fast, don't you?
Yes.
Because you just whisk...
Even though you ever go in a really fast car,
look across...
Everything's moving really fast, isn't it?
So, I once spoke to someone who was a pilot,
and he was going supersonic near the ground,
and he says...
He said that light poles were...
Looked like picket fences.
That's how fast he was passing them.
So...
Yeah, I think that's such a funny song, by the way, too.
Yeah, okay.
All right, there you go.
So, what happens here is when Schauberger attained
his ultra-high speed, or relative ultra-high speed,
it appeared to be stationary to the Earth,
even though it was very fast to you,
meaning that if you put your finger there,
you wouldn't have a finger, right?
But when it reached that speed,
it appeared to be at parity with the Earth's speed,
and now what it did was it coupled into the energy
that the Earth is coupled into.
Just like, you know, everything...
The Earth is moving 1,000 miles per hour, let's say,
and that's moving 60 times faster than that around the Sun,
and the Sun is moving about 3,000 times faster than that
through here.
Do you know that if you stopped something,
if you had the ability to ground,
let's say, an ordinary object in the room
that you're in right now,
ground it and stop it from all those other motions
that it would be so energetic
that it would probably create a nuclear explosion?
You see?
So, I don't know if you're still here.
No, no, I am, I am.
Yeah.
You see, if you, let's say, stop the pencil
from the movement of the Earth relative to the movement of the Sun
and relative to the movement of the Sun
through what's called space,
that pencil would be going, you know,
tens and even 100,000 miles per hour.
Right.
If you could just harness that pencil for half a second,
that would be enough to, you know,
pretty much run a city for a week.
So, it almost makes you question
if we're being told that everything's happening
in the way we're told.
Yes.
You're censored, basically.
Humanity is being censored from this.
And when you do find out about it, it'll be,
oh, no big deal,
because when humanity does find out how to manipulate
and actually, when they say manipulate,
meaning handle using the hand,
these things, you will be in a different state
where these things now will be secondary
where now they seem primary, right?
Because the primary, because, you know,
you've got to pay for energy, you know,
all these things, you know, wearing you down,
they seem oppressive sometimes.
But when humans or people go to the next level,
this concept of free energy
or tapping into the universal energy is,
you will have that,
but it won't be as big of a deal as if you had it now.
It'll be in its own time.
It's kind of like if you're four years old,
you want a fire truck,
and you get a real fire truck, a real one.
You know, somehow it's modified so you can operate it.
Is that a good thing?
No.
Well, to who?
It's good for you,
but is it good to everyone around you?
Probably not.
Not really.
So let's be objective,
and I always discuss this,
but there are many things,
you know, I also bring up the metaphor,
you know, someone went to an ashram,
wants to meditate,
and this guru supposedly was very good
to helping people see the light.
And he told you if you sat here
and you meditated on these particular concepts,
if you saw the light, you got to that level.
So one day, you know, a student did that,
and he joined this ashram,
and he did that for three or four months,
and he meditates diligently,
and he's in this meditative state,
and he sees this bright light,
and he jumps up and he tells the guru,
he says, yes, I see the light, I see the light,
I finally see what you're saying.
And you know what the guru told him?
He said, oh, don't worry, you'll get over it.
Right?
So this is what's going on.
It's like, here's the thing,
those that know how to do this tapping,
they just don't do it.
They don't do it,
because in order to get to that level
of know how to do it, you have to be objective enough
to know what's going on around you.
And when you know what's going on around you,
you don't do these things,
because it's better off to kind of sit back
and chill like everybody else,
because it's going to draw too much attention,
unless you think it's time to check out.
Yeah, so is that, is that,
I don't know, it's the wrong word,
it would probably be ego,
but is it something like ego?
No, it's not ego.
Ego is, that's Freud,
all that stuff that people use is Freudian.
When a lot of people use ego,
I would say it as being like a self-centered, arrogant,
you know, too much into what your needs are.
Well, I guess I'm just,
I just mean the kind of like the ability
to not be taken away by emotions,
or, you know what I mean,
a grandeur, or just something crazy like that,
like seeing the light, you know what I mean?
Is it, what's, what is that
that keeps that in control, you know?
Oh, the cosmic censorship.
I see.
There's many, there's many levels of censorship.
Do you know that one,
a decision you made yesterday
affects your life today, for example, doesn't it?
Yes.
But, but the general consensus is,
I give the metaphor of surface-dwelling earth inhabitants,
your average human,
is that you're all on this cruise ship
leaving, let's say England, going to New York.
That's, that's the, that's the plan for humanity.
Now, that cannot be changed.
Now, but while you're on this cruise ship,
all seven billion of you tourists,
you have an ability to go anywhere you want on the ship.
You know, you have your cabin,
you have to go to the deck,
ski, you know, you go to the theater,
go to, okay, but you're,
but everyone is going to New York.
And the state of affairs of humanity
and all this right now,
everyone is going to this point
because the decisions that were made
a long, long time ago.
Part of the cosmic censorship
is the adherence to modernism
and how wonderful that is.
And if you do some research on ancient civilizations
that are now considered to be a fallen,
if you look at their literature,
what's preserved of it,
they've always, before they fell from prominence,
they always described themselves as being what?
Modern.
Doesn't this society describe itself as being modern?
And no one is paying any attention.
If you look at the world's fairs
that were held in the 30s, 40s, and 50s of the last century,
didn't they promise you flying cars by the 1990s
and a hotel on the moon by the year 2000 or so?
Where is that?
You're not going to get any of that.
I assure you.
So I would suggest that,
how many times have you heard in Greek speak,
food, clothing, shelter, food, clothing, shelter,
up the quality of those.
And it sounds really base.
Oh, that sounds really basic.
I can do more than that.
But you know what?
If you pursue increasing the quality
of food, clothing, and shelter,
while you're seeking to increase those qualities,
you're going to learn a lot about many, many, many,
many other things on the way.
It's kind of like the Karate Kid movie.
You know, wax on, wax off.
Why am I doing all this?
You'll see.
It all goes together.
So, for example, that's why I've said many times,
this is a harsh criticism, but I assure you it's true.
Look at people that discuss politics wholeheartedly.
And if you get to know them personally,
they are of poor character.
You don't want them marrying the sister.
You wouldn't bring in all this other stuff.
So pay attention, folks.
And thank you for calling in, Wes.
And this is Solo 5 or Solo 6 is coming.
We'll be talking about what do cannibals, birthdays, and dolls.
Thank you, everyone, for contributing.
See you again.
Greek signing out.
Ciao.